[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises
that threatened our world.
They harnessed the power
of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
Dragon Callers are born
with the special power
to bridge the gap
between the realms
of nature, mankind,
and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us,
the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters,
and restore balance
to our world.
Okay, so where are we
headed off to next?
To the Light City.
The City of Exscion!
[CHARO, TAMAZO, ACE panting]
[GARNET] Pick up the pace,
you're falling behind!
[TAMAZO]
Tama...
This is the worst mission
the Guild's given us by far.
When they said we'd
be her assistants,
I never pictured this.
What did we do to deserve such
cruel and unusual punishment?
Stop whining!
We're on a special mission to
spread awareness of the Guild!
Now where's the tall one,
Assistant Number Three?
Who? You mean Tiger?
I better not hear that he ran
away to avoid this mission.
Nah, he was already gone.
He sorta decided
to head out solo
on his journey
to go for the top.
What?
Which seems pretty
selfish, doesn't it?
I had always assumed we were
going to do it together
as a team.
[GARNET]
That's just the way it goes.
The stage of life you're in
dictates your motivations.
But I doubt a little kid
like you would understand.
You realize I'm the oldest
one here, right?
And yet, I'm the more
accomplished Dragon Caller!
[laughs]
[BOTH groan]
I'm tired, tama! How far is it?
We're almost there!
Just look!
Tama!
Your attention!
Madam Garnet has arrived!
[GIRLS] Welcome back to the
Academy, Madam Garnet!
Salutations!
Hold on! Who are
these intruders?
My assistants.
[GIRLS] Welcome, Madam
Garnet's Assistants!
Oh, man. Where are we?
[GARNET] It's an academy
for Dragon Callers.
[CHARO] I didn't even know
they had such a place.
The Light City sends
gifted children
who may become
Dragon Callers here.
And I'm an alumna of
this fine institution.
[BOTH]
Good to see you, Madam Garnet.
Hello, ladies.
[STUDENT A, STUDENT B]
And greetings, Servants.
Yes, hello, tama.
Everybody here seems
super polite, tama.
The way she always
acts around us,
it's hard to believe
she ever came here.
For real.
I heard that, short stuff!
So, uh, are those girls training
to become Dragon Callers?
[STUDENTS grunting]
Yes, that's why
it's too dangerous
to keep this place
inside the city.
[ACE]
That makes sense.
They invited me here
as a special guest
for today's graduation ceremony.
When I first heard we were
coming here for your concert,
I assumed it would
be at some empty,
out-of-the-way shopping mall.
--[ACE] Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
--[TAMAZO] Tama.
Shut your grease trap!
Hiya, Master Garnet!
[GARNET gasps]
Master who now?
Oh, Cynthia!
It's been too long!
Have you gotten taller?
I think that you have!
[CYNTHIA laughs]
We've all been waiting for you!
Come right this way. Follow me!
You heard the lady.
Let's go, boys.
--[ACE, CHARO] Fine.
--Tama.
[ANNOUNCER A]
And now, a real treat.
A speech from academy alumna,
and Guild Dragon Caller,
please welcome Miss Garnet.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[GARNET giggling]
They adore her!
That's unexpected.
Garnet is in the house!
You guys. Congratulations
to every one of you!
I have the perfect song to
celebrate this special day.
I really hope you enjoy it!
[music playing]
[GARNET] All of their
faces are so full of hope
for what the future
holds in store for them.
It really brings back memories
of the time I spent here.
[STUDENTS panting]
[GARNET panting]
I'm done for.
[STUDENT C]
Oh, I can't run.
I can't either.
[HERRIOT]
You sure about that, Garnet?
[GARNET]
Yes, Herriot!
That's "Master" to you.
Now, Gold Dragon! Bite Garnet!
[GOLD DRAGON roars]
[GARNET screams]
So you can still run.
Ten more laps for lying!
[GARNET]
No!
Herriot seems to like hazing
Garnet. Bad luck, huh?
Diana, I love that new ribbon.
Where'd you get it?
[DIANA] Mommy bought it for
me. It goes with my shoes.
[STUDENT D] My mom just
sent me a dumb letter.
Becoming a Dragon Caller
isn't worth this headache!
The sooner you fill this
basket with four leaf clovers,
the sooner you'll
be allowed to eat.
What're you talking about?
There aren't any clovers here!
We couldn't find any.
[MYER]
It is what it is.
Try harder next time.
Yes, sir.
[GARNET]
Mister Myer!
Look! I found a
four leaf clover!
[giggles]
[MYER] Good. Now keep at it
until you fill the basket.
Huh?
You already found
one, didn't you?
That means you should
be able to find more.
[GARNET]
What?
Good luck out there, Garnet.
I'm so cold,
and so very hungry.
Why am I the only one out here?
[GARNET]
Enough is enough.
I'm gonna leave
this stinkin' place!
[MYER]
Oh, my.
Do we have a daredevil
trying to make an escape?
She'll have to go through the
guardian angel of this academy,
our Valkyrie.
[squeals]
[thud]
[GARNET screams]
[crying]
[GARNET]
Mister Myer. Master.
This is stupidly easy.
Now, get back to it.
You guys are evil!
[GARNET]
There! Basket's full! Satisfied?
You see? I knew
you had it in you.
[GARNET yelps]
You sure got spine, kid!
So then, Herriot, Master,
did you have a good
time hazing me all day?
It was a cold,
wet pain in the butt.
But it was just me out there,
and I'm not allowed
to leave the school.
Why are things so harsh?
Because sadly, kid,
you were born with a gift.
[whines]
So I can't let you out
until you start getting the hang
of controlling your power.
And great power without control
makes for a dangerous
combination.
But I don't suppose any of
those words change how you feel.
[GARNET cries]
[HERRIOT sighs]
Cheer up, would ya?
I want you to have this.
[GARNET gasps]
Y'know, I'll be graduating
soon, so it's all yours.
Hold on. You passed?
Of course I did!
[GARNET gasps]
That's great! It means
I'll finally be free!
--Yeah, well...
--Thank you!
--You better not slack off
--No more Master Herriot!
--just 'cause I'm not around.
--My life can be normal!
[GARNET gasps]
[GARNET]
Pop Idols?
Who are they?
They're practically sparkling!
They're so cute
I wanna explode!
[MYER] Miss Garnet,
are you still awake?
[GARNET] It isn't fair.
I wann sparkle, too.
And I wanna do it while I'm
still young enough to enjoy it!
[MYER]
Hey! Lights out!
Oh wow, Diana!
You look gorgeous!
I wasn't sure about it at first,
but Mommy asked the
photographer for a favor.
That's amazing! You could
be a model, Diana!
--[DIANA] Thank you.
--[GARNET growls]
[GARNET] I'm sick of
wearing this uniform!
I want to do the things that
normal girls get to do!
Like go shopping or have
tea with petit fours!
You better believe I'm getting
outta here this time!
Go! Angelion!
[GARNET screams]
[ANGELION cries]
Curse you!
Wow, Miss Garnet! You sure
do have a lot of guts!
Going head to head with
the Valkyrie like that!
Thank you. And you are?
I'm Cynthia, a freshman.
I hope you don't mind, but
I'd like to call you "Master"!
Yeah, sure, why not?
That stupid Valkyrie!
One of these days,
I'm gonna pulverize her!
[CYNTHIA yelps]
[GARNET, ANGELION screaming]
[CYNTHIA] Master Garnet!
I'll wait for you down here!
[GARNET]
At long last,
Master Herriot's
graduation day arrived.
[MYER]
And now a word
from student body
representative, Garnet.
Master, are we really
going to do this?
You bet we are!
[MYER]
Miss Garnet? Is something wrong?
[GARNET sighs]
Graduates.
Thanks for all the hazing you
did throughout the year!
Especially Master Herriot!
What's gotten into her?
To tell you how much
I appreciate it...
...I'll sing for you!
[HERRIOT]
Huh?
♪ What is this pain
that I am feeling ♪
♪ as the story unfolds
before my eyes? ♪
♪ Youthful flower,
growing like a weed. ♪
♪ Just give us a
little more time... ♪
Who would've guessed?
Little Miss Honors Student
went off the deep end.
That's quite enough.
I know you hear me!
I won't be stopped!
Release!
I'm gonna sparkle, even
if I have to force it!
Yeah, Master Garnet!
Stickin' it to the man!
No, wait. This is
gonna end badly.
It's her. It's the
Academy's guardian angel!
You caused a disruption
during the ceremony.
She's here to keep order!
The enemy of youth! Valkyrie!
I'm ready! Bring it on!
[ANNOUNCER A] Thus concludes
our commencement ceremony.
Now please rise and bow.
Everybody's looking at us.
So, Garnet, I never thought
that you had the guts
to do something like that.
I'm impressed.
That was pretty cool.
[gasps]
[DIANA]
I just wanted to tell you.
[CYNTHIA cuckles]
Oh, yeah! Looks like you
made a good impression!
Stop it.
[CYNTHIA yelps]
What is it?!
[CYNTHIA]
I'm really sorry.
[GARNET] Cynthia was only
following the orders
that I gave her, sir!
But, Master!
You made the
ceremony a disaster.
Don't you feel bad about
ruining it for Miss Herriot
and the rest of
the graduating class?
Well, uh, they actually
seemed to enjoy it!
Sure did.
Especially the part
where you dopes
got blasted head-first
into the vases.
[MYER sighs]
[MYER] Training activities
every afternoon,
and not a single
snack for Garnet
until she's completed
the Guild Exam.
Understood?
[GARNET screams]
Betcha can't wait for the
Guild Exam now, can ya?
Best of luck!
I'm not gonna make it!
[MYER] Today is your chance to
earn your place in the Guild.
You're the only one taking
the exam this year, Garnet.
I wish you the very best.
Thank you!
[GARNET] Like I'm actually
gonna take that dumb test!
It's been ages since
the last time I got out,
and I'm gonna make
this one count!
You?!
Don't you look at me like that!
I know what you're going to say!
I just wanna enjoy my youth a
little bit while I still can!
Is that so wrong?
You're not even willing
to hear me out, are you?
Well, then so be it!
I'm gonna take you down,
then enjoy my time in the sun!
Release!
--[thudding]
--[GARNET, ANGELION scream]
[GARNET]
Let me go! Please!
Oh, mighty Valkyrie!
Just give me a break!
Hey! Been a while.
Oh, wow. You look bad.
Yeah, whatever.
[HERRIOT]
Right, well,
I was afraid you weren't even
going to show up for the exam.
Nope. I made it.
[HERRIOT]
Go on.
Give it your best shot!
All right already!
I'm here, right? Let's do it.
[GARNET]
So annoying!
--[STUDENTS cheering]
--[applause]
[giggles]
Wow, her performance
really moved them.
No joke. She really
gave it all she had.
I kinda have a higher opinion
of her after seeing that.
[GARNET] Ninety-nine percent of
the reason I'm where I am today
is because of the hardwork
and dedication I put in,
but that remaining one percent
I owe to that annoying Valkyrie.
Wow! Master Garnet,
what a great show!
[TAMAZO]
Terrific, tama!
Something the matter?
[GARNET]
You guys can go on ahead.
I have one last piece of
business to attend to.
--Huh?
--Tama?
[GARNET] Hello, Valkyrie.
Still here guarding the academy?
Long time no see.
Thanks for being so hard
on me while I was here.
I want to show you exactly
how strong I've become!
Prepare yourself!
Now! Release!
Today's the day that
Angelion and I are gonna
defeat the mighty Valkyrie!
[GARNET]
Angelion!
[ANGELION cries]
I'm not falling
for it this time!
You sent me flying head first
into so many different
things over the years
with that old move of yours!
And it was super annoying!
But after I became a
Guild Dragon Caller,
I started fighting monsters
all over the world.
I finally realized that
you'd been holding back.
That you were only trying
to make me better!
But you can stop that now!
Test my might! Come at me!
[GARNET]
Like I told you,
I'm not the same
person I used to be.
[GARNET] Valkyrie. You were the
best rival a girl could ask for.
[GARNET]
And well, I...
[GARNET] I owe you so much.
For everything you've done!
[VALKYRIE] I've been
waiting for this moment.
I'm proud of how much
you've grown, Garnet.
You've achieved your potential.
Let me entrust my soul
into your hands.
I swear, we'll fight
evil together.
And we can be sparkly too!
Hey, cut it out!
What are you up to, egghead?
Tama!
An Armor Drop. There you go!
How'd you do that?
Uh, never mind. I think the
less I know about it the better.
But, all the same, thank you!
[ACE]
A horrifying island inhabited
by monsters called Death.
And it was there
that we discovered
the SDF's secret base.
I wonder what those
guys're up to.
Next time! "Breaking
into SDF's Secret Base."
Great, Lance is gonna be there.