Johnny?
What are you doing?
Sto-o-o-o-o-o-p!
Takizawa? What's wrong?
I swear, I am seriously gonna
punch that guy out.
Anything else you need, sir?
Y'know, I don't think putting on
that t-shirt was the best idea.
Nah, it's okay.
I think I get why Seleção
number two wanted me
to wear it.
I don't think that it
can actually hurt anything.
You must be. Akira
Iinuma, I take it?
Yeah, that's right.
My name is Chigusa Iinuma.
I am Seijiro Iinuma's wife.
Now tell me. Who are you?
And what did you have to do
with this "incident" yesterday?
The "incident"?
Oh right, the missiles.
I think I was supposed
to be one of the targets.
I see.
So, you freely admit that you're
aligned with the terrorists.
The government already
released the details
of last night's events.
They claim it was a
preemptive strike against
the terrorists behind
Careless Monday.
Huh?
But what would make them
say something like that?
Was that part of Mononobe's
request, too? Really?
No matter.
What's clear enough is
that someone like you
is not even worthy to speak
the name Seijiro Iinuma.
He was a great man.
While others were content
to let Japan crumble,
he spent his last ounce
of strength trying
to make it whole...
He gave his life to the
service of his country.
And you dare exploit his death
by declaring yourself his son?
You are a liar and a coward!
And I will see to it
your crimes are exposed!
I want this DNA tested,
immediately!
Hey...
Sorry, it looks like they're
not gonna let me leave with you.
So listen...
I need to ask you
for one more favor.
I need you to try to
find my mom for me.
No, really...
She's here somewhere-
I'm pretty sure I saw
her on Careless Monday.
It was while we were
evacuating everyone,
before the missiles hit.
There was this lady
walking a mini Shiba;
she looked at me and ran
like she'd seen a ghost!
Get it? I think that was my mom!
And... the mini Shiba was.
Yeah, I think she recognized me,
and that's why she panicked
and ran away without her dog.
I even went around
to all the shelters
looking for her,
but she wasn't there.
Hey wait a second...
does this mean you got
all your memories back?
Sorta... The "Takizawa"
stuff at least.
So, you think you
can do that for me?
I'll do my best.
Thanks, Saki...
I'm counting on you!
Oh! And I almost forgot this.
This is...
A memento of our time
together in New York.
I'll be in touch, okay?
Your attention please.
Paging Mr. Kenji Kamiyama.
Please pick up the nearest
white courtesy phone.
Mr. Kenji Kamiyama...
please pick up the nearest
white courtesy phone.
Saki! Over here!
So you're alone?
Prime Minister Iinuma's
supporters
stopped Takizawa and
dragged him off somewhere.
What?
On the bright side,
they at least helped him
avoid the media for now.
Not to mention all
of these guys.
They started showing up
once word got out
you were coming.
Some of 'em have been
camped out since yesterday.
We need to get out
of here, and fast.
Come on.
Before someone
recognizes you from TV.
I should call
Hirasawa right away
and tell him about
Takizawa's mother.
Oh, hold on... Here...
If you're gonna use your cell,
download this
Air Ship app first.
It links to a secure Voice Over
IP site Itazu set up for us.
You can't be too careful.
Use this to talk from now on.
We think all of our
phones are being tapped.
By who?
Guess you've missed a lot huh?
We found out the
police are trying
to frame Eden of the East
as the terrorist group
behind the missile attacks.
Look, don't worry.
I'll go get the car.
Yes, Hello. Saki?
Ah. Good.
Well, I'm glad you're safe;
we were starting
to worry about you.
And Takizawa?
Right. Right. I see.
Got it. But listen,
we had to shut down
the main Eden site
for the time being.
We've moved back into
our college club room;
we're setting up
the old system here.
Right. Not a problem.
We'll send you a password
so you can log in.
Yeah, that'll help, thanks.
I'll talk to you soon, then.
'Kay, let's see. Next is.
Yes, hello? Saki?
You okay? What's wrong?
Wait--you're back? Already?
What, now? You're joking, right?
What'd she say?
She's asking us if we
can bring her the dog!
Saki, you know how early
we have to get up
to open the bakery.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
You're a life saver, sis!
So are they bringing the dog?
Yeah.
Good. That's great.
Oh and, I just tried
running a quick image search
to see what turned up.
Check it out.
"Have Public Security Division
investigate Eden of the East?"
That's bad.
And we've still got to worry
about Mononobe trying
to attack Juiz again.
I got lucky Kuroha was
watching out for me last time.
But I'm on my own
from this point;
it's up to me to get
everyone out of this mess.
C'mon, think...
I can't use Juiz or the other
Seleção'll know where I am.
Okada...? No, Takizawa!
Found you, you son of a bitch!
Well... Actually,
I'm Akira Iinuma now.
I know! And what's up with that?
First you're the Air King,
and now you're s'posed
to be the PM's son?
Then you call us to the
airport and try to sneak off!
What in the hell are
you tryin' to pull here?
I tell you one thing,
I am not gettin' naked
again, you got me?
So you're one of the NEETs?
One of the twenty-thousand?
I didn't call you.
I dunno, maybe Number Two
gathered you guys here.
Quit jerkin' me around!
We're already far enough up
shit creek as it
is thanks to you!
Everyone was callin'
us "AKX20000",
treatin' us like popstars...
next thing you know
we're yesterday's news.
We stopped bein' cool and
started bein' NEETs again.
all 'cause a' you!
Actually...
I don't think that part
was really my fault.
Dude... It so was!
Okay... You win...
I'll make it right... but first,
I'm gonna need a favor.
You promise we're gonna
go back to bein' cool again?
Uh. Sure. Probably.
Hey, we don't have all day here!
The press and the NEETs
are still combing
this place for you.
We need to leave.
That's good, keep your face
hidden 'til we get to the car.
Okay, all set.
I just sent the Air Ship
app to Takizawa's phone.
Hey... and there's some
new activity on his log!
What's this about?
"Order business cards"...
"Lease office"...
And wait-- "Request
campaign strategy
from advertising agency"?
Yeah, and all that's
just for starters.
It looks like he's
also throwing money
at anyone in
government or business
with even an ounce
of political clout.
It's like what someone would do
if they were trying
to buy votes.
So he's really making a bid
for the Prime Minister's seat.
That's him now.
Takizawa. Yeah, I heard.
Saki already contacted us.
That's good.
And I'm gonna assume
you already know
more about what's
going on than I do...
Like with the
missiles yesterday...
Right.
If Number Eleven
hadn't taken my place
at the last second like she did,
it would've been game over.
And I don't think I'm ready
to get knocked out if
Mononobe tries again.
I'm gonna need a way
to secure my Juiz somehow.
Yes, I couldn't agree more.
After all, if you get
eliminated from the game,
it's bad for us too,
right? Here.
We've already been doing
some digging into this.
I'm going to pass the
phone to someone
who'll be able to give you
better answers than I can.
'Sup, Vintage Boy.
'Bout time you got back.
Hey, Panties?
How's it goin', man?
We can do small
talk later, dude.
Now listen, I've looked through
all the old activity logs,
so I knew that Number Twelve
was placin' a lot of orders
for drivers and
gasoline for some reason.
'Part I didn't
know 'til yesterday,
was that he had these
trucks drivin' around on
an endless loop up
and down the expressway.
That slick bastard Number One
definitely got the
drop on us there.
Soon as that missile
attack happened,
I started monitoring
all the traffic cams
on the Chuo Expressway.
The trucks scattered at first--
guess they didn't like gettin'
the shit blown out of 'em--
but I confirmed that they
started formin' back up
into a new caravan
a few hours ago.
Really? Man, you are the best!
I cannot argue with the truth.
So... I've got eyes on
Trailer Number Nine right now,
just past the
Kawasaki-Ukishima exit.
And by my math,
considering the time
and distance they've
been traveling,
I figure they're about
due for a pit stop
so they can fuel up
and switch drivers.
So that means?
It means the Juiz's are prob'ly
gonna pull over in Umihotaru!
"Umihotaru"?
And there you have it.
So. You have your
next move figured out yet?
Looks like I need to head
to this Umihotaru place
before I can do anything else.
I mean, without Juiz,
I'm just a guy with
no memory, right?
If you're "just a guy",
then what does that
make the rest of us, huh?
Know what I said when they
started coming after Eden?
"What would Takizawa do."
Because no matter what
anyone's thrown at you.
You're still out there
on your own, fighting.
But, this time,
we'll be fighting
right there beside you.
However this turns out,
we're with you.
I'll head to Umihotaru now.
Let's meet up there, 'kay?
You sure?
If you guys get any
further involved you
won't ever be able to go
back to your normal lives.
Well, you let us
worry about that.
Besides, we're NEETs.
We never had normal
lives to begin with.
Okay, then.
See you at Umihotaru.
Hi!
I think it's safe
to come out now.
Hey!
Bam! Got'cha!
Aw, you should see the looks
on your faces right now!
Totally fooled!
Am I good or what?
Hey, wait, what're you doin'--?
Yeah, well, I still got you!
You're never gonna find him now!
Suck it, assholes!
Hey.
Sorry. Traffic was bad.
Listen, I know you're busy,
but, it'd be nice if you
came home once in a while.
Yeah...
Well. Here you go.
Look, I promise...
I'll explain everything
soon, okay?
Don't worry.
We're on your side here.
Thanks, Ryosuke.
That's good.
Looks like she's finally found
something she can
devote herself to.
Ah... Good deal.
You work fast, as always.
Okay then, the guy I told
you about is on his way,
so be ready with a
nice lukewarm welcome.
Yeah... That's the one...
I know, he looks like
a crazy person,
but he's harmless enough.
You just give him the
goods like we talked about.
Exactly!
Whatever works
for you's okay by me...
I know that you'll get it done.
"The message on the
back of his shirt,
'Hey Outside, shoot
some more,' appeared to be
a defiant accusation
that the missile attacks
were launched from abroad.
Clearly the sharp
nationalist rhetoric
of the right leaning Iinuma
is still alive and well."
Yeah. That oughta'
stir up some shit.
That's good.
I'm sure Number Nine thinks
he was just thumbing
his nose at Mr. Outside...
but the rest of the world
won't see it that way.
Don't sneak up on me like that!
I thought you were asleep.
You're still playing even though
your Juiz was destroyed?
Why wouldn't I be?
I still got my pride
on the line here, right?
Sure. I guess...
I've got everything
ready for you, so...
time to get goin'.
Should be more
money than you need.
You'll find the
address in there too.
Got it, thanks.
I'll pay you back. Somehow.
Yeah. Don't sweat it.
So, what now?
Annie?
You found your way back!
I knew you would!
So... your dog's name
is "Angelika",
is that right?
Yeah. It's a pretty
name, isn't it?
Now then.
As for if I'm this missile
terrorist's mother, I'm sorry.
There's not a chance.
Just think about
it for a second.
According to your story,
he only lived with his
mother in New York
until he was five, right?
Even if he says
he recognized me,
childhood memories
aren't very reliable.
So then, what was that
on Careless Monday?
Why would you run off
and leave your dog
when you saw him?
It's simple.
I ran because they told me to.
It saved my life, but it
doesn't change the fact
that my apartment
was completely trashed.
Have you ever even
been to New York?
Oh, sure... Once...
On a long vacation.
And... did you ever
stay at the Gramercy?
It's possible.
There's a movie
theater near there,
it's called the Angelika.
The same as your dog's name.
Is that just a coincidence?
It must be.
All right, so what about
children, do you have any?
Yes, I was a mother, once.
And what happened, if you
don't mind my asking?
He told me that
when he was five,
his mom abandoned him
in a department
store here in Japan.
She gave him some
money to buy something,
and by the time he turned around
from the register she
was nowhere to be found.
Sorry, but do you have
a restroom here you
think I could use?
In the back.
Hey, this is her.
She was kinda' hot.
Is that who I think it is?
Saki, here.
Is that her?
Yeah.
But check out the
guy behind her.
Who does that look like to you?
Prime Minister Iinuma?
Yeah, right?
Dead ringer.
But what does that mean?
I don't know exactly.
But this whole story
about Takizawa being
Iinuma's illegitimate son.
What if Juiz didn't
just make it up?
What if there's a chance
that it's really true?
Correct me if I'm
wrong about this.
But I thought the plan was
to have Public Security
arrest the man who
launched the missiles,
along with his cohorts,
and tie this whole
thing up nice and neat?
Yes.
You assured me that
this could easily
be arranged with Mr. Ato's
little "magic" phone.
And yet, not only
does he remain at large,
but now I'm hearing word
that his claims might be true.
He may actually be Iinuma's son.
Oh?
And when our
foreign neighbors see
the alleged son of a hawkish PM
wearing brazen
accusations on a t-shirt.
They may not respond
kindly to the insinuation
that they are responsible
for the missile attacks.
I will look into all of this.
You have nothing
to worry about, sir.
Mononobe.
I've called in many
favors to build support
for the one-hundred-percent
estate tax bill.
Likewise for the reestablishment
of the Home Ministry.
I am aware, sir.
Then perhaps you'll
agree that the time
has come for some slightly
more extreme measures.
This is it.
Yes, hello... It's Mononobe.
Listen, it turns out
there's a possibility
that Seijiro Iinuma
had a secret lover
about twenty years ago.
I need you to see what
you can dig up on that.
You don't say.
Is that something you found out
during your recent
investigation in New York?
Yes. Yes.
So you're saying that
it was Mr. Iinuma himself
who kept the reservation
on the hotel room
at the Gramercy.
It was empty until he
moved in six months ago,
but it was paid for all along.
Understood. Good.
I'll leave it to you, then.
Juiz... Put me through
to the Tax Bureau's Criminal
Investigation Division.
Umihotaru?
Oh... it's from Grandfather.
So where did all the
drivers run off to?
I'm having them
take a little break
in the rest area.
They did drive non-stop
from Yamanashi.
We've been working
non-stop, too.
Well, c'mon. What did he say?
He says we're taking
the current measures
as a precaution to keep
the game progressing...
And beyond that.
We keep doing our
jobs like we always do,
and we don't interfere
with any request...
No matter what.
We know that already.
Like he always says, the
Seleção and Juiz play the game.
"And we're the kids
who shag the balls."
We got it.
But what happens
if Number One decides
to order another
missile attack right now?
Personally, I'd rather
not get blown up, you know?
Maybe we could try hiding
the trucks on our own?
Yeah?
Come on...
You know we can't do that.
We'd be violating
Grandfather's orders.
And besides, I doubt
even Number One
would be daring enough
to launch a missile here.
Hey... Look over there.
Isn't that Number Nine?
Yeah, you're right!
Juiz speaking.
Hey!
Number Nine!
You seem to be within the
system's effective range again!
Yeah.
Matter of fact.
I'm patting you on
the back as we speak.
Can't you tell?
What? I'm afraid
my system's not equipped
with a sense of touch.
So that's a bit beyond me.
Too bad.
I guess that sort of
spoils the whole surprise.
Now doesn't it.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
It's nothing to apologize for.
I'm just glad I finally
get to meet you.
Number 9...
What brought you here to see me?
Well.
There was a missile
attack on you guys
so I came out here
to rescue you.
Didn't you know about that?
No... I didn't...
So how will you protect
me from more missiles?
Good question.
I haven't actually thought
that far ahead just yet.
Hey, Number One just asked
for his trailer to be moved!
So this time he just plans
to steal his own Juiz?
Juiz...
Can you make it
so that I know how
to drive a trailer real fast?
Y'know, like in The Matrix?
Pardon?
Number Nine, you know
you're already licensed
to drive all vehicle classes,
from Heavy all the way
down to Motorcycle.
Huh? You don't say.
How 'bout that. Okay...
And I think I just figured out
what to do next, Juiz.
Now Number Nine is doing it?
There's nothing
in his activity log.
Does that mean
he's driving it himself?
I get it!
If he wants to stay
safe from missiles,
then all he has to do
is keep his trailer close
to Number One's, right?
That's my Number Nine!
So what now?
You think we should
tell Grandfather?
Hmm. That's against
the rules, too.
As long as
Number Nine is doing this
without any help
from his Juiz...
then the other Seleção
don't know what he's up to.
And if they don't get to know,
neither does grandfather.
Good point.
What? He says he's driving Juiz.
Yeah...
And it looks like
Number One's trailer
is headed back into town, too.
So where are all
you guys right now?
We're close.
We're in the tunnel now.
Really?
Well alright, then! So am I!
So you're in the
tunnel next to ours
going the other way?
We'll make a u-turn at
Umihotaru.
Tell him we'll call him
back in a few minutes.
Got that?
So he hijacked Juiz, eh?
Guess I'm not surprised.
It's Number Three.
She's requesting
"Sweets for Saizo".
"Saizo"? Wait.
Like as in Saizo Ato?
It's too bad I don't have Yuki,
I could send him to
pay a visit in advance.
Yes, Juiz...
I'd like you to send a message
to this sweets parlor for me.
So that's it.
I'm not Japanese anymore.
Yeah, so listen.
If you two aren't gonna
order anything else,
I wanna go ahead
and close up shop.
Oh! Uh...
We'll take two more
Mango Lassies, please.
Perfect...
It looks like these two have
brought some unwanted
guests to my door.
No way their tab was worth this.
Right. Right...
Yeah... I got'cha...
I was just lookin'
at the same entry.
According to the detail log,
it looks like he's in Tokyo.
But doesn't Number Three live
all the way out in Fukuoka?
That doesn't sound good.
What'cha got?
Well, I hate to say it,
but I think we might have played
right into Public
Security's hands here.
'Til a few years ago,
this room was used
by an extremist student group
called the Eastern Federation
of Revolutionaries.
All they gotta do
is connect a few dots
to make it look
like we're a spin-off.
And from there, it wouldn't
be much of a stretch
to frame Eden as a
terrorist organization.
Open up!
You are wanted
for trespassing...
as well as aiding and
abetting subversive activities!
Come out of there right now!
What's going on, Panties?
Hey! Panties--!
Well, the good news is.
I have a hiding place
all ready for us.
Over here.
You know I'm kind'f
a big guy, right?
Hey.
Damn, Kasuga.
You didn't dig this
whole tunnel, did ya?
Sure, why not!
Okay, Fine man,
it was already here.
It has been since
the late sixties.
During the All-Campus Joint
Struggle Committee era,
the Eastern Federation
of Revolutionaries dug
this tunnel to try to aid
the Narita Airport protests.
I see.
Who'da thought that
some tunnel built
for baby boomers
to play militant
in would wind up
savin' my ass one day.
Yeah, I know,
it's like we're usin'
their own dirty tricks
against 'em, right?
I think the irony's great.
Sure. So I guess it's true then,
the only thing those
old bastards ever did
for us was dig us
into a great big hole.
Good to see you, Takizawa...
So what's up?
Takky!
Hey! How's it goin'?
Been a long time, right, Mittan?
My name's not Mittan!
Still as feisty as ever.
So let's get to it.
That other driver went
inside to take a break.
Hirasawa...
Why don't you jump in there
and try takin' the wheel.
And don't worry 'bout missiles,
Trailer One is totally safe.
Hold on!
I don't know the first thing
about driving a
monster like that!
Hey, I managed!
I'm sure you'll do fine!
This is not a good idea.
Now that I think about it,
I used to have a
Heavy-class license.
You what?
Let's go you muthas! Movin' out!
All right... Try to keep up!
Shouldn't you at least tell me
where we're going first?
And here you go.
Take a look out front,
but don't be obvious about it.
There's a window
in the storage closet
by the bathroom.
You can slip out through there.
Now, if you'll both
excuse me, I'm going first.
All right. Listen,
Saki, you go after her.
I'll stay behind
and try to stall them
for as long as I can.
If Takizawa really is
Seijiro Iinuma's son...
then that might just be enough
to turn this whole
situation around.
Talk to her.
Do whatever you have to do,
but get the truth out
of her, no matter what.
But--! Osugi!
Just go! Now, Saki.
Thank you... Osugi.
Oh!
Sorry, guys, but we're actually
already closed for the night!
Ah, Ms. Iinuma
testifies tomorrow.
Now that ought'a
be pretty interesting.
So, Mononobe...
Looks like I'm about
to call checkmate
and I didn't even need my phone.
The Tax Bureau?
2G, we've got problems!
There's an army of tax
inspectors out there!
Not bad, bastard.
So you're okay. Good.
Then have you figured
out the connection
between Number Three
and Mr. Outside?
No, we're still
workin' on that...
but, we know we're not
the only ones
watchin' her activity.
Check it... These sweets?
They come from Shinbashi,
this shop called "Odafuji".
It's in Number One's log, too.
He made a request to
have a message included
with the sweets when
they're delivered.
And you are not gonna
believe what it says.
Get a load of this, dude--
I see.
Well, Takizawa has
his hands full now.
I'll go myself.
Look, just send me
the detail log, okay?
Hey, hold on!
It's too dangerous to go alone!
Anything could happen out there!
If it does. You guys take over.
I trust that Eden will
be safe in your hands.
Shut up, dipshit!
Don't even joke about that!
Just promise me you'll
be nice to Micchon, okay?
You know, she was
pretty mad at you earlier
when you hung up
the phone on her.
What? Ahh.
Wait! Please!
I apologize.
I borrowed this
without asking you.
This photo...
It's you and Prime Minister
Iinuma, isn't it?
And, um. I can't
help but notice.
You're pregnant.
You said you were a mother once.
Wasn't that child Takizawa?
Takizawa's past is...
Well, it's almost
completely lost now.
So, if he were to get
even a piece of it back,
I can't begin to
tell you how much
that knowledge
might help him out.
Even if the public
ends up despising him
as the terrorist who launched
the missile attacks
on Careless Monday.
If there's a chance
that he really is
Prime Minister Iinuma's son.
He might be able to do
something to fix this situation.
Please tell me the truth.
You really are Takizawa's
mother, now aren't you?
This picture really
does take me back.
Here's what I know.
Money is the great equalizer.
If you have it, then
that's all that matters.
Things like age and
status mean nothing.
It may seem shallow,
saying money is the most
important thing there is,
but that's what
my life has taught me.
And if I could teach
my child only one lesson
about the world, there it is.
So, how does your mystery boy
feel now about being
given, what was it?
500 yen? And abandoned.
I'd guess he'd have
some strong opinions
about money as well.
It's a long story...
but Takizawa...
he was put in a position
to use ten billion yen
however he wanted.
But even with all that money,
he's never spent a
single yen of it on himself.
That's the kind of guy he is.
I see...
Then he couldn't be my son.
I'm afraid that
I can't help you.
Good night.
Saki!
What happened?
Did you find out if she's
really Takizawa's mother?
It's her...
She didn't come out and
say it, but it has to be.
I mean. She knew
that it was 500 yen.
I should call Takizawa now...
Shouldn't I?
I should just tell him
"I found your mother".
"You were right all along,
she really was your mother."
Yeah. Okay.
So then what are
you waiting for?
Because if... I tell him.
I mean... when I tell him.
I don't think.
I don't think Takizawa will
ever come back to me again;
I'll lose him for good!
C'mon, Saki.
Come on! I won't
let you give up now!
Let's just go find Takizawa.
We'll go talk to him
in person. Okay?
I'm sure he's waiting
for you to come to him.
I'm sorry.
I know I've put you through
a lot of trouble, ma'am.
Take a seat.
First you disappear without
a trace from the airport.
Then you drive a truck up
to my front door.
Moreover, I have
been told that this
is the very same truck
that the government
launched an
attack on last night.
So then, what is the
meaning of all this?
Well... the thing is...
that truck's my only hope
of salvaging this situation.
so I kinda had
to bring it with me.
I guess it is
pretty inconvenient.
You're very bold...
but I suppose you have
to be to be a terrorist.
Wait. I'm not a terrorist!
Then what would
you call yourself?
It's kinda hard to explain,
but I guess you'd say.
I guess you'd say that.
I'm someone who's been chosen
to make this country better.
All terrorists make such claims.
Uh... well... yeah, but...
How do I put this.
There's just no
easy way to explain.
I've no interest in hearing
your rationalizations...
And I have
absolutely no intention
of arguing the finer
points of your position.
All I do want to know,
in no uncertain terms,
is what you are after.
I want to know what
it is you hope to gain
by suddenly claiming to be
my husband's illegitimate son.
So, is it attention?
Or is it money?
Or is this just another
terrorist act designed
to spread confusion
and harm this nation?
None'a that!
I promise, this business
about being Iinuma's son,
it wasn't my idea.
Things just got out of hand.
All I wanted, was to become
the king of this country.
I thought that maybe
then I'd actually be able
to do some good
for all the people
who are struggling out there.
But, somewhere along the way,
I guess "king" got turned
into "prime minister".
Now wait...
Do you honestly expect me
to take this seriously?
Yes. And believe me,
I know exactly how crazy all
of this must sound to you.
But... it's still the truth.
Honestly, I'd rather not
become king if I can avoid it.
It is a tough job...
People want you
to take responsibility
for all their problems,
and then they complain
about everything you do.
I might have to erase
my memories again
just to deal with everything.
But still my request
was accepted...
so that means it's got
to be worth a try, at least.
Your request to become king...
was "accepted"?
My late husband... Seijiro...
he actually retired
from politics...
He was determined
to live a carefree life
as a private citizen...
Then his supporters
convinced him
to become Prime Minister again.
And in the end,
he passed away before
he was able to do anything.
Even if you do somehow convince
the public to accept
you as "Iinuma's Son".
I would say that's hardly
a guarantee of success.
You do understand you'll have
even less power
than a terrorist.
Yeah... I get that.
But I refuse to give up
'til I meet the man
who got me into this mess.
I still owe'im a good punch.
Mister Mononobe?
That's very odd; how did
he know to look here?
Mister Mononobe.
Wait, I'm sorry,
but did he come here
to see me by any chance?
Well, yes...
Actually, he did ask for you.
This is so strange.
I'm sorry.
In any case.
You may use the study for now.
However, you should be aware,
I've been summoned
to give testimony
before the Diet
inquiry panel tomorrow.
While I may have
temporarily harbored you here
as a matter of courtesy,
given the possibility
you're my husband's son.
Ultimately, when asked,
I will still have to
report you as a terrorist.
Right. Understood...
You do what you have to do.
So it's been a full thirty years
since anyone's even seen Ato.
I have to hand it to you.
Somehow you even
convinced Juiz to like you.
Not only that you kept making
out-of nowhere requests that
completely trumped my own,
and neatly turned all
of my plans on their head.
You have managed to outplay
me in this game at every turn.
You came here to tell me that?
Yes.
That, and also to request
a small favor from you.
I've come to ask you to
withdraw from this game.
Please.
My desire to change
this country of ours
existed long before I began
my career in public service.
But the reality is
that Japan's problems
have grown too large,
and become too widespread
for any mere bureaucrat
to solve them.
At least by honest means.
By the time I realized this,
it was far too late for me
to change course but,
fortunately, that was when this
phone came into my possession.
Sorry, but you're
Saizo Ato aren't you?
Well, that depends...
Who're you?
Well, I'm a friend of Number
Nine's, Kazuomi Hirasawa.
There are some things
I need to ask you, sir,
if that's alright.
So young man.
If someone suddenly
handed you ten billion yen...
and then said...
"improve this country",
what would you do?
Wait, is that how you
selected the Seleção?
By asking that question
to all of your passengers?
What am I going to
do about that Toshiko?
So? What do you want?
Well...
It's obvious you
have no intention
of stopping the game...
no matter how dangerous
the players' requests become.
But I think it's time you
at least told someone
what the name of
the game really is.
When Ato asked me
what I would do
if I was suddenly
given ten billion yen.
I told him I thought
that the first thing
this country needed
was to go on a diet,
on a nationwide scale.
A government-led redistribution
of human resources...
where the only priority
is the effective functioning
of those sectors
with global currency.
I said that,.
we had to make Japan
smaller and lighter
on its feet to have any
hope of success in the future.
But... to make that
happen more quickly...
it would first require me
to temporarily emasculate
the government.
And that's what Careless
Monday was all about right?
Correct...
But it needn't have been
a missile attack specifically.
Any event that
stressed the nation
to near the breaking point
would have allowed
my plan to proceed.
Because after that...
the magic cell phone would
no longer be necessary...
I could take my time
getting the rest done
by simply working
my network of connections.
So you're saying that
everything I did was.
Yes, as it turned out,
you and Yuki were kind enough
to handle most of
the dirtiest work for me.
I do appreciate that.
If that was the plan
you should've told
me from the start.
We've all been acting on our own
because of some idea
that we'd get killed
if we didn't play to win...
But I would've had no
problem teaming up with you.
If we'd put all
our heads together,
who knows what we
coulda' come up with.
Well, I'm afraid I'm not
so eager to share the glory.
Then maybe you should
be the Prime Minister;
did you ever consider that?
I would say you're
definitely more suited
to the part than I am.
We're coming to open
the gate right now.
It's okay, nobody's watching.
Where's Takizawa?
They took him
inside the mansion;
he hasn't come out yet.
So... you have any
luck finding his mom?
And we found out
some other things, too,
that I really need
to tell him right away.
I'll happily bow out of
the game on one condition.
If you'll agree to take
the job as Prime Minister...
I'll even promise to
give you my full support.
Tempting as that may be,
I'm afraid I have
to pass on all this
"Prime Minister"
and "King" business.
We live in a nation
of a hundred million
short-sighted,
self-centered fools.
But I suspect your dealings
with the masses have
already shown you as much.
Well.
The Prime Minister functions
as little more than
a sacrificial lamb.
You could say he's an outlet
for the stress
of Japan's citizens,
who gained their freedom
and became unfree.
Take the late Mr. Iinuma here.
He died before
he could ever manage
to enact any meaningful change.
So then how are you gonna do it?
How do you plan to make
Japan "light on its feet"
without being its leader?
I suppose for starters.
I'll try to restrict citizen
freedoms without their noticing.
You see, they're
an irresponsible lot
who can't decide
anything for themselves...
but they still refuse to agree
to anything anyone
else suggests.
So my plan is to reestablish
the Home Ministry,
and from there, I will
be able to remove them
from the equation
a bit at a time.
What's the "Home Ministry"?
You mean you wanted
to be Prime Minister,
and you don't even know that?
Yes?
Hello... Takizawa?
Saki... Sorry...
I guess I never had a
good chance to call you.
No, it's alright...
but listen...
it's about your mother.
So how'd it go?
I found her.
The woman from Careless Monday.
You were right, she
really was your mom.
She's operating
a bar in Mishuku.
Really?
Yeah...
Her name is Aya Iwashita...
and apparently...
she was Prime
Minister Iinuma's lover back
when he was still
just a Diet member.
Your hotel room in New York.
You remember how you told me
it had been paid for all along?
Yeah.
I think that's where Aya stayed.
Twenty years ago or so.
We saw a picture of her
and Iinuma taken
together in New York;
she was clearly pregnant.
When you add it all up.
it looks like you really
are his son, Takizawa.
So that's what happened.
I guess that's why I had
all those memories of
being in New York, too.
Listen... So where
are you right now?
In front of the mansion...
I'm with Micchon and the others.
I see you... Look up.
Yeah, I see you too.
It's good to know that I have
a past like anyone else.
And now I've at least
got a little better idea
of what my mother's like, right?
Thanks for that... Saki.
It seems you've finally
recovered your past.
So... how does it feel?
Knowing that you really are
the Prime Minister's son?
You knew? Of course you did.
I dunno. Guess it
hasn't sunk in yet.
Well, then let's get back
to the business at hand.
I will match the
remaining balance
on your phone in cash,
as getaway money...
You'll be free to go anywhere
in the world that you like.
I will ensure you remain
safe from the supporter...
And I'll see to it
that your friends
are cleared of
suspicion as well.
Given those terms,
would you agree
to quietly walk away
and disappear?
Y'know, that might
not be so bad.
I just have one question though.
You talk about
"the citizens of Japan"...
but you don't actually care
for them too much, do you?
Do you have to ask?
The "citizens"
themselves are nothing
but a collection of parts
that serve the national whole.
It would be counterproductive
to have personal
feelings about them.
Yeah, but...
you can't deny that
each one of them
is an individual person that's
just tryin' to be somebody.
Well, now you're
just being naïve.
Whether they want it or not,
it would be impossible
for all of them
to get to "be somebody".
True, but that doesn't
mean they can't try.
And doesn't putting faith
in them as individuals
give them even more incentive
to lift themselves up
and try harder?
Take me for example,
if nobody had ever told me I was
one of the people
chosen to save Japan...
I doubt that I ever would've
accomplished this much.
It just seems your
way of doing things...
it's a little bit lacking
in the whole compassion
department... isn't it?
So does all this
mean you've decided
to turn down my proposal?
Yeah, I guess it does.
'Cause now I'm thinkin'...
I need a more direct approach.
I'm just gonna have
to try playin' the part
of the terrorist one more time.
At first I thought becoming king
was the only way I could help.
but there's plenty
of other ways... right?
I can still be the man
who's got nothing to lose.
the crazy naked guy in
front of the White House.
Juiz speaking.
Juiz...
Is it possible to
set up a phone call
that goes out to every
citizen in Japan all at once?
The communications
fees associated
with such a call
would be immense.
Depending on the length...
it's possible your balance
will reach zero
before you're finished.
Do you still wish to proceed?
No, I guess that
wouldn't be too good.
I need to make sure I have
at least a hundred million
left in the account at the end.
In that case, I may not
be able grant your request.
I see...
Hold on...
I know what we can do!
Tell me this much, at least.
When you asked Takizawa
how he'd spend ten billion.
What was his response?
Actually, I never did
ask that boy that question.
Say, excuse me, son.
Could I get a paper, please?
Yeah! Sure!
Nah, it's on me.
The only people who
ever ask for just one copy
are the ones who're
actually gonna read it.
Enjoy yourself.
Are you sure?
That's bad business.
I'll make my money
from all the people
who subscribe
then never read it.
Although... they are the ones
who never seem to wanna
pay their bill on time.
That's very true.
You seem a smart boy.
What would even possess you
to take a paper route
in the first place?
You gotta' practice
earning money, right?
Most people got
it all backwards.
I mean, even a
five-year old kid can
figure out how to spend
money, but it seems like
there's a lot of
grown adults out there
who never learn how to earn it.
I guess 'cause spending
money feels a lot nicer
than jumping through
someone else's hoops.
"The customer is always right!".
People think that means
being a consumer
gives them real power.
But honestly,
that's just something
the seller's supposed
to say, isn't it?
Yes, true.
And if we're all buyers,
who the heck's gonna
provide the services?
Seems like that's
the part most people
don't bother to think about.
Personally, I think
it'd probably be healthier
for society if people
thought that earning money
was more fun than
spending it away.
I see.
So that's the reason you
decided to make him a Seleção.
No. You were more
interested in how
he even came to that conclusion!
You just wanted
to figure him out!
I suppose our opinions
on what needs
to be done will
never mesh in the end.
Really? 'Cause the way I see it,
we've both been looking in
the same direction all along.
You can do as you like.
Hello?
Um... Get this...
It's a call directly from Juiz.
What?
Juiz speaking.
I am calling at
Number Nine's request.
For Vintage Boy?
Yes.
He would like to use
the Air Ship application
you created to connect
all of the cell phones
in Japan to Eden of the East.
What the hell?
What's that crazy
bastard up to this time?
It's from Takky.
Hey! Here it is!
Hello, and a good
morning to everyone...
For those that don't know,
I'm the man behind
Careless Monday
and the other
recent terrorist attacks,
Akira Takizawa,
aka the Air King. Bang!
I came home as Prime
Minister Iinuma's son
yesterday to
grab your attention.
I gotta say, it worked
even better than I'd hoped...
but the truth of it is,
I have no actual relation
to our late Prime Minister.
Before I do anything else,
I'd like to offer
my sincere apologies
for all the trouble
I caused his family
and friends these last few days.
Takky, what do you
think you're doing?
You're gonna throw all of Saki's
hard work right down the drain.
Now, to get to the
real reason I'm calling.
Listen up... because what
I'm about to announce is...
a new... terrorist attack.
Once again, I'm planning
to gather a giant crowd
of young people.
and then I'm gonna lead
them off to Paradise.
I'm expecting a
lot more to show up
this time than
the twenty-thousand
I took away six months ago.
What this means...
is that Japan is about to lose
the workforce vital
to its future survival!
If you want to
avoid that outcome
your only option now is
to meet my demands in full.
What's he doing playing
The Pied Piper of Hamelin again?
What could that possibly solve?
There is only one way
that you can do this.
First, I want all you old guys
who take it for granted
you're the winners to promise
you'll give up everything you've
been hoarding all these years.
And then, I want you to join me
and the other young
people of this nation
as we set out
for a new Paradise!
And there you have it,
that's my entire list.
If you fail to meet these
demands our nation's identity
and values will soon be lost...
and the paradise you envisioned
will be lost as well.
And listen--my previous
missile attacks?
They were just warm-ups
to prepare for today.
If you choose to
ignore my demands,
then I guarantee you something
even more terrible
will befall this country.
But, if you can do
what I've told you to do,
even a little bit.
then I'm sure that great things
are in store for all of us!
So, before I sign
off this morning
I'll be sending each of you
one yen in electronic funds.
Please consider this
my parting gift to you.
as well as a
promissory note proving
that everything
I've said today...
it's all going to come true.
'Kay Juiz.
I think that's gonna do it,
but before I hang up for good.
Send one Yen to every
phone we're connected to.
Request accepted.
I sincerely pray you shall
continue to be a wise
and loving king,
who instills fear
and hope into the hearts
of all his subjects.
And now, to all you NEETs
who've been holding
sit-ins in your homes!
The time has come to stand up...
My Air Ship is ready
to carry all of us
into the promised land,
Eden of the East.
I'll see you there.
What the hell's he playing at?
Does he really
think people are going
to go along with this,
just because he asked them to?
At one time, we worked like hell
to do something
for this country,
something that we
all thought was great.
Now... it's become a joke.
Now people call it 'a blemish
on our history', a 'mistake'.
Granted, at the time,
we were a bunch of novices
who didn't know up from
down or left from right.
But I ask you--if
everything we built up
was wrong, then what
would have been right?
Of course...
just when we thought we'd
finally achieved something...
the rules of the
game changed on us-
the whole damn world changed.
New ideas gained prominence.
and increasing our country's
depth was no longer a priority.
It's harsh...
telling the old guard like us
it's time to accept that fact...
that he wants us to
give up our authority...
that it's time for the young...
to start leading the way.
Men like Ryoma Sakamoto
and Jiro Shirasu.
They remain national
heroes to this day,
not only for the
things they did,
but because they were
good about drawing
the right kind of
attention to themselves.
But the true saviors of this
country are history's losers...
the nameless masses who
toil steadily every day...
and leave this world tainted
by crushing losses as a result.
In a time when that
truth is all too often
forgotten or
intentionally ignored.
Number Nine has gone
out on a limb for them.
and made himself
their scapegoat.
Fascinating.
I believe it's time...
to close the curtain
on this game.
The winner is clear.
That phone call...
did that truly go out
to every person in Japan?
Yeah. I think so.
I'm sorry again for
the trouble I caused you.
I guess now I really do have
to go on the run as a terrorist.
so you can tell them
whatever you need
to at the witness summons.
I understand, thank you.
You go on, then.
Oh, and... take this.
I don't believe I need
to look at it now.
You know...
he does remind me a bit
of Mister Iinuma in a way.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
I shouldn't have said that.
It's fine.
If that's what you
see in him, then...
I don't mind.
Your methods are every bit
as drastic as I'd expect...
However, the people of Japan
are an astonishingly
cynical lot.
If you expect to
get what you want
from them so easily,
you're bound for disappointment.
Well, I guess I just give
'em more credit than that.
And I'm just giving
you the facts.
What is this?
Greetings, Seleção...
This is Mister Outside.
I realize this comes
as sudden news,
but at the end of
this phone call,
our game will be concluded.
Overall, I am satisfied
with the results
of your actions.
Therefore,...
I have decided to declare
you all... as victors.
Though our game is ending,
I count on you to be people
who will steer Japan
in a better direction
from this day forward.
"From this day forward"--
c'mon man, I've
always done that.
And...
Finally... as a token of my
thanks for your participation.
I offer you the
greatest of gifts.
I very much hope
you appreciate it.
It's something I've had prepared
from the very beginning,
as an exclusive bonus
for the Seleção who
proved themselves worthy.
Noblesse oblige.
Farewell...
I sincerely pray
you shall continue
to be this country's
latent saviors.
Latent saviors?
Well, hey there, beautiful.
Now why you all
shakin' like that.
ya' ain't hungry, are ya?
You can lick on
my lollipop, suga'.
Yahh! Oh shit.
Someone help! Who am I?
Thank you, so much. Dear Saizo.
Take care.
So what was it? This "present"?
When I delivered
the cell phones...
I took the added
liberty of planting
a little something
in here as well.
And now they will forever
and truly be released
from the game.
Why, you!
How much of their lives
do you have to take away
before you're satisfied?
I'm not so old yet that I'd
lose to a milksop like you.
Takky!
Takizawa!
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Are you feelin' alright?
Yes, hello, excuse me.
I was told I could find
a man named Takizawa here.
Is that correct?
Mononobe?
Sorry, should I know you?
Now If you don't mind,
I'm in a hurry.
You act like you
don't even know me.
After everything
that I've done for you?
So, did I get away without
hearing that weird noise
because I'd already
erased my memory?
What are you worrying
about that for, Takky?
Right now, everyone in Japan
thinks you're a terrorist!
Yeah, well. I'm sure
it'll all work out.
I thought your message
was really brave.
I know they'll hear you.
Thanks, Saki. Really.
I wonder if my mom was
out there listening, too.
You gotta be kidding!
Well, you have to
give her this much.
Ol' Mom was a real free spirit.
What?
Wait, so now you're not
even the PM's bastard kid?
Come on!
Guess not...
But... that's alright;
I know it'll be a lot less
trouble for Chigusa that way.
Sure... Nice.
But now, that terrorist
label is really gonna stick!
I mean, this was your only out.
Yeah, she's right!
The whole damn country's
gonna be after your head now.
You gotta point there...
And on that note.
Guess I'll be goin'.
What? Just like that?
So after everything
Saki went through
to get back to you.
Now you're just gonna take off?
Takizawa. Listen, I...
I'm sorry. I have to go...
I remembered that
there's one last thing
I really have to do before
I can call this game over.
If you can wait, once
I've got that out of the way,
I promise I'll come back to you.
See ya'.
Oh, and Hirasawa,
Panties, and Kasuga...
tell all of them
I said thanks, too!
You'd better come back, okay?
You promised me.
I did. And I definitely will.
So far...
that morning was the last we'd
seen or heard of Takizawa.
Apparently... after he
made his terrorist threat...
the Seleção game ended,
which meant his
request to become king
was canceled as well.
As far as the
public was concerned,
he vanished just as
suddenly as he'd appeared.
But still...
there were more
than a few people
who would have been happy
to see him crowned all the same.
Like Chigusa.
Takizawa and the Prime Minister
weren't related by blood.
but in the course of her short
yet intense
involvement with him...
she sensed the same
fire in his blood
that had burned
in her husband's.
And Aya...
After her tacit admission
that Takizawa was her son...
she ran off again...
but this time, she remembered
to bring her mini Shiba.
I think she must
have circumstances
she can't tell anyone about,
but it's clear she intends
to keep the secrets of
Takizawa's birth for life.
As for the NEETs that
answered Takizawa's call.
they joined the
AKX20000 in the mall--
which is basically revered as
a holy land at this point--
and started living
a communal life,
supported by a
perpetual flea market.
Unfortunately.
Takizawa never came to
take them all to paradise.
but even though they're
furious at the Air King,
at the same time,
they're eagerly awaiting
his second coming.
And then, of course,
there were the old guys
who'd been given the ultimatum.
At first, some companies
came for the NEETs,
in accordance with
Takizawa's demands,
and announced that they'd
be taking a fresh look
at their hiring practices,
but that didn't last long.
Even so, the thousands of NEETs
who installed
themselves in Toyosu
and made it their
"Paradise" started creating
their own economic
opportunities,
and are now helping Japan
recover little by little.
Last but not least,
if you're wondering
what happened to us...
well... the bad publicity
we got as a 'terrorist site'
was too much to overcome,
so Eden closed its doors as
a company for the time being.
Since then, at Hirasawa
and Itazu's suggestion,
we've relocated to
Toyosu and joined
in the NEETs communal lifestyle,
where we've been
working to develop
an even more user-friendly
system for the future.
It's been six
months since that day
and as far as I can tell,...
Japan doesn't seem to
have changed all that much
on the surface.
But underneath...
maybe just out of sight...
it feels like some real
change is on the way.
I believe that it is.
And wherever he may be,
out there dashing around
the city on his own,...
I know that Takizawa still
believes the same thing...
...and I know that
he's still carrying
all of our hopes and
dreams on his shoulders.
A question for you.
If a stranger handed
you ten billion yen
then said "improve
this country"...
What would you do?
How would you answer him?
Sounds like you're still
up to your old tricks.
I finally found you.
Hello, Mister Outside.
I'm sorry... but who are you?
What? No...
Don't you dare go
senile on me now.
You said if I won,
then I'd automatically
get to see you face to face.
You could at least
keep your promises!
Well... I feel better.
So let's just say that
makes us even, alright?
Alright... Then as long
as we're startin' over,
I've got a lot of favors
to ask you, old man.
For starters, could you take
a right up at the
next intersection?
And step on it.
We still have a hell of a
lot more work we gotta do--
so no time for
this senile stuff!
Keep it together, I mean it.
This is the story
of Takizawa and me.
The story of just eleven days.