[NARRATOR:] It was a time
when humanity set out
into space in search
of new worlds.
This era was given the name:
Universal Century.
Clusters of massive
space colonies
were constructed
around the Earth,
where the future of
humanity now resided.
However, these second homes
were not the paradises
the people were promised.
Universal Century 0057
In Side 3, the cluster
furthest from Earth,
a leader appeared
who called for
Spacenoid independence
and the reformation of
the human race.
His name was Zeon Zum Deikun.
Universal Century 0068.
Just as Deikun began his speech,
he suddenly collapsed.
His death lead to
speculation of foul play.
Even within his own camp,
simmering tensions erupted
into factional infighting.
Degwin Zabi, a
longtime supporter
and right‐hand man of Deikun,
did not let this
opportunity pass him by.
The Zabis toppled their
rival faction,
the Ral family,
and seized power in Munzo.
Deikun's wife, Astraia,
was placed under house arrest,
alone in a tower.
As for his children,
Casval and Artesia...
My enemy, your enemy,
even Mother's,
everyone's enemy!
And I’m gonna take them out!
[NARRATOR:] The children
narrowly escaped to Earth
accompanied by Jimba Ral,
the head of the Ral family.
Three years later...
Artesia changed her
name to Sayla,
and Casval became Édouard.
The two of them were adopted
by the wealthy Teabolo Mass.
However, they were targeted
by Zabi assassins.
And Jimba Ral was killed.
Teabolo was gravely injured.
Heeding the advice of
Shu Yashima,
head of the Yashima Company,
Teabolo decided to move
to Texas Colony,
located in Side 5, also
known as Loum.
He had no idea a
fateful encounter
awaited them there.
Hi, I’m Edouard Mass.
And I'm Char Aznable!
Meanwhile, as Sayla was waiting
to be reunited with her mother,
she received some terrible news.
She’s dead...
[NARRATOR:] Her mother
Astraia had died.
No!
Édouard then bade
farewell to Sayla.
[CASVAL:] Artesia.
I’m leaving, so I won’t see
you for a while.
Goodbye, Artesia.
I beg you, please!
You can’t leave me, brother!
Casval!
Don’t go!
[NARRATOR:] Casval set
out on a new path.
And this...
was his first step
towards vengeance.
Universal Century 0074.
Édouard, secretly switched
places with Char.
He then entered
the Autonomous
Republic of Zeon's
military academy in his place..
Also at the academy
was Garma Zabi,
the Zabi heir.
I pledge...
Dorm 1, Garma Zabi!
Cozy, huh?
Think of it as your palace.
[NARRATOR:] It was at that time
when Char and Garma
forged a fateful bond.
Meanwhile, with the assistance
of the scientific genius Dr.
Minovsky,
Dozle Zabi advanced the
development of the mobile suit:
a new weapon he had
been working on.
But an unexpected accident
changed the political landscape.
The citizens rose up,
demanding independence.
[GARMA:] Attack the
Federation’s barracks?
[NARRATOR:] They could no
longer tolerate
oppression by the
Federation Forces.
And Char manipulated Garma
into inciting the academy's
cadets to take up arms.
It was to protect the lives,
the rights, and property
of Spacenoids!
All right! Then let’s move out!
However, there was
one cadet there
that managed to see through
Char's disguise.
His name was Lino Fernandez,
a fellow native of Loum.
Thank you very much, Lino.
[NARRATOR:] But
during the battle,
Char found a way to
silence Lino,
who had already pledged
loyalty to him.
[LINO:] Casval, call them off!
Fire!
[LINO:] Stop it! Don’t
do this Casval!
[NARRATOR:] Universal
Century 0077.
Under the command of Garma Zabi,
the uprising of some 200 cadets
forced the E. F. F.
security forces
to lay down arms.
This incident,
which later would be known as
the Dawn Rebellion,
was the event that
marked the beginning
of the One Year War,
the greatest tragedy in
human history.
As the military drama unfolded,
at Side 7,
which housed a secret
Federation facility...
Amuro Ray, I’m 13 years old!
[NARRATOR:] Tem Ray was also
conducting mobile suit
development research of his own.
This is it...this is Side 7...
MOBILE SUIT GUNDAM THE ORIGIN IV
[NEWSCASTER:] We’re at the
tickertape parade
for the Guardian Banchi heroes!
We honor these mere 200
academy cadets
who bravely took on the
Federation Forces,
and foiled the security
operation scheme!
And here comes the leader of
this Dawn Rebellion,
none other than our very
own Garma Zabi!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Oh, it looks like Cadet Garma
is waving to the crowd!
Following in the
cars behind him,
we have the photos of
those cadets
who fell in the battle.
They are proud
portraits of youths
who gave their lives for
their homeland!
What's the meaning of this?!
I demand an explanation!
These boys are criminals!
The Federation demands every one
of them be punished
and that the ringleader be
handed over immediately!
This so‐called ringleader is
my younger brother.
You expect me to hand him over?
I don't care one iota
about who he is!
Thank you, I’ve already
been briefed.
Vice Admiral Revil.
Firstly, allow me to
express my condolences
for the losses suffered by
you and your men.
Disciplinary actions will
be administered.
However, perhaps there
is someone else
we might discover
who is more appropriate
than young Garma
that can satisfy your
sense of justice.
The Republic of
Zeon's sole concern
is to avoid incidents of this
nature in the future.
I’d like to use this as
an opportunity.
Our chance to forge
a new relationship with
the Federation.
However...
We do have a few conditions.
That the Federation relinquish
their assets here
and withdraw their forces.
What kind of idiot are you?
Why do you think I appointed you
as the superintendent
of the military academy?!
You had one purpose! One!
That was to protect Garma!
Now listen, you useless oaf!
[GARMA:] Excuse me...
Sorry about this.
Am I interrupting
something important?
Not at all, we’re finished here.
Garma, why don’t you
come see me in my chambers.
Should I be worried?
Father seems to be in a
really bad mood.
Maybe I shouldn’t have
taken such drastic measures.
Don’t worry about it, it’s fine.
You’ve done well.
Your actions prove you’re
a real Zabi man.
I guess it does, doesn’t it?
The important thing is you
weren't hurt, Garma.
You’re important to the nation.
You must take care of yourself.
Gihren, Dozle, and Kycilia
are all bloodthirsty by nature.
Alas, of all of them,
only you have a
gentle disposition.
I should have encouraged you
to take the path of a scholar.
Instead, I enrolled you at the
military academy.
Come here Garma.
Approach me.
I would like you to
come over here
by my side and take my hand.
What do you think?
Does my hand feel cold to you?
Not at all. It feels warm to me.
Very warm.
Is that so?
Your cheek is also equally warm.
Stay like this for a while,
my son.
You have my sympathies.
When one has reached
a certain age,
it’s not fair to have children.
[DOZLE:] We all know
very well that
you're the one who got Garma
into this whole mess.
So don't think you're
getting a raw deal
‘cause you’re being scapegoated.
Now then.
What have you got to
say for yourself?
Nothing! Nothing at all, sir!
A straight shooter.
All right...
What are your plans?
Tell me.
I’ve always dreamed of
visiting Earth one day.
And now is my chance.
Then you’re in luck, Cadet.
Thank you!
This is Private Char Aznable,
and I respectfully
take my leave!
I am in your debt, Colonel.
Take care. All the best.
Colonel, one more thing.
I do have a little favor to ask.
If for whatever reason
in the future
should I ever be called
into service,
I’d like very much
to be given the opportunity
to be trained as a
mobile suit pilot.
Did you say mobile suit?
Garma must’ve blabbed about it.
All right, fine.
I'll consider your reques!
My sincerest gratitude, sir.
[ZENNA:] Cadet Zenna Mia to
see Col. Dozle!
Just what do you two
think you’re doing?
Leave us and give us
the room now!
I trust you’re not packing
heat today, Cadet?
N‐No, sir!
I must resign my post here
as a result of your
little uprising.
And so I must fall on my sword,
it’s Harakiri.
I see, I’m sorry.
Even a big tough man
such as myself
is capable of being
hurt sometimes.
Yes sir.
There are times when
maybe I just want to be
comforted by someone, I think.
The truth is, I never considered
taking a wife before,
and I'm embarrassed to
confess... now I want to.
Will you... will you, Zenna Mia,
consider bearing my heirs?
[DOZLE GULPS]
Move! Let us through!
What do you mean, we can only
take what we can carry?
I won’t forget this!
You are going to pay,
do you hear?
[CHAOS]
Eve of Destiny
MANAUS
Agha! Take care of the
guys behind me!
[FOREMAN:] Hey kid!
That’s enough!
You can take a break!
Did you hear?
[FOREMAN:] I simply can’t stand
those bastards over at Zeonic.
They’re planning on
terminating the lease.
You think they’ll take
‘em away from us?
Sure do, things looking
pretty dicey out there.
[FOREMAN:] They say if
things don’t calm down,
we could be looking at a
war on the horizon.
Hey, new kid.
Where the hell did you learn
how to drive a mobile worker,
anyway?
From hanging around
the Zeonic bastards, where else?
I worked in their
R&amp;D department.
That is, until I got fired.
So I know, all right.
I have firsthand knowledge.
They’re bastards.
[FOREMAN:] There sure is a lot
of development around here.
Huh! They’ve even got a
casino now too!
No! I can’t believe it!
I lost again?!
Hey, uh, let's call it a night.
No, just one last spin!
Please! You gotta spot me,
okay?!
I'll pay you back next payday!
Someone help me!
[AGHA:] My master
wishes to play.
Stand aside, losers.
You’re sitting in our seats.
He won!
[FOREMAN:] On a straight‐up bet,
too!
That's a 36x payout!
Next game! Place your bets!
He’s placing another
straight‐up bet!
That’s it! No more bets!
[WHISPERING]
Shift change! Change dealers!
Hi!
Here we go!
Place your bets!
He lost!
[FOREMAN:] He lost again!
He lost big this time!
Is that it? His streak
over already?
Hey, hello there.
What're you doing, huh?
It looks like he really
let you have it.
Do I know you?
I was at the casino yesterday.
Why did you guys start
losing all of a sudden?
It was because the new dealer
was so bad at her job.
You should stay away from me.
Bad things always happen
to people who get too close.
Oh, is that so?
Your friends sounds scary.
What's in your hand?
[CHAR:] Is that your family?
It’s quite big.
So where are they all now?
Mumbai.
In India?
You're a long way from home.
Do you go back to visit?
I send them money the
money I make.
Having money is much
better for them
than having me around, anyway.
Your family photo’s
seen better days.
It became all warped
when I got it wet.
Do you think it’s possible to
fix something like that?
Sure it is.
All you do is scan it, touch up
the image, and reprint it.
Really?
Would you be able to
do that for me?
It's my only picture of them, so
it would the world to me!
[GAMBLER:] Lalah!
What are you doing?!
You know you’re not allowed to
speak to strangers!
I was just admiring your boat.
It must have cost you a pretty
penny, am I right?
So how did you get the money?
Answer me that, Mr.
Genius Gambler!
No! It’s those guys from Manaus!
[GAMBLER:] Agha! Agha!
Get in the car! It’s time to go!
[GAMBLER:] Damnit, damnit,
damnit!
We’re gonna pay for this!
I’m sorry kid, but we don't need
someone like him
bringing us trouble.
I didn’t invite the guy!
He just ended up tagging along.
I won't let those crass Manaus
mobsters get the better of me!
[WORKER:] Excuse me.
There’s someone here by
the name of Agha.
I think he wants to
speak with you.
Good, he’s arrived!
Agha! You’re safe and sound!
Thank god!
Master.
I’m resigning and joining
the Manaus gang.
I can’t be hearing
this correctly!
They made me a really generous
offer. And I couldn’t refuse.
After everything I’ve
done for you,
how dare you do this to me!
[GAMBLER:] You would
have nothing
if it weren’t for all the
things I’ve...
No, wait! I’m sorry!
I get it now!
I’ll pay you whatever you want,
okay?!
[CHAR:] Hold on.
Leave the girl and just go.
Which one would you
like to lose?
An arm perhaps?
Or how about your head?
Neither, thank you very much.
Please, no!
I can see you even in
the shadows!
You just got lucky.
You won’t be able to dodge this!
No one can!
[MAN OVER LOUDSPEAKER:]
Attention Jaburo
Construction Office!
Be good little boys
and do as I say!
We all know you’re hiding the
Indian girl in there.
Send her out!
What are we gonna do?
[MAN OVER LOUDSPEAKER:] She's
the one with a dot on
her forehead!
Should be easy to spot!
There’s no use trying to
keep her from us!
‐‐ [MAN OVER LOUDSPEAKER:] I'll
give you 3 minutes to hand her
over! ‐‐ [CHAR: Stand up.]
We’re going to make
a run for it.
Try to keep up.
Jaburo construction workers are
my most valued customers!
[MAN OVER
LOUDSPEAKER:] I don't want
to resort to violence any
more than you do.
Just hand over the girl,
and you’ll have nothing to
worry about. Promise.
Don’t worry, I have no intention
of laying a finger on her.
I’ll put her up in my casino and
treat her like royalty.
That’s it, time’s up!
Get in there, boys!
And kill anybody who
gets in your way!
What the hell is that thing?!
Lalah, that’s your name, right?
How do you explain what
happened back there?
What do you mean?
The weapon came from behind me,
so I couldn’t have seen it.
But I was able to sense it,
and dodged at the
very last moment.
You didn’t say anything to
warn me, did you?
I didn’t, no.
I see. Very strange.
I’m sorry about the mess,
Foreman.
But I'll have this back
before its lease is up.
Lalah, if it’s true that
you don’t care
about going back home,
why don’t we go
someplace really far?
Where? Like, how far a place?
America? Or Japan?
Actually, I meant
somewhere farther.
[CHAR:] Let’s go to the stars.
[GOPP:] Thanks to the reckless
behavior on the part of several
irresponsible individuals,
our relationship with Zeon has
markedly worsened.
[CHAIRMAN, E. F. F. JOINT
CHIEFS OF STAFF]
It looks like the world
is determined.
[ADMIRAL GOPP] To see
this to the end.
How is the RX‐78 Project going?
Is it proceeding smoothly?
Yes sir, of course!
I understand that you were
one of Dr. Minovsky's
star pupils,
is that correct?
Yes, sir.
This footage you’re about to see
is from Dr. Minovsky.
It was leaked to us
through the back
channels we have.
I would like for you to give us
your honest opinion on it.
MS‐04 test flight?
Apparently, they’re calling
these things “mobile suits.”
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT:] We will be
docking at Side 7 momentarily.
Please remain in your seats.
[MR. RAY:] Area A Baoa Qu...
[GOPP:] We're unfamiliar
with that zone.
These must be similar to those
machines called
“mobile workers.”
We have those things at
our Jaburo
construction site too—
You’re wrong!
This is something
totally different.
It's evolved now.
And it’s become something
else entirely.
This must be A Baoa Qu.
[GOPP:] An asteroid
they're mining
for its mineral resources.
A mobile suit is equipped
with a shield and a weapon.
This footage that you’re seeing
right now is combat mode.
[MR. RAY:] 100mm
projectile rounds!?
[GOPP:] That's on par with a
tank cannon, right?
That's a freighter.
Arcana‐class, I believe.
They’re just doing
that to show off.
It'll take more than
100mm rounds
to take down one of our ships.
And besides, we have our
newly‐developed main
battle tank,
the RCX‐76 Guncannon,
which as we all know has bigger—
You’re wrong!
Dr. Minovsky succeeded...
He’s finally actually
made it happen!
Admiral Gopp!
Did you not just inform us
that you received this footage
through your back
channel connections
with Dr. Minovsky?
Let's continue this outside,
shall we?
Defecting?!
Dr. Minovsky is?
The reason for that is,
the good Doctor’s been poached.
Anaheim Electronics have
stolen him from Zeonic.
I need you to do
something for me.
Go to the Moon.
T‐To the Moon? Me?
The Doctor will be
heading from Granada,
where the Zeonic
factory is located.
From there, he will travel
all the way to Von Braun.
And I was hoping you could
assist with things.
I had heard Dr. Minovsky would
be a valuable asset,
but I wasn’t quite certain
just how valuable.
That’s why I wanted your honest
opinion about the footage.
I regret having to send you on
another long trip
after you just arrived from
a distant colony.
Don't you find it fascinating,
though, Chief Ray?
From here in Brasilia, you
can’t see Jaburo,
since it’s too far
up the Amazon.
But the Moon is plainly visible
even though it's much
farther away.
The more distance we cover,
the more we realize that space
is smaller than we
knew it to be.
[GOPP:] If Dr. Minovsky ends up
taking a leadership position,
you might find that your
project at Side 7
is positioned to make even
greater advancements.
There you go!
[FRAW:] You better eat, okay?
Bye, then!
See you tomorrow!
Make sure you get up early!
Don't be late for school!
Bye‐bye, Haro.
Bye‐bye, Fraw.
You must be Amuro's father,
right?
It's nice to meet you.
And you are?
I’m a classmate of Amuro’s.
My name is Fraw Bow.
And I live in the neighborhood.
Oh, is that right.
I’ve heard that your work
usually keeps you
extremely busy.
However, I think it’s
starting to affect Amuro.
It’s just that he’s
always alone.
And so...I feel real
bad for him.
Maybe you could try talking to
him a little bit more?
Sorry. I’m being nosy.
I gotta go, see you around!
Amuro! I'm back from work!
It's always such a
pigsty in here!
Oh hey, welcome back Dad.
Would it kill you to
clean up a bit?
This place is filthy!
Anyway, I have to pack.
[MR. RAY:] I’m going to the Moon
on another business trip.
I’m doing very important work.
[HARO:] You hurt Haro. Ow.
Go make me some coffee, okay?
[AMURO:] Okay.
I'm going to be even
busier from now on.
Which means you have to—
[MR. RAY:] Amuro!
Will you put some pants on?!
Don't be such a slob!
[AMURO:] Y‐Yes, Dad!
[MR. RAY:] I can’t believe
you had a girl over
when you were dressed like that!
Seriously.
No matter what, that boy just
refuses to grow up.
LUNAR CITY GRANADA
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT:] Ladies and
gentlemen, welcome to Granada.
[OTHER MAN:] It looks like we’ve
finally arrived, Doctor.
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT:] Please
remain seated until we
have fully berthed.
It shouldn’t be much longer now.
[BERGMANN:] We are here,
your Excellency.
Why don’t we get off, Catherine?
Yes, let’s. Thank you,
Major Bergmann.
[BERGMANN:] I'm been told that
Dr. Minovsky is planning
to head straight to Zeonic
from the spaceport.
Will we be proceeding
with the plan,
Your Excellency?
“Catherine, shall we go
ahead with our plans?”
Of course. Shall we go ahead
with our plans, Catherine?
Yeah, sounds good.
[PILOT #1:] Damn, it’s dark.
[RAMBA:] Yup. The far side of
the Moon is pitch black.
At night, anyway.
[PILOT #1:] This is
taking forever!
[RAMBA:] No jumping.
You'll just kick up dust.
There’s no rush.
Be patient. Walk slowly.
We just need to reach the edge
of Mare Smythii within 12 hours.
[PILOT #1:] I assume
there’ll be some place
to take a break between then
and now, Captain?
[RAMBA:] You won’t find a
five‐star hotel,
but our red friend
went up ahead.
He’ll be waiting for us
with some coffee.
That guy!?
[PILOT #2:] I really can't
stand that jerk!
They say he hardly has
any training!
And they just went and made
him an MS pilot!
I hear he got kicked out of
the military academy
and even has a criminal record!
I can just imagine him sucking
up to Col. Dozle, can’t you?
Bet he’s a smooth talker.
[RAMBA:] I wouldn't know about
that, but he's
definitely got talent.
Good lord!
You aren’t turning into a
softie, are you Captain?
Gaia, make those two shut up,
will ya?
[GAIA:] Afraid you'll just have
to grin and bear it.
Once those guys are worked up,
there’s nothing I can do.
Cut ‘em some slack, though.
They’re just pumped
about getting to be
in the first mobile
suit battle ever!
[AGENT:] Dr. Minovsky has
already left for the
industrial zone.
He’s slightly ahead of the
projected schedule.
It looks like our leak
did the trick.
Your excellency!
The Doctor, he’s already
Sorry, forgive me! I meant...
Catherine...
Now, if you'd be so kind as to
escort me, Major?
I'd be honored to,
Missus Catherine.
But...may I have permission to
ask you a question first?
What would you like to know?
This thing?
Could I...
I mean, would you mind if
I wiped it off?
You may do whatever you like,
Mr. Bergmann.
[VALET:] Have a pleasant
evening, Madam.
[DRIVER:] You two off for a
night on the town in Granada?
[CATHERINE:] That's right. We’re
curious about the nightlife.
Just take us to a club
with a nice vibe.
LUNAR CITY VON BRAUN
[EXECUTIVE:] You can't do that!
Do you know how much trouble
that would cause us?
That’s unacceptable!
I hate to tell you this after
coming all the way from Side 7,
but there’s nothing I
can do for you!
[EXECUTIVE:] L‐Look, I've
heard all the rumors.
I already know about Dr.
Minovsky defecting.
I also know he’s planning
on coming here.
But I ask you: what
did you hope to
accomplish by coming here
at the 11th hour?!
Wait a sec!
Admiral Gopp told me personally
that Anaheim had poached him!
Yeah, yeah, I know, I know.
But that’s the head
office’s doing.
The truth is, they have no clue
how things work here.
Our RCX‐76 Project is coming
along just fine, thank you!
Alright, fine! I’ll let you
see for yourself!
I’ll take you to visit our
latest production line.
You see that?
Those completed units,
ready to go and already
rolling off the line!
We've already started making
deliveries to the military.
And they’re passing all the
tests with flying colors.
I know for a fact that
over at Zeonic,
their MS‐04 is over budget,
so now they're
developing the MS‐05,
which actually has lower specs.
Don’t look so surprised: I
know everything!
Just like I also know
that your own RX‐78
is starting to fall
behind schedule.
I guess it doesn’t matter,
though.
There won’t be a need for the
RX‐78 anytime soon.
Oh, I know!
Why don't you keep Dr.
Minovsky occupied?
He's your mentor, right?
And besides, I’m sure
you can find
plenty of things to
ask him about.
Give the Doctor a warm welcome,
okay?
[MR. RAY:] This isn't it.
This isn't what Dr. Minovsky
called a mobile suit!
This isn't it!
This is not a mobile suit!
C’mon.
[AGENT:] Von Braun,
do you read me?
Von Braun, come in!
This is TYM!
We’ve entered the next
phase of the plan.
Be prepared to
receive the cargo.
[AGENT:] We’ve left
Granada proper.
We’re proceeding
westwards on Route 1!
ETA to Abul Wafa is 10 hours.
[SOLDIER:] Everything is going
according to plan.
The Doctor is currently at
this location, here.
He still has a long way to go.
Ready the welcoming party.
[SOLDIER #2:] Heat sources
detected in Mare Smythii!
I’m guessing it’s probably those
new Zeon humanoid weapons!
Are you telling me they
have those things
on the Moon now?
How many of them?
I think there are four, sir.
They only have four of
those guys, huh?
Dispatch the Iron
Cavalry Squadron!
[SOLDIER:] The squadron?
All of them?
That's right.
Normally, I wouldn't
normally choose
a sledgehammer to
swat a mere fly,
but this first
engagement is critical.
[MR. RAY:] Commander!
I would like to be sent out
to the battle site.
I want to see these Guncannons
in action with my own two eyes.
So Zeon is deploying their
mobile suits...
[SOLDIER:] Sending the
weapon to stop the man
who created said weapon.
How ironic.
[LOUDSPEAKER:] Emergency
mobilization alert.
Emergency mobilization alert.
Iron Cavalry Squadron,
prepare to mobilize.
Emergency mobilization alert.
Iron Cavalry Squadron,
prepare to mobilize.
[PILOT:] Erdush, launch
preparations complete!
[CLUB MUSIC]
The Federation forces at Von
Braun have mobilized.
They've even sent out their
prized Iron Cavalry Squadron.
Well, well.
This is going to be a night
we’ll never forget!
So this is twilight on the Moon.
[GAIA:] Hey Red, you jerk!
You weren’t at the
rendezvous point!
And why aren't you
sending out a beacon?
Sorry, you don’t
seriously want me
to answer that question, do you?
Damn straight I do!
And where does a private get off
speaking to me like that,
anyway?!
Alright, I’ll answer you.
A beacon would be seen
by the enemy.
Besides, you still managed to
locate me without one.
Didn’t you, Warrant Officer?
[RAMBA:] That’s enough,
both of you!
The rabbit's about to
enter the trap.
It's about time!
Let’s go rabbit hunting!
No one shoot, got that?
We’re just stopping the vehicle.
[AGENT:] TYM here!
We’re being ambushed by a
group of mobile suits!
Send help, now!
[PILOT:] Copy that!
We’re sending you some
assistance now!
See if you can make your way to
outside of the
Granada‐controlled sector!
[RAMBA:] It makes no sense!
Doctor, what are you doing?
We developed these very mobile
suits together, Doctor!
Doctor, wait! This is Capt.
Ral speaking!
I can guarantee your safety!
Just come back with me!
We're not going to make it!
We’re going to be fine!
The Federation is sending
assistance as we speak!
We can’t outrun them!
Don't shoot, Gaia! Not yet!
You're wasting our time,
Captain!
This is the perfect chance
to finish him off!
[FEDERATION PILOT:] Single red
mobile suit spotted.
Four more up ahead.
We’ve also located the
Doctor’s vehicle.
Five? I thought the report
said there were four!
Take them all out!
[ZEON PILOT:] Son of a...
That bastard started without
receiving the order!
Captain didn’t say I
couldn’t shoot you guys!
The enemy forces have engaged!
Copy that.
Squadron! All units, drop now!
[PILOT:] Our objective is to
protect the Doctor's car!
Here’s the play:
surround the enemy
and then take them out!
[AGENTS:] They're here!
They're here!
Don’t worry, the Federation
mobile suit forces have arrived.
They’re here to save us, Doctor.
Targets: 01 through 04!
Range, 400!
Fire!
Your ass is mine!
Good work, men!
Show those Federation scumbags
what real mobile suits can do!
No you don't!
You’re not getting
away that easily!
[PILOT:] I’m sorry, but
we can't, sir!
It’s too dangerous!
I’m not putting us in the
middle of a fight!
Don’t be an idiot! What the hell
do you think we came
all this way for?
[MR. RAY:] Do not take your eyes
off those sensors, got that?
I can't believe they've
advanced so far...
[SOLDIER:] Oh, no!
They’re gonna get
slaughtered at this rate!
Recall mobile suits!
All remaining forces, retreat!
[GAIA:] These aren’t
mobile suits!
These are playthings!
What the hell?
Let me guess, that’s the
handiwork of Red again?
Way to hog all the fun, you
smarmy bastard!
Another sucker bites the dust!
No...it can’t be...
[SHUTTLE PILOT:] We’re
overwhelmed with
multiple heat sources!
Our infrared sensors are
not functioning!
That’s Dr. Minovsky!
No, wait! Let that one go, Gaia!
That’s an order!
No, don't do it!
I'm afraid that I must refuse.
Granada is a neutral territory.
And as such, we cannot side
with Zeon and take
part in your war.
And as we are fellow
lunar cities,
we’ve maintained a cordial
relationship with Von Braun
for a number of years.
I cannot participate
in something
predicated on betraying
that relationship.
Someone like you can surely
understand that.
Just a moment.
I see. A job well done.
Please give Capt.
Ral my regards.
Mr. Mayor. There’s been an
interesting development.
My men have wiped out a
squadron‐sized Federation
force at Mare Smythii.
I’ll let that sink in a bit.
For this is the kind of power
that Zeon already possesses.
That can’t be possible!
We must confirm this with
Prime Minister Gihren!
That’s Supreme Commander Gihren!
Zeon is no longer a republic,
it’s a principality.
My father will name himself
as its sovereign,
and he’ll declare our
independence any time now!
Maybe, but I can’t
take your word.
I must confirm it myself.
Be careful on your way home.
Granada can be a very
dangerous place.
Tell me, Bergmann.
How do you suppose that the
Mayor knew about the war?
I made a request that we
merely be allowed
to place a garrison
force at Granada
equal in size to one that
the Federation has.
I didn't say anything
about using it
as a launching point to
attack Von Braun!
Uh...all I did was...
[SILENCED GUNSHOTS]
A secret agency has no need
for blabbermouths.
F‐Forgive me, Missus
Catherine...
Pathetic fool.
We can finally drop the charade.
[MR RAY:] Our company must adopt
new policies without delay!
The entirety of the RCX‐76
squadron that we delivered
was completely annihilated by a
mere five mobile suits!
That makes the score 12 to 0!
A complete shutout!
You speak as if you aren’t even
a part of the project.
You're as much to blame
as anyone else!
He's right!
How dare you point the
finger at us!
I admit...
The blame certainly does
lie partly with me.
Let me officially take full
responsibility.
Please, I need your help.
Help me to advance the RX
Project into the next phase!
You’re just in this for your
own self‐interest!
You don’t belong here!
If you’d like me to leave,
I will. Gladly.
However, what will
become of your
mobile suit development
program after this?
It will be dead in the water!
Which means you will be
forfeiting the game to Zeonic!
Dr. Minovsky decided to defect.
He sacrificed everything for the
chance to work with us!
And in the end, he
sacrificed his own life!
I was there when it happened,
but there wasn’t
anything I could do!
But we can carry on his work!
That is easier said than done...
I can certainly sympathize you,
however—
There’s no need for concern.
The project has been
coming along nicely.
In fact, it’s almost complete.
Allow me to prove it to you!
I will show you our
definitive plan!
Behold!
I present the RX‐78!
Codename: Gundam !
Is Dad back?
I didn’t expect him to
be home so soon.
Sorry about that!
[HARO:] Ouch. Ouch.
I guess he forgot to lock it.
Don't go in, Amuro.
He'll get mad.
He'll get mad. Stop!
Don't go in!
[NARRATOR:] Universal Century
0078, October 24th.
The Republic of Zeon ratifies
its transformation into
a principality.
Concurrently, it declares its
independence from the
Earth Federation.
Sieg Zeon!
Sieg Zeon! Sieg Zeon!
EARTH FEDERATION
FORCES GENERAL HQ
[GOPP:] Revil. Do you think
it's finally time
to carry out the
relocation to Jaburo?
Yes, I think it is.
Gihren Zabi is a man who
will stop at nothing
to get what he wants.
Who knows how this will
all turn out?
To think that war is
upon us again,
and in this brand new era, too.
[REPORTER:] We're coming to you
live in front of the Zeon
Diet building.
Today marks the first official
day after the Zeon independence.
Bye, see you tonight!
Be careful out there.
And no taking shortcuts through
construction sites!
I won't!
[TEACHER:] And so for
that reason,
the end of the A. D. century
was largely filled
with high poverty rates
and conflict...
Mr. Amuro!
Amuro!
Wake up!
Welcome home, Dad!
[FRAW:] Amuro, wait up!
Wanna head home together?
You, uh, seem really
exhausted lately.
Have you been pulling
all‐nighters or something?
Did you remember to eat your
dinner last night?
I ate it, okay?
Oh? Well, that’s good, I guess.
[KAI:] Woah, it’s the
conduct police!
Are you planning on giving Amuro
a yellow card, too?
[IMITATING FRAW:] “Keeping late
hours is a no‐no!”
“Falling asleep in class
is also a no‐no!”
“Flirting with monitors is
the biggest no‐no!”
You will regret this!
Shut the hell up!
Oo, scary!
Let her give your conduct a good
monitoring, Amuro!
Jerks! It’s best to
just not associate
with those kinds of boys!
That Kai is the worst of them!
He's been held back a year!
Are you okay, Amuro?
I just have something I have
to take care of.
I’ll see you later!
But, Amuro!
Oh yeah!
Have you made plans for
Christmas yet?
Huh?
You'll be alone, right?
I can bake a cake and bring
it over for you!
It'll be delicious, okay!
[REPORTER:] The Zeon government
has refused to apologize
for the recent
hostile engagement on the
lunar surface.
As a result, all talks have
since broken down.
Is it good, Amuro? Is it good?
Fraw is nice?
Haro likes Fraw. Likes, likes!
I love Fraw!
Shut up!
If you don’t cut it out, I’m
gonna yank out your battery!
More military mumbo‐jumbo...
These don’t look anything like
colony construction documents...
Alright, Dad...
What are you up to right now?
[REPORTER:] Vice Admiral Revil,
E.F.S.F. Supreme Commander,
recently said the following
in an interview:
I won't abandon the hope
of averting war.
The reason being that this war
will almost certainly
result in a disaster
worse than any other war mankind
has ever experienced.
U.C. 0079 JANUARY 3RD
PRINCIPALITY OF ZEON DECLARES
WAR AGAINST EARTH FEDERATION
SAME DAY DOZLE FLEET DESTROYS
E. F. S. F. CRUISER FLEET
SAME DAY MAJOR GENERAL KYCILIA'S
ASSAULT FORCE OCCUPIES GRANADA
AND THEN MAIN FORCE
ATTACKS VON BRAUN
[REPORTER:] The
Principality of Zeon
and the Federation are now
officially at war!
From what we've been
able to confirm,
the lunar city of Granada...
This has already turned out
to be a fine mess.
Where are you going now?
Just to a friend’s place.
Promised I’d stop by.
Hey, wait!
Now’s not the time to
be going out!
[FRAW:] Amuro! You decent?
I'm coming in!
Welcome, Fraw.
Please enjoy your stay.
You sure are clever, aren’t you?
Please pardon the mess.
[REPORTER:] Fighting continues
to rage on in the
Von Braun area.
The Federation government is
calling on all colonies to—
Amuro, are you going
to come down?
The lasagna I brought over is
going to get cold!
Why do you have to be
such a jerk?!
All you ever do is just sit in
front of that that computer!
Do you even realize there’s
a war going on?!
And tons of people are dying,
and you just sit there!
[FRAW CRYING]
I'm sorry.
I’m looking forward to
it... your lasagna...
Don’t you worry.
I’m gonna eat it.
It may seem like I don’t care.
But truth is, I’m scared
about the war.
However, there’s nothing I
can do about it.
There’s nothing I can do
anything about, really.
I’m really sorry.
[CHAR:] Lalah, what are you
doing right now?
[LALAH:] I’m gazing up
at the stars.
I love the way they twinkle.
It’s so pretty.
[CHAR:] The stars don't actually
twinkle here in space.
What, is that true?
Do me a favor and sit tight.
I'll be back as soon as I'm done
with this job, okay?
[VOCAL SINGING IN JAPANESE]