[NARRATOR:] It was a time
when humanity set out
into space in search
of new lands.
And they gave that time
the name: Universal Century.
Humanity entrusted their future
to gigantic space colonies
that had been constructed
around the Earth.
However, this second homeland
was a far cry from the paradise
they had been promised.
Universal Century 0057
In Side 3, the cluster
furthest from Earth,
there appeared a leader
who called for
Spacenoid independence
and the reformation of
the human race.
This man's name was
Zeon Zum Deikun.
It appeared to the people
that the Earth Sphere
would advance even further
under his leadership.
But instead, this was merely the
beginning of a thorny path
that would lead to a war
more tragic than any prior
in human history.
At Side 3, also known as Munzo,
Deikun founded an
independent government
and managed to convince the
Earth Federation Government
to grant them
conditional autonomy.
However, Deikun's struggle
to expand that autonomy
and his quest for an
eventual independence
was met with a harsh crackdown
by the Earth Federation Forces.
U.C. 0068.
Deikun stood before
the Munzo Diet
to deliver what would be an
historic address.
He was going to demand the
withdrawal of the EFF’s
garrison force
and issue a de facto
declaration of independence.
However...
Just as he was about to begin
his speech, Deikun collapsed.
Deikun's sudden death led to
rumors of foul play.
We want freedom!
The people believed the
Federation
assassinated Zeon Deikun.
And even from within
the Deikun camp,
long‐held tensions suddenly
erupted into
factional infighting.
Degwin Zabi, a longtime
supporter of Deikun,
known for being his
right‐hand man,
did not let such an
opportunity pass him by.
Which one of you is
responsible for this?!
He and his faction
defeated the rival Ral family,
who had been harboring
Deikun’s next of kin,
and for all intents
and purposes,
he seized power in Munzo.
Deikun's widow, Astraia, was
locked in a tower
by Deikun’s first wife.
However, her children, Casval
and Artesia along
with Jimba Ral,
with the help of Munzo Defence
Force Captain Ramba Ral
and his partner‐in‐crime
Crowley Hamon,
managed to sneak
aboard a shuttle
and narrowly escape to Earth.
My enemy, your enemy,
even Mother's, everyone's enemy!
And I’m gonna take them out!
The two young children
suddenly found themselves
facing a vast, unfamiliar world
as well as a cruel fate.
A fate that would utterly
transform their persons,
especially that of Casval,
who would learn of the dark
struggles that burden adults.
It was this that would transform
him into the Red Comet.
Into Char Aznable.
MOBILE SUIT GUNDAM THE ORIGIN II
Andalusia, Spain
[VILLAGER] Miss, you aren’t from
around here, are you?
You're ten?
I never would have guessed.
You're awfully mature for ten.
Thank you for your help.
I bet you'll make a
wonderful doctor someday.
What? You really
live over there?
Well, that sure is a surprise!
[VILLAGER:] Why, that means
you’re a princess!
Artesia's Sorrow
[TEABOLO:] Do you suppose the
influx of refugees
will slow down any time soon?
[WOMAN:] I highly doubt it.
The camps get more
crowded every day.
Algiers and Marrakesh have both
been swallowed by sand.
And now reports say North Africa
is no longer fit for
human habitation.
We needed more radical
and comprehensive
policies to combat
climate change.
Father!
I'm back!
Stop, Miss Sayla! Hold on!
You must disinfect
yourself first thing
after returning from the camp!
Is that the girl I've
heard so much about?
It is.
Oh, my!
You could’ve fooled me!
We do pass for father and
daughter, don’t we?
To be quite honest, I wasn't
keen on the idea at first.
Even if it was for an old
friend of mine,
I don’t need to risk
getting pulled
into a space colony political
struggle that has nothing
to do with me.
But for the first time, I
understand what it’s like,
the happiness that comes
with having a family.
My goodness! Aren't you going to
take a shower, young lady?
[ARTESIA:] I don't need to!
I'll just rinse off in the pool!
[MAID:] Be careful!
Stop running!
[MR. RAL:] Mr. Casval! Focus,
we’re not done!
This is the most important
part of the lesson!
When he had the realization of
the historic duty of Spacenoids
and turned mankind’s
reformation into an ideology,
that was the moment when the
grand concept of
Newtypes was born!
In every age, prophets have
been solitary figures.
Even Deikun's ideology was not
readily accepted by
the people...
Are you listening to me?!
Master Casval!
Of course.
Then let us continue.
Only after humankind has
gone into space
where they can see the Earth as
a single living organism
that a time of evolution
finally arrived!
These Newtypes will not only
transcend imperfect human
communication,
but they will achieve true
mutual understanding,
and gain new physical
possibilities,
to become this world’s
most eminent...
[ARTESIA:] What's wrong with me?
Your land will go to good use,
Don Teabolo.
Please, think nothing of it.
It's an honor to be able to be
of service, High Commissioner.
I ask only that public
safety and sanitation
is carefully monitored.
[MR. RAL:] Which
brings us to now!
Munzo is trying to rebrand
itself by calling itself Zeon!
The audacity!
Spearheaded by those Zabi swine,
who were responsible for the
murder of Zeon Deikun!
There’s no doubt in my mind that
your father was
clearly poisoned!
They gave him small doses of
poison over time to weaken his
heart, until finally he —
Come in, Miss Artesia! You have
such perfect timing!
I’ve already heard the
poison story.
Edouard, I don’t feel good.
What? Do you think
you’re getting sick?
You have a fever.
There’s a chance it's
just a cold.
You should take some
medicine and go to bed.
Master Casval! We need to
schedule your next lesson!
His name is Edouard now!
And you should really start
calling me Sayla Mass!
Boy, oh boy.
Being able to watch little ones
grow up is a blessing,
however, at the same time...
Hm? What is it?
I beg your pardon, but you
have a visitor, sir.
Oh! He's here!
[TEABOLO:] I won't allow you to
do these kinds of things
behind my back!
A Welfare Department official?
Don't lie to me!
That was Anaheim's executive VP,
Chelsea!
That man used to be my
business rival!
I could pick his face
out of a lineup!
Now that we’re clear,
we can talk about this further,
back in my office.
Start talking.
What exactly was it you were
discussing with them?
F‐Forgive me!
Let me guess, you're planning a
counteroffensive against Side 3?
You dare do such a thing
without informing me?!
I won't allow it! Besides, it
doesn't have a chance in
hell of succeeding!
But...if we don’t try,
we’ll never know!
And Anaheim reassured me that
they will give us
their full backing! Weapons!
Funding!
And also, they even say
they'll start lobbying
key Federation figures
on our behalf!
How can we not succeed with
that type of support?
Besides, we have something
else on our side...
Go on, I’m curious to know.
On our side, we have...the
children of Deikun!
We have all the pieces to
bring down the Zabis!
It couldn’t be more perfect!
Deikun’s heirs will be
their downfall!
The Zabis' power is flimsy!
In contrast, Deikun's influence
shines more brightly than
ever in his absence!
And when everyone sees
the fine youths
that Casval and Artesia
have grown into,
they won’t be able to resist
flocking to our side!
Edouard and Sayla are
my children.
Those children are legally
members of the Mass family
because you said they would
never survive otherwise.
Surely you realize that was only
a temporary arrangement!
You are going too far!
I'll never let you claim
Deikun’s heirs as your own!
If that's how you feel, then
plan your schemes
somewhere else!
You are no longer welcome here!
But if you are so determined,
and only if the children
agree to go with you,
then I will renounce all
parental rights
and I will pretend the last
three years never happened.
What you’re asking me to do is a
great sacrifice on my part.
But that is insignificant
compared to what Edouard and
Sayla will have to endure
if they decide to risk their
lives for such conflict.
Don’t be like this!
I’m sorry I got carried away!
I need your help! You're the
only person I can rely on!
I gave into temptation!
I was blinded by the support of
a massive corporation
like Anaheim,
And I thought they’d
guarantee our success!
[TEABOLO:] The only thing
they can guarantee
is that they’d be making
money off of you.
They couldn't care less about
Zeon, the Zabis, or your people.
That's just how a
military‐industrial conglomerate
like Anaheim operates.
[MR. RAL:] That may be so.
But I couldn’t help it!
I wanted so desperately to
believe the things they said!
I can't stand the Zabis
calling themselves Zeon!
I was hoping this would be
my last chance!
To fulfill my dream!
Are you going to deny
me even that?!
If you take away a man’s dreams,
what is even left for him
in this world?!
Don Teabolo, please!
Please help me keep
this dream alive!
[ARTESIA:] Mother, it’s a
full moon tonight.
It’s the 43rd full moon since
we arrived on Earth.
When I first learned that a full
moon only happens once a month,
I was mad at you.
It was cruel to make me
wait that long.
But soon it will be fifty times.
That's halfway.
By the hundredth time, I'll be
even bigger than I am now.
I bet you'll be surprised
when you see me.
Casval is already taller than
Mr. Jimba Ral now.
And Mr. Teabolo has gotten
bigger as well. He
reminds me of...
What’s the diagnosis, doctor?
It's most likely just
the common cold.
However, if she contracted this
from somebody at the camp,
there's a chance that it
could be Sahara Fever.
In any case, we should keep a
close eye on her.
If it helps, I can sit by her
side until morning.
Good idea. It sure
couldn’t hurt.
If her condition changes, let
me know right away.
[DOGS BARKING]
I can’t hear the dogs anymore.
What’s going on?
[GUNFIRE]
Artesia! Wake up!
Artesia!
We have to go!
What?
Edouard, I feel cold...
[ARTESIA:] What is it?
What's wrong?
Be quiet!
[MR. RAL:] You filth!
The Zabis sent you to do their
dirty work, didn't they?!
[MR. RAL SCREAMS]
Hurry! Try to keep up!
We can’t go this way!
We have to go up!
We can’t go this way either!
Why is it blocked?
[MENACING CHUCKLE]
Please! Leave us alone!
Please! Stop it!
[DETECTIVE #1:] What a mess...
[DETECTIVE #2:] It's like a
war zone in here.
[DETECTIVE #3:] A bit of
overkill for your typical
home invasion.
Do you think it was a vendetta?
Or maybe the killers did it to
send some kind of message?
Inspector! There’s someone here!
Who is it?
I told you, this is a crime
scene! You can’t let
civilians in!
Yashima Company CEO?
Shu Yashima?
[TEABOLO:] I’m so
glad you came...
You'll have to forgive me...
if I don't get
up... you understand.
I’m so sorry for what
you’ve been through.
It must’ve been horrible.
They worked for the Zabis.
Mr. Ral contacted
Anaheim Electronics
and we were attacked
in retaliation.
It appears we were under
surveillance all along.
I should have never, ever let my
guard down like that.
Three years without any
incidents, I was beginning to
think we were safe.
Luckily, the children
were not harmed.
But I fear this is the end.
And I no longer have the
strength to do what it takes to
protect my children.
Don Teabolo, perhaps you should
consider relocating to Loum?
Loum? You mean Side 5?
[SHU:] There’s a nice little
colony there, which I
happen to own.
It is called Texas Colony.
It was built as a theme park
during the last economic bubble.
It was left abandoned, never
completed. So I purchased it.
There’s no need to worry,
though.
I had them resume
construction on it.
It may be a little
out of your way,
but it might be exactly
what you need.
There are several places I
could go, why there?
Because it would be a way to
placate the Zabis.
I don’t understand.
They could watch you.
Loum is the closest to Side 3,
making it easy to keep
an eye on you.
Nobody located that close to
Munzo would dare defy them.
At least, that's what
they would think.
That said, you wouldn’t be doing
this to deceive the Zabis.
I suspect you have probably
had similar thoughts.
Yes, you couldn’t be more right!
Thank you so much! I’ll do
exactly as you say!
It means so much to
me... your kindness...
Especially when I’m so weak.
Th‐Thank you.
Thanks. My apologies.
What a fine young lady you are.
This is your daughter,
I take it?
Oh, forgive me. I should’ve
introduced her sooner.
This is my daughter, Mirai.
She's skipped a few grades and
will be starting college.
And she says she wants to study
to become an astronaut.
Can you believe it?
Well, you’re daughter’s smart.
You must be so proud.
It’s a pretty name. Mirai is
Japanese, right?
If I remember correctly, it
means “the future.”
A fine name indeed.
I hope a good future is in
store for you both.
[COPS:] Back up! Stay back!
Move back further!
What is it, Mirai?
There, in the window!
I saw a girl and boy
standing there.
Do you think those
were the kids?
Yes, it probably was them.
Poor things...
Side 3: Munzo
[CROWD:] Zabi! Zabi! Zabi! Zabi!
Zabi! Zabi! Zabi! Zabi!
[KYCILIA:] Director Gihren, the
Chairman requests your presence.
He’s making an appearance.
Kycilia, did you have
Jimba Ral killed?
I did. Do you take
issue with that?
And yet, you failed to take
care of the other two.
That's what happens when you
rely on the locals.
Don't you agree?
The Special Service isn't like
the old private army.
You're in command of it now,
so I suggest you act like it
and lead your men.
Are you're saying that as the
National Campaign Director?
Fine! Understood!
Where is Dozle? I don’t see him.
He couldn’t come. Had some
important business.
Garma, you should ride
with me in my car.
Y‐Yes, sir!
[HAMON, SINGING:] There you are,
looking discouraged.
Come here, let the
wind guide you,
and I will take away the
pain inside you.
Lean on me, until the dawn.
Even in darkness,
you are the only one
gleams in my heart.
Don’t give up hope, there’s
a better tomorrow
I’d go through whatever it
takes to protect you.
Tonight, I’ll be your light.
So bright, you won’t
lose the way.
I’ll be by your side,
day and night.
Like I’ve always been.
Here we are, holding each other—
[CRASH]
No‐one likes a sappy love song!
I’ve had enough!
I’d rather karaoke!
All right! Give me the mic!
C’mon, I’ll show you
how it’s done!
Bandage.
You do what you need to do, and
don’t worry about the mess.
Thanks, Clamp.
In that case, I won’t hold back.
Get in there!
What are you doing?
Don't lose to some
stinking colonist!
D‐Don't let him beat you!
Fight back already!
You there!
Where are you going?
It’s too early to
call it a night.
Here, take the mic.
You wanted to sing, so sing!
No...thanks!
I said sing!
Well, what’s wrong with you?!
I told you to sing!
[DOZLE:] I think they've
learned their lesson.
The head of the Ral family,
fistfighting against a bunch of
Federation pipsqueaks?
The Ral family?
They’re hardly relevant anymore.
Not since you dragged their
bloody bodies through the mud!
Yes, you have a point.
That was indeed regrettable.
What?!
I'm here to ask a favor of you.
Would you be willing to help me?
To keep me from losing face?
A favor from me?
Where exactly are you taking us?
[DOZLE:] The docking bay.
Are we accompanying you on a
lunar field trip, is that it?
[DOZLE:] No, we’re not
going that far.
It's right next door.
Side 3 Extra Banchi Dark Colony
Commence with the testing
straight away!
Yes, sir!
We've been waiting for you, sir!
[DOZLE:] Good!
[GAIA:] Captain!
I thought that was you,
Captain Ral!
It's been a long time, sir!
Sergeant Gaia!
Hang on, you made
commissioned officer?
Yup!
That sure was a quick promotion.
Did you do something to
distinguish yourself?
About to soon, Captain.
Something big! Very big!
[SCIENTIST:] Testing will
commence in 60 seconds!
All personnel to your stations!
Standing by!
Warrant Officer Ortega, are
you ready to proceed?
Ortega? He's a warrant officer?!
And Mash is here, too.
We're all on the
same assignment.
What the hell’s going on?
What could you need
those hoodlums for?
Corporal Ortega standing by!
No, I mean Warrant Officer!
I’m ready whenever you guys are!
Let's do this!
[SCIENTIST:] Colonel
Dozle is observing!
Stay focused!
What in the world is that thing?
That’s called
“Mobile Worker 01.”
[DOZLE:] And it is going to
crush the Federation.
Mobile Worker?
[SCIENTIST:] All sensors
functioning normally!
Starting at a range of 600.
Target standing by.
How'd you get that Guntank?
It's a Federation MBT we
acquired through back channels.
Begin testing now!
[SCIENTIST:] Speed at 30!
Standard walking pace!
Walking pace accelerating!
Range, 450!
Target is opening fire!
Both units are advancing!
All systems green!
Grouping nominal!
Damage within expected range!
Ortega! Make sure you don’t
let that shield down!
This is too easy!
Show me what you've really got!
Main guns: fire!
Damage minimal!
He’s continuing to advance!
Nice move! Good, Ortega!
Yes! You did it!
Test successful!
That was amazing!
[GATE AGENT:] Flight 005
to Side 5, Loum,
will begin boarding momentarily.
[BOY:] No, wait, come back!
No, stop! Don't go that way!
Hey. Let me go, let me go.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I am Haro.
Wait for me, Dad!
Quit dawdling!
Didn't I tell you not to
open that thing until later?
Let’s go.
Sayla, what’s wrong?
Nothing, there was a boy
chasing after his big toy.
It almost got away.
It did, eh?
I guess he wanted that
toy pretty badly!
The package is headed to Loum.
Prepare for pickup.
Lucifer, we're going
into space again.
If only we could go back
and see Mother.
It would make me so happy.
[ASTRAIA:] I see...Madam
Roselucia has passed away, then?
[HAMON:] Wait, did you
not know that?
Course not. I'm never told
anything around here..
They won’t even tell me how my
children are doing.
They have some nerve!
Before Artesia left, she
promised she would write
to me every day,
but I haven’t received any...
Don’t worry, they’re doing fine!
They’re living on Earth, and
they were adopted by a man
named Teabolo Mass, and...
That’s quite all right, Crowley.
I’ve heard everything I
need to know.
Tell me, how is the club?
Is Eden doing well?
You know, same as always.
All sorts of people drop by,
and brawls break out every
once in a while.
I see. That takes me back...
It’s been so long since I’ve
been there. Feels like decades.
We were all still so
young back then,
without a care in the world
about what tomorrow might bring.
And one day, a
tired‐looking man walked in.
I just wanted to show him
some kindness.
Kindness to a man who was
clearly hurting.
But I didn’t know what
that would lead to.
And yet, I don't regret a
single moment.
Crowley, if I could have
anything I wanted,
do you know what I
would wish for?
I would wish to be with my
children, just for
one more night.
[MAID:] I’m afraid
your time is up.
You must leave. She
needs her medicine.
Astraia has only just
fallen asleep.
You should leave and give
her some peace.
Surely you can grant her
something like that.
It’s the least you
people can do.
Is that all you got?
Why you...!
...the hell?
Impact coefficient, 1.2 mega!
[SCIENTIST:] Instantaneous
acceleration, 800,000 gal!
Test Unit 02, abnormality in
first joint of the left arm!
Damn you!
[SCIENTIST:] Damage to Test
Unit 02's head!
Measurement disabled!
Gotta hand it to the Captain!
He actually won!
Get those two out of there!
Don't stop us!
I don't need a head to
keep fighting!
Colonel! This entire
setup is insane!
Did you see how Mash
tried to kill me!?
Look who's talking!
Climb on out, you two!
If you want to keep fighting, do
it on your own time!
Alright, fine. But for
what it’s worth,
I think this damn cockpit is a
deathtrap waiting to happen!
And the manipulators on this
thing need to be
completely modified!
Can’t stand the
restricted arm movement!
That's all valuable input.
I'll be certain to incorporate
it into the next prototypes.
Captain Ral!
What happened to you, sir?!
Another brawl?
[JIMBA:] None of your business.
Working your side job
again tonight?
[TACHI:] No, this is a
volunteer gig!
Be careful, sir! Lean on me!
Don’t touch me!
Hey.
Is the back room occupied?
[HAMON:] But why do you have to
be the one to do this?
Look how I’ve fallen.
I’m nothing more than the Zabis'
hired dog now.
But you're doing this for Col.
Dozle, right?
He’s different from his
siblings. He’s no
Gihren or Kycilia.
Today, I was able to
visit Lady Astraia.
I assume the Colonel must have
pulled some strings.
Probably as a thank you
for your help.
And how is she holding up?
Well, she asked me about how
the bar was doing.
After that, we talked a little
about the good old days.
It's just so unfair,
it’s so sad.
She's going to die soon.
However, Casval and Artesia...
they were supposed to go to
Loum, weren't they?
Yes, that’s right.
Loum, eh?
Side 5: Loum
[ROGER:] We've been
expecting you.
I'm Texas Village's chief
manager, Roger Aznable.
This is my lovely wife,
Michelle.
This place was originally
built as a hotel.
And while it’s supposed to
have a Texas theme,
it feels a bit more like
Wyoming to me.
What do you think?
I hope you find it to
your liking.
It’s charming.
All right, Lucifer!
Time to explore our new house!
[ARTESIA:] Edouard! Wait for me!
You're so mean!
Don't leave me behind!
The house looks so
small from here!
I didn’t realize we’d
ridden out this far!
[ARTESIA:] Not again!
C'mon! We have to chase
after my brother!
C’mon horsey, we have to go!
Hurry!
Oh wow, when did he get so
good at riding horses?
Wait a sec...
That's not him!
Then who is he?
[CHAR:] You’d make a
dashing little cowgirl.
Your name wouldn't happen to be
Sayla Mass, would it?
Nice to meet you, my
name’s Char Aznable.
I'd heard that your family was
coming to stay here.
Char Aznable?
Yeah, you met my dad.
He didn't mention me?
That’s funny, considering I’m
the exact same age as
your brother.
[ARTESIA:] He looks
just like Edouard!
The only difference is
their eye color...
Edouard's are blue, but
this boy's are...
Oh, and the way you’re holding
the reigns right now is wrong.
You gotta loosen up and
relax your shoulders.
Try it!
Yeah, there you go!
[CHAR:] Don't try to make him
run fast, and lift your
butt off the saddle.
Good, good, just like that!
That's called a trot!
Now, if you tap his sides with
your feet, he'll go even faster!
Nice, that's called a canter!
You’re a total natural!
Didn’t I tell you that you’d
make a good cowgirl?
See that over there?
That's Center Village.
That’s where the school
and church are.
And my parents house, too.
So is that where you live?
Not me, because I’m going to the
central colony’s high
school right now.
It's my brother!
Hi, I’m Edouard Mass.
And I'm Char Aznable!
[ARTESIA:] Dear Mother, I have
so much to write about today!
There are a lot of new things
happening in my life.
[CAT NOISE]
Lucifer made a funny
noise just now.
He's gotten older, too.
Texas Colony is nothing like
what it was on Munzo.
There’s so much starlight and
moonlight that it's
bright even at night.
I can see the lake clearly
from my window.
I can even see the village off
in the distance, too.
Mr. Aznable's and his
wife live there.
I got to meet Mr. Aznable's son.
His name is Char.
Mr. Char is the same
age as Casval,
and they look amazingly alike.
They look so similar that I
wasn't sure what would happen
when the two of them first met.
But in the end, it was fine.
I think they’re gonna be
really good friends.
Mr. Char has been teaching me
how to ride a horse.
I've already mastered cantering.
Next time, I'll try a gallop!
Edouard?
What's the matter, are you okay?
Artesia...
it’s Mother... she’s...
She's dead.
[HAMON, V/O:] I’m sorry to write
you such sad news.
However, I feel you must
face the truth.
Brace yourself for what you
are about to read.
Last night, your mother
Astraia passed away.
No!
Loving mother of
Edouard and Sayla.
[THEO:] She spends all her
free time down there.
It simply breaks my heart.
I really would have liked to
place a proper inscription
with the name Astraia on it,
but there's just no telling who
might come across it.
Yes, we understand.
Don’t worry, your secret
is safe with us.
Not even our son, Char,
knows the truth.
All I can do is pray that
God protects them.
Them, and all the other
kindhearted people
like yourselves.
[TEABOLO:] My meeting with the
headmaster shouldn't take long.
Why don’t you two wait at Mr.
Aznable's cafe
and I’ll meet you there after?
I must say, both your children
are excellent students.
Your son Edouard in particular.
It’s up to you, but
if you wanted,
he could advance to high
school right away.
You’re not being
straight with me.
Has Edouard done
something wrong?
Well...
I’m just not sure if we’re
suited to provide for
young Edouard.
Has he been misbehaving?
No, not at all!
Quite the opposite, actually.
Several of our more
problematic students
have suddenly started performing
better, and it’s thanks to him.
It's just...
Just what?
I'm afraid of him.
The boy terrifies me! Truly!
We have seen many young students
pass through our doors over
the years, but, well,
I’ve never come across
one like Edouard.
He has a keen mind.
Acute sensitivity.
He's a special boy with many
unique qualities.
However...there’s a
coldness to him.
He's hard like a steel knife,
just waiting to cut you!
It’s my concern that one day
he will be the cause
of some sort of catastrophe.
Enough! Say no more!
Oh, you're done with the
meeting already?
I want that headmaster fired!
I’ll take a beer and a hot dog.
I can’t believe his nerve.
He had no right to say
the things he did!
Mr. Aznable, I have a
proposal for you.
Your son and mine seem to have
really hit it off.
How would you feel if
the two of them
were to attend the same school?
Well, I don’t think it’s a bad
idea, but the truth is,
Char dropped out of school.
He took the Munzo
military academy exam.
The Zeon military academy?!
Edouard? Where are you going?
Quit your staring.
What do you want?
How long do you plan on
following us?
Look here, kid.
I don't know what kind of
joke you're playing—
Stop it, Edouard!
Father, help! Make Edouard stop!
You think you’re a tough guy,
huh?
Well, I’m gonna teach you a
lesson, you punk!
Edouard! Stop it now!
[HEADMASTER, V/O:] The boy
terrifies me, truly!
What's going on?
Is it part of a show?
No, it's for real!
That’s the boy who started it!
You think I won't lay a hand on
you, cause you’re a kid?
Think again!
I’m gonna beat some sense
into you, brat!
[ARTESIA:] Stop it!
Please, stop it, Edouard!
If you don’t, you’ll
kill that man!
What did he do, anyway?
I just don’t understand why
you would do this!
Besides, what good do you
think it will do?!
And what do you think Mother
would think if she saw
you like this?
I hate it! I hate it whenever
you get like this!
I'm sorry, Artesia...
I won't let it happen again.
[ARTESIA:] What's the matter,
Lucifer?
You haven't been
yourself lately.
We'll go into town and take you
to the vet tomorrow, okay?
Don't worry, the shots
don't hurt much.
[CHAR:] I did it! I passed!
I got into the military academy!
Isn't that amazing?!
I wasn’t sure I would
pass the exam!
The competition to get
in is intense!
Zeon is where all the
action is right now!
The world’s changing!
The times have finally caught up
with Zeon Zum Deikun's ideas!
Hey, I know you must
agree with me!
Oh. Yeah...
It is simply unfair the way
colony communities are
being exploited!
[CHAR:] It's just like
Gihren Zabi says!
Spacenoids are being robbed
of their wealth,
and Earthnoids are then
turning around
and using that hard‐earned
wealth to drive the
Earth into ruin!
[ROGER:] Char, why don’t we
change the subject?
This was supposed to be a
celebratory dinner.
Oh, I’m sorry.
I suppose I might’ve gotten a
little too carried away.
You know, even if what you say
is true, I doubt we’ll
really go to war.
That certainly may be
true for now.
But ten years, who can say?
In fact, it may be as
short as five years.
You never really know.
Char! Is that why you wanted to
join the military academy?
Because if that’s the reason,
I won't allow it!
I’m against war!
Now, now, Dad...
All we get is bad
news these days.
I wonder if Char has
always felt that way.
Lucifer, I'm sorry I left
you all alone.
Did you finish your dinner?
Hey there, Lucifer?
Lucifer, goodbye.
I know you left because
you were afraid
Mother was lonely
all by herself.
Please keep her company
and cheer her up for all of us
back here, okay? Please?
[CASVAL:] Artesia.
I’m leaving, so I won’t see
you for a while.
I’ve already discussed it
with Mr. Teabolo
and decided to go to Loum's
central school.
But why? Isn’t that the same
school that Char went to?
He’s not going there anymore,
though!
He wants to be a Zeon soldier!
That doesn't matter to me.
I'm my own person.
Goodbye, Artesia.
Don’t go! Why does everybody
have to leave me?
[ARTESIA:] Why is
everyone going away?!
Our mother is dead, and now even
Lucifer has left me!
Are you really going
to leave too?
I beg you, please! You can’t
leave me, brother!
Casval!
Don’t go!