[suspenseful music]
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0079, January 3rd.
The Principality of Zeon,
a nation founded at Side 3,
the space colony cluster
furthest from Earth,
declares war on the Earth
Federation government,
demanding its independence.
‐ If all you do is follow your
parent's orders all the time,
then how do you expect to grow, huh?
Be your own man.
Come on, you know I'm right.
‐ Go!
‐ [Narrator] And at Side 7,
which had yet to be touched by the war,
Amuro gets roped into
reluctantly uncovering
the secrets of the
Development Sector by Kai.
He learns that his father, Tem Ray,
has actually been working a job related to
military development for the EFF.
‐ April's cherry blossom season in Japan,
it's the best time of year.
‐ Do you think so?
‐ [Narrator] For its first offensive
in this war of independence,
the principality of Zeon
attacked Side 2, called Hatte,
which had maintained an anti‐Zeon stance.
It carries out Operation British,
in which it wipes out the population
of Side 2's capital Banchi
by using the chemical weapon
GG gas on the citizens,
pushing the colony out of
orbit and dropping it on Earth.
Having split into three parts,
debris from the colony
rains down across the Earth,
but Zeon fails in its initial objective,
the destruction of EFF
headquarters at Jaburo.
‐ It's about Casval Rem Deikun.
He's still alive!
[gasping]
‐ [Narrator] Meanwhile
Artesia, now going by Sayla,
is living at Side 5, also called Loum.
She is rattled when Tachi tells her
that he believes her brother
Casval is still alive.
At Loum, clashes between pro‐Zeon
and pro‐Federation forces
have escalated into full‐blown riots.
Sayla chose to take up arms
and defend her childhood
home against the rioters.
‐ We're going to have to
build some barricades!
Seal up the doors and windows
and prepare to fight for your lives!
[shouting]
[gun fires]
Bunch of animals!
‐ Let's do this!
[cheering]
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0079, January 23rd.
A battle between the two
sides eventually takes palce
in the Loum area.
The Tianem Fleet, the pride
of the EFF, and the Zeon fleet
under the command of Vice Admiral Dozle
slam into each other head‐on.
The Special Assault
Regiment, a mobile suit force
led by Gaia, Ortega, and Mash,
is launched from A Baoa Qu
and rushes to the battlefield at Loum.
‐ I'll remind you that I'm‐‐
‐ [Narrator] Char, Sayla's older brother,
has now become a lieutenant
junior grade in the Zeon forces.
He goes out ahead of his own
battalion manning his MS‐06S.
He is the streak of red light
that blazes toward Loum.
[lasers blasting]
[shouting]
‐ [Officer] Retvizan heavily damaged.
Kiel has been hit!
‐ We are going to be
altering our formation.
Inform the rest of the fleet!
Do not panic!
Disperse and change heading
while returning fire!
From here on out it's do or die!
Now get on with it!
[dramatic music]
[lasers blasting]
‐ It looks like they'll be wiped out
in our first engagement.
Those Zeon bastards.
[lasers blasting]
‐ [Soldier] Admiral Dozle's Valkyrie
appears to be changing formation.
[voices overlapping]
‐ [Officer] Captain, enemy
formation breaking down.
‐ Some of their ships are
still shooting back though.
Hit them with concentrated fire!
[lasers blasting]
‐ [Officer] Iwo Jima hit!
They're still returning fire!
‐ [Officer] Admiral Dozle, my ship is lost!
Good hunting sir.
‐ Thank you, my comrades.
I promise I won't forget you!
Do not let the sacrifice
of our brothers be in vain!
Now turn this ship around!
All right, aim for the enemy's main force!
Target the Revil Fleet!
[lasers blasting]
‐ Their flagship Valkyrie
appears to have changed its course.
‐ Let's make sure to confirm that.
‐ Yes sir.
‐ Do you think they could be retreating?
[grunts]
‐ Then we've won.
‐ There is still a possibility
that they might regroup.
‐ Then we will just have to
treat this as a pursuit battle.
Send out our very fastest advance groups.
‐ [Officer] Yes sir.
‐ The rest of you reestablish formation.
Hunt them down with everything we've got.
‐ [Officer] 2nd cruiser
squadron, accelerating.
4th frigate squadron, accelerating.
[dramatic music]
‐ [Officer] Each of our
forces has changed course.
They are beginning to transition
to operation trajectory.
The Tianem and Revil Fleets
have not altered their courses.
‐ We're changing course mid‐battle?
Is that our strategy?
‐ You fool, Tianem.
You've lost sight of Dozle's fleet.
However...
Garma, my boy.
This is about to become
the new front line.
‐ Report from advance group.
We're maintaining pursuit of them sir,
but Dozle Fleet has
dropped off our sensors.
‐ They what?
‐ We can't locate them without
further reconnaissance.
‐ Just great.
‐ [Officer] Minovsky particle density
is increasing steadily.
‐ [Officer] It's like
they're hiding in a fog.
‐ Do we report this to headquarters?
‐ I could try to establish
a laser comm link.
‐ However we don't want the enemy to know
that we've lost sight of them.
‐ Have the fleet maintain
its current heading.
Additionally, prepare
to send a coded message.
‐ [Officers] Yes sir.
‐ Come on, where'd you go?
‐ Mr. Ryu, the engagement
zone is dead ahead.
It's in an area ranging from
10 clicks to 100 clicks.
I can't use radar, so please
conduct a visual scan.
[groans]
‐ We're leaving something
like this to my eyeballs?
‐ Unfortunately the
Minovsky particle density
is still too high.
And my eyesight is terrible,
even with glasses on.
[groans]
I think I might see something.
I mean I don't think it's debris.
Hard to tell.
‐ I have visual on it as well.
Multiple nozzle plumes.
Must be the rear of one of our fleets.
Looks like they've arrived
at the front lines.
‐ Hang on...
Something's weird about this.
‐ They're far too close.
And their bearing is‐‐
‐ What's the vector analysis?
‐ Doing it now.
Let's see...
They're approaching from our 2:00.
But that means...
It's the enemy!
‐ [Ryu] This is the Duckbill!
Come in Falcon!
This is the Duckbill!
‐ This is bad!
The enemy is all around us!
‐ Crap!
The Falcon isn't responding!
[suspenseful music]
‐ Unidentified craft on our sensors.
‐ Yeah, so?
‐ It could be an enemy recon unit, sir.
‐ But what's it doing way out here?
‐ Sir, this could prove to be problematic.
‐ I don't care.
We are sticking to the plan!
We're holding our course!
‐ Right.
Holding our course.
‐ Well, all of our vessels
have completely ceased fire.
‐ All units, load in initial rounds,
and make sure your safeties are engaged.
Nicely done.
So far so good.
‐ Find anything?
‐ I can't tell what it is.
‐ Let me have a look.
‐ I thought it was debris, but from what?
‐ Those are...
They're ships!
Come in bridge, this is the right wing!
‐ Are you positive that they're ships?
What is the CIC saying about it?
‐ [Officer] Admiral on the bridge!
‐ Hmm?
Keep working on confirmation.
‐ [Admiral] As you were.
‐ Yes sir.
‐ All right then, what's
our current status?
‐ Sir, of course.
We're making our way
toward the engagement zone,
and the fleet's acceleration is steady.
[dramatic music]
‐ There it is.
I've found their main force.
[beeping]
Be amazed at what I am
capable of, almighty red!
‐ How's Tianem's Second Fleet doing?
‐ Right.
They have engaged the enemy
and now have the upper hand.
Also, CIC relayed a
report from a recon unit
a few moments ago.
[alarm beeping]
‐ [Officer] Fifth Battleship
Squadron has been hit!
‐ Wait, what?
I see fire!
‐ [Officer] There's another flash!
‐ That's ship number two, the Forrestal.
Damage to superstructure spotted.
Most likely due to an enemy attack.
‐ [Officer] But from where?!
The fire appears to be
spreading inside the ship!
‐ [Admiral] What's the enemy's bearing?
‐ [Officer] 4:00, according
to passive sensors.
[gasping]
‐ Deploy our cruiser squadron
in the direction of the attacks.
‐ [Officer] 16th cruiser
squadron, accelerating!
Bearing 207!
Encoded message from Tianem Fleet.
They've lost track of the Dozle Fleet.
‐ Wait, they've what?
Apparently a few minutes prior,
there was a report from a recon craft
that claimed to have spotted enemy ships.
‐ Deploy air defense squadrons.
‐ [Officer] Roger.
‐ And prepare for anti‐air combat.
‐ [Pilot] Wing to bridge.
‐ Direct call from lookout.
‐ [Pilot] Unidentifiable ship!
‐ [Officer] Shall I ping their IFF?
Receiving emergency
messages from consort ships.
‐ What is that there?
‐ Multiple ships, 12:00!
IFF unknown.
They are not friendly forces!
[gasping]
‐ [Officer] Target spotted.
It's Revil's own fleet.
All thrusters ahead, steady as she goes!
‐ All ships, full speed!
Attack!
‐ [Officer] All weapons, fire at will!
[gasping]
‐ Turn to port!
[lasers blasting]
[shouting]
‐ And fire!
Keep firing till you're out of ammo!
We're gonna blow a hole right
through their ugly mugs.
We won't stop till we
put 'em down for good!
[lasers blasting]
‐ [Officer] Heavy damage to
port, bow and midsection.
‐ [Officer] We can't contain the fires!
‐ CIC, please respond!
CIC!
CIC not responding!
I think they've been hit!
‐ Give the order to turn around.
The enemy is going to
attempt another pass.
‐ [Officer] Fleet,
prepare to change course.
‐ So the cornered rat
wants to attack the cat.
We were bitten, all right.
Pretty badly.
‐ [Officer] Each squadron, form a column!
We still outnumber them!
‐ [Officer] Port quarter hit!
‐ [Officer] Heavy damage to engine room!
[exploding]
‐ It's below us!
‐ It's moving too fast!
‐ The Zeon are to be feared.
‐ Another fire!
‐ At 5:00, I can see it.
[dramatic music]
‐ One more round left.
Reload your magazines while
we're coming back around!
[shouting]
‐ Get me a damage report!
‐ What are those?
Are they people?
No way!
They're mobile suits!
That's what they are.
[exploding]
[guns firing]
‐ [Officer] 108, you are clear to launch.
‐ [Pilot] Launch clearance confirmed.
Launch!
‐ [Pilot] 109, ready to launch.
‐ [Stream Leader] Stream
Leader to Stream Master,
launch all birds.
‐ [Stream Master] Stream
Master to all units.
Eliminate enemy vessels that
have penetrated our fleet.
‐ [Stream Leader] This is
Stream Leader, acknowledged.
[guns firing]
‐ This is the Duckbill,
requesting landing clearance.
This is the Duckbill here.
Falcon, do you read me?
We've already lost this many ships?
‐ [Controller] This is Falcon Control.
‐ [Ryu] Falcon, this is Duckbill 306,
request landing instructions.
‐ [Controller] Duckbill, unable
to grant landing clearance.
‐ Why the hell not?!
‐ [Controller] We're prioritizing launch
of combat units right now.
You'll have to land on another ship.
‐ Falcon Leader, come in!
This is the Duckbill!
Falcon Leader, come in!
‐ Dammit!
‐ [Officer] Abandon ship, abandon ship!
[alarm beeping]
[exploding]
‐ Captain, enemy rockets at 4:00!
‐ Hard to port!
[suspenseful music]
[exploding]
Third wave, incoming!
[guns firing]
‐ I've found you!
It's the Ananke!
Their flagship.
So that's Revil's ship.
And we're taking it out, yeah!
[guns firing]
‐ I'll leave the bridge to you, Mash.
‐ Sure, thanks.
[gun firing]
[shouting]
‐ Damage report!
‐ [Officer] Fire in the engine room!
They can't contain it!
‐ We have three mobile suits on us.
‐ Admiral!
‐ [Officer] Primary power holding steady.
‐ Our engines are offline.
We need to transfer you to a new vessel.
Abort flyer response.
Prepare to abandon ship.
‐ All hands, abandon ship immediately!
‐ All hands, abandon ship at once!
[exploding]
‐ All right, go get 'em Mash!
‐ Shut up and let me work.
‐ Leave it to me, I'll finish her off!
[growls]
[dramatic music]
[weapon firing]
‐ Those are nice and small.
Makes 'em more fun to shoot down!
[beeping]
‐ Hold your fire, take a closer look.
Huh, the admiral's flag.
[guns firing]
[exploding]
[shouting]
[lasers blasting]
‐ What happened?
Where am I?
I'm in space.
I thought I was a goner for sure.
One minute you're a pilot,
the next you're space trash.
Look, more trash is coming to join me.
Hey, Four‐eyes!
Where are you?
[dramatic music]
‐ Three rounds left.
Let's try and take down two more.
‐ He's fast.
Hold on, a red mobile suit?
Must be Lieutenant Char.
‐ It's that bastard!
‐ Char you mean?
‐ He's moving at three
times the normal speed!
Ha, the guy's a veritable red comet.
[gun fires]
[exploding]
‐ He took out a cruiser
with a single bazooka?
How in the world can I
compete against that?
‐ [Officer] Lieutenant Char?
‐ Master Chief Petty Officer Cozun.
‐ I have a spare magazine, sir.
Shall I top you off?
‐ [Char] You should focus
on grabbing your own glory,
I don't need help with mine.
‐ Sorry.
‐ [Cozun] I was only‐‐
‐ You served under Lieutenant
Ramba Ral, didn't you?
‐ Yes sir.
‐ Then do your part to make up
for the lieutenant's absence.
[grunts]
‐ I should congratulate you.
What a grand victory for our forces.
Please accept my sincere compliments.
We have the Supreme Commander's
masterful leadership to thank.
I underestimated your brilliance.
‐ I wasn't expecting such lavish praise,
especially not from you.
‐ This will guarantee the negotiations
will be quick and easy.
I'm sure the agreement
will skew in our favor.
‐ A bit premature.
This was just the first
step on the road to victory.
We mustn't allow the fighting to end,
at least not until we have achieved
our ultimate triumph over the Federation.
‐ Oh, I guess I've underestimated
you again, brother.
‐ If an opportunity presents itself,
one must adapt to seize it, Kycilia.
‐ Might I trouble you with a question?
‐ What is it?
‐ The Sovereign's ship, the Great Degwin,
is currently out there on
the front lines by herself,
and she is exposed.
‐ I'm sure it's just as Father wanted.
The troops are inspired, and
he is now able to witness
our historic victory firsthand.
I expect he's most pleased.
‐ Hypothetically speaking, if
the Tianem Fleet were prepared
to sacrifice itself in a suicide run,
do you think the Sovereign
would be able to fight them off?
‐ A needless concern.
The corrupt bureaucrat
soldiers of the Federation
do not possess the heroic recklessness
to attempt such a thing.
‐ But let's say they did,
what do you suppose would happen then?
‐ Do I really need to answer that?
‐ Perhaps not.
‐ This concludes the
summary of estimated losses
suffered by the enemy fleet.
‐ Way to go, Dozle!
Amazing, a complete victory!
Our forces are unbeatable!
‐ It's not over yet, Garma.
There is the possibility
that the Federation
could still send in their Tianem Fleet.
If that happened, the Zeon
homeland would be defenseless.
[gasps]
They would be adopting a lose the battle
to win the war strategy.
[gasping]
‐ Enemy ships, dead ahead.
We have them on optical sensors as well.
The large one is Gwazine‐class.
It is likely the Great Degwin,
the sovereign's flagship.
Mobilizing the Dozle Fleet
may have stretched the enemy
so thin that they've
been forced to send out
even their flagship.
‐ If we can get past those,
we'll be on their doorstep.
‐ If we make a run at the Zeon homeland,
we could force a surrender.
‐ Admiral, our fleet has only
sustained very minimal losses.
‐ Not a chance.
We aren't attacking, no way.
‐ But why not?
‐ The outcome of this battle
is already written on the wall.
‐ Admiral!
‐ Our most pressing duty is
to aid the fleeing Revil Fleet
by making sure they have
cover for their retreat.
All ships, come about!
‐ Yes sir!
Attention all ships!
Prepare to come about!
‐ Changing course!
‐ [Officer] Laser comm link established!
‐ [Officer] Confirm engine pressure!
‐ [Officer] Course is clear!
‐ You haven't defeated us yet.
This isn't over.
[suspenseful music]
‐ [Officer] The Tianem
Fleet has turned around.
They are 4000 kilometers
away and counting.
‐ We did it!
A decisive victory!
This means that we've
definitely won the battle,
right Father?
Next time, I'm gonna fight too,
for I am ready for anything!
After all, I'm a soldier
of the Principality!
‐ Garma.
You are still young.
No, rather you are still a child.
You are not yet fully
capable of comprehending
the true horrors of war.
I caution you never to act rashly.
Send the following to Dozle!
Admiral Revil has surrendered to us,
so he is to be extended
every courtesy possible.
‐ [Officer] There's a ship
returning fire at 10:00!
‐ [Officer] Turn to port!
All engines ahead, full speed!
Open fire!
‐ [Officer] Magellan‐class at 038!
Continue firing!
[lasers blasting]
Direct hit, direct hit!
‐ [Officer] Enemy battleship
group's battle line collapsing!
‐ [Officer] Heavy damage to
Magellan‐class confirmed!
‐ [Officer] Crew has
begun to abandon ship!
‐ It's nothing personal.
This is the fate of the vanquished.
[solemn music]
Hold your fire!
Attention fleet!
A moment of silence for
all the brave soldiers
who breathed their last breath out here.
Let us honor them!
[cheering and chanting]
[shouting]
‐ Long live the Sovereign!
‐ Long live Lord Gihren,
the Supreme Commander!
[triumphant music]
‐ Gihren, an immediate peace agreement.
That is our goal here.
I believe the wisest course of action
is to use this victory to force
the Federation to the table.
‐ With all due respect,
our victory doesn't have to end here.
We'll win the next battle.
And the next, till the very end.
When we do negotiate, it will
be at a time of our choosing,
when we determine that it
is most advantageous for us.
‐ Others preached this
before their downfall.
Men with the names of Napoleon and Hitler!
‐ There are no lessons to be learned
in the follies of ancient history.
After all, we are living
outside the bounds
of anything they ever experienced.
Forget their history,
we'll cultivate our own.
To think that such words
would come from my own father,
Zeon Zum Deikun's closest comrade!
What was it that Deikun said?
Did he not declare us
the future of humanity?
That Spacenoids would
become the new species
that will usher us into the
next stage of human evolution?
We have at our fingertips
the perfect opportunity
with which to make
Deikun's ideals a reality.
An opportunity like this will
not present itself again.
It would be folly not to press on.
We shall never compromise,
but always press onwards.
Onwards!
[groans]
‐ Kycilia.
‐ Yes Father.
I am right here.
‐ What do you think?
Quite frankly he frightens me.
‐ No need to worry, I will assist you.
‐ Please do.
At this point I am afraid
nobody can stop him except you.
He's turned into a monster.
Deikun's unfinished business has become
an evil spirit and possessed him.
He will destroy this country,
and our entire family along with it.
‐ Rest easy, Father.
I will always have your back.
‐ [Garma] No!
I don't want to be assigned to staff HQ!
‐ Sorry, but there's not
much I can do about it.
‐ I want to be on the front lines!
Please let me make a name for myself!
‐ Well, here's the thing.
This is what Father wanted,
and the top brass has agreed,
so, it's out of my hands.
‐ I find that hard to believe.
‐ Huh?
‐ They can't say no to you, they love you.
You're the hero of Loum, after all.
‐ Well, I guess.
‐ I won't be outdone, not by Char.
I heard that the decoration he's getting
has a two‐rank promotion.
He'll be a lieutenant commander!
Then that means I'll be...
‐ If that's why you're worried,
I can make you the same rank easy!
‐ Who cares if I didn't actually earn it?!
All I've done is watch
battles from a safe distance.
‐ There, there...
‐ I hate it.
I'm not taken seriously.
So doing me this favor
isn't really going to help.
People will say my only
accomplishment was being a Zabi.
[crying]
‐ Huh?
‐ All right then.
I'll be sure to talk to Gihren about it.
Don't come crying if
it doesn't go your way.
[triumphant music]
‐ [Reporter] We're coming to you live
from the Battle of Loum
victory celebration!
At the newly‐completed
Principality Government Building,
Deikun Hall!
The decoration ceremony has just ended,
and our brave soldiers are
now filing into the building.
Here comes our fleet
commander, Vice Admiral Dozle!
The commanding presence he radiates
is most certainly palpable.
Following close behind
him are the triumphant
Black Tri‐Stars!
Lieutenant Gaia!
Lieutenant Junior Grade Mash!
Lieutenant Junior Grade Ortega!
And now the man who earned
the nom de guerre Red Comet,
our ace of aces, Lieutenant JG Char!
Strike that!
The dashing cape of a field officer
is now fluttering on his shoulders!
Make that Lieutenant
Commander Char Aznable!
[growling]
‐ With this glorious victory,
these warriors, our pride
and joy of the battlefield,
have proven to the world
that Deikun's great teachings
are true, that we Spacenoids stand
head and shoulders above all
the others in the universe!
[cheering]
But countrymen, we
can't relax our efforts,
because our fight has only just begun.
May I remind you there are parts of Loum
who've yet to acknowledge our principality
and continue their futile resistance.
We must eliminate these rabble rousers
so we can unite the colonies as one.
It's only then we will be victorious
in our final battle
against the Federation!
[cheering]
‐ Yes, it's true.
That is what happened.
‐ We were the ones who were responsible
for taking Revil prisoner!
So why's it that guy who's
getting all the attention?!
‐ Just let it go, Ortega, and cool down.
The Sovereign's watching.
‐ Char.
[gasping]
How are you doing, my friend?
I've been following your exploits.
‐ Ah, Garma.
It appears that you're doing well too.
‐ Yes, I'm a major with our
elite airborne division.
My assignment just came through today.
‐ Why then congratulations.
That's a very fitting post for you.
‐ Ground combat is far more
risky than fleet warfare.
It's dirty, bloody work.
‐ Mhmm.
‐ I may only be a major,
but a whole armored regiment
will serve under me.
And with that regiment
behind me, I'll mop up
any remaining enemy forces in Loum.
‐ Oh?
‐ You think I can't handle it!
That's what you're thinking, huh?!
‐ I swear to you I'm not.
‐ It's just, it sounds rather dangerous,
and I didn't think that you
liked to get your hands dirty.
I'm more shocked that Sovereign Degwin
and Admiral Dozle would‐‐
‐ They've nothing to do with this!
I'm responsible for my own successes!
[chuckles]
Don't underestimate me, okay?
We are of the same ilk.
Neither one of us are the
little boys we were back then.
[light music]
[suspenseful music]
[exploding]
[shouting]
[guns firing]
‐ Do not let up the pressure!
Advance!
Let's send these
Federation lackeys packing!
[exploding]
[guns firing]
[shouting]
Concentrate your fire on enemy defensives!
They're there, right there!
Don't let any of them surrender!
[eerie music]
‐ [Curator] Aphrodite of Capua.
This statue is said to date
back to fourth century B. C.
of the Earth calendar.
‐ It's most certainly fake.
[gasps]
The real one's a replica
from the Roman era.
This one must be a copy of that copy,
made during the Renaissance era.
‐ Well, this item is a standout
among the museum's collection.
A Grecian urn!
The creatures depicted on
it are called centaurs.
The earn was found in
Vulci, in southern Italy‐‐
‐ This one is also a fake.
[gasps]
Something you would sell to tourists.
Even worse than a pure
counterfeit, one could say.
And this?
‐ [Curator] This is an example of a mask
used in theatrical
performances in the Roman era.
‐ [M'Quve] This as well?
‐ [Curator] Yes, we believe
that to be the case.
‐ These must have cost a small fortune.
‐ Yes, to say the least.
‐ For all the grandeur
of our Universal Century,
our history does not even
stretch back a mere 100 years.
That's why we're looked down upon.
‐ [Kycilia] Dismissed as nouveau riche.
‐ If you'll excuse me, I have
other things to attend to.
Feel free to view any
of the other exhibits.
‐ You have made your
feelings abundantly clear.
I appreciate you coming.
I agree that this war
is by far the worst ever
in human history, and we
must find a way to end it.
‐ Ever since Cain lifted
that rock to kill Abel,
violence between men has not ceased.
We're no closer to understanding
our fellow man either.
What a deplorable state.
Zeon Zum Deikun's intent
was to liberate us from this old cycle.
Though from space we are
still God's creation,
subject to his laws,
and as such might it be possible
that the space immigrants'
hope for liberation
surpasses that which
Earth's people once sought
when they crossed over to the New World?
That was Deikun thinking when he set forth
his protocols for the new era.
A group of us as his comrades
gathered under that banner.
But that this new humanity
would be used to justify
such destruction is
something we never predicted.
Admiral Revil, is there nothing
we can do to defuse this?
A way to somehow work together?
‐ What could I possibly do?
And how could I provide assistance?
I am a prisoner of war right now.
‐ Point taken.
I hear you.
And I understand you, Admiral Revil.
I'm hardly the ideal man candidate
to conduct such negotiations.
‐ Is that because you
instead hope to invade Earth
and restore the fruits of
our culture and civilization,
as well as our spiritual holy land?
‐ You have surmised correctly.
‐ That makes you the
right man for the job.
Make no mistake, the war must continue!
Let me be clear,
Lieutenant General M'Quve.
You will not be going as
an emissary to end the war.
You will be going there to
lead the Earth Invasion Force.
I didn't come up with this idea on my own.
Supreme Commander Gihren
is of the same mind.
We will seize the Earth's
bounty and her lands!
Which is precisely why
we must send someone
who can appreciate Earth's charms.
‐ Would you mind it terribly
if I asked two questions first?
‐ Please do.
‐ As I'm sure you are aware,
war requires there to be an opponent.
In the event that the Federation
has completely lost its will to fight,
who do you then suggest
that we aim our fists at?
‐ You said you had two questions for me.
What was your second?
‐ Ah, yes.
What assurances do I have?
My troops and I will be
parachuting into the enemy's lap.
I'm sorry for my bluntness,
but I've no wish to be a sacrificial pawn.
‐ I shall address your second question.
We have assigned Garma
Zabi to serve under you.
My dear brother Garma, whom
my father, Sovereign Degwin,
cherishes above all else.
You can be sure our sovereign
would never abandon you.
What greater assurance could you ask for?
And now, as for the answer
to your initial question,
regardless of the time or place,
mankind fundamentally desires warfare,
because man is foolish.
Sometimes war is the smartest choice.
In terms of prolonging the war,
plans are already in motion.
Lieutenant General M'Quve,
please try to rememeber this one thing.
You aren't like those mediocre commanders,
because you're a man who's
extraordinarily insightful.
As for Supreme Commander Gihren,
I detest him.
‐ What's so special
about that bastard M'Quve
that he gets to represent Zeon?!
He didn't so much as break
a sweat at Loum or Hatte!
I simply cannot stand that guy!
And to handle the peace
talks of all things!
If it blows up in their faces
they better not come crying to me!
In all honesty though, I was concerned
that a talented officer such as yourself
would be going down there with him.
I am happy to see you'll
be staying behind.
‐ Earth doesn't really agree with me.
I'm a true‐blooded Spacenoid
through and through.
He did approach me informally,
but I turned him down.
‐ Hmm.
Don't get me wrong here.
I'm not in the habit of
squabbling over subordinates
like a bunch of schoolchildren.
I have a good reason for
not wanting him to have you.
I have a specific job in mind for you.
‐ That so?
And what would that job be?
‐ The Federation is developing
a brand new mobile suit.
The project's being conducted in secret.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Apparently its codename is Operation V.
This development is being
carried out right now
somewhere in space.
[suspenseful music]
It was mobile suits that
ultimately determined
the outcome of our recent battles.
That said, even if I convinced them
that Operation V is a threat,
they still won't
understand its importance.
That's the reason I'm giving
you the following orders.
Pursue any clues you discover
and annihilate any resistance.
Ssniff out Operation V's
headquarters and destroy it.
‐ Sir.
‐ I had a feeling you'd get it,
how important this mission truly is.
Which brings us now to this!
Even if you are such a great
big hero of the Zeon Forces,
I don't expect you to carry out
such a crucial mission by yourself.
Look, that ship is now yours.
Feast your eyes on The Falmer.
I named her myself.
She's a Musai that
surpasses all other Musai!
She is my special gift to you.
I even handpicked a crew
that's the best of the best.
You will not have to answer to anyone.
This mission is your only priority.
Do you have any questions?
‐ I do not.
Thank you sir.
Lieutenant Commander Char, heading out.
[engines firing]
[whistles]
‐ We lucked out, this
baby is quite the ship!
Next to my rundown old
Papua resupply vessel,
this beauty is so shiny
it's almost blinding,
Congratulations, Captain.
‐ You're the ship's captain
now, Lieutenant Dren.
‐ You really shouldn't
joke about stuff like that,
Lieutenant Commander.
‐ Except I meant it in all seriousness.
No matter how good the ship, rest assured
I have absolutely zero desire
to be chained down by it.
Do not forget this, my men.
I have never once had the desire to become
a fine sailor such as yourselves.
I prefer to be a warrior of the cosmos.
A knight who possesses the freedom
to race faster than any
ship across the heavens.
[laughs]
Continue with the testing, Captain.
‐ Of course sir!
Then I, Lieutenant Dren, will humbly serve
as acting captain!
We shall engage in combat
drills immediately!
Attention, all hands take your posts!
[alarm ringing]
Anti‐ship battle stations!
Listen up, don't think of this as a drill.
Treat this like a real combat situation!
Let us make for the
designated battle area!
Turn her about, 90 degrees to port!
[engines firing]
‐ [Officer] This is Oak Tree
calling Queen of the Night.
Commencing screening of Blue Bird.
‐ Failure's not an option.
‐ [Officer] Understood ma'am.
‐ Permission to speak, ma'am.
‐ What is it?
‐ This name of this operation, Blue Bird,
what is it in reference to?
‐ In the Cold War period of the old era,
it was the name of the first film
jointly produced by America and the USSR.
If you want to know more, ask M'Quve!
[suspenseful music]
‐ Sorry to interrupt your rest.
Come with us.
‐ I'm moving?
What's going on?
I wasn't informed of any transfer.
Hmm?
‐ We must hurry, sir.
‐ [Admiral] Would it be all
right if I asked you something?
‐ I'll do my best to answer you.
‐ Where exactly am I being moved to?
‐ I see.
Understood.
[exploding]
[shouts]
‐ Please sir, if you would.
Unfortunately a field offer's
uniform is all we could find.
[guns firing]
We'll be breaching the
cargo terminal in this.
There'll be a launch scheduled
in that berthing bay,
so be ready to run for it.
‐ So are you the individual
in charge of this operation?
May I ask you your name?
Who do you serve under?
You're not at liberty to divulge that.
Is that correct?
[suspenseful music]
[lasers blasting]
[exploding]
‐ Let's go!
We have to make that launch!
[guns firing]
Hurry!
Come on or we won't make it!
‐ [Announcer] Emergency
incident is active.
This berth cannot be used at this time.
This is Oak Tree reporting in.
Blue Bird has been secured
and is in the cage.
We will now proceed to
the rendezvous point
with Maeterlinck.
‐ [Kycilia] Understood.
Well done.
‐ [Officer] I have lock on target ship.
Salamis‐class, dead ahead.
Distance, 8210.
‐ [Officer] Mega particle
cannon energy charge at 92%.
Anti‐ship missiles, ready to launch.
‐ All right, start with
three missiles, rapid fire!
Once they're away, lock on the ship
with the mega particle cannon,
and then hit it when it's
between 50 and 60 out!
Got that?!
‐ Energy charge at 120%!
‐ Tubes one through three,
ready to be fired, sir.
‐ [Officer] Distance, 8110.
Almost in...
Huh?
Huh?!
‐ Is there a problem?
‐ Captain!
Or I mean Acting Captain, sir!
There's something strange
about this target ship!
Its closing speed is too fast!
This Salamis...
...it's active!
‐ What's that?
‐ [Officer] The ship's speed
is 1.1 kilometers per second.
It's almost within our firing range!
‐ What do we do?
‐ What indeed?
You're the captain though.
‐ [Officer] Distance, 7900!
Speed has dropped off slightly.
‐ They've spotted us.
What now?
‐ What the heck?
This wasn't part of the original plan!
I thought you said that
there weren't going to be
any warships in this area!
‐ [Officer] The Musai closing in, sir!
‐ Why don't you order them to stop?
We've discovered an enemy ship
in a sector where there should be none.
There are two ways to
deal with this situation.
You can capture it, or you
can choose to destroy it.
Well Captain, wouldn't you agree?
‐ Yes, of course.
Attention, Federation vessel!
Halt immediately!
This is the Falmer, with
Lieutenant Commander Char Aznable!
And so any resistance is futile.
You will stop at once!
‐ Did he say Char?
‐ He's the one who destroyed
five battleships at Loum,
and is known as...
‐ The Red Comet.
‐ Of all people, why did we run into him?
‐ [Dren] I repeat, halt at once!
‐ Dren.
‐ Huh?
‐ Let's fire a warning shot.
A volley.
[gulps]
‐ Ready the turrets and prepare to fire!
Turret 1, aim starboard of the enemy ship!
Turrets 2 and 3, aim to
the ship's port side!
This is a warning!
Got that?
Don't hit them!
‐ This is Turret 1, we
have target acquisition.
‐ This is Turrets 2 and
3, we're aimed and ready.
‐ Fire!
[lasers blasting]
[shouting]
‐ [Officer] Enemy ship has
powered down its engine.
‐ Good, that was skillfully done.
Dren, I'm going out in my Zaku.
Have Denim provide cover.
Pull up alongside them and wait.
[sighs]
‐ What?!
Hold on, Lieutenant Commander Char,
you're not supposed to leave the...
[eerie music]
‐ That thing must be Zeon's
brand new mobile suit, the Zaku.
‐ I've never seen one before!
‐ A red Zaku.
‐ That's the Red Comet!
[gasps]
‐ As I'm sure you men are all aware,
we are currently at war.
By all rights, we should've
destroyed you without warning.
What would possess you to
sneak into the heart of Zeon?
How did you manage it?
And for what end?
‐ There's just one of
him, we can take him.
‐ I doubt that this is a
reconnaissance or sabotage mission.
‐ Here I go.
[gun fires]
[shouts]
‐ I asked you men a question.
Failure to answer will
only result in further harm
to your ship and her crew.
[suspenseful music]
[gasps]
Pardon the presumptuousness of my asking,
but am I standing in the
presence of Admiral Revil?
‐ That is correct, I'm
indeed Admiral Revil.
‐ And what will you do
with that knowledge,
are you a Zeon officer who
is faithful to his duty?
[gasping]
‐ I was unaware that you were
aboard this vessel, Admiral.
Please forgive me for so rudely
interrupting your journey.
Admiral, I wish you safe travels.
‐ Lieutenant, Lieutenant Commander Char
has disembarked from the ship!
‐ Oh he has?
I guess there's no reason
for me to get involved, then.
‐ [Officer] He seems to
be returning to his Zaku.
[engine powering up]
Enemy ship has powered up its engine.
‐ Lieutenant Commander?
Should we really be turning a blind eye?
Sir, they violated our territory!
‐ [Char] It's fine, Dren.
That was a treasure ship that
was far too rich for my blood.
We came very close to
ruining a brilliant bit
of political theater.
[light music]
‐ All right Father, we're finally here.
‐ Yes, I'd say you did quite well.
Not so well that I'd hire you
for our regular company flights, though.
‐ Really?
In light of my future prospects,
your company doesn't even make my list.
‐ So you're considering Cameron?
I think he would be an excellent choice.
I have no objections to that, by the way.
[gasps]
‐ Please fasten your seat
belt, I'm taking us in to dock.
‐ Amuro!
I'm really sorry to bother you
while you're out and about,
but I need just a minute
of your time, if you will.
What do you say, buddy?
It's about your father.
I promise it won't take long.
And don't feed me that crap about how he's
a Colony Public Corporation engineer.
He works for the military, right?
Just like I always suspected.
What is he working on, huh?
And why is it so hush‐hush?
He's trying to get us
dragged into this war.
That's what he's doing, isn't he?!
‐ Get out of my way.
[groans]
It's too dangerous.
You could get hit by a car.
[suspenseful music]
‐ [Guard] Even if you are
the chief engineer's son,
I still can't let you in.
Besides, some company bigwig
is here for a tour today.
‐ My father asked me to come!
He said he wanted me to pick up a bag
with memory chips in
it from his laboratory!
‐ Sorry, kid.
Afraid I can't help you.
‐ I need to know what
the heck a Gundam is!
[gasps]
‐ Hey, you must be Amuro, right?
‐ And who are you?
‐ My name is William Kemp.
I'm one of the people
who have been working
alongside your father.
‐ If you really are a
soldier, then it's true.
You must be able to tell
me what the Gundam is.
Am I right?
‐ How long have you known
about the Gundam's existence?
And did you hear about it from Chief Ray?
‐ Are you kidding me?
My father, I mean the chief,
never tells me a single thing!
‐ Then how is it you know about it?
‐ Wait, I'm asking the questions here!
Are you gonna tell me what
this Gundam is or not?!
[electronic beeping]
‐ Check upstairs.
‐ Hey, who are you people?
[shouts]
Damn you!
Stop, thieves!
Activating security mode!
[shouts]
Haro!
‐ I won't divulge to Chief Ray
what you tried to pull today.
But you aren't to say anything
to anyone either, got that?
This is your one and only warning.
‐ Well, that was completely useless.
Hmm?
[gasps]
[door beeps]
[suspenseful music]
‐ Amuro, I'm so sorry.
I was taken off guard.
They got the best of me.
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
‐ [Reporter] Ladies and gentlemen,
we come to you today from Scott
City, located in Antarctica.
This is the picturesque setting
where historic peace talks
are about to take place.
‐ I see.
That's good to hear.
Nicely done.
I'll request a special two‐rank promotion
for the entire team.
‐ [Judock] Commander
Judock reporting, sir!
‐ Have the media arrangements
been taken care of?
‐ Yes sir!
Most major stations on Earth,
as well as the colony sphere,
have their live feeds set up.
‐ Hmm.
‐ This will be a speech that will go down
in the history books!
‐ I'll be honest, it'll
be difficult for us
to lose you right now.
At the same time, I understand if you feel
that you cannot remain here
while we are under Zeon control.
Now, that said, I can
assist you with a transfer.
Would you be interested
in taking a job at Side 7?
‐ At Side 7?
Why there?
‐ Well I know it's out
in the middle of nowhere.
However it is free from Zeon influence.
And this is Luna II.
The Federation forces
still have control of it,
at least for now.
‐ And is that it?
Side 7?
‐ Yes.
You see it's a development
area located opposite
Zeon's Side 3.
And because of that I
doubt they would ever
want to bother with it.
There's a construction worker population
of about 30,000 there.
They live in a remote frontier
town without a doctor.
Regardless of the current
political climate,
as a doctor, I just
can't turn a blind eye.
‐ I can do it.
I'll go.
I'll go to Side 7!
‐ In Scott City, where peace
talks are already underway,
delegates from both sides
are beginning to arrive.
Representing Zeon is
Lieutenant General M'Quve.
Representing the Federation
Forces is Admiral Gopp.
Will the talks be successful
and peace reached?
It remains to be seen.
[suspenseful music]
‐ We've been awaiting your
arrival, Admiral Revil.
‐ Good day.
Nice to see you, Wakken.
I'm happy to know you're still alive.
I'm very sorry for what happened at Loum.
‐ Please hurry, sir.
We don't have much time.
‐ Elran!
I must say I'm surprised.
That was quite the little
miracle you pulled off there.
‐ Nothing gets past you, Admiral Gopp.
Word travels fast I see.
‐ Hardly.
The entire general staff
knows about this one.
What do you suppose Revil's
going to say in his speech?
‐ One can only imagine.
[chuckles]
‐ I imagine these negotiations
we are about to engage in
will be a complete waste of effort.
‐ I wouldn't go that far, sir.
Settling on a wartime
treaty would be worthwhile.
We could have a ban on
nuclear, biological,
and chemical weapons.
And of course, let's not forget
the use of colonies or
asteroids as superbombs.
‐ If I'm understanding you correctly,
have your war, just do it cleanly?
[laughing]
[suspenseful music]
[alarm buzzing]
‐ We go live in 15 seconds!
10 seconds!
Five seconds!
Four!
Three!
‐ Citizens of the Earth Sphere,
I am Johann Ibrahim Revil.
[gasping]
As an admiral of the Earth
Federation Space Forces,
I led the operation at
our allied nation of Loum.
This ended in a resounding defeat for us.
Since I was the commander in charge,
the fault can only lay in my
strategy and combat leadership.
‐ Is that for real?
‐ Why is he in a field officer's uniform?
‐ Shh.
‐ As you are aware, I was
injured in the battle,
taken prisoner, and held
in the Zeon homeland.
The only reason I am able
to speak to you today
from an allied base is because
I was rescued from captivity
by a group of valiant
soldiers from our forces.
[gasping]
We lost hundreds of thousands of soldiers,
as well as a great many warships.
I take full responsibility for all of it.
The fact that I was
rescued by the very forces
that I robbed of both glory and pride
is solely thanks to the grace of God.
[chuckles]
‐ Lieutenant Dren.
‐ Hmm, what?
‐ You should all be listening to this.
‐ And I take it as a sign from God
that I must do something
redeem the loss and disgrace‐‐
‐ [Char] The curtain is
about to rise on a new act.
A second act, in which I
guarantee there's no God.
‐ If you decide that I can be entrusted
with that duty once again,
you can be assured I would
devote myself body and soul
to making up for that horrendous defeat!
[gasping]
Of course, I am aware
that we are in the process
of peace negotiations in
Antarctica at this very moment.
Naturally, I am praying for peace as well.
However, a truce must not be
signed at this point in time,
because this would not be a
truce, it would be a surrender!
[gasping]
It means that the good people of Earth,
with their long history of
culture and civilization,
would be giving up all they've
known to authoritarian rule!
[dramatic music]
‐ Rot in hell, Revil!
‐ [Page] Excuse me, sir.
The commanders of the
Earth Expeditionary Force
have been waiting outside
to receive your blessing,
Sovereign.
‐ Be right there.
‐ Well then Father, I am taking my leave.
I've been promoted to colonel
for my distinguished service
in the Loum mop‐up.
I'll be taking command of
the North American Force,
the Western Sector!
‐ Listen closely, Garma.
You go out there and
silence those ingrates!
‐ Yes.
‐ Go out there and crush the souls
of ever lost one of those
war‐loving Earthers!
‐ [Revil] It was a grand
endeavor that only succeeded‐‐
‐ I can't believe how
behind schedule they are.
All this extra construction is pointless.
‐ [Revil] Zeon slaughtered
billions of innocent people.
These people were the backbone
of that grand enterprise!
‐ It's so peaceful, isn't it?
‐ One can only hope that this
place will remain peaceful.
‐ Why did they dare carry
out as barbaric an act
as dropping a colony full
of civilians onto Earth?
‐ Do you think this means
the war will continue?
‐ I do.
Their taste for destruction
hasn't been sated.
Humanity hasn't taken this
thing as far as it can go,
not by a long shot.
‐ [Revil] And so I beg
you, citizens of Earth,
you must not believe the
lies of Degwin and Gihren!
‐ [Father] Regardless of what people say,
humanity has a desire for war.
[laughing]
‐ Hey!
The water's great!
Why don't you guys come in and play?
‐ Kai sir, I think she's
asking us a question.
And what are you doing, anyway?
‐ Some military bigshot is
giving an important speech.
And I'm listening to it!
‐ Oh wow.
So does this mean the war
is going to be ending soon?
‐ Based on this speech,
I would say it doesn't seem very likely.
You know how it is.
[laughs]
‐ Amuro!
Hey, come play in the water with us!
I promise you it'll be fun!
[groaning]
‐ [Child] Hey look, it's Hayato!
Wanna play with us in the water?
It's super fun!
‐ [Hayato] Sorry, I can't.
I have to go to practice.
[children whining]
Cut it out!
Hey, stop pulling!
[shouts]
[laughing]
[dramatic music]
‐ On the other side of that,
I bet that's where the Gundam is.
[laughing]
‐ Hey now.
Let's see.
Hey baby, come play with us!
You seem kinda bored.
I promise we'll show you a real good time!
Hey, what are you listening too, anyway?
It doesn't look to me
like you're enjoying it.
‐ I'll let you listen if you want.
But you just have to be quiet,
because it's a very important speech.
‐ I urge you to not overestimate Zeon,
because remember, with its limited
human and material resources,
there's no way Zeon can continue fighting
for that much longer!
We must not lose our courage
and play into their hands.
We must continue to fight
for what we know to be right.
There are no soldiers in Zeon!
So we are certain to be
victorious in this war!
[upbeat rock music]
[singing in foreign language]
[dramatic music]
‐ Atmospheric exit is complete.
Target orbit has been achieved.
Accelerating, and now
setting a course for Luna II.
‐ She sure is a mighty fine
vessel, isn't she, Mr. Bright?
‐ She is.
‐ Yeah, we're lucky to
have this state of the art,
Minovsky Craft‐equipped ship, all right.
I'll admit, it's quite
the thrilling experience
for this old reservist.
All we have to do now
is complete our mission,
isn't that right?
‐ Yes sir.
‐ Where's Chief Tem Ray?
‐ He's in his cabin, sir.
I can show him to the
bridge later if you'd like.
‐ Mhmm.
‐ At last.
I thought the day would never be here!
Amuro, your father has done it!
The Gundam is finally complete!
I haven't made life easy for you, have I?
[light music]
‐ [Narrator] But who will survive?