[gentle instrumental music]
‐ [Narrator] The history of
mankind is also
a history of warfare.
Why does humanity
foolishly repeat
this endless series of
sad conflicts?
Furthermore, why is it
that humans fight?
‐ The Zabi family will shoulder
the responsibility
of history to come.
‐ [Narrator] Some people
fight for power
on behalf of their family.
[yelling]
[grunting]
‐ The Ral family, they're
hardly relevant anymore,
not since you dragged their
bloody bodies through the mud.
‐ [Narrator] While
there are others
who are driven to fight by
their own pride.
[metal creaking]
And what about this young man?
What is his reason for fighting?
‐ Who cares?
I am still Zeon Zum
Deikun's son.
When I grow up,
I will make the rest
of your family
bow down before me.
‐ Goodbye, Artesia.
‐ I told you I'm not Casval.
My name's Char Aznable.
[dramatic instrumental music]
So this is twilight on the moon.
[ship exploding]
‐ [Announcer] Universal
Century 0068.
It all began with the
death of this man,
[glass shattering]
Zeon Zum Deikun, the
leader who called
for Spacenoid independence.
‐ Your father was assassinated,
murdered by those Zabi thieves.
‐ Listen, the political
tension has put us
on the verge of a blood bath.
[yelling]
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0069.
‐ The Federation is
Deikun's enemy.
‐ We want freedom.
‐ [Narrator] In these
turbulent times,
the unrest from within the space
colonies of Side Three,
just beyond the moon,
boils over,
as cries for independence from
the Earth Federation grow.
Universal Century 0071.
[guns firing]
To further advance things,
Zeon is in the process
of developing
a new weapon in
preparation for war
against the Federation.
‐ [Dozle] And it is going to
crush the Federation.
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0077.
‐ Your choice.
You can hang back,
or you can crank the
gears of history
with your own two hands.
‐ Alright, then let's move out.
‐ [Narrator] The animosity
towards the Federation
from within Zeon reaches
its breaking point,
and a counter offensive
against Federation
security forces
is launched by its military
academy cadets.
‐ Now.
[weapons firing]
‐ We're just a colony state.
There's no way we'll win
against the Federation.
‐ Yes, maybe.
But we won't know until we try.
‐ [Narrator] And now a
showdown is imminent.
‐ Those poor children,
why were they fated to be
Deikun's progeny?
[gentle instrumental music]
Grow to be nice girl.
Then grow up to be a
good person.
Then you can make a lot
of people happy.
‐ [Narrator] But the siblings'
lives
remain at the mercy of
these cruel times
and their unfortunate fate.
[yelling]
‐ I would wish to be
with my children
for just one more night.
‐ It's just so unfair.
It's so sad.
She's going to die soon.
‐ [Narrator] Perhaps these two
were never destined
to have a moment's peace.
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ Artesia, it's mother.
She's dead.
[gasping]
‐ [Narrator] With the loss
of his mother‐‐
‐ Please, you can't leave me,
brother.
Casval.
Don't go.
‐ [Narrator] And now separated
from his only remaining family,
his younger sister,
the man sets out to get revenge.
[guns firing]
[ship exploding]
In his mind,
revenge itself is a noble
and righteous cause,
and so humanity rushes
on towards a war
the likes of which it
has never known.
‐ Our chance to forge a
new relationship
with the Federation,
however, we do have a
few conditions,
that the Federation relinquish
their assets here
and withdraw their forces.
‐ It looks like the world
is determined.
It's going to see
this to the end.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Fire.
[weapons firing]
‐ [Narrator] Mobile suits, the
weapons that Zeon
had secretly developed,
debut in battle.
[gasping]
[weapons firing]
And they possess fearsome
combat capabilities.
[metal clanging]
‐ Dr. Minovsky succeeded.
He's finally actually
made it happen.
‐ Show those Federation scumbags
what real Mobile Suits can do.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Another sucker bites the dust.
‐ I'll let that sink in a bit,
for this is the kind of power
that Zeon already possesses.
My father will name himself
as its sovereign,
and he'll declare our
independence any day now.
‐ Sieg Zeon.
‐ [Crowd] Sieg Zeon,
Sieg Zeon,
Sieg Zeon.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ My enemy, your enemy,
everyone's enemy,
and I'm gonna take them out.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Fire.
[weapons firing]
‐ Stop it.
Don't do this, Casval.
[tank firing]
‐ [Sayla] And you, dear Casval,
could it be true?
Are you really gone forever?
‐ [Narrator] Whenever the
righteous causes
of different groups of
people clash,
the result is war.
[gasping]
‐ I present the RX‐78,
codename Gundam.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[gasping]
‐ [Narrator] After all
that's been sacrificed,
will we ever see the end of
this man's war?
‐ Everything's red.
I think I rather like it.
[guns firing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Stop it, Casval.
[gun cocking]
‐ [Narrator] The worst war
in human history
is about to begin.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[weapons firing]
Universal Century 0079,
January 3rd,
the Principality of
Zeon declares war
on the Earth Federation.
[weapons firing]
The Zeon fleet, led by Vice
Admiral Dozle Zabi,
crushes the EFSF's
cruiser fleet,
utterly wiping it out.
A Mobile Suit assault force,
led by Major General
Kycilia Zabi,
seizes control of the lunar
city of Granada.
She then goes on to capture
Von Braun as well.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[weapons firing]
‐ I can still fight.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ [Narrator] On that
exact same day,
Zeon also declares war against
and attacks Side Two,
called Hatte,
which had steadfastly maintained
an anti‐Zeon stance.
‐ Fire and brimstone
has rained down
from the heavens onto Side Two,
just desserts for anyone
who would dare harbor opposition
to the noble Spacenoid cause.
They've received punishment
they brought down upon
their own heads.
[weapons firing]
[yelling]
[ship exploding]
‐ [Man] Commander,
Commander Ral, we've
eliminated most
of the enemy's resistance.
‐ You can't call this a war.
‐ I've recognized that it
was the Federation
that poisoned the minds
of the foolish leaders of Hatte.
They are the true enemy.
[weapons firing]
‐ It's a slaughter.
My countrymen, you 150 million
citizens of Zeon,
our fight has only just begun.
Let us continue to march onwards
together in perfect unison,
and we will not cease until
we have victory.
[weapons firing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ The fighting in
Hatte continues.
Yesterday evening, the
Hatte government
put out a call to all colonies
in the Federation government
for military support.
The Zeon force's attack range
appears to encompass
almost all of Hatte's Banshee‐‐
‐ Uh, it's me, Hayato.
Kai wants you to come out, okay?
‐ [Reporter] The capital Banshee
given the difference in
fighting strength
between them and the
Zeon attack force,
they are at a clear
disadvantage.
With the exception of Side Six‐‐
‐ [Robot] Don't go.
Kai is a bad egg.
Do not go, Amuro.
‐ This is no time to stay
cooped up all alone.
Haven't you heard there's
a war going on?
‐ I wasn't really aware.
‐ Your old man, isn't
he in charge
of the development
sector or something?
‐ I know.
What if he's actually secretly a
member of the military?
[gasping]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Guys, if we're gonna check out
the development sector,
let's go already,
or I'll be late for Judo
practice this morning.
‐ Are you actually
gonna go there?
‐ Something's fishy
about the place,
so I'm gonna figure out what it
is they're hiding.
‐ No, you can't.
My dad told me not to go
anywhere near that place.
‐ You're too much of a
daddy's boy, Amuro.
If all you do is follow your
parents' orders all the time,
then how do you expect to grow,
huh?
Be your own man.
Come on, you know I'm right.
[murmuring]
[truck engine running]
Okay, development sector,
here we go.
[murmuring]
♫ Here comes Seven
♫ Side Seven
♫ Straight to victory roads
♫ Go ai, ai, oh
[dramatic instrumental music]
♫ Here comes Seven
♫ Side Seven
♫ Straight to victory roads
♫ Go ai, ai, oh
[gasping]
‐ Hey, Kai, don't you think this
looks kind of dangerous?
‐ Huh?
What's that?
Move it, you chicken.
[truck engine running]
‐ What the‐‐
‐ When you want a
job done right,
call Kai Shiden.
[truck engine running]
[yelling]
Go.
[truck engine running]
[yelling]
‐ Please stop, Kai.
‐ What's the big deal?
They're supposed to be
developing this area
into new living quarters for
all of us, right?
So we're just gonna
have ourselves
a little sneak peak at what's
on the other side
of that wall.
[grunting and murmuring]
[siren ringing]
[weapons firing]
[yelling]
‐ [Man] Do not resist.
Step out of the
vehicle immediately.
I repeat, step out
of the vehicle
with your hands in the air.
If you resist, we will
open fire again.
[boots thumping]
‐ Those guys are
Federation soldiers.
[grunting]
‐ Goddammit, what the hell were
you delinquents thinking?
Alright, which of you
dumbasses is the leader?
I'm guessing it's you.
[grunting]
Now, I wanna see all your IDs.
I'm confiscating them.
‐ Hand them over.
Commander.
[murmuring]
‐ Hey, loser, I mean you.
Is it true?
Are you really Chief
Tem Ray's son?
‐ Uh, yes, that's correct, sir.
‐ Well, why didn't
you tell us that
right off the bat, old buddy?
[laughing]
No need for you to stay here
with the riff raff.
How about I have someone
escort you home?
You're not off the hook,
you punks.
Why in the world would you pull
a stupid stunt like that?
You looking for a
beating or something?
Well, you're gonna get one.
[grunting]
[birds chirping]
‐ I'm sorry to announce
there has been
a most unfortunate incident.
Several students in this class
stole a construction vehicle
and attempted to enter the
development sector.
Thank goodness they
were released,
but anyone else who gets caught
may not get off as
easily next time.
As you know, war has broken out
between the Principality of Zeon
and the Earth Federation.
During this crisis,
we must do our utmost to avoid
dangerous activities.
That includes to not under
any circumstances
go near the development sector.
Is that clear?
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ [Man] Commander Ramba Ral,
entering the bridge.
‐ Ah, great, you're here.
The initial fleet battle was a
complete victory.
We sure showed that high
and mighty Reval
a thing or two.
Hey, now, what's with
the long face?
Isn't our victory worth
a little smile?
‐ Truth be told, I would have
much rather participated
in a fleet battle.
Hatte's defense forces are of
little to no consequence.
I saw no need to
declare war on them.
‐ Come on, don't be like that.
‐ That's Island Iffish,
isn't it?
We could have taken it
in half a day
if we chose to,
and yet we were ordered to
leave it untouched.
‐ Precisely, that's why I
called you here.
Our brilliant Supreme
Leader Gihren
came up with an ingenious plan.
In one stroke, he will put an
immediate end to this war,
ensuring Zeon a
decisive victory.
‐ We are going to murder
those citizens
and drop a colony?
‐ Sh, you may want to
rephrase that.
The way you're putting it,
it makes it sounds like we're
doing something wrong.
You there.
‐ [Soldiers] Yes, sir.
‐ This is confidential between
me and the commander.
Now get lost.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ Listen, this is war time here.
If we're at war with Hatte,
then they're the enemy.
Don't you get that.
‐ I know.
‐ I'm not done.
Before you say anything,
take a look at this here.
We'll attach external
engines to the colony,
take it out of orbit,
send it into low Earth orbit,
and drop it on Federation
General HQ at Jaburo.
You get it now?
They anticipated they'd be
going to war with us
and even prepped for it.
How else do explain building the
new Jaburo Headquarters
under 1,000 meters of bedrock?
But this will smash it.
‐ And I'm to carry this out?
‐ Exactly, with the assistance
of your Mobile Suit team.
‐ I will do no such thing.
‐ What did you say?
‐ I get it now.
Lord Gihren would plan
something like this.
However, a military man should
never even suggest this
because it's the work
of the devil.
It's evil.
‐ You dare call me a devil.
Look who's talking.
That makes you a hypocrite.
You have the blood of
hundreds of millions
of Hatte civilians
on your hands.
If anyone here is the devil,
that would be you.
Those poor souls are going to
wind up dead anyway.
At least this way,
their deaths are counting
for something.
When you think about it,
it's the most sensible option.
‐ No it is not.
‐ Why not?
Why don't you agree?
[yelling]
‐ Admiral Dozle, this war
is sheer insanity.
Zeon Zum Deikun would
never approve
of such a thing,
and so I refuse to
take part in it.
‐ Wait.
I said wait.
Did you forget I was responsible
for your double rank promotion,
you ingrate?
‐ Step aside.
You're in the way.
‐ Stop.
Come back here.
Wait, damn you.
You're going to regret
this decision,
mark my words.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[yelling]
[guns firing]
‐ Hey, don't waste ammo.
‐ That's right.
You tell them.
Just wait, we're
gonna show them.
‐ Yuki.
‐ Fan Lee, where are
you guys going?
‐ We're evacuating to
the shelter.
What about you?
‐ The docking bay
for guard duty.
‐ Wait, what are you, [yelling].
You could have broken your neck.
You should come along with
us to the shelter.
‐ No way, I'm not running away.
I'll escort you though.
[boots clomping]
‐ Hey, the other Banshees,
do you think that they
also lost to Zeon?
‐ Probably.
[murmuring]
Cheer up.
Look, we're gonna be safe.
‐ How do you know?
‐ Because this is the
Capital Banshee,
and we also have
plenty of shelters.
Trust me.
Don't worry, okay?
Federation forces will show up
any moment to help.
‐ You think so?
I sure hope you're right.
[engines running]
‐ [Man] Heat resistant
coating application,
proceeding as planned.
‐ [Man] Pick up the pace.
You're moving too slowly.
‐ What are they up to?
Zeon are maniacs.
‐ They're probably doing
that to keep us
from seeing what's happening.
‐ The bastards,
if they're gonna come at us,
the sooner, the better.
‐ Hey, shouldn't you get going
to the docking bay?
‐ Nah, it's fine.
I plan on staying to
guard the shelter
you and your family
are in anyway.
‐ And do you know how
to use that?
‐ Sure I do.
Easier than playing the guitar.
[murmuring]
‐ Things sure have gotten
really crazy quickly.
Given everything
that's happened,
you would have been better off
if you'd gone to Earth sooner.
‐ I couldn't.
The Yashima Company's
training institute
doesn't open until April.
‐ That's so weird.
‐ What's weird about it?
April is cherry blossom
season in Japan.
It's the best time of the year.
‐ You think so?
‐ Actually, I haven't seen
them first hand.
People say falling petals
look like snow.
‐ Like snow.
‐ Guess what?
You probably didn't know,
but I actually have a bit of
Japanese blood in me,
and also snow in
Japanese is yuuki.
‐ Your name means snow.
‐ Not yuki, but yuuki.
My yuki means brave.
[laughing]
That said though, I
do love snow.
‐ I imagine that it must snow
quite a bit in Japan.
Must be nice,
I'd love to go see it sometime.
‐ So let's go as soon
as this is over.
‐ Like together?
‐ Yeah, together.
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ [Man] Heat resistant coating
application complete.
Uprising at docking bay
largely eliminated.
Booster attachment
proceeding smoothly.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ Shelter 12 is closing.
Shelter 12 is closing.
‐ Wait for me here, okay?
Stay right there,
and don't go to the docking bay.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ [Man] Pumping in the
double G gas.
There's a wind speed of about 10
meters per second inside.
The gas should distribute
rather quickly.
‐ [Man] Elapsed pump time,
five minutes.
‐ It's nothing personal.
We're just trying to put a
swift end to the war.
Besides, I doubt you'd wanna see
the surface of the Earth
rushing toward you.
It'd be too terrifying.
[foreboding instrumental music]
[gasping]
‐ It's so cold.
I'm freezing.
Why is it so cold all
of a sudden?
[gasping]
[gentle instrumental music]
It's snowing.
I had no idea that it could
snow in the colonies.
I can't wait to tell Fang Lee.
She'll be thrilled,
but why is it so cold?
[gasping]
[wind blowing]
What happened to them?
That's weird, sleeping
at their posts.
I don't believe it.
It's supposed to be our job
to keep the shelter safe.
[gasping]
[wind blowing]
No, have to get up.
If I fall asleep out here,
then I'll catch a cold.
[grunting]
The shelter, I have to reach it
and get inside.
Fang Lee,
open up.
Let me in, please.
Let me.
Fang Lee.
[rocket engine running]
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0079,
January 10th, Island Iffish,
Mother Banshee of Side Two,
Hatte,
leaves it's Lagrange Point
and enters into a free fall
trajectory towards Earth.
Its estimated point of impact
was the Guyana Highlands
in South America,
which harbors Jaburo,
the Earth Federation's
General HQ, beneath it.
A fleet led by Vice
Admiral Tianum,
which had been en route to
engage the Zeon forces,
abruptly changes its
mission objective.
It attempts to
destroy the colony,
but is unsuccessful.
January 15th, Island Iffish
enters into low Earth orbit.
[foreboding instrumental music]
[metal creaking]
January 16th, the Banshee splits
into three chunks,
and each enters the
Earth's atmosphere.
[foreboding instrumental music]
[station exploding]
When Island Iffish makes
impact with Earth,
it causes massive destruction.
The bay section strikes
southern Australia,
eradicating it,
and the enormous land section
that strikes southwestern Canada
causes debris to rain down
across the majority of America.
The section that came
down in the Pacific
triggers massive
earthquakes and tsunamis
in densely populated East Asia.
[thunder crackling]
The Earth's crust and atmosphere
are completely ravaged.
The fatalities from this
terrible calamity are so vast
that its extent is not fully
realized for some time.
When the deaths from
secondary causes
such as disease and starvation
are factored into the tally,
it's clear that the final
number of casualties
is much greater than anyone
could have imagined.
It is roughly half of the
world's population.
However, this is not the end.
The war has only just begun.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ The most pressing matter
that we must deal with
at the moment is how to deal
with Side Five, Loum.
The sentiment at Loum
is still split
between siding with us or
standing with the Federation.
The situation
differs from Hatte,
because unlike them,
Loum has already been promised
strong military support
from the Federation government.
The Tianum fleet, the most
powerful fleet in the EFSF,
is already en route to Miranda.
These detail has had a
major influence
on the public opinion there,
and the parties opposed to us
have gained the
upper hand there.
It's clear we've no choice
but to purge Loum.
If we're to win this holy war,
then Loum will play a
crucial role in it.
‐ You already have the blood of
billions on your hands.
How much more blood
must be spilled
before your thirst
will be quenched?
‐ The number that we've killed,
no, rather how many have died,
is of no consequence.
All that matters is that we
vanquish our enemy,
given that Jaburo still stands
and that the Federation
doesn't show any sign
of submitting to our demands.
‐ [Degwin] Whose fault is that?
Isn't this the consequence of
our own failed plan?
‐ The man who led
Operation British
will of course be
punished severely,
and the one who supervised it
will also be held accountable.
‐ In case I wasn't clear,
the one who came up with
this failed plan
and the one who's at
fault is you.
‐ If we emerge victorious,
then none of this will matter.
I assume that you
all do not wish
to be prosecuted as
war criminals.
Then you should put
your faith in me.
I am the man best suited
to provide us with the
leadership we need
to win this war.
‐ I'm returning to my chambers.
Garma, if you would
please accompany me.
‐ Yes.
‐ Too bad, he's getting on in
years, dear father.
[growling]
‐ Zena, Maneva, where are you?
I'm back.
Are my two girls still awake?
Zena, Maneva,
oh, Maneva, you
waited up for me.
Pretty girl, oh how
I missed you.
[baby crying]
Oh, you opened up your eyes.
Your papa's here.
That's right.
I'm your daddy.
Who am I?
Your daddy. [laughing]
[baby crying]
‐ Oh, there, there, did
you get scared?
Your daddy can be so naughty.
[baby crying]
‐ [Dozle] Is she asleep?
‐ Yes, she's asleep.
We played together all day long.
I think it tires her out.
‐ Aw, how adorable.
Maneva's so previous.
I couldn't bear if something
happened to her.
What have I, [crying].
Just how many millions of little
Maneva's have perished
all because of me?
[crying]
[gentle instrumental music]
Maneva started crying the
instant she saw my face.
Does my face look
that terrifying?
I guess I must have the
face of the devil
or an ogre.
Yes, that must be it.
‐ Don't be silly, my dear.
She was cranky because
she was sleepy.
There's no need to read into it.
‐ Do you think so?
Is that why she was crying?
I hope that you're right.
You know, I like my family the
way it was before
back when we all lived
together in this house
and when we got along.
Sasura was still alive,
and Garma was just a tiny
kid and so cute.
Well, I guess Garma's
still really cute.
[grunting]
Zena,
I am going to make it
my personal goal
to make sure that you
don't regret
marrying into the Zabi family.
You and I together,
we can create a new
legacy for the Zabis.
I want you to bear me
lots of children,
brothers for Maneva
and sisters too.
We'll make plenty of good
little children,
and I swear I will
keep them safe,
every single one of them.
[murmuring]
Anyone who lays a hand
on you or Maneva
will answer to me, no
matter who they are.
I get it now.
This is the reason men fight,
see?
When you have people
that you love,
you have no choice but to fight.
Those fools living in Hatte,
and the same can be said
for the Federation,
they were too weak to keep
their Manevas safe,
so it was their fault.
I am not weak like them.
I will crush every
single one of them.
If they dare touch
Maneva and Zena,
I'll rip them in half,
on this I swear, dammit.
[baby crying]
‐ Oh no, she's awake again.
There, there, you poor thing,
I'm afraid your daddy just
loves to shout so.
Oh, oh.
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ Oh, oh.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[crowd chanting]
[metal clattering]
‐ [Reporter] The military has
mobilized to keep the peace.
They're opening fire on the
pro‐Zeon protestors.
The Loum government appears
to have hardened
its anti‐Zeon position
and has the full backing of the
Federation military.
[siren ringing]
‐ [Doctor] No, we can't accept
any more patients.
‐ Send the injured to
another hospital.
‐ Doctor, this kid is
hurt real bad.
‐ Please, you can't let him die.
[yelling]
‐ I'll do what I can
to treat him.
Please, move him to the
sofa over there.
‐ You're Miss Artesia,
aren't you?
‐ I'm sorry.
You're mistaken.
‐ Before you go, my
identification.
Might you consider giving
me a few minutes
of your time now?
[helicopter engine running]
‐ What did you want to speak to
me about, Lieutenant Tachi?
I've got to admit to you,
you are an odd one.
I've never had an
intelligence operative
show me his ID before.
‐ Long time no see,
Lady Artesia.
I don't know if you're aware,
but when you and your
brother escaped Munzo,
I played a
significant part in it,
although in truth,
the only thing I did was follow
Mr. Ral's instructions
on how to get you and your
party past customs.
‐ I would really appreciate it
if you would just stop
beating around the bush.
It's not that I'm not
interested in hearing
what you have to say,
but it isn't a good time.
A lot is happening right now.
‐ I'm well aware of that.
It's the reason why
I'm even here.
You see, I wouldn't have been
able to have made contact
if it weren't for the current
state of affairs.
Believe me, it's no easy task
to beat the Kycilia
Agency to the punch,
intelligence operative or not.
Now you're familiar with a man
named Char Aznable, aren't you?
‐ What?
Char?
[helicopter engine running]
[gentle instrumental music]
What is it?
What is this all about?
‐ I first took note when he was
expelled from the academy
for inciting the cadet uprising,
and since then, he's made a
name for himself
as the pilot of a red
Mobile Suit.
He's now a young hero of Zeon,
and he's risen from enlisted
man to lieutenant.
I suggest that you keep a
close eye on him.
‐ What exactly are you
trying to say?
‐ I have one other piece
of information.
It's about Casval Rem Deikun.
He's still alive.
[gasping]
[metal clattering]
Although to be perfectly honest,
all of this is just based
on my personal opinion.
‐ No, please wait.
‐ Sorry I can't stay longer.
If anyone here found
out I was Zeon,
they'd string me up for sure.
‐ Lieutenant Tachi, wait.
[electronic ringing]
Yes, hello?
Don't worry, I'll,
Mr. Aznable?
‐ [Roger] Sayla, it's me.
Mr. Teabolo's collapsed.
They say it was a heart attack.
Could you come home immediately?
Hello?
Sayla?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
Are you still there?
This is Roger Aznable.
Hello?
[helicopter engine running]
‐ [Man] Pilot inspection,
proceed to test mode.
‐ [Man] L Three gauge
isn't climbing.
‐ [Man] Start with L Five‐‐
‐ We're in the process right now
of attaching stronger
thrusters to the packs,
and the nozzle's range of motion
is now 50% greater.
We're also attaching
custom fins.
‐ Woah, not too shabby.
These new Zaku models are not
too shabby at all.
Now that's the kind of machine
worthy of us Black Tri‐Stars.
‐ I particularly like that star.
‐ [murmuring] After all, the
way you look fighting
is just as important as
the fight itself.
[murmuring]
[suit engine running]
‐ Hey guys, what was that?
[siren ringing]
‐ What's with that flashy horn?
He wants his to be red
because he wants to
deliberately stand out
from the rest of us.
Nobody else would make such
a request but him.
Why's he gotta be so obnoxious?
Told you so, see?
I was right.
‐ Mechanic, I'm currently only
getting 80% output
from the sub thrusters.
I don't believe that's
the response level
I requested, correct?
‐ Considering the
stress on the pilot,
we thought it would be best to
have a limiter installed.
‐ Remove it.
I don't need it.
‐ Hey, asshole. [growling]
‐ Oh, are you here for your
inspections as well?
Couldn't wait for your
customized machines, huh?
[yelling]
‐ Lieutenant Char, I suppose
I outta give you
my congratulations for
another promotion.
‐ A rather swift double pump
promotion at that,
while Commander Ral was
demoted to lieutenant
in the reserves too.
‐ That officer's uniform suits
you, Lieutenant Junior Grade.
There's just one
thing about that.
Not wearing a normal suit
while piloting that
is against regs.
‐ Lieutenant, if the suit I'm
piloting is destroyed,
I'll be just as dead regardless
of what I'm wearing.
I'm going back out.
I had no idea you three paid
so much attention
to one's promotions.
If you're looking to
climb up the ranks,
then you've got to actually
accomplish something.
All eyes will be on the
battle at Loum.
It could the
opportunity of a lifetime
for you three.
We can compete to see which of
us performs the best.
So long, Tri‐Stars.
I will see you on the
battlefield.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ [Reporter] We are coming to
you live from Miranda Bay.
The exodus of pro‐Zeon
citizens continues
amidst a state of high alert
issued by the
military and police.
It now seems inevitable
that the Loum region will become
the next battlefield.
The tragedy of Hatte,
who's Capital Banshee was
dropped on Earth,
is causing widespread
panic on all parts.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ He seems to be in
stable condition now,
and since you've managed to make
it safely back here,
I think we can all rest
a bit easier.
[murmuring]
[insects chirping]
‐ [Sayla] What?
You're moving to Zeon?
‐ If we stay here,
there's no telling what
danger we may face
since we're citizens of
an enemy country.
I'd like to relocate to Zeon
while they're still
offering flights there,
and besides‐‐
‐ Besides what?
‐ Well, it has to do with Char,
obviously.
[gasping]
I'm not at all interested
in seeing the man
who's suddenly become
the hero of Zeon,
but even if he hasn't written
us a single letter,
the truth of the matter is
he's still the only son we have.
‐ I understand you.
I know how you must feel.
‐ I'm sorry for
springing this on you.
I know this is probably
terrible timing right now.
‐ No, that's quite alright, Mr.
Aznable.
Please, don't you
worry about it.
You've done so much for us
over the years,
and I'm grateful for all of it.
‐ Thank you so much
for saying that.
Having you in our lives was
a great pleasure.
I have faith that one day our
paths will cross again.
[foreboding instrumental music]
[insects chirping]
‐ Oh, Casval.
‐ You're familiar with a man
named Char Aznable, aren't you?
You're familiar with a man named
Char Aznable, aren't you?
It's about Casval Rem Deikun.
He's still alive.
‐ [Sayla] Casval, what happened?
What did you do to
that poor boy?
[rocket engine running]
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ [Narrator] Universal
Century 0079,
January 23rd,
the EFSF's third fleet
launched from the newly
constructed Jaburo base
and rendezvoused with Admiral
Reval's first fleet,
which had been on standby in
the Luna Two area.
From there, it immediately set
out for the Loum region
located on the opposite
side of Earth.
With this force that
vastly outnumbered
the combined Zeon forces,
the Federation intended to
settle the war in one blow.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ A battle at Loum will decide
the outcome of the war,
or rather, it must decide it.
Steel your resolve, gentlemen.
I expect that the EFSF is
burning with desire
for revenge over the
blow it received
from Operation British.
Therefore, we mustn't
underestimate its will to fight.
Only by uniting our forces
under our sovereign
and putting the very fate of our
principality on the line
will our victory be possible.
Now then, on to the briefing.
Vice Admiral Dozle, you now
have the floor.
‐ Let us not forget.
Every one of us is a
war criminal.
Should we fail, it will be
the gallows for us.
[murmuring]
The enemy's forces are
split in two.
One of them, led by Vice
Admiral Tianum,
is currently hovering
near the Loum area,
composed of 15 Magellan
class battleships,
also 45 Salamis class cruisers,
as well as Lepanto class
missile frigates,
landing crafts and the usual.
This fleet alone is comparable
to our entire force.
[murmuring]
Furthermore, Reval's main force
will be joining them,
and this fleet will
probably be three times
the size of Tianum's,
a real armada.
‐ A force four times our size?
‐ That's right, four
times larger.
Nothing can be done about
the difference in
fighting strength,
so that's why we will not
be implementing
some ineffective plan to
divide our force
into smaller ones to
attack them.
Instead, we are going to hit
the Tianum fleet
with everything we have.
[laughing]
‐ Wait, and what do
you intend to do
about Reval's main force?
‐ Don't worry.
We will hit Reval's force
with a Special Assault Regiment
launched from [murmuring].
‐ A Special Assault Regiment?
Wait a second.
‐ I'm sorry.
What's that?
‐ I know that you generals are
unfamiliar with it,
but the unit has
already proven itself
more than capable in battle.
For this mission,
I'll organize it into
two battalions,
and the fleet led by Reval
won't know what hit them.
[crowd chanting]
‐ [Crowd] Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon,
Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon,
Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon.
[neon crackling]
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ Alright, you two,
I'll be going now.
‐ Really?
You leaving already, Clamp?
‐ Hey, Commander.
I mean, Lieutenant.
‐ Cozun, long time, no see.
Want a drink?
Join me.
‐ Oh, I'd love to, really,
but I'm afraid the
transport convoy
is leaving soon.
‐ And they say that
anybody who's late
for this critical battle will be
considered unpatriotic.
‐ They would do that.
Well, get going then.
‐ I volunteered in hopes
that I'd be able
to serve with you again if I
was a Zaku pilot,
but you had to be selfish,
and you mustered out already.
Petty Office Cozun Graham,
now shipping out to the front
lines of Loum, sir.
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ Yeah, yeah, good riddance.
Don't forget,
the Zabis are a bunch of no
good murderers.
There's no need for you to
shed a drop of blood
for that lot,
and whatever you do,
you'd better not die on
their behalf,
you hear me?
[neon crackling]
[gentle instrumental music]
[snoring]
‐ Who's there?
I'm sorry.
We're closed right now.
Well, look what the
cat dragged in.
From what I hear, you're working
in intelligence now.
‐ I need you to run.
The Kycilia Agency are
on their way.
They're going to arrest you
and the Lieutenant
for insubordination.
[footsteps]
‐ We're looking for
Lieutenant Ramba Ral.
Is he here?
‐ Ral's in the back,
but he's sleeping.
What's this about?
‐ He refused to obey
a direct order
during Operation British,
so an arrest warrant's been
issued for him,
and if you don't hand
him over to us,
we'll bring you in too.
‐ Must I remind you that he's
already been punished
with a two rank demotion?
Besides, the direct order that
you are referring to
was actually issued by
Vice Admiral Dozle,
and it has nothing to
do with Kycilia.
So if she wants to arrest him,
she's going to have to bring the
warrant here herself
instead of sending out a
group of flunkies
like you to do her dirty work.
So if you would,
please forward her that message
from a Miss Crowley Hamon.
[murmuring]
[snoring]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[gentle instrumental music]
♫ Deep in my mind
♫ Neon signs shining bright
♫ Smoke faded into the night
♫ The doors left ajar
♫ With a glimmer of hope
♫ Just so you come back again
♫ Time goes by
♫ Goes by
♫ No matter how hard you try
♫ Don't say goodbye
♫ Goodbye
♫ Now that our story has
come to an end
♫ Feel your life
♫ Bursting into flames
♫ Every day, everywhere
♫ I believe in eternity
♫ The stream of time
♫ Never stops, never
sets me free
[gentle instrumental music]
[glass clattering]
♫ The town's fast asleep
♫ It's asleep dreaming of you
♫ Melting the ice
throughout the night
[liquid pouring]
♫ Won't shed a tear
♫ And I'll keep holding on
♫ Until you come back to me
♫ Lonely night
♫ So lonely
♫ In such a distant world
♫ There is no choice
♫ I won't be afraid
♫ Now is the time to stand
strong against fate
♫ Feel me close
♫ Even when in pain
♫ Every day, everywhere
♫ I will love you eternally
♫ The stream of time
♫ Never stops
♫ Never sets me free
[gentle instrumental music]
[neon crackling]
[insects chirping]
‐ Oh, sorry, I must have nodded
off a second there.
‐ That's quite alright.
I'm glad that Mr. Teabolo is
getting some rest.
[dogs barking]
I'll go check it out.
[gasping]
Oh no, there's a fire
in the village.
[dogs barking]
[murmuring]
‐ Hey, hold it right there.
Stay where you are,
or we'll shoot.
‐ [Villager] Help,
somebody help us.
Please, you've got to help us.
Thugs came from the Bay
and started attacking
the village.
‐ Mr. Aznable's house
is on fire too.
‐ They said they're going to
kill everyone in the park.
They said it's because we're all
Zeon supporters here.
‐ They're planning on
coming here too.
[gasping]
[glass shattering]
[gun firing]
[laughing and screaming]
‐ [Thug] Yeah, burn it all.
[murmuring]
[guns firing]
[car engine running]
‐ [Villager] Oh no,
they're here.
[guns firing]
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ We're going to have to
build some barricades.
Seal up the doors and windows,
and prepare to fight
for your lives.
[glass shattering]
‐ What in the world?
Hey, wait.
Where's Sayla?
Where did she go?
Sayla.
‐ Sedatives, get the sedatives.
‐ Do we have weapons?
‐ Yes, we have plenty.
They're really old though.
How about this?
A Winchester model 1873,
it uses lever action.
It's loaded with eight bullets.
[guns firing]
[yelling and laughing]
[gun firing]
[gun cocking]
[guns firing]
‐ Those bastards.
[bomb exploding]
[yelling]
[gun firing]
[screaming]
‐ Bunch of animals,
Federation, Zeon,
they're all the same.
This is madness, pure madness.
[guns firing]
What drove them to this place,
hatred, greed?
[guns firing]
Or was it something else?
[car engine running]
[bombs exploding]
Don't run away.
Just put out that fire.
Head to the back of the
hall upstairs.
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
‐ Excuse me.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[crying]
‐ I'm very sorry for your loss.
I tried to do
everything that I could,
but all this chaos was just
too much for him.
[crying]
[gentle instrumental music]
‐ Mr. Teabolo, I'm so sorry.
You did so much for us,
so thank you.
You were a wonderful father.
You really, truly were.
[crying]
[gentle instrumental music]
[murmuring]
[fire crackling]
‐ What is that?
Is it dawn already?
‐ [Thug] No, it can't be.
[station exploding]
‐ Miranda Bay, it's [screaming].
‐ It's under attack now too?
[bombs exploding]
[screaming]
‐ Please remain calm.
Everyone, take your seats
and fasten your seatbelts‐‐
‐ Oh, Roger, I really believed
we'd see our son again.
[murmuring]
[station exploding]
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ Artesia, if there
is such a thing
as divine protection,
then I have faith that you are
not here right now.
Texas, what?
‐ The Bay has been destroyed.
We can't go back now.
[yelling]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ [Tachi] The pilot of a
red Mobile Suit,
the pilot of a red Mobile Suit.
‐ The pilot of a red
Mobile Suit.
[yelling]
[rocket engines running]
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ So Miranda's been attacked,
huh?
‐ Yes, there are multiple
damage reports
from all Side Five Banshees,
and those reports indicate
that their docking bay sections
have been largely crippled.
‐ This doesn't make sense.
I would have thought
Zeon would want
to focus all its efforts on
a fleet battle.
‐ Perhaps we should
divert some ships
to defend Loum.
‐ COO, analysis.
‐ If any of the fleets
were to go to Loum,
based on coordinates, we
the second fleet
would be the closest.
However, we are also the ones
who are located closest to
the Zeon fleet.
‐ If we turned around now,
we'd be attacked from behind
by Dozle's ships.
We'll have to leave Loum
to Reval then.
After all, we only
initiated this operation
based on intelligence that
Reval himself received.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ The enemy has hit
Miranda's Bay.
‐ Yes, and not only that,
the garrison fleet is
stuck there,
so they are requesting for
our assistance.
‐ I see.
We did not anticipate this.
‐ The area's docking
bay sections
have been heavily damaged.
‐ The Loum government
has issued‐‐
‐ They're even covering the
incident on the news.
‐ Shall we divert some of
the Tianum fleet
to assist them?
‐ That's not a good option.
Tianum's got his hands full
facing off against almost the
entire Zeon fleet.
I doubt he wants to
divert a single ship.
With that said, we must act.
Send Cunningham and Walking's
fleets over there.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ Also, dispatch supply
and landing ships
to provide aid to the
civilians in that area.
‐ Yes.
‐ Inform the bridge
that the combined
first and third fleet will stay
on its current course.
‐ [Officer] Yes, sir.
‐ Alright, men, looks like we're
upping our timeline.
‐ [Officers] Yes, sir.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ Uh, begging your pardon, sir.
Our fleet has arrived at the
final defense line
in the orbit between Side
Three and the Moon.
Ever since Vice Admiral
Dozle's fleet,
which is at the core of this
operation, set sail,
he has been advancing
towards the Loum front
under radio silence.
‐ To our fatherland, to the
principality of Zeon, salute.
‐ [Officer] As you can see, the
fleet has already spread out
and taken battle formation‐‐
‐ How frustrating.
Hey, father, I mean sovereign,
I think I made the
wrong decision.
I should have requested a
position in the space forces,
not the ground forces.
‐ No, strike that.
I have a new report on the
enemy's activity.
The rebel fleet has split
into two groups.
One has changed course
towards Loum.
They appear to have fallen
for our diversionary operation.
This alters our relative
fighting strengths considerably.
It is now roughly three to one.
We have also just
received a report
from the commando team that
was sent to Loum.
‐ That's the team
that Char's in.
‐ [Officer] Attack successful,
mission accomplished,
no losses to friendly forces.
Upon retrieval of
Mobile Suit forces,
you will make for the Loum area
and rendezvous with Special
Assault Regiment.
[foreboding instrumental music]
‐ Alright, men, this is the
battle we've been waiting for.
The curtain's rising on a
new kind of warfare,
and you will be the lead actors
in the opening act.
We have one goal here,
and that is to beat
the Federation.
If we win, the
world's our oyster.
Rank, glory, and bonuses,
all around.
‐ Plus there's one more thing.
There's a punk out
there named Char
with a red suit.
You better make sure we
outperform that guy.
There's no way he's
getting the prize,
not out from under us.
Let's do this.
[cheering]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[rocket engines running]
‐ [Officer] The Tianum fleet is
almost within firing range
of the enemy.
‐ Alright, go ahead and give
them the permission to engage,
and the Minovsky
Particle status?
[electronic beeping]
‐ Not good, it's already
causing some interference
with our radar and data links.
‐ Recon craft status.
‐ Handled, sir.
We've put together an
extra rotation
in addition to our
regular patrols.
[rocket engines running]
We've had them circling
the region nonstop
since this morning.
‐ Warfare has no choice
but to change.
Let's head up to the bridge.
Update me with new intel
as it comes in.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ Distance now less than 10,000.
Enemy composition, three
battleship groups‐‐
‐ Dammit, this is aggravating.
I'm just stuck here
watching all this.
I bet you Char's in
the thick of it.
He's probably pursuing the
enemy fleet right now.
‐ That's enough, Garma.
In this world, there are those
whose deaths do not matter.
Then there are those to whom
it is not permitted.
You must prepare
yourself to be ready
when the time comes.
‐ With all due respect father,
I cannot be systematic when it
comes to people's lives
at a time like this.
‐ [Officer] Minovsky
Particle dispersal
appears to be increasing.
Density increase is sustaining.
Visual feed quality
is degrading.
The battle is about to begin.
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ [Man] Minovsky
Particle density
has reached a combat level.
‐ [Man] Capacitor is
holding steady.
‐ [Man] Bearing 181 confirmed.
‐ All hands prepare to
initiate barrage.
‐ All hands ready the canons.
‐ Prepare to fire.
‐ Loading of launch tubes one,
two, three confirmed.
‐ Switching system over
to canon fire.
‐ [Man] Stabilizers activated.
Safety is disengaged.
‐ [Man] Bearing 181, 012.
‐ [Man] Parameters entered.
‐ Here we go.
Commence barrage.
[weapons firing]
‐ [Officer] Our fleet has
launched a first attack.
‐ But the enemy has
better firing range.
‐ That is correct,
but it is not a concern of ours.
While our firepower is inferior
to the Federation's,
our fleet's Musai class has
excellent hit deflection
due to its smaller
cross section,
and the maneuverability
from the placement
of its thruster nozzles
allows it to easily
take evasive‐‐
[yelling]
‐ What was‐‐
‐ One of our ships was hit.
Looks like it was a direct hit.
‐ Whose ship?
It wasn't Dozle's Valkyrie,
was it?
‐ [Officer] Uh, no, sir.
‐ But a hit is still a hit,
and what was that about
maneuverability, huh?
You said it had great
hit deflection.
The battle's only just begun,
and one of our ships has been
destroyed already‐‐
‐ Garman.
You are embarrassing yourself.
Calm down right now.
[weapons firing]
[screaming]
‐ [Man] [murmuring]
Heavily damaged‐‐
‐ [Man] That's the third ship of
our advanced fleet
that we've lost.
‐ [Man] Seltovic,
engines offline.
‐ [Man] Proton and Amagie both
appear to have been hit.
‐ [Man] [murmuring] Has given
the order to abandon ship.
‐ Okay, we're going to be
altering our formation.
Inform the rest of the fleet.
Do not panic.
Disperse and change heading
while returning fire.
From here on out,
it's do or die.
Now get on with it.
[weapons firing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ It looks like
they'll be wiped out
in our first engagement,
those Zeon bastards.
[weapons firing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Excuse me, the Tianum
fleet has begun
to engage the enemy, sir.
[laughing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ [Char] I'm launching.
Open the hatch.
‐ [Dren] I think it's
best you wait
until the captain gives the
order, Lieutenant Char.
‐ I'll remind you that I'm
the one in charge
of the attack team, Ensign Dren.
I'm going in ahead.
Dena, take command of the
team and follow me.
Can you do that?
‐ [Dena] On it, sir.
‐ Man, oh man, looks like
being teamed up
with the winner of
the Zeon Cross
is gonna be bad for our health,
sir.
‐ Initiate launch.
‐ Okay, bosun, can you confirm
that he has clearance?
‐ Launch procedures are a go.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[rocket engines firing]
‐ [Dren] All units, proceed to
combat area at full speed.
‐ Just like we practiced.
‐ And don't fall behind.
‐ You're gonna form up on me.
[rocket engines running]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[weapons firing]
[electronic beeping]
[alarm beeping]
[grunting]
[electronic beeping]
‐ There it is.
I found their main force.
[dramatic instrumental music]
I'm changing the
course of history.
[alarm beeping]
Be amazed at what I am capable
of, oh mighty one.
[gentle instrumental music]
[singing in a foreign language]