[scraping]
So you are...
...a Witch.
[ROBIN]
Witches must be hunted.
That's the rule.
[ROBIN]
Isn't that right, Amon?
I've hunted so many...
I thought that the
Craft was a power
meant to be used
to hunt Witches.
[MINORI] Let's have takoyaki
again sometime, okay?
[ROBIN gasps]
[MINORI]
From today on,
I'm gonna be Minori Yoshida.
[gasps]
[MINORI giggles]
[ROBIN]
Wait!
I'll survive...
[ROBIN]
...as a Witch...
So you want info
on someone who came
into the country
in the past month
through an American base?
I even tried goin' through
all of the Immigration
Bureau's data,
but sure enough, I didn't get
a single hit on anybody
fitting that description.
Well, that's not so surprising.
Okay, you're on then.
It'd be pretty dangerous work,
but since you're the one
who's asking me to do it...
I owe you one, buddy.
Well then, off to
the next informant.
[ZAIZEN sighs]
[TECH]
Are you busy, sir?
[ZAIZEN]
No, come on in.
[TECH] Have you received some
sort of new information?
It's only a partial report,
but it seems that they
may have discovered
the whereabouts of Amon.
You think they really found him?
I do.
As we suspected, Amon's
injuries from the attack
were treated back at
Solomon headquarters.
Which would suggest
that he's in Europe now.
Yes...
And it seems as if his wounds
have completely healed.
They're telling me there's
a very strong possibility
that he's already left
the European Continent.
Then there's also a chance
he's found his way
back to Japan?
[ZAIZEN]
Mm... It's possible.
What is it, sir?
It's also possible that Amon
might have gone over
to headquarters' side.
[TECH] Perhaps it's too risky
to let him run loose.
It doesn't matter,
that man hasn't been given
one single piece
of vital information.
I'll admit that he was second
to none at hunting witches.
But in the end,
that's all he's good for.
Anyway, what did you need?
[TECH]
Right. I've brought you
the most up-to-date information
about the progress
on the Orbo Project.
[ROBIN]
I know...
I know that Sastre won't
be the last one.
Solomon will definitely
send another hunter.
Will I fight them?
Can I fight them?
[OLD WOMAN]
The answer to that question
is hidden deep inside
yourself, little one.
Yes. I know that.
[computer beeping]
The next hunter is in Japan.
An earth Craft User...
Huh...
What's the matter with everyone?
Our hunt schedule
is completely backed
up with targets,
but if this continues...
We'll just fall further
and further behind.
That's true.
You might be right.
Maybe the answer to all of this
is that you need to go
over there and tell them
a joke or something to
cheer them up a little.
Are you kidding, sir?!
I think I can safely
say that my jokes
will make them feel even
worse than they do now.
[sighs]
[computer beeps]
Uh?
[MICHAEL]
A hunter from HQ?!
[SAKAKI] So, you really think
he's here to hunt Robin?
Can you think of another
reason he'd show up?
If that's the case,
then what's headquarters
saying about him?
Not a word.
All they're saying right
now is that a hunter's
been sent to Japan.
There's nothing about
his name or his objective.
What do you suppose
they're up to, then?
It's pretty clear that they
don't trust us anymore.
[DOJIMA]
What do you mean?
Oh c'mon, you know what
I mean, don't ya.
You mean the deal
with Zaizen and HQ?
Well yeah, I definitely
get the feeling
that they're not getting along.
You've got a point.
I guess the fact that there's
no talk of cooperation
between the departments
probably means
the bosses are on
bad terms right now.
In fact, I bet we could
easily find Robin
if we really set our minds
to tracking her down.
After all, our information-
gathering capability
here in Japan is far
better than theirs.
But then, if it turns out
that we have to help them
that would mean that we'd
actually have to take part
in the hunt for her,
wouldn't it?
Forget it. There's no
way I'd ever do that.
[inhales, exhales]
Huh?
What's the matter?
What's with the serious
look all of a sudden?
I'm sorry, I guess I was
just thinking about Amon.
I was wondering what
he was doing there.
If you're talking
about the other day...
It almost seemed like he was
being totally hostile
to Robin, didn't it?
And this is kinda weird, too...
He hasn't even bothered
to show up at the office.
I mean, man, what's happening
to this organization?
[footsteps]
[HATTORI] Hey, everybody,
what are you doing?
Don't sit here and mope!
Let's go to Harry's!
Then we can all have some hair
of the dog that bit ya!
Uh...
Well, what I mean is...
[KOSAKA]
Brrr! It's cold, isn't it?
I'm calling it a day.
I better check on her.
[NAGIRA]
Yo!
[ROBIN gasps]
What's up? Doin' some
late night shopping?
[ROBIN] I was just out
getting some dinner.
Funny, same here.
C'mon, that getup makes
it way too obvious
that you're trying
to hide your face.
[NAGIRA] You're tracking
a Solomon hunter?
Sastre won't be the last one.
I'm sure that Solomon will
send out another hunter.
So now you're out there trying
to get the drop on him, right?
But, how are you
gonna find the guy
when you don't know his name
or what he looks like?
I guess...
You know, you've changed.
Eh?
[NAGIRA]
It's like you'd been in a daze
ever since you got here,
but now you're different.
I'm just the same as always.
Only up until now, I've done
what Solomon told me to do.
But from now on,
I'm completely on my own.
Well you know, I sorta
got the impression
that you knew about that
last hunter beforehand.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Well in that case, why don't
you hit up that source again?
Well. It's because, I...
It's tough to go to them now
because they saw you
take out a hunter, right?
Huh?!
How did you know, Nagira?
Why do you sound
so surprised, Robin?
It's clear you've been
getting intel somehow.
So it's only natural
that you got it
from one of your old teammates.
It makes sense.
I'm sorry.
I guess I should have
been more careful.
[NAGIRA]
You didn't have much choice.
However, now you're
being too timid.
Uh?
So maybe they finally saw
that you can be a
dangerous woman...
It's a real shame to lose all
your faith in your friends
over a thing like that.
Well, that was quick.
I put a rush on it.
And?
It's just as you suspected.
Really...
This guy fits the description,
and also he entered Japan
under his own name.
His own name?!
Yeah, except that his ID said
he was a civilian from
the European Union.
[typing]
He's still at the same location?
[CORNELI coughing]
[coughs]
[typing]
Hey, what's up?
What are you investigating?
The hunter from yesterday.
Any luck?
[MICHAEL]
We haven't found anything yet.
[KOSAKA clears throat]
[KOSAKA]
Hmm... Uh...
Well, then. Far be it
from me to try to tell
you people not to
investigate something...
But, I'd appreciate it if you
didn't forget you
have a job to do.
And as for you, Dojima...
What do you think you're
doing, standing around
like that with your coat
still on your arm?
I realize you enjoy being
late, but you should have
gotten down to work
a long time ago.
He's withdrawing money
on a regular basis.
The most recent withdrawal was
at the Kamiigusa
branch two days ago.
Is there some sort of problem?
Not really, I was just kinda
wondering why he would
do something as obvious
as use his own account.
You were the one
who told me to check
his bank account,
so why are you surprised?
I know, but I didn't really
expect it to be this easy
to track the guy down.
It's almost as if...
As if he's trying to broadcast
his movements or something.
[door clicks, footsteps]
What the hell does Amon
think he's doin'?
Why would he go and deliberately
do things that would
leave a trail like this?
Is he tryin' to call me out?
That can't be it.
And even if he were,
what good would it do?
Hmm.
Well, then...
[coughs]
Okay, I guess we're gonna
call it a night, Michael.
All right.
Good work today.
Yeah, you, too.
[ROBIN]
Michael...
You finally showed up?
You wanna know about Amon?
[ROBIN]
Not now.
Huh? What, then?
[ROBIN] Michael, have you
gotten any information
about a new hunter
from headquarters?
A hunter? How did you--?
[ROBIN]
It won't end with Sastre.
I'm positive they'll be
sending another hunter.
If you know anything,
please tell me.
Just wait a second Robin,
you're not gonna try
to take on HQ all by
yourself, are you?
Don't worry. I'm the same
person I've always been.
But now headquarters has
classified me as a Witch.
Is it because I learned the
inner secrets of the Craft?
I have to find out. Otherwise...
You're pretty tough.
You know that?
I've got some information on
that hunter from HQ, all right.
And this time, they sent it
directly to my computer.
[ROBIN]
Why would headquarters do that?
[MICHAEL]
I don't know.
But if they were able to access
my computer, then they're
the only ones who've ever
been able to hack into it.
What's the matter?
It's not them.
[MICHAEL]
What are you talking about?
There's someone else who
could've broken in to your
computer system, Michael.
I seriously doubt it.
[ROBIN grunts]
The one who could get access
to your system is Amon.
Amon?
But if he did that, then...
[CORNELI coughs]
Robin...
[gasps]
[coughs]
You must be Robin, I presume.
[CORNELI coughing]
Well, in that case...
[ROBIN grunts]
[gasps]
My powers are being reflected!
[coughs]
You're caught in
the eternal maze.
What do you mean
"the Eternal maze"?
[CORNELI] You've been imprisoned
in the endless black shadow...
Which will forever
lead man astray.
[gasping]
It's an Ogham ward.
Is she trapped in it?
No! This is an illusion!
His element...
I have to sense his spirit...
[ROBIN grunts]
[coughs]
[coughing]
[gasps]
[coughs]
[ROBIN groaning]
[CORNELI screams]
[gasps]
You may have beaten me,
but I won't be the last!
[screams]
[panting]
What's inside Robin...
...is not just a power.
Can't you understand that...
...Big Brother?
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
The footsteps of destruction.
Phantom from the past.
Time that started to move again.
A portrait gives out speechless
whispers of frozen memories.