[MAN panting]
[panting]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[MAN yelps]
[MAN grunting]
[phone rings]
[ROBIN]
Hello?
Michael...
[ROBIN]
A strange corpse?
[MICHAEL]
It's 4:20 right now.
Be at the office by five, okay?
[COP A] All right,
I just got confirmation
from our commander.
We can't touch this case.
[COP B]
How come?
[COP A] It's officially been
turned over to the STNJ.
[COP B]
Is it that strange a corpse?
[COP A] Apparently, it's all
shriveled up like a mummy.
[COP B]
I see.
What are those guys
doin' in there?
[SAKAKI] The guys from
the Factory sure are late.
We're never gonna be able
to figure anything out
just standin' around lookin' at
a mummified corpse like this.
Robin! Don't mess up the
crime scene, all right?
[KARASUMA]
Amon...
I talked to the police and
look what they gave me.
They picked up this
licence near the corpse.
Haruo Katayama, 22 years old.
Old-lookin' corpse
for a 22-year-old.
Do you think this
is the same guy?
[AMON] We'll have to wait
for the Factory to tell us.
[SAKAKI]
Hey!
I told you,
don't touch anything!
[ROBIN]
Something's here.
An insect.
[SAKAKI] I'm sure Dojima
is ditchin' again.
I'll bet she's still not here.
Oh, there she is.
She's goofin' off again!
[SAKAKI] Jeez, what are they
up to? This is stupid.
[ROBIN]
What is it?
Well, it looks
as though somebody
is trying to hack their way
into the STN computer.
It's all right.
My security firewall
is just about perfect.
There's nobody that could
break through it.
But if they do,
he's got a collar
around his neck for life,
like you-know-who.
It's always the same, isn't it?
Uh, Hattori, what happened to
those files you were getting?
Um y-yes, those files.
I was just, uh...
They're right over, uh...
[AMON]
What are you doing?
Michael, let's go.
There's a meeting.
He's such a pain.
[KARASUMA] Mummified corpses,
similar to the one
we found, have been reported
in two other places
in the region.
The victims are
a 33-year-old male
and a 28-year-old female.
Furthermore, DNA testing
has confirmed that
the body from this morning
is that of the person
pictured on the
license we found.
Their powers hadn't
yet awakened,
but all of the victims
were descendants of witches
that are registered
in our database.
They were all witches?
[AMON]
Michael.
In an old file left by
the forerunner of STNJ,
I found several similar
mummified body incidents.
Hundred and twenty years ago
in Europe, 80 years ago
in Japan, and 40 years
ago in the USA.
All the victims were witches
or decendents of witches.
Back then, it was
determined that
it was caused by a
certain kind of witch,
and in the case 80 years ago,
they even found a suspect.
There was a suspect?
[DOJIMA] Hey, he's a
pretty good looking guy.
Kazuma Kurata.
He was 30 years old.
Kurata went missing
when his boat vanished
during a violent storm at sea,
so the case was never solved.
What about the body?
[MICHAEL]
It was never found.
It's 80 years ago, right?
Even if he survived, I'm sure
he must be dead by now.
[SAKAKI]
Wait a minute.
With all the past cases,
why would a witch
mummify another witch?
I just don't get it.
[AMON]
In any case...
It looks like we'll need
to investigate him again.
It might be another witch.
But it could also be the actions
of one of his descendants.
[ATTENDANT]
Mrs. Kurata?
There are some people here
who wanna talk to you
about the late Mr. Kazuma.
Mrs. Kurata!
[OLD WOMAN]
Kazuma?
She gets like this sometimes.
Just let me know when you're
finished and ready to leave.
[DOJIMA]
Sorry to trouble you.
Bow politely, now.
[OLD WOMAN]
That man will never die.
I know he's still young.
I married him and lived with
him for many, many years.
But he remained just like
he was when we first met.
He never seemed
to grow a day older.
It wasn't the same for me.
I kept aging and turned
into an old woman.
[OLD WOMAN]
You never change, do you?
You're just like mountains
around the lake.
[DOJIMA]
This was such a waste of time!
Yeah, we drove all this
way just to find out
that Grandma was
totally out of it.
Huh?!
Right! I got it.
I'll head over there right away.
Looks like they
found another mummy.
Sakaki, go check the
hotel's security cameras.
You got it.
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
[AMON]
Another insect.
[DOJIMA]
Miho!
[KARASUMA]
Well, you two are late.
Oh, and guess who
we just discovered
on the security camera video.
[DOJIMA] Kurata?! You mean
Kurata isn't dead?!
[SAKAKI]
This is impossible!
Even if he was alive,
he would be 110
years old by now!
[KARASUMA]
No matter how you look at him,
this guy looks like
he's in his 30s.
[ROBIN] Dojima, maybe
what that old woman
told us was true.
[AMON]
What?
[ROBIN] She said that
Kurata was always young,
that he never aged.
Never aged?
[SAKAKI]
No way!
How could somethin'
like that happen?
According to a hotel employee
who saw the guy
walking down the hall,
there was a tattoo of something
like a bug on his hand.
Wait a minute, I saw a
tattoo on Kurata's hand.
That's right,
a tattoo of a scarab.
[DOJIMA] Look at that.
Even the tattoo is the same!
[SAKAKI] All right, let's assume
that this guy is Kurata.
Why does he keep
goin' after witches?
He does it so he
can live forever.
[ROBIN] If Kurata is
a witch whose powers
are to absorb the life
energy of other witches,
then the cases in Europe
and Japan 120 years ago,
and 40 years ago
in the United States,
and the two we have now
are perhaps all connected.
It's obvious!
This guy has a need
to absorb life energies
from other witches
about every 40 years!
Kinda' like a vampire,
but for witches.
Michael, that hacker you had.
When did he start?
I don't know. Yesterday I think.
Why do you ask?
In the STNJ computer,
there is a giant database
containing a list of witches
and all of their descendants.
If Robin's hypothesis
is correct,
Kurata might very well
be in desperate need
of that list right now.
Then Kurata was responsible
for the hacking?
[AMON] Michael, if there's
another attempt to get in,
don't interfere.
Give him the info
he's looking for.
Huh?
I'll have a surprise for him.
[footsteps]
Robin.
I brought some donuts.
I'll go make some coffee.
Is this what's on
Kurata's tattoo?
[MICHAEL]
It's a scarab.
Yes, I know.
A beetle that was thought of
as a holy creature
in ancient Egypt.
There are reports that
sometimes witches
will use some sort of a symbol
in order to utilize
their powers.
I assume the scarab is the
symbol used by our culprit.
[ROBIN]
Can I ask you something?
[ROBIN] What's the meaning
of the "collar"?
[ROBIN] You know, what
Dojima was talking about.
[MICHAEL]
Oh. What did Miss Dojima say?
[ROBIN] She just said
I should ask you about it.
[MICHAEL]
I see.
[chiming, beeping]
[MICHAEL]
Hold it, we got somethin'!
[ROBIN]
Is it him?
Prob'ly
It's very primitive hacking,
but I guess I'll let
the guy in as planned.
Target confirmed.
[AMON]
Kurata!
[KURATA chuckles]
[KURATA laughs]
[yelps]
Water pipes!
[AMON]
Karasuma, shoot the water pipes!
Damnit!
You're kidding. You just
let him get away?
[SAKAKI]
You got no right to talk.
You ditched us again.
[DOJIMA] So, how come
the Craft didn't hit him?
[DOJIMA]
Hm?
[AMON]
What do you think?
Huh?
About Robin's powers.
Is she just out of control?
Or is she...
This is rather unusual for you.
You're not one to be
concerned about other people.
[phone rings]
[MICHAEL] I'm sorry but
I have some bad news.
The hacker from this morning
was just found dead.
[MICHAEL] I'm pretty sure it
must've been Kurata's doing.
[AMON]
I gotcha.
Well, that's it.
So, I guess we're back
to square one, then, huh?
[AMON]
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I didn't order this.
Japanese miso soup can
help to warm your soul.
Go ahead. It's on the house.
[ROBIN]
Thank you.
[gasps]
[KOBARI chuckles]
[phone rings]
[DOJIMA]
Robin, we've got an emergency!
It happened early this morning.
[DOJIMA]
Can I see it?
It says "the tenth of
June at the lake shore."
[ROBIN]
What's the name of the lake?
I don't know.
There's no way to tell.
Hey, wait a sec. This photo...
Maybe Michael can determine
the location using his database.
[gasps]
[tires screech]
[footsteps]
[AMON]
Hmph.
[SAKAKI grunts]
[grunts] Kurata!
Your... Your face!
[SAKAKI yelps]
[grunts, yells]
Hold it, Kurata! Don't move!
Damn all of you!
[yells]
Robin!
[KURATA yelps]
[KURATA screams]
Are you all right?
Yeah, I think so.
Amon!
[ROBIN]
Thank you.
Huh?
We got him because
you determined
which lake it was, Michael.
Look, I brought you some donuts.
I'll go make some coffee.
[MICHAEL]
I was a hacker once.
[gasps]
But I wasn't what
you call a cracker.
I just liked to sneak through
high-end security systems
to reach terminals that
seemed impossible to reach.
I would never
attack the systems.
I would just leave a small
trace so I could get back in.
That way I could
play around later.
That was it.
Every computer system
all around the world
became my playground.
But then, one day,
I wound up inside a system
that was too much
for me to handle.
And I got trapped.
The STN.
It was amazing.
I... just couldn't believe
what I was dealing with.
I couldn't get myself
out of the system,
even though I tried to logout.
I didn't realize
they were tracing me.
Soon after that, a bunch of guys
came and raided my apartment.
I thought I was history.
In fact, they were actually
gonna kill me right then.
But our boss stopped them.
You mean Zaizen.
[MICHAEL] In exchange
for sparing me my life,
I swore that, from that day on,
I would work for him.
Our boss has a collar on me.
So I'm stuck here.
I can't go anywhere
without his permission.
[gasps]
[phone rings]
[MICHAEL]
Hello?
No way!
[ROBIN]
What's wrong?
Kurata just died
over at the Factory.
[gasps]
[MICHAEL] His corpse turned
into something like sand.
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Beauty in disguise.
Death torn apart.
Pride and intolerance.
Rigorously kept her own world.
Her frozen heart
needs to be thawed.