So, this thing is the
Fragment of Wisdom, huh?
[exhales]
[gasps]
[snaps]
[NAGIRA] It looks to me
like it boosted your power.
[NAGIRA]
This Fragment of Wisdom...
Or rather, the
"Arcanum of the Craft"...
What the hell is it?
Why do you have
something like this?
[ROBIN]
Nagira...
There are some things even
I don't have answers to.
To be very honest, I don't know
if returning this thing to you
is really such a good idea.
I'll admit that
this thing's power
saved my life back there.
But on the other hand,
I may end up just like that guy
depending on how you're
feeling at any given moment.
The thought of one human being
having such incredible power
gives me the willies.
Can you control it?
This power?
Well, can you?
I don't know for sure myself.
[NAGIRA]
Hmph.
There are some people
that I want you to meet.
They might just know
something about this
"Arcanum of the Craft."
[gasps]
I want to meet them.
[NAGIRA]
I'm sorry to make you guys
come all the way out
here like this.
[door clicks, footsteps]
[NAGIRA] This is the girl
I told you about.
[ROBIN]
I'm Robin.
My name is Kannosaki.
[HITOMI]
Uh?
[KANNOSAKI]
And this is my wife...
Huh?
Honey?
[HITOMI]
Uh. Pleased to meet you.
[NAGIRA]
Well, this is it.
[KANNOSAKI]
I'd heard there was an object
that could bestow the inner
secrets on a Witch, but...
Is it all right if I
touch the Fragment?
Um... Of course.
[NAGIRA]
So, what do you think?
I heard that you two
were quite the experts
when it came to Witchcraft.
Well, it just sort of
turned out that way.
Hmm... I believe my wife
might actually know more
about this than I do.
Hitomi, have you seen anything
like this in the library?
Hitomi?
Uh. Yes?
[KANNOSAKI]
Well, have you?
Uh. Hm...
I'm very sorry.
I've never seen it before.
I'm terribly sorry.
Oh, no, that's quite all right.
However, I would ask you two
not to discuss this
matter with anyone else.
[KANNOSAKI]
We understand completely.
We would like nothing more
than to lead a quiet
and peaceful life.
I'm sorry that we
can't help you,
but we really should be going.
Right, Hitomi?
Oh, I apologize.
[KANNOSAKI]
Well, we're off.
[NAGIRA] If you ever need
any help with anything,
give me a call.
[KANNOSAKI]
Thank you, we will.
[door creaks]
[footsteps]
[NAGIRA]
That's too bad.
Well, sometimes coming up
empty can be for the best.
Don't worry about it.
Nagira, tell me, do I have
something on my face?
[NAGIRA]
Huh?
[ROBIN] The whole time they were
here, that woman was just...
...staring at me.
[NAGIRA]
You're imagining things.
It's true, she was!
[NAGIRA]
You're being self-conscious.
I'm not!
[phone chimes]
[NAGIRA]
Hm? Excuse me!
I'm sorry.
[NAGIRA]
I'm heading out for a bit.
[HANAMURA] You gonna go
play Pachinko again?!
This is an important
business call, okay?
You have an appointment
scheduled for this evening--
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Don't worry, I'll be back.
[pachinko machines rattle]
So, whaddya got for me?
[GAMBLER] Word on the street
is that there's this guy
who worked as an errand boy
for old lady Methuselah.
[NAGIRA]
I see.
[GAMBLER] I figure if anybody
knows about the Fragment,
he'd be the one.
They call him Lazarus.
Rumor has it that the old lady
brought him back to life just
as he was about to die.
That's how he got his nickname.
But I hear that
nobody's seen him
around the neighborhood lately,
so if you're trying to find him,
you might want to hurry.
[gasps]
Amon?
But how did you...?
Amon!
[ROBIN gasps]
[panting]
[HANAMURA]
Hey, Robin!
You've got a call from that
woman who was here yesterday!
Are you still sleeping
or something?!
If you don't come down,
I'm hanging up!
You've got 10 seconds!
Nine! Eight!
[ROBIN]
Okay, I've got it.
I'll be right there.
Where is Nagira?
[HANAMURA] He hasn't been
back since he went out.
I wonder where he's
goofing off now?
At his girlfriend's?
Huh?!
[ROBIN] Somebody said
they wanted to meet him.
Oh, that's right!
I totally forgot about that!
What's wrong with me?
I should've thought
of that before!
I really need to keep
a closer eye on him!
I'm going out for a bit.
[HANAMURA]
I wish he'd stop drinking,
gambling, and womanizing
during office hours.
[doorbell chimes]
[ROBIN]
Excuse me.
[HITOMI]
It's open! Please come on in.
Okay.
Hello! I'm so glad
that you came by!
Please, make yourself at home.
Um...
[HITOMI]
I know! I'll make us some tea.
Do you like black tea?
Sure.
[HITOMI] I received some
wonderful black tea a while ago.
But my husband doesn't
notice that kind of thing,
so there's no
point in making it.
Um...
[HITOMI]
Would you like something sweet?
I made you some of your
favorite orange cake today!
Um, about the Fragment, I--
[HITOMI]
Oh, could you wait a moment?
Sorry about that.
All right. Here we are.
This is the one-piece dress
you kept telling me you wanted.
Good thing I got a size 9, huh?
[KANNOSAKI]
Stop that, Hitomi. Please.
But, honey...
Would you please stop it, Dear.
That girl isn't Aya.
[KANNOSAKI]
What are you doing here?
She said that she remembered
something about the Fragment.
Could I have a word
with you alone, please?
[door opens]
[KANNOSAKI]
This was our daughter's room.
We don't use it anymore.
[ROBIN]
What happened to her?
[KANNOSAKI] Well, chances
are that she was hunted.
You see, Aya was a Witch.
You remind my wife of...
I'm sorry.
[KANNOSAKI] I've heard
about you from Mr. Nagira.
This place is
under surveillance.
You shouldn't associate
with us anymore.
[door opens, closes]
[HITOMI cries]
[TECH]
We've been expecting you.
[TECH] How has Solomon HQ
reacted to the attack?
[ZAIZEN] They've done
nothing whatsoever.
[TECH] Perhaps they're waiting
to see what move we will make.
[DIRECTOR] I sincerely doubt
they give us that much credit.
There are rumors that
the attack on the STNJ
means that Solomon headquarters
has cut you loose.
If any more of these negative
rumors continue to spread then
there's a good chance that we'll
end up losing our sponsors.
You'd like to replace
me that badly?
No, sir.
What I'm trying to say is
that perhaps you should refrain
from any overt activity for a
while until things calm down.
The STNJ is safe for now.
But if this place were
ever attacked...
Director. Clearly your true
motivating factor in this
is that you value your life.
And yet, what you don't seem
to understand, Director,
is that this place
is a fortress.
It's not easily captured,
even by an organization
such as Solomon Headquarters.
I realize, but...
[ZAIZEN]
It's time to make a decision.
We will speed up the project.
But certainly you
can't be serious!
[ZAIZEN] Solomon's views on
things will have to change
once they see the results
of the evolved Orbo.
We will no longer need to have
Witches' powers on hunts.
Now is the time to take that
first step towards our ideal.
What's our development status?
We're now getting results
in 97% of our simulations.
Give us authorization
to gather data in combat
and we will move out at once.
[ZAIZEN]
You are so authorized.
I'll forward the STNJ's
hunt list to you.
Begin your preparations.
Yes sir, right away.
I'll expect better
results this time.
[ROBIN]
Huh?
Why am I crying...?
[NAGIRA]
Uh, dammit!
That was close...
Is this guy really down here?
What's that?
Is that it?
Hey there, Lazarus?
[NAGIRA]
You sleepin'?
Excuse me.
[gasps]
Oh, crap.
[gunshots]
Hm?!
[NAGIRA grunts]
If you're gonna kill me,
come on and kill me!
[gunshot]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[footsteps]
[NAGIRA]
Hmph!
So that was just a warning, huh?
[NAGIRA]
Listen up, buddy!
I'm sending you
my cleaning bill...
...Amon!
[doorbell chimes]
Why are you here?
I was just passing by.
[KANNOSAKI]
It's you...
[ROBIN] I'd like to talk some
more, if you don't mind.
Please, come in!
Honey? She can come
in for just a little bit, right?
[HITOMI] I was just starting
to make us some dinner.
Is there anything
you don't like?
No, not really.
[HITOMI]
Oh, good!
In that case,
I'll make my specialty!
Thank you very much.
Huh?
[KANNOSAKI] It seems like
it's been forever since
I last saw her this happy.
You see, she's been crying
ever since you left yesterday.
Actually, she's been crying ever
since we lost our daughter.
Maybe I've been pretending
not to notice all this time...
I ignore it...
Because there's nothing
at all I can do to help.
[ROBIN]
Would you mind if...
...I asked about Aya?
[KANNOSAKI] It was three years
ago that her powers awakened.
Her abilities were very weak,
hardly enough to make
a pencil roll around.
But it was an unwanted power.
So we used every means
at our disposal
to find out if we could
make it go away.
In the end, we were
never able to find a way.
And then one day, she went
off to school as usual,
and we've never seen
our daughter since.
The STNJ calls
people like us "Seeds"
and keeps us under
constant surveillance.
And if we show signs
of powers, however faint,
we're ratted out, and our
very existence is erased.
Did you look for her?
We looked everywhere.
For months and months.
We even asked the media
and the police to help.
But all of them ignored us.
The only person who ever
offered us a helping hand
during that time was Mr. Nagira.
[KANNOSAKI]
My wife...
She had been fighting with
Aya over whether or not
to buy this new
dress right up until
the morning she disappeared...
My wife has regretted not
buying it for her ever since.
[HITOMI]
I'm so sorry.
I've neglected to entertain you.
[ROBIN]
Um... Let me help you.
Thank you.
But do you think you
might be able
to do something else for me?
[ROBIN]
Hmm?
I wonder if she'll
like this or not?
She just might.
--[clattering]
--[gasps]
[whimpers]
[HITOMI]
Darling.
When did you...?
[KANNOSAKI]
I'm sorry.
I might not be around
for much longer, I'm afraid.
[HANAMURA]
Mr. Nagira...
Well, you're back
early for once.
[NAGIRA]
Yeah.
[HANAMURA]
Just, "Yeah"?
Oh! You stink!
Mr. Nagira, where did you
pick up that stench?!
I'm sending that to
the cleaners--
[NAGIRA]
Where's Robin?
She went out to see that
couple from yesterday.
What did you say?
[ZAIZEN] They tell me you'll
be able to leave soon.
Where's Amon now?
You'd do best to forget him.
Don't go after him.
So then what do you
plan to do with him?
He is very different from us.
He's still a human being.
I have a special duty to
preserve the purity of humanity.
[ZAIZEN] I've put together
everything you'll need.
Touko, put this behind you
and make a new
life for yourself.
[ROBIN] I'm sorry for intruding
on you this evening.
[HITOMI] I'd like for you
to have this dress.
Please, keep it.
I'll come visit again.
Of course!
Well. Goodbye.
[door closes]
--Uh!
--[breaks squeak]
I forgot my--
Do you really think she'll
come by to visit us again?
It's going to be
all right, honey.
I'm sure she--
[KANNOSAKI]
Hm?
[footsteps]
Hitomi, go out
the back, quickly.
No, I won't.
[KANNOSAKI]
Hm?
[HITOMI] I'm staying. I refuse
to lose anyone else.
Hitomi...
[knocking]
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
It can't be...
Those people were just...
[NAGIRA]
Robin!
What are you doing?
Nagira...
They've both disappeared.
[ROBIN]
That couple, they...
They were just here,
and now they're gone!
[ROBIN cries]
[NAGIRA]
And then?
[ROBIN] I was sent to Japan
by Solomon headquarters
in order to retrieve
the Fragment of Wisdom.
Working as a hunter at
the STNJ was camouflage.
It was my cover
for that mission.
[NAGIRA] So in other words,
nobody outside of headquarters
was supposed to know
about you, right?
[ROBIN]
I retrieve the Fragment,
hand it over to a messenger
from headquarters,
and my mission
would be complete.
That's how it was
supposed to work.
However...
...it didn't end up
working out that way.
You're saying the
attack on the STNJ
wasn't because
of the Fragment?
If they wanted it,
all they had to do
was wait for me
to give it to them.
[NAGIRA] So you have no
idea what kind of power
this thing actually contains?
I was only assigned to retrieve
the Fragment and bring it back.
There was no need for me
to know what was in it.
[NAGIRA sighs]
Nagira...
...look after it for me.
Hey, wait a minute,
this is your wild card.
[ROBIN]
I know that.
But, right now,
I know I won't be able to
keep that power in check.
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
The visitor of death.
The nightmare of
the sacred goblet.
Lost hopes.
The silent hunter chuckles at
last from within the darkness.