[NARUMI pants]
[NARUMI gasps]
[panting]
[BOTH gasp]
[NARUMI groans]
[gasps]
[NARUMI gasps]
You must take
hold of the light eternal.
You must light the
man over there.
Deliver the power of
all eternity...
...from men of times
long since past.
Well, I hafta say:
you've been a real pain.
Look on the bright side.
It's much better
to die in obscurity.
This'll help ease your mind.
[NARUMI]
Heh.
[BOTH gasp]
[NARUMI snarls]
What the hell?!
[gasps]
Damn you!
[NARUMI chuckles]
[BOTH grunt]
[SAKAKI]
This is strange.
I mean, for the Factory
to be moving in so quickly...
[MICHAEL]
The police tipped them off.
The police are actually
cooperating with us?
Well, that's a new one.
[MICHAEL] According to their
regulations, they have to.
Well, they're supposed to...
and they say they do.
But don't you
think that deep down,
they figure we're just
a big pain in the neck?
[MICHAEL]
If you think so,
why don't you tell
the Factory directly?
[SAKAKI]
What about Amon and the others?
[MICHAEL]
They're already there.
[SAKAKI]
Gotcha.
[WORKER]
Take the tape off!
[AMON]
About the victim's condition...
The internal damage is
much worse than the external?
Yeah. Come on;
careful, you guys!
Is this the work of a witch?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
that's what we're lookin' at.
[AMON]
Pretty sure?
Yeah, there's an old case here
that sounds pretty
similar to me.
That witch could
create microwaves
that were strong enough to kill.
I'd say it's a good bet
that the witch we're looking for
is very similar--
Hey! Don't touch anything!
We've still got
a lot of things to check!
[AMON]
You alone?
No, but there's
a lot of traffic right now...
Where's the victim?
They're just starting
the investigation.
Do you want to watch?
[SAKAKI]
Eh...
I think I'll pass.
[sniffs]
[gasps]
So that means
this witch would be sort of
like an electric eel.
[SAKAKI]
Yeah, you could say that.
Apparently, this is
not the first time.
There was one years ago.
[MICHAEL] Well, it was 22 years
ago, so it's a bit old, but...
...far as I can tell,
it's basically
the same kind of
thing as this one.
Then shouldn't we be
looking at his descendants?
The probability of
a power like this
being inherited has
to be awfully high.
I don't think that's gonna
help us this time.
You see, back then,
the hunting was different.
So, logically there
shouldn't be any descendants.
[KARASUMA] Could there be a
connection with someone else?
--We know there are incidents...
--What do you have there?
[ROBIN] It was at the
scene of the incident.
At the scene of the...?
You took something away
from there without asking?!
[ROBIN]
Is that bad?
What do you mean,
"Is that bad"?!
[DOJIMA chuckles]
I'd say it's likely... that
the witch is still somewhere
in that area right now.
Since we don't have any leads,
we'll just have to keep
looking at everything.
[SAKAKI] And how's that gonna
work in a maze like that place?
It might not
in a normal situation.
But we're not looking
for a normal human,
now, are we?
[SAKAKI]
Uh.
[DOJIMA grunts]
[MICHAEL]
150,000 people...
It's amazing to
think that so many people
can actually live in
such a tiny area.
Maybe this is impossible...
I've gotta say, it's an
awful lot like looking for
a needle in a haystack.
Remember,
most witches are loners.
[MICHAEL]
Huh?
It's part of their nature.
Normal humans can
blend into the crowd,
but witches
aren't able to do that...
And that makes them vulnerable.
[sniffing]
[OLD WOMAN] Even if you do that,
you will not find what you seek.
What makes you say that?
And how did you know
what I was doing?
It happens
when you grow older...
You can see many things
you couldn't see before.
It happens
when you grow older...
It's really quite astounding.
What is?
Never mind. Not important.
Let us leave it at that.
You are not from
around here.
You should bear that in mind;
in fact, you might consider
leaving this place.
[ROBIN]
I won't be in any danger here.
[OLD WOMAN] True enough,
you should not be...
But, I cannot say the same
for the people around you.
What does this have
to do with them?
[phone rings]
I'm sorry, but it looks
like I need to stay here
for a little while longer.
Goodbye.
Where's the victim?
I figure the people who live
here must have taken him.
Yep, it's that kinda
place, wouldn't ya say?
Whatever's happening,
let's keep a low profile
until we can get some backup.
Do you feel something?
I felt this huge burst
of psychic energy here
just a little while ago,
but I'm not reading
anything right now.
[gasps]
It's just like the
one from the other day.
[NARUMI grunts]
[NARUMI gasps]
[MEN gasp, groan]
[MEN rasping]
[NARUMI gasps]
That's the third one...
At least this
was done during the day.
With any luck, there'll be
witnesses this time.
Well, I certainly hope
something like that turns up.
If we don't get a break,
it's gonna be hard to keep
the police out of it.
[knocking]
How did it go?
It was a waste of time.
Doesn't matter what I
ask 'em, I can't even get
any of these people
to say a word to me.
What about Dojima and Robin?
They're with the
Factory guys right now.
Apparently, they had this
light bulb they wanted
to get checked out.
A light bulb?
Something they found
at the last crime site.
What's with him?
[WORKER] What I want you
to notice is the pattern
of the burn on top of the bulb.
It's also obvious to
see that it was just made.
Are you saying
is that it was burned off
by the witch's powers?
Well, I wouldn't say directly,
but I wouldn't be surprised
if the microwaves from
the witch created a current
that lit up the bulbs that
had already burnt out,
and then they, in turn, charred
the whole area.
Should we think of it
as some kinda immense power?
Yeah.
[AMON] There's something
else to consider.
We can be pretty certain
that this witch isn't able
to fully control his powers yet.
It's a lot of unfocussed energy.
Sorta like Robin was.
Otherwise, there's
no explanation for
all the damage to the
surrounding area.
[MICHAEL]
Is that you, Amon?
Michael, what are you
doing right now?
[MICHAEL] I'm checking the
background of the victims...
[AMON]
You can do that later.
There's something
I want you to do instead.
[MICHAEL]
What's that?
The electrical power where
these incidents took place.
I want you to check
if the voltage was above
regulations at any
of the locations.
[MICHAEL]
Well, okay, but...
[AMON] And hurry.
I need to know right away.
The first victims were
a couple of guys who were
after him, so we
know why he did that.
But the third one
was likely just someone
who lived nearby.
So in other words,
now that he's been cornered,
he's beginning to take it out
on innocent bystanders.
At the moment, he most
likely believes that everyone
he sees is out to get him.
[MICHAEL]
Got it!
Here it is Amon;
somebody's crankin' out
some serious voltage there.
It looks like it's underground.
Sakaki.
[SAKAKI]
I got the coordinates!
You want us to get over
there and see if we can
find this witch, right?
[AMON]
That's right. Hurry!
[SAKAKI] This isn't a Vespa,
so you better hold on tight!
[MAN 11C] I dunno
how you managed to whack
my friends like that;
but it's time to say goodbye.
[NARUMI chuckles]
[MAN 11C gasps]
[gasps]
[NARUMI giggles]
[panting]
[MAN 11C pants, grunts]
[NARUMI giggles]
[MAN 11C]
Hey, wait a sec. Gimme a break.
Look, it's nothing personal,
okay? Come on.
I was sent over here
by the syndicate! Here!
Hey, listen to me, buddy.
You wanna get out of
this dump and I can help ya.
You need a guy
who knows this place or
you're never gonna make it!
Do ya hear me? You'll be rottin'
in this hellhole forever!
If you don't know
this place, you're through!
Don't do it...
I don't wanna die yet!
I'm beggin' ya, buddy!
I'm beggin ya!
You humans, hah...
[MAN 11C whimpers]
[MAN 11C wails]
[NARUMI chukcles]
[NARUMI]
Who the hell are you?!
So you're the one!
You're the guy who's been
causing all this trouble lately!
[yells]
[SAKAKI groans]
--[grunts]
--[shots fired]
[yells]
[SAKAKI grunting]
[gasps]
[NARUMI screams]
[MAN 11C whimpers]
[NARUMI pants]
[NARUMI chuckles]
[yells]
[NARUMI gasps]
[SAKAKI pants]
Robin!
[NARUMI grunts]
[gasps]
[NARUMI groans]
[wails]
Sakaki reporting in.
This hunt is now over.
[MAN 11C whimpers]
[ROBIN]
Oh... Amon?
Are you here alone?
Yeah...
What're you doing here so late?
[ROBIN] I was over at Harry's
place for a while, that's all...
--What about you?
--[AMON] Oh...
I was just going over
the information that
Michael found on
that witch earlier.
The one from today?
So what did you happen
to find out about him?
Juzo Narumi, 33 years old...
As it turns out,
he was a distant relative
of the witch Michael mentioned.
So you mean
that he was actually on
the STN's list after all?
[AMON]
That seems to be the case.
[ROBIN]
Hmm...
But it's strange.
[AMON]
Hm?
Well, you'd think that
someone with that much power
would be a little closer to
the top of the suspect list.
They said there
were basically no signs
that Narumi had
powers up until now.
What do they mean
"basically no signs"?
And if he had all that power,
how could he hide it?
Do you suppose he was
just awakened to his craft?
[gasps]
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing...
When all is finally
said and done...
...the words of time proved
far too heavy a burden...
However...
You are...
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Enchanting voice, forgotten
past, time sunk in darkness...
Deep down in murky water,
I touch the soul that
has wandered in eternity.