[DOJIMA]
Here ya' go, boss.
Table three wants to add
a Milano-style cutlet and a
seafood salad to their order.
Right. Table number three.
Hm?
[MAN 10A] I've been here
before. It's a good place.
[WOMAN 10A]
It looks nice.
Looks like we've
got more customers.
Go ahead and seat them.
[DOJIMA]
My pleasure!
[chipping ice]
[MAN 10B]
You do that well.
You've got the makings
of a good bartender.
Though you might
be a little young.
Thank you.
[chipping ice]
[typing]
[MICHAEL grunts]
Anything?
[MICHAEL]
No. Nothin' yet.
Huh?
--What?
--Here's something.
The automatic detection system
has found a possible match.
[KARASUMA]
This guy?
[MICHAEL]
Height: 174 centimeters,
weight: 59 kilograms.
This guy definitely
fits the physical data
that we were given.
[CUSTOMERS murmur]
[TAKANO sighs]
[TAKANO gasps]
[KOBARI]
Oh, Mr. Takano!
What a surprise!
[TAKANO]
Yes, well...
I just happened
to be in the area.
I see that you've
hired some new help.
[KOBARI chuckles]
Actually they're
my regular customers.
It looks like we're in
for a long one tonight.
[KARASUMA]
So, you're back?
Yeah.
Well, it looks like you
spent the night here.
No.
I just got back in
from headquarters.
The managers?
[KARASUMA]
Any new developments?
I see.
I don't know if this is
worth reporting or not
but Yutaka Kobari
never showed.
We we're up all night waiting
for him and nothing happened.
[AMON]
I see.
[SAKAKI]
Good morning!
Hey, Miss Karasuma.
Well, you came prepared today.
[SAKAKI]
Uh?
Oh.
[ROBIN]
It's really dead in here.
Sure is.
[KOBARI]
You two look terribly bored.
[ROBIN]
Just feeling time.
What'd you say?
[ROBIN]
By the way...
Is it... okay for this
place to be so empty?
Well, I don't quite
know about that.
But seeing how I've managed
to keep the place going,
it can't be bad.
Oh, I see. I guess
that means you must be
some kind of a miracle worker.
You may have meant
that as a compliment
but that's not how it sounded.
[KOBARI]
Hm?
Ah, good afternoon, sir.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[growls]
[video game sounds]
[slurps]
[SAKAKI sighs]
Hey, so where do you think
the chief was headin' out to?
[slurping]
Ya know, our chief,
the guy that you--
[HATTORI] I heard you.
But I was a little busy.
In case you hadn't noticed,
I was sipping my tea.
Please forgive me.
But you know, if you hear me,
you don't gotta ignore me.
Huh? Did you say something?
Nope. I didn't say a thing.
So, about the chief--
[HATTORI] Don't be redundant.
I heard you the first time.
The chief is over
at Harry's right now.
[SAKAKI]
He is?!
[HATTORI]
He went to check on the girls.
They're always causing problems,
and now we've sent
them over there.
[slurping]
[HATTORI] Since we are the ones
who are responsible for them,
we must keep track of them.
So, that's why he looked
like he was all wound-up.
[HATTORI]
Sorry, we're you speaking to me?
Nope. It was nothing.
I just hope that
what he sees at Harry's
doesn't send him back
here in bad mood.
Yes, me too.
Uh?!
[HATTORI chuckles]
[KOSAKA]
Look at you!
This is exactly what
I was afraid of!
That you would just
sit around and do nothing.
[KOBARI]
Please, Mr. Kosaka...
This isn't what it looks like.
The girls have been
working hard for me.
I just gave them a break,
now that it's
finally calmed down.
[gasps]
Tell me this, Dojima!
Why is it normally
you're barely able
to drag yourself
to work every day,
and yet you manage to pull
12-hour shifts at this place?!
Wow, Chief, you look
more worked up than usual.
Does that mean you miss me?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
[ROBIN]
Dojima.
Maybe the Chief sort of
misses having someone
to toss anger into.
Huh?!
Robin...
You've an odd way of
stringing words together.
Huh? You really think so?
[DOJIMA]
You're pretty weird.
--[ROBIN] I am?
--[KOSAKA sighs]
[beeping]
[phone rings]
[MICHAEL]
What's up?
[AMON]
Around what time
did you get that possible
match last night?
[MICHAEL] It was right after
we did the routine checkup,
so it must have been
somewhere around 21:30.
Is that all?
Yeah.
Huh?
[AMON] Call everyone to
the briefing room right away.
[AMON]
Here.
Take a look at the
footage from last night.
This is when the suspect
enters the restaurant.
[AMON] Notice the guy
sitting at this table.
Just for a moment...
he reacted to the suspect
as he entered.
What's that mean?
If you remember...
we suspected this guy
because we thought that he
looked like Yutaka Kobari.
[gasps]
I still don't get it.
You mind clueing
the rest of us in?
He reacted to this guy
'cause he thought he
was Yutaka Kobari, too.
[gasps]
Then that means
someone other than us
is also lookin' for Kobari!
Check the footage
from the past few days
and see if last night
was the first time
this guy's been to Harry's
or if he's been there
every night waiting for him.
I'm on it.
[KARASUMA]
Yutaka Kobari became a witch
that the STNJ had targeted
around two years ago.
[KARASUMA] The informant
was the owner of Harry's.
And Yutaka was his son.
Yutaka trusted and confided
in his father about his powers.
Kobari managed
to escape the STNJ
and then completely disappeared.
[AMON]
About six months later,
stories began to surface
regarding a series murders
in the U.S. that bore
a strong resemblance
to his style of killing.
Yutaka Kobari had
moved to the United States
and become a hit man
for this organization.
However, eight days ago,
the STN headquarters
received word
of new activity on him.
It appears that Yutaka Kobari
has secretly re-entered Japan.
[SAKAKI]
Amon!
He has been there!
You were right.
[liquid gurgles]
[gasps]
[DOJIMA]
Hey, what's wrong, Boss?
Huh? Oh, it's nothing.
[TOUKO]
This is typical.
From out of nowhere you decided
to call and ask me where
I am and what I'm doing.
[AMON]
I'm sorry.
That's new.
[AMON] I haven't been
able to sleep lately.
There's a new case.
[AMON] It's actually a case
from a couple of years ago
that's come back.
For some reason,
I'm having a hard time
trying to stay focused on it.
My mind wanders
and I find myself
thinking of you.
Strange.
[AMON]
Yeah.
Not that.
What I think is strange is that
you're actually willing
to admit this to me.
[AMON] I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
[TOUKO] I was wondering when
you were going to say that.
[TOUKO]
Can I ask you one thing?
What's that?
[TOUKO]
Do you--
[inaudible]
[ROBIN]
Here.
It's on the house.
[phone vibrates]
[MICHAEL]
He's leaving.
[SAKAKI]
Huh?
[KARASUMA]
Enlarge it.
[SAKAKI]
But...
Why's he's leavin'
so early tonight?
Damn it!
[SAKAKI] He's been waiting
for days and he leaves now?
The man with
the trench coat left.
[MICHAEL]
I know.
And nothing seemed to happen.
He's walking out
the front door now.
Maybe he just
gave up early tonight.
[MICHAEL]
Maybe.
After all, he has been waiting
there for over a week.
[KOBARI] Oh, Miss Robin...
That customer's all right.
I'll wake him up
a little bit later.
It's getting rather late.
Why don't you help
clean up as well
so you two can go on home?
Uh, sure.
[sirens blare]
You were finally able
to get 'em to leave.
I take it you received
the message I sent you?
[YUTAKA]
What's wrong?
Why don't you
say anything to me?
Or... are you afraid of me?
Is that it?
I don't know.
Maybe. I might be afraid.
Hmph.
Maybe you feel guilty
'cause you betrayed me.
[YUTAKA]
Anyway it's pretty pathetic.
A father who's
afraid of his own son.
[typing]
Oh, hey. Welcome back.
[AMON]
Has everyone gone home already?
Yeah.
They've been puttin' in
a lotta hours this week.
Guess they wanted to
get home early for once.
Early?
Yeah.
The guy with the trench coat.
He decided to bail outta
Harry's pretty early tonight.
For some reason.
[AMON] Let me see
the footage of the guy
leaving the restaurant.
Huh?
So, tell me,
do you still resent me?
Resent you?
I guess I do.
It's true that I hated
you for a long time.
When I left this country,
I dreamed about nothing else
but coming back here
and killing you.
Do you know how it feels
to be treated like a monster
then thrown away like garbage?!
I am... still a human being.
I just happened to have
gained some extra powers.
And because of that...
...you threw me away.
I kept thinking,
"I'll kill him!"
"Someday I'll go back to Japan
and force the same
terror upon him
that he turned upon me."
That's what kept me going.
Then, I finally let it go.
[YUTAKA groans]
[KOBARI]
Yutaka!
[YUTAKA whimpers]
[YUTAKA] Are you really
going to call me...
...by my human name? [groans]
You must believe me
when I tell you this.
I tried very hard to
ignore your powers
and convince myself that
you were a normal man.
Then one day...
I realized that your
powers had become
so developed that I simply
could no longer deny them.
I knew it was only
a matter of time
before your powers took over
and you'd start
hurting other people.
It was my tainted blood
that did this to you,
and I knew I had to stop it.
[YUTAKA]
I know that.
But... I was in the U.S.
before I understood.
The only thing this power
is good for is killing people--
[YUTAKA groans]
[YUTAKA] He got me on the way
in, and it's starting to...
[KOBARI]
Yutaka, it's all right.
You don't have to
say another word.
It's not... all right.
I didn't think
that I would survive...
...as long as I have.
The people I work for...
They have no problem killing
anyone who betrays them.
"Betrays them"?
I... I betrayed
the organization.
[gasping]
I felt I had to see you...
just one more time.
I wanted to tell you that...
...that I'm sorry.
[KOBARI]
Yutaka!
Forgive me... Father...
[KOBARI sobs]
You're too late.
I didn't betray
my own son because
I was afraid of the power
that runs through his blood.
What I was afraid of...
was my own blood.
And what powers that I may
have lurking within myself.
I have no right...
to call myself... a father.
Why do you think
Miss Dojima is so late?
[ROBIN]
She said she was bored.
I believe she's very
easily attractive.
I think you mean to say,
"very easily distracted."
[ROBIN sighs]
Want one?
[ROBIN]
Mm.
May I... ask something?
Sure. Go ahead.
I wanted to ask you how
you felt about your son.
You must mean when I found out
about Yutaka's powers. Right?
I'm not really sure.
Two years can seem
so very long ago
when you're faced with
something like this.
It was a confusing time for me.
But there is one thing
that I know for certain.
And that is...
he truly was my son.
[gasps]
He "was"?
[liquid gurgles]
[NARRATOR]
Three hundred and twenty years
have passed since the
coven sank in the dark.
Walled city.
Those who had
forgotten their past.
Wandering runaways.
The child of the darkness
who strays there will
be judged by the soul
called "Eternal."