[AMON] You're certain that it
was a Factory prison van?
[DOJIMA]
I'm positive.
Plus, Miho and the others
weren't working
a case last night.
What the hell has
Zaizen started now?
Amon...
Exactly... how much
did you learn
about Zaizen at headquarters?
[AMON]
Hmm...
Do you know his intentions?
I thought it was to hunt
witches using Orbo.
Well, that's only half of it.
[AMON]
Hmm?
[DOJIMA] His real objective is
to develop a new type of Orbo
that would allow an ordinary
human to hunt witches.
[gasps]
It's true.
Zaizen's working
on it as we speak.
[AMON]
Now that you mention it,
there has been a sudden
spike in Factory activity.
[DOJIMA]
You've been watching?
[AMON]
I keep my eye on them.
[DOJIMA]
Hmm...
There's something about this
I still don't understand.
Why would headquarters
be afraid of this?
It seems to me that using
normal humans to hunt Witches
is right in line with
Solomon's ideology.
Are you gonna stake them out?
[DOJIMA] We need to find out for
sure whether or not the Factory
has started using Orbo that can
be used by normal humans.
[AMON]
I see.
[door opens]
Where are you going?
To get confirmation.
If anything happens, call me.
You're really in no position
to order me around, ya know...
[AMON]
Huh?
Don't worry. I'll call
if anything happens.
Oh man, what am I gonna
do about this guy?
[ROBIN]
"August 30th.
At long last, the truth
finally lies before us.
This tiny mutation is
the Devil's true form."
[pages turn]
[ROBIN]
"October 5th. After further
consideration, I fear I may have
been making a grave mistake.
I'm afraid that our
God has turned away
and completely forsaken us."
[ROBIN]
Uh?
I wonder what was written here?
[ROBIN]
What was he doing with Juliano?
[crow caws]
It's morning already?
[MICHAEL]
It looks like there was
an intensive genetic
research program
being conducted at Solomon
HQ's special R&amp;D facility.
[SAKAKI]
At Solomon?
[KARASUMA] Yes, but over the
past few years, there's been
a huge boom in genetic
research all over the world.
It's hardly surprising
that an organization
with Solomon's financial muscle
got involved in it as well.
Only if their goal was the same
as other research agencies.
What do you mean?
[MICHAEL]
Apparently, Solomon succeeded
in mapping the human genome
more than five years
before any other research
agency could do it.
However, it turns out
that their research project
was disbanded right
after the discovery
and their findings were
never published.
That order came
from Solomon, right?
I can understand why they
wanted to go public,
but why was the project
itself suddenly aborted?
See, strange isn't it?
You think it's related to Orbo?
Bingo! That's exactly
what I was thinking!
[KARASUMA]
So let me get this straight.
What you're saying, Michael, is
that headquarters attacked us
because they don't approve
of Orbo development, right?
It's not like I have
any hard evidence,
but after digging around
here and there,
I have to come
to that conclusion.
[KARASUMA] But I still don't
understand what would make them
hate the very idea of Orbo?
Beats me.
But if you think about it,
we use Orbo all the time
for hunting even though we
don't really know what it is.
I never really thought
about that before.
[KARASUMA]
Say...
--[SAKAKI] Hm?
--[MICHAEL] Huh?
Nah, just forget it.
I was...
I was just thinking that
if it really was HQ
that attacked us that day,
then they think the
Orbo is dangerous
and they'll probably go to any
length to stop us from using it.
Hey, stop that.
You're freakin' me out.
Okay? Uh...
[HANAMURA]
Hmph.
[inhales]
Wake up girl!
How long are you
gonna stay in bed,
you juvenile delinquent!
Oh, hi there. Good morning.
[HANAMURA] Well, I'd hardly
call this morning!
Do you know what time it is?!
This is bad. I overslept.
[HANAMURA]
Where's the boss?!
"The boss"?
[HANAMURA]
Both of you were out until
all hours last night,
weren't you?!
I know all about
you two, ya know!
[ROBIN]
I don't know.
Is that the truth?
[ROBIN]
I don't know.
[HANAMURA]
Hmm...
Darn it, we've got clients
coming into the office soon!
Hirata!
Go check the pachinko machines
at the International Center!
[footsteps]
[HANAMURA]
Hmph.
You really don't
know where he is?
[ROBIN]
No, I don't.
[DOJIMA laughing]
[NAGIRA] So she burned the guy's
hair right off his head?
[DOJIMA]
She sure did!
If she's not wearing
her glasses,
she'll set just about
anything on fire!
--[door clicks]
--[NAGIRA laughs]
Considering he's
your big brother,
this geezer's pretty cool, Amon.
Hey! Who you callin' a geezer?
Well, go ahead and continue
last night's little
heart-to-heart.
I guess I'll get out
of your hair now.
Buh-bye!
See ya later, Yurika!
You, me, and Robin oughta
have a barbecue someti--
Looks to me like this
whole situation
is getting more complicated
than I thought.
[STAFF 23A] For the time
being, the Japan branch
isn't showing any
overt activity.
[ZAIZEN] Seeing which way
the wind blows, hm?
In any case, they're bound to
show some activity soon enough.
If anything happens,
contact me immediately.
[STAFF 23A]
Yes, sir.
Also, according to the
intelligence division's report,
the STNJ was definitely
responsible for the system
intrusion the other day.
[ZAIZEN]
I see.
[STAFF 23A]
What would you like us to do?
[ZAIZEN] Don't worry about it,
I'll deal with it.
But make sure to keep them
under close surveillance.
[STAFF 23A]
I understand.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
[TECH]
Not at all, sir.
[ZAIZEN] From what you told
me about the incident,
I'm to understand that
the damage was caused
by some sort of mismatch?
[TECH]
Yes sir.
We believe that the
character of the test subject
is rejecting the
lingering traces
of Witch individuality
present in the Orbo.
This causes the symptoms
we have seen to manifest.
[ZAIZEN] Is there any
way to confirm this?
[TECH] Not unless we are able to
get a little more clinical data.
So you're saying that we should
continue our human testing.
Humans aren't the
same as Witches.
But, sir--
[ZAIZEN] At any rate,
I'll have to give the order
to restrict Orbo usage to known
safe levels for the time being.
Even with the lower levels,
our results ought to be enough
to shut up the skeptics that
keep raising such a stink.
Yes, sir.
If you'll excuse me...
[ZAIZEN grunts]
I should get back to work.
I can't afford to
waste any more time
dealing with this matter either.
[NAGIRA]
So tell me.
Do you still hate Dad as much?
[AMON]
Our father?
I'd be lying if I said
that I wasn't bitter,
but I suppose you can't
really hold a grudge
for years against a man
you've never even seen.
I'd forgotten all about him
until you brought him up.
So you're angry with
your mother, then?
I'll be honest with you, she was
a complete stranger to me,
but from what I did
know of her she
seemed like a pretty nice lady.
Even if she was a Seed.
Is it because
the man your mother
chose to be your father
happened to be a Witch?
[AMON]
She was...
She was always kind to me.
The life of a Seed never
really seemed that bad.
Even if my father wasn't there,
it was enough as long
as she was with me.
But I was wrong.
[NAGIRA]
That little incident, huh?
[AMON]
Yes...
My mother awakened as a Witch.
And she did it right in
front of my very eyes.
And after that day,
I just couldn't get
through to her anymore.
And that's why you
hate your mother.
No, that's why you hate all
witches in general don't you.
[AMON]
I doubt you'd understand.
How could you possibly
understand the fear of her blood
that's lying dormant inside me.
It could awaken at any moment,
just like hers did.
Because I'm human
I can't understand?
Witches, Seeds,
whatever you call 'em,
they keep showin' up at my door
for some reason one
right after another,
and of all the ones
that have come to me,
none of them look
any different than humans.
Besides, I'm your bother
and I have Dad's blood
pumping in me, just
the same as you.
It's not as simple
a thing as saying,
"That person's a witch"
and "this person isn't one."
Your mother chose Dad
as much as he chose her.
So doesn't that prove
to you just how much
she was really in
love with the guy?
[NAGIRA] So... What are you
gonna do about the girl?
Remember now,
you were the one
who asked me to help
her in the first place.
That's why I hired
her as a messenger.
I thought you'd
finally realized that.
[AMON] The situation
has changed since then.
[NAGIRA]
What situation?
[AMON]
You see...
There's a secret that Robin
knows that we don't.
A secret, huh?
So that's the reason you've
stayed hot on her trail.
But I have a funny feeling
that Robin doesn't know
what that secret is herself.
[AMON]
Just as I thought...
[NAGIRA]
What's making you hesitate?
They're hunting her.
Solomon is chasing Robin
and she doesn't know why.
In order to hunt her, I have
to know about everything.
I need to know the truth.
[NAGIRA] Assuming you
find out this "truth,"
would you be able to hunt her?
Forget it.
With her power, you're nowhere
near a match for Robin.
Yes, I know that!
But it doesn't matter.
I have to find the answer.
[NAGIRA]
Hmph.
Get goin'.
Robin's too much
for me to handle now.
I'm givin' her back to you.
[car starts]
[door opens]
[gasps]
Uh. Hey, wait a minute, what
do you think you're doing?!
You're tailing Amon, right?
Wrong answer.
Too bad. I guess you can't trust
a lawyer's intuition, either.
Hey, cut me some slack!
Well, where are you going then?
To the Factory.
[NAGIRA]
The Factory?
That's right. Does it scare you?
[NAGIRA]
Huh?
Nah, let's get outta here.
[SAKAKI]
I'm gonna head home now.
How about you, Ms. Karasuma?
I think I'm going to stay
and do a little more digging.
I'll see if the police
know anything about this.
[SAKAKI]
I don't think it'll do any good.
I'll check, just in case.
[SAKAKI]
If you say so. Well, good night.
See ya later, Michael.
[MICHAEL]
Yeah.
[tires squeal]
I guess I should...
I should go over there and
ask about that picture...
Nagira might have gone over
there to do some digging, too.
[footsteps]
[knocking]
Uh?
Nagira?
[gasps]
[AMON]
If you use your Craft...
...you could incinerate
me before I shoot.
Amon...
I can't believe you'd actually
do something this illegal.
This organization of
yours is really--
[DOJIMA] It's not my
organization, okay?
Huh?
[ROBIN] You saved me from
being captured back then.
[AMON] That's true, but that
may have been a mistake.
So you think that I'm a Witch?
[AMON] That's what
headquarters believes.
[ROBIN]
What do you believe, Amon?
My instructions come from
a special person at Solomon.
He ordered me to hunt you.
That person is the most
influential hunter trainer
at Solomon. He's also the man
who raised you, Juliano Colegli.
He was the one
who ordered the hunt.
You're lying...
[AMON]
It's not a lie.
Father Juliano gave
me specific orders.
There was no hesitation
in his voice.
"Robin has gained
dangerous power
through the Craft Arcanum.
She must be hunted."
That can't be...
Father would never say...
But that's--
You were the one who
took the letter Amon?
[AMON]
If I hadn't read this letter
right before they attacked
you at your apartment,
I might not have saved you.
[ROBIN]
Uh.
I can read it?
Father...
But, this letter is...
[AMON] A confession
to one about to die.
At first, I wasn't able to
understand it, either.
What the Father wrote in there
is a jumbled mix of
fear and love for you.
As well as regret.
Father Juliano is afraid of me?
But... why?
How could he be afraid of me?
[AMON] When I stood in front
of him at headquarters,
I could feel that
something didn't add up.
How could the man who
wrote you that letter be
the same person who
coldly explained to me
the need to hunt you.
The Arcanum has given
you a dangerous power.
And it's clear from that letter,
that the Father was
afraid of something.
But despite that,
it seemed that his fear
stemmed from your
very existence.
[ROBIN]
My existence?
I had to find out for myself
what his intentions were.
I tracked Toudou and
found out about your past.
[ROBIN]
So that Toudou person
has something to
do with my past?
[paper crinkles]
I'm sorry Amon, but if you
can't have faith in me...
...and if you honestly think
that I'm such a dangerous
Witch, then go ahead.
[ROBIN]
I have faith...
I have faith in
your heart, Amon.
[AMON grunts]
I suppose that is my answer.
That's your answer, Amon?
[phone rings]
What is it?
Hey, Amon. They look like
they're on the move.
They just drove out of the gate.
[AMON]
I see.
Try to follow them, Dojima.
I'll make sure to
meet up with you soon.
[ROBIN]
Did something happen?
It's the Factory.
"The Factory"?
[AMON]
An assault team just left.
You coming?
[DOJIMA] One of the vans split
off in a different direction.
The one we're following
seems to be tailing a bike.
I wonder if they'll keep
heading towards the coast?
Our location is--
[ROBIN] A technology to hunt
Witches without using hunters?
That's what Zaizen's
trying to do?
Solomon Headquarters is nervous
about his activities, as well.
If they don't need
hunters to hunt...
Then...
Hunters will...
[DOJIMA]
No way! Sakaki?!
Why is the factory after him?
Great. Here they come!
[FACTORY HUNTER 21 A groans]
[DOJIMA]
Robin!
Sakaki?
Why is the Factory
going after a hunter?
[SAKAKI groans]
That hurt...
[gunshots]
[FACTORY HUNTER 21 B grunts]
[ROBIN gasps]
Thanks, Amon!
[ROBIN grunts]
[FACTORY HUNTERS groan]
[FACTORY HUNTER 21 G groans]
[wind howls]
[AMON]
Wait.
[DOJIMA]
Why did you let them go?
Calm down Dojima, we know
where they came from.
Plus, they seemed to be
having some sort of trouble.
And don't forget him...
[DOJIMA]
Oh, yeah! That's right!
[NAGIRA]
Hey there.
[ROBIN gasps]
Nagira?
What are you--
I guess you two came
to an understanding.
[DOJIMA]
Are you okay?
[SAKAKI] Dammit! What
the hell was that all about?
That was a Factory
assault team.
That's exactly my point! Why
would the Factory attack me?!
Come on, take it easy!
I don't know why, either!
Wait a sec. Dojima?
What on earth are
you doin' here?
There's Amon...
And Robin's here, too...
Hey, what the hell's
goin' on here?!
I'll explain it all later.
But the real question is why
would the Factory attack you?
[AMON]
Karasuma...
What?
Sakaki, where's Karasuma?
Huh?!
She said that she was gonna
be leavin' a little after me.
[gasps]
[phone rings]
[ringing continues]
[NARRATOR] Three hundred and
twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
A broken shell.
A forbidden power.
A prisoner.
The name of the sacred
mother brings back
an awe carved in the darkness.