[DOJIMA]
Uh!
What do you think you're doing?!
You traitor.
That's the pot calling
the kettle black.
Come on, tell me Amon.
I'd like to know how what
I did was any different
from what you're doing now.
Unlike you, I would never
sell out a friend.
[gasps]
[train rattling]
[NAGIRA]
So, find anything?
[knocking]
[NAGIRA]
It's me. You in there?
Uh, yes.
[NAGIRA]
Can I come in?
[ROBIN] Oh, sorry. Come on in.
The door's unlocked.
[NAGIRA]
I found a guy
who says that he saw somebody
who resembled Amon.
He saw Amon?
Yeah, he did and twice
in the same place, to boot.
Amon was scoping out
a house all day
from a car parked on
the side of the road.
But why?
Beats me.
But if we go snoopin'
around that house,
I bet we'll find out something.
What do you say? Wanna
go check it out with me?
[door clicks]
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
But the Commissioner is still
in a meeting at the moment,
so can I ask you to please
wait here for a few minutes?
Oh... Yes, of course I will.
[door opens]
[ROBIN]
Mm?
Looks like we're back
to square one.
So you didn't find anything?
[NAGIRA]
Nope, not really.
There's an old lady that's
been living in that house
for a long time now,
but that's about it.
Amon must've tailed
somebody back to this place.
There's no doubt about it.
That's what I think, anyway.
If you think that's really true,
then maybe Amon came here
to ask that lady about
somebody else.
The only thing that
old lady could tell us
about is ancient history.
Who could he possibly
ask her about?!
Overconfidence...
I'm talkin' about me.
Up until just now, everything's
been comin' really easy.
Maybe I've been jumpin'
to conclusions
and simplifying Amon's motives.
Where are we going?
To do a little digging.
If he really came here to
ask that old lady something
then we need to make sure
we clear the decks first.
"Clear the decks"?
Yeah. We'll find out who
that old lady might know.
Whoever she's connected
to attracted Amon's attention.
Then we'll track him down.
[COMMISSIONER] I called you
here today for a reason.
Yes, sir.
[COMMISSIONER]
You drink tea, don't you?
Y-Yes, of course, tea
is fine, thank you sir.
[COMMISSIONER] Excuse me,
could you bring some
hot tea for myself and
Inspector Kosaka?
[CLERK]
Right away, sir.
It will be here in a minute.
Yes, sir. Thank you
very much, sir.
Let us now get back
to the point at hand.
The reason why I asked
you to come down here
is because your reports suggest
that Administrator Zaizen
hasn't been seen at your
office for some time now.
Is that true?
Yes.
It would seem that various
matters, of which I am unaware,
have kept the Administrator busy
since the attack on the STNJ.
So, there has been
no word from him?
[KOSAKA]
Not for the past month or so.
[COMMISSIONER]
Hm... Now I understand.
Is the Administrator in
some sort of trouble, sir?
[COMMISSIONER]
Hmm...
It looks like there may be some
trouble brewing between
Mr. Zaizen and
Solomon headquarters.
It's still merely a
possibility at this point,
but Administrator Zaizen's
standing within Solomon Japan
may undergo some changes
in the near future.
Naturally, we have no
intention of making an enemy
of him just yet.
For the time being,
we will need to keep
a very close eye on
their power plays.
And that brings me
to a small matter
which will require your
cooperation, Inspector Kosaka.
Huh?
A 40% cut in the
project budget?!
What's going on here?
[SECRETARY]
Yes, sir?
Connect me to the
chief accountant
at Solomon's Japan branch--
No, wait.
Get me CFO Sugimura immediately.
[SECRETARY] CFO Sugimura
of the Japan branch, sir?
One moment, please.
[ZAIZEN]
Hmm...
[SECRETARY]
I'm very sorry Administrator,
but Mr. Sugimura doesn't seem
to be answering my call.
What's going on?
[SECRETARY]
I'm not sure, sir.
Just to make certain, I tried
calling the other departments,
but there's no answer
from any of them.
I see then...
I hate to trouble you,
but wait a while
and then try reaching
them again.
[SECRETARY]
Yes, sir.
Is it pressure
from headquarters?
Or could it be--
[computer chimes]
Huh?
A hunter from HQ?
They've gone right
over my head.
But why?
So they're planning to
oust me now, are they?
Hello there, it's me.
I'd like you to get me
some verification
on a very important matter.
No, it's about Solomon Japan's
Finance &amp; Administration
Department.
Well, it looks like we're
in for a little rain...
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Find out anything?
Yeah. I did some diggin'
around and found out
that the old lady had a son
that lived there for a while.
So, you think Amon was
looking for him?
[ROBIN]
What's the matter?
Huh?
Well, it's true that
her son did live there,
but as it turns out,
the guy actually died
about 15 years ago.
What?
[NAGIRA] I still can't figure
out what would make Amon
chase after ancient
history like that.
So, you don't think it was him?
Maybe not.
Where to now?
To visit the university
that the son worked at.
[KOSAKA]
Hmm...
[footsteps]
Good morning, everybody!
Good morning, Dojima.
Hiya.
Does it look like it's
morning out there to you?
[DOJIMA laughs]
Huh?
[laughs] And a very fine
morning to you, Chief.
[KOSAKA]
Yeah, good morning.
Huh?!
The Chief, what's
wrong with him?
Why are you asking me?
How should I know?
[KOSAKA]
Hmm...
[UNIVERSITY CLERK]
Ah, here it is.
Hiroshi Toudou.
This is him, right?
[COLLEGE GIRL A laughs]
[NAGIRA] I'm starting
to see the big picture.
Looks like the reason the son
left his assistant professorship
was because he was scouted by
some European corporation.
A European one?
Yeah, they're called
FZ Genemics.
It's a pharmaceutical company
that was once rumored to have
close ties to Solomon.
To Solomon...?!
Looks like the pieces are
startin' to fall into place.
[MAN ON THE PHONE] The hunter's
name is Willem Hasselbaink.
Age, 42.
He's a hunter from Holland.
I understand. What are
his movements now?
[MAN ON THE PHONE] We've
determined his route of entry
into the country.
We should be able
to track his movements inside
the country any time now.
Put more people on it
if you have to.
Put a rush on this
investigation.
[WILLEM]
A memory of death.
So, this is where you were...
...Old Corneli.
[doorbell buzzes]
[MOTHER]
Yes?
[NAGIRA] Hello, I'm terribly
sorry to be disturbing you
at this hour. My name
is Takane, and I worked
as a research assistant at
Professor Toudou's lab.
The thing is, the lab
is putting together
an alumni registry for
all the members so I--
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
Are you Mr. Nagira?
[NAGIRA]
Uh! Yes, ma'am.
I was told I should be
expecting your arrival.
[gasps]
Is there something
the matter, ma'am?
[MOTHER]
Um, no, not at all.
I'm sorry, please, why
don't you come on in.
How did she know who you were?
[NAGIRA] How else?
It must have been Amon.
Heh.
So, he was giving us
an invitation after all.
[MOTHER] Everything is exactly
as it was 15 years ago.
Nothing has changed.
I haven't touched anything in
here since... it happened.
Oh, you don't say,
and what did happen?
Nothing.
I'm very sorry, but you two
will have to excuse me now.
If you want to take a
closer look at anything,
please feel free to
move things around.
[door closes]
I guess that means we can dig
all we want around here.
She sure seemed to know
everything about us...
Well, shall we avail
ourselves of her hospitality
and start diggin' around then?
I don't understand this stuff.
[NAGIRA]
That's no surprise.
But Amon was definitely
checking up on something
that's around here.
We ought to at least be able
to figure out what that was.
Uh?
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
Huh?
It's a diary?
Hey, check this out, the stuff
in this notebook is all from
when Toudou worked at that
European research agency.
Huh? What's the matter?
[NAGIRA]
A picture of Toudou, huh?
Hey, hey. Who's that little
cutie there next to him...
She looks like you.
Nah, on second thought,
maybe not.
Come to think of it...
The old lady looked
a little shocked
when she saw you
at the front door.
Who knows, maybe she thought
that you looked like
this young woman
here in the picture.
Nagira, let's go.
Huh? What's the big
rush all of a sudden?
Hey, wait a minute!
[NAGIRA]
Hey, Robin!
[NAGIRA grunts]
[gasps]
I'm really sorry,
but would you mind
if I borrowed this book
from you for a while?
Go right ahead.
Thank you for the tea.
Now if you'll excuse us...
[door opens, closes]
This is a surprise.
I thought you were heading home
for the night, Ms. Dojima.
Oh. I forgot something,
that's all.
And I thought I'd bring
the prisoner a treat.
Just kidding.
[MICHAEL]
Hey, thanks. I appreciate it.
Well, you're quite welcome.
Oh, yeah. Hey, Michael...
Have you ever heard
of something called
the Solomon Genetic
Research Team?
"Genetic Research Team"?
No. What brought this on?
[DOJIMA]
I only heard the name, myself,
so I don't know
what it is really.
But it sounds interesting!
What's your source
for this info?
Now that is a secret.
Anyway, I'm outta here.
The Genetic Research Team...
[typing]
[MAN ON THE PHONE] We have
confirmation on the hunter.
The same as this afternoon?
[MAN ON THE PHONE]
The exact same location.
Could he be waiting
for something?
[MAN ON THE PHONE]
Sir?
Never mind, it's nothing.
So, the hunter is
just standing there
in the middle of
the street, then?
[ZAIZEN]
Hmm...
Aw, it's freezing...
She's still far away...
Hm?
[grunting]
[SQUAD LEADER]
Operation concluded.
Now returning to base.
[SQUAD 22C gasping]
[SQUAD 22A]
What is it?
[SQUAD 22B] Doctor!
Something's wrong with zero-two!
[SQUAD 22C groaning]
[groaning continues]
[gunshot]
[SQUAD 22B]
Get me security at HQ!
[ZAIZEN] I see. Yes, please
forward the assault data
to the foundation right away.
But be sure to make
no mention whatsoever
of the Orbo's side effects.
Is that understood?
Well, now...
It seems this has finally
become an all-out war
with Solomon headquarters.
[gasps]
[DOJIMA]
A Factory van?
[gasps]
Those are--!
I wonder if this is a
code word for somethin'.
Huh?
This symbol that seems
to keep poppin' up.
Omega? No, well
then maybe it's pi.
Something about "Analysis of the
pi genome is almost complete.
Pi then becomes a
genetic factor.
With this, a means of
controlling the abilities
has been opened to us,"
or so it says...
What does that mean?
This "pi" thing he was
talkin' about was probably
the focus of the research
he was involved in.
Whatever it is, it's definitely
got somethin' to do
with genetic engineering.
Amon must've been
searching for it.
So is this some sort of link
between genetics and Witches?
Now, this bit here about
controlling abilities.
I can't make sense out of it.
There's just not enough--
The Orbo!
Or--? What the hell is "Orbo"?
Um, It's nothing.
By the way, Nagira,
I was wondering
if maybe you had come across
anything in the diary that talks
about a priest named Juliano?
"Juliano"?
Nah. Doesn't look like it.
Oh.
What are you hiding? Who is
this Juliano guy anyway?
Nobody. Forget about it.
At any rate, it looks
like we're still gonna
have to look a little deeper
into this thing after all.
But it's a little too late to do
anything about it today.
[yawns]
I think I'm gonna adjourn our
meeting for a little while.
You should call it a day
and get some sleep, too.
Yes, I know.
[thunder rumbles]
But why...?
Why on earth would he
have been there that day?
Why him...?
Juliano...
Damn it, it's really
startin' to-- Huh?
I knew I was right.
Admit it. You deliberately
left us a trail.
You wanted us to
follow you, didn't ya?
What the hell are you up to?
I have come here to hunt Robin.
What's that? What the hell
did you just say?
I've come here to hunt Robin.
Amon. Are you completely
out of your mind?!
No, not really.
Robin Sena has become the most
dangerous Witch in existence.
What're you talking about?!
You're calling her a Witch now?
She's only a witch
because Solomon
has decided to see her that way.
Wait a second, this
isn't because of some
unresolved issues with
your mother, is it?
It is not.
Then what's the deal?
You must have seen it...
...Robin's power.
So what. That doesn't
matter to me at all.
Robin is still Robin.
And that girl hasn't
changed one bit
since the day you first
left her with me.
[NAGIRA] Listen to me,
it's not a person's past
that tells you whether
or not to trust 'em.
It's whether you can trust that
person's heart that matters.
At the very least, you must've
believed in her back
when you told her to
come to me for help.
I thought that you wanted me
to take care of her!
Are you trying to tell me now
that that was all a mistake?
Well, I'm gonna protect Robin!
Even if I have to
take a bullet--
[NAGIRA]
Amon...
[thud]
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Reunion. Hatred for blood.
A dead-end alley.
The forbidden encounter restarts
a stalled spinning wheel.