[ROBIN]
Who are you?
Who am I, you ask?
How shall I explain...
[ROBIN gasps]
[OLD WOMAN]
I am time.
[gasps]
[OLD WOMAN]
From the distant past,
time that has been
piling up like dust in
this little valley of a world...
That is who I am.
[AMON]
Yes, it's a witch's symbol.
[KARASUMA]
You know it?
Have you ever heard anything
about a certain incident...
...called the
Salem Witch Trials?
[KARASUMA] As I recall, it was
back in Colonial America.
A number of women were
murdered after they were accused
of being witches.
That was something like 400
years ago, though, wasn't it?
[AMON] Yes, it was
the late 17th century.
This is the symbol that
was carved into their bodies
to mark them as being witches.
[KARASUMA] I don' t know why,
but we've been repeatedly
receiving this symbol
on the office computer
since late last night.
At least I know where it's from.
It's coming from
Robin's workstation.
--[AMON] Robin's?
--That's right.
I'm not sure what
to make of it,
so Michael's trying
to figure it out.
As far as I can tell, there
doesn't appear to be
too much damage to the system.
[AMON]
And where's Robin now?
Do you mean you
haven't heard about it?
We got a call
from Touko earlier
asking if we knew anything.
She said that Robin's been
missing since last night.
A Salem Witch...?
But how...?
So you have
finally figured it out.
You're lying.
There is no way this is true.
[OLD WOMAN]
Lying?
[ROBIN] The Salem witches were
executed over 400 years ago...
And yet...
Why do some of those
witches still seem to exist?
Time does not always
oblige us and choose to flow
in the same predictable manner.
It can even come
to a halt and sit
in complete stagnation.
At least, this is true
for some people.
[ROBIN gasps]
[DOJIMA] Maybe she just
decided to play hooky today.
No, that's
more like your m.o.
Robin wouldn't do that.
Just as I thought;
Robin's not answering.
And she hasn't been to
Harry's this morning either.
[DOJIMA]
Maybe she just ran away.
Once again, I'd say
that's more your speed.
[MICHAEL]
Excuse me.
I know you like to chatter,
but if you've got free time,
why aren't you out
looking for her?
Even if Robin didn't
have anything to do
with sending that image...
...it's connected to her
somehow or other.
[SAKAKI] Boy, he's in
a bad mood, isn't he?
[DOJIMA]
What do you expect?
Now that someone's hacked his
impenetrable security system...
[ZAIZEN]
I see.
So you don't think she's
the one who sent this?
Robin's workstation
is simply an entry point.
I'm pretty sure that
what we're really looking at
is a case of someone from
the outside using her terminal
as a proxy. That's how
they were able to hack
the STNJ's security system.
[ZAIZEN]
So what's it all about?
Why go to all that trouble just
to send us some cryptic symbol?
[AMON] We don't know what
the intruder's intentions are.
Right.
And how long have these
intrusions been going on?
[AMON] The first traces
of it were a week ago.
So it started a week ago...
[AMON]
What are you thinking?
It's been precisely
one week since
we hunted Narumi, hasn't it?
[AMON] Yes, it has, but
Narumi's being held by
the Factory, so that should
rule him out, should it not?
True enough.
However, what if there
were other witches involved
that might still be at large?
Now, as far
as I understand it,
Narumi never gave any
indication of exercising
his powers until very recently.
As far as we can tell.
If he had been
using them before,
the STN would have
been watching him.
[ZAIZEN]
That means...
...it could be a witch...
...who can control
other witch's powers...
In any case, keep
a close eye on that intruder.
And while you're doing that,
I'll have a look around
and see what I can find out
about this Salem mark.
[AMON]
You're going to do it yourself?
There's something about this
that strikes me as peculiar.
[OLD WOMAN]
You tell me that I am not real?
But can you honestly say
that you yourself are real?
You are a witch, yet you
willingly serve the Confraria.
[ROBIN]
No, that's... I'm...
[OLD WOMAN]
Oh?
Then tell me: what are
these powers of yours?
Are you saying that
it's not witchcraft?
So you're simply
a human being?
Just another descendant
of Saturn, nothing more?
Who is this Saturn?
We're supposed to go
to the Walled City
and just wait around there?
What's the deal? I don't get it.
Hey, is Robin inside
there or something?
I dunno... I'm sure
Amon's got a plan though,
or he wouldn't send us over.
Anyway, let's get over
there and stand by.
Okay, but why on stand-by?
What's the point?
[OLD WOMAN] What do you know
about the great witch hunts?
Do you know when
the last ones were?
Tell me, do you know?
18th century England.
The year 1717.
France. In the year 1745.
Germany. In the year 1775.
And finally... In the
year 1793 in Poland.
How many innocents were killed?
The enormity of the destruction
is impossible to comprehend.
It has been said that
several hundred thousand
perished during those periods.
Some even say that
as many as 9 million witches
were burned to death.
[ROBIN]
Nine million...
However... that was
far from the end
of the tragedies
visited upon us.
Some envied the witches
because of their powers
and they never stopped
persecuting them.
They were always in
the bowels of society.
Just waiting for the time
to continue the hunt.
You're wrong.
It's not persecution
to pursue those whose hearts
have been taken over by evil.
I have been watching this
happen for over 300 years.
And I have been listening
for over 300 years...
...to words like those.
[ROBIN gasps]
For some reason,
you still cannot believe it.
Hardly surprising.
I will show you what
you and your associates
have been doing...
The meaning behind it.
[OLD WOMAN]
In the name of the mages...
I call on you, O Loki...
[computer beeps, whirrs]
Hm?
[DOJIMA gasps]
Wait a minute,
what's going on here?
What's that supposed to be?
Hey, Michael!
Dammit!
[MICHAEL] How the hell
are they getting through
my security system?!
[cell phone rings]
[MICHAEL]
Hi, Amon.
[AMON] What's wrong?
The communicator isn't working.
[MICHAEL] I can't use the
terminal lines right now.
What's the matter with them?
[MICHAEL]
It's that symbol again!
We got hacked about
5 minutes ago.
Most of the system's
down right now.
Is it an attack on the STNJ...?
[OLD WOMAN] The images of
gods engraved by humans
of the ancient past...
with a sacred heart.
Do you understand,
o maiden witch?
[ROBIN]
Is it a devil?
No, i-it is not a god!
That's...
That's something...
--[OLD WOMAN] ...different?
--[gasps]
[OLD WOMAN]
So what you mean to say is...
...that it is not a god,
but rather a devil.
[ROBIN gasps]
[OLD WOMAN]
But you see, this is a god.
The oldest in shape and form...
The very first god...
[YOUNG WITCH]
...humans have ever known.
[MICHAEL] Okay, Amon, I think
I'm actually gonna be able
to find out who's
responsible for all this.
Really? You figured
out how they got in?
[MICHAEL]
Yeah, I found a loophole.
I think what happened is
they hacked into the system
through our
communication devices.
[AMON]
What?!
[MICHAEL] As long as the
access code's been entered,
they can get into the system
directly through the device.
That's why the
firewall didn't work.
[AMON]
Have you located Robin yet?
No, I've been trying
to track down her device
for a while, but it looks like
they did something to it,
and I haven't figured
out what's up yet.
[AMON]
Try the Walled City.
What, are you telling me
you've got a lead on her?
I'll explain it to you later,
I need you to hurry.
[MICHAEL]
Gotcha.
[KARASUMA] Yes...
It's Robin's scooter all right.
It looks like
she is here after all.
[AMON]
I see... Okay, I'm on my way.
Don't go in;
just stay right there.
[KARASUMA]
Roger.
[ROBIN]
A demon!
You're wrong. That's not it.
That's not why demons
fell from Heaven.
They fell because they
drowned in their own greed.
That's why the gods--
How can you possibly
say that the demons
were the ones who
fell from grace?
[ROBIN gasps]
[OLD WOMAN]
The ones who committed
the truly horrible acts of
history were actually the ones
who had been labeled as "gods."
[ROBIN] That was necessary;
i-it was to save them
from their misguided ways...
[OLD WOMAN]
Salvation? That's not true.
It's wasn't as simple as that.
What really moved
the gods to act...
...was jealousy.
Jealousy and fear
of those individuals
who harbored strong powers.
These two emotions
drove them forward.
The feelings consumed them,
and led them to annihilate
their former comrades.
And they did it.
They who had shared the
same blood were renamed.
They were "fallen gods."
They called them "witches".
That can't be true!
[YOUNG WITCH]
It is true.
Why would they play upon
the doubts of people
who were living in fear?
[OLD WOMAN] Why did they go to
such great lengths to implant
these feelings of
doubt in people,
and send innocent people
to burn at the stake?
You, of all people, should know.
I should know?
[OLD WOMAN]
Yes, you should...
...because you carry
the blood of countless people
who died that way.
That's right. You can't deny it.
You have witches' blood in you.
[AMON] Yes, I think that's
probably what's going on:
the intruder must have lured
Robin here under some pretext,
and then used the personal code
in her terminal to hack into
the STNJ's system.
[ZAIZEN]
Hmph.
As I mentioned,
I did a little research
on the Salem incidents myself.
It seems quite a few
witches are very well versed
in that period.
And their knowledge
is surprisingly accurate.
Do you know anything about
the Witch of Methuselah?
The clan of the immortal?
[ZAIZEN]
That's right.
Perhaps it's true.
Maybe they really do exist.
Knowledge that dates
back a few hundred years
can become a very powerful
weapon in the right hands.
A weapon?
[ZAIZEN] Even if they don't
have power of their own,
they may be able to use
such vast knowledge
to control other witches.
[ZAIZEN]
What's is it?
Nothing... But something
just struck me.
Sakaki told me about
the last time with Narumi
when all his powers seemed
to just suddenly dry up.
[ZAIZEN] Find Robin
as quickly as you can.
That may very well be
where the answer is.
[AMON]
Understood.
[OLD WOMAN] This is
the last prayer of a girl
who is soon to be
burned at the stake.
[OLD WOMAN] Those who choose
to hunt their shadow...
...will be destroyed
by that shadow.
Does that mean...
...that I've been hunting...
...my own shadow...?
[OLD WOMAN] You see, the truth
always has two faces.
[ROBIN]
Amon?!
A witch...
must always be hunted.
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
No! I'm not a witch!
[OLD WOMAN] No? What's
so different about you?
[ROBIN] My craft is one
that's used to hunt witches...
[OLD WOMAN] So you burned
the bodies of the witches...
...by the fire of
the burning stakes?
[ROBIN]
No... That's not true...
[OLD WOMAN] It's no different
than 400 years ago.
The history of suffering
is not over yet.
Still, it continues.
No... You are continuing it.
Those who carry
the witches' blood...
[ROBIN gasps]
A witch...
...must always be hunted.
[ROBIN]
Amon...
Amon?
Amon...!
[YOUNG WITCH] I am finally
able to put an end to it...
[OLD WOMAN]
...after such a very long time.
[gasps]
It was such a long time.
It was far too long...
[ROBIN]
400 years of knowledge...
Everyone needs to attain
the mysteries of the Craft.
[ROBIN gasps]
What's that...? Could it be...?
[ROBIN]
This is the craft's...
[AMON]
Methuselah...
A witch who was
given eternal life...
The only thing that can
bring death to its eternal soul
is a fire that burns
its entire body.
[ROBIN]
That's why she chose me...
So that she could
end her eternity...
[AMON] If it's true, then
the burning of the witches
at the stake... may have
been something prompted
by some distant memory
of the Methuselah.
Such memories...
...are just too sad...
[MICHAEL]
Hm?
Hey.
[AMON] Did you find out what
the witches were after?
No, I still can't figure it out.
It seems that they
just used the system
because they wanted to send
a message to Robin, that's all.
To Robin?
Yeah. They were trying
to get in touch with her;
they wanted to send her
information about her powers,
but that's as much as I know.
Saturn, is it?
[MICHAEL]
What's that?
[AMON]
Greek mythology.
He was someone
who feared that his child
would someday
usurp his position...
...so much so,
in fact, that in the end,
he killed the child
and ate its flesh.
[MICHAEL]
His own child?
[AMON] Those were the words
that the witch left with Robin.
[MICHAEL]
The witch?
[ROBIN] I've recovered a
relic that's possibly related
to passing on the
secret of the Craft.
I'll stand by
for further orders.
[NARRATOR] Three hundred and
twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Inquisitors. Witch hunters.
A crushed fate...
The child of darkness chosen by
the Lord shall see the judgment.