[CROWS cawing]
[gasps]
Here, try using these.
There's nothing wrong
with my eyesight.
[AMON]
I'm not so sure...
Hey!
[ROBIN]
My eyes are just fine.
Do you wanna come up?
Is what I'd really
like to say, but...
[lock clicks]
Hi, I'm back.
[ROBIN humming]
[ROBIN gasps]
Welcome home.
Well, from the looks of things,
I'd guess that you're the one
who cleaned the place up.
[ROBIN]
Ah. Yes.
[TOUKO] So you're sort of
a neat freak, huh?
It's not that I like it.
It's just a habit.
When I was at the monastery,
these were my daily chores.
[TOUKO]
Hm...
[water splashing]
[laughs]
[organ playing]
[ROBIN]
It's rather good.
Huh?
You've captured the mood well.
I was just curious, that's all.
About what kind of picture
you were painting.
I was curious, too.
[ROBIN]
Hm?
I was curious about you.
It seems you're
here every morning.
And so I am. For a
little prayer time.
[SAYOKO]
For prayer?
Then you believe... in God?
[ROBIN]
Hm...
It's sort of a habit.
I see. Well, I believe in Him.
Because He was the one who
brought me into such an
incredibly beautiful world.
[SAYOKO] And that's why
I'm preserving it like this:
the world as its beautiful self.
My name is Sayoko.
Huh?
Oh. Hello. My name's Robin.
[SAYOKO]
Robin... What a beautiful name.
[KOSAKA]
Robin.
Yes?
I've just received
a telephone message
from Amon about you.
You should memorize the
contents of these files
as soon as possible.
[ROBIN]
Files?
[KOSAKA] They're reference
files for unsolved crimes.
There are abstracts in here
for the last two years' worth.
Each and every one of them have
a 50 percent chance or greater
of a witch being the culprit.
[KOSAKA] I'm sure that just
seeing how the initial
investigation is handled will
be quite a learning experience.
Where's Amon now?
He's out right now.
He's with Sakaki.
With Sakaki?
[HATTORI] It wouldn't be bad if
he took her along, would it?
Well, I guess that's true.
Since Robin was supposed
to be his partner.
Thank you, Dojima.
Tell me, did you also find time
to get all your work done yet?
[DOJIMA] Ugh! What's
that supposed to mean?
Of all the nerve.
As a matter of fact,
I'm doing it
right now, so there.
[KOSAKA]
Oh, really?
Then what's that
magazine on your desk?
[DOJIMA]
Well, to you it might look
like a fashion magazine,
Chief, but it's actually
reference material
for one of our cases.
So you don't believe me, huh?
[MICHAEL] These cases are
all horrible, aren't they?
Whether the perpertrator
was a human or a witch.
They still happened.
There are people as bad
or worse than witches
wandering around out there.
[ROBIN gasps]
[MICHAEL]
Hm?
Oh, that one. The
Yotsuga Lake murders.
Three victims, with no
discernable patterns
of age or occupation
or anything.
The only similarity
is that they all
bled to death from
external wounds.
[MICHAEL] Each of them
had several dozen wounds
all over their bodies from
an undetermined weapon.
But how they were
killed or what might
have led to their deaths
is still a mystery.
[ROBIN]
This park...
It's the same park I walk
through every morning
on my way to prayer.
[MICHAEL]
Oh, yeah?
I never would've thought
that something like that
could happen there.
[MICHAEL]
Of course not.
The last of the three...
...was a whole four months
before you got here.
[ROBIN] So the killer might
still be in that area.
[ROBIN]
A witch.
Or just some insane person.
[KARASUMA]
Maybe we should go over
and take a look at the place.
[ROBIN]
Hm?
You never know. We might
find something there.
But how about getting some
lunch before we do it?
If it isn't already too late.
[KARASUMA]
Thank you.
[ROBIN]
Hm...
You can "read" me can't you.
Huh?
What I'm thinking right now.
Who knows?
Please try reading.
What's on my mind right now?
It's Amon.
[KARASUMA]
Partner...
Left behind...
Why's it always like this?
That's amazing!
You're absolutely right.
You really can see
into people's hearts.
Well, that wasn't from
using any of my powers.
Huh?
Oh, that was easy
enough to see.
Without much help.
[KARASUMA] Besides, the only
things that I'm able
to read are strong feelings
left behind in objects.
I'm not able to see
what's happening
in someone's heart.
But you're an S-class.
Oh.
I see, so even a Craft
master's has concerns
about someone else's
power class?
I wouldn't say
I'm actually worried.
I believe you're an
A-class, aren't you?
Huh?
You could become one.
You just need to
hit your targets
with a bit more precision
That's all you'd really have
to do to become an S-class.
Why do you think you
can't hit your targets?
I'm don't know.
[caws]
[gasps]
[cawing]
[SAYOKO gasps]
[inaudible]
[cawing]
[ROBIN]
Here.
Thank you very much.
You know, we'd be in
a whole lot of trouble
if the chief were to
find us here right now.
[ROBIN] Do you wanna stop off
at my place on the way back?
Huh?
It's not far.
Just so we could
talk for a while.
It's not really
considered appropriate
for us to hang out together
in our off hours.
Yes, I know that, but it
doesn't really matter.
Might not be a bad idea.
[KARASUMA]
It's so peaceful...
I can't believe
a thing like that
happened right here.
The press made such a big deal
out of the whole thing, too.
They're so heartless sometimes.
It was just four months ago.
It's as if it wasn't real.
[gasps]
You know her?
No.
I just happened to talk
to her one morning.
[pants]
Well, that wasn't
incredibly productive.
My feet are about
ready to fall off.
[MICHAEL]
Robin's not here right now.
I think she went
to check out the
Yotsuga Lake Park
with Miss Karasuma.
[whistles]
Fancy that: speaking
of Yotsuga Lake Park.
[gasps]
[SAKAKI]
Amon?
Just as I thought--
there's nothing here.
Well, that's not surprising,
since the police did give it
a pretty thorough search.
What do you think, Karasuma?
Who do you think did it?
A psychopath? Or maybe...
[KARASUMA]
I'd say it was probably a witch.
The wounds on
the victims' bodies
were not inflicted
after their deaths.
In other words,
they were hacked up
while they were still alive.
There's no evidence to suggest
that they might
have been drugged
or tied up or
anything like that.
Yet there's no sign that
they resisted either.
Or rather, that
there was time enough
for them to resist.
Either way, I can't bring myself
to think of this as
just an ordinary case.
But that's just my opinion.
Either way, we might as well
have another look around.
[ROBIN]
Well, if it's okay,
I'd like to check
something out myself.
That's fine. I guess I'll
just have a look around
by myself. See ya.
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[cawing]
[caws]
[CROW caws]
[CROWS cawing]
Crows?
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[KARASUMA]
Could it be...?
That girl!
Robin!
[CROWS cawing]
[ROBIN]
Stop it!
[grunts]
[SAYOKO whimpering]
...so-- Yo-- Y-You so--
You soiled... You soiled...
You soiled...
You soiled...!
[grunts]
[KARASUMA]
Robin!
She's dangerous, take cover!
[ROBIN grunts]
[SAYOKO]
I'll never forgive you.
You have soiled this world.
And I...
...won't forgive you!
It's no use; we can't fight off
a power like that with the Orbo.
[gasps]
[yelping]
[screams]
[SAKAKI] Her type of power
wasn't even listed
in the STN's database.
That means they didn't
have her targeted at all.
Yes, and it also means there are
a lot of people walking around
with the genes of witches.
That's true.
I feel a little sorry
for the victims, though.
Killed just because
they got between
someone and what they happened
to be painting at the time.
[KARASUMA]
Witches who terminate the humans
who soil their world.
And witch hunters who terminate
witches for the things they do
that soil the human world.
[SAKAKI]
Huh?
Maybe that makes us a little
more alike than we thought.
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
A lost landscape.
A scent of memory.
An oppressed heart.
A wandering heart haunts the
town clamoring for the past.