Hmph!
[gasping]
[DOJIMA gasping]
[KARASUMA grunts]
Hey, Michael, it looks
like we lost Muroi.
Can you do anything to find him?
[MUROI chuckles]
[MUROI]
Hm?
Well, now who the hell are you?
I get it. You're one of them!
[growls]
Why--?
[MUROI groaning]
[rustling]
[MICHAEL] It seems like we
haven't been on very good terms
with HQ since the attack.
I don't know what's
goin' on over there.
[ROBIN]
But there's nowhere else
that Amon could be
right now, is there?
Well, you may be
right about that...
[ROBIN] You told me before that
there was a large bloodstain on
the ground from where
Amon was dragged away.
That's true...
But afterward,
Karasuma and the others
assured me that it wasn't
enough to be life-threatening.
So he's at headquarters, then.
That is, if he's still alive.
[ROBIN]
Michael, you just--
[MICHAEL]
Shh!
We're clear.
[ROBIN]
He's alive.
Eh?!
Amon just can't be dead.
But how can you be so sure?
I don't know.
I guess... He could...
But, I can't accept that.
I can't believe Amon
could be dead.
Robin...
I guess you have a point.
Heh.
Hey, that reminds me,
I came across some
interesting information
while I was accessing
Headquarters' Database.
It looks as though they're
going to be sending us
a new hunter very soon.
[ROBIN]
A replacement?
Not quite, I didn't
get that impression.
[ROBIN]
But you said you guys
and headquarters
weren't getting along.
Yeah. It's strange.
And as if that weren't enough,
the fact that I was
able to snoop out
that particular piece of
intel is awfully suspicious.
[ROBIN]
It was intentional?
[MICHAEL]
Yeah... Probably.
Hey. Do you know anything
about a hunter named Sastre?
[ROBIN]
Sastre!
[camera clicks]
They said that
Muroi's been killed?
Other than a puncture
wound from a sharp object
there's apparently nothing
unusual about the body.
We can't get involved
in this yet.
[DOJIMA]
What's Michael say?
I've been trying to
reach him for a while.
He's not there?
That's unusual.
Maybe he's sleeping.
[KARASUMA]
We've gotta get the corpse
to the Factory before it gets
taken away for an autopsy.
Hey, don't look at me.
You know I'm no good
at that sort of thing!
Oh, calm down, no one's
asking you to do anything.
[DOJIMA laughs]
Uh.
[phone rings]
[HANAMURA] Good morning,
Nagira Law Offices.
May I help you?
Mr. Nagira?
Um, I'm sorry, but he's...
[pachinko machines rattle]
[GAMBLER] She's an acquaintance
of yours, that right?
Not really.
All right then. I'll buy it.
[GAMBLER] Apparently, there
was an origami crane
left next to the body that
was found last night.
And this name was written on
the inside of that little crane.
[NAGIRA]
Hmm...
[ROBIN] Sastre...
Is he here to hunt me?
[ZAIZEN] If I understand you
correctly, you're telling me
that the Orbo's
effectiveness on humans
is still limited at this stage.
Based on the results
of the analysis of the
most recent hunt, we have
clearly observed a 30% drop
in efficiency in comparison to
the use of normal hunters.
In addition...
What else?
[TECH]
We've observed some damage
to certain members of the team.
It seems to be an unwelcome
side-effect of Orbo use.
Damage?
So we can't do without
the hunter's powers.
We'll need them for
a little while longer yet.
You're off your crutches?
Yeah. I'd like to say
that I'm back up to 100%,
but I guess I'm still
just a little slow.
Where's everybody?
[MICHAEL]
I think Karasuma and Dojima
are still working
last night's case.
What about the Chief
and Hattori?
[MICHAEL]
Beats me.
The two of them have been going
out of the office a lot lately.
[SAKAKI]
Hm?
[HANAMURA]
Hi, Boss. Welcome back.
Hey.
Hana, have you seen
Robin around today?
No, I haven't seen
that girl at all today.
But, since you happened
to bring her up,
all I hear is Robin
this and Robin that!
Could you stop chasing
skirts for a second
and do a little work?!
For instance, how many
cases have you personally
worked on these past
few days? Any of them?
The clients have been
complaining about--
[water running]
[knocking]
[NAGIRA]
It's me. Can I come in?
That was last night?
[NAGIRA]
Yeah.
The cops found a guy
who had been killed.
[ROBIN]
Why are you telling me this?
Apparently, an origami
crane was left by the body.
I have no idea if
this is true or not,
but I've heard a
rumor that your name
was written on the inside of
that crane for some reason.
[ROBIN]
It's Sastre.
[NAGIRA]
"Sastre"?
Never heard of him. Who is he?
A hunter from
Solomon headquarters.
[NAGIRA] From headquarters?
So what's he doin' here?
It was a message.
A message?
[ROBIN]
Yes. It's Sastre's trademark.
It's how he hunts down witches.
He hunts a witch
who's unrelated,
and then leaves his message.
"You're going to
end up like this."
[NAGIRA] So you're telling me
that last night's killing
was just his way
of saying hello?
Hey, wait a minute.
Then that must mean the
person he's really after is...
[NAGIRA]
Damn...
In any case,
I'm gonna go do some more
digging on this murder.
It's too early to get
depressed about it.
[ROBIN]
No doubt about it.
Sastre is out there.
[ROBIN]
I'm being... hunted...
The Fragment...?
That's it.
The Fragment is my
only hope right now.
[NAGIRA]
Looking for the Fragment?
[NAGIRA] If you had the
Fragment, then you might just
be able to beat that
Sastre guy, right?
[NAGIRA]
I see.
That thought had occurred
to me, too, but...
[NAGIRA]
I should've seen this comin'.
To this day, that thing
is still thought of as
the Holy Grail of
artifacts to witches.
[ROBIN]
It was stolen?
[NAGIRA]
What else could it be?
But then...
It's too early to
throw in the towel.
I have a good idea
where it went.
[MAN 20A pants]
Hey, wait a minute!
You wanna know
about the Fragment?
You're one of the people
who's lookin' for it, right?
[SASTRE grunts]
Yeah. That's what I thought.
All right, I'll talk!
I promise, I'll tell ya
everything I know.
So let me go, okay?
[SASTRE grunts]
[engine revs]
[SAKAKI] Is it another crane
with Robin's name on it?
Most likely.
Well, it looks like
your leg is healed up now.
[SAKAKI] Yeah. It still
hurts, though. Heh.
It's all the rehab.
Do you think they're supposed
to mean our Robin?
I don't really know.
But I think it would
be crazy to think
there isn't some connection
between them.
[SAKAKI]
By the way, where's Dojima?
Her? I have no idea
where she is.
[SAKAKI]
Jeez... So, what's the hold up?
When is this case gonna come
under our jurisdiction, anyway?
[KARASUMA]
It can't be helped.
Other than the fact
that the victim
happened to be a witch, there's
no grounds for us to step in.
[SAKAKI] Yeah, but if the
Administrator were here...
[beeping]
What is it?
[MICHAEL] I've tracked down the
victim's most recent movements.
It looks like the Walled City
was his base of operations.
[SAKAKI]
The Walled City?
Michael, could you do
some more digging for us
and find out what
he's doing in there?
[MICHAEL]
I figured you'd ask that.
I'm looking into his
known associates now.
You should probably
head over there yourself.
Roger that.
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
[SUZUKI yelps]
[NAGIRA] Hey! Come back
here, you bastard!
[SUZUKI panting]
[SUZUKI groaning]
All right, you
out-of-shape jackass!
I'm sorry! I-I'm sorry!
I see. I had a feelin'
that it was you.
You're the worm
who told everyone
that the Fragment of Knowledge
was at my place.
No, it wasn't me! Uh.
I didn't spread any rumors!
You see, I just...
Just what?
Well? Who did you
sell it to then?
Uh...
[phone rings]
[HANAMURA] Hello, Nagira Law--
Oh, hello Mr. Nagira.
Huh? The girl upstairs?
No, she hasn't come
out of her room yet today.
[NAGIRA]
Robin, are you there?
I found it. It's in the
Walled City like I thought.
It looks like this guy they call
the Priest has the Fragment.
Stealing it from me was
one thing, but the idiot
must not have any clue of how
to actually use the damn thing.
Apparently, he's poking
around the old lady's place
tryin' to find the secret to it.
[BRUISER A]
If we put the rumor out there,
they'll come flocking
to us, right?
[PRIEST]
Yes, just like hyenas.
[BRUISERS chuckling]
[PRIEST, BRUISER A]
Hm?
Well, what do we have here?
It looks to me like
another pathetic fool
was drawn out by this thing.
Idiot. He doesn't seem to know
how to introduce himself.
Go teach him some manners.
Be polite and
take good care of him.
[SASTRE]
Hm...
[exhales]
Hey. I've been waiting for you.
[NAGIRA]
Let's go.
It doesn't look like he's here.
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
[gasps]
[NAGIRA]
Is that him?
I've been waiting
for you, Robin.
Robin?
Sastre...
That's him?
Shoot, you mean he got
the drop on us?
What's wrong with me?
I must really be losing my edge.
[ROBIN gasps]
Robin, I'll keep
this freak show busy!
Get out of here! Now!
Dammit!
[NAGIRA]
Huh?
[gasps]
[NAGIRA groans]
[SASTRE]
Heh.
[panting]
[grunts]
[ROBIN groans]
[NAGIRA grunts]
[gasps]
Nagira!
[NAGIRA yelps]
[groaning]
[SASTRE]
Hm?
[ROBIN panting]
Why are you after me?
[KARASUMA gasps]
[SAKAKI]
What is it?
[KARASUMA]
I'm not really sure, but...
It's a psychic burst.
This way.
[ROBIN grunting]
[panting]
[ROBIN grunts]
[SASTRE grunts]
Wha...?!
[ROBIN]
I can see it...
[grunts]
[growls]
The inner secrets
of the Craft...
[SASTRE groaning]
Robin?
[ROBIN]
I can see his element of air...
[SASTRE gasping]
[ROBIN] You burned
the Fragment to ashes.
I see.
This is the true Craft,
this is the power derived
from the elements...
...lying dormant in my body...
Not captured in some
Fragment of Wisdom.
[SASTRE gasping]
[ROBIN]
And that's why you attacked me.
[SASTRE screams]
Tell me.
What is it that makes you
think that I am a witch.
[ROBIN whimpers]
Robin!
[AMON]
Hold it!
[SAKAKI, KARASUMA gasp]
[KARASUMA]
Amon!
Hey, Amon!
Robin is not a hunter anymore.
She's a Witch.
Amon...
What're you doing...?
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
A hunter who waits for his prey.
The footprints.
Endless darkness.
The child of darkness still
wishes to see tomorrow.