Uh. Thank you.
Huh? What's this for?
[ROBIN]
Here.
[HANAMURA]
Hey, answer me!
[ROBIN]
Nagira.
Please eat that.
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
[gasps]
What're you--
[door opens, closes]
She isn't leaving, is she?
Nagira...
[ROBIN]
...thank you for everything.
[CROWS caw]
[computer chimes]
Hey Chief, these are
the three guys, right?
[KOSAKA]
What do you think?
Is it possible to get them
all registered right away?
[MICHAEL] Sure thing, Chief,
that's not gonna be a problem.
But do you really think we need
the police to protect us?
What are you talking about?!
Have you forgotten
about the attack
on the police prisoner
van already?
We can't even say for sure
that we're safe here!
And I'm not about to put up
with the security system
going off all the time!
Hurry up and register them!
[MICHAEL]
Gotcha.
[TECH]
Sir, about Mr. Toudou's Data...
It's clear that 80% of the files
were decoded 15 years ago.
[ZAIZEN]
What about the other 20%?
[TECH] Their contents seem
to have been decoded as well,
but since they weren't directly
connected to genetics research,
the last 20% has been
deleted from the report.
Are you able to
retrieve the data?
[TECH]
It was deleted to prevent it
from being leaked,
but I expect to have
the data decoded from the
original by the end of the day.
Send me the results
as they come in.
I don't care if it's just
pieces--forward me everything.
[TECH]
Understood, sir.
[DOJIMA] Looks like it's all
quiet again today.
Hm?
What's up? Thinking
really isn't your style.
That guy yesterday
said somethin' about
"The Devil's child."
You think maybe he was
talkin' about Robin?
Beats me.
Hey, don't give me that crap.
Robin's power is growing.
It's way above normal.
And that guy from yesterday...
He was a Solomon
scientist, wasn't he?
If it's bothering you that much,
then why don't you go ask
Robin it about it yourself?
[SAKAKI]
Yeah, like I could do that.
You saw her, she already looked
like she was about
to start crying.
[phone rings]
Hello?
[DOJIMA grunts]
[DOJIMA]
Yes.
[ROBIN]
The Devil's child...
That's what he called me
when he saw my face.
[ROBIN]
And they...
They started hunting me
because I learned the
Arcanum of the Craft.
But I sensed that there
was something else
in the letter Father
Juliano wrote.
Maria, a woman who
looked like me...
Toudou's research...
The Devil's child...
[ROBIN]
He meant me.
If that's true...
...then I never
should have been born.
[CROW caws]
[doors slam]
Robin, you have a visitor.
A visitor? Who is it?
All he'd say is that
he came from Italy.
He wants to see you alone.
What do you wanna do?
Take me to him.
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
Juliano...
Juliano!
[ROBIN] Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
We all sin, my child,
every one of us.
[ROBIN]
This is different.
Please Father, I want
to know the truth.
Tell me the truth behind
the horrible sin
I've been made to carry.
Does this mean you're willing
to accept everything?
[ROBIN] It is far better for
the truth to tear my flesh
to pieces than for my soul
to wander through darkness
in eternal damnation.
Very well, then.
O Lord, grant me strength.
Give me the courage to accept
the truth, whatever it may be.
[ROBIN gasps]
[ROBIN] Juliano, am I
a manufactured Witch?
[JULIANO]
Yes, my child.
You are a designed Witch created
through genetic manipulation.
The fragrance from the fruit
of the Tree of Knowledge
leads man to forbidden desires.
When Solomon
Headquarters abandoned
their genetic research
into Witches,
Toudou, one of their
science team,
refused to abide
by their decision.
So he chose a certain Witch's
DNA and created you himself.
Created me?
From another witch?
Maria...!
[ROBIN]
So, I was right.
I'm that woman's--
Juliano, you're Maria's...
Maria was my...
[JULIANO]
Maria...
Maria was my daughter.
[gasps]
She was your daughter...?
So that means that I'm...
[rattling]
What're you two doing?
[MICHAEL]
Acting as Robin's lookouts.
What?
[AMON]
Has something happened?
The word just came down from HQ.
Solomon is sending out
an assault team.
Why an assault team?
The Factory!
Bingo. And if we don't do
something about it soon,
we're gonna lose our
chance to rescue Miho.
[AMON]
When?
Just before dawn.
[MICHAEL]
That's not much time.
What now? It's not like we can
force our way into the place.
Actually, that might be
exactly what we need to do.
[DOJIMA]
Mm?
[CROW caws]
[JULIANO]
You are not the only one
who has borne this
sin, my child.
[ROBIN]
How long have you known?
Ever since the day
you were born.
This whole time...
...you knew everything...
If you knew all of this,
then why didn't you hunt me?
I'm the Devil's Child and I
should never have been born.
If you had just hunted me
before I had learned anything,
I wouldn't have had
to suffer like this.
Yes, you're right.
I should have killed you
the moment I found out
you'd been brought
into this world.
And, on that day, I went to
Maria fully intending to do so.
But I was unable to do it.
[ROBIN]
You couldn't?
[JULIANO]
Maria was a Witch.
Since I was a member of Solomon,
that fact was difficult
for me to accept.
But when I learned that Maria's
days on this earth were numbered
due to a genetic abnormality
she inherited...
I didn't want to
lose my daughter.
I didn't want to lose Maria.
When I heard that she was
having a baby with Toudou,
I was filled with joy.
I believed that God was
still smiling upon me.
[JULIANO] But I discovered
that Toudou had deceived me.
To him, Maria was nothing
more than a test subject.
And then, I stood
over you that day.
[JULIANO]
But when I saw you Robin.
This little girl whom Maria
had sacrificed her life
to give birth to...
...all I could do was walk back
home, carrying you in my arms.
It was possible that you
didn't necessarily possess
the power that Toudou
had designed for you.
Or so I told myself.
[JULIANO] Perhaps all I've
been doing is putting off
the day when I must
learn that answer.
I was relieved to discover
that the powers
your father had tried to design
into your body had not
manifested yet and
I prayed in my heart that you
would stay this way forever.
[ROBIN]
But I've changed now.
I've learned the
Arcanum of the Craft,
and I've become a source
of anguish to you, Juliano.
No, that's not true.
It was the weakness of my heart.
From the moment you left my side
Robin, my heart was filled
with the most intense
anxiety imaginable.
Misgivings...? Yes, that's it.
I had misgivings that you
would awaken one day,
that eventually
you would change.
It was possible that I was
already being deceived.
These misgivings
turned into fear,
which spurred me
to order your hunt.
[CROW caws]
The source of my suffering
was the weakness inside
my own heart,
nothing more and nothing less.
I'm sorry, I didn't
want to change.
You have not changed, my child.
[gasps]
Power corrupts, and absolute
power corrupts absolutely.
It terrified me.
The thought of you, addicted
to your own immense power.
However, it would seem that
my anxiety was unfounded.
Robin, the question
I must ask you now is
having confronted the truth,
to what penance do you
sentence yourself?
I would sooner take my own
life than to go on like this,
as one's original sin.
I believe in you.
And no matter how cruel
the truth may actually be,
I have every faith that you
will meet it head-on.
I know you have that
strength within you.
These pages are part
of Toudou's secret journal.
Not even I know the whole truth
about what he was
trying to accomplish.
But if you read it,
I think you will know
where the answers are hidden.
Robin...
My daughter, Maria, insisted
on calling you her "hope."
Her hope?
But why?
[ROBIN] Why? What would
make her say that?
[JULIANO] I'm sorry to say, I
don't have that answer to that.
But now... Now that I've
seen you here, unchanged,
I believe I understand
what she may have meant.
What you decide
to do with that truth,
I leave in your hands.
Robin...
If you can, please
forgive this old fool.
[JULIANO] O Lord, please bestow
Thy blessings upon this child.
[beeping]
[ZAIZEN]
Hm?
What's this "Project Robin"?
[ZAIZEN]
Robin?!
[FACTORY HUNTERS gasping]
[FACTORY HUNTERS groan]
[FACTORY HUNTER 25B groans]
[DOJIMA]
He got away!
[SAKAKI]
Amon!
Inside! One of them got away!
[FACTORY HUNTER 25E panting]
[FACTORY HUNTER 25E groans]
Another one bites the dust.
[AMON]
Nagira.
Heh.
Your follow-through
always was a little weak.
[NAGIRA] Hey, mind if I
join your little gang?
Nagira?
Why are you here?
I guess I just can't bear
to stand by and watch.
Oh, Robin, by the way,
we don't really have a
tradition here in Japan
where you eat noodles
to say goodbye.
What does he mean?
Oh. Nothing.
We're running out
of time. Let's hurry.
Right.
[ZAIZEN] The file decoding
is behind schedule?
[TECH]
Yes, sir.
I apologize but
some of the files
have extremely heavy encryption.
I believe I may be able to have
it done by tomorrow night.
That's going to be too late!
Pull more personnel
if you have to,
but put a rush on that decoding!
Yes. I understand, sir.
[ZAIZEN]
A ghost from 15 years ago.
[SECURITY SYSTEM]
Now conducting security check.
Please open your face guards.
[SECURITY SYSTEM]
Pupil scan confirmed.
[DOJIMA, SAKAKI exhale]
That took years off my life.
You said it.
I wonder if Amon and
the others'll get in?
[SAKAKI]
I'm sure they'll be fine.
[DOJIMA] If they screw up,
we're on our own.
[SAKAKI]
That's... true.
[KOSAKA]
Hmm...
[HATTORI] Here, I made
you some tea, Chief.
[KOSAKA]
Hm?
Ah, thanks a lot.
[phone rings]
[KOSAKA]
Yes, sir. I understand.
I'll be there right away.
[HATTORI]
Wh-Where are you going?
[KOSAKA]
The Police Agency.
That means--!
[KOSAKA]
Mmm.
Hold down the fort, Hattori.
Yes, sir.
Please be careful out there.
[DOJIMA] Sakaki!
It's Amon and the others!
[SAKAKI]
Way to go!
[ROBIN]
Think it's them?
[MICHAEL]
Yeah.
[AMON]
Let's move out.
Sorry we're late.
Looks like it didn't matter
whether we changed
into these things or not.
Hey, I haven't seen a
person since we got here.
You sure this is
the right place?
[MICHAEL]
From what I can make out,
the real base is underground,
it's not up here on this floor.
Underground?
How do we get down
there, Michael?
We just use an elevator.
It looks like there's
only one elevator
that'll get us down there.
[elevator chimes]
[MICHAEL]
It's here!
[beeping]
[MICHAEL] You sure you wanna
go through with this?
Last chance.
[NAGIRA]
Gee, whatever shall I do?
[AMON]
Let's go.
[MICHAEL]
In that case, here goes nothin'.
[ROBIN] We're sure going
down a long way.
[SAKAKI] Security's more
lax than I expected...
[DOJIMA] But if anything
does happen down here,
there's only one exit.
[NAGIRA] So the way in is easy,
but gettin' out is a bitch, huh?
[MICHAEL] Maybe they're holding
Karasuma someplace else...
[NAGIRA gasps]
[NAGIRA]
Damn, this is confusing!
Don't you think it's safe
to take these masks off?
[AMON]
I suppose you're right.
[DOJIMA]
Hey, guys, check this out!
[AMON]
What is it?
[SAKAKI] There's a door that's
not accepting my access code.
[MICHAEL]
Let me see it for a second.
I'm gonna try looking
up a different code.
[beeping]
[MICHAEL]
Got it.
It didn't occur to me earlier,
but according to
the data I confirmed
when we were upstairs, this
place doesn't officially exist.
[NAGIRA] In other words,
we hit the jackpot.
[elevator door opens]
[SAKAKI]
What is this place?
[MICHAEL] The word "Plant"
was written by the entrance.
[NAGIRA]
"Plant"?
[DOJIMA] At any rate,
it looks like this might be
the Orbo production plant.
[SAKAKI] Hey, even if we search
this place top to bottom,
you really think Karasuma
is in here?
[ROBIN gasps]
[AMON]
Let's go.
[ROBIN]
Where?
[AMON]
We're going up there.
It's weird, she doesn't
seem to be here either.
And there's no sign of
a Witch detention center.
[NAGIRA] So then what
that hell do these guys do
in this creepy place?
[AMON]
I have no idea.
[beeping]
[gasps]
Hey, haven't we told you not--
[ALL gasp]
Oh, c'mon Robin. What did you--
A...
...girl...
[SAKAKI]
But these are...
These are witches we hunted.
[DOJIMA]
Then the Orbo back there was--
Hey, wait a minute!
That means...
This place is--!
[SAKAKI]
I get it.
This is what was really
behind our "humane" hunts!
Don't you see?
All this time we've been
helping them do this!
[ROBIN]
Karasuma...
[MICHAEL]
Huh?
I know that Karasuma is here.
It can't be...
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
The trap of perdition.
A refused successor.
An eternal war.
Believing in a hope and its
power to create the future,
I start walking now.