[MAN 18A pants]
[grunts, gasps]
I don't know!
I don't know anything about
the Fragment of Wisdom!
I know that already.
[MAN 18A]
Then why are you after me?!
Because you just happened
to find out what it is
I'm searching for.
That is an unforgiveable sin.
[MAN 18A groans, rasps]
I can't do it...
I can not go back there...
[NAGIRA]
Are you up?
[ROBIN gasps]
Uh, yes...
[NAGIRA] Sorry, but
I've got a job for you.
Can you get dressed
and come downstairs?
I understand...
[ROBIN]
Is it a rush?
You could say that.
I'm sorry I had to wake
you up so early for work.
[ROBIN]
It's okay.
I'll get going.
Oh, good morning, sir...
'Mornin'.
You're up early.
[NAGIRA] Well, I've got
something to do...
So, what's up with him?
[NAGIRA] Jeez, did you have to
meet me in such a creepy place?
I hope you're not
trying to sell me some more
useless information again.
[SUZUKI] I'll guarantee that
you'll buy this info from me
no matter how cheap you are.
[NAGIRA]
That's a mouthful.
All right, I'm listenin'.
[SUZUKI chuckles]
A little while back,
the old lady who was the master
of this whole area finally died.
[NAGIRA] Yeah, I've heard
something about that.
You mean the old lady that
people used to think
was immortal.
Yeah.
Oh, c'mon now, is that
all the information
that you've got for me?
Just give me a second.
Well, then how about
the fact that the old woman
happened to be
a pretty good informant
when it came to witches?
[NAGIRA]
She wasn't just "pretty good."
Rumor has it that the old lady
knew everything
that there was to know
about witches and then some!
Yeah, well after the
old woman finally gave up
the ghost, it seems
she left a little thing
called the Fragment of Wisdom.
The Fragment of Wisdom?
What the hell is
that supposed to be?
Who knows?
But the rumor around
town is that Solomon
is looking for it...
--[NAGIRA] Solomon?!
--Ugh.
This isn't some
sort of hoax, is it?
I told you before,
it's just a rumor.
Well then, if Solomon
is actually looking
for this thing...
Does that mean it has
information on witches?
If something like that
were to fall into their hands...
...this could get
real messy real fast.
I see, you're
interested, aren't you?
[NAGIRA]
Hmph, all right then.
I'll buy it off
of you this time.
But you're gonna
have to work a little
before I pay you for it.
What do you mean, "work"?
I want you to go
and find out for me where
that little Fragment
of Wisdom is now.
Hey, wait a minute!
That's asking way too much!
If that's a problem,
then the story ends here.
You're not the only one
who sells information.
Oh, c'mon!
Be reasonable!
Okay, fine...
You're always like this,
you know that, Nagira?
So, the Fragment of Wisdom...
Huh...
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
That convenience store...
That's the one
that's close to...
...Touko's place.
[ROBIN gasps]
[DOJIMA]
Hm?
What are you guys doing?
--Oh, hi there, Miss Dojima.
--You're here early.
So, what is it
you're checking out?
[SAKAKI]
A recent murder.
Do you remember the Walled City?
You know, that area where we
hunted that witch a while back?
Well, it seems
that there have been
quite a few murders there
in the past few days.
So you think it
might be a witch?
[MICHAEL] Turns out, one of
the victims just happened to be
on our list.
So, we looked up
the other ones, too...
So what? Some of
the others are witches?
[SAKAKI]
No, more like all of them.
All of 'em?!
C'mon, you guys make it
sound like the witches are
out there fighting each
other or something!
[MICHAEL] Yeah. Chances are
that's what's happening.
Huh?
[ROBIN]
Mailbox.
The letter...
[ROBIN]
How could I forget
something so important...?
[ROBIN]
It's still there.
It's dangerous...
But I have to...
[ROBIN]
It's gone...
What could've happened to it?
[pantin]
You mean that someone
else is looking for it, too?
[SUZUKI] There's something
bad going down.
It's better you stay out of it!
[NAGIRA]
Who is it?!
[SUZUKI]
Are you sure?
[NAGIRA]
Spit it out!
All right, then,
I'm gonna tell you...
It's the Professor.
The Professor?
And there seems
to be a few other people
that are after it, too.
So it's not just Solomon,
but it looks like the
ever-cautious Professor
is on the move as well...
I guess that means
this thing is pretty important.
Hey, let's leave
this one alone, okay?
There are rumors flying around
that people are
dying for this...
They're dying for it?
You mean they're
killing each other?
I'm sure the allies
betrayed one another.
What do you mean, "allies"?
'Cause from what I've heard,
the Professor always
works by himself.
Well, that's true enough--
In any case, just keep up
the investigation.
That's easy for you to say--
And in return, I'll be very
generous with your reward.
Well, okay then. All right...
[NAGIRA]
See ya.
[rock music blaring]
[KARASUMA] Hey, Michael, I read
that report from this morning...
Maybe we should
check out this case
and see if there's anything--
[MICHAEL]
I can hear you.
Yeah, the Walled City
case, right?
I guess you got a point.
But isn't it too dangerous
to go in alone?
I'm just gonna go over there and
see how things are going.
[MICHAEL] I see... In that
case, I'll retrieve the data.
I appreciate it.
Looks like the police
are on the move as well...
I guess the rumors
about people dying
for this are true after all.
Well, Professor, it's
not like you to be in
such a rush to get something.
[knocking]
Who is it?
[NAGIRA]
It's me. Can I come in?
Oh, sure.
[ROBIN]
What is it?
There was something that I
wanted to ask you about...
About a month
and a half ago now,
a certain old lady died
in the Walled City area.
[gasps]
I see, then...
So they were watching
her after all.
But how did you
manage to find out about
that old woman's death?
It wasn't that hard--there
were all those insane rumors
going around that she was
immortal and would never die...
But even if it
turned out she was a witch,
I wouldn't put much
stock in those rumors.
Anyway, that's beside the point.
The problem now is
that after she died,
she left behind something
called the Fragment of Wisdom.
The Fragment of Wisdom?
Yeah. And because of that thing,
the Walled City is a bit
of a mess right now.
So I was wondering if
you'd heard anything about it.
Nothing...
Being sworn to secrecy.
Don't tell me that you're still
tied down to that syndicate.
Never mind, then.
I don't have to hear
about it from you,
I'll just look for it myself.
Sorry to have bothered you.
How did you hear about it?
I've heard that Solomon
is looking around
for this thing as well.
[ROBIN gasps]
I can't just let myself stand
by and watch as people are
being killed and not
do anything about it.
[ROBIN]
The Fragment of Wisdom...
The Secrets of the Craft...
She clearly knows
something about all of this.
This could turn
out to be a bigger case
than I had imagined...
[gasps]
[HANAMURA]
Oh, good morning.
Where's Nagira?
Hey, what's with the hairdo?
Well...
I really don't think
he's come in yet today.
[DOJIMA]
Hey, where's Miho?
[SAKAKI]
Dunno...
She went to go
check out the Walled City.
She went to the Walled City?
[SAKAKI]
She checkin' out the murders?
[MICHAEL]
Yeah.
--[DOJIMA] Hmm?
--[SAKAKI] You forgot already?
We were just talking
about it yesterday...
Oh, you mean the
place where the witches
are fighting each other...
Unbelievable...
[DOJIMA] Hmm, but is
she gonna be all right
going in there by herself?
[NAGIRA]
A guy who knows where
the Fragment of
Wisdom is located?
[SUZUKI]
Yeah, that's right.
[giggles]
Right. So tell me-- what
happened to your face, anyway?
My face? What?
It's no big deal.
I just had
a little girl trouble.
Anyway, what do you wanna do?
Do you wanna meet him?
Huh.
All right, then. Let's go
ahead and do this thing.
But if it's a hoax, you're
gonna need some more band-aids.
Huh?
What? This is no hoax,
trust me on this one.
And spare me from your wrath!
[guffaws]
[phone ringing]
[HANAMURA]
Well, that's strange...
He's not picking up...
Usually he calls to
check in with me at least...
I don't have to
hear about it from you,
I'll just look for it myself.
I can't just let myself
stand by and watch as people are
being killed and
not do anything about it.
I'm going to go look for him.
What? Look for him?
Do you mean to say
you know where he went?
[ROBIN]
I don't really know...
...for sure.
But on the other hand...
...I do.
What does she mean by that?
Is this it?
[NAGIRA] Is this where I'm
supposed to meet this guy?
[PROFESSOR]
That's right.
[NAGIRA gasps]
The Professor...
I see now.
So you're the one
who invited me here.
[NAGIRA]
Tch. That idiot...
[PROFESSOR] You have a sensitive
nose for sniffing things out.
However...
It seems you're
not quite as aware
when it comes to matters
concerning your own life.
[NAGIRA]
Ugh!
[ROBIN]
Michael...
Huh?
[ROBIN]
Are you're there, Michael?
Robin...
--Are you in there?
--[ROBIN] Be careful!
Act as if nothing's going on.
[MICHAEL groans]
This well seems to have a lot
more to it than I thought.
Anyway, what have you
been doing for the past month?
[ROBIN]
I'm sorry...
I was worried about
all of you, but...
Yeah, I understand...
Although, I'm not sure what's
going on around here nowadays.
So, what is it
you'd like me to do?
[ROBIN]
Huh?
You took a big risk
coming here to see me.
So tell me what
I can do for you.
About the Walled City?
You mean that guy really
went in there to try to find out
about the missing witches?
[ROBIN]
Most likely.
That's probably not the
safest thing for him to do.
It looks like there's
a huge war going on
between all the witches
in the Walled City.
There's a war?
It's about the secrets...
Michael, do you
think you can track down
his current location?
I'm searching for
him right now.
[ROBIN] I'm sure he has
his cellphone on him.
Maybe you can trace that.
Well, that's
not impossible, but...
This place is like a rat's nest,
it's a maze of
buildings and alleyways.
Even so, if someone
with one of our terminals
was nearby the place,
I could track him
using their connection...
That's right, Miss Karasuma!
She was headed
that way earlier this afternoon.
If she's still there,
I should be able to
use her terminal.
Robin, what's that person's ID?
It's really hot down here.
Do you think you could at least
turn on the air conditioning?
So you're still trying
to play the wise-guy.
I did a little bit
of research on you...
It looks like I was completely
mistaken in thinking
that you knew anything
about this matter.
It's vexing how you made me
waste my valuable time.
[NAGIRA chuckles weakly]
You contemptable fool.
[gasps]
A woman?
[PROFESSOR snarls]
What's that?!
[gasps]
[gasps
[ROBIN]
Nagira...
Impossible...
[NAGIRA]
That's hot!
Oh, I'm sorry.
[NAGIRA grunts]
Forget it.
[NAGIRA]
Thanks...
It's nothing...
[NAGIRA grunts] I gotta say your
powers are pretty impressive.
Must be pretty nice
to be a hunter.
That guy you just
killed--the Professor--
he happened to be the most
powerful witch around here.
And you were able to
take care of him so easily!
[ROBIN]
I didn't.
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
That was a power that
was not controlled by my will.
I didn't intend to send
that much power out.
[ROBIN gasps]
The secrets...?
[NAGIRA]
What's that thing?
[ROBIN] This is the deepest
knowledge of the craft
that was given to
me by Methuselah.
It's the Secrets of the Craft.
The Secrets of the Craft?
And, most probably,
it's the Fragment of Wisdom.
What?!
You mean you had the Fragment
of Wisdom this whole time?
Dammit, what the hell
have I been doing then?!
[ROBIN]
I'm sorry...
Wait a second.
If the secret that you have in
your hand there really is
the Fragment of Wisdom,
then the power you just used...
Oh. I get it now...
So that's the reason they
were killing each other--
to get their hands
on that dried-up stick.
Solomon...
Robin.
I was just thinking about
something.
The reason that you
were being chased
by the guys from Solomon...
Do you think it might
actually have been
because of that thing?
[NARRATOR] Three hundred and
twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Forbidden knowledge.
Endless Remorse.
One ideal.
Those without a future aren't
even allowed to think now.