[COPS gasp]
[TOUKO] Robin? Robin?
Sleeping out here again.
[ROBIN]
Mm... Uh, good morning.
[ROBIN grunts]
[TOUKO] Looks like you were
up late again last night.
Are you all right?
[ROBIN grunts]
[TOUKO]
You'd like some coffee, right?
Yes, please... Touko?
[TOUKO]
Hm?
[ROBIN]
I saw you the other day.
When you were with Amon.
[TOUKO gasps]
I had no idea you
knew each other.
Perhaps you're lovers?
[TOUKO]
Don't be silly.
[ROBIN]
Hmm...
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
Yes?
Amon...? Yes.
You mean right now?
[ROBIN]
All right.
[MICHAEL] Normally,
the impact from falling
or even the water
pressure afterwards
couldn't crush anything
as badly as this.
It's someone with
extraordinary powers.
That is, if it was
actually done by a witch.
The driver who died in it was a
32 year-old named Ryoji Kasai.
Do you remember the big
200-million-yen robbery
that happened in
Tokyo last month?
Are you talking
about the one where
those guys took that
armored car out?
They checked the bills
in Kasai's pockets
to see if they matched,
and one of the serial
numbers was traced
to the shipment in the
armored car that day.
Not only that,
but Kasai worked
at a security company
that did armored transport
until about three months
before the incident.
[KARASUMA] So in other words,
they think he had a hand in it.
[DOJIMA]
Okay, so what?
Do they expect us
to find the rest
of the money or something?
[ZAIZEN]
No, that's for the police to do.
Until we hear otherwise,
they're handling it.
For now, it's a
potential homicide
with a ties to a
robbery and that's it.
We'll stay in the loop.
I want to see how this
investigation develops
in case signs of
a witch show up.
[KOBARI]
So, how are things going?
[ROBIN]
Huh?
You made a big
change moving here.
Well... it seems like every
day's a battle against time
and I always lose.
Like this morning.
Somehow I couldn't
get any breakfast.
Well, that doesn't
sound very good.
You're going to have to take
better care of your health.
Now then, would you care for
another espresso, perhaps?
[ROBIN]
Yes, thank you.
--[phone rings]
--[ROBIN] Oh.
[ROBIN]
Yes?
[AMON] This is the hospital
where they brought
the driver of the armored
car that was robbed.
They already took
a police report,
but it wouldn't hurt
to double-check.
[DRIVER]
This again.
Just like I said
every other time.
No matter what I did,
the steering wheel
just wouldn't respond.
[AMON] So... you're
saying it wasn't a case
of driver error.
Yeah, you heard me.
But then...
...what caused you to
lose control like that?
How do you expect me to know?
I was too busy trying
to make it out alive
to think about that.
Understood.
But when they inspected the
steering mechanism later,
they couldn't find
anything wrong.
Isn't that why you
guys suspect me?
You figure I was
just playing dumb.
I musta been in on it
from the beginning, right?
But I wasn't! It's true.
I didn't have anything
to do with it!
[DRIVER groans]
I'm sick of the whole thing.
[computer beeps]
Oh, yeah, that's what
I want to see.
[phone rings]
[MICHAEL]
I've got an interesting bit
of police news here.
They've been looking
into this Kasai
and they think one of his
buddies might be involved.
Suneo Tazawa, 37 years old.
He used to work for a
scrap metal company.
[ZAIZEN]
What about the witch list?
[MICHAEL] There were
no hits from the list.
I see. And what are
the police up to now?
[MICHAEL] They're on
their way to arrest him.
Should we go ahead of them?
We can't. They won't allow us
to meddle in something like this
until we actually know
that this Tazawa's a witch.
We'll have to tell them to
exercise some patience here.
[MICHAEL]
Gotcha, boss.
[COPS quizically grunt]
[COP A]
Mr. Tazawa!
[BIRD chirps]
[COP A]
Hm?
[car engine sputters]
[COP A]
Tazawa!
Dammit!
[gasps]
[DOJIMA]
Hey, that's Tazawa!
[grunts]
[DOJIMA gasps]
[KARASUMA]
This is bad!
[DOJIMA gasps]
Michael. Hello, are you there?
[MICHAEL]
What is it?
Tazawa just ran for it.
There are two cops
pursuing right now.
[MICHAEL]
Are you guys okay?
We're fine, but the
car's a mess.
He's a witch, all right.
I'm sure he's the one
who demolished that car.
[grunts]
I'm not gonna let 'em catch me.
[MAMORU]
Uncle!
I'm really thirsty.
[TAZAWA]
Here, have some juice.
Oh, thank you, Uncle.
[MICHAEL] The police were
right on his tail...
..but they lost sight
of Tazawa's vehicle
somewhere around the
Sasajima intersection.
[AMON]
Sasajima?
[MICHAEL] Yeah, so I
did a little searching
and it looks like the
scrap metal company
where Tazawa used to
work is right in that area.
[MICHAEL]
You want to go check it out?
[AMON]
Where is it?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
--[tires screech]
--[TAZAWA gasps]
Sakaki, you gotta
stop that machine!
[SAKAKI pants]
[SAKAKI]
How do I work this thing?!
Get out, Sakaki, I can do it!
[SAKAKI gasps]
Robin! Use your
glasses, will ya?!
Oh. Sorry about that.
I guess I forgot.
[SAKAKI]
Jeez. Watch it, okay?
What are you trying
to do, burn me?!
[ROBIN]
You're not gonna burn, Sakaki.
You've got the Orbo.
[SAKAKI]
That's not the point!
When we go on things like this,
you should always
have your glasses on.
[AMON]
Sakaki!
Get Michael on the line,
we're gonna need an ambulance!
[ROBIN, SAKAKI]
Huh?
[AMON]
There's a child inside the car.
[ROBIN]
There's a child?
[DOCTOR]
It looks like somebody gave him
some juice that was drugged.
He's in a very deep
sleep right now,
but he'll be fine
when he wakes up.
Well, that's good to know.
[MICHAEL] The case itself
is simple enough.
Tazawa must have
been the mastermind.
He probably just
brought Kasai in
because he had
inside information
about the cash deliveries.
Perhaps. But now that Tazawa's
power has been revealed,
he's going to be that much
more aggesive and dangerous.
And as I'm sure
you all realize,
witches prefer to
hide their powers,
and they try to blend in
as much as they can.
It's very rare to reveal it to
someone who's not a witch,
and when they do,
it's usually the
result of a trauma
or some kind of mental
stress that's caused
by an emotional breakdown.
According to the police records,
they were both compulsive
gamblers who owed a lot of
money to various people.
So does that mean he
killed Kasai to cover
his own tracks and also
not have to divide
the money afterward?
Maybe they both wanted it
all and he just got lucky
and pull it off
before he got to him.
[AMON]
In any case,
whatever happens, Tazawa knows
that the law's after him
and he knows he's
opened Pandora's box.
We don't necessarily
know what he'll do next,
but he won't hesitate
to use his powers.
[KARASUMA]
What about the boy?
[MICHAEL]
Mamoru Kudo, age seven.
He's a distant
relative of Tazawa's.
It seems his parents
passed away recently.
For the past six months or so,
he's been living with Tazawa.
[DOCTOR A] How do you feel?
Do you have any pain?
Good. You should be fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
We'll keep an eye on you here
for the next two or three days
just to see how you're
doing all righty?
If he starts having headaches,
call me immediately, okay?
Well that's a relief.
I'm glad nothing's
seriously wrong.
Hey, that's not so bad.
Is there anything you need?
[MAMORU]
Uncle...
[gasps]
[MAMORU]
Uncle...
[ROBIN]
Huh?
What happened to my uncle?
Where's my Uncle Tazawa?
Oh, Mamoru...
[ROBIN] He doesn't know that
his Uncle tried to kill him.
He seems very worried
about Tazawa.
That's horrible! He was
like a parent to him.
And also... that little
boy trusted him.
He's just a big oni .
Hm? Oni ?
An Oni is probably what they'd
call a hobgoblin or a troll
in Europe. No, that's not
exactly right.
[ROBIN]
A demon...
A witch.
[DOJIMA]
Huh?
[DOJIMA] Look, the only
reason we came here
was so we could pick
up the boy's clothes
and some everyday things
for him, that's all!
[ROBIN]
And to feed the parakeet.
[COP B] We'll send it
over to you later on.
Just give us a list.
Right now, this site's
part of an investigation.
And even the STN needs a
proper warrant to enter
a sealed investigation
site like this.
Look, he's a little boy
in the hospital, okay?
Why don't you give the
kid a break, okay?!
[COP B]
As I keep trying to--
[COP A]
Oh now, hold on a second.
It can't hurt to
let them do that.
But it's against--
Oh, okay. Wait here!
Don't worry.
Just regulations, okay?
Try not to let it bother ya.
Okay...
[COP B]
Here! This should be enough!
Why don't you just
take them and get lost?
[DOJIMA grunts]
...Hmph!
Thank you very much.
Dojima!
Okay, I'm curious now.
Do you mind telling
me about this STN?
I suggest you forget 'em.
I've known too many detectives
who dug into their business
and then disappeared.
[COP B gasps]
That guy was a jerk!
[WOMAN A]
Did something happen over there?
Oh, that's Mamoru's
parakeet, isn't it?
Do you know the
boy named Mamoru?
Oh, you must be from social
services to look after him.
You know, I really feel
sorry for that boy.
The way I hear it,
both his parents
died and since then
he's been passed around
by his relatives.
What does she mean,
"passed around"?
[DOJIMA sighs]
Go on...
Well, after all that,
Mr. Tazawa took over custody,
but he's pretty
much neglected him.
It was pretty bad.
He didn't pay much
attention to him.
Then on the other hand, he is
an awfully strange child.
Oh, now there, there, darling.
Do you remember those stunts
people used to do on TV?
Bending spoons and such?
I guess he just thought
it was fun to show folks
how he could twist
things with his mind.
Maybe that's why none
of his relatives
wanted to keep him for very--
[DOJIMA]
Wait a minute!
Are you telling me Mamoru
was the one bending them?
It wasn't Tazawa?!
Tazawa bend things?!
Fat chance!
All that good for nothing
can do is drink himself silly
from the time he gets
up till he passes out.
He can bend an elbow
and the truth,
but I'd say that's about it.
[MICHAEL]
There we go!
Signs of a witch
just two degrees
away from that little boy.
That's gotta be it then.
So I wonder why
our friend Tazawa
wanted to kill the boy then.
He just wanted to
cover his tracks.
[ROBIN]
Mamoru?
[AMON] The guys from the factory
are heading for the hospital.
We need to take
custody of the boy
before the police get to him.
Yes, but the Factory would...
[AMON]
Keep your emotions out of it.
I know he's just a kid,
and we know Tazawa
totally controlled him,
but he's already
killed one time.
[bird chirps]
[DOJIMA gasps]
[beeping]
[NURSE A]
May I help you?
[DOJIMA] Yes, hi, it's about
the patient in room 203.
Is he with a doctor
or something?
[NURSE A-7]
No. Isn't he in his room?
[DOJIMA]
When did they check him last?
[NURSE A-7]
About 20 minutes ago.
[DOJIMA gasps]
[NURSE A-7]
Is something wrong? Hello?
[chuckles]
[TAZAWA grunts]
[police sirens]
[TAZAWA]
Dammit! Stupid Cops!
[MAMORU]
Uncle?
[TAZAWA]
Huh?
[gasps]
Hi, Uncle! I haven't
seen you for a while.
M-Mamoru...!
[MICHAEL] The police
have Tazawa surrounded.
You should head over
there and join Amon.
The location is--
[ROBIN gasps]
Mamoru...
I don't get it. Why would
he want to save Tazawa?
Amon...
Let's look around!
We have to find that kid or
it could mean serious trouble!
[TAZAWA pants]
[MAMORU]
Come on, Uncle, hurry up!
Um... Uncle?
You didn't... You didn't
try to kill me, did you?
Why? Who told you that?
Aren't you gonna pick those up?
Listen, I...!
Pick 'em all up.
[TAZAWA gasps]
[MAMORU] Why? Was I in
the way, Uncle? Was that it?
Look, I'll give you
the money, okay?
You can have it all, I swear.
[MAMORU giggles]
You're strange, Uncle.
You know the money's
already mine,
cause I earned it
myself with my power.
Right?
But then you, Uncle...
And Uncle Kasai, too.
You guys tried to
take it from me
and hog it all for yourselves.
You gotta...
You gotta forgive me!
I-I... Somebody help me!
Help! Help!
[gasps]
[TAZAWA gasps]
You shouldn't have tried to
kill me like that, you know.
No. Don't do it.
No! Don't do this, Mamoru!
Don't do it, Mamoru!
Stop it, I beg you! No!
[TAZAWA screams]
[MAMORU]
Huh?
But he... my uncle...
He tried to kill me, and then...
I mean, I only...
They're not going to
take me away, are they?
[MAMORU]
Oh, it's all right.
Don't worry,
they'll forgive me.
I'm only a kid, after all.
I'll be back to
see you real soon.
I'm just a little boy.
Huh?
[MAMORU gasps]
[ROBIN]
That was the Factory?
[AMON]
Let's go.
[NARRATOR]
Three hundred and twenty years
have passed since the
coven sank in the dark.
Ritual of darkness.
Changing lives.
[NARRATOR]
Straying from the right path.
Even a chosen one is not
allowed to evaluate souls.