[police sirens wailing]
[COP 17A] Can we get the
coroner over here as well?
[COP 17B]
Hey! Be careful over there.
[KARASUMA grunts]
[KARASUMA]
It's no use...
I can't get a good reading.
My powers...
They're definitely
beginning to weaken...
[MICHAEL]
Keiko Muramatsu, 23 years old.
[MICHAEL] If I put
the info from the police
and Miss Karasuma together,
then it's pretty clear that
she's the one
bombing all these ATMs.
[KOSAKA]
I'll leave this to you,
but better be quick about it.
We still have
a very long way to go.
How much longer
will it take, you think?
Before we hunt them
all of them down?
[MICHAEL]
Let's see...
From this list of
possibilities...
And... at the pace
we're going...
I'd say it'd take
about 30 more years.
Aw, that long?!
[MICHAEL]
That long...
[sighs]
I guess I'm gonna
spend the rest of my life
hunting and paying off loans...
But you're not
doing any of the hunting.
[KOSAKA] It would be
a lot easier for us
if our manager could narrow
down the list of targets...
...just like he
always used to do...
[SAKAKI] I'm sure things'll
be getting better soon.
Heh?
[SAKAKI] When I get
back onto the front line,
the hunts will be
a lot more effective.
And besides, it's not
like you administrative guys
are stuck here for
life or anything like that.
Unlike the rest
of us actual hunters...
[HATTORI]
Y-You misunderstand.
It's not that I
don't like this job...
[MICHAEL] But even if
you come back, Haruto,
we're still gonna
need a replacement.
[GROUP gasps]
[MICHAEL] I think it's about
time that we faced the facts...
Either they were abducted...
...or they're in hiding.
Or else they were killed.
In any case,
Amon and Robin aren't here.
You seem so calm,
don't you, Michael?
[KOSAKA growls]
[gasps]
[NAGIRA]
You know where it is?
[ROBIN]
I went there the other day...
[NAGIRA] Be sure to follow their
instructions once you get there.
[ROBIN]
Okay.
[NAGIRA]
Oh, and when you're done,
make sure you have them
treat you to some soba noodles.
Soba noodles?
[NAGIRA] Yeah. The reason
I want you to get
the soba noodles is because--
[HANAMURA] Are you
stepping out for a second, sir?
[NAGIRA] Um... Yeah, just
for a bit to see Robin off.
Yeah, or so you say.
You sure you're
not going for pachinko?
[NAGIRA gasps]
Hey, wanna come with me?
Our client will be
here any minute!
Can't you get
a hold of yourself?
You completely stood
them up last time
and then you blamed it...
[KARASUMA]
Ask Robin? To hunt?
Yeah, let's get her to help us.
Robin, huh?
Robin was nice enough
to help me out the other day.
But then, if I get
caught like that again...
If I get into that
much trouble next time...?
Even being invulnerable
isn't enough.
Besides, Miho, aren't you
pushing the limit yourself?
Huh?
[DOJIMA]
You're planning every hunt,
and then executing
them all by yourself...
I know that you have to
pick up the slack now
that Amon's gone, but you're
gonna burn out if you
keep this up.
And you know how Sakaki is.
Who knows if he'll
actually follow orders
when he's ready to hunt again?
So, just have Robin...
[KARASUMA]
...put herself in danger again?
[DOJIMA gasps]
[KARASUMA] If the people
who attacked this place
before really
were after Robin,
then we'll just be putting
her in danger again.
[DOJIMA] I don't think we
have to worry about that.
[KARASUMA]
Why not?
Because, those guys
were only after the Orbo
and Michael's data.
[KARASUMA] How can you
be so sure about that?
We don't even know
who they really are yet.
And, also...
If that attack squad
really did come from Solomon,
it means that Robin is the one
that they're hunting now.
In tha case...
[KARASUMA]
Could you bring yourself to...
...hunt her...
...with your own hands...?
[MOTHER] It's all right,
I'll be able to see you soon.
Do you really mean it?
[MOTHER]
I mean it.
Here, ♪  I swear on this pinky,
a red bean pastry, ♪
♪ a chocolate pastry! ♪
[BOTH giggle]
[MOTHER]
If you're a good girl,
your baby sitter promises
to buy you takoyaki.
[MINORI]
Okay!
What are the chances of
that happening again...?
[sighs]
[gasps]
Yeah, bingo!
All right, let's go!
Start! Come on, dammit!
Ugh! Please, I'm begging you!
Why won't you just start for me?
[ROBIN]
So, What am I supposed to do?
[GUY A] You mean, Mr. Nagira
didn't tell you, huh?
[ROBIN]
No...
[GUY A] All you need to do
is babysit the girl.
Babysit?
[GUY A]
Yeah, that's it.
I can't believe my luck!
Clearly, this has gotta
be a sign from God.
Let's do it!
C'mon! Not this again!
[gasps]
Oh...
Damn this stupid thing!
[GUY A]
Well, have a nice time!
Let's go.
[MINORI]
Wow!
It's yummy.
[MINORI]
U-Uh...
What's is it?
Do you need a drink?
[gasps]
This big thing was inside there!
[ROBIN]
A devil...
Huh?
Across the sea from us,
some people call an octopus
a "devilfish." They think it
must be a fish of the devil.
Wow! Is that true?
You bad little devilfish!
Devils like you get eaten!
Aah!
But this little devil
is very tasty.
Bad people can be
devils, too, you know.
[ROBIN]
Huh? People?
Yeah! They took my daddy away.
The devil people came and
took him far away from here.
[ROBIN]
They came and took him away?
[MINORI] Mama told me we had
to move out of our house or else
the devil people would
come and take us away, too.
So that's why my mama said
that we have to move away
from this place.
Devil people...
that take you away...
This devil right here
is gonna move into my tummy!
That's very strange.
Why does that little
ball shine so much?
I mean, it's just
a ball of mud...
Dumpling.
This is a mud dumpling.
[ROBIN]
Dumpling?
Yeah, that's right!
It gets much, much, much,
much, much, much, shinier!
♪ Shiny, shiny, shiny!
Make it shiny, shiny! ♪
But this is...
What are you doing?
Huh...?
What did you do just now?
Tell me what you did!
[MINORI]
Ah!
[whimpers, wails]
[ROBIN]
No doubt about it.
That was definitely...
a witch's power...
Dormant ability...
Then uncontrollable
powers suddenly manifest...
[wailling continues]
[ROBIN] If I had met this
child a month ago...
...would I have hunted her?
[DOJIMA] What do
you think you're doing,
making a little girl cry?
[ROBIN]
Huh?
Dojima...
[MINORI]
Mama!
I wanna go back to my mama!
I wanna go back!
[wails]
I'm so sorry...
Yes, that's right.
You have to apologize
now, little Robin.
Please, forgive me.
Okay. There we go. And now,
it's time to make up.
Heh...
Well, isn't that nice?
You did very well there,
little Robin.
Now, I wonder, do you
think you can tell me
what your name is, little lady?
It's Minori!
Minori Nakayama.
But Mama told me that
I'm going to be Minori Yoshida
from today on!
[DOJIMA]
Oh, I see!
Well then, Minori...
It's time to go on the slides!
Yay! I love that!
[DOJIMA]
Okay, but be careful!
From today on, huh?
[MINORI]
Whee!
I take it this isn't a
normal babysitting job, is it?
Well, I'm sure that you
must have your reasons.
Maybe you're on the run
from a loan shark?
Or just maybe you're just
trying to hide your identity.
[MINORI laughs]
[DOJIMA]
Your job now...
Is it a lot more dangerous
than being a hunter?
Anyway, it's fine.
I'm not gonna pry too deep.
Uh, Dojima...
What is it?
Why did you come here today?
What? Why did I come?
I just wanted to
see you, that's all.
I was checking out
that area where you saved me,
and I looked up
and saw you go by.
So I chased after you
using your scooter.
But the thing kept
breaking down and I--
[ROBIN]
I told you.
Huh? You did? When was that?
What did you tell me?
If you stay too close to me,
you'll be in great danger.
I know, but I don't care.
Please. Listen, Robin--
I'm begging!
As a huge favor?
Oh, come on, Robin, just
think about it for a minute.
I know it's a hard
thing to talk about, but...
[ROBIN]
I can't do it.
I thought about it, but
I just can't go through with it.
[DOJIMA] Look, the chances
of you being chased by
the syndicate are
basically zero, I'd say.
[ROBIN]
Why is that...?
[DOJIMA] You're trying
to blend into the crowd,
because you think
the best place to hide
a tree is in the forest, right?
But if Solomon
headquarters had really wanted
to hunt you down, Robin,
they would've done it already.
You wouldn't be running
around free this long.
So please, Robin,
I'm begging for you
to help me out with this.
Lend me a hand.
Besides, I'm really scared.
And if things
stay like this, then I...
[ROBIN]
But, you have to keep going...
Huh?
[ROBIN] If you try
to stop hunting now,
you'll become the
one who is hunted.
But Robin...
[DOJIMA]
What am I supposed to do?
Well, I'll see you both later.
Well then...
We'll leave the rest to you.
[SAKAKI] Those two
always seem to make sure
they never work overtime.
I should follow their
example for once.
--[ringing]
--[gasps]
Hey there, Miss Karasuma.
[KARASUMA]
I'm following the target.
I'll wait for an opening
and then proceed
with the operation.
[MICHAEL] Wait a second!
It's dangerous to move in alone!
--Have Dojima join you.
--[comm static]
What's up with her?
She keeps on going in solo!
Why is she in such a hurry?
[cat yowls]
I'm commencing the
operation immediately.
Send a request to the Factory.
[SAKAKI]
Dammit!
Where the hell is Miss Dojima?!
I've been calling her
for a while now!
[DOJIMA]
Come on, please, help me!
I'm begging you!
It's the biggest
favor of my life.
Please, just this once!
[ROBIN gasps]
It's impossible.
Even if I wanted to,
I'm babysitting right now...
--[car approaching]
--[MINORI gasps]
It looks like her ride's here.
How lucky is that?
[KARASUMA]
Hold it right there!
Oh, I've heard of
you people. Of course...
But I never really
thought we'd meet.
Just can it.
Humph!
[MURAMATSU grunts]
[MURAMATSU]
Rah!
[MURAMATSU grunts]
[KARASUMA]
This is the end of the line!
Time for you to sleep.
[gun clicking]
[MURAMATSU chuckles]
[KARASUMA groans]
[MURAMATSU]
This is gonna be a big one!
[MURAMATSU laughs]
Time for you to die now!
[MURAMATSU]
This next one is the best!
[gasps]
Robin!
She said "Robin"?
What's that? Are you sure?!
Was that your doing?!
Dojima! Hunting her is your job!
But!
[MURAMATSU growls]
[MURAMATSU grunting]
[MURAMATSU yelps]
Hey! I did it!
I really did it!
I hunted a witch!
That's right.
You did a good job, Yurika.
So it's true. You're safe.
Thank goodness.
Yeah...
Looks like you're having a...
...hard time.
[DOJIMA]
See? We really do need you.
This just proves that
we need your help, Robin.
[KARASUMA] The Factory
is headed here right now...
You should get going.
I understand.
Thank you so much, Robin...
Ah...
Could you fix my partner?
If you don't mind.
[DOJIMA chuckles]
[NAGIRA slurps]
[NAGIRA] In Japan, there's a
custom where you eat soba
when you're moving.
[slurps]
[NAGIRA] Now, I won't
ask you what happened,
but I'm not gonna
clean up after you, either.
If something happens...
...you better be prepared.
[ROBIN]
That child...
...she was a Seed, wasn't she?
[NAGIRA]
Hm?
[ROBIN] Nagira, are you
trying to save witches?
[NAGIRA slurps]
[ROBIN] Are you the leader of
a syndicate that opposes
the STN-J or something?
[NAGIRA] That's enough
dinner for tonight.
I don't do anything
as troublesome as all that.
But you see... It's like
I was saying before.
I just don't appreciate
it when people
try to lock folks up.
I guess that's all
there really is to it.
[ROBIN] I see. That's why
you're helping them.
[NAGIRA]
Who knows?
But if that's true...
Amon is...
...your enemy...
Yeah, I guess so.
But then, why do you help him?
I just can't sever
ties with him.
[ROBIN]
Sever ties...?
Way back, Amon
and I actually lived
together for a few months or so.
A long time ago,
when we were both just kids...
Together... with Amon...
[NAGIRA]
Yeah...
[ROBIN] I helped hunt
down a witch again today...
From now on...
...what should I do...?
[ROBIN]
Amon...
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
The fragment
for three centuries...
Stalking nightmares...
A letter from back
of the memories...
An immortal phantom
drives habitants
of darkness to the
feast of lust.