[KARASUMA]
Amazing.
[MICHAEL] Her maximum range
is up by ten percent,
and her accuracy
is now 98 percent.
That makes her almost perfect.
[whistles]
That means we'll finally
get some use out of her.
She can go home.
--[beeping]
--[MICHAEL] Hm?
But, she says she wants
to do some more.
[AMON]
Tell her to hold back a bit.
[ROBIN] I didn't think
I was running that low.
[thunder]
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
What should I do?
I'm lucky that you came by.
[EIKO]
Yes you are.
Because it'd take you
well over an hour
to get to town from here,
And besides, a girl shouldn't
be walking here all by herself.
There are too many
scary criminals around.
Oh, I didn't know that.
[EIKO] Oh, very much so,
and there are a lot of kids
like you out there these days.
[ROBIN]
Huh?
[EIKO] I'm on my way right now
to give a piece of my mind
to a young girl who couldn't
even bother to call in sick.
If she really doesn't
feel like working,
I wish she would just quit.
Ridiculous.
Kids nowadays, I swear.
[EIKO] Work is how society
knows that you exist.
And life just isn't any fun
unless you pitch in
and work hard,
at least to show that you
wanna be a part of it all.
I know what you mean.
[EIKO laughs]
[ROBIN]
Did I say something strange?
[EIKO]
I'm sorry.
But it's just that I didn't
expect you to agree with me,
that's all.
Well, thank you very much.
Oh, wait a minute.
Here, go ahead and take this.
Oh, it's not very far.
[EIKO]
It's all right.
Take my business card.
You can return it whenever
you feel like it.
Oh.
Uh, thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
"Eiko Yano." Huh.
[CHIE sighs]
[CHIE]
I've got no energy.
I ditched work again today.
I'm probably gonna
get chewed out again.
[JEANNE] You have nothing
to worry about, Chie.
If anyone tries to harass you,
I'll never forgive them.
[CHIE]
Thank you. I--
[doorbell rings]
So what's going on?
You didn't even call in!
That's the second
time this month!
[CHIE]
I know.
[EIKO]
Are you sick or something?
[CHIE]
No.
I'm just bored.
[EIKO]
What?
[CHIE] The only work I get
to do is the boring stuff.
[EIKO] You have to walk
before you can run.
If you do well with
what I give you,
then I'll trust you with
more interesting work.
[EIKO growls]
Stop that--are you
even listening?!
[EIKO] You mind telling me
what you're doing
washing dishes when I'm
trying to talk to you?!
[CHIE] I thought it would be
impolite if they were dirty.
[sighs]
[EIKO]
Jeez.
Why can't you just
get your act together?
If you can't, it's all
gonna be on my head.
[CHIE]
Okay.
--[EIKO] Hm?
--Is there something the matter?
Well, I thought I just
heard something.
[CHIE]
Really?
[sighs]
[EIKO] All right then,
I guess I'll be going.
Just make sure to come
in to work tomorrow, okay?
[CHIE]
Okay.
[sighs]
Oh, hi. Good morning.
Excuse me.
Do you mind if I
leave this here?
[GUARD]
Oh, sure.
Ah, for your Vespa, huh?
Yes.
[GUARD] Do you want me to
bring it to you later on?
[GUARD]
Miss Robin?
[ROBIN]
I need to borrow this.
Sure.
[SAKAKI] Hey. You guys look
pretty bored somehow.
And what do you mean
by that, Sakaki?
If you're trying
to say something,
you might just spit it out.
Oh, nothing. No big deal.
[MICHAEL]
It's just an accident.
In fact, it looks
like the police
closed their
investigation yesterday.
Can you find anything
else about it?
[SAKAKI]
What is it?
Is there something wrong?
No, it's just that...
[KOSAKA]
Do we have an incident?
Well, Robin?
[ROBIN]
Uh, no.
It's nothing really.
[ROBIN gasps]
[ROBIN]
Amon!
I want to go pick up my Vespa.
Huh?
H-Hey!
[AMON]
This is the last time.
You know, you're much
too young to be using--
I'd like you to take me
somewhere else, okay?
[AMON]
What?
[KARASUMA]
So what's the big deal?
Why'd you call me with my
personal code like that?
[AMON]
Sorry to bother you.
[KARASUMA]
I was up all night working,
and I haven't slept a wink.
Besides, we don't do accidents.
Yes, I know that.
[KARASUMA]
Then why are we here?
I thought it would be better
than touching a corpse.
Come on, that's not what
I meant, and you know it.
[ROBIN] Well... I saw her
just before she died.
If it hadn't been for
her I'd have gotten
soaked in that big storm.
And that's really the only
thing I know about her.
I'd like to think that someone
knew what happened to her
in the last moments of her life.
That's not it.
I need to know for myself.
[KARASUMA] I'm not on call
just to help satisfy
some idle curiosity of yours.
Our job is to hunt down witches,
not to waste our
time messing around
with normal traffic accidents--
[AMON]
You've made your point.
It's a child's selfishness.
Let's try to humor her.
What is it?
It's surprise and amazing shock.
I'm not really quite sure why.
What made her feel like that?
I just told you, I don't know!
Maybe a cat jumped
out in front of her.
I don't think that was it.
Huh?
[ROBIN]
There are no skid marks.
If something had jumped out,
she would have immediately
hit her brakes.
And that doesn't
explain her neck wound.
Maybe she wasn't looking
where she was going.
She did hit the windshield;
a wound like that isn't
all that strange.
[AMON] Humans are fragile;
they die easily.
[ROBIN]
Amon...
I'd like to go see who Miss Eiko
was on her way to visit.
Well, great, suit yourself.
It's fine by me.
I'm gonna go home.
Hang in there, Amon!
[doorbell rings]
I have to say, I never expected
you'd be so aggressive.
[doorbell rings]
Yes?
[CHIE] Well, for her sister,
you don't look much like her.
[ROBIN] She was going
to be my sister-in-law.
He was Miss Eiko's boyfriend,
and as his sister,
I was concerned.
You see, after she passed away,
my brother went into shock.
[ROBIN] Did Miss Eiko say
anything to you last night
that struck you as
out of the ordinary?
Huh?
[AMON]
Perhaps she had an enemy?
Well...
Miss Eiko is very pretty.
And she does a good job at work.
Aren't you sad about this?
Huh?
What do you mean?
She was your boss. You spent
time with each other.
Ah, I have to go to work now.
Miss Eiko gave me a
big lecture last night.
Yes, but--
Let's go.
I'm sorry we bothered you.
[AMON]
Are you satisfied now?
Why are you so
curious about this?
That girl is pretty strange.
True, but her
alibi's pretty good.
The landlord saw
her say good-bye
to Miss Eiko as she left.
Yeah, I know, but then again...
You must admit,
she's a bit weird.
I can take you to pick up
your bike now, if you want.
Oh.
I forgot to get the gas.
Oh, Miss Robin!
Mr. Michael asked
me to make sure
you went to see him in the
office when you got back.
Michael?
I found out a few things, Robin.
Doesn't it look suspicious
if we're all in here
at the same time?
[DOJIMA]
Oh, it's all right.
This girl Chie that you
guys met earlier today.
We shouldn't be
doing this, you know.
If it's the law or curiosity...
...I'll choose curiosity.
[ROBIN]
What's that?
[MICHAEL]
It's a CAT scan of her brain.
Apparently she had a
concussion a while back,
and when she was in the
hospital, they took these.
Here. See this area?
Do you notice how it looks
like it's all divided up?
[SAKAKI]
What do you mean?
Is it supposed to be
connected or somethin'?
Yup. Separated sectors
are pretty rare,
and they're a classic symptom of
multiple personality disorder.
But if she's displaying
any other personalities,
there's no record of it.
So in other words,
she's able to get by
just fine in everyday life.
As far as I can tell.
Why don't we just stop here?
We shouldn't spy
on innocent people.
But this one's a witch.
What makes you so sure of that?
And how would you explain it?
I don't know if
I can explain it.
I wouldn't know how.
It's not a very good habit
to go around suggesting
that everybody
who acts a little unusual
might be a witch, now is it?
We're gonna be in trouble
if we cause another false alarm!
Look, Robin, I know you
want to try out your powers,
but this isn't the way.
[gasps]
Don't you know what
it's like to want
to use your power sometimes?!
[KOSAKA clears throat]
Everyone was missing,
so I figured
you were up to something sneaky.
To search through
personal information
without reasonable cause.
That is an abuse of power,
even for the STN!
Amon, you of all people
should know that!
I wanna know who
started it this time.
[ROBIN]
I did.
[gasps]
They were doing it
because I asked them to.
[KOSAKA]
Robin...
Since you were only
assigned to us recently,
I'm sure you must be
very tired right now.
You can go home for
the day and rest up.
But I'm not...
[AMON]
Robin.
You need to do as you're told.
[KOSAKA]
Okay, now, let's break it up.
[DOJIMA] Aw, jeez,
and it was just getting
interesting, too.
[SAKAKI] Imagine that: you're
interested in your work.
[DOJIMA]
Like me more now?
[SAKAKI]
Not really.
[MICHAEL]
Hm?
Michael.
How many degrees of kin
did you look up?
I went out to three degrees.
Go ahead and look all
the way up to the sixth.
But that's really
an abuse of power--
[AMON] Law or curiosity--
which would you prefer?
How's this?
If you find something,
I'll show you a killer website.
[MICHAEL]
Okay, I'll do it!
[GUARD]
What are you doin' with that?
I'm measuring the oil.
[ROBIN]
It runs on a mixed fuel.
Well, that's a bit
of a pain, isn't it?
[GUARD]
Anyway, I guess I'll get going.
Please be careful
on your way back.
Okay.
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
I'd better hurry...
Here, go ahead and take this.
[AMON] Humans are fragile;
they die easily.
Ridiculous.
Kids nowadays, I swear...
Huh? What do you mean?
Look, Robin, I know you
want to try out your powers,
but this isn't the way.
[MICHAEL] One of her distant
relatives was a witch.
Is that so?
Yeah, but I found out something
even more interesting than that.
Three years ago,
her boyfriend died
in a very strange way.
Blood loss from wounds in his
Achilles' tendon and an artery.
That's a strange way
to get killed, isn't it?
[MICHAEL]
This guy...
He sounds like he was quite
a bit of a player, too.
I get the impression that this
girl Chie was just a fling.
[AMON]
Was she a suspect?
[MICHAEL]
Nope. And she had a solid alibi
for that case, too.
Sorry to make you
go through all that.
Hey, wait! What about
the killer website
you were talkin' about?
Oh. I almost forgot.
I'll tell you about it
when you're an adult.
What's up with that?
[thud]
[AMON]
This is...
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
I'm sorry.
That's it. From now on,
I don't want you to use
those powers in the house.
It may not be a big deal to you,
but it really gets on my nerves.
[kettle whistles]
You're so straightforward.
I guess it means
you're still young.
Robin, you know about
conservation of matter, right?
Boiling water
decreases in volume.
But that's only because some
of it's escaped in the air
in the form of steam.
It's the same thing
with human emotions.
You can deny your feelings,
but they're always
hiding somewhere.
Even if you think
you've controlled them,
they're never really gone.
[ROBIN]
Yes, I think you're right.
I think... I should trust
my instincts more than I do.
Well, that's a dead end.
[DOLLS echoing]
Unforgivable!
[JEANNE]
[phone ringing]
[CHIE] Hello, resource
management center.
[JEANNE]
Chie, we've got a problem.
That guy just came by again.
[CHIE]
Huh?
[JEANNE] The guy who said he
was that woman's boyfriend.
He was just in here sniffing
around for something.
I did what I could
for the moment.
But I'm still worried, so get
home as soon as you can!
[CHIE]
All right.
[clicking]
Huh?
[JEANNE]
Unforgivable!
[grunts]
[AMON]
I see.
So that's it.
[gasps]
[ROBIN]
Excuse me.
[click]
[gasps]
[JEANNE] Those who learn
our secret are unforgivable!
[DOLLS echoing]
Unforgivable!
[JEANNE]
Unforgiveable!
[JEANNE screams]
[CHIE]
Jeanne!
[DOLL A]
Kill her, Chie, kill her!
[DOLL B] We have to
avenge Jeanne's death!
[DOLL C] We can't let
her out of here alive!
[DOLL A]
Let's kill her!
[DOLL B]
Chie!
[DOLL C]
[DOLL A]
Hurry!
[gunshots]
Robin!
Use your power and
burn the dolls!
They're part of the witch!
[gasps]
[DOLLS scream]
[DOLLS screaming]
Everyone!
Wait!
Stop.
It's too late.
[KOSAKA]
...45, 46, 47, 48...
...49...
I thought that,
according to Amon's report,
there were 50 dolls
in the place.
Oh, yeah? Then, what
happened to the other one?
Hey, ya never know.
It could still be out
there running around.
[HATTORI] But, that
wouldn't make any sense.
The witch died, right?
[KOSAKA] She certainly did.
No, that's impossible.
[KOSAKA laughs]
[KARASUMA]
Nice work.
[ROBIN]
Not really.
Oh, don't be so modest.
[ROBIN]
It's not that.
[ROBIN] It's just
always a very sad thing
when someone you know dies.
I sort of... wanted to
get my mind off of it.
But, she was quite different.
It didn't bother her.
And that was...
I wanted to believe that...
when someone passes away,
everyone close to the person
is deeply affected.
You can return it
whenever you feel like it.
I'm sorry I couldn't
return it to you properly.
Touko...
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
Innocent heart.
Summoning of destruction.
Parasitism and awe.
A tragic genius of gray soul
cannot see the
existence of darkness.