It can't be...
How could Karasuma be here?
[MICHAEL]
Miss Dojima.
[DOJIMA]
What is it?
You said
that an assault team was gonna
attack this facility, right?
Huh? Yeah...
Then we have to
stop them, quickly.
This place is rigged
to crush everything in it
if there's any sort
of emergency.
If we're not careful,
it'll collapse on us!
[gasping]
[phone ringing]
Uh-oh. I can't get
through to them.
What is it?
The attack is going to start.
We had it planned so they would
begin the assault immediately
if my signal was ever cut off.
Let's move.
[SAKAKI]
Uh?
[SECURITY] Intruders are
crossing the security line.
[DIRECTOR]
Seal the security gates.
Security personnel,
circle behind the gates.
Stand by for intruders.
[PILOT] November Foxtrot
to command base.
I've just passed point 3-A.
Proceeding to combat altitude.
[ZAIZEN] They're equipped
with heavy weaponry?
I understand.
Evacuate the scientists quickly.
Is it an attack
by headquarters?
That would be my guess.
But sir, why would they choose
to rush matters like this?
I don't know.
Hm?
Is something the matter, sir?
It's Toudou's hidden data!
Of course. That must be it.
How is the decoding coming?
[TECH]
We're currently at about 78%.
Send it to me right away.
[TECH]
Very well, sir.
What is it?
About the test subject, sir.
She has tested completely
negative for Orbo extraction.
Then eliminate her.
Eliminate?
But, sir.
I believe she will be
an excellent specimen
for further testing.
You do, do you?
[gasps]
Have it your way.
Look like it's gone offline.
Does that mean the attack's
started already?
Probably.
We've gotta get outta here.
Where should we go?
You mean, up?
[DOJIMA]
Mm...
Goin' up there now
would be dangerous.
I know that.
You know that, huh?
And the elevator?
How you gonna get that working?
I think I might be able
to help with that.
You think so?
[MICHAEL] There ought to
be a panel someplace
that lets you control
the elevator directly.
For instance...
Someplace like that.
Ms. Dojima, jump in once I
get the door open, okay?
But what about you?
[MICHAEL] This situation
isn't gonna solve itself
by staying down here.
Besides, where you're going
is even more dangerous.
I'll keep ya company.
[gasps]
[MICHAEL] This won't exactly
be safe, either.
You don't have to tell me that.
Sakaki...
Well, I guess I'll tag along
with you, little lady.
I'll go with you, too.
[AMON]
No.
You and I are going
to be staying here.
[gasps]
[NAGIRA]
Robin.
There's something
special that you need
to take care of
down here, right?
Nagira...
Amon...
[MICHAEL]
Let's get to it...
[SAKAKI grunts]
[gasps]
[whistles]
[phone rings]
[ZAIZEN]
Yeah. It's me.
Hm?
The elevator's moving?
Is it Robin's group...?
Send security to the
elevator hall immediately.
That's right.
And also...
How is it?
[MICHAEL]
They should be okay.
I think we've probably been
spotted by now, though.
[BOTH gasp]
[gunshots]
We got company!
[whistles]
[gunshots]
Keep 'em busy, Haruto.
[clanging]
[TOUDOU]
...must be eradicated...
...by the ultimate Witch...
[ZAIZEN] I believe that
you've seen it by now.
Robin's true form.
[ZAIZEN]
Robin is no ordinary Witch.
Can you let power
like hers exist?
Can you allow a world in
which genetically altered
superior beings, make the
weak bow down to them?
The choice is
completely up to you.
Even if your abilities
have weakened now,
it doesn't change the simple
fact that you're a Witch.
The question then becomes,
will you join my organization
and survive as a hunter.
Or will you decide instead
to become a fugitive
just like Robin?
It's your choice.
What I'm offering,
is one last chance.
[KARASUMA]
One last chance?
You want me to hunt Robin?
That's right.
[KARASUMA]
Where is she?
[ZAIZEN] She's somewhere
inside this facility.
[door hisses]
Dammit!
Michael! How long?!
[MICHAEL]
C'mon, c'mon!
They're close!
Dojima. It's up to you now!
[NAGIRA] They must know
we're in here now.
Don't get yourself killed,
little lady.
Same to you, buddy.
[gasps]
[DOJIMA grunts]
[phone ringing]
[ZAIZEN]
Hmm...
Impressive.
I never imagined that you would
actually come to visit me.
Karasuma.
What did you do to Karasuma?
[ZAIZEN]
Hmph.
You mean that you came
all this way to see me
for such a trivial matter?
Trivial matter?
Karasuma is working for me,
just as she always has.
Amon. I can't say
the same for you.
You're mistaken if you think
that's the only reason
we came here.
Toudou's message.
The one he left with you
15 years ago.
Then you know about
the hidden data?
[ZAIZEN]
Hmph.
Do you have any idea
what sort of message
he actually recorded
in that ROM?
Yes. Some of it,
but not everything.
Yet, in spite of that,
you still wanna know?
I do, if it explains
who I really am.
So you're absolutely
certain, then?
Toudou...
[TOUDOU]
Zaizen, by the time you,
or anyone else,
listens to this recording,
chances are I will be dead.
Even so, I can't simply consign
all of my research to oblivion.
This work I've done, as a
Solomon research scientist,
and a member of the Genome...
Perfect Witch...
I have decided to call this
special project of mine
"Project Robin" in honor
of the King of Witches.
My colleagues have
laughed at my efforts,
calling it "Project
Devil Child."
They've brushed me off,
dismissing the research
as mere armchair theory.
To tell the truth,
I probably never would've
put this project into motion
if I had not met her.
Maria.
[TOUDOU] Normally, Solomon
should have discovered
what I was up to when
they finally decided
to pull the plug on
all of our research.
As it turns out, however,
they were far too lenient
when it came to my work.
Eventually, I started
achieving results
that began to run counter
to many of Solomon's ideals.
But fortunately, the project
made it to the final stage
without being discovered.
I have a feeling
that in the future,
Solomon will disavow any
knowledge of its existence.
However, her father
was the one person
in Solomon I was
never able to deceive.
Juliano Colegli. He will never--
You're the Devil's child.
You understand?
At the core of your being,
that's what you truly are.
That's it?
What's that?
[ROBIN] Is that all of what
Toudou recorded?
I don't understand. What more
do you expect there to be?
[dings]
It's me.
I don't care about
whatever is missing,
just put it on the
monitor right away.
[TOUDOU]
That is to say that...
...to Solomon, the success
of the research
behind Project Robin
would mean the rebirth
of the Devil in a literal sense.
Her existence would
validate a past
that they must obliterate
at all cost.
In ancient times,
mankind was ruled
by a more powerful species
of humanity called "gods."
The species that possessed
these special powers,
what we now call Witches,
were seen as nothing
less than gods to us.
But then, suddenly,
a genetic mutation in a god
born about 3,000 years ago
changed their destiny forever.
It was to have a profound
effect on the future
of the gods, as well as humans.
The gods, having
lost their ability
to pass on their own
genetic information
to their descendants
due to this mutation,
lost their status as
heirs to humanity.
What the hell is he saying?
[TOUDOU]
Having now risen to power,
humankind feared
the rebirth of the gods.
They sought to suppress and
eventually control them
over the years.
They call them
devils and witches,
saying that they had powers
that humans were not
meant to possess.
That is the truth
behind Solomon.
This research was branded
with the mark of heresy.
And Solomon destroyed
every last trace of it.
Witches are supposed to
be our successors?!
No, that's impossible!
I refuse to accept that humans
are inferior to Witches.
[ZAIZEN] Delete all of
the files immediately!
Including the ones
you've just decoded!
No, wait!
[TECH]
Are you sure about that, sir?
I am!
Do it!
[KARASUMA]
Hold it right there!
[ZAIZEN]
Uh!
[KARASUMA]
Continue the playback.
Karasuma...
[TOUDOU] I attempted to recreate
a Witch that had their innate
powers and had the ability
to pass on its genes--
I met a hunter named Maria...
[ZAIZEN] Karasuma, are you
trying to betray me?!
[KARASUMA]
I'm not betraying you.
Can't you see?
I was terrified
of losing myself.
I had to cling to something.
If I didn't,
I was afraid that I'd gradually
fall to pieces and go insane.
I knew that you were lying.
I never believed you
for an instant!
[growls]
[TOUDOU] ...but within her
now, a new life is growing.
Who may be able
to change the future.
A child I've designed.
Able to change the future?!
[TOUDOU]
It seems almost fantastical
and yet my mind has
become obsessed...
[ZAIZEN]
There is only one future!
And impure witches like you
will have no place in it.
Neither do you!
Nor you!
[TOUDOU]
...not its power, per se--
but rather the ability
of the Witches
to once again
inherit the species.
They are terrified
that this child
will become the Eve of Witches,
believing that she...
You're supposed to be some
sort of "Eve of Witches"?
You call that the truth?!
He's wrong!
Witches are nothing
more than filth!
They're a race that pollutes
the pure water that is humanity!
In order to protect the
beauty of that purity,
to protect humanity itself,
we must wipe Witches off
the face of the Earth!
You would exterminate
Witches even though
they're God's chosen creation,
just like humans?
Witches? Chosen by God?!
Then why did their genes
mutate and become abnormal?!
I'll tell you!
Because witches had
become corrupted!
They could never be the
successors of humanity!
They were corrupted because
they had been forsaken by God!
God doesn't forsake
any of his children.
[AMON] I'll admit that
I can't fully accept
the existence of
Witches, either.
Not yet.
But despite that,
I have to accept
what that man said just
now... as the truth.
There's no denying it.
[ZAIZEN]
No!
It's not!
[ZAIZEN]
You're saying that Witches
will take the place
of humanity?!
I refuse to accept that!
It's not the truth--
it's just garbage!
[alarm blares]
What's going on?!
The Witches in the holding tanks
are sending the
system out of control!
[alarm blaring]
That's impossible! The
Witches inside them are--!
If we don't do
something soon,
the self-destruct
device will activate!
"Self-destruct device"?
[TECH] It'll bring down
the entire building!
This can't be.
How can this be happening?
Could it be you?
Your very presence here
is stirring the spirits!
Now I understand.
It's all clear.
It's time for me to kill both
you and Toudou's nonsense!
Obviously, this is all
part of God's will.
The bullets in this gun contain
the purest Orbo we've ever made!
Don't do it!
Just shut up!
[AMON groans]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[ROBIN grunts]
[ZAIZEN]
Weren't you listening?
I told you, this is the
purest Orbo ever made!
[grunts]
[ZAIZEN chuckles]
Your power can't touch me!
[gasps]
[ZAIZEN groaning]
The side-effects of the Orbo...
[ZAIZEN]
No, I won't give in...
Not until I defeat this Witch...
You're trying to defeat Witches
using the Orbo you made from us?
You won't be forgiven.
Your forgiveness?!
You can go to hell!
[gasps]
Juliano told me something.
That woman...
Maria...
He said she called me "hope."
Hope, huh?
What a joke!
[gunshots]
[ZAIZEN groans]
You're disgusting.
There's no hope for your kind!
[gasps]
What the hell have I done...
Does this mean
that it's possible
headquarters was
right all along?
[ZAIZEN laughs]
[alarm blares]
This place is coming down!
Robin, we have to leave!
[ROBIN]
Their blood flows inside me.
The blood of Witches
that have been persecuted
over and over
since ancient times.
I don't just feel their power.
I also feel the sadness
caused by that power.
Maybe that's why that woman
who struggled to give birth
to me called me "hope."
A Witch who knows sadness
might be able to understand
humans even when
surrounded by a sea of them.
That's why I...
I don't know for sure
whether or not
someone as powerful
as you ought to exist.
But the only way to
find the answer to that
is for you to survive.
If what Karasuma was worried
about ever comes to pass,
I'll kill you...
...before it consumes you.
I guess that makes you
my watchdog.
[VOICES murmur]
Robin, what's wrong?
[ROBIN]
I hear screams...
They're crying.
[VOICES cry]
[alarm blares]
Let's go!
[TOUDOU]
Maria told me something.
She said that if she could
truly change the future
with a power that's lying
dormant within her,
she wanted to pass
it on to this child.
[TOUDOU]
As my final gamble,
I have decided to entrust
our unborn child to Juliano.
Will he actually be capable
of killing Maria's child?
I will have to stake her
slim chances of survival
on his mercy.
[TOUDOU]
Even if she survives, however,
he will probably
never forgive me...
For all eternity.
Worm here, calling Charlie.
Collapse seems to
extend to entire facility.
Request temporary
abeyance of assault plan
until ground situation
is verified.
[RADIO MAN]
Charlie here, roger that.
Glad you're alive.
[DOJIMA]
Thanks.
I want my STNJ members
extracted at once!
[NAGIRA]
Hey! You made it!
[BOTH gasp]
[DOJIMA]
Hold your fire!
Miho!
[NAGIRA]
I'm amazed you guys made it out.
[MICHAEL]
Where are Amon and Robin?
[NAGIRA]
What do you mean?
Weren't they supposed
to be with you two guys?
[SAKAKI] So then,
they're still inside...
[NAGIRA]
Aw, don't worry about them.
There's no way
those two are dead.
[MICHAEL]
But how can you be so sure?
I dunno.
Somethin' just tells me.
[SAKAKI, MICHAEL]
Huh?
[police sirens blare]
[KARASUMA]
It was a fluke.
A fluke and a miracle.
No, that's not it.
It wasn't like that.
[DOJIMA]
Uh?
Are you saying that
Robin and Amon are--
I'm not. I don't know
what happened to them.
Maybe the two of them were
caught in the collapse.
Yeah, that's what happened.
[birds chirping]
[MICHAEL]
Good, just as we planned...
And so, we went back to hunting,
same old thing, day in and
day out, just like before.
[MICHAEL]
Haruto, report your status!
[MICHAEL] Of course, there were
a few changes here and there.
[MICHAEL yawns]
[HATTORI]
Careful, sir, it's hot.
Administrator.
About the new hunter who's
being assigned to us today...
[KOSAKA]
Hmm...
[KOSAKA slurping]
[spits] Ah! Hot! Hot!
[HATTORI] I warned you
that it was hot, sir!
[HANAMURA]
Hey, boss.
Here are the files
for your next case.
And one other thing...
[NAGIRA]
Hmm?
[HANAMURA]
When is that delinquent girl
supposed to come
back here anyway?
Wh-What do you mean when
you say, "when"?
[HANAMURA]
Some lawyer you are.
Seems like you can't even
reform one little girl.
Hurry up and drag
her back here.
Right...
[MICHAEL] Amon and Robin
supposedly left this Earth
when the Factory collapsed.
That's what Miss Dojima
said anyway,
but I don't really trust her.
I mean c'mon!
Do you really expect me to
believe a word that woman says?
[MICHAEL]
Know what I mean?
[GUARD]
"Good luck is coming.
You might have a wonderful
rendezvous in the near future.
Your lucky color is black."
Hmm?