[AMON]
He's 20 minutes late.
You must be Inquisitor Cortion.
I'm Amon from STNJ.
We'll be the one's escorting
you from here on-- Ah.
[AMON]
Sir.
I can carry your bags for you.
The air tonight...
...is heavy.
[SAKAKI]
Check that one out.
[MICHAEL] Hold on. I gotta
test the link out first.
[SAKAKI] I'm telling you,
that's just a waste of time!
[KARASUMA grunts]
[MICHAEL] If you know so much,
then why don't you do it?
[SAKAKI] Why should I have to?
Come on, check out the next one.
[MICHAEL groans]
Fine.
[KARASUMA grunts]
Problem?
No, we're good.
Everything's fine.
You can go back
to sleep, Miss Karasuma.
Are you looking at websites that
you know you shouldn't be?
Of course not.
The chief does that, not us.
[KARASUMA]
Careful now.
The Inquisitor?
--[SAKAKI] Yep.
--Are you looking into
the inquisitor that's
coming today?
[SAKAKI] Well, you know how
none of the information
ever gets passed onto us.
So we thought we'd
check things out ourselves.
[MICHAEL groans]
[SAKAKI]
No good, huh?
I can't get anything
on the inquisitor.
This is isn't normal. This guy's
got some tight security.
[SAKAKI] That means we
got a really big fish then,
doesn't it? Why do you think
they're sending us
such an important guy?
[KARASUMA] 'Cause he's here
for the inquisition of a witch.
To see if we can
use the witch as hunter.
[SAKAKI]
Who is it?
[KARASUMA] Well, if you're
really that curious about it,
then why don't you
just ask him yourself?
[SAKAKI] If I could,
I wouldn't be here right now.
If you ask me, the whole
thing's a little funny.
[SAKAKI] Hey, maybe we
can trace the Inquisitor
by using this witch
as a starting point?
[MICHAEL] I dunno...
That might be tough.
[KARASUMA]
A heretic inquisition...
[SAKAKI] Well, it's at least
worth a try, isn't it?
--[CORTION] You.
--[gasps]
[CORTION] I want you to pull
over just past the next light.
But St. Sebastian Church
is just a few blocks away.
As you wish, sir.
Is this where you wanted me to--
Ah.
[AMON]
Just a moment. Where are you...?
Those who seek this
moment will forever...
Hmm?
[gasps]
[ZAIZEN]
Are you the only one here?
Huh?
[gasps]
O-Oh, yeah. I just got a call
from Amon a few minutes ago.
What'd he say?
[MICHAEL] He was lettin' me know
the Inquisitor has entered
the church where
he'll be staying.
[ZAIZEN]
I see.
[MICHAEL] He also said that
the Inquisitor wants to begin
the inquisition
as soon as possible,
so he sent Miss Karasuma
and Sakaki out
to get the suspect.
I suppose that's the one that's
going to be questioned, then?
[MICHAEL]
Yes.
I checked him against our list,
but there weren't any matches.
So, uh... how'd the
Inquisitor find this guy anyway?
From what I understand,
they have a system
for finding witches that is
completely different
from what we're used to.
[MICHAEL]
What kind of system?
It's old. It dates back
to the middle ages.
I'm sure this case will
be dealt with entirely
through their system.
Michael, when you get a chance,
I'd like for you to forward me
all the data you've
found on this man.
You got it. No problem.
[KARASUMA] Artificial
Intelligence can only determine
to a certain point
whether or not a person
is suitable as a hunter.
It's the final decision
that's the most important,
and that has to be
made by a human.
Understand?
I think I got it.
[KARASUMA] And, the only
ones that are authorized
to make that decision...
are the Inquisitors.
[SAKAKI] So in other words,
it all comes down to him...
Whether you end up
becoming the hunter...
...or the hunted.
That's what makes
this guy so important.
[SAKAKI]
That kinda bothers me.
Over there.
[CORTION]
So, you are here.
See this?
It's an inquisition machine.
We're here on behalf of the
Shinjuku Temporary Agency,
regarding the request you made.
--[SAKAKI grunts]
--[MASUDA] What is it?
[KARASUMA]
You're Shirou Masuda?
Y-Yes, I am, but--
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Whaddaya want?
[KARASUMA] We'd like you to
come with us for a little while.
[MASUDA]
What for?
[gasps]
[MASUDA]
This is...
[CORTION] I don't think
this device is necessary,
but those at the
Factory disagree.
[ROBIN] When they tested me,
they just used words.
[CORTION]
Just words?
I see, so that is how
you felt about it.
What do you remember?
Can you recall the symbols
I gave to you when
I put you under the inquisition?
The Hagal's Eight.
The sacred runes that will lead
you to the depths of the Craft.
However... that is all
forbidden fruit I'm afraid.
By passing along
the power of God,
we separate the lambs into
angels and fallen angels.
"Power of God"?
Symbols?
[CORTION]
Of course, at the time,
you were completely
unaware of the true identity
of the forbidden fruit
of knowledge
that I passed on to you
on that very day Robin.
[AMON]
He's here.
Then we shall begin immediately.
Have them bring him to me.
Right.
[MICHAEL]
Looks like they're gonna start.
I see...
Can you forward the
video to my office?
[MICHAEL]
Done.
[CORTION] Two years ago,
in Tokyo, a corpse was found.
The body had been brutally
crushed beyond recognition.
Because the corpse was
so badly damaged,
the police eventually filed
the death as an accident.
However, the truth is that
it was far from an accident.
What are you trying to say?
[CORTION]
You know the truth.
You know exactly how
that man was crushed to death.
You're wrong. I've no idea
what you're talking about.
[CORTION]
The Hagall for the stone axe.
Does it look familiar?
You used this rune.
The realization of evil, to
unleash your own Craft,
in accordance with the Gematria
in the Sepher Yetzirah,
the Book of Creation.
Wh-Who are you?
Wh-Where do you come from?
[CORTION]
Destruction, ruin, revenge...
You unleashed the dark desires
that lay deep in your soul.
[MASUDA]
It's not true. It's not true...
--Did you enjoy it?
--It's not true...
[CORTION] Did you like watching
a human body crushed to death
by your own will?
No!
That's not what happened!
[THUG]
Quit messing with us, fool!
[MASUDA]
I only did it to protect myself!
I just wanted to get
out of there alive!
[CORTION]
To protect yourself?
That's right!
That's right. I just
wanted to get out of there.
You want me to believe
that you killed someone
to protect yourself?
That's very convenient.
[THUG groaning]
[MASUDA]
He wasn't human. He...
He tried to...!
[CORTION] Do you have the right
to kill if they're not human?
And... do you think that he
really wanted to kill you?
[MASUDA] Not human.
He wasn't human...
If I hadn't done it, he
would have killed me!
[CORTION]
Perhaps your imagination
is running a little wild.
Can you honestly tell me
that you weren't wishing
for his death from
the very beginning?
Not true! Not true! Not true!
[CORTION] But death has always
seemed to surround you.
[MASUDA] It's not me!
That was... That was...
[CORTION] Is it your wish
to confront anything
that chooses to challenge you?
[MASUDA]
I wasn't... It's not true..
No! I'm not a monster!
I'm... I'm...
[CORTION] But you have wished
for the power of God.
And although you are human,
you still seek divine power
by enslaving yourself
to the heretics.
[MASUDA]
Heretics?
Are you saying that
I work for the Devil?!
[CORTION] It's nobody's
fault but your own.
You fell of your own free will.
Of my own free will?
[CORTION] I insist that you
reveal your true self to me!
My true self...
[MASUDA] I'm not a monster!
I'm not a monster!
[MASUDA] My power...
My... My true power...
[MASUDA] No! Don't come out!
Don't come out! No! Stop it!
[MASUDA]
K-Kill... I can't...
I'm gonna kill... No...
I will kill! I can't!
It's all right to kill.
[MASUDA]
Stop it! I can't!
NO!!!
[MASUDA]
I'm gonna kill you!
[CORTION grunts]
[MASUDA grunts]
Die!
[CORTION groans]
Amon!
[AMON]
Calm down. Just wait.
[MASUDA pants]
[growls]
[yells]
[MASUDA groans]
I didn't want to kill you...
I mean it...
I didn't want to kill anyone.
[CORTION]
Hmm...
[sighs]
The inquisition's over.
[AMON]
Let's go.
I didn't wanna kill... anyone.
[ROBIN]
But he was able to control it
during the inquisition.
[AMON] You're right.
It did appear that way.
However, the darkness that
was hidden inside his heart
has now been revealed.
You can't ignore that.
The Inquisitor
feels the same way.
[ROBIN] Yes, but everyone has
at least some darkness
in their heart.
[AMON]
Perhaps.
But the distinction
lies in whether it is
a shade of gray or truly dark.
But...
[AMON]
Wait. He's coming out.
Michael! Masuda is on the move!
[MICHAEL] Okay. This guy
looks like a tough one,
so be careful.
[AMON]
The Fourth district.
[AMON] We've got him
pretty much cornered.
[gasps]
[CORTION] Overwhelming
power will guide humans
to eternal darkness.
That is why one must always
maintain constant vigilance.
So those that have
awakened to the Craft
must endure whatever
treatment they receive?
They must try, if they wish to
continue living in this world.
[gasps]
[CORTION] However, in the end,
it will prove impossible.
[ROBIN]
Then how... do you...
[CORTION]
You should know.
You must relinquish
yourself to us
and leave everything
to our doing.
I don't have the powers of a
witch because I wished for it.
Why is it that you
use those powers?
I don't know. I... I just do.
[ROBIN gasps]
[MICHAEL] It looks like this
guy hasn't had a real job
for over two years.
[AMON]
Two years?
[MICHAEL]
Yeah, what's up?
[AMON] That's right about
the same time he started
showing signs of his craft.
[MICHAEL]
No way.
[AMON] Do you really think
it's out of the question?
Forcing someone
out of society...
...just to awaken their powers.
I wouldn't put something
like that past Solomon.
For a new hunter...
I could see them going that far.
We're just tools.
[AMON]
You disagree?
Regardless, let me
know what you find.
[MICHAEL]
You got it.
[AMON]
The truth can be difficult.
But if you don't face it,
you may as well stop living.
[RAMEN COOK]
Here ya' go! My specialty.
Japanese Soup-Spaghetti!
I'm so bummed, man. I've
spent like 20,000 yen
on my cell phone this month.
Hey, man, that's your own
fault for tryin' to pick up
so many chicks.
I bet if I look, I'll find a
wallet somewhere around here.
[MASUDA grunts]
--[BOY A] Surprise!
--[MASUDA groans]
[MASUDA]
What did I... Why?
Why are you punks
doing this to me?
[BOY A]
Who are you calling "punks"?!
[BOY B]
Yeah, tough guy!
[BOY C]
You're a joke! Loser!
[AMON]
This is bad.
[MASUDA grunting]
[MASUDA]
Me... Me...
Who are they...?
What are they doing to me?
Why?!
[BOYS panting]
What's this? You a
little tougher than you look?
[MASUDA] It isn't my fault...
They've done this to me.
It isn't my fault!
[BOY A]
Huh?! [whimpers, groans]
[ROBIN]
Put him down right now!
You kids should leave!
Wh-What's goin' on here?!
What the hell's he doin' to him?
[BOY A groans]
[AMON]
That's enough!
[MASUDA growls]
[AMON grunts]
Amon!
[BOY B] I-Is he like
a monster or something?!
A monster?
[BOY B gasps, grunts]
[MASUDA chuckles]
[ROBIN grunts]
It's over.
[AMON grunts]
[AMON gasps]
[MASUDA]
What do you want from me?
Who are you?
Are you going to try
to attack me as well?
[chuckles]
[AMON groans]
Do you really derive
that much pleasure
from crushing people?
[MASUDA]
Huh?
Fallen angel...
Are you like me? Are you?!
Answer!
[gasps]
I won't allow it.
[MASUDA screams]
Robin... You...
[ZAIZEN] That headstone
that he stopped to see...
According to legend,
it's there to calm the souls
of those who've died,
betrayed by their followers.
[AMON]
Martyrs.
What it most likely
refers to is a witch.
How is she?
I see.
You think something's
wrong with her?
I'm leaving Japan today, and I
doubt that I will see you again.
Huh?
[CORTION] It appears as though
you may finally have awakened.
[ROBIN]
What do you mean?
[CORTION] To the rapture
one receives from using...
...their craft.
What do you mean by that?
What do you...?
Inquisitor...
Robin is--?!
[NARRATOR] Three hundred
and twenty years have passed
since the coven
sank in the dark.
A bullet in the dark.
The letter from the past.
A smeared bond...
The nightmare without
a vanishing point
visits from the
abyss of darkness.