[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga,
we got a dance lesson
from some cool old people,
but then some scary biker girls
had us dancing
between a rock and a hard place!
Guess I just look like
an easy target!
And get this,
their boss turned out
to be the daughter of Saki’s old
ride-or-die gal-pal!
Then, our fearless leader
cranked up a bike
for the world’s
deadliest game of chicken!
Thanks to that,
we’ve got some scrappy new fans!
Glad to have you guys!
[ROMERO snoring]
[dance music plays]
[music stops]
[AI]
Sweet, we did it.
That was killer!
I can already
see us takin’ over!
-Don’t get carried away.
-I mean, I’m just sayin’.
[LILY]
Don’t be so strict, Ai!
[SAKURA]
Saki seems really happy now
that one of her old buddies
is a fan of ours.
...you’re the one
who gives her a reason to be!
[SAKURA] And Lily’s been
bursting with energy
ever since her dad started
coming to see our performances.
[AI]
That’s good, but make sure...
[SAKURA] Ai and Junko
have been a lot more relaxed
since everything that happened
with the Saga Rock Festival
this summer.
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
And me...
I still don’t have
my memories back.
I wonder what happened
in my life before I died?
[snores, grunts]
[SAKURA]
Huh?!
-A show for five hundred people?
-That’s right.
-You’ve come very far.
-Is that like a lot?
Duh! I mean, think!
A hundred times five!
-Well, we are at that point.
-[TAE groaning]
This’ll be a first for you.
You all are the main event.
Can you fill five hundred seats
on your own?
Well, can you, Sakura?
Huh?!
[KOTARO]
You’d better!
[yelling]
Ah! Anyway!
[shuddering]
You’re booked at an exhibition
hall in Karatsu.
[ALL]
Huh?
The famous Furusato Hall Arpino!
[AI gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
-[SAKURA] Ar...pino?
-[LILY] Uh, where's that?
[KOTARO]
Glad you asked...
it’s right here!
♪
-It’s huge!
-[LILY] Woo-hoo!
[LILY giggling]
[YUGIRI]
It feels like we’re finally
staking our claim in this world.
This’ll be different than
performing under an open sky.
Takes me back.
This is the place
where my old group
did our very first show in Saga.
♪
Actually, it feels
kinda familiar to me too.
Maybe...I’ve been here.
Recently, this
multi-purpose hall
hasn't hosted
many musical events.
But after we perform here,
perceptions will change.
Thanks to you, Arpino will be
recognized as a venue,
and you’ll have completed
your first step
to saving Saga prefecture!
[gasps in excitement]
[crickets chirping]
[SAKURA]
That feeling...
For some reason,
I’m super excited now!
Maybe there’s something
about that place
that has to do with my old life!
And when we perform there,
I bet the memories
will come rushing back!
Gah, I can’t fall asleep!
I might as well get
in some practice instead!
-[button clicks]
-[music plays from stereo]
[AI]
Sakura! Sakura!
Huh? Yeah?
[LILY and JUNKO panting]
You’re getting too far ahead.
Try to keep pace with us.
[SAKURA]
Oh, I’m sorry!
[AI]
Think you might need a break?
Of course I don’t need a break.
I feel like I could keep
practicing forever!
This is our big solo show!
We gotta make sure
it’s perfect, y’know?
Damn, you’re actin’ like
a bigger nerd than usual.
Don’t be silly!
Oh, and by the way,
I had an idea while I was up
all night rehearsing!
I was thinking during the hook,
it might be cool
to throw in an extra step!
Shouldn’t we focus
on learning the basic pattern?
[SAKURA]
I get where you’re coming from,
but just let me
show you real quick!
I promise,
you’re gonna love it!
-[AI] I’m not so sure--
-Ooh, wait!
The weather
is really beautiful today.
It might be fun to practice
outside for a change!
Let’s go to the roof!
We can’t do that!
There’s no roof access!
Good morning,
-Franchouchou-lay-hee-hoo!
-[ALL groan]
Well, straight to business then.
In light of your big concert,
you get a special
training regimen!
What is that supposed to mean?
You’re going to the mountains!
Uh, you can’t be serious.
Like, now?
It has to be now!
You can’t pull off
something this amazing
without a training montage
in the mountains!
See. You get your butts kicked,
you grow, and you return!
[ALL groan, annoyed]
And you’ll be stuck there
till I come to the
rescue-de-lay-hee-hoo!
[ROMERO panting]
[SAKURA] Do you think there’s
any real benefit to this?
[SAKI] Hell if I know.
But if he’s messin’ with us,
I’m gonna punch the shades
right off his face!
[AI]
Looks like we’re here.
[YUGIRI]
Goodness...
he certainly chose
a barren spot, didn’t he?
[JUNKO panting]
If I weren’t dead,
I’d probably die here.
I feel like a zombie popsicle.
This really sucks. I’m bored!
[SAKURA]
What do we do?
We can’t practice
in a place like this!
If we’re dead,
can we still freeze to death?
Not to death.
We’d be fine
after we thawed out.
Assuming we didn’t get eaten.
What? Eaten?!
None of us can freeze!
No one!
It’s kinda late for that.
-[SAKI] Look.
-[SAKURA] Tae!
[SAKI]
Sure wish we had a fire.
Oh, I can make one for us!
-[SAKI] For real?!
-Sure I can, duh!
I mean, I was the lovable star
of "Girl Scout Mania
Case Files 3," remember?
[SAKI]
What’s that?
In the meantime, I suppose
I should try to find
something for us to eat.
[AI] You’re right,
we won’t get anything done
if we’re just sitting around.
-[JUNKO] Yeah.
-But wait.
Shouldn’t we be practicing?
We have Arpino coming up.
[SAKI]
Yeah, but figuring out how
to survive is more important.
[JUNKO]
“Survive” is a strong word.
[SAKI] I’m gonna go pick up
some branches
and stuff we can use
as firewood!
[lightly gasps]
[LILY] Branches from pine trees
are really good for that.
Now, now.
Let’s get settled.
Then perhaps
we can practice a bit.
[SAKURA]
‘Kay.
[LILY humming]
-[SAKI] Check it out, squirt!
-Huh?
Here’s more sticks than
you can shake a stick at!
-This is plenty, right?
-[LILY] Mm--
Hey, don’t do that!
I told you,
you’re supposed to let them
dry out by the fire first!
-Oops.
-[TAE groaning]
-Look what I found.
These mushrooms
look delightfully tasty.
Though they might
be poisonous.
Who cares?
We’re zombies!
[worried groan]
-[AI] Stop!
-[SAKURA grunts]
[SAKURA muffled]
What are you doing?!
I’m hunting, obviously.
-[SAKURA] Hunting?
-Shh, it’s under that tree.
[leaves shaking]
-[pig snorting]
-[SAKURA gasps]
Please don’t shoot
the cute little piggy!
[pig squealing]
-Sorry.
-It’s no big deal.
I’ve got a quicker eye
than the others.
-I’ll find something else.
-If you say so.
I’m gonna go take
a look over there, you in?
Uh, no, think I’ll pass.
-[water rushing]
-[footsteps]
Sakura.
Are you trying to catch a fish?
Uh-huh, I get to sit quietly,
so it’s kinda
the perfect job for me.
[SAKURA]
I see.
[JUNKO]
There’s so much chaos.
Huh? Really, where?
Oh, it’s inside
your heart, of course.
Oh...
[JUNKO] Is there something
bothering you?
[SAKURA]
Well. Yeah.
I guess I just want
to feel like all of us
are doing the best we can.
And I think we need
to practice a lot more
if we want the concert
to be any good.
I know you do,
but panicking won’t help.
It’s like when you’re fishing
and don’t catch anything.
You wonder how deep
the fish are.
Did you use the right bait?
Or maybe you picked a bad spot.
If you’re calm and think
about it from different angles,
you can usually find
the answer, you know?
[exhales]
-[ALL] We did it!
-[TAE and ROMERO howl]
[SAKURA] I have to make sure
I’m ready to perform at Arpino!
Even if I’m all alone!
[TAE and ROMERO howl]
[SAKI]
We’ve been here a few days
and nobody’s gotten eaten yet,
so I’d say we’re killin’ it!
But still, we’ve got one thing
left that needs to be done.
Somethin’ that’s
really important!
I’m so glad!
Thank you!
I thought you guys
had forgotten it!
No way!
We need meat.
-Huh?
-And not just fish, either!
We’re zombies, we gotta have
somethin’ worth catchin’!
I’ve been trying my best,
but that baby boar
is just so skittish!
Don’t beat yourself up about it.
We’re new to this.
None of us really know
-how to mess with wild game.
-[SAKURA gasps]
[GROUP grunts in agreement]
-[SAKI] All right, let’s talk
-[ROMERO grunting]
-about who does what.
-[AI] Sure.
-[JUNKO] Sounds good.
-[LILY] Okay!
[ROMERO jumping, grunting]
[JUNKO]
The trap’s totally hidden.
Good! He’ll come by
any minute now!
Are you sure about this?
[gasps]
He’s close!
-[ALL gasp, surprised]
-Okay, hide!
-Hey, wait up--!
-[crash]
[ding]
Oh my word!
-She just ruined the trap!
-[AI] Saki!
-[SAKURA grunting, gasps]
-[SAKI] Okay, don’t move!
[rustling]
[roars]
-[SAKURA shrieks]
-There he is!
What the hell is that?!
I guess he’s the daddy boar.
[booming footsteps]
One thing’s clear,
we need a much bigger pit.
Oh no, this is about to
get worse.
[trembling]
[SAKURA] Oh my God,
what do I do, what do I do,
what do I do, what do I do?
Nice piggy.
Damn it! How do we save her?
I think I might have an idea!
I learned it from a Joi
missionary back in Shimabara.
Listen carefully, Lady Sakura,
you need to play dead!
-[JUNKO] But she is dead!
-[SAKI] Come on!
[SAKURA groans]
[BOAR snorts, chomps]
[ALL gasp]
He chomped ‘er head!
[SAKURA grunts]
[TAE growls, bites]
-[BOAR spits]
-[SAKURA groans]
-[SAKI grunts]
-[BOAR grunting]
[SAKI]
And safe!
You okay, Sakura? Say somethin’!
[SAKURA]
This is wrong.
No joke. That thing
was really disgusting.
Not the boar.
I mean this.
We’re supposed to be
running our dance routines,
not running away
from wild animals.
We should be showered
in spotlights, not drool.
There’s not much time left.
So, why are we spending it
on pointless stuff like this?
Oh, I see now.
[KOTARO]
Found you!
And good yodel-odel-ay-dee-day,
lay-del-ay-del-ay-dee-hees!
How’d it go?
Did you learn any
yo-del-oh-del-ode-life lessons?
Are you kidding?
Just look at us.
Your idiotic games won’t
prepare us for anything!
The big show is only days away.
I see no point being here!
I’m over it.
Don’t you?
Then you should close
your eyes and listen.
That way,
dear Mother Gaia will speak.
And then you’ll know,
that even up here,
you are never alone!
I just said I’ve had enough!
Oh my...
[squish, bones cracking]
I’m going home.
[KOTARO]
What?
Great job.
So what’s the plan?
[echoing]
Go home!
[music playing from stereo]
[SAKURA]
This is bad.
Things have been super awkward
since yesterday on the mountain.
But our performance at Arpino
is right around the corner!
-[AI] Sakura.
-[SAKURA] At this rate,
we’ll be way under-rehearsed!
-[AI] Sakura!
-[gasps]
-You’re still fast.
-[SAKURA panting]
Like I said before,
-you need to match our pace.
-[BOTH panting]
[SAKURA moans]
This isn’t a solo.
Let’s try again from the top.
[SAKURA]
It’s not my fault
-we’re out of sync.
-[AI scoffs]
While you guys were
goofing off out there,
I was actually
practicing our dance!
Well, that was rude.
What gives?
[water pattering]
[glasses clink]
[door opens]
-Welcome to-- huh?
-[door closes]
-Greetings, gentlemen.
-What do you want?
Well, I am a courtesan.
[scoffs]
You’re here to dance?
[lightly chuckles]
I’m also trained as a geisha.
[KOTARO]
Not what I asked.
[YUGIRI] You sent all of us
into the mountains
hoping that Lady Sakura
would find some inner peace
before the concert.
Is that right?
[water pattering]
[KOTARO]
The beauty of a group
is that it makes up
for individual weaknesses,
resulting in greater
collective strength.
But if Sakura can’t see that,
what’s the point?
Indeed, sir.
But couldn’t you just tell her?
It’s something she needs
to learn for herself.
You’re different
with Lady Sakura.
She must be dear to you.
[scoffs]
I only care about saving Saga.
[YUGIRI]
And I have a soft spot for those
who can’t express themselves.
[KOTARO] Saga’s depopulation
problem is so exhausting.
Every time we
climb one mountain,
there’s a taller one.
And now, with this show,
it’s like we’re lost
in the wild.
Listen, I’ll be honest here...
I think she can do it.
-[slaps]
-[KOTARO grunts, groans]
-[slow-motion slap]
-[slow-motion groan]
[grunts, whimpers]
That’s enough foolishness,
Lord Kotaro!
Mark my words.
That brave girl can do anything!
Uh, yeah, that’s what I just--
You should have
more faith in her! Hmph!
[KOTARO lightly gasps, whimpers]
I just said I do.
You guys heard me, right?
[SAKURA groans] It just keeps
getting more complicated!
How can I make this right?
I mean, no matter what,
I want the concert to be great.
That venue might have some kind
of connection to my past,
and performing there
could be huge for us!
We have to do everything we can!
It’s okay!
I know I’m in the right here!
And after we put on a good show,
I’m sure they’ll understand!
[AI muffled] So, everybody knows
their positions now, right?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[AI] All right, let’s try the
whole thing from the beginning.
[SAKURA]
It’s funny.
I’ve never actually watched
Franchouchou from the outside.
[music playing from stereo]
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
Wow! Their timing’s so perfect!
[SAKI]
Let’s talk about this part.
Kinda feels like I’m standing
in one place for too long.
I see.
Oh you must mean the bit when
we’re across from each other?
-[SAKI] Yeah, exactly.
-[AI] Hmm.
[AI] Well, Arpino’s
a pretty big place.
Do you want to try spreading out
farther on the sides?
-Like, at this part?
-Ooh, good idea!
[AI] The extra space
would give me and Junko
more room to move, too.
[chuckles]
That sounds great.
Hey, if you want me to,
I could just switch positions
with Tae.
Oh, I get it.
Everyone moves around Sakura.
That sounds really interesting,
let’s do it!
[SAKI] I love it
when a plan comes together!
Let’s make sure we’ve
got it down so it’ll be easy...
[SAKURA] These guys
haven’t been rehearsing at all.
So how did they
get so in sync?
It must be because
they pulled together
to make the best
of those harsh conditions.
Everyone...except me.
[exhales]
-[ALL gasp]
-You’re back.
[SAKURA]
I’m sorry.
I’ve been thinking, and I see
now that I was being selfish.
Ever since I found out
about the Arpino show,
I’ve just been so worked up.
I started obsessing
over doing a great job
and making everything perfect.
But because of that,
I didn’t consider you guys.
I forgot about Franchouchou,
about our team.
Yeah, That explains it.
I thought you seemed
kinda hot under the collar.
[KOTARO] You still haven’t
figured it out?
[SAKURA]
Mr. Kotaro?
Think Nijinomatsubara.
A pine forest.
Pine as in alpine.
Alpine as in the Alps.
Hence the mountains!
Mountain-climbing,
except with your issues!
I have no idea what that means,
but I’ll do my best, sir!
-You guys.
-[ALL giggle]
Okay!
Let’s work hard and make this
the best show ever!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[GIRLS laugh]
I’m glad everything worked out.
What do you mean?
[GIRLS talk indistinctly]
[SAKURA]
Good morning, Ai!
I’m going running!
Keep an eye out for traffic!
[SAKURA]
Okay!
[SAKURA] There’s one week left
before our big solo concert.
I’ve got all the songs
and dances memorized,
and we’re totally in sync!
So I’m beyond excited!
Plus, if I step onto that stage,
maybe I’ll remember
something important.
And then I’ll finally be able
to make peace with my past life!
I know my future will be full
of happiness and excitement!
-Come on, Romero!
-[ROMERO barks]
-Here I go--!
-[crash, glass shattering]
[slow-motion crash,
glass shattering]
[slow-motion tires squeal]
-[thud, squish]
-Oh God, poor girl! Oh!
-[ROMERO growling]
-[MAN] Let me check--
[yells]
I’ll go get help,
okay, doggie?
[tires squeal, car speeds away]
[MAN]
Be right back!
[ROMERO barking]
[whimpering, sniffing]
-[ROMERO whimpering]
-[SAKURA gasps]
Where am I?
I don't--
-[thud]
-[ROMERO barking]
[LILY]
Lily here!
Franchouchou’s really
become an unstoppable team!
I can’t wait to dazzle
everyone at the big show!
Next time on Zombie Land
Saga, episode 11:
“A One-of-a-Kind Saga!”
Don’t miss it!