[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga.
After screwing up
our first paid job,
we got not one,
but two more chances to shine!
First, we starred
in a commercial
for Drive-In Tori
and worked our tail feathers off
to try and cluck up
some quick bucks!
The next step in our quest
for press
was competing
in the Gatalympics!
But instead of getting
a taste of fame,
we just got a mouthful of mud!
Chicken and mud?
Those must be the ingredients
for success!
People are bound to know
who we are now!
Uh, why’s no one
agreeing with me?
Come on, please tell me
we’ll make it!
[indistinct office chatter]
[typing]
[INUBASHI]
Agh, dammit,
this is starting to get
really frustrating!
How’s it possible that none of
these girls have social media?
And their website’s nothing
but photos of their past events.
I kinda like that.
It means they don’t
just follow the trends.
I know you wanted us
to track these kids,
but there’s nothing to track!
After a month, you’d think we’d
have something to show for it.
I wonder.
Who the heck are they?
[music playing from stereo]
Hey. Time out!
[AI] We’re still too slow
on that last part.
I’m so sorry.
[AI]
It’s okay. I’ll just slow down.
[JUNKO moans]
[KOTARO]
This new song has a duet
that highlights Ai and Junko.
You two will be front
and center.
I feel so guilty.
I’m supposed to be
on lead vocals, but...
Well, it is fast.
We’ll just have to focus
on perfecting the most crucial
parts of the song.
Okay. I’m gonna run through
the whole thing myself
to see how it flows.
You guys can take a break.
[music playing from stereo]
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
Something... about her.
[ROMERO howling]
-[water turns off]
-[moans]
Hm...
-[continues pumping]
-Hello?
We’re out of shampoo!
[typing]
[YUGIRI]
What’s this glowing box?
It’s called a computer.
We’re gonna use it to figure out
what kind of idols
are big right now.
[YUGIRI] Mmm... they come up
with the wildest things.
Hey, stop,
you’re gonna break it!
Oh dear. My apologies.
Hold on you guys.
-What if Kotaro catches us?
-[AI] Don’t worry.
His nighttime bath should take
at least another 20 minutes.
Are you sure?
[AI] Yeah, it’s my third time
doing this.
-[SAKURA gasps]
-Hey, Ai!
Do you think Franchouchou
has its own homepage?
[AI] We do, and I am not
going back to it.
-But why not?
-You’ll die from cringing.
-Huh?
-Uh, die again, I mean.
[ALL groan]
Hello? Uh--
-[TAE groans]
-Uh...
[AI]
Anyway.
I’ve been doing a lot
of digging around lately.
So much has changed
since my day.
Especially for idols.
Lots of popular groups
who seemed like
they would stay together
forever already broke up.
Public interest in idols
does fluctuate.
Wait, what’s that mean
for us, though?
Even if idols
aren’t in right now,
we’ll still try our best.
Okay?
Um, yeah, okay.
All right.
Who’s doing events?
Let me see.
[computer mouse clicks]
This new technology
is so useful!
[SAKURA]
Just look at them all!
[AI] Let’s start with the ones
that seem interesting.
Ooh, what’s Saga Rock?
That sounds like fun!
Sure does!
-Do you like rock?
-Yup!
We all know Mentai Rock
is huge in Kyushu!
-Mentai what?
-Ha-ha! I’ll kill you.
But I seriously don’t know.
Says here it’s the largest
outdoor rock event
on the island of Kyushu.
No way!
We gotta get in on that!
Looks like it’d be easy to get
on one of the big stages, but...
[SAKURA] It must be
amazing to perform
at a place like that
with so many people!
I’ve done a lot
of press appearances,
so I won’t even be that nervous!
Yeah let’s go for it!
If we put in enough practice,
we’ll bring the house down!
It’s not that easy, though.
[ALL]
Huh?
You have no idea.
The venue’s huge.
A lot of work goes into
performing somewhere like that.
Oh... right...
[JUNKO] It would be better
for us to take small steps
than dive head-first
into the deep end.
Sorry.
[AI]
I understand you.
But we don’t really
have the time
to gradually build
our popularity.
-[JUNKO gasps]
-[AI] We need to find a way
to get our name out there quick.
Take the group
I was in before this.
We played for audiences
in the tens of thousands
after just a year on the scene.
One year?
How did you attract
so many people?
[AI sighs]
If you’re trying to be
perfect from the beginning,
then you’ll never
get anywhere.
Fans like to see you
improve over time
and feel like
they’re a part of it.
-Like it’s a journey.
-I don’t know...
And, obviously,
we still need
to try our best
every step of the way.
[gasps]
Hey, look!
Isn’t that your old group, Ai?
Which one?
Right there! You see?
[SAKURA]
They’ll be at Saga Rock!
[SAKI]
Iron Frill? Sweet!
-[thud]
-Hmm?
[water drop]
-[ROMERO panting]
-[TAE groans]
[KOTARO growls]
[whack]
Ah, good day...
to you...
dear Fran...
chouchou!
I have come
to bring you good tidings!
I am the great idol,
Magistra--
That’s enough!
Just spit it out!
All right.
I’m delighted to say
that I’ve got some
excellent news
for you all!
Does anybody wanna guess?
You have some fans now!
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
Thanks to the chicken ad,
followed by the Gatalympics
coverage,
you’ve gained a bit
of traction online.
-Wow, really?
-What’d I say?
Can’t get any better
than Drive-In Tori!
No matter how stupid we look,
I guess there’s no such thing
as bad press.
[KOTARO]
What are you talking about?!
Even when you’re
covered in mud,
Franchouchou always finds
a way to sparkle.
Ahh...
Drive-In Tori! Huh?
[SAKURA giggles]
You’re close!
Let me show you how!
It’s like this...
To-ri!
Oh, okay,
I think I get it now!
To-ri!
That’s not really it either.
Right, one more.
To-ri!
[chuckling]
Are you even watching--
[yelling]
Who the hell cares?
-[whimpering]
-Why would I need to master
your stupid dance routine?
Don’t you look down
your nose at me, Pinocchio!
I own you, remember?
What? Pinocchio?
You’re not a real boy yet!
Ah! Mm--
Now that I’ve made that crystal
clear, here’s your new mission.
You’re all about to spend
a little quality time
with the fans of Franchouchou!
Short notice as always.
[KOTARO] I already announced it
on our homepage.
[JUNKO]
When you say “quality time”...
For now, I think we’ll
start with a photo op!
Wait a minute.
What is he talking about?
Oh, I guess
what he means is...
the fans will take pictures
of us but not with film.
They’ll probably
just be digital.
Digital?
Uh, how do I explain?
You don’t have to wait
for the pictures!
Oh! Like a Polaroid, right?
[SAKURA]
Mm...
[JUNKO]
I see.
We’re taking glamour shots
with Polaroids!
[SAKURA groans]
No, it’s not gonna be
a big formal thing.
Actually, it will be.
Whoa, for real?
Usually there’s a mini-concert
and some merch sales,
then pics.
[JUNKO]
Ohh.
Merch sales, huh?
We have some T-shirts,
but no one wants to wear
those tacky things.
You must be confused.
Are you keeping up?
I’m fine.
I’ve found that getting
confused doesn’t help much.
I’ll just relax
and take things as they come.
And after this I’ve got
an even bigger pan on the fire.
So, don’t let me down!
Or you might get cut!
♪
-[CROWD cheering and applause]
-[TAE groans]
That's it!
And we are...
[ALL]
Franchouchou!
Thanks for all your support!
[cheering and applause]
[SAKURA gasps]
People really showed up!
I can’t believe
we actually have fans now!
And, uh,
if you want, we’re gonna have
a photo op right after this.
Oh, man, that’s crazy.
You all came here to see us.
I mean... you guys rock!
[cheering and applause]
[GIRL 1]
That was awesome!
-[GIRL 2] Where’s Coo-coo?
-It’s Cocco, dammit!
-[CROWD gasps]
-[SAKI] Uhh...
[TAE squawking like a chicken]
-[CROWD excited murmur]
-[WOMAN] This is so exciting!
-[TAE squawks]
-[CROWD squawks]
[KOTARO clears throat]
We have official
Franchouchou
T-shirts available,
as well as these
cute hand towels.
Anyone who buys at least
one item will be eligible
for the photo session!
[SAKURA] When did he have time
to get this stuff made?
[AI] Yeah, and what’s
with that weird design?
All right, everyone,
it’s time to get those
photo sessions rolling!
We’ll start with the lines
for Number 0 and Number 1,
then we’ll get Number 2
and Number 3.
Photo sessions?
-With who?
-[AI sighs]
The fans are lined up to take
individual photos with us.
-What else would this be?
-Huh?
[SAKURA and TAE
gasping, groaning]
[nervously]
Eh...
[AI chuckles]
Ready!
[camera clicks]
[whimpering]
-[KOTARO] Here we go!
-[MAN and AI chuckle]
-[KOTARO] Smile!
-[camera clicks]
-[AI gasps]
-[camera whirs]
[AI]
What... was that?
[KOTARO]
Okay, next, we’ll do photographs
for Numbers 4, 5, and 6!
-[KOTARO] For Number 5...
-Number 4! It’s your turn!
[JUNKO]
I can’t.
-[AI sighs]
-[SAKURA] Huh?
I’m not posing for pictures.
But why not?
Hurry up, they’re waiting--
No!
But you’ve got the longest line!
You have to!
Idols are supposed to
dazzle people from
up on stage!
How does this have anything
to do with that?!
[FANS gasp, murmur]
[FAN]
She doesn't seem happy...
-What's wrong?
-[OKOBA] Uh...
[KOTARO screaming]
What the hell was that?!
-I’m so disappointed in you!
-[ROMERO panting]
Do you wanna know
how disappointed I am?
Well, if I had to give
you a metaphor
it’s like...
[stammering]
Dumb zombies! Gah!
-[ROMERO panting]
-[door opens, closes]
[AI] You do understand
that this whole thing
was your fault,
right, Junko?
Walking out on a job
doesn’t affect just you.
It hurts all of us.
[JUNKO]
So that’s part of our job?
[AI]
Of course.
But it’s so personal.
I don’t wanna do that.
Listen to me!
Idols do this!
We have fans,
and they love us,
so they need to feel like
we’re within reach.
But that’s just it!
Besides, you bragged about
going big after your first year!
Just from fan events?
Is that more important
than being a great performer?
Wait a sec!
Don’t put words in my mouth!
You better back off.
[SAKI]
Guys, take a chill pill.
[SAKURA]
She’s right. Relax!
[JUNKO]
I just think we need to decide
what our relationship
with fans should be.
You’re the only one here
who doesn’t get it!
[SAKURA]
Oh my God, what do I do?
I agree that we need our fans,
but we have different opinions
about the role they should play.
A good performer doesn’t
have to depend on them!
No.
But being above your fans
is so last-century!
You aren’t exactly
fresh blood yourself!
-Don’t fight!
-[SAKURA whimpers]
[panting]
[AI] If you wanna be
in a real idol group,
then you’re gonna have
to leave your fear behind.
[JUNKO gasps]
[door opens, closes]
That was uncalled for.
[SAKI]
Hey!
Dammit.
[SAKURA sighs]
♪
[screeches]
[AI]
I’m not gonna be history yet
-[knocking at door]
-Hmph...
Come on, Ai. Can’t you
two bury the hatchet already?
Just shake hands and admit
you were both wrong.
Yeah, that’s a good idea.
I’m sorry, you guys,
but I don’t feel like
I should go back
on anything I said.
Just because each side
has a valid point
doesn’t mean the disagreement
can’t be resolved.
[AI] I thought the rest
of you were serious
about becoming idols.
We just want you and Junko
to stay friends!
But we’re not friends!
We work together!
You were in show business, Lily,
you should understand that!
Jeez, you don’t have
to make her cry!
[LILY crying]
Don’t you walk away from me!
I wouldn’t worry.
Things will settle down soon.
Won’t they, Leader?
[SAKI]
Agh, what a friggin’ pain!
[MAN chuckling]
-Come on. Hurry!
-[WOMAN] I told you.
I didn’t bring a swimsuit!
[MAN and WOMAN laughing2]
[wind whooshing]
[gasps]
-[gasps]
-I'll get it!
[grunts]
[JUNKO]
Oh, it’s you!
Ehh-- ahh!
[SAKURA]
I see...
So you’re from a generation
earlier than me, huh?
It’s more like two.
I would’ve been
an old lady by now.
I was just thinking,
I’ve never really had the chance
to ask you what kind of idol
you used to be.
Back in those days,
it just wasn’t the norm
for idols
to have that kind of
fan interaction.
Maybe a meet-and-greet once
in a while, but that’s all.
So, no matter where
we were,
on the stage or the tube,
there was always
a clear boundary.
[SAKURA]
Hm?
Um, wait,
what about a tube?
I’m lost.
[JUNKO] It’s an idol’s
job to give people
something to aspire to.
I could never let the fans get
close enough to see my flaws.
Or at least,
that’s the way it was
for the idols I knew.
Just like I’d grown up
admiring them.
I wanted to become
a role model for others too.
That’s why I worked hard,
day in and day out.
I was starting to feel like
I’d accomplished that,
and I thought maybe...
I could keep on doing it.
But, on my way to Saga
for my first tour in Kyushu.
And that was that.
Oh, Junko.
[JUNKO]
Not just anyone can be an idol.
The same goes
for being a zombie.
And if my approach
is holding the team back...
I’m sorry, but...
I can’t be in Franchouchou.
I just don’t belong.
[SAKURA whimpers]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pours]
[gasps]
Mm...
Ahh!
[shivering, whimpering]
Ai?
Found ya!
Tell me what’s wrong!
[SAKI]
Hey...
Ehh, well,
this is messed up.
[chuckles]
You look like a wet cat.
Guess we both do.
Y’know,
if I’m bein’ honest,
I don’t get all this stuff about
bein’ idols and havin’ fans.
But I do know you need
guts and good backup!
-That’s all we’ve got.
-[thunder cracks]
I’m surprised.
You’re really
scared o’ lightning?
[AI] That’s because...
it’s how I died.
[gasps]
♪
[thunder cracking]
[rain pouring]
Damn, what a way to go!
Talk about legendary!
That’s not the kind
of legend I want to be.
[AI]
My story isn’t over.
I’m still here.
I’m not history yet!
I don’t care if I’m a zombie.
I’m gonna get back
on stage again!
And then I’ll--
[gasps, whimpering]
You’ve always
been a firecracker, huh?
[AI crying]
[door opens, closes]
Saki.
You’re still awake?
Yeah, I had trouble sleeping.
[SAKI]
Those two.
If this was my old gang,
I’d beat both their asses.
Or maybe worse.
[SAKURA]
Please don’t hurt them.
[SAKI chuckles]
I won’t.
But for real, we won’t get
anywhere if they keep that up.
They need a wakeup call.
The sooner we can fix this,
the better.
Yeah...
[rain continues]
[KOTARO]
Good morning, ladies!
Look!
I’ve got great news,
so pay attention, please!
Anybody wanna guess what?
Fine, I’ll tell you!
We’re on the newcomers’ roster
for this year’s Saga Rock!
[gasps]
Yes, you may applaud me!
The Saga Rock?
You’re kiddin’ me.
-[BOTH gasp]
-This a once-in-an-after-
lifetime chance.
And that means,
you girls better not
screw it up!
[KOTARO]
For one day,
Saga will be the center
of the music world,
and you need to stand
as the center of Saga!
This is Franchouchou’s
-first outdoor show.
-[gasps]
Your music will light up the sky
and shake the Earth!
Junko here.
If I’m gonna be
in everybody’s way,
I might as well turn into
a big, stupid mushroom.
Next time on Zombieland Saga,
episode 7:
“But It’s Zombiemental Saga”.
I’ll go away now.