[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga:
Our name is really starting
to get around
after the Saga Rock Festival!
It's exciting
and kind of embarrassing!
The other day, Lily's papa
showed up out of nowhere!
She wasn't sure
what to do at first,
but I think it made her happy
to see how much he still loved
and cared about her!
The whole thing was so sweet,
it warmed my cold, undead heart!
And that's it!
[bird screeching]
[SAKI]
Damn, those Korosuke chicks
don't know when to quit,
do they?
[REIKO] Eh, I'm sure
they're just freakin' out
'cause they can't stop us
from takin' over Kyushu.
[SAKI]
What a pain.
Maybe I'll crush 'em now
and save us the headache.
Jeez. You should do somethin'
about that crazy streak.
-It might kill you one day.
-No way in hell I'm gonna die.
And neither is
this little fella.
Check it!
A Maskutchi! [chuckles]
[chuckles]
Let's go.
[SAKI] Man, I'm starvin'!
I wish Tori was open this early.
Hey, Reiko!
Last one to Tenmangu
is a rotten egg!
Guess you never learn.
I beat you every time.
Speed is my specialty.
-[SAKI] And mine's guts.
-Keep tellin' yourself that.
[BOTH grunt]
-[tires screech]
-[engines revving]
[engines revving]
[indistinct chattering]
Huh? What are you sayin'?
For the last time!
Those young gals wanna join us
for the Kashima dance!
-Clean your ears out, pal!
-What?
Okay. So how's this gonna help
Franchouchou get more popular?
Uh, somehow.
Kotaro didn't really go
into that much detail about it.
[KOTARO] As you can see from
this very informative chart,
the elderly make up a large
portion of Saga's population.
So, if you want to take
the prefecture by storm,
then you're going to have
to work hard to win the hearts
of these oldie-goldies
by any means necessary!
[inhales]
Time for you to learn...
[shouting]
Kashima dance!
I could be wrong,
but I don't think
there's ever been an idol group
that had a significant
senior citizen following.
Yeah, I've definitely never
heard of anything like that.
All right, I guess we better
get things started.
[grunts, groans]
[grunts]
Music, come on!
-[bright folk melody playing]
-Ah!
[elders humming
along with melody]
[ELDERS]
♪ Yassa, yassa, yassa, yassa! ♪
Look at that!
Damn, they're sharper
than I thought!
That's the dance!
Now get on in here!
Wait, we're supposed
to have it down?
Think we can keep up
with them?
There's only one way
to find out!
[bright folk melody continuing]
♪ Ha-yassa! Ha-yassa!
Ha-yassa, yassa, yassa, yassa! ♪
[sighs] Wow. That was
even more exhausting
than our rehearsals, wasn't it?
[gulping]
-[SAKURA] Hey, you two!
-Huh?
Everybody's waiting for you!
'Kay!
[TAE babbles]
-[engines revving]
-Huh?
[grunts]
♪
[whimpers]
Hmm?
-Really?
-Hey, twinkle-toes.
Who gave you the right
to come to our turf
and do that stupid dance
with the old geezers, huh?
[SAKURA]
Huh?
What middle school
do you two losers go to?
Whoa.
Saki two-point-O.
I'm gonna be a grade-school kid
for good, if you must know!
Huh?
Let's just go, Maria.
We shouldn't pick
on a little kid.
She's right,
that wouldn't be cool.
[LILY whimpers]
Okay, fine,
I'll leave you alone.
But, you,
what makes you think
you can make
a big racket in our park?
Um. I'm sorry.
But, technically, this park
belongs to everybody, so...
-Say what?!
-[whimpers]
-[TAE groans]
-[girls gasp]
-[TAE growling]
-[MARIA screaming]
Yeah, get her, Tae!
[laughing]
This can't end well.
Hey, let go of her!
-[LILY shouting]
-[MARIA shrieks, gasps]
What the hell?
These bitches are crazy!
[SAKI]
Sakura, what's the holdup?
If we don't get on the road
soon, I'm gonna kill ya!
-Saki!
-Where'd you come from?
You better stay outta this
or I'll kick your ass too!
[growls]
[whimpering]
Don't go pickin' fights
that you can't win.
Let's back off.
I mean, they seem like
they're really dangerous,
and possibly insane!
I agree, we should leave.
[scoffs]
Huh?
[gasps]
-[engine revs]
-Next time, remember:
This is Dorami territory,
you best watch your back!
Okay, well, that was awkward.
You scared them off.
Thank you.
[BOTH gasp]
Seriously?
[SAYAMA]
You know, I'm starting to think
we shouldn't even
bother anymore.
[UKAWA] Maybe it's time
we all quit being Dorami girls.
It's a biker gang,
not a sleepover!
We ride around on scooters.
Yeah, and being
in a gang is hard work,
-and it's just not worth it.
-Don't be stupid!
I'm never walkin' away from
Dorami, no matter what happens!
Things would be
different if your mom--
uh, the first boss was here.
Huh?
How many times have I ordered
you never to talk about her?
Uh... I'm sorry.
-[horns honking]
-[engines revving]
Korosuke!
What do they want?
[tires screech]
♪
[GIRLS whimper]
Oh, no, they brought their
tenth boss along with them!
[SAYAMA]
Misa the Fallen Angel!
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, Maria?
I think I'm about ready to shut
you guys down once and for all.
Why don't you take
that crap and shove it?
-Dorami's not goin' anywhere.
-[chainsaws rumbling]
-[GIRLS whimpering]
-[MISA scoffs]
Nobody interfere.
Let's settle this right now.
We've had bad blood
since day one.
[chuckles]
Sounds good to me.
Hey, Tae!
Did you eat my dried squid?
[mumbling] Mm-mm.
[LILY]
Liar! Just open your mouth!
Would you two please cut it out,
it's cramped as it is!
Sorry, but could somebody
open a window?
Oh goodness.
You don't feel well, Lady Junko?
I know of a pressure point
that might help you.
You think it still
works on a zombie?
-[howls]
-[screams]
[KOTARO] All of you,
silent as the grave, now!
-[SAKI gasps]
-[LILY] Hand it over, already!
-Do you know them or something?
-[LILY] I told you It's mine!
[LILY] Give it back!
-[SAKI growls]
-[SAKURA yells]
Whoa, what's she doing?
Uh, sir?
-Whatever it is, I don't care!
-Saki jumped out of the van.
[shrieking]
What?
Why?!
[wind blowing]
-[SAKI] Hold up!
-[GANG] Huh?
[shrieking]
[grunting]
-There we go.
-[GIRLS gasping]
[KOROSUKE MEMBER]
Hey, back off!
This is none of
your business, all right?
Huh?
[whimpers]
♪
Who the hell are you?
My name is... uh, hang on.
[COP]
Everybody freeze!
What do you young ladies
think you're doing over there?
[ALL] Huh?
-[bicycle clattering]
-[COP shrieking]
Uh. I'll call for backup!
Unless you're trying
to get arrested,
you'd better run along now!
[MISA scoffs]
Well, that killed the mood.
I'm sure we'll find another way
to settle the score,
sooner than later.
[engines rumbling]
-[MARIA] Why'd you butt in?
-[SAKI] Huh?
Because your wimpy ass had
no chance against that chick.
You're not one of us,
so what do you know?
I know she'd mop
the floor with you.
[gasps]
Say what you want.
I'm still gonna keep
Dorami alive
no matter who gets in my way!
[SAKI]
Sure, whatever.
Anyway, here's
a question for ya.
Huh?
[SAKI]
You got a mom, right?
You mind tellin' me her name?
[MARIA gasps]
She's a wuss!
Why would you care?
-Time to go.
-[UKAWA] Maria, wait up!
[running footsteps]
-[crickets chirring]
-[dog barking]
[clock ticking]
[door opens, closes]
[gasps]
[REIKO]
Maria, where have you been?
-I was worried sick!
-Get off my back.
Wait, don't go!
I checked the mail.
-This was in there.
-[gasps]
Those dumbasses!
Give me that!
Please, dear.
You can't keep doing this!
Be quiet!
It's got nothing to do with you!
I'm sorry.
Why are you always apologizing?
And for no reason!
You're such a weakling!
-[door slams]
-[running footsteps receding]
[KOTARO, screaming]
What is the matter with you?
Have I not made it abundantly
clear that communication
with the living
should be for idol business
-and idol business alone?
-I remember.
[sighs]
You don't get it, do you?
Hmm?
You can't get near violence.
It's a taboo for idols.
Just one of you slips up,
and it could ruin everything.
Don't forget that.
[sighs]
[REIKO] I'm so grateful
to have you in my life, Maria!
[MARIA]
Bye-bye, Mommy!
[REIKO] Be sure to use
good manners today!
And be safe!
[MARIA]
I'm heading out!
[REIKO]
You're such a big girl now!
-Have a good morning!
-[MARIA] I'm leaving.
[REIKO] I'm so glad you're
the kind of young lady
who stays out of trouble.
Take care!
Hey, welcome home!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[growls]
[shattering]
[REIKO]
If you could see me now...
I wonder what you would
even think of me.
Saki.
♪
[crickets chirring]
[REIKO] So? Do you know
what your plan is yet?
-For what?
-[REIKO] The future.
[SAKI] I guess once
we take over Kyushu,
we'll take the whole country.
[chuckles]
That sounds like you.
-Well, what's your plan?
-[REIKO] Me?
Get married, have kids.
You know,
just normal life stuff.
[SAKI]
Huh?
I mean, my parents
are divorced,
and I'm in a biker gang.
Nothing's been
that normal for me,
and, you know, it kinda sucks.
I wouldn't want my kids
to grow up the same way I did.
You keep sayin' "normal."
What do you mean by that?
[giggles]
Oh, Saki.
-[crickets chirring]
-[SAKI] Hmm.
That girl had
the same eyes as Reiko.
-[engines revving]
-[horns honking]
Huh?
I'm sure we'll find another way
to settle the score,
sooner than later.
This is pretty damn soon!
[panting]
[KOTARO]
Going somewhere?
[ROMEO whines]
Did you not absorb a word
that I said earlier?
[SAKI]
I told you, I get it.
Well, then where are you off to?
[SAKI]
Where do you think, Shades?
I got some idol business.
-[door closes]
-[running footsteps recede]
[fabric flapping]
Maria?
Are you hungry, honey?
[gasps]
[running footsteps]
Kagamiyama?
♪
[grunting]
[gasps]
[engine rumbling]
You ready to do this?
[SAKI] I dunno, are you ready
for a haircut?
Reiko, hang on
to this guy for me.
-[REIKO] Saki!
-[SAKI] Relax.
There's no way
in hell I'm gonna die.
[exploding]
Saki! Lemme go!
[DORAMI member]
Reiko, you can't help her!
Saki!
-[engine revving]
-[tires screech]
This overlook has a bit of
history for Dorami and Korosuke.
I think it's a good place
for your gang to die.
Damn, you're mouthy.
[MISA] We'll play chicken
to the cliff's edge.
First to hit the brakes, loses.
You can still back out.
That's enough talk!
Let's just do it!
Now that's what
I wanted to hear.
[KOROSUKE MEMBER A grunts]
Three!
-Two!
-[tires screech]
-[MARIA gasps]
-[MISA] What?
-[engine speeding]
-[tires screech]
Wait, Maria!
[KOROSUKE MEMBER B]
Who's the old bat?
[KOROSUKE MEMBER C]
Her bike's pretty sweet, though.
What the hell
are you doin' out here?
This ends this instant.
Would you butt out?
This is my business!
Hey!
Listen.
Please call it off.
I'm begging you!
[MARIA growls]
How pathetic can you get?
[REIKO gasps]
All you know how to do
is bow your head and apologize!
[sniffs]
And I thought you were supposed
to be the first boss of Dorami!
So how the hell
did you end up this way?
I'll never be like you,
and I'll prove it!
You walked away from this team,
but I never will!
-Maria...
-[footsteps]
[REIKO]
Wait, don't do this!
[bicycle bell jangling]
[REIKO gasps]
Oh... crap! This thing has
the worst brakes I've ever seen!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
-[clattering]
-[gasping]
[KOROSUKE MEMBER D]
Who is she?
[KOROSUKE MEMBER E] Did she try
to drift on a bicycle?
[SAKI gasps]
[groans]
Even if my heart stops beating,
-I can still hear an echo.
-[GANG gasping]
It's the voices
of all my old friends.
And to show them my thanks...
I'll keep racin' down
the road of carnage.
The hell are you doin' here?
This doesn't concern you.
Actually, it does, bitch.
Read the sash.
Says I'm Dorami's
Captain-for-a-Day!
[ALL gasping]
Well, this is
definitely a first.
You have no right to do that!
Eh, it's no big deal.
You should be happy.
You just got
another group member.
Don't mess with me!
If you're in this gang,
it's only right that you know.
One of your girls
got killed doin' this.
Are you seriously
willin' to die here?
I don't care which one of you
I'm up against.
I'm still gonna run Dorami
into the ground.
Lemme use your bike.
Don't take one more step!
You have no idea
how dangerous this is!
What if you die?
There's no way
in hell I'm gonna die.
[REIKO gasps]
Saki?
[SAKI]
Who’s Saki?
[chuckles]
♪
I hope you're ready, newbie.
Oh, I'm readier
than you'll ever know.
[KOROSUKE MEMBER A]
Three! Two! One!
-Go!
-[tires screech]
[shouting]
[engine revs]
Did she really just speed up?
[gasps]
[tires screech]
[SAKI]
Eat... my... dust!
[shattering]
[silence]
[silence continues]
[thuds, exploding]
[gasps, whimpers]
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
Damn, that hurt.
[mutters]
What the hell?
I've never seen
anybody that brave.
Jeez, I just wanted to help,
and I ended up
trashin' your ride.
Well, I'm sorry for causin' you
so much trouble, I guess.
-Huh?
-[grunts]
[gasps]
[SAKI groans]
You dumbass!
What were you gonna to do
if this thing ended up
goin' south, huh?
Maria, from where I'm standin',
your mom's got plenty of guts.
If you wanna keep Dorami alive,
then you need to stand up
and look her
straight in the eye.
Show her that you're strong too,
so she won't have to worry.
[BOTH gasping]
Uh... [growls]
I still don't get it, though.
What is normal, anyway?
Can't be this.
[MISA]
Guess you win.
You know what?
If you were a biker,
you'd probably be legendary.
Legendary...
Aah! Oh crap!
I forgot, that's
the most important part!
[ALL]
Huh?
Listen up, everybody!
There's nothin' legendary about
throwin' your whole life away!
I've found somethin' way
more badass to work toward!
I'm here to show ya
a little taste
of what it means
to be a real legend!
[sobs softly]
-Now, music, come on!
-[snaps fingers]
Man, they pick up a new group
of misfits everywhere they go.
Right right, mate!
That's the beauty
of Franchouchou, innit?
Go, girls! Rock on!
Number Two.
-[applause]
-[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
[chuckle]
[YUGIRI]
Greetings, all.
Witnessing such powerful
friendship touches my heart.
I've dreamed of living
for that kind of affection.
Next time on Zombie Land Saga:
Episode 10:
"No Zombie No Idol Saga."
Till we meet again.