[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga!
We found out we're doing a show
for 500 people!
And once I realized it
might bring back
some memories of my past,
I got super hyped about it!
But then, Kotaro decided
to have us train
in the mountains
for some reason?
And I may have gotten
a little upset
that everyone was focusing on
survival instead of rehearsal.
But then, I learned
a valuable lesson
when I realized that
working together like that
made them way more
in sync as performers!
Turns out, I was the one
who lost my head, literally!
And just when I decided
it was better
to put that energy
into being a good friend
and working toward the future,
a truck flew by out of nowhere
and knocked the hype
right out of me!
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pouring]
[SAKURA groans]
What was I doing?
[door creaks]
[rain pouring]
[SAKURA]
What is this place?
-[TAE growls]
-[SAKURA screams]
-[TAE groaning]
-[SAKURA whimpering]
[BOTH grunt]
-[SAKURA gasps]
-[squish]
[screaming]
-[groans]
-[bones crack]
-[SAKURA panting]
-[door closes]
-[LILY yelps]
-[SAKURA stammering, screaming]
[SAKI grunts]
Ah, I'm so sorry!
-[SAKI] What in the hell?
-[SAKURA whimpers]
[SAKURA crying]
[SAKI]
Sakura?
It looks like you
finally woke up!
-That's good.
-[SAKURA continues crying]
Easy.
[AI]
Hey!
-[SAKI] What's wrong?
-[SAKURA cries loudly]
[SAKURA steadies her breath]
-[SAKURA whimpers]
-[AI screams]
[panting]
-You okay?
-Uh-oh.
I think she lost her mind.
[BOTH gasp]
[continues panting]
-[SAKURA] I can't.
-[thud]
[LILY]
Sakura?!
It doesn't matter what I do,
it won't work.
There's no point in trying.
I'm all outta guesses here.
I think she's afraid of us
or something.
Perhaps a slap to the face
will help.
-Hang on, I might know--
-[TAE growls]
-[TAE panting, growling]
-[ALL gasp]
[growls, yells]
[JUNKO and SAKI gasp]
[TAE screaming]
-[JUNKO whimpers]
-[SAKI] Tae!
[SAKURA]
You see?
[SAKI]
Stop!
[SAKURA]
I'm not capable of anything.
[SAKURA gasps]
What just happened?
Oh, God!
-You're up.
-[SAKURA whimpers]
Ai Mizuno?
-In the flesh?
-[AI] Mmm.
Wait, what are you doing here?
[huffs]
Look, do you remember
what your name is?
Uh... my name?
It's Sakura.
Your address, your phone number,
and your family, all that?
Well, yeah, of course.
I see.
[SAKURA]
Hey.
You're Ai from Iron Frill,
aren't you? Big fan!
-Sakura!
-Yes?
I can explain everything
that happened to you,
but you probably not
gonna like what you hear.
So, please stay calm.
See, you're kind of a zombie.
[SAKURA]
What?
Come on.
That's not--
Ten years back,
you died.
Not sure how.
[SAKURA]
No way...
[gasps]
[heart beating slowly]
[squish]
[LILY]
What's gonna happen to her now?
I'm certain Lady Ai's
doing everything she can.
[LILY whimpers]
Damn!
Where the hell is Shades
at a time like this?
He's out.
He left this morning,
saying there was a business
errand he needed to run.
Huh?
-[SAKI] Well?
-[LILY] What's up?
Is Sakura okay?
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
Getting hit by that
truck yesterday
made all her
real life memories
-come back.
-[SAKI] Say what?
But that's not all...
now she doesn't remember
anything that happened
after she became a zombie.
-[ALL gasp]
-Not good!
I know.
I've tried to explain
some things.
I told her about us being
the undead,
and about Franchouchou.
Hey, these are the other girls
I was telling you about before.
[SAKURA gasps]
[JUNKO gasps]
You mean you really don't
remember our group, Sakura?!
Ahh... I don't.
Wait a sec,
does this mean
she can't be in the show?
Uh, show?
Umm, what sh--
[AI]
It's our first solo concert,
for 500 people.
[SAKURA gasps]
It's in just a few days,
at a place called Arpino.
Arpino?
Yeah, it's a big deal.
A total turning point
for our group.
I think I--
So, you see.
All of us have practiced
really hard.
-And you, too.
-[gasps]
I'm sure you're really
confused right now,
but when the time comes,
I know you'll be ready.
[SAKURA] Wow... I really did
become an idol!
No.
You guys can do it without me.
[SAKI]
Come on, you'll be fine!
If you practice,
I bet it'll come right back!
-Cool?
-I'm telling you, I can't do it.
You don't know until you try!
I don't want to!
'Cause working for something,
and succeeding...
well... I just...
don't have what it takes.
Have what it takes?
What's that mean?
No matter what I do, things
always turn into a disaster.
It's like the world punishes me
for even trying.
But...
[SAKURA]
Sorry.
Hey! Uh--
And just when she was finally
coming back to her senses.
This is worse than our journey
to the mountains.
Guys, am I crazy, or did
she just quit Franchouchou?!
[LILY]
Oh, no!
[ROMERO howling]
[XU FU]
How have things been going?
[KOTARO]
Well, they're going.
When you first told me
about your plan,
[XU FU] I thought your damned
brains must've gone rotten.
Uh, what did you
call it again?
“The Original Zombie Village:
Hizen's Highway Dream Project,”
or something like that?
It's called
"The Zombie Land Saga Project."
[chuckles]
That's the one.
“Have compassion, act for
the sake of man,” right?
[sighs]
Yeah, "Hagakure."
Great book, but this
isn't that noble.
Just keep your hands off Yugiri.
I owe a hell of a lot
to that woman.
How old are you?
[XU FU groans]
We sure had some
interesting times back then.
It isn't good to dwell
on the old days.
-Makes you uncool.
-[XU FU scoffs]
You're one to talk.
[SAKI]
Man, this sucks.
I can't even get into the music.
[JUNKO] How can we
during a crisis like this?
[LILY] Guys, do you think
Sakura's gonna
forget about me forever?
[TAE groans]
Look, I know this is upsetting.
But if the rest of us
don't stay strong, then...
the whole thing falls apart.
The show must go on.
It's not like the audience
knows our problems.
Yeah, but still.
It'll be okay.
We've gotta trust Sakura.
[whimpers]
[TAE snores]
[SAKI]
Man, I'm all gross and sweaty.
One sec.
I need to go wash off.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
But you were so worked up
about it before now!
Well, what can I say,
I guess I wasn't myself.
Just forget it.
Stop bein' selfish!
I'll kill ya!
You're just wasting your breath
at this point.
Doesn't matter how much you
stomp your feet and yell at me,
I've already made
my decision.
[huffs] Gah! I've heard
enough, smartass!
Stop it.
I said quit!
[growls]
Ughh...
damn!
[JUNKO groans]
I can't sleep.
I'll listen to
some nature sounds.
Hey there.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Um, well...
[JUNKO crying]
[LILY]
What's that?
I think the stars
are calling me!
I'll go look at the sky!
Sakura.
I can't believe you
don't remember me.
You're so young.
That's right,
I'm 12 years old forever!
It's magic!
That's good,
so you'll stay cute.
Like that star thing
you're holding.
Uh-huh!
You told me my star
was cute before, too,
and you said
you liked my smile!
I had lots of fun
doing idol stuff together.
And I think you're cute, too!
Really?
What if I wear the star,
does it look good then?
Uh, you're doing it wrong.
If you're cute,
those details don't matter.
But the harder
I try to be cute,
the dumber and uglier
I end up looking.
[LILY whimpers]
Because... I'm a failure!
[SAKURA]
For the last time,
I'm not going to be an idol!
[whimpers]
[LILY crying]
Well, it's time.
I suppose I must
begin preparations.
♪ ♪
[footsteps continue]
[ALL gasp]
[YUGIRI]
Lady Sakura?
The city's best courtesan...
is here!
Oh.
She's gone.
[door closes]
[TAE groaning]
Where did that nerd run off to?
How troubling.
Hang on, the mutt's gone, too.
Some dogs are known
to sense people's emotions,
but I don't think
Romero was that clever.
[ALL gasp]
Whoa!
What is this, some kinda
zombie intervention?
[SAKURA] They don't realize it,
but this is for the best.
If I stayed,
I would just ruin everything.
In third grade,
we put on a play.
And I got the lead part.
It was a lot of
responsibility for a kid.
But I rehearsed the role
every night in my room,
until I could recite
all of my lines
without making
a single mistake.
Then, the day of the show.
Even though
I'd had all my shots,
I ended up getting sick,
and had to stay home anyway.
Bad memories.
For fourth grade field day,
I got picked to be
on the relay team.
So, I stayed up late
every night to practice,
until I had the fastest time
in the whole school.
But the day of the race,
I somehow managed to pull
a muscle at opening ceremonies,
and had to forfeit.
Each year, I kept working hard
so I could make a comeback.
And I made relay team in fifth
and sixth grade, too.
But, of course,
I always pulled a muscle before
the race ever got started.
More bad memories.
Fast-forward to middle school.
All summer, I crammed for
high school entrance exams.
I wanted to erase the bad luck
I'd had before,
so I tried to get into the best
school in the prefecture.
I didn't keep up with music, TV,
my friends, or anything else
I used to love.
I spent my entire middle school
career hitting the books.
And because of my hard work,
I got an A on the mock exam!
Then, the real one came.
As I was leaving the hotel
I had stayed at to be closer
to the testing location,
I ran into not one,
but multiple old ladies
who were having
some kind of trouble.
I made it to the test
in the nick of time,
but I was all frazzled
during the exam
and kept making mistakes,
so I didn't get into
my top school.
One of the worst memories.
Everything I can remember
is awful!
They don't understand.
Even if that one girl
is the real Ai Mizuno,
there's no way I'll ever
become an idol.
[FRIEND] It's such a waste
that you're not in a club!
I mean, you're really good
at sports
and physical stuff like that!
Look, I told you, I'm finished.
I might as well not bother.
The harder I try, the worse
everything seems to turn out.
I just don't have what it takes.
So, it's better
if I don't try at all.
I dunno, I guess it's because
I've never really thought
of mistakes or failures
as being a bad thing.
They always end up helping you
with whatever happens next.
And if I want to be
the best version of me,
then I'll just have to find
a way to overcome
any hurdles, ya know?
[gasps]
"I guess it's because
I've never really thought
of mistakes or failures
as being a bad thing.”
I was trying my best.
And just when I thought
my bad luck would change,
I died and came back
as a zombie.
Am I cursed or something?
[COP] Hey, what are you doing
out so late, young lady?
Are you trying to get arrested,
‘cause I'll arrest ya!
Did you run away from home
or something?
What gives, miss?
What's the difference?
All right, come with me to--
[COP whimpering]
Not again!
-[thud]
-[grunts, groans]
-[ROMERO barks]
-[SAKURA gasps]
[KOTARO] You know damn well
this isn't where you need to be.
Right, Sakura?
Uhh...
-And you're--?
-Kotaro Tatsumi, dummy!
[ROMERO panting]
[SAKURA]
I'm sorry.
What are you trying to show me?
[KOTARO]
Nijinomatsubara.
[SAKURA]
Yeah, I know, the forest, but...
it's too dark out
to see anything.
-[KOTARO] That's you right now.
-[SAKURA] Huh?
[KOTARO] There are bright points
all around you.
Saga may be small,
but there's a person
for every light you see.
[SAKURA] Uh, what are you
getting at here?
[KOTARO] Just like
they're waiting for the sun
to rise over Nijinomatsubara,
there are people out there
waiting for you
to shine as an idol.
-[SAKURA gasps]
-Two or three, at least.
Just do your concert
without me, okay?
I'm sure it'll be much better
if I stay far away from it.
I know I don't have
what it takes.
So, you really don't want
to be an idol, then?
Can you look into my eyes
and tell me that honestly?
[SAKURA]
Back then...
[CROWD cheering]
[SAKURA]
I want to be just like Ai!
She's so strong and confident!
[AI]
All right, make some noise!
[CROWD cheering]
[SAKURA] I wonder if I'll
ever shine as bright as her?
This is it.
I'm gonna try one more time!
I can't be afraid
to give it my best!
-[car crashes]
-[glass shatters]
And look at how well
that turned out.
I should've known I'd fail at
that, just like everything else.
That the best choice
was to give in,
but I was stupid and got
my hopes up about being an idol,
so I rushed out of the house
earlier than usual,
and then boom, dead.
That's just who I am.
[KOTARO]
But you came back to life,
as an idol who can save Saga.
[SAKURA] What makes you
think that'll happen?
And why me?
I mean, I never asked
to become a zombie!
One day, you'll understand
all of those things.
Don't give me hope!
Hope is what got me killed
in the first place!
How bad can
one person's luck be?
If you want to do this idol
thing, then go right ahead,
but leave me out of it!
I just... don't want to be
dragged into this, okay?
Well, all right.
Then go wherever you want!
If you're determined to spend
your life this way--
er, afterlife, whatever--
then please,
don't let me stop you.
[SAKURA]
I know I'm doomed.
He didn't have to rub it in.
If I had had any choice
in the matter,
I would've never come back
in the first place.
Did you miss me?
Oh, come on,
did you really think
I'd let your little pity party
go on all night long?
Get lost!
You don't know anything
about me!
I mean it's not like
you've died before and--
-I have what it takes!
-[SAKURA whimpers]
Whether or not you have
what it takes is irrelevant,
because I do, got it?
And what it takes,
is good stuff!
Good stuff that I definitely
have, all right?
Listen to me!
I will never,
and I mean never, abandon you!
[lightly gasps]
[SAKURA]
Sakura here.
Why are they bugging me
when they know I can't do it?
How can I go on with life
if I'm dead?
Next time on Zombie Land Saga,
Episode 12:
“Good Morning Again Saga.”
What does it all mean?