[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga,
the others woke up and started
acting like people again!
Then, it was time for us
to start our idol activities!
Or it would have been,
but nobody really felt
like singing and dancing.
Then, there was some drama,
which made Ai and Junko realize
how tough the streets
could be for a zombie.
It was mostly just people
getting mad at me!
But it all turned out okay,
because that gave me the courage
to step up to the mic
and spit some hot fire!
And that's how we took
our first step
to becoming a real idol group!
Uh...if you can call us that.
All right! Good morning again
to all you lovely ladies!
[groans]
[TAE continues to groan]
A good morning to you.
I said: good morning to you.
Don't get in her face!
You're gonna freak her out!
[KOTARO]
Straight to business, then.
Clearly, diving into
that Saga Castle show
prematurely was reckless.
So, I'm going to be blunt.
-You girls...
-Huh?
...were absolutely wonderful!
[ALL surprised]
You somehow managed
to keep your rotten,
little secret under wraps,
all the while playing hot potato
with a disembodied head!
Now that is team spirit!
Your bodies may fall apart,
but your hearts stick together!
Which is why I will now bestow
my most enthusiastic clapping
upon each one of you.
Feel free to join in and applaud
your fellow decaying flesh-piles
on a successful
zombie-ing endeavor!
Nice zombie-ing!
-And another thing, Sakura!
-Sir?
[rapping]
Girl, you got the beat.
Uh-huh. Those raps were neat.
Yeah. You brought
the heat! Fool.
[chuckles]
Uh...uh, yeah!
But don't you dare
go getting cocky!
[whimpers]
[ALL groan]
[KOTARO]
Now that your show's over,
you think it's all
happy-party-fun-time?
Do not lose sight
of our main objective!
Snap those necks back around
to what's in front of you!
Just because you're dead
doesn't mean
you can take
your sweet time and relax.
The next task I want you
crumbling corpses to tackle
is...one of these.
[KOTARO audible struggling]
-[SAKURA] Guerrilla?
-[LILY] He couldn't spell it.
Do forgive me, but what is
a guerrilla performance?
Um. You put on a show in public
and don't tell anyone about it.
So, it's like a fun,
surprise type-thing.
Oh. Like testing your sword
on a passerby.
[SAKURA laughs]
Wait, but if we do
a street concert,
won't the police
come after us again?
[JUNKO gasps]
Not to worry!
As long as you hide
your gross faces with makeup,
you'll all just get
a slap on the wrist.
[SAKURA sighs]
[SAKI]
Don't be such a wimp, Sakura!
We can't just let the pigs
ruin our rally, right?
And you won't be able
to freestyle
your way out of it this time.
I'll make sure you're all pretty
and cute and perfect,
the way an idol group should be!
I'll teach you!
-One thing.
-[TAE moans]
-Yes, Junko?
-It's just...
I've done plenty
of solo concerts,
but I've never been part
of a group before,
-so I'm uh--
-A loner!
A loner?
Uh-huh!
You're a lonely little loser!
Anyway, the performance
will be tomorrow morning,
in the plaza by Karatsu Station!
[SAKURA, AI and JUNKO]
Tomorrow?!
We can't learn a whole song
and the choreography
with just one practice day!
Guess you'll have to pull
an all-nighter, then.
I mean, what are you gonna do,
die from lack of sleep?
[KOTARO laughs]
[SAKI] Damn, I had no idea
how much crap
you're s'posed to memorize
when you're an idol!
[SAKURA] Yeah, but learning
new things is good for you.
[LILY]
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
[SAKI]
What's with the racket, squirt?
My name's not squirt!
I'm the shining star
of stage and screen!
-Miss Lily Hoshikawa!
-Pain in the ass.
Did you want to say something?
Before we practice, I think
we should pick a leader!
[SAKURA]
Leader?
Yeah! Somebody's gotta
be in charge of us!
That way, there's always someone
to make the tough decisions!
In that case...
I think it would be a good idea
for one of our more
experienced idols to be the--
Out of the question.
[SAKURA sighs, gasps]
[clears throat]
[deep inhale]
[yelling]
I'm the first captain of Dorami,
the legendary all-female biker
gang from Saga prefecture!
The name is Saki Nikaido!
I did a damn good job bossin'
all those biker chicks around,
so wranglin' a buncha babydolls
like you'll be a walk
in the park!
-I pick me!
-Jeez, we heard ya.
[SAKI] Who wants to fight me
for captain?
[SAKURA]
Looks like it's just you.
Aw yeah!
We're coming to get you, Japan.
Y' wanna start with Kyushu?
[SAKURA]
It's "leader," not "captain,"
this isn't a biker gang.
[LILY]
Leader!
We need a group name!
Huh? We don't have one?
You mean like "Death Musume"
and "Green Face"?
None of Tatsumi's dumb ideas
are idol-y enough!
-That's a good point.
-How about this one?
We could be "Magical Cutie Lily
and the Lily-ettes!"
[giggles]
That's a lot of Lily.
I'm not gonna spend eternity
with a kiddy-ass
group name like that!
I was thinkin'
somethin' more like this...
[SAKURA]
Could you read that out loud?
-Says "Joan of Arc!"
-Does it?
I think it has
a noble ring to it.
You do?
[SAKI]
She gets what I'm talkin' about!
However, perhaps
this would serve us.
[SAKURA]
"The Mibu Wolves?"
[SAKI]
Hey, that's pretty awesome!
As if.
They'd visit me.
Back in Shimabara.
Aw, no fair, you guys, I want
to be called something cuter!
-Idols do need to be cute.
-[SAKI] Why you little!
Hey, Tae?
We're trying to have
a conversation here.
-[TAE moans]
-[ALL] Huh?
[groans]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL groaning]
Eww...
Don't put that in your mouth!
It could kill you!
For the last time,
we're zombies.
-[TAE growls]
-[JUNKO screams]
[SAKURA groans]
Ugh, this is gettin' ridiculous.
-Figure it out, Sakura.
-Huh? But why me?
-Because I said so.
-Well, let me think here.
-Oh, how about Framboise?
-Aw, that's really cute!
[SAKI]
Framba-what now?
That's kinda hard to read.
[SAKI] A badass logo
is half the battle!
You took a cute word
and made it look stinky.
Well, we are dead, so I'm sure
we do have a terrible stench.
-[ALL gasping]
-[TAE groans]
[sniffing]
[ALL laughing]
Let's get back
to that group name!
-Any more?
-[SAKI] I bet Sakura's got some.
Uh, let's see.
How does Franchise sound?
Not that, but it should
be something French.
French Bread, French Fries,
French Toast?
What else is from France?
Cream puffs?
-[TAE sneezes]
-[ALL gasp]
[LILY]
Ew, she's all inky!
She's sneezing from the marker?
[TAE sneezes]
-You okay, Tae?
-[LILY gasps]
I get it now!
-[SAKI] Huh?
-Am I missing something here?
[LILY] I don’t think Tae
was just sneezing.
Really?
[LILY] I mean, she is,
but it's more than that!
[TAE sneezes]
You see? We needed a new name,
and she picked the perfect one!
[ALL]
Hmm?
Franchouchou! Doesn't it sound
so pretty and cool?
Franchouchou?
Yeah, you like it?
Franchouchou.
Franchouchou?
-[JUNKO] Uh...
-[AI groans]
[SAKI]
Y'know, I don't hate it!
Indeed!
It is quite an elegant name.
So cute, right?
It's way better than
what he came up with!
[SAKURA]
Franchouchou...
Wow, the more you say it,
the more adorable it sounds!
You did a great job, Tae!
[groans]
[SAKI]
Franchouchou...
Yup, looks good to me!
[SAKURA]
Don't write it like that!
[SAKI] Have it your way.
All right, it's official!
From now on, the seven of us
are gonna be called
Franchouchou!
[LILY]
Now, we just need to actually
learn the song for tomorrow!
[SAKURA giggles]
Right!
Sweet! Here we go,
Franchouchou!
It's time to practice
till our butts fall off!
Ya ready?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[LILY]
I don't think we can do this.
[SAKI]
It's way too hard.
I thought I was
starting to understand
but singing and dancing
are way tougher than I thought.
[TAE moans]
-If we blow it, we're done for.
-There's just not enough time.
[SAKURA]
Ai and Junko are the only ones
who know what they're doing.
[TAE grunting]
Uh...uh, Tae?
[SAKURA] We haven't even pulled
it off once during practice,
and tomorrow
we'll have an audience!
[TAE grunting quickly]
We're about to get thrown off!
I don't wanna!
[SAKURA] We should've
thought about this logically.
Being zombies is crazy enough,
but zombie idols?
[TAE panting]
-[LILY] Sakura!
-[SAKI] Get off that thing, now!
[SAKURA] Still, though,
I have to see this through!
I want to relive that feeling
I had the first time
I was on stage,
and figure out what it was!
[TAE panting rapidly]
Ahh!
[gasps]
[giggling, gasping]
[crunch]
[SAKI]
Sakura!
[LILY]
Are you okay?
[SAKURA] I'm going back in
so I can practice some more!
-[SAKI] Whoa.
-Saki. Lily. Tae...
Even though we're zombies now,
as long as everybody works hard,
I know we have a chance
to achieve our--
[slap echoing]
[gasps]
[SAKI gasps]
Mm.
Shame on you!
Whatever happened to practicing?
I'm confident that even
though we're zombies now,
if we work hard,
it'll be possible for us
to achieve our mission!
Um. That's what
I was about to--
[SAKI] Yugiri's right. We don't
need your negativity.
But...
Yeah, she knew just what to say
to get us all motivated!
Cool...
[JUNKO]
They've been gone a while...
[AI sighs]
[JUNKO] Yugiri was supposed
to bring the girls back here.
Do you think they gave up?
[JUNKO] I think it might
be better if they did.
You can't pull off an idol
performance overnight.
Besides...
If the show doesn't go well,
then the audience
won't have a good time.
If it's from the heart,
they'll still appreciate it.
[AI]
But that's if.
[SAKI]
All right, let's get crackin'!
[SAKI] We're gonna put on
a damn good show tomorrow!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[SAKURA] One, two, three, four!
One, two, three, and four and
One, two, three, four! One...
Ahh!
[SAKURA]
One, two, three, four! One, two-
Oh, Lily! Are you hurt?
[LILY] The steps for this part
are so tricky!
-Then try dancin' better!
-Wow, thanks for the tip!
Stop bickering,
both of you!
[SAKURA gasps]
Sorry...
Well...
I think we should keep
practicin', with or without 'em.
Come on, girls, let's try again!
I'll start the song!
[JUNKO gasps]
-[AI] What?
-[KOTARO] If you don't dance,
then you're just plain
old zombies.
Being an idol is hard!
You don't understand!
Oh, cry me a river.
I'm telling you,
there's no way this'll work!
Is that what you
honestly believe?
[gasps]
Trust me, I know.
[KOTARO] Then why were you
two idols when you were alive?
You're dead, but at least
the others are trying to live.
Will you join them, or would
you rather just sit and rot?
Okay, is everybody ready?
Starting now, you're
a guerrilla squadron.
Boldly prowling through
the ruthless concrete jungle.
This train station
is your battleground
where you will unleash
confusion and wonderment
upon the passersby,
so as to claim victory!
All right ladies,
time's a-wastin'.
Go go go go go go
go go go!
-[LILY] Showtime!
-Go, go, go...
[KOTARO]
Let's go!
[sighs]
-Ai. Junko.
-[SAKI] Sakura.
I guess the show'll have
to go on without them.
Okay. This is our chance to make
those practice hours count!
Uh...hey everybody,
we're Franchouchou!
We worked hard on this,
-so we hope you like it!
-[CROWD] Huh?
[MAN]
Okay...
[WOMAN] Hey, look! Is she
singing with squid in her mouth?
[MAN]
Whoa, she is! But why?
I wonder how
everyone is feeling.
I think they're okay.
Ah!
Oh no!
What? Don't stop singing,
you idiot!
-[SAKURA] You okay?
-[LILY] Sorry. I didn't mean to.
[SAKURA]
I didn't rehearse enough.
[SAKI] Whoops!
Stay calm!
[SAKURA]
We can do it, guys!
[SAKURA] For now, all we need to
do is put our hearts into this
and try our hardest!
Here we go.
Time for the final verse!
[SAKURA] Oh no.
What are the words again?
I forgot! What do I do?
Come on, brain!
Please don't do this to me!
[SAKURA gasps]
[SAKURA]
That girl.
She's having a blast!
-Look at her smile!
-[FAN GIRL giggles]
[ALL panting]
[SAKURA] Is it over?
-[AI] We should sign off.
-[SAKI] Yeah!
[SAKI]
Anyway, uh. We're Franchouchou!
[FAN GIRL giggling, clapping]
Thanks a lot.
We'll put on a better show
next time, I promise!
-I'll see ya then!
-[FAN GIRL'S MOM] There you are!
Let's go.
That was fun!
Well, that coulda gone a hell
of a lot better, huh?
[MALE COP]
Hold it right there, ladies!
[ALL gasp]
Hate to tell ya,
but you can't do
street shows without a permit!
What are you tryin' to do here,
get arrested?
Because I will arrest ya!
You'll never take me alive!
[YUGIRI]
No, Lady Saki,
-now isn't the time!
-[LILY] Yeah, you're the leader!
Um, sorry, officer,
we'll leave right away!
Hey. You look familiar.
-Huh? Me? Uh, no I don't!
-[tires screech]
-Get inside the van! Go! Go! Go!
-Oh, wow! That guy's weird!
[YUGIRI]
Farewell, then!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go! Come on, come on!
-Okay, go! Go, go! Go! Go!
-[breaks screeching]
She seemed really jumpy.
Guess I musta poured
on too much of the ol' charm!
[JUNKO] We still ended up
performing, huh?
Hey guys, can we talk?
Thank you. Really.
If it hadn't been for you,
nobody would have stayed
through the whole song.
That all?
Both of you did an amazing job,
you totally saved the show!
It made me feel like
the rest of us
might not ever make it
as idols without you.
[BOTH groan uneasily]
No, wait!
I mean, because of that,
I want to practice even harder!
[SAKURA] I know we might not be
real idols yet,
and we're zombies too,
which just makes everything
that much trickier.
But I'll give it my very best,
and if each of us does that,
then despite
what we're up against,
I'm sure Franchouchou can become
something really incredible
in the future!
I think that's how we all feel.
[ROMERO panting]
[ROMERO barks]
[SAKURA]
Have a good night!
You know,
today was a total disaster.
But performing with everyone,
felt so much better
than I ever thought it would.
[JUNKO]
You were great, too.
Well, this is it.
We're starting over
from scratch.
Junko here.
Singing is my greatest passion.
Is this my chance
to return to the stage
and feel the glow
of the spotlight?
Next time on Zombie Land Saga,
Episode 4: "Warming Dead Saga."
Hope you like it.