[SAKURA]
Last time on Zombie Land Saga!
We ironed out
some of the details
about our name and group leader!
We decided Saki should be
in charge,
and that our group's
called Franchouchou!
That really screams "cute zombie
girls," don't you think?
Once that was all squared away,
we had a guerrilla-style
pop-up show in the street!
It was our first time
doing anything "idol-ish,"
and that was cool,
but it's pretty clear
we have a long way to go!
We'll have to keep practicing
till we die all over again!
But I believe in me,
and I believe in Franchouchou!
Good morning, ladies!
[ALL groan]
Aw, come on, you look like
you're dead inside!
Good morning!
Good morning to you too, sir.
-[TAE snores]
-[SAKI yawns]
Okay, first thing.
It looks like you've been taking
your lessons
pretty seriously lately.
By the way, how have you been
settling into your new name?
Franken-choo-choo!
You're saying it wrong,
it's Franchouchou!
-Franny-fanny-shoe-shoe!
-Franchou--!
Yeah, yeah, I know,
it's Flannel-foo-foo!
[in a French accent]
"Ooh, we have a French name,
look how cute we are!"
-[KOTARO laughs]
-[whimpers]
Okay, Franchouchou, even though
only a month ago
at that guerrilla concert,
you were still just a brain-dead
gaggle of drooling zombies,
you all may have improved
the tiniest bit.
[huffs]
And this is the part where
the real game begins.
Right, boss?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
Spoken like a true leader.
What's your take on it, Lily?
Me? I'll do my--
-[KOTARO] Great!
-Ahh!
Now, which one of you ladies
would like to guess
what your next move should be?
Sakura!
Oh!
I'm not sure...
Maybe it's time for us to record
a single and put it out?
Excellent, you've got a good
head on your shoulders!
[giggles]
Let me just call up
a recording studio and--
No, dumbass!
[whimpers]
Are you crazy?
Where are we gonna
get the money?
You honestly think I've made
a single buck off of you
and your raggedy-ass
performances so far?
Not to mention your expenses?!
Somebody's gotta make sure
there's gas in the van,
ya dumb zombie!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[TAE continues snoring]
My point is, our budget's
as dry as your skin!
Huh? So, what's your plan?
The only solution
is "get more money."
I'm sorry, what?
Does Saga even have businesses
that would hire idols?
Thanks to my supreme
awesomeness, yes!
And it's a big-name
pharmaceutical company
known as Hisanaka.
We could form a partnership
if this goes well!
Partnership?
This is way over my head.
Just tell me when it's
supposed to go down.
We start right now.
-Now?!
-[TAE snores]
[KOTARO] The old group
they had booked for their
company trip is
no longer available.
[AI]
Your ideas are so last minute.
'Cause we can't afford
to miss any chances!
Idols have a limited shelf
life nowadays, y'know?
And it's not like I can work you
girls to death, amiright?
We're doing it and that's final.
[groans]
Just don't stop practicing!
We have to knock
their socks off!
Next stop.
The Ureshino Hot Springs.
Hot springs?
[JUNKO whimpers, embarrassed]
So, we get to take a real bath?
We've just been hosin' off
in the yard!
Perhaps this is the perfect
opportunity
to cleanse a bit of stench
and decay from our rancid flesh.
[ALL gasp, sniff themselves]
They're kind enough to let us
stay the night,
so please behave yourselves.
We get to stay?!
That means plenty of time
to chill out!
There will be no hot springs fun
for you!
[ALL]
Huh?
'Cause you won't be able
to leave your rooms
unless you're
in your full makeup!
Sucks to be you!
And besides, if you've got time
to splish-splash
in a hot spring,
then you've got time
-to practice!
-[SAKI growls]
[KOTARO groans]
[KOTARO]
Ow, ow, o--
-[KOTARO] Ow.
-Sir?
What's that?
This pharmaceutical company.
Do they sell pills or...?
[KOTARO]
Check it out!
[ALL gasp, confused]
Huh?
[SAKURA]
Saganship...Z?
[KOTARO] 'Kay, your room
number's six-oh-six.
You go on at 6:00 PM, got it?
-[SAKI groans]
-Understood, sir!
I went to the trouble
of reserving
a rehearsal space for you.
So, you girls better practice
while I'm gone.
Of course!
Wait, what will you be doing,
Mr. Kotaro?
Sightseeing.
Those sights ain't gonna
see themselves!
Okie-dokie, where do we
wanna go first?
Uh, to the room?
Of all the cool stuff we could
do, you really pick work?
We should practice.
Yeah, later!
Not while Shades is out
paintin' the town
without a care in the world!
No, now.
Look. Do you wanna die?
[nervously]
Ehh...
Come on, we've been cooped up
in the house for a solid month!
Let's take advantage of Ureshino
while we're here!
I wanna go for a walk!
The squirt knows what's up!
I said my name's Lily,
not squirt!
[groans, annoyed]
[YUGIRI] I suppose we
can relax for a bit.
I haven't seen a modern-day
city yet,
and I'd like to explore.
We look totally normal
with makeup.
If we're super careful,
no one'll be able to tell
we're zombies!
Good thinkin', squirt!
My name is Lily.
[sighs]
[SAKURA]
If that's what we all want.
Ai, Junko, what's your vote?
-[TAE groans]
-[AI and JUNKO sigh]
It seems risky, but...
♪
Listen to this, Junko!
That sculpture is said
to make you healthier
and help your skin!
You have to splash water on it!
Let's do it!
-[water splashing]
-[BOTH panting]
Damn, look at 'em go.
Crazy!
-[AI sighs]
-[ALL] Huh?
-[TAE growling, biting]
-[bells ringing]
[ALL groaning]
[scoffs]
[KOTARO]
It’s such an honor to hear from
an esteemed company
like Hisanaka Pharmaceuticals.
We heard about you from the
people who manage the inn.
How fortuitous that my
regular interactions
with local businesses
and the chamber of commerce
has led us to this encounter.
A Saga-based idol group?
That must be hard these days!
It can feel like we're fighting
the flow of history.
But the way I see it,
if we make even the smallest
impact, it's all worth it.
That's wonderful.
We're planning to bring
new life to Saga.
As a matter of fact, that idea
is at the core of every endeavor
Franchouchou undertakes.
New life to Saga?
Right.
You and I may be
in two different fields,
but my group has a great
admiration for your company's
standing as one of the biggest
in the prefecture.
Well.
I appreciate the kind words,
but we're actually
working on ways to expand
our overall customer base.
We would like for our brand to
appeal to a younger demographic.
In that case, we might just be
what you're looking for!
If we were to become partners,
I'm confident we could meet,
and exceed, your expectations.
I'm looking forward to this
evening's performance, then.
That's excellent to hear!
My hardworking girls
are practicing
their hearts out...
-[GIRLS talking, indistinctly]
-right...
[TAE groans]
now...
Is something the matter?
Oh--
[sighs, flattered]
Oh!
[sighs]
Oh, wow! This feels great!
I've never used one before.
Nothing short of heavenly.
It's still a little crazy
that this is happening, though.
What do you mean?
Well, if we hadn't come back
from the dead,
the seven of us would never
have gotten the chance
to meet each other.
'Cause we're all from
different times, ya know?
Hell yeah, and the best part is
I don't feel dead!
It's not too bad.
Even if we were alive
at the same time,
I wouldn't have
hung out with Saki.
Shut your yap!
Well, honestly, you all
make me feel like
I'm a young girl again.
Oh yeah, that's right!
It must be so different for you!
But bodies are cremated
in Japan,
so how'd we get like this?
[ALL gasp]
I'm a little curious
about Mr. Tatsumi.
Don't look at me!
Well, you were the first one
of us to awaken, right?
Yeah, but I don't know
why or how!
Oh well.
Just let it go!
[AI] Not like he'd give us
a straight answer if we asked.
The one thing we do know
for sure is that we're here now,
enjoyin' this awesome
foot bath together.
-See, aren't ya glad?
-Mm-hmm.
But we really do need
to practice--
Yeah, I know!
[ALL]
Hm?
[AI gasps]
So, tell me.
-[sighs]
-Do you think we have any chance
of making it
as a real idol group?
That depends, what do you think
it means to be "real idols?"
[gasps]
Uh, like singing and dancing,
making people feel happy,
and creating lots
of excitement!
If that's it, we have a lot more
practicing and learning to do.
[SAKURA and YUGIRI sigh]
So if we work harder,
do you think we'll pull it off?
[wood locks]
Listen.
I'll do all that I can.
Everything I said last time?
I meant it!
-[pensive sigh]
-[footsteps]
I don't like to half-ass,
so count me all the way in!
To the art of performing,
I swore my life,
and now my death.
Trust me, I know
how hard showbiz can be!
[JUNKO]
As for me...
I always used
to do things alone.
That's why the thought
of being a team
doesn't always sit well with me.
That said, if the rest of you
really feel strongly about this,
then maybe...
I'd better do my part, too,
right?
Thanks, Junko!
But, look, the second
I feel like this
might not work, I'm out.
I swear, you won't
feel that way!
Hm...
Aww yeah!
They're not gonna know
what hit 'em
when they see our concert later!
Ooh, fun.
How do we make that happen?
Uhh, not sure.
If we do our best
to service them,
I'm certain the result will be
pleasurable for all parties.
Wow, we need
to work on your phrasing.
We should probably start
by finding out
everything we can about
the product they're selling.
Oh yeah!
We don't even know what
Saganship Z is supposed to do!
I say we go try it out
right now!
Yeah!
[TAE stretching, groaning]
So you just slap
these suckers on
and they make your back
and shoulders feel good?
That's the general idea.
For real?
That's what's up!
Says you can't put them
on other people
because it counts
as "practicing medicine."
Like I give a crap.
And besides, we're not people,
we're zombies.
[SAKURA]
Ehh...
I don't think there's really
a difference--
-[SAKURA] Hey!
-[SAKI] Ha!
[screams in relief]
Awesome! It's like all my muscle
fatigue is melting away!
That's so cool!
-Guess we absorb stuff faster!
-Look at me!
I can move as much as I want,
and it doesn't fall off!
[JUNKO sighs, relieved]
[YUGIRI sighs, relieved]
You should try it, Ai.
No, I'd rather not.
I don't have any pai--
[AI yells in relief]
[AI crying]
[relieved]
Uhhh!
Let's use this
in the show somehow!
That way everyone can see
how well it works!
[ALL]
Hmmm...
[gasps]
Hey, guys!
I understand that work
can be super stressful.
So we hope our
performance helps you unwind
and recover
a little bit tonight!
And there's nothing better
for relaxing than Saganship Z
-by Hisanaka Pharmaceuticals!
-[ATTENDEES sighs, relieved]
[MAN chuckles]
I'm Number One!
-That's Number Two!
-[SAKI chuckles]
-Thanks, everybody!
-[SAKURA] Three! Four!
Five!
Six!
And Zero!
Together we're.
Franchouchou!
-[ATTENDEES cheering, applause]
-[SAKURA] Thanks for having us!
[KOTARO]
Songs for the soul.
And Saganship Z for the body.
The perfect match.
ATTENDEES cheering, applause]
[panting]
[sighs, triumphantly]
[SAKURA]
The crowd really liked us!
I'm so happy!
-[SAKI] Sakura.
-Hm?
Don't take your makeup off.
But it's bedtime.
Not yet, it isn't!
-Let's hit that hot spring!
-What?
We can't come all the way here
and not get in it!
But once our makeup melts off,
it's all over!
Nobody's gonna be out there
this late, c'mon.
If Kotaro finds out,
we're in trouble.
Here's the solution.
[exhales]
We try not to get caught.
-[SAKI chuckles]
-But what if we do?
Doesn't matter, we won't!
I really wish I knew
where you got that
unlimited confidence of yours.
[SAKI] Let's just say I've
gotten into way more trouble
than you ever have.
Is it just us?
Who else did you tell?
I think two zombies is plenty.
[chuckles]
Less suspicious, right?
Ugh. I see what your game is.
[gasps]
Huh...ahh!
Hey, Junko.
You're still up?
Yes, and I was planning
on taking off
all of my makeup after you.
But, then I heard--
Oh! We're not going.
-Too risky.
-Huh?
I really...wanted to go.
Can we?
[devious chuckle]
You hear that?
Two to one.
Uhh...
The water here's supposed to be
really good for your skin,
though!
[SAKI]
Makes it all shiny and smooth.
Maybe it'll even hard-boil
that egg head of yours!
-Ha!
-[SAKURA groaning]
[water moving]
[BOTH gasp]
[SAKI]
Cowabunga!
Come on, you two!
Let's get in and out
while we got time!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[SAKURA relieved]
Ahh...
Wow, I feel so alive right now!
Me, too.
But for the last time,
we're dead.
[SAKURA gasps]
My skin already looks
a lot smoother!
[SAKI]
Told ya!
Zombie skin absorbs
stuff faster!
It's great!
Totally worth the risk!
Your head's all shiny, too!
-Hm.
-Huh...
You know somethin'?
It looks like your egg head
went rotten.
Huh?
[JUNKO screams]
I think something
just touched me!
[SAKI]
Aw hell no!
Come out and show yourself,
jackass.
I got some action for ya
right here!
Uh--
[SAKI]
Is that some kinda bandage?
Oh yeah, it's a Saganship Z.
Damn, these things
are absorbent!
[SAKURA]
Phew, that scared me!
I guess you forgot
to take it off your back.
Ohmigosh, I must have!
I'm sorry!
Anyway.
I think today went pretty well.
-[SAKI] You?
-Oh, definitely!
[groans]
But, uh...
Well, the audience did look like
they were having a good time,
and at the end of the day,
that's most important.
[gasps]
Still, though, our performance
could use a lot of improvement.
Yeah.
I say we all keep
doing our best,
so next time we can wow them
with just our singing
and dancing.
Okay!
-[BOTH gasp]
-Aw, sweet!
It's like Marutchi
just became Tamatchi!
-[gate opens]
-[ALL] Huh?
[JUNKO] Look, it's the lady
from Hisanaka!
This is bad!
She'll see us!
Go underwater!
We're zombies, so we probably
don't need to breathe!
[inhales deeply]
-[JUNKO inhales deeply]
-[SAKURA] Uh...
'Kay, here goes!
-[head bounces]
-Ahh!
-[water splashes]
-Hm?
[HISANAKA REP]
Hello?
Hmm...?
Hmm...
♪
[HISANAKA REP
hyperventilates, screams]
Sakura!
[HISANAKA REP gasps]
[HISANAKA REP screams,
in the distance]
What?
[panting]
Huh?
[gasps]
[rapid breathing]
-[TAE] Ah!
-[HISANAKA REP screams]
[TAE groaning]
-[bones cracking]
-[HISANAKA REP screaming]
[panting]
-[HISANAKA REP screams]
-[AI screams]
[panting]
Miss!
Help me!
-[HISANAKA REP crying]
-[YUGIRI] Oh, dear.
How may I be of service?
Ahhh!
[BOTH panting]
Whoa! Hey, did I miss something?
I'll catch you up later!
Right now, we gotta
get to the room!
[panting]
[HISANAKA REP screams]
-[SAKI] Ahhh!
-[HISANAKA REP gasps]
[SAKI] Sorry, ma'am, your patch
things are really slippery!
[HISANAKA REP screams]
Thank you again for inviting us.
And if you decide you'd like
to do business,
please be in touch.
Hm?
[HISANAKA REP whimpering]
Oh.
Sorry about that.
Turns out she had some kind of
big scare last night.
The shock's
caused her to forget
everything that happened
yesterday.
Yikes.
[SAKURA whimpers]
You better be glad you're dead.
-[SAKURA crying]
-They say there's no bad press,
but this is bad.
Who would publish that crap?
Let's go kick their asses!
Sorry, it's all my fault.
Don't worry, I promise I'll be
a lot more careful from now on.
There, there.
At least we got the chance
to enjoy
that luxurious foot bath
together.
[YUGIRI] I've never had
a communal experience like that.
I think it was
a worthwhile journey!
We had fun!
I bet the better
we all get along,
the better we'll be on stage!
Do you think so?
Hope you're right.
And another benefit.
No more fatigue,
thanks to these.
The old school chick is right!
Next time, we'll nail it!
-'Kay!
-Yeah!
Starting now, we bust
our ass and get paid!
[ALL]
Yeah!
You know that's not going to
solve all our problems, right?
[stretching, groaning]
Ahh!
[ALL laughing]
[ROMERO howls]
[ROMERO barks]
Yugiri speaking.
The seven of us are now working
toward a common goal.
Isn't that a noble ideal?
Next time on Zombie Land
Saga, episode five:
"The Nice Bird
SAGA in Your Heart".
We hope you'll join us.