[music playing]
AMY: If you're using
this route, there's
a shortcut you can take that
will save you some time.
But remember, you can't cross
here or here without a kite.
So when you don't
have a kite, you'll
have to take this
extra detour here.
-And this area here is where
all the handsome boys hang out
all the time.
-Above all, be careful.
There's lots of
dangers on that route.
-There are lots of small ships
all crammed together here.
And the connecting
bridges between them
are all narrow too.
So watch where you step
and don't fall overboard.
-But Amy, if this
is so dangerous,
is it OK for children to do?
-That's why we're
here helping them.
-Will it not be difficult?
-Oh, Ledo, don't you remember
when you started working?
Wasn't it hard at first?
-Yes.
-Everyone makes a few
mistakes in the beginning,
and that's why when they make
the first couple of deliveries,
we'll be going
along to help out.
-But even with help, what
if they mess up and packages
cannot be delivered?
-That's a good question.
Let's say, that some
Yunboro schematics that
were supposed to be
delivered got lost.
It'd be impossible
to maintain Yunboros.
-And what's worse, if all the
Yunboros couldn't be properly
maintained, they'd
just shut down.
-Then, everyone's work
would be affected.
MELTY: No matter what they do.
We work with just about
everyone in the fleet.
So we have to do our jobs right.
SAAYA: We'd all be
in serious trouble
if we couldn't get
food or supplies.
-Nobody would be
able to survive.
-There have been cases where
that's actually happened.
All the people on a lone ship
or even a small fleet died off,
and it just became abandoned.
LEDO: Abadoned ship?
-Yep.
A ship that has become
just an empty shell.
It floats along aimlessly, and
the people who once lived on it
are all gone.
Some people call
it a ghost ship.
-That's scary.
-I'm afraid of ghosts.
-I want to go home.
-Yeah.
And I know a true story
about a real life ghost ship.
Once upon a time,
there was this ship
interlocked with
a certain fleet.
And there was a
messenger girl, who
had to deliver a package there.
So she went to that
ship all by herself.
AMY (VOICEOVER): However,
once the girl got to the ship,
there was nobody on board.
All the doors and
hatches were left open.
And there were
half-eaten meals left
on tables that looked like
they'd been there for a while.
The girl was very nervous,
and she thought to herself,
could this be one
of those abandoned
ships I've heard about,
where there's not
a living soul on board?
SAAYA (VOICEOVER): So
then what happened?
AMY (VOICEOVER): I don't
think it's a good idea
to stay here any
longer, the girl
thought as she turned to go.
But then, out of the corner
of her eye, she saw something.
She thought, there can't
be anyone left aboard.
Maybe it's a ghost.
Suddenly, she felt--
-Chamber, define
the term "ghost."
CHAMBER: A word
for ghost does not
exist in the standard lexicon
of the Galactic Alliance.
-It does not exist?
Does that mean it
is something that
only exists on this planet?
CHAMBER: Insufficient
data to answer that.
However, given the
information offered here,
one might infer it is
a type of life form.
-A life form?
AMY (VOICEOVER): A trail
of bloody footprints
that came up to
right behind her.
The girl was so scared.
She couldn't move a muscle.
And then she heard, boom, boom.
[knocking]
A strange knocking
sound at the window.
She turned around
without thinking.
And there she saw--
[alarm blaring]
-The alarm.
-Ridget, ghost ship.
-I understand.
Talk about bad timing.
[theme music]
Pretty big, isn't it?
-Looks to me like
more of an abandoned
fleet than an abandoned ship.
-Standard procedure
dictates that we
dispatch a reconnaissance team.
We'll search for any
remaining survivors
and determine the reason
for the abandonment.
-Let's ask for volunteers
for the reconnaissance team.
Ten from the escort ships.
And perhaps a few
other should be
enough to canvas
a fleet that size.
-Hey, I'll go.
-You can count me in too.
-Ledo, you should
come along with us.
-Me?
-We might find a huge haul
of treasure over there.
Then, we'd need the tin can.
Ridget, is that cool?
-Fine.
Go ahead.
-Ah.
The hottie's going to go too.
-Lucky.
-We all tagged along.
-Girls, honestly.
-Sorry.
Please let us help too.
-We won't be in the way.
Promise.
-Maybe we should stay here.
OK.
BOTH: Huh?
-I-- I mean just that
someone needs to keep an eye
on the ship we took
to get here, right?
What?
The ship is gone?
-The escort ship went to
search the fleet's perimeter.
-Oh no.
-Well, this place is
bigger than we thought.
We could sure use them.
-All right, Bellows.
They can help.
BOTH: All right.
-What?
Hey, is anybody in here?
I don't know.
You try.
-Anyone.
Is anybody in here?
Was that OK?
-Mm-hm.
-If we call, will a
ghost answer to that too?
-We-- we don't want
to see any ghost.
All right.
-These ghosts are enemies?
Should I go fight them?
-No.
Don't do anything to them.
-Understood.
Amy, it could be a survivor.
-But it's--
-Do not worry.
I am here.
-What is in there?
-What the hell?
There ain't nothing on
this old piece of junk.
So disappointing.
-You're telling me, bub.
Why do I always get
stuck teamed up with you?
-If you really don't like
it, we could always split up.
-Uh, no.
-Then quit grumbling.
It is what it is.
-But Pinion.
-OK.
Want to try something?
BOTH: Huh?
-Let's play a trick
on our friends.
-Huh?
-What do you mean a trick?
-We'll dress up as ghosts.
Then, when Ledo and Amy
come by, we'll scare them.
BOTH: We're in.
-Who is here?
Show yourself.
The door just closed on its own.
Is anyone here?
Come out.
-Ahh!
-Hold your fire.
LEDO: Pinion?
-It was a joke.
Don't shoot me.
-Pinion's a moron.
He made the hottie snuggle
up even more with Amy.
It's not fair.
-No kidding.
AMY: Don't do stuff like that.
You scared me half to death.
MELTY: What are you
complaining about?
-I wish those guys would
take this seriously.
Right, Ridget.
What's wrong.
Did you find something?
The sickbay.
What is?
Is there something on
this ship after all?
-Bellows, I think
I know this fleet.
Gargantia has had contact
with this fleet once before.
It was about seven years ago.
-This is very important now.
So pay close attention.
Right here.
This is the main winch.
You have to make
sure it's oiled.
STORIA: Hey, Ridget.
-Hm?
-You know this fleet sure has
a weird way of interlocking.
Don't you think?
-Their fleet does it that
way, because their ships
are designed
differently than ours.
Their interlock ships have
arms already attached,
so they don't have
to use Yunboros.
STORIA: Huh.
You sure do you know a lot
about this stuff, Rigdet.
Wow.
Look at that.
--Storia, don't point like that.
Remember.
We're here as representatives
of the Gargantia fleet.
-Sorry.
But it's not everyday
we get the chance
to check out another
fleet up close.
-I guess.
Even though they say
this is for our benefit.
I just don't see
the point of having
us perform
interlocking manually.
-I know.
But I've had fun meeting
so many new people here.
Like Ritona, who's
the one teaching us
the interlocking today.
He's the head of the
entire interlocking guild.
He's definitely a lot younger
than any guild masters
on Gargantia.
-I admit.
He does appear to
be a competent man.
-You up there.
Stop daydreaming.
It's dangerous.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-May I say something?
-What is it?
-I do not feel that this kind
of training is beneficial, sir.
-Your name is Ridget
if I'm not mistaken.
Are you saying that a future
candidate for fleet commander
doesn't need to learn
the interlocking
methods of other fleets
she may encounter?
-Well, to speak frankly, sir.
I don't.
-Oh.
OK.
Then, can you do me a favor?
Be a dear and take
that group down there
through the
interlocking process.
-Huh?
-Hey, guys up here.
You've got a new teacher
for the rest of the day.
So pay attention.
-Hey, wait a second.
-What's wrong?
You know all there
is to know already.
Don't you?
Show them your excellent
Gargantia style interlocking
technique.
-But I can't.
-If you can't teach someone
else how to do something,
it means that you still
have a lot of things
left you need to learn to do.
Am I wrong?
If you come to bear a
great responsibility,
experience will be crucial.
Even if how you do
things on your fleet
is different than
how we do them here,
learning something new
really is important.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-Right.
OK, kids.
Were you paying
attention before.
Show me what you learned.
KIDS: Yes, sir.
-Ridget.
Ridget!
Somebody get a stretcher.
-I, uh--
-Dammit, girl.
I told you it was dangerous.
Are you injured?
-No, sir.
-I see.
Thank God.
-Stay still now.
-Ritona!
FEMALE SPEAKER:
Are you all right?
-Don't worry.
I'm fine.
-You're not fine.
You're bleeding a lot.
Hurry up and get
stretcher already.
Call the medic STAT.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Yes, ma'am.
Right away.
Let's go.
MALE SPEAKER: Go.
Hurry.
Come on.
STORIA: Ridget.
Did you come down here
to pay Ritona a visit?
-No.
I was just going to
leave him some-- Storia,
have you been down
here this whole time?
-Come on in, Ridget.
-Wait.
STORIA: Ritona, look.
Ridget came to see you.
-Um.
I-- I don't, uh--
-Thanks for coming to visit me.
-Sure.
-Oh.
Don't worry about that.
Come have a seat.
Sorry about what I said.
-It's not your fault.
You didn't do anything.
I was being careless,
and you got really
hurt all because of me.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
-Don't worry about it, Ridget.
-Hey, is that a camera that
you're working on there?
-Oh.
I'm surprised you know that.
Yeah.
I recreated it from
ancient blueprints I found.
-I saw a camera once
when I was a little girl.
I am amazed you were able
to make one from scratch.
-And it works too.
Hold still.
-Oh.
-Here we go.
[click]
STORIA: Sorry for
just dropping by.
RIDGET: You're always welcome.
Tell me.
Is anything wrong?
-Well, it's Ritona
asked me if I would
come with him when they leave.
-I see.
STORIA: But just the idea
of leaving Gargantia-- I
mean I've never thought
about it before.
Obviously, since
I have no family
that wouldn't be a problem.
But I have friends,
like you, Ridget.
So I don't know
if I could do it.
How could I leave
people I care about?
-Storia, how do you
really feel about Ritona?
Be honest.
You're in love with him, right?
Then go.
Don't worry about anything else.
-Ridget, I don't want to
completely abandon you.
-You could visit.
You can always come back to
Gargantia whenever you want.
Over there, you'll
meet new people
and make more friends,
especially now
that you've forged a new bond.
-A new bond.
-Storia, I know you'll be OK.
-Oh, Ridget.
-Huh?
This is--
-Ahh!
-What is it?
-It's the main ship's
power generator.
-Wow.
I've never seen one before.
-Now, I get it.
-Did you figure something out?
-Looks like the light bugs did
a real number on this thing.
-The light bugs?
-Why?
-Light bugs multiply
continuously,
and they're small enough to
get into just about anything.
When enough of
them get together,
they crystallize and
get as hard as a rock.
If we can see them eating away
at the outside of this thing,
then the inside of the engine
must be completely encased
in light bugs.
This fleet must have been
dependant on this power source.
And they had a lot of ships
that either couldn't produce
any power or couldn't produce
enough on their own to leave.
Most likely, those
ships were the only ones
that were left here.
I think it's safe to assume
that all the people on board
got on the ships that
did have their own power
and just took off.
-That's a relief.
-Then there aren't any
ghosts here after all.
-Does that mean that the
ghosts escaped as well?
-Sure.
We can say that if you want.
RIDGET: Roger, thank
you for investigating.
The fleet commander's journal
supports Pinion's explanation.
-Then are we done searching?
-Yes.
Let's go back to Gargantia.
-Uh.
At the end of the day,
no treasure at all.
BELLOWS: That's
not entirely true.
-Huh?
-Hm.
-That's right.
-What the hell, Bellows?
You found something valuable.
-That's my secret.
-Come on, you tight-lipped cow.
Don't be a hard ass.
BELLOWS: What was that?
Come here.
[thump]
PINION : Ah.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
-We're back everyone.
-Were there any ghosts?
-Was it scary?
-Yeah.
There were a ton of
ghosts everywhere.
-Really?
-Hi, Bebel.
-Amy.
-It was incredible.
You should have seen it.
-Amy.
[theme music]