-Hmm-umm.
Where's Ridget?
-I'm here, Fleet Commander.
Take this.
-Huh?
-Oh.
-This is--
-Take care of the fleet.
-Don't say that,
Commander Fairlock.
The Garantia Fleet
needs you, not me.
-In your hands, I'm not worried.
-But Commander, I can't.
-You're a fine officer.
When I see your
father, I will give him
a glowing report
of your service.
-No, Commander!
-Hmm.
-No.
No.
Commander.
First coordinates confirmed.
-Huh?
CHAMBER: Galactic
alliance inner coordinates
in its current
position confirmed.
-Does that mean you
know where we are?
We can go?
CHAMBER: Negative.
A subspace guidance
method is necessary.
I am not capable of
navigating without it.
-What?
What about an SOS?
CHAMBER: SOS, emergency landing
on Earth signal has been sent.
Estimated time to arrival,
approximately 6,582 years,
16 hours, 20 minutes.
-Impossible.
It can't be.
CHAMBER: Returning to the
main force at this time
is not feasible.
-I can't go back.
[MUSIC - "THIS WORLD HAS
BEEN WAITING FOR US,"
MINORI CHIHARA]
-Ridget?
Are you serious?
That little girl?
-The Commander appointed her
himself on his death bed.
Maybe I should be getting
out of here with Flange, too.
-Ship Masters, there you are.
I'm glad I caught
you altogether.
Flange's departure is imminent.
I must consult with you.
It cannot wait.
-Hey, come on.
-Now ain't the time for that.
-Today is Fleet Commander
Fairlock's funeral.
-Yes, but my first
priority is the fleet.
-You were like a
daughter to Fairlock.
How could you not attend
the man's memorial?
-The man raised you, didn't he?
He took you in
when Chevron died.
-What are you doing?
You're supposed to assemble
at the bow of the flag ship.
-Yes, we're on our way.
-Let's go.
-Change is never easy.
-Yes, I realize that.
-So you can't go home?
-No.
-That's a shame, kid.
I feel for you.
But, you know, if you
have to be stuck here,
you should make the best of it.
You really want to kill
some whalesquid, right?
-Killing them is my
primary objective.
-Then I may be able to help.
I know where their nest is.
-What?
They have a nest?
-Easy now.
Attacking a whalesquid now
ain't no simple feat, kid.
But there's treasure.
-I don't care about money.
-No problem.
You kill the
whalesquid, and I'll
salvage the treasure
after you're done.
Sound good?
-As long as I can
kill the Hideauze.
-Then it sounds
like we have a deal.
-Release all the ships
that want to leave,
30 interlocks have
to be unfastened.
Be careful, work fast.
Let's do this.
-Flange, please reconsider.
Don't leave Gargantia.
-My mind is made up, Ridget.
A fleet lacking in
strong central leadership
is a ripe target for pirates.
-But Flange.
-There is also the treasure
Pinion talks about.
It's a legacy from the past that
could be the key to our future.
But I'm doing this for the
citizens who came to me
and said that they
wanted to leave.
My duty is to them.
I've sworn to protect
the people on my ship,
and that is what I intend to do.
-Thanks for the package.
-You're welcome, bye.
-Melty.
-Saaya.
Amy.
-Melty, are you
really leaving us?
-Yep.
-Do you have to go
with Flange's ship?
Can't you stay here?
-I'd stay if I could, but
I can't leave Grandpa.
-I see.
-I never imagined our ship
would leave Gargantia.
I thought we'd always be here.
But things change, so I'm going.
But I'm actually
looking forward to it.
One upside is that I may get
to meet some cute new guys.
-Rich ones?
-Definitely.
Plus, it looks like the
hottie is coming, too.
-He is?
-Pinion's telling
everyone in the fleet.
He says that with
Ledo's flying Yunboro,
we'll all be safe
from the whalesquids.
-I understand.
-Fairlock should have chosen you
to be the next Fleet Commander,
Crown, not her.
-I don't have much
time left myself.
I must guide the next
generation to go on without me.
-Train her as much as you
possibly can, my friend.
Fleet Commander, we have had
fair winds and flowing seas,
but now our voyage
together has ended.
May all the blessings of
the virtuous waves be yours.
-Huh?
-Don't you need to wear
black to a funeral?
-Pinion.
-Sign the release for
the departing ships.
-How many times do
I have to tell you?
No.
-Prove to me it will
be worthwhile to stay,
and I won't go.
Just give me what I want.
-You know, I can't.
-Then you got no
business stopping me.
You ain't got the balls
to command this fleet.
See you around.
[squeak]
-What's wrong?
-Oh, Saaya.
Nothing, I'm fine.
-You're thinking
about Ledo leaving.
-No, it's not that at all.
-It's OK.
You should go with him
if that's what you want.
Leave with Flange.
OK?
You'd get to be with Melty, too.
-With Melty?
Of course, I'll miss
you both like crazy.
But it's better than
seeing you look like that.
Judging by your look, you'd
think the world was ending.
But maybe that's what it's like
for you since he's going away.
-There isn't anything
between us yet.
-Huh?
Then--
-I can't go.
I have to stay here.
-How come?
My brother needs Dr. Olton.
He's the only one
who can treat Bebel.
And I couldn't leave Bebel,
not for anything in this world.
-I see.
I'm glad then.
It's selfish, but I'd
be real lonely with you.
-Yeah, me, too.
-Got your hands full, huh?
-It's nothing I can't handle.
-OK, but you still need
a break now and then.
-I know that, but
I can't stop now.
I have to set an example.
I'm sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
-With Commander
Fairlock gone, I have
to keep it together
no matter what.
-Don't beat yourself up.
You're working hard.
You've done enough.
-If it were enough, they
wouldn't be leaving.
-Enough and perfect
aren't the same.
I've been there.
I know what it's like to
be suddenly running it all.
-Huh?
-Back when the Chief first
left me the salvage business,
I was eager to do
everything myself
to prove that I
could go it alone.
One day I found a huge treasure.
I was determined to show
off and be the big hero.
But a current swept
up my Yunburo,
and I ended up pinned
under my big find.
I thought I was going to die.
Afterwards, Pinion
laughed his ass off.
Called me a stupid little girl.
I was so eager to be
as good as the boys,
I forgot to work with them.
Trying to do it by
yourself is the same
as not trusting your friends.
Ask for help.
-But Commander Fairlock
did it all by himself.
-No, he didn't.
He relied on you.
Did you forget?
Ask yourself who
you can count on.
Think about who's
reliable, and who
you know you can trust
and let them help you.
-Like who?
-Like yourself.
You make sure everything I
salvage gets put to good use.
Someone I can work
with who only wants
what's best for the fleet.
That's who I'd want in charge.
-I'm back.
-Welcome home, Sis.
-Sorry I'm late.
I'll hurry up and
get dinner started.
-Hey, is it true that
Ledo was leaving?
-Oh, you know?
But how?
-The neighbors said Pinion
was telling everybody.
-He is.
Too bad, huh?
And here I though he and
I were getting along,
but I guess it was wrong.
-I wonder why he wants to
do something so dangerous?
-Seriously, that jerk.
-Amy.
-What happened to him?
Why doesn't he care
about anything?
When we were at the festival
together, he was laughing.
He was smiling.
Now, it seems like he's
more tormented than ever.
I know the boy I went to the
festival with is the real Ledo.
-There are some who
decided to stay.
Fleet Commander,
what about the boy?
How do you intend
to deal with him?
-I'm going to let you
decide what to do.
-He let me decide.
-Bebel.
-Are you really going?
-Correct.
I am.
-Do you have to?
Isn't there another way?
-There's not.
-But Ledo, is leaving
us what you really want?
-I have to protect humans
and protect Amy also.
-But she doesn't want
you to protect her.
She wants you to stay.
-Bebel, I want you have this.
-Huh?
But I thought this
one was special.
-A child who looked like me
made it and then gave it to me.
-He looked like you?
-It is possible that he
was my younger brother.
-Uh, Ledo.
-In the Galactic Alliance, one
who cannot fight cannot live.
The Hideauze are to blame.
They threaten the existence of
the human race and our enemies.
-But Ledo.
-Earth Hideauze, too.
If their domain expands, they
will wage war on more humans.
I'm certain of it.
-But whalesquid wouldn't.
-Yes, they would.
If Earth becomes
like the Alliance,
then you would be killed.
For Amy's sake, too, I cannot
let her lose someone that she
loves.
-You're wrong.
You're wrong, Ledo.
No one's going to die.
Don't go.
-I do not want Amy to suffer.
I must destroy the
Hideauze completely.
-Wait, please.
-Hmm?
-Hmm.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm late.
Thank you so very much.
Listen to me.
I have something
to say to you all.
-What?
-Fairlock has left us, And
he has left Gargantia to me.
My predecessor cared for
this fleet and its people
until he drew his last breath.
And I pledge to do
the very same thing.
The Commander dearly
loved this fleet
and gave his entire life to it.
I promise to do nothing less.
I will give you
everything that I have.
But that isn't enough.
I couldn't stop all those
people who wanted to leave.
They didn't believe
I could protect them,
and they were right.
By myself, I can't.
I need you.
I need you all to
lend me your strength.
If you want to
protect this fleet,
if you want to
protect Gargantia,
this fortress that we
live on, this place
which is our home, then please,
I really need your help.
-We're all old salts
who know the ropes.
We got your back, kid.
-That's right.
When you need someone to
count on, you can count on us.
-There's no point in crying
over the jerks who left.
Buck up and move on.
-With you at its
heart as Commander,
we'll build a new fleet
around you better than ever.
-Well done.
-You'll be fine.
-Everyone, I thank you.
-Oh.
-Hi.
What are you doing down there?
Come up.
-I am leaving soon.
-I know.
-Ledo, you're really going?
-Yes.
-OK, well then, I'll
hold on to this for you.
You can come back at
any time and get it.
-Thank you for everything.
May all the blessings of
the virtuous ways be yours.
-They've made up their minds.
Once that happened, there was
nothing we could do about it.
They're idiots.
Every last one of them.
[MUSIC - "SKY AND YOUR MESSAGE,"
CHOUCHO]