[music playing]
-This token can buy one meal.
And that paper slip can be
converted to 100 tokens,
correct?
-Rationed meal tickets
to the closest equivalent
to this concept that exists
in the Galactic Alliance.
-Too much.
-Hypothesis.
On this planet,
tickets maybe exchanged
for supplies other than meals.
LEDO: Oxygen is
so plentiful here
that it will never run out.
What other supplies
could be needed?
Could it be a mistake?
Is it possible I was
accidentally overpaid?
-Ledo.
-Hm?
Ah.
[giggling]
-Huh?
Ledo, what's the matter?
-I do not know how to use money.
-Huh?
That's right.
I think you told me before
there's no money in space.
Well, it's perfect timing.
Soon there'll be all
kinds of fun things
to spend the money on.
-Hm.
-Because it's festival time.
-Festival?
-Yep.
The fishermen catch
a whole lot of fish.
And afterwards, everyone
comes together to celebrate.
Oh, that reminds me.
You could try fishing.
We'll need extra men.
You'd use a yunburo
to catch the fish.
-Guild master, delivery for you.
[chuckle]
-Thanks.
-Direct from the
chief navigator,
the fleet's next course.
-Thank you.
-Also, I got a new recruit.
-Yea kid?
You really want to
be part of my crew?
-Yes.
I want to try to work
at fish catching.
-Finally gonna work
Mr. Lazy Bones?
-So what happened to that
flying yunburo of yours?
-I do not need him.
I will do the work.
CHAMBER: Objection repeated.
Activity inefficient.
-That's a swirling galaxy.
CHAMBER: It appears to be
formed by nano machines
called light bugs, remnants
of the former civilization.
[gasp]
FISHING GUILD MASTER: Due
to the ocean's currents,
when two sea galaxies intersect,
sometimes a ring gets formed.
When that happens, the
fish can't get out.
It makes a perfect honey hole.
Now let's go catch some fish.
[opening theme song]
[music playing]
FISHING GUILD MASTER: Can
you understand the controls?
-The system is basic.
No problem.
-That's great kid.
Try not to break it.
Test it out.
Try moving the arms.
-I understand operation system.
Where is information support?
FISHING GUILD MASTER:
The hell is that?
LEDO: Computer-based
tactical situation analysis.
-We ain't got that.
Just use your eyes.
LEDO: Roger
[grunt]
[panting]
-Ah.
-Good.
Just like that.
Now move to the swirling galaxy.
But listen, go quietly and don't
open up a hole in the ring.
-Set axis.
Map position.
Chamber respond.
FISHING GUILD MASTER (ON
COMMS): What the hell
are you doing, kid?
Get your bearings.
-Info support.
-You need to swim.
Just relax and you'll float.
-But I cannot swim.
-Ledo!
FISHING GUILD MASTER:
For crying out loud.
If he didn't know how swim,
why didn't he tell me?
LEDO: I did not know machines
here cannot understand voice
commands.
-Also there's no
oceans in space, right?
Least you tried.
Come on.
Let's go have lunch.
-One maiden meal set
and one seaweed bread.
-Thank you very much.
Ledo, are you sure that seaweed
bread is enough for you?
There's lots of tasty
food you can try.
-It is sufficient.
-Aw.
Being a soldier is tough.
Come on.
Cheer up.
You gave it your
best shot, right?
I make mistakes all the time.
Everybody does.
[chuckle] You're
too serious, Ledo.
You gotta relax more.
-What does one do to relax?
-Oh.
You just gotta let loose
and have a little fun, like
at the festival later.
But before we do
that, let's dig in!
-Let's dig in
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
It is good.
-Oh, really?
I've got an Idea.
If you like it, try
showing it a little.
-Try showing it?
How do I do that?
-Hey.
You're not even changed yet?
-Oh, I forgot.
-Hurry up.
If you're late then all
the hot guys will be taken.
Wait, one's here.
-Yep.
He is.
-Keeping him for
yourself, are you?
-Sorry, Ledo.
I promise we'll go to
the festival later, OK?
-Uh, sure.
SAAYA: Hurry up.
Let's go.
AMY: Bye Ledo.
CHAMBER: Proposal.
If the objective is to capture
fish, it is possible for me
to do it alone.
Ensign Ledo may remain
in standby mode.
-Do as you wish.
-So you brought your own
yunburo this time, huh.
-Negative the first.
This machine is not a yunburo.
Designation, Machine
Caliber K6821.
Request to join
fishing objective.
-OK.
-Negative the second.
My pilot, Ensign Ledo,
is not currently present.
What?
The kid ain't in there?
-Proceeding to execute
fishing objective
by capturing marine life.
-Hey.
Take a net.
[blowing]
-Yo, Ledo.
Nice work today.
You did a great job at sinking.
-No problem.
Chamber is working in my place.
-Aw.
Don't sulk like that.
Come on, hang out
with me for a while.
So, I hear you don't know
how to spend your money.
Let me show you then.
And just for today, I'll
even pick up the tab.
We'll call this lesson one.
Hey waitress, over here!
So what will it be?
-Seaweed bread.
-Huh?
Waitress, two special
dinners with everything.
-Got it.
Two special dinners
coming right up.
-Tell me kid, what's your deal?
You home sick?
You miss space?
-I have no map.
Going back is not possible.
-Well, I guess
you're stuck then.
What about life here?
You like it?
-Not bad.
But, people are distant.
-Of course they are, you nut.
You don't need anything
but seaweed bread.
-People do not
like seaweed bread?
-Not that.
People can't see
who you really are.
-They cannot see me?
[cheering]
-Woohoohoo.
Look, what do you want?
You must be interested
in something.
-I want to return to the
Alliance battlefront.
-No.
Not that soldier boy.
I mean something
here on this ship.
LEDO: I do not know.
[sigh]
-How's a guy supposed to be
trusted when he doesn't even
know what the heck he wants?
-It's good.
-Why not team up
with me and salvage.
-Salvage.
Is that work?
Oh, yeah!
With that super
tin can of yours,
we can score some big stuff.
-But more money is too much.
-Trust me kid, it
won't be too much.
Besides, when you
make more money,
you can eat more tasty things
or get yourself a nice boat.
Spend it.
Learn what you like.
Find out what your
heart desires.
-What my heart, desires.
-Hm.
-Not so fast, Bub.
No way you're stealing the kid.
-Stealing what?
If he's gonna team up with
anyone, it's going to be me.
I can train you to be a
first-class salvager kid.
What do you say?
-Salvager.
I do not understand.
-I'll teach you.
It's real easy to pick up.
If there's ever anything
you can't do, ask me how
and I'll tell you.
Or just watch me
and do what I do.
Piece of cake.
-Don't listen to Bellows kid.
Stick with me and I'll get
the best food in the fleet.
-I can teach you to
read tides and currents.
You're smart so you'll
pick it up quickly.
Booze kid.
All you can drink.
-Yeah, sure.
But don't you want
to learn how to swim.
-I'll get you all the
ass you can handle.
-Pinion!
That's sleazy.
Don't be such a creep.
-Oh shut up turtle shell ass.
-Who are you calling
turtle shell ass?
You can't even swim.
PINION: I can swim.
I just can't dive.
-Sorry it took so long.
Thanks for your patience.
Here's your main dish.
-Oh, yeah.
The main event.
-What is it?
-Hideauze!
[grunt]
[gasp]
[cheering]
[panting]
-Whoa.
Calm down.
What's wrong?
-Hideauze.
Enemy of humans.
Objective, destroy.
-That's just an octopus, kid.
It's good.
-Mm If this little
thing freaks you out,
you don't ever want to
run into a whale-squid.
You might lose it
completely and pass out.
-Octopus?
It's good?
[beeping]
CHAMBER: Requesting
support from pilot.
Ensign Ledo, please respond.
[music playing]
[startled]
-Beginning capture.
Gravity waver formation, fire.
Capture complete.
-Both you and Ledo.
What the hell are
you thinking, eh?
-Nutritionally, there is
no difference in its value.
-That's not the point.
-Correct responsible unknown.
Ensign Ledo, request
pilot support
to remedy current situation.
-Nice job.
There all fish paste.
[sigh]
[chuckle]
-This time, use a net.
Watch the guys who know
what they're doin'.
-Chamber, use the
largest net there is.
Also, work together with
the other unit yunburos.
-Great job kid.
-See.
-When did you suddenly
start believing in Ledo?
-Ah.
That was yummy.
I'm totally stuffed.
[flute playing]
-Huh?
[grace screeching]
-Chamber, assessment.
-Ah.
CHAMBER: Measuring energy
signatures in the vicinity.
Threat level minimal.
-Nothing to worry about.
See.
Look.
-Ah.
[gasp]
[gasps]
-What is that?
What's happening?
-Those are veils of light.
They form when a swirling
galaxy comes apart.
-Ah.
[gasp]
-Here.
You should practice more.
-Practice the flute?
Like Amy practice dancing?
-Ah.
[chuckle]
-I want to see Amy dance.
-OK.
As thanks for earlier.
-As thanks?
-Bebel, I brought you a present.
-Welcome home Amy.
-Hello.
-Hi, Doctor Oldham.
Did you two have fun
while I was gone?
BEBEL: Ledo.
-I brought a gift.
[vibrating]
-Thanks Ledo.
It's great.
-With money, I can get
things for others, presents
and good food to eat.
-The pay you received
is not just a reward.
It signifies that you
gave aid and support.
-I gave aid and support?
So that is working.
I was invited to
do some more work.
-Doing what?
-Salvage work with
Chamber down below.
-Wow.
How cool.
LEDO: It will be cold?
-I mean how exciting to get to
see all the things down there.
You can find all sorts
of great treasure
and see what the
Earth used to be like.
-I want to work on salvage.
[sigh]
-You're a big help Ledo.
I'm glad you're here.
I really thought
Pinion had talked you
into partnering with him.
-I want you to teach me Bellows
and to learn much from you.
BELLOWS: Thanks.
But so long as you have
that high-tech yunburo,
you'll forget it all.
Nothing I'd tell you
will stick for long.
-I wish to learn.
I will remember.
FEMALE YUNBURO PILOT: Yes!
Looks like another
treasure trove.
-Be gentle with it.
It's valuable.
[chuckle]
[alarm sounding]
-Ah.
[scream]
-Enemy signature identified.
Interceptor type.
LEDO: Confirm identification.
-Characteristic response
analysis complete.
Probability 99.97%
subject is Hideauze.
-Engage.
Annihilate the Hideauze.
CHAMBER: Roger.
[ending theme song]