-Bellows.
I have a delivery for you.
-OK, thanks.
Good work, Amy.
-Thank you.
-You seem a bit cheerier.
-Well, I can't go on
being sad forever.
It looks like Flange
and the others
are staying in the Sea of Mist.
The Milky Way curves
that direction.
Our current course will
take us right by them.
Maybe we can check up on them.
-I just hope that Pinion hasn't
made a complete mess of things.
-As long as everyone's
safe, nothing else matters.
Bye.
-Hey, what is that?
-Hmm?
-That's huge.
Don't tell me they're pirates.
-Fleet Commander,
sound the alarm.
I want all ships in the
fleet to be on highest alert.
-Let's err on the
side of caution.
Order Pinion to--
No, I'll do it.
-Ledo.
-Commander Kugel.
Commander, is that really you?
-Long time, no see.
But I'm glad you're
alive and well.
-You, too, Commander.
I picked up the distress signal
your Machine Caliber sent out,
but I was on the other
side of the planet
and unable to get to you.
-You should have sent a signal.
I would have come
to you, Commander.
-It was necessary to
maintain radio silence.
Can you come here
and join me, Ensign?
-Yes.
I mean, yes, sir.
Ensign Ledo ready
to rejoin command.
-What is that?
-I've never seen
pilots that big.
-This is bad, very bad.
-Maybe we'd be better
off running away.
-You want us to runaway?
Run where?
Don't worry, OK?
We've got the cannon, plus
the tin can's with us.
Let's fire a shot off the
port bow to say hello.
-Uh.
-Aye.
-Television angle six.
-Ready to fire on command.
-Fire!
-Firing!
-Heh, heh.
Take that.
Hmm?
What the--
-What was that?
-That looked like
a lightning bolt.
-What the hell do you think
you're doing to my treasure?
What's that?
A tin can?
No, it's different.
Hey, Ledo.
Ledo, where are you?
-This is Ensign Ledo.
I'm returning to active duty
at the Galactic Alliance
Army of Humankind.
-What?
Ledo, what the hell
are you talking about?
Ledo, take 10.
[MUSIC - "THIS WORLD HAS
BEEN WAITING FOR US," MINORI CHIHARA]
-Guide signal received.
Preparing to land.
-What are they doing?
-Unknown.
Hypothesis.
Collective action indicates
military proficiency.
You mean these people are
living under military command?
-Welcome, envoy from the sky.
Giant Clad and Lightning.
We are humbled to
be in your presence.
In the name of Providence, we
wish you peace and prosperity.
-What is she talking about?
-Speculation.
She is using an
idiomatic expression
to refer to a Machine
Caliber and pilot.
-Where is Commander Kugel?
Take me to him.
-This way, please.
Please enter.
The Commander will be
with you in a moment.
-Apologies for the holograph.
-Commander Kugel.
I never imagined I'd see you
again, alive and well, no less.
-I may be alive, but
I have not been well.
I have a disease and must
remain in my sterile cockpit.
How is your health?
-I haven't been ill.
-I see.
You're lucky.
Issuing orders from
here hasn't been easy.
-I can imagine.
-It won't be so hard
now that you're here.
Are you willing to
follow my command again?
-Of course, I'll follow
you Commander Chamber
K6821 to Striker
X3752, please respond.
Request for all information
on Commander Kugel's disease.
Striker X3752 to Chamber
K6821, request granted.
Transmitting information
on specified disease now.
-Wow, it looks like
we're surrounded.
This doesn't look too good.
-We've got the treasure.
We'll be fine.
-You sure about that?
-Don't panic.
If things get bad, we've
still got the tin can.
-Didn't it leave a
little while ago?
-Uh.
-We're screwed.
-OK, calm down.
They might not want to kill us.
We don't even know
what they want.
-They want all the treasure
we brought up you big moron.
-How would they know about it?
-Because you broadcast it.
Any bright ideas?
-Well, I, uh--
-Why are you standing around?
-Stay out of this old man.
-Look around at what's going on.
Everyone returned your
posts immediately.
-Thanks for bailing me out.
I heard the owner of that weapon
is Ledo's friend another space
man who fell to Earth.
-Yeah.
-Apparently this planet has
had more than one visitor
from the sky.
The question is now
that he, too, is here,
what does this person
intend to do with us?
-Urgent delivery.
We just received a message
addressed to the fleet.
-Flange, here.
Go ahead.
MESSENGER ON RADIO:
They're demanding
to see a representative
from our fleet.
-What do they want?
MESSENGER ON RADIO:
They didn't say.
-They must want the relics.
I'll go.
-Hold on a second.
I'm the reason
that they're here.
I should talk to them.
-Don't be ridiculous.
You're not qualified to conduct
diplomatic negotiations.
MESSENGER ON RADIO:
Well, actually,
they specifically requested
that Pinion of the Sea of Mist
be the representative.
-See?
My time to shine.
-Don't be stupid.
But Flange, if you become
their hostage, then
who's going to keep
the fleet together?
-Good point.
Still--
-Don't worry about me.
No one's going to want
to follow me after this.
Besides, I got us
into this mess.
I should be the
one to get us out.
If I can't, I'm just
getting what I deserve.
-Very well.
Just be careful at every step.
-Sure thing.
Well, I guess I'm off then.
-Pinion.
-Huh?
Melty?
-They said to wait.
They're going to send
a boat over for you.
-Oh, really?
-I got us into this mess.
No one's going to want
to follow me anymore.
-Oh, shut up.
-You're wrong, you know.
People won't give up on you.
-Oh, yeah?
-You've always been
a screw-up, Pinion,
but everyone knows that.
They're not going
to count you out.
-Thanks for the pep talk.
-Oh, look.
What?
No way.
-It couldn't be.
The Surfing Monster.
-I'm here to escort
Pinion of the Sea Mist.
That's you, isn't it?
-Yeah, and I gotta tell you.
I never thought I'd get to meet
the great pirate Lukkage here.
-Don't be so formal.
Just call me Lukkage.
However--
-Huh?
-For now, I'd watch my tongue
if I were you, understand?
-OK.
Huh?
Everybody looks depressed.
Aren't they getting
enough to eat around here?
-The weak exist to
serve the strong.
That is divine Providence
apparently, or so I'm told.
-So is that their
god over there?
-That is a lightning giant.
Supposedly they're divine envoys
that deliver holy judgment.
-Even as the humans
of this planet
are blessed was an environment
of non-extreme temperatures
and breathable air, they
are overrun with Hideauze.
It is, therefore, our duty
to teach these humans how
to fight, and enlighten
them as to the dignity
of the human race.
-Well, about that, Commander.
The Hideauze, Commander,
they are human.
-You mean were human.
-Huh?
Commander Kugel, you
knew the truth all along?
Amongst the command higher-ups,
it was tacitly understood.
But for front line
soldiers in the field,
the information was
deemed unnecessary.
-Unnecessary?
The Hideauze lived by
instinct and reproduced
however they desired.
They are not human beings.
-Yes, sir.
-The weak serve and
support the strong.
And the strong, in
turn, protect the weak.
Both groups know their
roles in society.
They understand their place.
This rationale is
what makes us humans.
-That may be true, sir, but--
-Since my arrival, I've
brought order to this fleet.
As a result of the
system I put in place,
there's been a
marked improvement
in the level of citizens'
happiness across the board.
-Request.
Please clarify the definition
of happiness in this context.
According to Galactic
Alliance, philosophy,
happiness is the
realization of circumstance
in which individuals
service to the entire group
makes the cost benefit
ratio most efficient.
Therefore, happiness is
commensurate with the degree
of command stability.
Definition and
conclusion are valid.
-Is that true?
-Now, Ledo, how would you like
to help me change this world?
-Sit over there.
Ah, but nobody's here.
Hmm?
What the hell is it?
Huh, this thing is cool.
This goes like this.
And that one here.
And voila.
-Greetings, Pinion
of the Sea of Mist.
I bid you welcome as a
most distinguished guest.
-What the hell?
A com device.
The humans remaining
on Earth require
improvement in
technical proficiency.
This was a test to measure
your mechanical engineering
capabilities and
problem solving skills.
Conclusion.
You are proficient
in these areas.
-I've heard that fancy
pants way of talking before.
You wouldn't, by chance, be
a relative of the tin can?
I am a pilot support
enlightenment interface system.
Striker X3752.
-And what does the
all powerful Striker
want with someone like me?
-Your ability to
repair weapons that
have been recovered from the
ocean floor is most admirable.
However you only
restore basic functions
due to insufficient knowledge
of operating principles.
-Hey, my fault,
like I'm supposed
to know how machines were
put together way back when?
-I can provide you with
information regarding
construction of these ancient
devices, including schematics.
-No way.
With your aptitude, you
need not limit yourself
to repairing weapons.
You will be capable of designing
and producing new weapons
as well.
You're giving me
way too much credit.
-Incorrect self-assessment.
You are capable
of such learning.
It is my request that you become
an engineering officer, Pinion
of the Sea of Mist.
-An officer?
I ain't no soldier boy.
Wait a sec.
What about my fleet?
Can you guarantee its safety?
Your fleet's humans
are a valid resource.
Rest assured they
will not be wasted.
-Not wasted?
Never mind.
Promise everyone stays safe
and I'll do what you want.
-I have high hopes
for your development.
-Huh?
Whoa.
Hmm?
-If you would before you die.
Do as you're told, and
it will go quickly.
-Fine, but do you have to
act so stuck up about it?
Hey.
-If you desire to
be finished quickly,
I suggest you hold still.
-Friends, this is Pinion
of the Sea of Mist.
Commitment and cooperation
are at the heart
of what makes
human beings human.
By joining the Flange and
Kugel fleets together,
you have the chance to attain
peace and greater prosperity
for all citizens.
This is the wisest
course of action
for all humans concerned.
It is what it says.
-It's a polite demand
for our surrender.
-Fleet Commander.
-I know.
We must surrender.
There's no choice.
-Am I addressing Fleet
Commander Flange?
-Indeed, you are.
-We respect you for this
choice, Fleet Commander.
It was wise.
-I would like to believe
it was the right one.
What do you intend
to do with all of us?
-I can guess.
These guys want to
split up our fleet.
-Is that true?
-Each of your ships will
be requisitioned separately
according to its use.
-I'm afraid that
will be a problem.
This fleet is like a family.
It won't work unless
we are all together.
-From this day forward,
you will all be of service
and work together in
an even bigger family.
-But we--
-Those who comply with the
divine shall be blessed.
However, those who
go against that will
shall be crushed by
the hammer of god.
-Understood.
-Kneel then, Fleet
Commander, so that you
may receive the benediction.
I declare the a servant of
Kugel in the blessed name
of divine Providence.
You shall henceforth devote
yourself body and soul
to the furtherance
of the great cause.
-This place is totally different
from what I saw before.
The guys who live here must
be making the big bucks.
-This fleet has no
form of currency.
-No money?
How does that work?
-The fleet issues appropriate
rations in accordance
with the duties one performs.
It's an extremely fair
way of doing things.
-Oh, it's fair, huh?
-This is your residential area.
I'll show you to
your side quarters.
-Huh?
What's with them?
Where's my crew?
-Right about now, each
part of your fleet
should be getting
requisitioned and reassigned.
-Each part?
-Yes.
You didn't really
think this fleet would
allow the consolidation of the
potential insurgency, did you?
-Why'd you bring
us in if you were
worried about
rebellion breaking out?
-Take my advice.
You're better off not having
any contact with your friends
right now.
Trust me.
-Fine then.
-Virus data analysis complete.
Running physical evaluation
on Ensign Ledo now.
Evaluation complete.
No abnormalities detected.
-All this time, the Commander's
been leading this huge fleet
while confined to
such a crap space.
I couldn't do that.
-Hypothesis.
Commander Kugel has
withdrawn into his cockpit
because he wishes to
exist as a symbol.
He desires to instill both
awe and fear in all those
around him.
Speculation.
Stronger and more
overarching leadership
is possible because
of this tactic.
-So it's scarier if he
can't be seen, right?
Still, is it a good idea
to rule through terror
and superstition?
-Coping with fear is one of
the fundamental behaviors
of all living things.
A show of strength
can cause one's enemy
to be afraid while
at the same time
inspire feelings of safety
and obedience in those one
is protecting.
- I suppose that's true.
-Conclusion.
As a countermeasure
against a powerful enemy,
such as the Hideauze,
a display of force
is a valid means to
optimize leadership.
It mobilizes
individuals collectively
and is connected
to the maintenance
of a high degree of
community functionality.
In addition--
-I've heard enough.
Maybe I-- maybe I shouldn't
have left this cockpit either.
-Welcome back, Mistress,
I hope all went well.
Thanks for your effort.
Mean It's good to be home.
-I was wondering what the
man called, Pinion, was like.
-He knows his way around.
-Oh.
-Will you get rid of him then?
-It's still early for that.
In his own way, he
does seem capable.
But honestly, I'm getting
bored with all this free time
on my hands.
-Awakening process complete.
Incoming communication
from Commander Kugel.
-How are you feeling?
-I am well.
-I require your assistance
for an urgent matter.
-Is it the Hideauze?
-No.
It is a new awareness
program for the inhabitants
of this planet.
-I am at your command, sir.
-I like that answer.
With your arrival, we now
have two Machine Calibers
at our disposal.
So I'd like to use this chance
to carry out a major awareness
strategy I've had in mind.
This is the target.
-Ah.
That's-- that's Gargantia.
[MUSIC - "SKY AND YOUR MESSAGE,"
CHOUCHO]