[music playing]
-Hm?
-What happened out there?
Is Bellows OK?
And the pirates?
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
There were no casualties
among Gargantia personnel.
The enemy force
has been destroyed.
-They've been destroyed?
You mean you killed
all the pirates?
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
Affirmative.
The enemy threat has
been neutralized.
-[gasps] Ledo, you idiot!
-What's going on?
[theme music]
FAIRLOCK (ON RADIO): The pirate
fleet was completely destroyed.
BELLOWS: Not just their fleet.
All of the thugs who boarded
my boat were wiped out, too.
FAIRLOCK (ON RADIO):
Now, that there's
been bloodshed, I'm certain
that they'll return for revenge.
-Those two made a real
mess of things for us.
-Fleet Commander, we need
to get rid of that boy
as soon as humanly possible.
-Perhaps we should hand
him over to the pirates.
-Do you really believe
that would placate them?
-Wait a minute!
What will we do if he ends up
teaming up with the pirates?
-What would you
have us do, then?
-Like I've been saying, keep
the Yunoboro and lose the kid.
FAIRLOCK (ON RADIO):
I believe that what
we need to do right now
is determine the pirates'
movements and formulate
our counteroffensive.
We can decide on how to
deal with the boy later.
AMY: I never imagined
something like this happening.
What he said about fighting a
war in outer space was true.
Maybe I shouldn't have opened
my big mouth about the pirates.
[sighs]
-I've been looking for
you all over the place.
-Huh?
-I've got a little
favor to ask of you.
-Uhh.
LEDO: Looks like they
really despise me now.
CHAMBER: Their response
defies all rational analysis.
-I thought it would be the first
step towards a negotiation.
CHAMBER: Airborne
object overhead.
-Uh.
-It's Amy and Bellows.
Lower your guns.
-Look.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Are you mad?
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER: No,
there is no need for apologies.
-Really?
That's good.
-My name is Bellows.
I wanted to talk
to you about today.
Here's a gift.
CHAMBER: It seems
she would like you
to consume the animal carcass.
-Not again.
-Ledo, that's your name, right?
Why did you kill
all of the pirates?
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
Does eliminating the enemy
necessitate a reason?
-I don't know how
things are in space,
but around here,
taking a life is
something that
must be justified.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS
INTERPRETER: How is it
not an issue if you kill a
living organism for food?
-Well, it certainly is
true that we kill animals
in order to eat.
But we only kill enough to
provide our fleet the food
that we all need to survive.
We don't take lives needlessly.
Furthermore, the
pirates were human.
Same as us.
You just can't go around
lightly taking lives.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER: If it is
forbidden to shed human blood--
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
--why do you possess weapons?
-Because if someone feels
like it, they could kill you.
Pirates use the
threat of death to try
to get people to
do what they want.
And so we've taken the
attitude that we're not
going to just roll
over and die for that.
I suppose you could say that
making a display of arms
to each other is a kind
of negotiation in itself.
We have an old saying,
it goes like this.
Give fresh water to the
one who catches the fish.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER: Are
those words a recommendation
for humans to aid each other?
-That's right.
Because we can't
survive unless everyone
works to do their part.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
But the pirates
do not seem to
adhere to that rule.
BELLOWS: That's right.
They don't.
And of course, we believe
that they're wrong,
so we resist them.
We're not letting
any pirates take
our lives or our possessions.
But you see, our message
to them by resisting
is that there is no
profit in attacking us.
We think it's enough to just
communicate that to them.
But when you add death to the
mix, it changes everything.
In order to fully regain their
position as the aggressors,
they are left with no choice
but to retaliate and spill
more blood.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER: I
understand the situation.
-I'm glad.
-Anyway, no matter
what people say,
we need your power to equalize
our fight against the pirates.
This is a communication device.
Eventually, I want you to use
it to speak to the others.
Even if things didn't end up as
they should have, you saved me.
This food is my thanks for that.
See ya!
-Hey, Ledo, I was thinking
that if you don't have a place
to go, why not stay here?
I'm sure that we can find a
way to make things work out
smoothly.
-She wants me to live here.
Impossible.
CHAMBER: Shall I refuse?
-No.
Be noncommittal.
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER:
I will consider it.
-Wow, you will?
You really will
consider staying here?
Well, I should get back now.
Ledo, thank you for
protecting Bellows's ship.
I'm grateful.
Goodbye.
I mean it!
Thank you!
-Such unusual words.
-I understand the situation.
You can leave now.
That Gargantia fleet has
always been quite the pain.
But I didn't think they'd
dare mess with us like this.
-Hey, Captain, that flying
Yunoboro they got really
worries me.
-Maroki.
Making a fuss over
a little incident
like that only serves
to make them cockier.
-Uh, aye, aye.
-And what happens to those
who dare to get cocky with us?
-[whimpers]
-No matter what secret
weapon they may have,
they are no match for me.
MAN: Captain,
fleet at 3 o'clock.
And there's a ton of ships.
-What?
It's them.
It's the pirates!
MAN: Commander Warren,
incoming message
from the cargo ship "Etui."
They've got a large pirate
fleet approaching them.
-They're here.
-They're requesting
permission to interlock
with our fleet for
emergency shelter.
-He reported that there
are at least 30 ships
in the pirate fleet
that's approaching.
-They've got 30 ships!
That's almost all of the
pirates in this area.
-Moreover, he said they
saw a lobster insignia
in some of the ships.
-That's the great
pirate Lukkage.
-What's their course?
-They were spotted
right around here.
At the time, it looked like they
were headed east by southeast.
It's safe to say their
objective is our fleet.
-They'll be on top
of us by nightfall.
Let's change course.
-That's useless.
We don't have the
speed to get away.
-But, sir, we're talking
about 30 pirate ships
loaded to the gills
with firepower.
Even including the
small patrol boats,
our escort fleet
has just 15 ships.
There's no way they
could protect us.
-What about trying to
negotiate with them?
-They're coming because
they want revenge.
Only bloodshed
will appease them.
-Fleet commander, why don't we
just ask that kid to help us?
-Huh?
-What are you saying?
-Can you hear me, Ledo?
LEDO (ON RADIO): Do
you require assistance?
-The pirates are
heading this way.
We'll have to tangle with
them by this evening.
LEDO (ON RADIO): I have
already acquired targeting data
on the approaching fleet.
I am prepared to assist you.
Is that your wish?
-Fleet Commander, won't
you try talking to him?
-Ridiculous!
We're in this situation
because of him!
-Regardless!
If we can use that Yunoboro,
it will give us the advantage.
-Do it, Ridget.
-Yes, sir.
RIDGET (ON RADIO):
This is Ridget.
I'll speak to you on behalf of
the fleet commander, all right?
-No objections.
RIDGET (ON RADIO):
Let me confirm.
You say that you'll help
us against the pirates.
But do you understand
that it's your fault
we're in this
dangerous situation.
LEDO (ON RADIO): Yes, I
understand the circumstances.
And I apologize for
killing the pirates.
-Then I have a question.
With your weaponry,
it's possible
that you could destroy us
if you wanted to, correct?
LEDO (ON RADIO): Affirmative.
This machine alone can
annihilate this entire fleet.
-Then I'm very curious
as to why you would even
offer to help defend
weaklings like us.
LEDO (ON RADIO): I
desire an arrangement.
RIDGET (ON RADIO):
An arrangement?
-Bellows told me
that your people
say "Give fresh water to the
one who catches the fish."
She also informed
me that the pirates
don't abide by the
spirit of those words.
That's why I decided it would
be more beneficial to make
an arrangement with you
than with the pirates.
RIDGET (ON RADIO):
[non-english speech]
-I wish to base myself here.
I'll need aid to do so.
-Fleet Commander, I think
it's in our best interest
that we accept the deal
the boy has just proposed.
-You-- you're not serious?
-I agree with Ridget.
We mustn't neglect
to give fresh water
to the one who catches the fish.
-Hm.
-Confirmation requested.
The mission of this machine
is only to divert the pirates.
Is that correct?
-Yes.
All you have to do is
get their attention.
Please restrain yourself
from excessive attacks.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER AS INTERPRETER: I
understand your requirements.
If at all possible,
I will take care
not to cause human casualties.
-Oh!
Whoa!
CHAMBER: Do not enter the
cockpit without permission.
-[grunts]
What the hell was that
for, you tin bastard?
MAN 1: Unbelievable!
We're actually entrusting the
defense of our entire fleet
to that strange kid
and his machine?
MAN 2: It's the fleet
commander's decision.
I can understand why he made it.
-I know.
But even so.
[ship horn blowing]
-Maroki, when should we expect
a welcome from Gargantia?
-[snickers] Soon, I'm sure.
Once they notice us.
-On a night as
dark as this, they
might even have a chance
of winning this battle.
-You're joking, right?
There's nobody in the
world who could even
hope to defeat us
in a night battle.
-Oh, really, is that so?
[laughter]
Uh, what's going on?
LEDO: Pirate fleet confirmed.
Commencing battle engagement.
-Up there!
Shoot it down!
-All ships.
Cannons at the ready.
All right.
All ships, open fire!
-Don't tell me they beat us to
the punch in a night battle.
-What the hell is that Yunoboro?
It's flying all over!
-Well, don't just stand there.
Begin the counterattack!
-All ships, target the
enemy fleet and fire!
-The "Shezzy" and
"Nephalim" are hit.
The "Shezzy" is too
damaged to continue.
-Have it retreat.
Order all the other ships, too.
CREW: The "Marcus" is hit.
-Just keep firing.
We've got to win!
CHAMBER: Even more allied
ships have been hit.
Estimate.
It's 17 minutes.
The allied force will no longer
be able to continue fighting.
-No choice, then.
We're going to have
to enter the battle.
Avoid human casualties and
disable the enemy's firepower
and mobility.
CHAMBER: Roger.
No signs of life.
No human casualties.
-Good.
PIRATE: It's coming this way!
[men yelling]
-The "Crocodile" is on fire!
CREW: The "Gretch"
is reversing course.
Are they trying to run away?
-I think by now, everyone
should have arrived.
We had better get ready as well.
SLAVES: Aye, sir.
-[snickers]
CREW: Something's over there!
CAPTAIN: Light it up!
-We're attacked!
-Citizens, evacuate
to starboard!
-Fire!
-Hoover, Yunoboros on, too!
We're under attack!
CHAMBER: Warning.
Gargantia is being invaded
by armored enemy troops.
-When did they get here?
-You are not the only
one fighting this battle
with a special Yunoboroid.
-The empress is on the attack!
-I haven't Empress Lukkage's
lobster in a really long time!
-The surfing lobster.
It's heading straight
for Gargantia.
-Call nearby heavy Yunoboros.
Fire on the lobster!
She's broken through!
Damn it!
-[snickers]
[grunts]
-What's happening?
-Rockets just crashed
into the superstructure!
-She what?
She's climbing!
-Deploy the garrison
to superstructure 1.
-Everyone, evacuate!
I'm the one that Lukkage wants.
-Fleet Commander, no.
LUKKAGE: I wonder where
Fleet Commander Fairlock is.
I want to crush him
like a tiny bug.
Ugh.
My, my, suddenly embracing
a lady from behind, eh?
But not too worry, I kind
of like aggressive men.
-Uh!
What is she trying to do?
-Gung ho!
-Semper fidelis.
BOTH: Sorry to keep you waiting!
LUKKAGE: It seems you're good
at flying around in the sky.
But how do you think
you'll do in water?
-Wha-- ugh!
-I don't believe this!
LUKKAGE: Uh, this can't be!
CHAMBER: Warning to
the invading enemy.
Surrender immediately.
-Surrender?
Who do you think I am?
-It's no use fighting.
CHAMBER: Repeat.
Surrender.
[women shriek]
CHAMBER: The safety of your
lives will be guaranteed.
-What a bore!
No matter how many times
you say it, I'll-- ugh!
CHAMBER: Surrender.
Surrender.
Surrender immediately.
Repeat.
Surrender.
-You can just go to hell!
I'll never surrender.
Even if it kills me!
-Oh, crap!
Pull out!
-Yeah!
-Wait for me!
[cheers]
-He did it.
That kid did it.
MEN: Thank you!
Thank you!
[cheers]
-They all keep saying that word.
-It is a phrase
denoting gratitude.
-Gratitude.
Oh.
-Yes, I see.
He did quite well.
-Fleet Commander,
what about the boy?
How do you intend
to deal with him?
-I-- I just wonder what
Chevron would have done.
-Uh, my father?
-I'm going to let you
decide what to do.
AMY: Good job!
I'll cook you a
special dinner tonight.
-Uh, Tuh-- thanguh-- thanguh--
-Hm?
-Thank you, Amy.
[music playing]