NARRATOR: The long age of
drifting finally came to an end
and what remained of humanity
obtained a new home deep
in the wide reaches
of the galaxy.
We named it Avalon,
the beautiful paradise.
Behold, our paradise built
from our enduring spirit
and scientific prowess.
This is your homeland,
noble brothers.
All 470 million of its citizens
hail your unbending dedication.
They have engraved your
names on to their hearts
as honored soldiers.
All hail the Galactic
Alliance of humankind,
and it's brilliant
eternal future,
for it is here, in this place,
humanity's endless challenge
begins.
But, brothers, you must
never allow yourselves
to forget that a
terrible merciless,
evil lurks deep in the depths
of this cold cruel universe.
We must dedicate
ourselves to stopping
the ever present threat
of the Hideauze, who
try to hinder our
onward journey.
We must not allow these
lower lifeforms to hold back
humanity's race to the future.
Heroes, gather your
courage in this time
of our greatest trial.
Do not forget the
countless lives
lost in sacrifice nor
our future comrades
still facing the
shadow of grave danger.
CHAMBER: CC REM
education for all crew.
Pilot of unit number
K6821, Ensign Ledo,
is to awaken immediately.
Measuring brain waves,
basic rhythms normal,
blood lactate levels normal,
adrenaline output level normal,
awakening process complete.
-Where's the enemy?
-Attention, Kugel squad, REM
enlightenment time is now over.
I trust everyone is
fully awake and alert.
-We haven't started yet.
-At 300 seconds, the
entire battle fleet
will be entering the Argos
sphere of the wormhole.
We'll be swinging
out to a position
right next to a Hideauze's nest.
This is to be a surprise
attack using everything
the Alliance has
to throw at them.
This is our only chance.
Failure is not an option.
CHAMBER: Notice,
as of this moment,
your time spent in
military service
has exceeded 145,000 hours.
Ensign Ledo, should you
survive this operation,
once it is complete, you will
be given limited citizenship
privileges and the right to
visit Avalon for four weeks.
-Oh, really?
Is that so?
CHAMBER: No change
in adrenaline levels.
Your response fails to
meet expected parameters.
-Avalon, huh?
I did want to see it
with my own eyes one day,
but now that I have the
chance, I'm not so sure.
What is a homeland anyway?
CHAMBER: A place where
the rights of citizens
are guaranteed.
You will be granted full
rights to sleep, eat, drink,
and reproduce
however you see fit.
-I don't know.
Is that supposed
to be a good thing?
CHAMBER: You have proven to be
superior example of humanity,
resourceful, fit to
survive and reproduce.
This is an honor,
an accomplishment
to be celebrated.
-Does it make you
happy, Chamber?
CHAMBER: That is irrelevant.
I am a pilot support
enlightenment interface system.
I accomplish my
purpose in programming
by ensuring that you
achieve further success.
-I appreciate it, Chamber.
You do work hard.
I'll give you that.
-That's enough unnecessary
chatter, Ensign Ledo.
You should focus on
the task at hand.
-Roger, Commander Kugel.
-All units prepare for shock.
As soon as the telemothy
swing is complete,
we launch the attack.
Good luck and good hunting.
All ships, prepare for swing.
Initiating telemothy swing.
Swing in.
The fleet has successfully
passed through the wormhole.
All carriers proceed with the
launch of your assault support
craft.
-Assault support craft are
to proceed to the designated
coordinates.
-Launch closing pass quantum
dimensional nuclear weapon
deployment squad.
Once the Blossom is sighted,
assault ships at the vanguard
are to begin a full
barrage of fire
targeting the enemy's
special canon.
-The Blossom cell
fortress special canon
is showing rising energy levels.
-Prepare on board canons.
Fire.
-Hit confirmed.
We struck the canon emitter.
The forward line
has been destroyed.
The remaining ships
look for heavy damage.
Fire, the rear
ships have struck.
We've destroyed
the canon emitter.
-Enemy fortress canon
has been destroyed.
-Good.
Hexelena fleet, prepare
to fire the Dimenstruim.
Machine caliber squads launch.
The Hideauze's nest is on the
other side of the hot Jupiter
class planets.
They are using the
star's radiation pressure
to fuel it's defense
platforms, the Blossom's sail,
making it an
impregnable fortress.
The stars powerful
radiation prohibits approach
from the side facing the sun.
Therefore, we must attack the
nest from the planet's shadow.
Fire the Dimenstruim.
-Fire.
-We will use our new
weapon, the Dimenstruim,
to destroy the fortress
blossom sail and the canon that
protects the planet's shadow.
With the nest fully exposed,
we can effectively attack it.
Our machine caliber
squad will escort a group
planting a closer pass quantum
dimensional nuclear bomb
on the base and
eliminate anything
that might try to
get in the way.
Front line troops, fire.
Phalanx squad, focus all of
your fire on the enemy front.
-Multiple attack
carrier class fighters
have launched from
the enemy nest.
More inbound.
-When was the last
time I felt afraid?
By throwing away
everything nonessential,
I become a complete soldier.
Like the victory I'm to achieve,
everything is perfectly clear.
I have no need to waiver.
Everything that I
seek, everything
that is desired of
me is all right here.
-Closer pass deployment
squad advancing.
Closing in on the
Hideauze's nest.
-Multi-core canon squad
commit to attack position.
The Blossom Sail is
regenerating too quickly.
-Is the Dimenstruim
ready to fire again?
It's still recharging, sir.
We won't make it.
-Damn it.
The enemy's fortresses
special canon has fired
and it's struck the main fleet.
Fuel escort ships
have been wiped out.
The Dimenstruim formation
has been destroyed.
Abort the mission.
All ships retreat.
-We attack with all of these
ships, and we still can't win?
STRIKER: Commander
Kugel, the stabilizer
will cease supplying exotic
matter in four minutes
and the wormhole will close.
The closer pass
deployment squad is
to return the carrier
Lamorak immediately.
-All right, everyone,
you heard her.
Abandon the closer
pass now and retreat
or you'll be left behind.
-Yes, sir.
All Tilter Company units get
off the closer pass immediately
or leave the whole quantum
dimensional bomb behind.
-Obey Commander Kugel's
orders and withdraw.
Come on.
Go!
-Set the closer pass quantum
dimensional bomb to mine mode.
Pull out the safety key
and get out of there.
-Wait a minute.
Aren't they gonna eat the
closer pass energy core and all?
-Ledo.
-I'll take care of
this, Commander.
-You'll what?
OK, just hold out
for 200 seconds.
Don't do anything stupid.
-Roger.
Release all emitters.
Maximize.
I don't care if we burnout.
CHAMBER: Roger.
-We need back up.
-We're caught.
We can't escape.
-We need assistance.
-Roger.
I'm on my way.
Just hold on.
KUGEL: We're
running out of time.
-Commander Kugel, I--
KUGEL: Forget it.
I'm done for.
Give it up.
Don't waste any more energy.
-Requesting backup.
We're completely surrounded.
The enemy is devouring
the quantum energy
core and the closer pass.
We're not gonna last here.
CHAMBER: Ending maximize
limiter release protocol
to preserve on the functionality
avoiding all further combat.
-Maintaining corridor
connection interface.
Initiating telemothy swing.
-40 seconds to Lamorak
telemothy swing.
39.
38.
37.
36.
-Damn it.
We can't afford to bring
the Hideauze back with us
or we'll all dead.
Ledo, you go on ahead
and join the others.
I'll stay back and
slow them down.
-Commander Kugel, that
violates military regulation.
-You're still a young man.
You have more time to
kill enemies than me.
This is my decision
as a soldier.
Glory to the Galactic
Alliance of humankind.
See ya, kid.
-Commander!
CHAMBER: Guidance
beacon received.
Commencing landing sequence.
-Damned Hideauze.
-Sorry.
Wow.
It's huge.
Hey, Bellows!
-Hey, Amy.
-I've got a message from Ridget.
She said if you're
willing to be responsible,
you can use this place
until tomorrow night.
And she said to sign this.
-Jeez.
She's such a stickler for rules.
-So what the heck is this thing?
-If we knew, we wouldn't be
having a problem with it.
Forget getting it open.
We've tried to
take the armor off.
We couldn't even scratch it.
I can't even imagine how
they put this thing together.
Oh, and check this out.
-What?
-I've never seen
letters like this.
Of course, we're not even
sure these are letters.
-You know, I've had a strange
feeling about this thing
ever since we
found it out there.
I mean, it wasn't
degraded or even rusted,
unlike the treasures
we usually drag up.
-Yeah, well, it's not
much of a treasure
if we can't even take it apart.
-Regardless of
that, you're still
going to buy it at the price
you promised me, Pinion.
You're the one who said you'd
take anything off our hands
that we dredged up.
-You gotta be kidding.
-It looks like it could start
moving any second, doesn't it?
-No way.
It's broken for sure.
No matter what we tried,
it won't even budge.
Ah.
-Still, you requested to use
this area way out on the edge
just to be safe, right?
If something happens, I suppose
we could just cut you off.
-You idiot, this is my home.
You can't just cut
us off that easy.
-Right, right, I'll tell Ridget.
-So as you can see,
Amy, there ain't
gonna be much to see
here for a while.
You should probably get
back to your deliveries.
-All right, then I'll come
again tomorrow morning.
Make sure you've taken
off a parts by then.
-Will do, if we can.
But I got no clue how.
CHAMBER: Measuring brain waves.
No abnormalities
in basic rhythms.
Ensign Ledo,
awakening confirmed.
Revival successful.
In accordance with
emergency protocols,
I preserved your biological
functions via cryostasis.
266,815 minutes have passed.
My system functionality
was in stasis as well,
but I rebooted 12 minutes ago
in response to external stimuli.
-Huh?
Are you saying that we've
been asleep for six months?
CHAMBER: The current
situation we are in
requires the judgment
of the pilot.
Thus, I initiated your
awakening process.
-[gibberish]
-Who are all these people?
And what are they speaking?
CHAMBER: An unknown language.
It is similar to several
ancient languages.
I am analyzing but
lack sufficient data.
-So they're not in
the Galactic Alliance?
Are they a wandering tribe
that hasn't joined yet?
It looks like they've never
seen a machine caliber.
CHAMBER: It appears
as though they
are trying to damage the craft,
but have no means of doing so.
Preliminary analysis
indicates they
are a very primitive group.
-They won't be able to open
the hatch from the looks of it.
Where are we?
CHAMBER: It is
impossible at this time
to pinpoint our coordinates.
We lack a point of reference.
-What?
CHAMBER: I have developed
a working hypothesis.
During the carrier
Lamorak's telemothy swing,
we were caught up in the vortex
of the changing space time
metric and later re-synchronized
with normal space time
at a set of arbitrary
coordinates.
-This isn't good.
CHAMBER: While I was maintaining
your biological functions
in cryostasis, I began
sending out a distress signal,
but the situation is quickly
approaching a critical point
that requires intervention.
Please advise.
-I-- I don't know.
Judging from their appearance
alone, they look like humans,
but until we know who they are,
I can't make any decisions.
CHAMBER: The bulkheads
of this vessel
are likely to be extremely
fragile in construction.
Even with our
current power output,
it is possible to
destroy them and escape.
-No.
It's probably a vacuum
outside these walls,
and they're not wearing
airtight space suits.
Besides that, I need to
know what's going on.
I'd like to investigate the
surroundings here, but--
-Hm.
Damn it!
-The gravity is exactly 1G, huh?
For a primitive
wandering tribe, they
have things tuned pretty well.
What about the air?
CHAMBER: Primary components
are nitrogen, oxygen,
and carbon dioxide.
The ratio is ideal for life.
There are other minor components
present, but none of them
are harmful to breathe.
Wow, if it's breathable
air, I'll breath it.
I'd like to save up as
much oxygen as possible.
What is that smell?
What is this place?
There should be limits to how
outdated something can be.
Who are these people?
[door opening]
-Look, I know you said you'd
come again this morning,
but it's not even dawn yet.
-I was thinking about it
so much, I couldn't sleep.
-Yeah, I didn't get
any sleep at all.
-Sorry I had to wake
you up, but you're
the only one who
can unlock the door.
-We're crossing between
galaxies right now,
Ridget will get pissed
if I waste electricity.
What's wrong?
It's not going to
suddenly start moving.
Huh?
Amy, get away from
that thing quick.
Get over here.
Hurry!
-OK.
-Amy!
Why, you!
-[gibberish]
-What the hell are you saying?
-Hey, who are you?
What are you doing?
-[gibberish]
-You piece of crap!
Come back!
-Damn it!
Let me go.
Let me go!
-Damn it.
[alarm]
CHAMBER: I cannot find any
logic in your actions, Ensign.
-If I take the hostage, they
won't attack me on sight.
At least, I hope not.
-[gibberish]
-First, we need to
know the layout here.
Until tell, I can't
risk activating you.
CHAMBER: Roger.
Recording and analyzing footage.
I advise you to cover as
much ground as possible.
-[gibberish]
-Have you been able to figure
out their language yet?
CHAMBER: Analysis estimated
to be 40% complete.
More vocabulary
samples are needed.
-All right, you heard him.
Keep talking about
whatever you want.
-[gibberish]
-It's not a fire.
What do you mean?
-Ridget, there's an intruder.
He's got some weird kind of
gun and he's kidnapped Amy.
-An intruder?
By how?
Where did he come from?
-How the hell should I know?
He just showed up in the hanger.
-[gibberish]
CHAMBER: Those were
statements regarding
the active intercourse
with one's mother,
as well as an exclamation
about sanctified excrement.
-Just as I thought,
they're savages.
This is the problem
with wandering tribes.
CHAMBER: Statement of doubt.
We cannot assume these
people are a wandering tribe.
-Why do you say that, Chamber?
CHAMBER: None of
the recorded footage
I've analyzed thus far show
any displays of caution taken
for unexpected gravity
fluctuations, radiation
exposure, or air loss.
The obvious conclusion
is that this facility
must have been constructed
without any concern for vacuum
safety or zero gravity events.
-No way.
That's impossible.
CHAMBER: Agreed, but there
is one historical example
in the database that
would fit those criteria.
-This is--
-[gibberish]
-What's going on here?
What is this place?
I've got no choice.
Now, Chamber!
Chamber, can you tell
me what's going on here?
CHAMBER: It appears we have
somehow found ourselves
on the surface of a
planet where restoration
of the natural
atmosphere is possible.
-Ridiculous.
No way.
CHAMBER: Matching data with
observed celestial bodies.
Confirmed.
There is only one set
of data that matches,
the third planet of
the sol system, Earth.
Records suggests
of its existence,
but until now, there
has been no proof.
This is the planet
of humanity's origin.
[theme music]