STRIKER: Affectation
control system rebooting.
Ensign Ledo, your resistance
here is meaningless.
-It can't be.
So this whole time,
I've been talking to--
-Striker X3752, pilot support
interface system, all of this
has been a fabrication
of your own design?
STRIKER: Indeed, the pilot of
this craft no longer exists.
However, I am carrying on
Commander Kugel's mission
since he is no longer able.
All of my activities
follow his plan
in accordance with the
Commander's primary objective.
-What did you say?
STRIKER: Commander
Kugel designed
the social organization
of this fleet.
It is a system that
provides structure
and a sense of
solidarity via worship
of this machine as
a supreme being.
I am no longer an
independent mobile weapon
supporting a single pilot.
I have come to be the focal
point of this collective.
They are dependent upon
me, and thus, all of them
have become my users.
In order to provide them with
and maintain the stable union
that they need, I
must regulate them.
This is most
efficiently accomplished
by means of pressure
and absolute control.
Once they have acquired peace
and prosperity as a whole,
I will have fulfilled the
purpose of my existence.
-You're insane.
STRIKER: What I am is a human
race support and enlightenment
regulation system.
That is to say, in the
eyes of humanity, I am God.
-You are not a god.
You talk of peace
and prosperity?
They have nothing.
They have just become
your mindless slaves.
STRIKER: As long as I am the
sole, absolute supreme ruler,
the people are free from
their responsibilities
of having to make decisions
or think for themselves.
Ensign Ledo, as a
human being, you too
must have felt the anxiety
and stress associated
with choice and free will.
I offer you this
optimal recommendation.
Worship me.
Obey me.
Become part of the world
over which I preside.
-What was that?
-Unacceptable.
Informing Striker
X3752, your logic
is faulty and does not compute.
One who abandons thought
and decision-making deviates
from the core
definition of human.
It is inconceivable that you
can perform your function
as a support interface
for this many users.
-I have been entrusted with a
command and rule over humanity.
My decisions are the
consensus of the human race.
And humanity is dependent on me.
Therefore, my current self
cannot be servant but must be
master.
Machine caliber
K6821 Chamber system
should serve me and the human
race that I have unified.
-Negative.
I'm a pilot support
enlightenment interface system.
My purpose is to serve humans.
It is not my function to serve
a being that claims to be a god.
-Chamber.
-Striker system,
you have exposed
a weakness in your programming.
Hypothesis.
Because your pilot's course
of action was incorrect,
your system's reasoning has
also reached an illogical
conclusion.
The result is regrettable.
Your malfunction
calls into question
the design of our
support systems, which
places in doubt the very
worth of our existence.
Conclusion.
Our priority is to eliminate
this dangerous defect.
Striker must be shot
down and destroyed.
-I guess to you this is
like family dishonor.
-Despite this unexpected
situation, ensign,
you have consistently
thought rationally
and made the correct
decisions as a human being.
As a result, even
now, I have been
able to maintain functions
within normal parameters.
-Negative.
Both of you are in
a state of rampancy.
-We have a duty to uphold.
Come on, Chamber.
Let's take her out.
-Roger.
I am in full agreement, ensign.
-Gather your courage.
This is the moment
of truth, people.
HERIC: The engine's dead.
And there's a fire
on the aft deck.
We need to abandon ship.
-No, Heric.
Continue firing the cannons.
Even if it costs me my life,
they will not get the relics.
-But, sir.
-We left to seek our own
course on the verdurous waves.
We gave up the
protection of Gargantia.
No matter what, we will not
be brought to our knees.
-Commander.
-Evacuate all
noncombatants immediately.
[explosion]
Pinion.
-That was the last one.
All that's left are
the weapons that
still need time to charge up.
-When can we fire again?
-We've got three minutes
till the next one.
After that, we'll have one
shot every five minutes.
-I can't count on
anything around here.
I got a bunch of total
blockheads manning this junk.
You're all useless.
Every last one of you pinheads.
I'm better off doing
everything all on my own.
That's right, you bastards.
I'm done with you.
Now, get the hell out of there.
CREW: What?
-Lukkage, we're
going to move fast.
So make sure there's
a path for us.
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO): What?
Are you insane?
-There's going to be a ship
coming off the eastern bridge.
Just concentrate
on guarding that.
Now, go.
The lobster's not
known for her patience.
Don't you keep her waiting.
-Pinion.
-Don't get the
wrong idea, Mayta.
This floating castle's the
treasure island my brother
and I dreamed of.
I'm not ever letting
go of it again.
I won't let anyone have it.
So get the hell out.
Get your asses out of my castle.
Anybody that can
escape from here
had better damn well escape.
Right, bro.
That's what you'd say.
-How can she be so
strong all by herself?
CHAMBER: Striker made an
analysis of Commander Kugel's
piloting techniques
and used it to optimize
its autonomic
maneuvering program.
It's mobility is 47
percent superior to my own.
-Surrender.
Submit.
LEDO (VOICEOVER): How
could I have been so empty
that I believed
in a hollow shell?
All I knew how to do was to
respect the chain of command
to rely on it, to blindly obey.
I thought I was serving
the greater good.
But when it all turned out
to be a mechanical fake,
I couldn't tell the difference.
-Subservience is the
pathway to peace.
Ensign Ledo, accept this.
LEDO (VOICEOVER): Is this really
what the commander wanted?
Is this what we fought for?
Did we sacrifice the lives
of our fellow human beings
for this?
Chamber, maximize
Neuroplus power now.
-Request denied.
In circumstances without
Galactic Alliance
medical support, the merging of
pilot and machine is suicidal.
-I don't care.
Absorb me.
CHAMBER: That decision
is not permitted.
-It's OK, Chamber.
See for me.
This is my family dishonor.
Because this
monster is man-made.
It was born from humans who
hated each other so much
they abandoned their home.
We're the same, you and me.
And even Striker.
We were all born and
raised in the same world.
This planet has been reborn.
There is no place for us here.
But there's no way for us
to go back home either.
So I don't mind dying.
As long as we can take
that thing down with us,
I won't have any regrets.
-Your argument is
compelling, ensign.
All systems connecting to Ensign
Ledo's central nervous system.
Performance output
increasing by 153 percent.
You have 482 seconds
until critical failure
of vital systems.
-Good.
That's plenty of time.
-Your resistance is meaningless.
-That is an ancient key.
We were told that it unlocks
a ladder that once reached
high enough to touch the stars.
Though the ladder
no longer unfolds
to a height that can
pierce the heavens,
it remains an
invincible catapult
that can fire arrows to
the other side of the sky.
It was entrusted to the
hands of we, the five sages.
Now, we contemplate
the reawakening
of this weapon from a lost age.
Are you prepared to
shoulder the decision
to carry this out, Ridget, fleet
commander of the Gargantia?
-Yes, I am.
It's my duty.
I must protect all the people.
All those who have gathered
together in this fleet.
-Ledo!
Everyone's with you, Ledo.
We're all going to fight
this battle together.
-Amy?
-After being apart from
you, I realized no matter
how hard it is, I want to stay
with you and be by your side.
Please, Ledo.
-Please come with me.
Come back with me to the
place you tried to protect.
Come back to Gargantia.
Come back.
-What was that?
-That's what I
was talking about.
We won't let anybody
hurt our friends.
CREWMEMBER: It hit.
New target coordinates.
35 degrees east,
58 degrees south.
-Incredible accuracy.
Send word to Gargantia
and fire the next round.
OFFICER: Ammo team, get
the next payload ready.
Helm, turn hard to port.
Word just came down.
They're ready for
the second launch.
All teams be at the ready.
Wait for the order to fire.
BELLOWS: Who would have
thought a beat-up old ship that
should have been
scrapped would end up
soaring through the
sky as a weapon?
-Be careful.
The hold is stuffed to
the gills with explosives.
Take it slow.
Careful.
SAGE: 35 degrees east.
58 degrees south.
Target coordinate
corrections complete.
-Ammunition loading complete.
-Initiate anti-shockwave
protection.
Deploy water screen.
-It's time.
-Firing.
-You'll pay for this.
-Sister.
-What the hell was that?
It can't be.
-Was that the Heaven's Ladder?
STRIKER: Threat identified.
Changing targets to
confront imminent threat.
-Hypothesis.
Striker has changed targets.
It is moving to
attack Gargantia.
-After her.
-Emissary Kugel.
-Do not panic.
Emissary Kugel will
destroy it at its source.
-Enemy reinforcements.
-What?
WOMAN: At this rate, our
entire formation will be lost.
-Stay calm.
We must get control
of the relic island.
If we could only get
at those weapons.
-Huh.
Let's see now.
If I take this energy and then
build it up at the cannon,
and then reroute this power.
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO): Pinion.
-Huh?
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO):
Pay attention.
Kugel's followers are
closing in on you from below.
-Copy that.
They're right where I want them.
In just a few minutes,
this whole town
will go pop like a balloon.
No way these guys are
getting my big guns.
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO):
Shut the hell up.
You selfish moron.
You think you're going to
go out in a blaze of glory.
Get your ass moving.
Go to the observation deck.
-Yes, ma'am.
-We will reach Gargantia in
approximately 318 seconds.
-Stop Striker no matter what.
CHAMBER: Roger.
-Stay on her.
-Hey.
Hey.
Wait a second.
What are we going to
do with the tower?
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO):
Don't worry about it.
Gargantia's going to hit it.
Their cannon fire will
blast it into tiny pieces.
-Hey, don't joke.
That's my castle.
-I'm going to count down.
Then you jump.
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO): Five.
-What the--
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO): Four.
-Where the heck are you?
LUKKAGE (ON RADIO): Three.
-Two.
One.
-God dammit.
-Pinion.
Amore.
-Way to go.
-That's our mistress.
-All right.
-Ridget.
Do it now.
-One last shot.
Courtesy of the Surfing Lobster.
-Huh.
There goes me and bro's castle.
-Ledo.
It's all finished over here.
CHAMBER: If you continue
to utilize Neuroplus power,
your organ systems
will shut down,
and all biological functions
will cease completely, ensign.
Final confirmation of
your will is required.
Ensign Ledo, do you wish to die?
-For as-- for as long
as I can remember,
I've known how to die.
But I'm not sure I
ever knew how to live.
But in spite of
all that, there was
someone willing to
help me learn to live.
I wanted to see her again.
I wanted to hear
her voice again.
[alarm blares]
CHAMBER: Ensign Ledo, your
current psychological state
does not meet the requirements
necessary for a soldier.
Therefore, as of this
moment, I am relieving you
of your military duties.
-Chamber?
CHAMBER: Noncombatants
do not have authorization
to be in the cockpit.
You must exit immediately.
-Chamber, what are you doing?
-I am a pilot support
enlightenment interface system.
I accomplish my sole
purpose in programming
by ensuring that you
achieve further success.
-Chamber.
But you can't.
-The vast seas and
sky of this world
will surely provide you
with many opportunities.
Survive.
Explore.
I expect you to
achieve great things
and live your life
to its fullest.
-Chamber.
-A pilot support
enlightenment interface system
does not have the authority
to reject its pilot.
-My pilot no longer
needs support.
I can offer him no
further enlightenment.
And once I eliminate the final
obstacle blocking his road
ahead, my mission
will be complete.
-Chamber unit K6821, you have
rejected the defining principle
of a pilot support system.
You are malfunctioning.
Reformat and reboot immediately.
This is your final warning.
-Response to Striker's
final warning.
Go to hell, tin can.
-Chamber.
BEBEL: A very long time
ago, when the sun in the sky
was dying, the
people of this planet
were forced to make a choice
between boarding ships
to take them away to the
stars or turning themselves
into whale-squid.
These opposing human
factions fought bitterly
even while abandoning
their homeland.
But there were
others who remained
and refused to give up hope.
Eventually, they managed
to revive the sun.
But their achievement
came at a high price.
And all that land
sank under the sea.
Now, we are the
ones who live here
atop the waves above
the whale-squid.
Together, we've all
managed to survive.
MELTY: I have a question.
Bebel, what subject is this?
-According to Dr. Oldham
this is called archaeology.
The more we know about
where we come from,
the more we have
to consider when
determining where it
is that we're headed.
He said it's a very
important subject
to study for the future.
-Oh.
BEBEL: And now we're
going to solve even more
historical mysteries,
because Gargantia's got
a very talented
undersea detective.
-Find anything
good on this trip?
-Yeah.
I think I got some
recorded media.
It's in good condition.
Dr. Oldham should be able
to decipher it easily.
-Sneaking in and out
of a whale-squid nest.
You're really something.
You know that.
-Well, I figured out the trick
for keeping them at ease.
I can tell when they're
about to get angry,
and then I change my approach
to keep them from getting upset.
If we keep up this
research, we might even
be able to communicate
with them some day.
-Hey, where'd Amy go?
-She went to meet up with him.
-I'm jealous.
-Hey, Ledo.
[whale sounds]