-Reverse all stops.
-Where the hell are we?
-For now it doesn't look
like there's any danger.
-But are we really going
to be OK after this?
Yeah, the tin can massacred
all the whalesquid.
I'm sure of it.
-Uhh.
-Don't tell me that's-- Hey,
tin can Ledo, welcome back.
How'd it go?
-Confirm, all Hideauze
inhabiting this sector
have been exterminated.
-Ha, ha.
Fantastic.
Go, get the Yunburos ready.
The legendary treasure of the
whalesquid is ours to take.
-Yeah.
-Whoo.
-Oh.
[MUSIC - "SKY AND YOUR MESSAGE,"
CHOUCHO]
-All right, stop.
The shaft is this way.
Go ahead.
Nice and easy now.
All right, that's good.
-Nice.
Looking good over there.
-Pinion, come here a sec.
-Sure.
-Looks promising, doesn't it?
-Yeah.
-Ah.
Ahh.
Oh.
Huh?
Oh, oh.
Ooh.
-Big, Bro, I wanted to
drink this with you.
-Pinion.
-Pretty awesome isn't it?
And this is just the beginning.
-So this is the grand
legacy of our ancestors.
-Yep.
And there's even
more amazing treasure
waiting deep inside
the whalesquid nest.
It's just like my
big brother told me.
There's no rust.
It's not rotted
out and down there,
there's an unlimited supply.
-Yes, this treasure could
bring back civilization
and restore the world.
-Bring back civilization?
We're the ones who found it.
The treasure belongs
to us and no one else.
-What are you talking about?
I only left Gargantia
because I thought
we were going to use all this
to enrich people's lives?
-Who cares about
saving the world.
Let's enrich own lives first!
-If we hoard it,
others will come
and try to steal it from us.
-We've got tons of
weapons and ammo to spare.
There ain't nothing
to be afraid of.
-That is not the issue, Pinion.
-We'll sink anyone
that even gets close.
Hey, send out a message.
I want it blasted
on all frequencies.
The whalesquid are dead,
and we've got the treasure.
-No.
It could stir up trouble
with other ships in the area.
-It'll warn them to
stay the hell away.
Boost the signal strength.
I want to broadcast
as far as we can.
I have a message for every
ship that can here this, so
listen up.
We annihilated the
whalesquid that
were living in the Sea of Mist.
Wiped them out completely.
All the pods, all the
nests, everything.
And it was all thanks to me.
From now on, I'll be known
as Pinion of the Sea of Mist.
If any of you bastards out
there had your own sights set
on the whalesquid
treasure, forget it.
But don't go thinking you can
steal it out from under us.
The treasure belongs to us.
It's ours.
All of it.
So I hereby issue a
warning to all ships.
Any vessel that comes close
to us will be sunk on sight.
-Pinion might be onto something.
-Not you, too.
-That being said, pirates
will be targeting us.
We'll need to prepare for when
they arrive and attack us.
-Why must we assume the worst?
Will we have to fight?
-Commander Flange.
I have a delivery for you.
-Bring it here.
-Thank you, Commander Flange.
-Is there something else?
-I heard that Ledo killed
all the whalesquid.
Do you know if that's true?
-Yes.
It's true.
-I'm worried.
Do you think we're
going to be all right?
-I don't know.
I wish I did.
-Are you really
OK with everything
that's going on around here?
-That's enough.
-How could I be?
Thanks to Ledo and
Chamber, we were
able to scavenge deep
inside the whalesquid nest,
and I was eager to do it.
But with not sharing,
or even trading
the treasure we found
with anyone else,
and with Pinion spotting
threats over the radio,
I'm not so sure anymore.
-Can't you stop him, Commander?
If you don't, we could
end up being outcasts.
-The ship masters who followed
me when we left the Gargantia
began to follow Pinion.
-Oh.
-Pinion continues to be
someone the fleet needs.
His skills as a
repairman are required
to make use of the salvage.
There's little that can
be done to stop him.
-Oh, no.
-Ensign.
-Why aren't you helping?
Come give us a hand.
-You can take care of
the salvage yourselves.
You don't need me.
-But the treasure is
clogging the shaft.
I need the tin can to help
bring up all the stuff.
-Forget it.
-What's gotten into
you all of a sudden?
You scared of a
little hard work?
-You think I'm scared?
You go to hell.
I destroyed the Hideauze.
I fear nothing.
Nothing.
-Hey, Joe, let's hang it
up for the day, all right?
-Sounds good.
-Fleet Commander, has the
new fleet configuration
been finalized?
-Yes.
The ship masters were
all very cooperative.
Now all we need to do is
reset the ship interlocks.
No simple task, but
we will get it done.
-Fleet Commander, have you
heard Pinion's broadcast
from the Sea of Mist?
-Yes, I've heard it.
-Frankly speaking, what
do you think of it?
-Until there's factual
evidence to back up his claims,
I don't think
anything of it at all.
However, did the rest of the
fleet hear the broadcast?
-Everyone heard it
or knows about it.
-I see.
If the ship masters
believe it, some of them
may wish to leave to
seek their own treasure.
-And if they do?
I'll respect their
wishes and let them go.
-Dr. Olton, is it true?
Did Ledo destroy
the whalesquid nest?
-Yes, at least
that's what Pinion
said on the radio broadcast.
-How sad.
-It was very foolish.
How could he do such a thing?
-I swore that I'd get
revenge for my big brother.
-You said that it was
only a dream, remember?
-Amy?
I wonder how Mayta is doing?
She must be OK.
Pinion said they'd be all right.
Hey, Amy.
-I don't know if
she's all right, OK?
I don't know anything.
Ledo.
Why?
-Do they look like
they're going to give up?
-I don't think so.
-But they're
probably out of ammo.
-Continue firing.
-Are you serious?
Why not?
We've got plenty
of ammunition left.
Besides, they started it.
They attacked us.
-But that would sink them.
-Unless they put
both hands up first.
Repairs on the treasure
should be done by now.
I think we should
fire a test shot.
-All right.
Keep going.
A little more.
There.
That should do it.
-Locked and loaded.
-Yes.
Fire!
-Fire, he tells me.
But how do I do that?
This one, or maybe that one.
-Dammit.
What kind of aim is that?
-They're radioing to give up.
-It took you long
enough, morons.
You guys sure took your time.
You've got some nerve
picking a fight with us.
You were warned.
-Please, spare us.
Let us join up with your crew.
-Huh?
-We'll give you all our cargo.
Just please let us
join your fleet.
-What?
We can't just take
every groveling dog
that says "please."
This fleet would get
huge pretty quick.
Wait a sec.
If the fleet did get huge,
no one would challenge us.
We'd be unstoppable.
There'd be no end to
the treasure we'd haul.
OK.
Anyone that wants to jump
ship, welcome aboard.
-Yes, thank you.
-Hear that?
Seems your crew is mine now.
-Uh-huh.
-Hey, let's lock this
guy up somewhere.
Ledo.
About this stuff we salvaged.
I, uh, well, I'd really like the
tin can to check it out for us.
Will you do it?
The ensign's permission
is required for me
to participate in any activity
outside of military service.
-So how about it?
Can he help?
-Do what you want.
-Great, then we're good to go.
Get up, kid.
You're coming with me.
We can't start the party
without our big hero.
Follow us, all right, tin can?
Come on, let's go.
-Huh?
-To our victory.
Drink.
-You should have
seen this one guy.
Huh?
-We won today.
Great job everyone.
Pirates picked a fight with
us, but we kicked their asses.
-Yay.
-Has Lady Luck been
on our side ever
since we struck out on our own?
You betcha.
But none of this
would've been possible
without Ledo and Chamber.
So to say thanks, let's all kiss
the tin can's joint metal ass.
-Play.
-What is this?
What am I doing?
What am I doing it all for?
Who am I doing it all for?
When did it start?
Was it when I first
regained consciousness
on this strange planet?
Or was it earlier,
like the first time
I got inside Chamber?
Inside a Machine Caliber.
Or did it start at the very
beginning when I was born?
-Well then?
-It is a primitive
electromagnetic weapon.
-A what?
What the hell is that?
-This weapon's basic
structure is essentially
the same as the electronic beam
armor that I am equipped with.
-Seriously?
-However, I estimate
its maximum power output
to be 150th the
strength of my own.
-Even 150th the strength in
your power is a big deal.
-Compared to current
Earth technologies,
power output is approximately
76 times greater
than that of this entire fleet.
-Yeah, yeah, that's great.
But the question is
could we get to work?
-It appears possible to restore
basic functions via repairs.
However, a vast
amount of electricity
would be required for operation.
-Electricity?
Hey, would it work if we could
harness enough light bugs?
-Further investigation
is required.
-Then investigate.
I'll find Ledo and
tell him the news.
-I have uncovered evidence
supporting the information
in the Hideauze
digital recording.
It is the light bugs.
Light bugs are nano machines
that actually comprise
the material that the adult
Hideauze shell is made of.
They absorb
electromagnetic waves
and convert them into highly
efficient chemical energy.
While synthesizing this
energy the light bugs
are also self-replicating and
through carbon bonding function
as a durable exoskeleton.
This symbiosis indicates
origins and intelligent life.
Conclusion.
Hideauze evolve from humans.
-You.
How can you tell me this?
It goes against everything.
Everything the
alliance taught me.
Everything that I've
been fighting for.
-I recognize significant
errors and omissions
in your knowledge base.
-Can I fight the Hideauze if
they're evolved from humans?
Is it right to be fighting them?
What's the reason?
Is there a point to all of this?
If not, I can't-- I
can't keep fighting.
Those living creatures.
I can't murder them.
-That is unacceptable.
Your realization
is the antithesis
of the Alliance Mission.
It refutes the purpose
of our existence.
-You saw them, didn't you?
The newborn whalesquid,
what they all looked like?
We're all humans, and we're
just killing each other.
Admit it.
That's what this war
we're fighting really is.
-Even with this
additional information,
there is no compelling
reason to forgo
the eradication of
the Hideauze house.
-Maybe for you.
But not me.
-That is unacceptable.
The Hideauze pose a threat
to fundamental destruction
to the human race.
Preventing that destruction
is your sole mission
and the reason for existence.
-But we're all one human race.
Be quiet, Chamber.
I've heard enough propaganda.
-You are incorrect.
The link between myself and
the Alliance has been lost.
This is not their dogma.
I have arrived at this
conclusion independently based
on the analysis of
current information.
-What?
-Reconciliation between the
human race and the Hideauze
is impossible.
The reason being, because
the Hideauze have rejected
civilization in its entirety.
-What does that mean?
If instead of flesh
and bone, human beings
were equipped with
strong versatile
bodies like the Hideauze,
then the development
of advanced Machine
Calibers like
myself would not
have been necessary.
My system is the culmination
of the superior intelligence
of the human race, but Machine
Calibers are also necessary
for human survival
in order to offset
the fragility of human form.
Conclusion.
The reason humans developed
their intellectual capabilities
and built complex
civilizations was in order
to overcome their
bodily limitations.
The existence of
advanced civilizations
is what separates the human
race from all other primates.
Unlike humans, the
Hideauze, having discarded
their feeble bodies, no longer
have physical limitations.
Further, as their instinctual
desires drive them only
to seek out food
and reproduction,
it has not been necessary
for them to retain or develop
a superior intellect.
Machine Calibers are the apex of
what human beings can and would
create to promote self-reliance.
In other words, we are
the greatest realization
of pure intellect
born to civilization.
By negating the essentiality
of this pure intellect,
the Hideauze, in effect,
have reached the sublimation
of one form of existence.
-Are you saying that
they're an ultimate life
form, the Hideauze?
-Affirmative.
Hence, you and I
must battle them.
Both the dignity and the
survival of the human race
hang in the balance.
In a war against a species that
shares the same genetic origins
as you, failure means
certain extinction.
One side seeks civilization,
the other abandons it.
The war between the Hideauze
and the Galactic Alliance
of humankind is a
conflict between two very
different survival
strategies, a conflict
in which the losing
side will be culled.
-Be culled?
-As long as you desire
to continue existing,
you do not have a choice.
-So I have to fight.
Is that a command?
You, a machine, are
commanding a human?
-I am a pilot support
enlightenment interface
system, Ensign Ledo.
I accomplish my
purpose of existence
by insuring you achieve further
success and increasingly
greater results.
Receiving.
A polarized photon sequence
Galactic Alliance standard
encrypted communication wave.
-What did you say?
Identified as an allied craft.
-An allied craft?
That's Commander Kugel.
[MUSIC - "THIS WORLD HAS
BEEN WAITING FOR US," MINORI CHIHARA]