[music playing]
-[gasp]
-We've been gathering what
we believe to be weapons
from among the sacred
relics that have already
been brought to the surface.
-Oh-- oh, wow!
A mountain of treasure!
-Your sacred duty will be
to restore these relics.
-That's a lot easier
said than done.
I don't even know what's
inside half these things.
Huh?
What's this?
[digital beep]
Wha?
I can see through the metal!
Whoa, this thing is awesome!
-We desire only the
items that are weapons.
Do as you wish with the rest.
-What?
Uh-- fine.
I'll do that!
You can count on me.
-Hm.
We'll leave you to it, then.
[laughs gleefully]
[laughs]
Ooh!
[gasp] This is so awesome!
LUKKAGE: You
certainly come cheap.
-What?
Did you say something?
-I was remarking on how
easily you sold out.
-Huh?
-You're as easy to placate
as a child with a new toy.
I thought you were a
man with more backbone,
but I guess I was wrong.
-What the hell are
you getting at?
Go on, say it!
-Well, have you seen
the flying Yunboro?
-Yeah.
What about it?
-I'm going to need to borrow its
power, if you catch my drift.
-I don't see where
you're going with this.
-I've grown rather tired of
this fleet and its methods.
I think it's about
time for a change.
-Huh?
What--
-I've decided to return
to piracy just as soon
as this fleet's resting
on the ocean floor.
[gasp]
-Commander.
Sir, about the Gargantia,
would you cancel the attack?
-Why?
-Well--
-If you feel an affinity
towards them, all the more
reason to enlighten them
as quickly as possible,
don't you think?
-Oh!
-To increase the
prosperity of humankind,
we both need superior
people and resources.
-But sir!
-Ledo, our mission is
to bring a new sense
of order and stability
to this world.
-I understand.
Just like in the Alliance.
-Since we can't return
to the front lines,
we'll make this Earth into
our Utopia, a second Avalon.
Our ultimate objective
remains the same.
Don't waver now.
-Yes, sir.
[deep rumbling]
[machinery running]
-Heh.
It keeps getting
better and better.
ACOLYTE: Master Pinion,
you have a guest.
-Oh, sure.
That's fine.
-Now it's "Master Pinion"?
[scoffs] No way!
-Oh, it's you.
What do you want?
-They went through all
my packages, you know.
They're hassling everyone else,
but suddenly you're a VIP?
-Hey, it's not like
I asked for it.
MELTY: Here.
-Hm?
Uh?
-Avalon.
Utopia.
We'll make this Earth into
our Utopia, a second Avalon.
Don't waver now.
-Uh?
[squeaking]
-Is that you, Grace?
-Grace, wait!
[squeaks]
-Oh-- oh, that's right.
Grace is on Gargantia with Amy.
Amy.
-Oh, he's here!
-Pinion.
-Let's keep it short.
-Do you have any
idea what the devil's
wrong with these people?
-Huh?
-It's like the people of
this fleet are all ghosts.
-Their eyes are glazed over, and
they've got this weird stare.
It's creepy.
-Yeah, I've noticed.
-It's like a disease.
And before long, I'm sure
everyone from my fleet
will also be infected by it.
I'm starting to
wonder why we ever
left Gargantia in
the first place.
Are you OK with the way
things are turning out?
-Someone I know has plans
to start a rebellion.
-They do?
-Really?
-Remember the red Lobster
that came to pick me up?
-You mean the great
pirate Lukkage?
-Great!
Let's work with
the lobster then.
What's the problem?
-She's counting on getting
help from the tin can.
But I don't think Ledo's
going to go for it.
-Mm.
-So then we live like this
for the rest of our lives?
[squeaking]
[drip]
-Oh.
[rain starts]
[squeaking]
-There's a tarp over there!
Spread it out and collect
all the rain you can.
-You know you're soaked, right?
You'll get sick like that.
[low wailing]
-Uh?
[squeaking]
Hey!
[panting]
[low wailing]
-What's that?
What the hell is going on?
Chamber, what's happening?
CHAMBER: This is weather
phenomenon called rain.
We have observed it before.
I do not detect
any abnormalities.
-What's that?
-What is
This?
PRIESTESS: Fresh water
falls from the sky as rain.
It is a blessing from heaven.
These citizens will now make
their journey to our god.
Blessings be on the
few who must die
for the sake of the
many yet living.
-What?
Oh no!
Stop this.
What are you doing?
PRIESTESS: May honor and
glory be eternally unto them,
for they are
humanity's salvation.
[gasp]
[splashing]
[horrified gasp]
-People.
Those were people!
-I can't-- I can't
believe what I just saw.
I didn't come here to see this.
-These guys are insane.
LUKKAGE: You're right.
They are, indeed.
And do you want to take a guess
where this insane fleet is
going to go next?
Gargantia.
-What?
Yeah, this ain't for me.
No way!
-The reason I left Gargantia
was to protect everyone
from the Hideauze--
Amy, Bebel, all of them.
I just wanted to protect them.
But I--
[footsteps]
CHAMBER: Incoming message
from Commander Kugel.
It reads as follows.
"Ensign Ledo, Board your
machine Caliber and assume
battle command."
I await your decision, Ensign.
-My decision.
I make the decisions
and you carry them out.
That's how it's been.
But really, I don't
think I decided anything.
I never made a choice
in my whole life.
-The meaning of your
utterance is unclear.
Response to Commander's order--
-Chamber, how do you
compare against Striker?
-Insufficient data
to answer that.
And I cannot comprehend the
logic behind your question.
[sighs heavily]
-What if I asked you
to take on Striker?
Can you?
-The current actions
of Striker X3752
would not be classified
as part of Alliance
military operations.
Therefore, it is possible to
authorize engagement in battle.
-I see.
In that case, tell
me-- can I fight Kugel?
Chamber!
-The answer to that question is
beyond my function as a Pilot
Support Enlightenment
Interface System.
Combat policy formulation
is entirely in your hands.
Whether you can fight Commander
Kugel or not is up to you.
-Uh?
Huh?
-Hm.
-Melty, a radio warning
will just be intercepted.
The only way is to go over
and tell them directly.
Please, Melty, there's no time.
-But Ledo, I don't know if I
can do something so important.
LEDO: Yes you can.
You're the only one who
can fly to Gargantia.
Melty.
Please, save everyone!
-OK.
But you owe me.
Mm.
[wind whistling]
-Chamber, prepare for combat.
CHAMBER: Roger.
[wind howling]
-Huh?
Ah, there it is, Gargan-- tia.
[wind whistling]
AMY: Melty!
-Huh?
-So it was you, after all!
-Amy.
Amy!
Gargantia's gonna be attacked!
-Melty!
-She pushed herself
way too much.
She flew all the way here
by herself on a surf kite.
-Mm.
[all gasp]
-Oh, Melty!
-S-- Saaya.
Amy.
RIDGET: To ensure the
safety of Gargantia,
we have no choice but
to do as Melty say.
We must change
course and evacuate.
From where things stand now,
I think that we should all--
AMY: Wait!
RIDGET: Amy!
--[panting] Melty told
me something else.
She said that Ledo's going
to fight so that we might all
be able to escape.
-[gasp]
-What did you say?
-I said Ledo's going
to fight for us,
and he's doing it all alone.
He's even going to turn
against one of his own,
just to give us a chance.
And we're just gonna let
him while we run away?
Are you really OK with that?
-It's just--
DR. OLDHAM: If that's what
Ledo has chosen to do,
then we have to make
a choice, as well.
-What do you mean, Doctor?
-Fleet Commander, it appears the
time has come to use that key.
[gasp]
Heaven's Ladder.
-Huh?
[crowd murmurs]
-Are you serious?
As Gargantia's resident
sage, it is my responsibility
to offer counsel to
the fleet commander.
The time has come.
Amy, I will require
your assistance.
-Uh?
Mm.
COMMANDER KUGEL (ON
COMM): The whole world
shall be made aware of my grand
design and the great power
of Almighty God.
I declare this the beginning
of a new holy crusade.
We will bring absolute
order to this planet.
We will create a peaceful
and glorious Utopia here.
We will reshape this
world for the better,
and we will be victorious.
Follow me, my fellow citizens,
on the only path that
will lead to eternal
happiness and salvation.
[rumbling]
[screaming]
[gasps]
-Ledo.
[squeaking]
Ensign Ledo, what kind
of madness is this?
-You're the one
that's mad, Kugel.
-Is that any way for a soldier
of the Alliance to talk?
-This is Earth.
It's not the Galactic Alliance.
-The human race
resides on this planet.
That means the responsibility
for their fate is in our hands.
-In our hands?
No!
It's theirs!
The people on this planet
built their own world.
You have no right to destroy it.
-Our ultimate objective
remains the same.
Don't waver now.
[digital warning beep]
-Uh?
[blast]
[crowd screams]
-Stop.
Do nothing.
This is a battle between gods.
[crowd screams]
-She has so much power!
CHAMBER: Hypothesis.
Instead of an
internal generator,
Striker is using an
external energy source.
-She's been conserving power?
COMMANDER KUGEL (ON
COMM): Ledo, our mission
is to bring a new sense of order
and stability to this world.
[boom]
LEDO: Pinion.
This is my fight!
Get out of here, now!
-Shut up, kid!
We may not always get along, but
this guy pretending to be God
makes me 10,000 times
more pissed off.
-Ready?
Here's two.
-Hm!
-Go!
Kill him!
[explosions]
[crowd exclaims]
PRIESTESS: What was that?
[explosions]
-Attention all citizens
not involved in the fight.
Take shelter behind
the bulkheads.
Prepare the lifeboats.
This ship is the
flagship of our fleet.
It will likely be
their primary target.
-How dare they?
No one stands against us.
Insurrection will
not be tolerated!
[gasp] It's her!
[crash]
-Sorry.
This is not going
to be ladylike!
[screaming]
You're more of a
man than I thought.
You do have balls.
-Oh, knock it off!
Just take out those
guys and get over here!
-With pleasure.
[machine gun fire]
CHAMBER: I am having difficulty
securing a strategic advantage.
Suggestion-- employ
hit-and-run tactics.
Concentrate your attacks on the
enemy Machine Caliber's head.
-I don't want to kill Kugel.
CHAMBER: Enemy
maneuverability is superior.
Take evasive action.
-[cries out]
COMMANDER KUGEL
(ON COMM): The weak
serve and support the strong,
and the strong, in turn,
protect the weak.
This rationale is
what makes humans.
Am I wrong?
-Ledo!
Damn!
[gasp]
-Uh?
-(SHOUTING) Fire, now!
-Aah!
-(SHOUTING) Take that, bastards!
-Pinion!
PINION: Oh, yeah!
-Generator, maximize!
[boom]
[crowd exclaims]
COMMANDER KUGEL (ON
COMM): Now Ledo,
how would you like to
help me change this world?
-I've reached his cockpit.
Input emergency release code.
COMMANDER KUGEL (ON COMM):
It won't be so hard,
now that you're here.
[gasp]
COMMANDER KUGEL (ON
COMM): (HALTINGLY)
Are you willing to
follow my command again?
[static]
-Commander!
STRIKER: Affectation
control system rebooting.
-Aaahhh!
STRIKER: Ensign Ledo, your
resistance here is meaningless.
[gasp]
[theme music]