-You're saying this is Earth?
-Hm?
-It's hovering!
-[gasps]
-The current threat level
has climbed by 225%.
I propose a preemptive attack.
-No, wait, Chamber.
Tell them in their language
that we mean them no harm.
-Discontinue attack.
-(STAMMERS) It talked!
-We are not enemies.
-Is there something
inside that thing?
CHAMBER: Please
lower your weapons.
-I am the fleet
commander's aide.
I am Ridget.
Identify yourself.
CHAMBER: The female is asking
for your name and affiliation.
-Right, understood.
-[non-english speech]
-"I am pilot of the
anti-Hideauze annihilation
weapon, Chamber, Ensign Ledo."
-Ledo.
-"Annihilation weapon."
What the hell is "Hideauze"?
-Enemy.
Coexistence is impossible.
You are all fellow humans.
Join us in the Alliance.
We request a dialogue.
Who is your commander?
-Chamber, what did you say?
CHAMBER: In their language,
I requested a dialogue
with their commander and told
them of the Alliance's purpose.
-Good.
But why are they still
acting hostile towards us?
-Drop your weapon and
come out of there now.
-What is she saying?
CHAMBER: Unclear.
This machine is unmanned.
-Huh?
How can that be?
[theme music]
-Amy, you're late.
-I had to make up all the time
I lost doing my deliveries.
So what's up?
-I want to know what you
think about that boy.
-Well, you talked to
him, too, Ridget, right?
-Yes, but you're the one
who's come in closest contact
with him.
Your thoughts?
-Um.
Normal?
-Huh?
-Well, you see, it was like
this was his first time here,
so he was real
surprised and all.
And it really didn't seem like
he wanted to do me any harm.
Although he did kind
of touch my butt.
-Your what?
-But I did sort
of understand what
the person inside the
Yunboro was trying to say.
Why don't you try
just asking him?
-You've got to be kidding!
What do we do if he goes wild?
He's the guy who
wrecked the hangar
without even breaking a sweat.
-Pinion, you examined
that Yunboroid thoroughly,
didn't you?
-Yeah.
And I've got absolutely no
idea how it's put together.
I couldn't even fit
a knife into a seam.
That thing's tough.
-Bellows, anything unusual
when you brought it up?
-No, I just did
what this guy asked
me to do, which was
to pull something up
that he said looked valuable.
By the way, the crane
is totally trashed!
I didn't think that Yunboro
was going to be so damn heavy.
I'll send you a bill.
-Huh?
It's trashed because
you have no skills!
BELLOWS: What was that?
--[sighs] Now,
Commander Fairlock.
FAIRLOCK (ON RADIO):
Yes, I'm listening.
-I feel that Yunboroid is the
product of advanced technology.
RIDGET (ON RADIO):
It's possible.
I'd like to take it
apart and study it.
Hm.
-That's right!
That mech's different from
anything we've ever dredged up.
Let's bust the
thing open, already!
I say we take down the kid
and drag out the guy inside
and sink them both!
FAIRLOCK (ON RADIO):
We're not doing that.
What if there are others?
Think about it.
Attacking it could
endanger the whole fleet.
-I understand your
reasoning, but--
-Man, what a drag.
-The fleet commander
is absolutely right.
-They could easily
wipe us all out.
CHAMBER: Ensign Ledo, I fail to
see the logic in your actions.
Please explain why we are
prolonging this stalemate.
This machine has
more than enough
armaments to deal with
the current situation.
-Right now, this
is our best option.
CHAMBER: Reasonable
course of action.
Overpower the arms
and subdue them.
Neutralize their nerve center
and suppress any retaliation.
LEDO: Chamber, our
immediate priority
is establishing
contact with our troops
and determining our location.
If you can't figure
that out, then we'll
have to rely on them
and any information
that they might have.
CHAMBER: Agreed.
With reservations.
-What's important here is
that Earth, as we discovered,
is able to support life.
We were taught that
abnormal solar activity had
made the Earth a
frozen, dead planet.
But this is the reality.
CHAMBER: Agreed.
LEDO: Securing a
habitable planet
has been the Alliance's
greatest wish.
If this world has
abundant water and air,
it could easily replace
Avalon and become our new hub.
CHAMBER: I believe
that judgment goes
beyond the limitations
of your post.
-Hm, you're right.
Have you made contact yet?
CHAMBER: I am continuously
broadcasting a distress signal.
I have received no reply.
If you continue to
operate independently,
you will not be able to obtain
necessary supplies, which
will then cause
metabolic issues.
Reasonable course of
action-- to consider
escaping these surroundings
and returning to cryo-stasis.
-[puffs]
-Hey!
Hey, Pinion!
-Huh?
-Who the hell is
going to fix my boat?
-I don't know!
-See you!
-Good work!
-Amy!
[giggles]
So what's the merman like?
-The merman?
-Yeah, you know, the boy
that took you hostage.
Is he handsome?
How old is he?
-Everywhere I go, people keep
bugging me to ask you about it.
-Jeez!
You're interrupting my work!
SAAYA: Hey, Amy!
Don't jump until the
wings are spread!
MELTY: You need to
be more careful!
-So I'm supposed to
keep my mouth shut
after Ridget and the others
snatched my special treasure?
We're going to search
the exact same spot.
[door opens]
AMY: Bebel, I'm back!
-Welcome home, sis.
-Hi!
Sorry, I'm so late.
-Hey, are you OK?
I heard someone
took you hostage.
-Yeah, he did.
But I'm fine.
I'm so lucky he
wasn't a bad guy.
It seems his name is Ledo.
-Ledo?
So what's this guy like?
-I don't know.
I'd guess he's about my age.
He's got pretty slim
arms, so he really
doesn't look at that manly.
-Oh?
-And there's another one who's
still inside the huge Yunboro.
He can speak our language.
Enough to understand him anyway.
-It'd be good if they could
talk things over with them
and become friends, right?
-Exactly!
That's what I've been
thinking, too, but-- oh.
I brought you something.
-Huh?
Hah!
Thank you!
AMY: Can you use it?
-Mm-hm.
Ha-ha!
A perfect fit!
Thanks a lot, Amy!
-[giggles]
I'm glad.
-You know, I wish I
could talk to Ledo, too.
-Hm?
-I mean, after all, he might
have come from the sky.
-Huh?
-From the sky?
Ledo?
-Yeah.
You know all the legends, right?
About the people who
escaped to the stars way
back when the Earth
became frozen?
-Aw, come on!
It's just a fairytale.
And besides, that
Yunboro was brought up
from the bottom of the ocean.
-Mm-mm.
I'll bet you anything that
they came down here from space.
The people that escaped so long
ago have finally come home.
-Space, huh?
I don't know why they
bother coming all this way.
-Dr. Oldham once told me that
if a ship could travel straight
up in the sky, it would reach
space in just half a day.
-Oh?
CHAMBER: Someone is approaching.
PINION: I don't know about this.
RIDGET: The fleet commander
said that we shouldn't provoke
him, which is perfectly
understandable.
But we can't just sit here.
-And so you chose her?
-We had no other volunteers.
Would you like to?
-Yeah, right.
CHAMBER: Hypothesis.
The threat level is minimum.
It is possible that she
has been sent as an envoy.
-Envoy?
But she's a kid.
CHAMBER: Shall I intercept her?
-No, not necessary.
CHAMBER: Roger.
-Uh.
CHAMBER: It is the corpse
of an aquatic organism.
-Corpse?
-Hm.
-Ugh, what is it she wants?
CHAMBER: Hypothesis.
It is edible.
-So she wants me to eat it?
CHAMBER: Hypothesis.
It is a friendship ritual.
-Um.
But it's a corpse.
CHAMBER: I will leave the
decision to you, Ensign.
-[sighs]
Chamber, ask her what
her objective is.
CHAMBER: [non-english speech]
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER: She seeks conversation.
-All right.
-Hey!
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER: She says
her name is Amy.
She would like to know
from where you originated.
-Huh?
The sky?
So you two are
soldiers, and you're
fighting in a war against
those Hideauze thingies?
CHAMBER: Correct.
-Then are you
stronger than them?
-Super strong.
-Oh, you're really from space?
Then Bebel was absolutely
right about you.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER: "This planet
Earth is different from how
it appears in our records.
I seek an explanation."
-You're getting
better and better
at speaking our language.
Interpreting must
be really tough.
Won't you , at least,
show me your face?
-What is meant by
"show my face"?
-I mean that there is one more
person inside of there, right?
-There is no one inside.
-Huh?
Oh!
It really is empty!
-I am an Autonomous Pilot
Support Enlightenment Interface
System.
-System?
Then that machine is
talking all on its own?
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER: "Chamber is an
artificial intelligence
that aids in battle and in
maintaining life support."
-So cool!
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
There's really no one in here!
You're a machine!
CHAMBER: I will repeat the
earlier question regarding
Earth in its current state.
-Wow, wow, wow!
[squeals]
We were taught that it was
once a giant lump of ice.
But then one day, it melted
and became a water planet.
Long ago, there were
supposedly places called land.
But I really don't get that.
Anyway, everyone in the world
lives on ships like this.
All grouped together.
We find ancient
ships and materials
that are at the
bottom of the sea,
and we hoist them all
out, like Gargantia.
Uh, that's the
name of this fleet.
We brought it up, too.
CHAMBER: Gargantia?
-Yup.
Gargantia.
-Do more exist?
-Hm.
Oh, there are lots of
other fleets out there.
Small ones, big ones.
When ships join up, it doesn't
take long to form a fleet.
And there are pains in the neck
out there, too, like pirates.
-[non-english speech]
CHAMBER: "Are pirates
your enemies?"
-Yeah, I guess so.
[rumbling]
Look, it's all right.
It's the Milky Way.
Sometimes called a sea galaxy.
Look at it.
It's so beautiful.
Thank goodness.
Now, we can travel
on a new Milky Way.
CHAMBER: What is a Milky Way?
AMY: It's a glowing path
that runs through the sea.
None of us would be able
to survive without it.
So the ships all forge
ahead, staying on that path.
But there's no guarantee that
the path will go on forever.
And when it disappears, we
search for a new sea galaxy
and switch over to that path.
-Uh.
-Lightbugs are what
makes sea galaxies glow.
They're swarms of tiny organisms
that accumulate electricity.
We get all the electricity we
need from this band of light.
-Uh!
AMY: It's so pretty!
-[non-english speech]
-What?
-What is the analysis of
our present coordinates?
-Due to the existence
of an atmosphere,
lack of information,
and the limitations
of optical analysis,
further observation
is required to derive
our current coordinates.
-Uh.
-Hm.
I'm telling you, it's true!
I think.
-You'd think they'd come up
with a better lie than that.
-If that really is
a talking machine.
-It is!
-Honestly.
Even if it's true, a
war with an alien race?
-It's unlikely.
But that aside, I say
we should find out
for sure if it can talk
or not by taking it apart.
Then throw the kid overboard!
-Seriously?
He's in trouble and
has nowhere else to go.
Everyone should listen
to what Ledo has to say.
-Having undue contact
with an outsider
wouldn't benefit either side.
Not for the sea and
neither for space.
MAN: Confirming terrain.
There's no mistake.
This is where we
found that Yunboro.
-Right!
Let's get it
together and do this!
LEDO: They've got an abundance
of basic commodities.
The threat level of
these natives is low.
-Agreed.
With reservations.
-We can't get back on our own.
All we can do is
wait for our troops
to notice our distress signal.
Our best option is to look for
a cooperative relationship.
-Agreed.
LEDO: "The front," "troops."
The people who
live on this planet
wouldn't be able to comprehend
what those words mean.
The struggle against the
Hideauze has no meaning here.
[siren blares]
-Huh!
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-Hey!
What's going on?
-A salvage ship is being
attacked by pirates.
Bellows' ship.
-Bellows and the
others are-- oh.
-We're in trouble.
They've got us surrounded.
Escort, Commander.
-It's no good!
There are way too many of them!
-Salvage team.
Secure yourselves
underwater, now!
-I detect several new
sources of engine noise.
-What are they?
AMY: Ledo!
-Amy?
[gunfire]
-They're using kites?
MAN: The enemy has nine ships
and several small craft.
They're starting a kite attack!
-Reinforcements?
-They're not going
to make it in time.
-Enemies?
-You two are strong, aren't you?
That's a super-strong
Yunboro, right?
Do something.
Please help us.
CHAMBER: She seeks assistance.
-I accept.
This will be a good
bargaining chip.
Activate floater!
-It's that Yunboro!
It's starting to move!
-What did you say?
-What are they doing?
-Lift off.
[men laughing]
-Hey, you're Bellows from
Gargantia, aren't you?
-You've got what you came for.
Now, get the hell out!
-I think it's time
you finally dumped
that rinky-dink fleet
you're with and joined us.
Empress Lukkage's noticed
you and your skills.
-Hah!
Don't make me laugh,
you filthy pirate scum!
-Oh?
-[shrieks]
-What are you doing?
-You should think a little
harder before refusing.
-You bastard!
[machine whirring]
-Huh?
CHAMBER: Identification of
main enemy targets complete.
I advise we identify
smaller targets.
-Do it.
CHAMBER: Identification
complete.
Deflector beam on standby.
-Annihilate all targets.
-Huh?
-Ugh!
-What the hell is--
-Uh.
Huh?
This is horrible.
-What just happened?
[music playing]