‐ [Ruri] Mars.
The planet of war
and destruction.
The planet of death.
The ancient Babylonians
called it Nergal,
the namesake for the
company that sent us here.
Having found only new
mysteries and deaths
on the red planet, we fled,
although our final
destination is unknown.
Kind of typical, isn’t it?
("You Get to Burning"
by Yumi Matsuzawa)
(singing in foreign language)
(lasers firing)
(loud explosions)
‐ Gravitron waves increasing
in Chulip Force One, sir!
‐ What?
‐ It’s off the scale, sir.
Something huge is
coming through.
‐ Bring up the main guns.
And if those don’t work,
we’ll ram the gladiola
down their throats!
‐ [Man] Whatever it
is sir, here it comes!
‐ Huh?
That can’t be what
I think it is.
(loud explosion)
‐ [All] It’s the Nadesico!
(machine beeping)
‐ The Nadesico has
returned to normal space.
I’m now calculating
our current position.
Will everyone
please wake up now?
Um, hello?
It’s time to get up.
May I have your attention?
Your attention please.
Wake up now.
Please return to your
assigned positions
and begin your emergency
alert checklists.
Captain.
Captain, wake up.
‐ Ah!
‐ The ship has returned
to normal space, captain.
May I ask why you’re
in the recreation area
instead of on the bridge?
‐ Huh?
(screams)
(dramatic music)
Stop that!
‐ [Ruri] Captain?
‐ What’s going on Ruri?
‐ There’s something outside
that I believe you
should look at captain.
‐ Oh my gosh,
we’re under attack!
Configure the gravity blast
cannon to maximum spread.
Fire at will, Ruri!
‐ Have you gone out of
your mind, you imbecile!
You’re just lucky
that none of us were
in the direct path of the blast
so there weren’t any casualties!
As it is we’ll be
shipping their dollar bill
for the 2066 jockey
shorts that were ruined.
Sansley out!
(sighs)
‐ I said that we were sorry.
‐ Maybe he’ll calm down
once his ship cools off.
‐ Ruri, how bad were the
damages to the second fleet?
‐ By that I assume you mean
the ones that we inflicted.
Fortunately, there were
only five serious injuries
and no deaths.
‐ Still, we can’t
deny that we did
almost vaporize most of them.
‐ True.
And considering that we were
just saved by another admiral,
this is pretty embarrassing.
‐ [Goat] Yes, if you
had been on the bridge,
you would have had a
better understanding
of the situation.
‐ By the way, Akito,
just how did you, me
and Fressange get down there?
‐ What were you doing?
Inquiring minds
want to know.
‐ Now wait a second!
‐ [Megumi] Yeah, I’d
like to know as well!
‐ Well...
‐ How could you sneak
off during an alert?
It’s disgraceful!
If Miss Fressange
hadn’t been there,
I’ll bet the two of
you would’ve been‐‐
‐ [Both] Doing what?
‐ Oh!
‐ I don’t know what happened
or how we got there!
If you’re all so hung
up on finding out,
why don’t you just
ask Miss Fressange!
She’s still asleep?
‐ [All] Mm hmm.
‐ Wait, that doesn’t
mean anything at all.
‐ [All] Uh huh, uh huh.
‐ Will you all just shut up!
If my Tenkawa says that
he didn’t do anything,
then we should trust him!
Not that I really care anyway.
‐ [Both] My?
‐ Huh?
What does that mean?
‐ You just called him
my Tenkawa, Ryoko.
‐ How possessive.
‐ Will you two keep
the channels clear?
We’re supposed to be on standby!
‐ [Both] My Tenkawa, my
Tenkawa, my Tenkawa, my Tenkawa.
‐ By the way, the
enemy’s attacking.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Ryoko] All units, spread out!
Seek and destroy!
‐ [Hikaru] What’s our strategy?
‐ [Ryoko] Improvise!
(dramatic music)
‐ Maintain the fields
at maximum and standby.
Keep the gravity blast cannon
on continuous recharge.
‐ [Ruri] Roger, captain.
‐ [Yurika Voiceover] The
thing is, I don’t understand
how I got down there either.
I know I was here on the bridge.
‐ Not that I would
mind being down there
all alone with Akito.
‐ Hello captain,
I have some things
I need to talk to you about.
‐ We were all fully
clothed, weren’t we?
‐ Huh?
(laughs)
That may not look like
a private debriefing.
I’m sure it’s fine.
I think they just
want to go over
some new policies
and procedures.
‐ Oh.
‐ [Hikaru] (laughs) Got ya!
(dramatic music)
Huh?
I don’t believe it!
I only nailed three out of 10!
‐ [Izumi] It appears that
these grasshoppers have
a few legs up on us in
terms of defensive fields.
‐ [Hikaru] When
did they get those?
‐ Who cares how
many legs they have?
We’re still one up on them
when it comes to
hand to hand combat!
Alright, that takes
care of those lizards,
but where in the
heck is Tenkawa?
‐ [Both] Who?
‐ Will you two knock it off?
Tenkawa!
Tenkawa?
Where are you Tenkawa?
(dramatic music)
Tenkawa, why aren’t
you responding
to your radio, you idiot?
Do you need assistance?
‐ It’s too late!
(gun fires)
(screams)
‐ Hold on Akito, just
keep it calm and go back.
‐ Tenkawa, we’re coming
as fast as we can.
‐ [Ruri] He’s been
surrounded captain.
‐ There’s something
wrong with me.
‐ He’s freaking!
‐ Calm down!
‐ [Akito] My hands won’t move!
‐ Akito.
‐ [Hikaru] Try to
imagine that all
the grasshoppers are naked‐‐
‐ We’ve got to help him!
‐ No goddammit!
Just hold on five
more seconds Akito!
(yells)
(breathing heavily)
‐ What in the hell’s
wrong with me?
I thought I’d
beaten this already.
I wasn’t afraid but
now it’s back again.
(breathing heavily)
(heart beating)
(screams)
‐ [Ryoko] Tenkawa!
‐ [Nagare] Stay back!
It’s about to get
extremely dangerous here!
You three return
immediately to base.
Don’t just stand there.
Do it!
‐ Just who do you think
you’re talking to!
Huh?
‐ [Ruri] 20% of the enemy
have been vaporized.
‐ I don’t believe it!
‐ Second blast approaching.
‐ Wow.
‐ A multi‐barreled
gravity blast cannon.
‐ Huh?
But that means...
‐ Oh!
That’s a brand new
model of Aestavalis!
A new frame, a new generator!
Look at that head, look
at those thrusters!
Oh, it’s so smooth, I’m
in love, I’m in love!
‐ [All] Geez, what a loser.
‐ But I don’t understand
how they could have made
a new model so soon.
‐ Yeah, and didn’t
those liars tell us
that our sweet little
Aesties were the latest
state of the art
just two months ago?
‐ Ah, but you see,
that’s not exactly right.
(machine whirring)
Actually, it’s been eight months
since the Nadesico
disappeared from Mars,
during which time the
Earth has been steadily
reinforcing its arsenal.
‐ [Man] Who the heck are you?
‐ I’m Nagare Akatsuki.
From the space
battleship Cosmos.
‐ So if you understand captain,
we sincerely hope
that you will accept
the terms and conditions
we’ve just given you.
Otherwise I’m afraid
that the Nadesico
could be severely
damaged in the cross fire
between the Earth’s space forces
and the Jovian lizards.
‐ Well, it’s just that
this is so sudden.
‐ Mm.
Well, I’m sure we can
have a nice meeting
and draft up the proper forms.
‐ Very well.
I’ll arrange to
have the Cosmos dock
with the Nadesico.
‐ The Cosmos?
‐ Yes, the Nadesico’s
sister ship, the Cosmos.
(triumphant music)
‐ We are now receiving
guidance beams.
‐ Roger that.
Wow.
It’s all automated!
(triumphant music)
‐ It is now obvious that passing
through a Chulip entails
far more than just
simple teleportation.
Eight months have passed
since we left Mars.
During this time, Nergal
has settled its differences
with United Earth forces,
and has begun building
new battleships for them.
Together, the two have
reclaimed the surface
of the moon from the enemy.
And based on my project‐‐
‐ Yes, that’s very
interesting Inez.
However, at the moment,
our main interest must be
on what this entails
for this vessel.
Captain?
‐ What it means is
that the Nadesico
has been reassigned and
that we will be integrated
into the United Earth
navy’s far eastern command.
‐ [All] Huh?
‐ Are you saying that
we’ll have to do what
those idiots tell us to do?
‐ No not at all.
Simply means that we’ll
cooperate for a while.
‐ And you would be?
‐ Nagare Akatsuki,
at your service.
Think of us as the
privateers of old,
flying our own flag but rallying
around the cause of liberty.
After all, it’d be a
shame to spoil a hand
such as this with the
duties of a common soldier.
‐ And what about Mars?
‐ Yeah!
Minato’s right.
What about Mars?
Are we just going to abandon it?
‐ [Prospector] Do you
really think we can succeed
if we went back?
‐ But we‐‐
‐ No I’m afraid that
we have no chance
of defeating the
Jovians on Mars.
So until there is a
reasonable hope of victory,
the Nadesico is far better
utilized defending the Earth.
‐ [Jun] Strategically speaking,
it would make more sense
to cooperate with
the United Forces.
‐ [Seiya] Now wait a second.
I’m not sure I like the idea
of becoming mercenaries.
‐ [Nagare] If you don’t like it,
you can always just
collect your back pay
and get off the ship, you know.
(triumphant music)
‐ [Man] Hello class!
Today we have a new student!
This is Genji Akara.
‐ I’m Akara, it’s nice
to meet all of you.
(girls squeal)
‐ [Boy] Damn it, I’m
better looking than he is.
‐ By the great lizard!
Is it possible that earthlings
have the same capacity
to love as we do?
This is an amazing
discovery I’ve made!
‐ Huh?
‐ Oh, excuse me, but
your door was open and...
‐ And what!?
‐ Rokotsu!
He’s going in for a kill!
Huh?
‐ [Man] Let’s go everyone!
‐ [Man] It’s time to
launch Gekigangar!
‐ It can’t be!
Ken and his friends are
the pilots of Gekigangar?
(laughs)
‐ You don’t have to
watch it, you know.
‐ I just don’t get it.
‐ No, I’d say that it’s
obvious that you don’t.
‐ What I don’t get
is how you can be
such a fan of this anime stuff
and not welcome the integration
of the Nadesico into the
United Armed services.
(growls)
‐ [Akito] Just who the hell
are you anyway?
‐ Hi Akito.
‐ [Nagare] I’m just a man
who enjoys a good fight.
Not unlike yourself,
I would imagine.
You do know that the
image feedback system
tends to stimulate a person’s
aggressive instincts,
don’t you?
‐ I never asked for this!
I got my implant so I
could do my job on Mars!
Why does everyone here have
such a hard time understanding
that I just don’t
like to fight!?
‐ So, what you’re saying
is that you’re afraid?
‐ Hell, I’m not scared of you.
‐ Let’s not fight Tenkawa.
But how about a nice
game of one on one?
(screaming)
By the way, I was about
to say that the gravity
in this room has been
lowered to zero G.
But I guess it’s
a little late now.
(screaming)
What’s wrong Akito?
n’t ylike your anime heroes?
‐ Aw, shut up!
‐ Look, Tenkawa!
The trick is to create
a counter force.
‐ Oh dammit I’ll counter
your force in my‐‐
What?
Oh!
‐ [Nagare] (laughing) See?
That’s all you needed.
‐ Shut up!
This is basketball!
In a real fight, I would’ve‐‐
‐ Enemy fleet approaching!
Aestavalis pilots,
prepare for war.
‐ What the hell are
you waiting for,
a great invitation?
Get moving!
(adventurous music)
‐ [Man] Don’t let them
lure you out of formation.
‐ [All] Roger!
‐ Well, you wanted a real fight.
‐ Shut up!
‐ [Ryoko] Assume
closet formation!
‐ [All] Roger!
‐ [Akito] Oh, oh.
Hey, hey, ah!
‐ I like it.
A very safe and reliable
method of engagement.
‐ I didn’t become a pilot
so I could be a soldier.
‐ Then why are you still
on board the Nadesico?
(engine whirring)
‐ Ah!
Dammit I didn’t join the
Nadesico to fight at all!
I just wanted to be a cook!
Ah! (yelling)
‐ Huh?
Hey Akito, let go
of the grasshopper!
‐ I don’t think he can hear you.
‐ Akito!
‐ [Akito] Ah!
‐ [Ruri] Pilot Tenkawa’s
Aestavalis is entering
the moon’s shadow.
His graviton power
beam has been severed.
‐ [Goat] I’m afraid
he’s lost at space.
‐ Lost in space?
‐ [Goat] Could he get back
to the Nadesico on his own?
‐ [Inez] I’m afraid not.
‐ Without the gravitron beam
to feed his Aestavalis energy,
his only source of power
is his back up battery.
That’s five minutes of thrust.
‐ Well in girl scouts they said
that the best thing
to do when you’re lost
is to stay in one place.
So I doubt he’ll
try to go very far.
(women groan)
‐ [Woman] His chances
of making it back
would increase greatly
if the Nadesico
were to get closer to him.
‐ Unfortunately the
Nadesico’s weapon systems
are still down for repairs.
If we took off right now,
we’d be sitting ducks.
‐ Akatsuki.
Do you know if the Cosmos has
any standard fighters onboard?
(engine starting)
‐ You’ve got four
hours worth of fuel.
Come back if it gets
too hairy out there.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I didn’t realize you were
going after him personally.
I wouldn’t have
thought a captain would
get so involved in a rescue.
‐ Oh I’m one of that
new type of captain.
But on the other
hand, you haven’t had
any zero gravity combat
training, Megumi.
‐ True, but I had
a pilot’s license
even before I joined Nergal.
And there’s nothing
you can say to keep me
from coming captain.
‐ Okay Jun.
I’m entrusting you with my baby.
‐ Mm hmm.
I’ll take good care of her.
(engine thrusting)
‐ Eight hours until my
power reserves give out.
Although my air will give
out long before that.
Huh?
Someone’s shooting at someone.
Not much I can do either way.
Not without a power feed.
Wait!
Jettisoning feet!
I can’t believe that worked!
It’s like something out of
an episode of Gekigangar!
(laughs)
(screaming)
‐ Are you alright Megumi?
‐ [Megumi] I’m losing
thruster control!
(screaming)
‐ [Both] Oh, you saved us!
‐ You’ll always be my knight
in shining armor Akito!
‐ Aren’t you afraid anymore?
‐ Well, when I
realized that I needed
to help you two, I
suddenly wasn’t afraid
of fighting anymore.
Just like before.
‐ You mean your love
overcame your fear?
‐ His love for who?
‐ Knock it off!
We’ve only got 30
minutes of oxygen left!
‐ Is that all?
‐ Well we’ve got three
people in just one ship.
‐ Exactly!
‐ [Yurika] Um, so
what are going to do?
‐ At this rate of
acceleration, we won’t be
in range of the Nadesico
for another two hours.
That’s not enough.
‐ By the time two
hours have gone by,
we’ll all be frozen solid.
‐ Okay!
Now if we deploy the
emergency solar sail,
we should be able to
accelerate even faster.
But it’s still 40 minutes.
‐ [Megumi] What about
that figure at the bottom.
How can we get there
in just 20 minutes?
‐ That’s if there
was only one person.
For two it’d take 30 minutes.
‐ [Megumi] So if one of us
got off, the remaining two
would reach the Nadesico
10 minutes earlier?
‐ [Yurika] Then the
others could refuel
and come back for
the one left behind.
‐ [Megumi] Yes, but
Akito has to stay because
he’s the only one who
can pilot an Aestavalis.
‐ [Yurika] Which means‐‐
‐ [Akito] I have to decide.
Yurika.
‐ [Yurika] Um, is that
because I’m heavier?
‐ [Akito] No, it’s
because I’d have
to come back for you.
‐ [Yurika] Oh why, Akito!
‐ Well maybe I should get off!
‐ Forget it Megumi!
Not only do I have
better survival training,
I’m much larger every
place it counts.
‐ [Megumi] Not every place,
in case you hadn’t noticed.
‐ [Yurika] Only proportionately.
‐ [Megumi] Well that’s
beside the point.
‐ [Akito Voiceover] Gai.
What would Gai do?
‐ He’d go for it!
Deploying solar sail!
‐ Wait Akito!
I’m supposed to jump
off the ship, remember?
‐ It’s alright.
We’ll all go together.
The military may have
to sacrifice something
to save something
else but I don’t.
We’ll make it work
somehow, just like Gai.
Into danger, Gekigangar.
‐ I think we just
ran out of energy.
‐ I’m sorry girls, we must
have strayed off course!
Or maybe there wasn’t
enough acceleration!
‐ It’s not your fault!
‐ Yes, that’s right.
‐ Akito, you’ve always been
my knight in shining armor,
and you’ve always done
the very best you could.
I know this will work out!
‐ You mean the only
reason you like Akito is
because he’s always
there to help you?
‐ Huh?
‐ I see.
That’s not why I love him.
‐ But you do love
him, don’t you?
He’s very special to us in
different kinds of ways.
But maybe different
kinds of love
can be equally strong.
‐ Well as long as
we’re baring our souls,
what were you thinking the
first time you kissed me?
‐ Huh?
‐ Excuse me, but
just how many times
have you kissed her anyway?
‐ Huh?
Me?
‐ I wanna know too!
‐ So do I!
‐ I wouldn’t mind knowing.
‐ I really couldn’t care less.
‐ [All] Huh?
‐ [Megumi] Hey, if
our communications
have been restored...
‐ You’re the last
person I’d imagine
taking a risk like this.
‐ (laughs) What fun would it be
without a little competition.
‐ Hey Akatsuki.
I’m going to stay
on the Nadesico.
‐ So you finally come around.
That’s good.
I knew there was a
warrior there inside you.
‐ No, let’s just say I found
something worth protecting.
Gai.
My friend Gai didn’t want
to fight a war either,
but he realized that the
Earth was worth protecting
and worth any sacrifice.
By protecting the Nadesico‐‐
‐ Oh, it’s just like Gekigangar!
‐ Yeah, that sounds like
something he’d say, alright.
‐ I’m back!
I bet you thought you’d
seen the last of me, right?
‐ [All] Huh?
‐ Yes, Admiral Munatake
has been assigned
to our ship as the United
Earth forces liaison.
‐ It’s cool!
Really!
‐ And I’m Erino Won.
I’ve been assigned
to the Nadesico
as your new co‐helmswoman.
‐ Yes, that’s right!
Damn it, what is the chairman’s
secretary doing here?
‐ [Erino] Well, I
certainly didn’t expect
to find you onboard.
‐ [Nagare] Will
I be in your way?
‐ [Erino] Of course.
‐ [Nagare] So, what is this?
‐ [Erino] Akito Tenkawa,
the moment the Nadesico
jumped from Mars.
‐ How interesting.
‐ (laughs) Oh yes.
Very.
("Being Myself" by
Houko Fuwashima)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Announcer] Look
out for icebergs!
The Nadesico is sent
to the Arctic Ocean
on a mysterious rescue mission.
Will Akito make it back
from a deadly journey
over the frozen sea?
Or will he succumb to the
frigid sleep of icy death?
On the other hand, with the
way his love life is going,
will he even want to come back?
He’ll need all that
ice just to cool off
as the battle for Akito’s
heart really begins to heat up!
You’ll get to see the girls
in incredibly short skirts
in the next thrilling episode
of Martian Successor Nadesico,
Operation Miracle The Kiss!