‐ Well, the Nadesico has
joined the United Earth Forces,
but either they don’t want us
or they don’t know
what to do with us.
We’ve had two new arrivals,
both of whom are clueless
and extremely annoying.
Very irritating people.
And what began as
a love triangle
is now a septagon by my count.
It’s really getting hopeless.
(upbeat jazz music
in foreign language)
(space ship flying)
‐ Chulip detected entering
Earth defense sphere.
Chulip now entering second
defensive line airspace.
(rockets launching)
(explosions)
(explosion)
The Nadesico has been
selected to investigate
a new type of Chulip
that apparently
landed on Tunisian Island.
And why was that?
Because of my leadership!
That’s right, the Supreme
Commander has finally
noticed how I’ve turned
this ship around.
So where the hell is my crew?
Why hasn’t anyone
come to the bridge
to listen to my
brilliant orders?
What’s going on here?
‐ Well, as a wild guess it
might be because it’s two am.
That’s the middle of the night
in case you didn’t know, sir.
Everybody who has any
sense is probably asleep!
(Admiral yelling)
‐ The Nadesico is
a combat vessel!
You can’t just shut it down!
Hey, wait a minute,
you’re the helmswoman!
You’ve got to stay at your post
untirelieved you!
‐ Sorry, but it’s
the end of my shift.
‐ [Admiral] What!?
Come back here!
I’m an admiral, damn it!
Listen to me when
I’m talking to you!
I’ll report you to the captain
for insubordination, damn it!
‐ [Erina] We’re going
to Tunisian Island?
Hmm, on the Equator.
White sand beaches.
I’m afraid this place sounds
entirely too appealing.
‐ [Yurika] Doesn’t
that look good?
But we all know what
boys like, right?
If that Migumi is
gonna play dirty
then I’ll fight fire with fire!
After all the way to a man’s
heart is through his stomach!
‐ I wondered why
she wanted to use
the kitchen, but now I see.
‐ Ahh, yes.
(jazzy lounge music)
Bon appetite, Akito!
‐ Wow!
(Akito yelling)
‐ My tongue has died
and gone to heaven!
‐ (laughing) You like it?
‐ It was perfect. Only one thing
might taste more wonderful.
‐ I’m willing to cook
anything you want, Akito.
‐ That one thing is the
taste of your sweet lips.
‐ Oh, Akito.
(food burning)
‐ [Yurika] (screaming)
Oh, no! It’s burning!
Fire! What’s going on?
‐ Tenkawa sure is unlucky.
(microwave beeping)
(slurping)
‐ How depressing.
There’s nothing more
lonely than eating
instant noodles by yourself
for sixteen days. Huh?
No, could it be? Do I see a
special meal baked with love?
Could it possibly be for me?
‐ Goodnight, Jun.
‐ Y‐Y‐Yurika.
‐ They’re all idiots.
‐ My gosh, are you okay, miss?
Do you have any idea
what happened to you?
‐ I don’t know. I
don’t know anything.
I don’t even know who I am!
‐ Huh? Now what? Right when
it’s getting good, too. Coming!
‐ Oh, Akito, how are you?
I was cooking and wondered
if you wanted to share it!
‐ I guess I could.
‐ Are you watching anime again?
‐ Yeah.
‐ This is the first time that
I’ve ever worn
clothing like this.
‐ [Yurika] Okay, so what’s
the story on this one, Akito?
‐ [Akito] Well, this is
episode thirty three,
"The Smile of Holy
Maiden Aquamarine."
That young girl is
really Aquamarine,
one of the twin
pilots of the enemies
Gemini robot, but
she gets amnesia
after a crash
landing, and winds up
falling in love with Ken.
Anyway, it turns
out that Aquamarine
is almost a perfect girl.
She’s pretty, great
at cooking, and‐‐
‐ You mean you like girls
who can cook, Akito?
Well, I made this just for you!
Please, try some!
‐ Um, well.
‐ Come on! Well,
go on, just dig in!
I’m sure you’ll love
it! Pretty please?
(Akito gagging)
(Akito struggling)
(Akito yelling)
‐ Oh, my gosh, Akito!
(coughing)
Akito, are you alright?
‐ Water! (grunting)
‐ Oh, my goodness! Akito!
‐ Water!
‐ Try this special
stamina drink I just made!
So what happened in here?
It smells like a
poison gas attack!
(Akito yelling)
‐ [Yurika] Just what in the
heck was in that stamina juice?
‐ Milk, water, vinegar,
Tabasco sauce, cod liver oil,
bourrignuesse, oatmeal
powdered mushrooms,
and a couple of different
energy drinks as a base.
(Akito yelling)
‐ Get out!
(girls screaming)
‐ [Doctor] What
did this idiot eat?
Get him to sick
bay on the double!
And incinerate that pan!
Is this some kind of new attack
the Jovians are trying out?
‐ I think it’s the
fatal poison of love.
‐ Oh, wow, oh, wow!
This is delicious!
You know, I always told
myself that the girl
I was gonna marry had
to be a great cook!
‐ [Aquamarine] Really?
‐ Please, Akito,
this time it really
does taste good, I’ve tested it!
‐ Don’t try hers, try mine!
‐ Akito, Akito!
‐ Just one bite, Akito!
(girls yelling)
(Akito yelling)
‐ (laughing) Die,
Geki Ganga Three.
‐ Akito?
‐ Is he dead?
‐ [TV Character] Aquamarine!
‐ [Ken] Aquamarine!
‐ Ken, my time
with you was great,
but I was so happy
while it lasted.
‐ Aquamarine, don’t do it!
‐ I must do this
because I love you!
Goodbye, Ken!
(yelling and explosions)
‐ [Ken] Aquamarine!
‐ Aquamarine.
‐ Oh, Ken!
‐ Man, wouldn’t it be great if
there really were
girls like her?
(spaceship humming)
‐ Land the Nadesico
by those reefs.
Are the landing parties
ready to go ashore?
‐ [Girls] Yes, sir.
‐ But before that,
Ruri Ruri, you’d better
take this special UV
blocker the lab made up.
‐ This is for me? How odd.
I’ve never been to
the ocean before.
(group celebrating)
‐ Take the beach, men!
‐ [Men] Yeah!
‐ Now wait just a
minute all of you!
Do you have any idea
what you’re doing?
You’re all still employees
of Nergal Heavy Industries.
And that means that the
time you spend playing
will be deducted from your pay.
I made these
brochures explaining
how to have fun at the beach.
Never go into deep water alone.
Always wear sandals
on rocky surfaces.
Don’t use sun tan lotions that
aren’t biodegradable, also‐‐
Oh, they could have
at least read it!
(group laughing)
‐ Come on, step right up!
What’s a trip to
the beach without
the ever popular greasy hot dog,
soggy ramen noodles,
and melted snowcones?
Fortunately for you I’m here
to continue that tradition!
Uribatake’s beachside deli
is now open for business!
‐ Ramen, please.
‐ You betcha!
(yelling)
Swish and swirl,
swish and swirl, swish
and swirl and rinse!
Now eat it!
‐ That’s nasty.
‐ That’s the tradition, kiddo.
‐ Mr. Tenkawa. I have a few
things I’d like to ask you.
You were born on
Mars, weren’t you?
‐ Yeah, that’s right.
‐ Oh, excuse me.
Would you like some?
‐ I’m sorry, but‐‐ (yelling)
‐ Are you alright, Mr. Tenkawa?
(slurping)
That sucks.
‐ Where am I?
(grunting)
Oh, I’m really sorry, ma’am.
‐ At long last I’ve found you!
My prince charming!
(laughing)
‐ Aquamarine?
(theme music)
‐ What in the
hell? What is this?
Don’t you realize that
we’re on a special mission?
We’re supposed to be
searching for that new Chulip.
Don’t you know that? I wanna
know what we’re doing about it!
Hey, you, I just
asked you a question!
Why aren’t any of
you answering me?
Alright, I’ve had just
about enough of‐‐ (yelling)
‐ Alright! Let’s bury him!
(group cheering)
‐ Do you think you’ll
get away with this?
I’m an admiral, damn it!
I have powerful friends!
You can’t do this,
you cannot do this
to me you just‐‐
(yelling)
(gagging)
Okay, okay, okay you’ve had
your fun, now dig me out.
Hey, wait, come back here,
what do you think you’re doing?
(yelling)
(relaxing music)
‐ By the way, my name’s
Akito Tenkawa. What’s yours?
‐ Aqua. My name is Aqua Crimson.
‐ Aqua?
(laughing)
‐ I wonder where
Akito disappeared to?
‐ [Megumi] Akito!
(electric static)
‐ Hey, it’s a hat!
‐ And it’s a woman’s beach hat!
‐ [Both] A woman?
‐ [Aqua] This is all I could
cook up on such short notice.
Please, help yourself!
‐ Everything looks so wonderful!
Hey, that’s good!
‐ I’m so glad you like it!
Is something wrong, Akito?
‐ Oh, no, it’s nothing
at all, really.
But, Ms. Aqua?
‐ Please, it’s just Aqua.
‐ Okay, are you all
alone here, Aqua?
Where are your folks?
‐ My father and
mother are both dead.
I’m just an orphan all
alone in this world.
All alone by myself.
‐ Oh, I’m sorry.
‐ No, don’t be. I’m not!
(Aqua laughing)
‐ Alright! It’s time to
find that Chulip, pilots!
‐ Nag, nag, nag!
‐ Hey, you’re not leaving
without me, are you?
You wouldn’t do that, would you?
(yelling)
‐ Has anyone seen the captain?
You don’t suppose
she drowned, do you?
‐ Come to think of it, Akito
and Megumi are missing, too.
Now wait just a darned second!
‐ Well, there’s
nothing to be worried
about with those three,
unless it’s very continental.
‐ It appears that the
deed to this island
was recently sold
to a private owner.
The title is now held
by the Crimson estate,
a large Australian conglomerate.
‐ The Crimsons?
I know that name!
Aren’t they the
multi‐billionaires
who rented Monte Carlo
for their daughters debut?
It was the social
event of the decade!
‐ Crimson? They’re one
of the top manufacturers
of barrier shield
systems, right?
Satellites for the big
barrier are their specialty.
However, if I recall
things correctly
their daughter has proven
to be a real problem child.
‐ Problem child?
‐ For example, she
added a paralyzing agent
to the entrees at
a formal reception,
and kidnapped a noted
artist so that she
could draw a romance
comic featuring herself.
She’d gotten so bad that the
Crimsons’ had practically
dropped out of proper society.
‐ Well, that’s definitely
the new Chulip.
Let’s blow it up and
get back to the beach.
‐ Hey, wait a second! That’s
a force field generator!
What’s that doing here?
(computer beeping)
‐ The Crimson family crest?
‐ A force field?
What’s going on here?
‐ Who cares? Let’s just
blow everything up.
‐ [Nagare] What’s going on?
Why would the Crimson’s
build a barrier here?
(harp music)
‐ I’ve been all alone ever
since my father and mother died.
Its been lonely, but
somehow I’ve managed.
‐ Aqua, I‐‐
‐ Butloneliness is over now.
I think you’re the
knight in shining armor
that I’ve been waiting
my whole life for.
‐ I understand. It’s strange,
but I feel as if
I’ve known you‐‐
‐ Oh, Akito, I don’t ever
wanna leave your side.
‐ But, Aqua.
‐ I want you to stay
with me forever.
‐ [Megumi] Akito!
‐ [Yurika] Akito!
(panting)
‐ Who are you?
‐ Yurika Misumaru, and you?
‐ That’s not what’s important!
Who in the heck is this person?
‐ Well, I, actually‐‐
‐ It’s time to end this chapter.
‐ The force field
barrier is down!
(explosion)
‐ What is that thing?
‐ Ah! That’s a giant spider!
‐ It would appear
that this Chulip isn’t
another transdimensional
gate for Boson Jumping,
but a large transport
vessel instead.
The enemy is obviously
trying a new tactic.
‐ Well, at least
it doesn’t appear
to be fully operational
yet, whatever it is.
Neutralize it immediately.
(metallic clanging)
(rockets launching)
‐ Akito, just who
is that floozy?
That’s right, get away
from our Akito, you tramp!
‐ Wait a minute! You
don’t understand!
This girl is as
precious and important
to me as Aquamarine was to Ken!
(explosion)
(group yelling)
Aqua, are you alright?
‐ Oh, I’m so excited. Maybe
we’re all going to die now!
Wouldn’t that be so romantic?
(rocket launching)
(explosions)
At long last my
dream will come true.
I shall be consumed in
the flames of battle,
perishing with my one true love.
‐ Are you sure you’re
feeling alright, Aqua?
‐ I’ve never felt better in
my entire long dreary life!
In love and in death I
shall attain fulfillment!
Yes, at long last I will be
the perfect tragic heroine!
(explosion)
‐ Akito, get away from
that girl this instant!
Can’t you see that she’s crazy?
‐ That’s right! Let go
of Akito you nutcase!
(grunting)
‐ Oh, don’t worry, darling.
That’s just the paralyzing
powder I put in
your beef brochette.
‐ What!?
(gunfire)
(explosion)
‐ Akito!
‐ Why are you doing such
a horrible thing anyway?
If you want to die why don’t
you do it all by yourself?
‐ Ever since I was
a child I’ve been
given everything I ever wanted.
Everything except the one
thing I wanted most; misery!
I love to experience true
sadness, to be a tragic heroine!
‐ A tragic...?
‐ Heroine?
‐ Being too happy with the
cause of my unhappiness,
but in dying with my lover I
shall experience true anguish.
God wanted me to suffer so
he sent that Chulip to me!
‐ Let go of me you
out‐of‐your‐mind‐crazy‐person!
‐ Oh, no, my sweet,
I’ll never let go!
We shall become ashes on
the pyre of true love!
‐ Akito!
‐ Let go of him!
‐ [Ryoko] No way,
bug! He’s mine!
Are you alright, Akito?
Hey, just what the
heck is going on here?
‐ Ryoko! Behind you!
‐ I know, I know!
‐ Yeah, do it! Knock him dead!
‐ Beat the living crap
out of him please!
(gunfire)
‐ Die!
‐ Oh, mama.
(fire venting)
(upbeat music)
(spaceship humming)
‐ Akito, come back!
You can’t leave!
Life is a tragic play,
and we were meant
to leave the stage together!
‐ You ate that crazy
girls’ cooking, didn’t you?
‐ If you ate hers you aught to
be able to try mine at least!
‐ Please, I just want to live.
‐ Akito. I just thought I’d
try my hand at cooking as well.
‐ Please, somebody help me!
‐ Akito!
‐ Tenkawa!
‐ Please try my cooking
just one more time, okay?
‐ Akito!
‐ Leave me alone! Can’t you
see I’m the tragic protagonist?
‐ Lucky bastard.
‐ They say that
one persons’ misery
can be another ones paradise.
At least we can
savor his suffering.
‐ Well, I still envy him.
‐ Akito!
(Akito screaming)
‐ For God’s sake! Don’t leave!
You can’t just leave
me here like this,
I’m your admiral!
‐ Soon the tide will come in
and both of us will be
underwater, my new love.
(Aqua laughing)
‐ What are you
giggling like that for?
Someone come back and help
me! This girl is crazy!
‐ Doesn’t the ocean make
you feel so happy, darling?
‐ I’m definitely not
happy! (screaming)
(ending theme)
‐ Get ready for grand excitement
in the tradition of the
Battle of the Bulge,
Kelly’s Heroes, and
the ever popular
an idiot in a tank.
Yes, that’s right, the next
episode will feature tanks!
Big armored plated things
that go vroom‐vroom‐vroom!
With a squeal of grindy metal,
and the clackity‐clack
of armored tracks,
these armored backs from
a bygone era live again!
Oh yeah, and some
old friendships
are rekindled in the flames
of passion burn bright, too!
It’s the next episode of
Martian Successor Nadesico!
"Finding Yourself
in a Routine Plot!"