‐ Human beings just
can’t keep themselves
from opening
mysterious packages.
And the giant robot
we captured has turned
out to be a real Pandora’s box.
Can you believe what
we found inside,
Gekiganger merchandise?
And I thought this was supposed
to be a realistic anime.
(upbeat music)
(upbeat music with singing
in foreign language)
‐ It does look like someone
was on board, doesn’t it?
‐ But is that possible sir?
The Jovians have always used
unmanned weapons in the past.
And didn’t Miss Fressange
say that no ordinary lifeform
could survive that
passing through a Chulip?
It just doesn’t make sense.
‐ Stop arguing.
Start looking.
If there was an enemy
pilot on that robot,
then he must be hiding
on this ship someplace.
‐ Yes sir.
‐ And what if there’s
an enemy pilot on board?
If there’s a spy then it’s a
job for the security people
not us, geez.
‐ We’re luggers not fighters.
‐ [All] Yeah.
But if we call them in
then everyone will find out
there’s an alien on board.
We’d have total
panic on our hands.
And what’s worse the
top brass would blame me
for everything.
Absolutely not.
‐ Did it ever occur to you
that this just might be
some kind of UEAF weapons test.
(man screams)
Perhaps the UAEF are testing
some kind of infiltration
system using
Nadesico as a target.
‐ Well I suppose it’s possible.
‐ Right come on men, let’s
give this Jovian invader
a good shellacking.
(men cheer)
‐ This is surprising.
(tapping ball)
I thought that Nergal’s new
policy was to coordinate
all of our actions
with the UEAF.
And yet here we are
sneaking to the moon
to pick up Mr. Tinkawa.
‐ We’re also supposed
to conduct an exchange
with the forth vessel
reducing our exposure
once the military gets
their hands on it.
However, recovery
Tinkawa is more important
to my own agenda.
‐ So have you fallen for
Mr. Tinkawa’s charm as well?
(woman coughs)
‐ What?
Are you serious?
Why does everyone
on this ship assume
that any relationship
between a man and a woman
has to be sexual in nature?
I’m not that way.
My only interest in him
is due to his importance
as a test subject for
the company, okay?
‐ No it’s not okay.
‐ Captain.
‐ I’m getting sick
and tired of the way
you treat my Akito.
Either you stop bothering
him or else I’ll‐‐
‐ Or you’ll do what?
‐ Ah?
‐ Hit me?
Kick me?
Rearrange my hair?
‐ Ah?
‐ Well?
‐ Um, well?
‐ Don’t worry.
‐ Huh?
You mean you’ll‐‐
‐ Let me explain
this to you clearly.
‐ Hhmm, explain?
Explanation?
(pouring tea)
‐ I hope that video
cleared thing up.
Now do you see how the
Nadesico jump from Mars
to orbiting the moon?
‐ Yes, I did.
It showed how Akito’s love
for me caused a miracle.
And also how Miss
Fressange tried to but
in between us.
(slaps head)
Ow. (starts crying)
‐ I should have known you’d
detect an explanation.
I’m sorry I’m so late.
In any case it does seem
that Akito is our best chance
at unlocking the secret
to bozen jumping.
That does make him especially
valuable doesn’t it Arena?
Now be a dear and
pour me a cup of tea?
‐ Oh now I understand.
‐ Huh?
‐ And I’m willing to
forgive you for trying
to come between us.
‐ That’s not it.
‐ Oops.
‐ In order to make organic
bozen jumping a reality,
we first have to discover what
makes Akito able to do it.
Time is of the essence
if we’re going to beat
the Jovian lizards.
So we’ll do whatever it takes.
(upbeat music)
‐ Oh hi ladies.
(ladies gasp)
Have you seen anything
peculiar recently?
‐ Peculiar?
‐ No nothing peculiar at all.
We haven’t seen
anything peculiar.
‐ I see.
‐ So is there
something going on?
‐ I’m on a top secret mission,
so please keep
this to yourselves.
(footsteps)
‐ I don’t think we should
mention this to anyone, do you?
‐ I sure hope Gekiganger
phantom isn’t contagious.
(electronic noise)
‐ I’ve completed
littering the hanger
with Gekiganger stickers.
‐ I’ve put the action figures
and Geki plushies
on the bridge sir?
(man laughs)
‐ I’m so clever it kills me.
Our Gekiganger fan intruder will
never be able to
resist this bait.
(man laughs)
And once he comes after the
stickers, we’ve got him.
(footsteps)
‐ Minato?
‐ I’m not leaving this ship.
‐ I’m just trying to do my job.
‐ Just exactly what
is it that you do
on the Nadesico
mission, Mr. Horey?
It can’t be keeping me
under surveillance, can it?
Or is that what
your job really is?
‐ My job is to protect
the Nadesico’s crew.
That’s all I’m trying to do.
‐ And I suppose that
after the war’s over,
you’ll be wanting a nice
little family to come home to.
‐ I’d rather not talk
about my private life.
‐ So am I part of your
private life or your job?
‐ I can accept
either, but not both.
‐ All systems are nominal.
‐ Huh?
Oh my goodness, Murray.
How long have you been here?
‐ I got here before you did.
‐ Um, really?
‐ However, since I’m
just a young girl,
I wouldn’t understand such
an adult conversation.
‐ No, of course you wouldn’t.
I’ll just be leaving
to powder my nose.
Hold down the space
fortress for me, okay?
‐ I‐‐
‐ Minato?
(footstep)
(door closes)
‐ Aw is it over already?
‐ Hmm?
‐ Ssh, be quiet you idiot.
‐ You three.
‐ We were just servicing
the panel under there
with the two of you walked in.
And since it would have
been rude to interrupt,
we didn’t in any way.
We couldn’t really hear nothing.
Right, right?
‐ Ahoy Moby Dick,
I stab at thee.
Harpooned. (laughs)
‐ I’m so glad, you’re not
mixing work with pleasure.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Idiots.
‐ Please Ken, Recrew
is my older brother.
He may be evil, but I
still care about him.
I’m sorry, but
he’s now a warrior
for the Dark String
Universe, Nanaco.
This makes him our enemy.
‐ What’s the matter Gekigaga?
Aren’t you brave enough
to fight with me?
(loud commotion)
‐ Nanaco.
‐ Please Ken.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Why Ken?
Why do we always have to
fight among ourselves.
Why?
‐ Yes Akito. (cries)
Why do we always have to
fight among ourselves.
‐ There you are Ken
Kinko. (continues
talking in background)
‐ I played that scene a
lot better than she did.
‐ It is my duty as a
warrior to vanguish you.
This is our destiny.
‐ Wait don’t turn that off.
(girl gasps)
‐ Huh?
Ah, Mr. Bun‐Bun?
‐ I was right.
This is the lost episode 13,
The Tragic Holy Night (mumbles).
This is incredible.
‐ Ah‐ha.
(banging noise)
‐ It’s okay.
There’s nothing
wrong with being open
with your feelings for Akito.
‐ No, I have to disagree.
Just think of your position.
I mean you’re a captain.
‐ Right, I am a captain.
‐ Then what is it that
motivated you to become
the captain of the Nadesico?
‐ Huh?
I guess the reason I’m
here is because at home
nobody ever though
of me as anything
except my father’s daughter.
And it was the same all
the way through school
and even at the university.
But here on the Nadesico, I
feel like I have a purpose.
That’ I’m part of doing
something important.
‐ You mean that’s all there is?
Nothing more?
‐ Well, there’s also the part
about capturing Akito’s
heart and living
happily ever after just
like in the movies.
‐ Will you please stop
talking about that idiot.
Do you have any idea how
frustrating it is for me
to watch you acting as if
position means nothing to you?
Don’t you have any ambition?
What have you achieved as
captain of this vessel?
‐ It seems to me
that she’s been doing
a pretty good job
as captain thus far.
‐ Do you think all
the people who died
on the ship would
agree with that?
How can you devote so much
time to frivolous pastimes
when you still haven’t mastered
your professional duties
as a senior officer?
Have you even defined your goals
as the Captain of the Nadesico?
What is your purpose?
What is your vision?
‐ How can she answer
her if you keep
hammering her like that?
‐ Well I don’t think Ms. Wans
questions are so unreasonable
‐ [All] Huh?
‐ Not that there’s anything
wrong with chasing Akito around.
However, as a
member of this crew,
I’m also very
interested in learning
what our captain’s
specific goals and vision
for this ship might
be beyond that.
‐ I think my goal is the same
as any captain in times of war.
All I really want is to
be able to keep my ship
and crew safe from harm for
as long as the war continues.
But that doesn’t mean
that we can’t also try
to make the best of
things in the meantime.
‐ And what will you do if
the war never ends, Captain?
(women gulping their drinks)
‐ [All] Ah.
It does a body good.
‐ What I’m saying
is that I don’t care
if you think of yourself
as captain first.
But if you can’t figure out
what your role in the war is,
then you’re just playing around.
And I don’t want someone
who’s not completely focused
on her duties getting in my way.
‐ Well if you’re so
focused, just what is
your vision Miss Smarty Pants?
‐ I intend to be in charge
of Nergal within three years.
‐ [All] Oh.
‐ Being in charge of
Nergal would mean the power
to influence nearly every
single economic sector on earth.
And with that kind of power,
I could reshape the course
of the human race.
‐ Well maybe my goals
aren’t quite as grandiose
as yours are, but I think
that protecting the Nadesico
and Akito is pretty
important as well.
And I don’t think
there’s anything wrong
with not wanting
to be a big shot,
if you’re doing
something that helps
other people achieve
their own goals.
‐ That’s assuming that, that...
‐ You do know that they’ll
throw us out of an airlock
if they catch us
watching them again.
‐ Who the heck cares,
just kill me now.
(man screams)
‐ Are you trying to kill me?
‐ Isn’t that what
you said you wanted,
you bad boy?
So just what are you
doing out here anyway?
‐ A well, actually
we were just looking
for an intruder.
‐ An intruder?
‐ [All] An intruder?
‐ Admiral, is it true
that there’s an intruder
running around stealing
people’s underwear?
‐ And is it true that
you ordered Mr. Rebatawki
to be a peeping Tom?
‐ Huh?
‐ Admiral what is this about,
‐ (mumbles) maintenance
crew to examine
the women’s locker room
while we’re in there.
‐ Degenerates.
‐ What?
Why me, why is it
always... (screams)
‐ Admiral.
(man screaming)
‐ Idiots.
‐ One tranquility‐based
Tonkatsu combo,
fried leaks and livers, Mmm.
‐ I made those deliveries sir.
‐ Well that didn’t take long.
‐ So were you able to contact
the Amoto this time, Akito?
‐ I keep telling you
it’s not the Amoto.
It’s called the Nadesico.
‐ Yes I finally got
through to them.
They’ll be arriving
in just a few days.
‐ Well that’s great,
although I guess that means
that we’ll be losing you.
‐ Isn’t that nice and
I’m sure you’ll be glad
to get away from
my bossy husband.
‐ Who’s bossy?
I’m a peach to
work with, a peach.
‐ You can grab a bit, while
helping Koomey in back.
‐ Here you go Akito.
‐ After all that, my message
didn’t make it there in time.
‐ Oh, you shouldn’t
blame yourself Akito.
‐ I can’t help but feel
she died in my place.
‐ Please don’t say it like that.
‐ Our families lived here
on the moon for a while,
so we’ve known a lot of
people who were killed
in blowouts and things.
In a place like this,
you learn that the fact
that you live an somebody else
dies doesn’t mean anything,
just that you’re lucky
and they weren’t.
Ah, I mean...
‐ I know what you’re
trying to say.
But that girl
didn’t have to die.
For the first week, I was
locked up in that hospital.
And then all those people from
Nergal kept interrogating me.
I didn’t realize
what was happening.
That I’d somehow
gone back in time,
when I used the crystals.
I had two full weeks in
which I could have contacted
the Nadesico and kept them
from attacking that robot.
And if I had been able to get
a message through to the UEAF,
then that girl wouldn’t
have had to die.
But by the time
I finally managed
to get through it was too late.
Get over it kid.
Like I said, it’s just
the luck of the draw.
‐ The logical part of my
brain understands that,
but the emotional side
is having a harder time.
It just feels like there must
be a reason for what happened.
‐ [Man over ship’s radio]
Attention all crew,
there’s evidence that our
ship has been infiltrated
and there may be
an alien aboard.
All hands are to
remain...(continues
to talk in background)
‐ If the Jovians could
plant a spy on board
that means they be humanoid
or have human allies.
‐ That’s true but we
do know for a fact
that mankind is never gone
past the orbit of Mars, right?
So there’s no way
that the Jovians
could have found human spies.
‐ That big oaf is acting like
the announcer at a fox hunt.
‐ Huh?
(knock on door)
Ah, don’t move.
‐ Fukomi, you’re supposed
to go up to the bridge.
‐ Yeah, of course, I just
wanted to tidy up first.
‐ To yidy up?
(loud TV)
(girl screams)
‐ Aquamarine.
‐ Huh?
‐ What’s that?
‐ Pardon this deception.
I am Lieutenant Commander
Tsukomo Shiratori
of the Space Assault
Superior Male Forces
of the Anti‐Earth
Cooperative Federation
of the Jovian Realm and
Associated Moons and Asteroids.
‐ The what’s, what?
‐ Our Federation has held all
space outside of Jupiter’s
orbit for 100 years.
‐ Now hold on.
Haven’t you read
any history books?
Human beings have only
gone as far as Mars
in this Solar System.
‐ The history that your
people have learned is untrue.
(knocking on door)
‐ This is security.
(women gasp)
Is something wrong in there?
‐ We’re fine.
‐ We’re asking for
everyone to assemble
in the cafeteria ma’am.
‐ We’ll be there in a second.
(man moaning)
‐ Are you sure about
this? (whispering)
Mr. Horey, will be angry.
‐ I really couldn’t
care much less
what Mr. Horey
will be right now.
Anyway, I want to hear what
our visitor has to say,
before we throw
him to the wolves.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Hold it, what are the
two of you doing out here?
Don’t you know we have a
security alert in effect?
‐ I know and I can see
that you’re enjoying
your little blood sport.
‐ I’m just saying
that you’re in danger.
‐ And I’m saying that
you can arrest me,
if that’s what you want.
‐ Hold it.
How dare you claim
to be a soldier,
when you would distress
these fair maidens.
‐ Hold, you’re under arrest.
‐ Your under arrest.
(loud spacecraft noise)
(boy gasps)
‐ You’re having a nightmare.
Was it the same one?
‐ Ah.
Yeah.
I feel like a little kid.
Why do I keep having
the same dream?
‐ Do you think that glittering
castle means something?
Wouldn’t be fantastic if
you’re a reincarnated warrior
from a mysterious
ancient civilization?
‐ A reincarnation?
‐ Well it does explain
a few things about you,
like how you became
an Nadesico’s ace
pilot without training
and can teleport by yourself.
You’re pretty mysterious.
‐ I’m nothing like that Koomey.
‐ I’m just a little‐‐ (screams)
(loud thunderous noise)
‐ Great Neil Armstrong.
(crashing noise)
‐ No longer will you build
these demonic weapons
to use against us earth‐scum.
‐ Di Majin tornado.
‐ Thank God we have a pilot
with your experience here.
We need to take
care of that thing
before the UEAF
reinforcements arrive.
‐ Why’s that?
‐ That’s the reason over there.
Nadesico Class Vessel
number four, the Shokuyoku.
We’ve been building her
secretly as part of our plan
to return to Mars.
‐ Sonargol’s been
withholding information
from the military?
‐ Please we need you
to pull this one off.
‐ I don’t give a
damn, what Nergal
and the UAEF want anymore.
I’ve got a personal score to
settle with these lizards.
And if I run away this time,
I couldn’t forgive myself.
(crashing thud)
‐ Mighty is the fist
that fights for justice.
You’re evil giant robot is
no match for my di Majin.
(giant robot yelling)
(loud laser noise)
‐ I knew it.
That’s the same giant robot
I just fought on earth.
‐ That lunar surface frame has
a self‐contained PT engine,
however, you’ll reaction
time is slowed down
by the larger mask.
Use your real gun
at close range.
I understand, don’t worry.
There’s no way I’m gonna
let that thing fire
off a gravity blast.
‐ The lab reports said his
DNA was slightly modified,
but otherwise normal.
It seem our guest as an
earth human just like us.
‐ Don’t call me an
earthling, earthling.
I’m a proud soldier of
the Jovian Federation.
‐ Captain.
(man screams)
We are receiving an
S. O. S. from the moon.
It appears that a
Nergal Aestivalis is
engaged in combat with one
of the Jovian Goliath units.
‐ Oh my gosh.
That’s gotta be Akito
in the Aestivalis.
Well, I guess I’d better
go up to the bridge.
‐ If you would‐‐
‐ What about the prisoner
and those two traders?
‐ Saving Akito’s life
is more important
than bullying those two Ms. Wan.
‐ Well if that’ your decision.
‐ Have you lost your mind?
How can you put
something between a man
and a woman in front
of a war captain.
‐ Why not?
Or is the crew of this
ship not men and women?
‐ The captain is just too soft.
Hold it.
I think this is far enough.
‐ Huh?
(man gasps)
I think the public is
better off believing
that the Jovians are
inhuman invaders.
I’m afraid that
makes your existence
rather inconvenient.
It’s too bad‐‐
(load thud)
(man moaning)
‐ Start running, but I just
can’t break my prisoners
parole like that.
‐ Huh?
‐ Well you’re not capture now.
‐ This is your last
chance at freedom.
‐ Stop.
(man and women gasp)
In the name of the UEAF.
(gun clicks)
‐ I’m sorry.
(gunfire)
‐ How’s that?
‐ How’s this?
Yakegan (mumbles)
(boy screaming)
(loud thud)
(robot laughing)
‐ Why are you doing this?
It doesn’t even make any sense.
(strong motor force)
Why you attacking all
these innocent people?
(loud thrusting noise)
‐ I swear you’ll pay for
that one you birth scum.
‐ What did...
Who the hell are you?
‐ You’ll never
extinguish the flame
that burns within my soul.
I will defend my
Jupiter even if to do so
may mean my own death.
‐ Oh my God.
You’re fighting for
the Jovian lizards.
‐ Ah, thank goodness,
are you okay Akito?
‐ What’s going on here?
Who are you?
‐ We might have been...
We might have been
friends, had we been born
in another place in time.
‐ Hold on Akito,
we’ll be right there.
‐ Quiet I can’t hear.
‐ What?
Reinforcement, I
must flee for now,
but I will surely defeat
you when next we meet.
‐ Hey wait, where you going?
(loud thud)
‐ He was human.
The lizards are humans.
That’s impossible.
‐ Do you see what the
consequences of your actions
are Captain.
Because of you our
prisoner has escaped
and our helm’s woman and
communication’s officer
are both missing.
‐ I’m sorry.
‐ None of this changes
who the enemy is Eureka.
You can’t let your emotions
sway your decisions
as Captain.
‐ I know that June.
‐ This isn’t gonna be pretty.
Hunting your friends never is.
(slaps dash)
‐ I’m coming with you.
This was partly my fault.
‐ No way.
‐ I just heard that the
enemy prisoner got away.
‐ Oh Akito, are you okay?
How wonderful.
But you should rest after
all you’ve been through.
I really thought I was
doing my best to do
what I thought was
the right thing to do.
But maybe I was wrong about
what I was right about.
‐ I won’t let them
get away with this.
(Captain continues
talking in the background)
All this time we’ve been
fighting other humans
just like us.
How could they be so evil?
‐ Don’t you?
‐ Ah, shut up already.
Shuttle one now taking off in
pursuit of escaped prisoner.
(loud squeaking noise)
(thrusting noise)
‐ What’s wrong Akito?
There’s something
different about you.
You’re scaring me.
(upbeat music with singing
in foreign language)
‐ [Voiceovers] Xebec
Studio Newsletter.
Beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep...
‐ [Man] And so here
we are at Xebec,
the studio that
animated Nadesico.
‐ [Woman] Hey there’s someone
sleeping under this desk.
Let’s talk to the director.
‐ [Director] A hello, I’m
(mumbles) the director
and the next episode,
Eureka and Akito will
finally have a bigger
romantic scene.
‐ [Woman] Oh really.
How wonderful.
‐ [Man] Hey, what
did you just say?
‐ [Woman] Nothing.
What are those?
‐ [Man] Gekiganger animation so,
I’m gonna wallpaper
my room with them.
‐ [Woman] I see.
‐ [Man] Don’t mill
the next episode
of Martian Successor Nadesico,
the beginning of Nadesico’s war.
‐ [Woman] And maybe a lot more.