(gentle music)
‐ [Ruri] Everything
started on Mars,
and now it looks like everything
may end on Mars as well.
Whatever the case, it looks
like we’ll be fumbling about,
making a lot of noise
until the very end.
However, when you
think about it,
I guess that’s rather
appropriate for us.
("You Get to Burning"
by Yumi Matsuzawa)
(singing in foreign language)
(ominous music)
‐ Hey, what in the
heck is going on here?
Why are these guys
all retreating?
‐ Well, there’s not much point
in fighting at the
moment, is there?
I doubt that you’ll
keep firing on the ruins
with both Akito and Ms.
Fressange down there.
So, I guess we’ll
just have to wait
and see how this works out.
‐ Akito.
‐ Just how deep is
this thing, anyway?
‐ Well, according to
our research, it’s
about 10 kilometers
deep, with distortion fields
in place every 800 meters.
But who does the doctor
plan on greeting?
‐ [Akito] I don’t know.
(gasping)
‐ Could it be Ai?
‐ Huh?
‐ Of course!
‐ We of course.
‐ If it’s Ai, that explains why
the doctor was acting
a little strange.
‐ What I don’t understand is how
you can say it’s Ai so easily.
‐ Could the Ais have it?
‐ Now, wait just a darn second!
Would someone care
to explain just who
this Ai is that you’re
all talking about?
‐ Did you say explanation?
Since the explanation lady
has shut off her transmission,
I’ll act as her substitute.
Ai is a young girl Mr. Tenkawa
met in the utopia colony
shortly before he Boson
Jumped from Mars to Earth,
and whose apparent
death caused Mr. Tenkawa
a great deal of
personal anguish.
However, it would appear
that Ai is not dead.
‐ [Ai] Isn’t he here yet?
‐ [Inez] Hold on,
he’ll be here soon.
‐ [Ai] Okay.
‐ Unfortunately, with all
those distortion fields
blocking his path I’m
afraid that it’s going to be
difficult for him to get here.
(Ai giggling)
Is something wrong?
‐ You smell nice, old lady.
(laughing)
‐ Do I seem that old to you?
‐ Just like mommy.
‐ Huh?
‐ You smell just like my mommy.
But mommy went to sleep
and wouldn’t wake up
and then there
was this big boom,
and it was dark.
Then Mr. Akito started
shining really bright,
and there was this crazy
sound and I started running.
Wait for me, wait for me!
Mr. Akito, wait for me!
‐ There’s a free falling object
approaching from above, captain.
(wind whistling)
(object crashing)
‐ What the heck was that?
‐ [Man] Analyzing.
(computers beeping)
‐ Mam, object is
a Jovian Chulip.
(gasping)
(object crashing)
(woman screaming)
Damage to our starboard engine.
Field shrink down 20%.
We were hit with
a gravity blast!
‐ What?
(dramatic music)
‐ [Man] Completed
analyzing enemy strike.
Two phase transition
core powered battleships,
one of which is the Nadesico!
‐ It’s the Nadesico?
Did you hear that captain?
At last, we’re finally
going to get a rematch.
‐ So it seems.
Well, let’s see
what that dashing
man of action will do this time.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Man] The Kannazuki
is advancing, captain.
‐ [Tsukiomi] Hail the Kannazuki.
‐ [Man] Yes sir.
‐ Tell them to deploy all robots
for combat deployment
immediately.
(dramatic music)
‐ I’m scared!
‐ It’s going to be fine.
What’s going on?
‐ Ms. Fressange, a Jovian
Chulip just came out of nowhere,
and started launching
battleships and gyros at us.
‐ So, the close proximity
of the Jovian Boson Jump
must be what caused the ruins
to accelerate their activity.
‐ [Ai] Huh?
‐ It really is Ai!
‐ Ms. Fressange, are you there?
Ms. Fressange!
‐ Multiple mobile enemies
weapons approaching.
‐ We’ll have to handle the
ones who are closest first.
Ryoko?
‐ I got you, captain.
Just let me at ’em.
‐ Prepare the gravity
blast cannon, Jun.
‐ [Jun] Yes mam.
‐ I’m detecting
enemy Gekigan type
units approaching
via Boson Jump.
(dramatic music)
(Ai gasping)
‐ [Inez] Akito, please hurry.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Akatsuki] This
is the last barrier.
Keep pushing forward.
‐ Right, I’m coming
as fast as I can Ai!
Hold on!
‐ Hurry, hurry Mr. Akito, hurry!
Oh, I don’t wanna go lady!
I wanna stay!
I wanna see Akito!
‐ You will.
Maybe not now, but you
will someday, trust me.
You’re a strong girl,
Ai, I know you are.
That’s why you need to believe,
why you can never forget
his face, his voice.
No matter what happens you
can’t forget those things.
Please don’t forget,
promise me you won’t, Ai.
‐ Uh huh, I won’t, I promise!
I won’t ever, ever
forget Mr. Akito, lady.
(gasping)
Oh, I forgot!
When I got here, I was
supposed to give you this.
They asked me to
give this to you.
(electricity buzzing)
(metal clanking)
(ominous music)
‐ [Inez] The gift.
(men screaming)
‐ Ai!
Ms. Fressange, where’s Ai?
‐ You just missed her.
That’s why I told you to hurry.
But, maybe it was
meant to be like this.
‐ What’s that mean?
‐ The first letter
in Inez is I, Akito.
‐ Huh?
(Inez chuckling)
‐ She was thinking of
you when she jumped,
but because you were
Boson Jumping to the earth
she got lost.
‐ [Akito] What?
‐ She ended up on ancient
Mars and the people who built
this ruin sent her back, and
thanks to everything that
just happened, she just
jumped again, and ended up
in the middle of
the Martian desert
where she was found
wandering 20 years ago.
You know what
happened after that.
You saw it when all of our
memories were joined together,
when you saw my memories.
‐ Are you saying...
‐ [Inez] You saw it
too, right Akatsuki?
‐ That’s right.
‐ And of course all of the
other pilots, the captain,
and Ruri saw it as well.
‐ I see, and that incident
must have been when
you started to recover
your memory, am I correct?
‐ That’s right.
The little girl lost all of
her memory from the shock
of being left in the desert.
Fortunately, she was
found and rescued by some
Nergal researchers, and
eventually she was‐‐
‐ Wait, I know that!
I know all of this!
But I just never put all
the pieces together before.
I’m so sorry, Ai, I
should have saved you.
(Inez sniffling)
‐ It’s so wonderful
to see you again, mister.
(wind whistling)
‐ Okay, okay, I
understand, I got it!
It’s a time thing, some kind
of chronological paradox
or whatever you call it, right?
Now, if I could tear you
away from your soap opera,
the Kakitsubata really
needs some cover here!
‐ [Yurika] That’s true,
it’s as if the Kakitsubata
was being attacked
by rabid octopi.
(dramatic music)
(shots firing)
‐ It’s said that he who
hunts two hares loses both.
Therefore, we shall deal
with this other ship
before focusing our attention
on the more formidable Nadesico.
Saburota!
‐ I know what you mean, sir.
Gekigan punch!
‐ Erina, abandon ship!
‐ What, but‐‐
‐ Just do it, damn it!
(dramatic music)
(explosions detonating)
‐ [Saburota] Gekigan beam!
(explosion detonating)
‐ The Kakitsubata!
‐ It exploded!
‐ Erina Won, blown to bits
along with her ambitions.
‐ I was not blown up!
‐ Let’s pray.
(sobbing)
‐ Hey, I said I wasn’t dead!
‐ [Izumi] Yes, you are.
‐ [Erina] No, I’m not!
‐ [Akito] It’s all my fault.
‐ You’re wrong!
You mustn’t blame yourself!
‐ The Ai that I met two
years ago was a sweet
and innocent little girl.
But when I jumped she was
somehow sent back in time
and lost her memory.
She grew up to be a dried out,
walking encyclopedia
because of me.
‐ [Girl] But you didn’t know,
and you can’t
change anything now.
‐ [Woman] That’s right.
‐ [Woman] Come on, Mr. Akito,
have an nice a rice bowl.
(women chattering)
‐ [Akito] No, I’m not‐‐
‐ [Girl] Eat it, eat it!
(Akito mumbling)
(women chattering)
(bell chiming)
‐ I’ve got to go
now, big brother.
There are too many things
that need doing right now
and I’ve got to help.
But I swear, I’ll make
your dream come true.
(wind whistling)
‐ [Tsukiomi] What’s the
status of the enemy ship?
‐ [Man] No movement detected.
They’ve gone completely silent
since they descended
into the ruin excavation.
‐ Hail the enemy vessel.
‐ [Man] Yes sir.
‐ Tell them to abandon the ruin
and surrender their
ship to us immediately.
‐ If you surrender within
30 minutes you have my word
as the commander of this battle
group that I will guarantee
the safety of your crew,
sincerely, The Jovians.
‐ [Group] Hmm.
‐ It certainly looks like
we’re completely cornered.
So, what now, Captain?
‐ Well, we can’t surrender,
and we can’t let other side
take those ruins either.
So, it’s time to
drop the big one.
(explosion detonating)
‐ [Joe] Ken, are you all right?
‐ [Ken] But we can’t fight
against this many of them!
‐ After fighting for
so long it appears that
this moon will be where you
meet your final reckoning!
Die Gekigangar!
(dramatic music)
(robot crashing)
(man screaming)
(man groaning)
‐ [Joe] Gekigan sword!
(explosion detonating)
(dramatic music)
‐ This is nothing
compared to the real hell.
Pulls yourselves together!
Ken, Akira.
‐ Joe?
‐ Joe Umitsubame, so
you’re still alive?
‐ Joe!
(chu‐ Let’s do it partners!
That’s right, if
all your passions‐‐
‐ So convenient, dying
and resurrecting.
‐ [Joe] Use this, Gekigangar V!
‐ [Group] Gegikan sword!
‐ Now, hyper passion slash!
‐ [Minato] I can’t
believe that you saw
so much in someone
that’s so shallow.
‐ Mmm‐hmm.
‐ Did you want
something, Yukina?
‐ I’d like you stop blubbering
and act like an adult
with responsibilities.
‐ I can act this
way if I want to.
‐ No, you can’t!
You said, you promised
you’d marry my brother
and be my family!
(bell chiming)
(upbeat music)
‐ Huh?
‐ [Ruri] To self destruct?
‐ We’ll overload the ship’s
phase transition engines
and turn it into a bomb.
That ought to
destroy those ruins!
‐ Now, wait just a second!
Are you asking us to
sacrifice ourselves?
‐ Of course not!
The only person who will still
be on the ship will be me.
‐ Wait a sec‐‐
(group screaming)
What’s wrong with you?
Are you trying to get killed?
‐ Don’t worry,
I’ll be just fine.
‐ You idiot!
Can’t you see how many things
can go wrong with your plan?
You’ll die, nut bar!
‐ Don’t be stupid, I won’t die!
‐ Will!
‐ Will not!
‐ Will too!
‐ Will not, will not,
will not, will not!
‐ Yes, you will, you ditz!
What’s that look mean?
(sighing)
‐ [Men] You made her cry!
‐ Yeah, well, better
crying than dying!
‐ All I wanna do is destroy
those ruins, and end the war.
‐ But would self destructing
the ship even work, captain?
‐ Huh?
‐ If you’ll just turn
the ship over to Nergal,
we’ll take care of everything.
‐ Yes, you can trust us.
‐ Nevermind that their own high
mobile battleship
was just blown up.
(group gasping)
Oh, don’t pay any
attention to what
the precocious child is saying.
‐ In any case, you
can’t blow the ship up!
‐ [Yurika] And why not?
‐ Because I said so!
‐ But it would be worth it!
Think of the people
we would save.
Isn’t it worth
risking my life to end
this stupid war
once and for all?
‐ But if you do it,
you’ll be killed.
‐ Well, that might
not be exactly right.
‐ Huh?
‐ According to Ms.
Fressange’s explanation,
these ruins are like
a huge time machine.
So if we blow the ruins
up, then it’s possible
that all the Boson Jumping
that ever took place
in the past, present, and
future will all be voided.
‐ Huh, I wonder just how
much would be changed.
‐ Huh?
(strumming guitar)
Well, that can’t be me.
‐ [Girl] Then who is it?
(strumming guitar)
‐ [Group] Huh?
‐ It’s impossible!
(strumming guitar)
♪ Being my own self ♪
♪ That’s just what I be ♪
♪ Looking for a future ♪
♪ That’s only for me ♪
‐ [Admiral] You really
shouldn’t be thinking
about self destruction, V.
(explosion detonating)
‐ [Group] Admiral!
‐ But we thought
you died months ago!
‐ [Admiral] Are you disappointed
that I’m still alive?
‐ I found him inside the ruins.
He was saved by the
grasshopper units
and was being held
as a prisoner of war.
‐ [Group] Oh!
‐ V!
‐ But I don’t
understand, admiral.
Why can’t we self destruct?
‐ [Admiral] Because
self destruction
is really, really stupid!
‐ But sir, you were willing to
sacrifice yourself
once, weren’t you?
Huh?
Ruri?
‐ We can’t self
destruct, captain.
‐ [Yurika] But why?
‐ If we were to destroy
the ruin then all
of our recent history would
be rewritten as a result.
That means that the war
would never have happened
but we’d also lose
something important.
(dramatic music)
Two minutes until retrieval
of ruin unit will be complete.
‐ Will it still work after
we have it on the Nadesico?
‐ Theoretically,
time and space have
no meaning to the
jump controller.
‐ Hmm, could you
say that in English?
(giggling)
‐ It means
we’re never farther away
than we are in our hearts.
(gasping)
‐ [Girls] Minato!
(giggling)
‐ I’m sorry that
I had you so worried.
‐ Are you okay now?
(giggling)
‐ Thanks to Yukina.
‐ [Girls] Huh?
‐ She said that if
Tsukumo couldn’t marry
me that she would.
‐ What?
‐ I think it’s the
thought that counts,
so I guess I’ve got to hold
it together for her sake.
‐ Or vice versa.
‐ I think we’ll be ready
to start in a minute, Ruri.
‐ Of course.
If we destroyed the
ruins we would have lost
the thing that’s
most precious to me.
The year of my life I’ve spent
here onboard the Nadesico.
In the end, that’s all
we really have, memories,
memories of the people
who have become my friends
and family, memories that we
earned by living through them,
memories I wouldn’t
sacrifice for any price.
Tell me captain,
aren’t those memories
just as important to you?
‐ Why did you give
them 30 minutes?
You’re too soft, Tsukiomi.
‐ [Tforce may be weak,
but they have taken possession
of the city’s interior.
‐ You must attack immediately!
(dramatic music)
‐ You know, I’m really not very
comfortable in this outfit.
(laughing)
‐ But you’ve never looked
more dashing, captain!
‐ You be quiet!
‐ [Yurika] Five enemy Gekigan
type units approaching.
‐ Oh, we’ll take
care of ’em somehow.
You just take care of
things on your end.
‐ Don’t worry.
Are you two ready
to get started now?
‐ [Akito] Are you
sure we’ll be able
to make the Nadesico Boson Jump?
‐ Theoretically, yes.
‐ As expected the ruin
is made entirely from
the same material as
the Chulip crystals.
‐ And are you ready, Ruri?
‐ [Ruri] Yes.
‐ Okay, Erina,
start the sequence.
‐ Choosing our memories
over world peace.
I guess this just
proves everyone has
their own priorities,
and what we have now is the
most precious thing of all.
(dramatic music)
(electricity zapping)
‐ The Boson Jump field
was unable to stabilize.
‐ Hmm.
Okay, you two have
to kiss each other.
‐ What?
‐ Since there isn’t a Chulip
with an open field nearby,
it’s obvious that we’re going
to have to create a field
large enough to accommodate a
ship the size of the Nadesico.
In order to do that, we’ll
need to have a membrane
to membrane contact
among ourselves,
and the simplest way
of doing that is to‐‐
‐ Is, is kissing?
‐ [Inez] Right.
‐ We’ll all be in big trouble
unless the two of you hurry.
‐ No!
‐ But, Yurika‐‐
‐ I won’t do it, I
won’t, I won’t, I won’t!
‐ This is no time to
act petulant, captain.
‐ Yeah, let’s just grit
our teeth and endure it.
‐ Endure it?
If that’s all you feel you
could just kiss Ms. Fressange!
‐ [Man] Gekigan beam!
‐ You gotta be a lot faster
than that, snail boy.
(man groaning)
‐ Wait a second, so only
those individuals who
are born on Mars are
capable of Boson Jumping?
Tenkawa, the doctor,
and the captain,
which means that the
ruins must have caused
the nano machines to
rewrite their DNA structure.
That’s why they can withstand
the jumping process.
‐ That’s the size of it.
(sighing)
And now one of those martians
is jumping all over the ship
while the other chases her.
‐ It figures.
(laughing)
‐ [Erina] They’re
crazy, but amusing.
(dramatic music)
‐ I’ve made up my
mind, big brother.
I’m going to Earth with Minato.
That way you can watch
both of us at once.
‐ Hey, stop that!
Get out of there captain!
Are you listening to me?
‐ [Akito] Yurika!
‐ Oh, it’s about
time you got here!
Why in the hell is the captain
trying to take your Aestivalis?
‐ Please, Yurika!
Get down from there!
You can’t pilot that!
‐ [Man] Yeah, you
don’t have the implant!
‐ Huh?
‐ How the heck did the
captain get an IFS implant?
‐ Beats me.
‐ You can still jump, Akito.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Inez] Visualize the
inside of Aestivalis.
‐ Visualize.
‐ [Group] Whoa!
‐ Oh!
(screaming)
‐ [Akito] Stop it, Yurika!
‐ [Yurika] Go away!
‐ [Akito] Go away where?
‐ [Yurika] (Mumbles).
‐ [Akito] Ow, you
hit me, my eye!
(both chattering)
‐ [Yurika] Get out of my way!
‐ And what was that?
‐ It sounds like a couple
arguing on an open comm channel.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Akito] Let go!
‐ [Yurika] You let go!
‐ [Akito] Come on, please?
‐ [Yurika] I don’t want to!
‐ Jeez will you please
start using your brain
and stop being so stubborn?
‐ Me?
And when will you realize I was
just trying to help you and Ai?
‐ What are you talking
about, you nut bar?
‐ I know how guilty you
feel about what happened
to Ms. Fressange,
which is the reason
why I tried to turn back time.
‐ [Akito] Idiot!
(Yurika crying)
‐ Incidentally, I’ve
been relaying the feed
from the Aestivalis to
every ship in the area.
‐ So this is the
lovers spat that
will decide the fate
of the universe.
‐ Uh huh.
‐ [Yurika] I’m not stupid,
quit calling me that!
‐ Yurika, I watched
the last episode
of Gekigangar Three last night.
‐ Huh?
‐ Yeah, and it was the
worst episode of the series.
(gentle music)
But as awful as it was,
I felt shivers going down
my spine as I watched it.
Seeing Gekigangar Three
and Gekigangar Five
fighting side by
side with each other.
‐ [Yurika] Side by side.
Sounds kind of nice.
‐ [Akito] I guess there’s
a part of me that wants
to believe in perfect
good, happy endings,
and hot blooded passion.
The part of me that
loves Gekigangar‐‐
‐ Is the part of you that’s
in love with me, isn’t it?
‐ Look, I was just
about to make a major
and very profound
speech here, damn it!
But since you mentioned
it, yes I do, you wacko.
You’re supposed to say
something back, you know.
‐ Excuse me?
You know how I feel.
I love you with all my
heart and soul Akito!
‐ That’s the first time
I’ve heard you say it.
‐ It is not!
‐ I’m sure it is.
‐ It is not.
‐ Yes it is.
‐ It is not!
‐ Is too!
‐ No, it’s not!
‐ Yes it is!
(romantic music)
‐ [Yurika] I love you Akito.
‐ [Ruri] So all of that
being said and done,
I still have to wonder if
kissing was really essential
for the two of them to
start the Boson Jump.
All Ms. Fressange would
say is that when I was
a little older I
would know the truth.
In the end, a lot of big
mysteries remained unexplained,
like the meaning of
the plate that Ai gave
to her older self, and who
the ancient martians were,
and what happened to
their civilization.
Still, since we had the
calculation unit from
the ruin onboard the
Nadesico, we were able
to Boson Jump far away.
The war between Jupiter and
the Earth will probably go on,
but they won’t be able to
do much more than growl
at each other for a while.
I guess we’ll have to wait
for another opportunity
to find out what happens next,
in the inevitable sequel.
(gentle music)