‐ [Narrator] Most people believe
that there is only
one time continuum.
That was what we believed.
That history was the
same for all of us.
We never imagined that it might
be possible for someone else
to be living with a different
history from our own
until we learned that the
Jovians were doing exactly that.
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
‐ You certainly
do have a weakness
for these blushing
wallflower types, Megumi.
Is that your maternal side?
‐ Huh? I don’t know what
you’re talking about.
But that doesn’t mean you
can’t come and sit next to us.
‐ Sit between you two ladies?
Oh, I couldn’t do that.
It’s not proper, you know?
‐ Oh, so rigid.
Come on.
(yelps)
‐ But I might
accidentally touch you
and that’s not proper.
‐ You’re adorable.
‐ No, please don’t stop.
‐ Menato.
‐ [Menato] Why don’t we all
three sit comfortably together?
‐ Please do not sit...
Oh, don’t touch that.
‐ [Menato] What about this?
‐ [Megumi] Menato.
(giggling)
(light orchestral music)
‐ That ship is moving
extremely strangely.
‐ Megumi and Menato
must be fighting back.
Can’t we establish a com link?
‐ I’ll try.
Hey, lizard lover.
Leave those two women alone.
‐ Huh? What the
heck is going on?
That ugly boy’s face
just appeared in mid‐air.
(screaming)
‐ What did you call me?
(growling)
(yelling)
‐ Magumi.
Hold on, we’ll be there
as soon as we can.
(screaming)
Someone’s attacking us.
‐ Well, what did you expect?
We’re entering Jovian
controlled space.
There’s no way this
shuttle could make it.
‐ But we can’t
just abandon them.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Right.
Then hang on
’cause we’re going in.
(ship engine roaring)
‐ [Nagare] So you were saying?
‐ [Ryoko] Oh, shut up.
‐ [Yurika] Hey, I
was just thinking.
Did that Jovian spy remind
any of you of somebody we used
to know?
‐ [Akito] Huh?
‐ The pilot who collects
Gekiganger merchandise.
Hmm.
That’s it!
He reminded me of Jiro Yamada!
And he even looked like him!
‐ Huh?
‐ I thought he was
like Mr. Yamada too.
‐ Maybe he just
pretended to be dead
and then joined the enemy.
Maybe he was a spy all along.
That’s the kind of plot
twist he’d be into.
‐ You’re blocking my
view screen, Jeno!
‐ The bullet was stopped by the
silver dollar in his pocket?
‐ The bible and metal
lighters are also options.
‐ That’s enough
of this nonsense!
Gai wouldn’t do
something like this.
He liked Gekiganger,
and he liked to show up.
He wouldn’t let
innocent people be hurt.
‐ You mean the Jovians are
actually human beings like us?
‐ Now that the Jovians
have found a way
to send living creatures
through a Chulip,
they can infiltrate us at will.
‐ And the human spies
make it even easier.
‐ Confirming signal!
Descending into
underground docking bay.
Control online.
‐ Good work.
Initiate docking sequence.
‐ Preparing to land.
‐ There’s no way
it could be Gai.
‐ So this is the famous
Shakuyaku, is it?
‐ [Man] Yes.
And from the way they’re
focusing on our PT engine
and job research labs, it
would appear that the enemy
knows exactly what we’re up to.
‐ Yes, that’s true.
With their human
spies, they’d like
to know our infrastructure.
‐ We can’t afford to
waste time wondering.
Our immediate concern
should be for the Shakuyaku
and its mission.
‐ Do you mean the third
reclamation of Mars?
‐ As cooperating
with the military has yielded
unsatisfactory results,
the chairman has decided to
return to our original plan
of action.
What that means is
that the company will require
massive amounts of CCs
from Boson Jumping experiments!
‐ The company, the
company, the company.
Do you think that’s
what the rest
of the human race
really wants, Erina?
‐ Well, of course!
Don’t you want to retake Mars?
Even this crew of lame
brains, blackwoods,
and ne’er‐do‐wells has
bought into that bit
of Nergal propaganda.
‐ Perhaps.
But will they still
follow us once they start
to realize that they’re
being used again?
‐ Shakuyaku will
launch in total secrecy
with a handpicked crew.
The Nedesico will act as a decoy
and draw the enemy’s attention.
The operation will
commence in 12‐‐
(wild laughter)
‐ Ms. Won, do
something with him!
Please!
He demands that
you speak with him!
‐ So what sort of evil scheme
are you brewing up this time?
I sure would love to hear
about it before it happens,
Miss Won.
(wild laughter)
‐ [Man] Admiral,
control yourself!
‐ Fine.
If you really think
you can handle it,
I’ll show you evil.
‐ All right.
Lock the cockpit and close
the breast plate panel.
All the basics are the
same except a lot bigger.
That means it takes more
time to do everything
so no rushing!
Treat her like your
sister, not a girlfriend!
‐ [Men] Yes, sir!
‐ Man, once you figure it
out, it’s really not all
that complex.
‐ Why are their jump
patterns so simple?
‐ It’s like sex.
Only so many ways to do it.
‐ What’s going on here?
Why do you know so much?
How did Nergal know we
were fighting other humans
when I didn’t?
I demand to know the answers!
Why did the military
tell you and not me?
Why didn’t they trust me?
You little!
‐ Behave yourself, Admiral.
Dragging a female officer into
your quarters is bad form.
‐ This is none of your business!
‐ You are a dim
bulb, aren’t you?
‐ What you don’t
know is (whispering).
‐ You mean you’re?
‐ Yes, I’m afraid I am.
‐ Oh darn.
These modern security systems
are getting to be too much
for an old packer like me.
‐ Actually, there is a way
to bypass the privacy
lockout circuit.
‐ Ooh, these kids
are so technical.
We can’t allow there to be any
secrets on this ship, can we?
‐ You know what?
You’re right.
‐ Huh?
‐ My, you do have a
way with machines.
‐ What are you doing with
the security system, Ruri?
‐ I just did it.
‐ I’ll get right to the point.
The Jovian lizards were
banished 100 years ago.
‐ Banished?
‐ From the planet Earth.
‐ Gazeta net!
‐ It’s too flexible for
our net to catch it!
‐ That monster keeps
stretching like a rice cake.
‐ Rice cake?
Wait a second!
That’s it!
‐ Do you have an idea?
‐ Remember back when Junpei
and Miss Manako were eating
rice cakes the other day?
The rice cakes
were soft while hot
but once they cool, they
become firm and solid.
‐ Brilliant plan!
If we can freeze
that monster solid,
‐ Then he won’t be able to
stretch out of our way anymore!
I’m taking the lead!
All right!
Let’s Geki in!
Changer!
‐ I hope I’m not interrupting.
If there’s anything
that you are needing,
please don’t hesitate to ask.
‐ We’re fine.
‐ Hold on.
I thought we were
your prisoners.
‐ But you’re women
before you’re prisoners
and women should be treated
like delicate flowers.
‐ I see.
‐ We are not like those ignorant
barbarians back on Earth.
The youth of the Jovian
federation are taught
to conduct themselves properly
in the presence of women.
(screaming)
‐ You’re all fans of
Gekiganger, aren’t you?
‐ It’s the blueprint
of our society.
‐ Wait.
If you’re the captain of
this ship, why were you
in the Daimajin?
Why pilot it yourself?
‐ Surely you must
be joking with me!
Only our finest warriors
can become commanders.
We all must train
in every aspect
of the ship’s mighty functions.
But to truly be a leader, one
must be an ace pilot as well.
‐ Hmm?
(screaming)
‐ Oh, don’t worry.
Fluffy’s just a harmless pet.
Come on, I’ll show you.
As you can see, they also
double as computational units
inside the ship.
We’re rather short on
manpower so we make do.
‐ So only a small number
of your people can go
through a Chulip?
‐ Yes.
We, the superior male forces,
are the glorious culmination
of 100 years of experiments.
‐ Megumi, are you all right?
‐ I’m okay.
‐ How inconsiderate of me!
I’ll have a medic
summoned at once!
‐ No, I’m fine.
It’s just realizing it’s true,
that they’re really
the Jovian lizards.
How could people who seem so
nice do such horrible things?
‐ Your people have
done even worse things!
‐ Di‐na‐chee‐ro!
You’re all right!
We thought you were dead!
‐ Well, I’m not.
Although things did
get a little hairy
when I was transported to
the moon two weeks ago.
‐ Well, serves you right.
You’re the ones who started
this by dropping Chulips
onto Mars.
‐ Chulips?
‐ She means the
dimensional leak gates.
‐ Then say so!
Don’t use such strange
words, you nincompoop!
‐ The words I use aren’t
half as strange as you are.
‐ In any case,
the reason we attacked
Mars two years ago was
because your people were
planning to attack Jupiter.
‐ Planning to do what?
(upbeat music)
‐ 100 years ago a
certain incident occurred
that’s been wiped from the
pages of our history textbooks.
‐ [Man] You see, there were
certain districts on the moon
that sought to
become independent,
so the UE infiltrated
both the separatists
and the moderates and aggravated
the friction between them.
This led to a series of
violent purges now referred
to as the war for
lunar autonomy.
‐ Wait.
I thought the Earth had
nothing to do with the war
for lunar autonomy.
(laughing)
‐ Yes, but you only know the
things that they taught you
to know.
‐ In fact, the Earth was
not only deeply involved
in the Civil War.
It was the UEA of space fleets
that drove the rebel groups out
at gunpoint.
The scattered
remnants disappeared.
First to Mars, then
to the astroid belt
in Jupiter.
End of story.
Or so we thought.
‐ The UE government
eliminated all records
of their existence as if
they’d never even existed.
‐ Why did they have
to erase all the
records concerning them?
‐ To cover up their own role
in fermenting the rebellion.
‐ Yes.
And for other reasons as well.
‐ The truth is
that your dirty Earth scum
comrades justified the theft
of our homes in the name
of pacifying an unstable
political situation!
The survivors of the
purge had settled on Mars
when the UEAF attacked again!
They used nuclear warheads
to destroy our new colony.
‐ It was all part of a plan
to keep the Earth profitable
and under control.
In the end, Jupiter
and its satellites were
the only place left
for our ancestors
to go, and that was
when we found the artifact.
‐ What artifact?
(suspenseful music)
‐ A factory?
‐ Yes, for the construction
of phase transition engines.
‐ Phase transition engines
and unmanned weapons such
as the Grasshoppers and Jeros.
The Chulips.
‐ Discovering the plant
in Jupiter orbit gave the
separatists the technical base
they needed to survive.
It also gave them the
ability to build the weapons
for their revenge.
‐ This is unbelievable.
If the public ever finds out.
‐ [Erina] Oh, but they won’t.
‐ Yes, they will!
‐ [Erina] You were spying on us?
What kind of captain are you?
‐ [Yurika] One who
cares about her crew!
One who believes that they
have the right to know
why they’re really fighting!
How dare you keep something
like this a secret?
‐ [Erina] It won’t
make a difference!
We’re still at war!
‐ Do you really believe that?
How could you sit there
and watch people go
into battle knowing
that everything
the UEAF has told us for the
last 100 years has been a lie?
‐ Opening Infinity
Cannon Barrels, sir.
May we extrude the Mega
Mass Projector, sir?
‐ You may extend
the Infinity Cannon.
‐ Daimaijin One is
ready for launch!
‐ Break a leg, Gi‐na‐ji‐ro.
‐ I’ll destroy their Contortion
Bomber from the inside.
(laughing)
‐ Wait a second!
What’s going to happen to
our ship, The Nadesico?
‐ Unfortunately,
we have no choice.
‐ It will be destroyed.
‐ [Messenger] Excuse me, ma’am.
Here are your tapes.
‐ They’re just copies.
You can keep them.
‐ Oh no.
We wouldn’t dare.
‐ So you completed duplicating
the long lost episode,
have you?
‐ Yes, sir!
And the condition was
as superb as you said!
‐ What was that?
Are you talking about the
legendary lost 13th episode
of Gekiganger?
‐ Not only that but copies of
episode nine and 33 as well.
‐ What?
Are you serious?
(exclamations)
(exciting music)
‐ No matter how
powerful our foe may be,
‐ [Group] The superior male
force will never be defeated!
Our fists and shields
shall shatter our enemy!
‐ Daimaijin, go!
‐ Remember, Earth is our home!
‐ Our blue planet Earth.
‐ [Group] We will protect it!
Geki gun out!
‐ [Ruri] The colonies distortion
field is starting to fail.
‐ That’s not good.
‐ Raise the fields
to full power!
‐ How’s the Shakayaku?
‐ It doesn’t look promising.
They’re still in the process
of attaching the last module.
‐ Fire!
(explosion)
‐ The Shakuyaku!
‐ If only the Earthlings
appreciated life as we do,
I would not have to
kill so many of them.
(blasts and explosions)
‐ We’ve got a limited supply
of inner ship missiles
so make ’em count!
‐ I understand!
We’ve got your
jump pattern code.
Now you’re mine.
‐ Move! We’ve gotta hurry, men!
There’s no reason why (yelling).
‐ [Men] Yes, sir!
‐ Are you really sure you
wanna try this, Captain?
The Nadesico
and the Shakayaku use
different electrical systems.
We might explode!
‐ That’s fine.
Don’t worry.
I believe in you.
‐ Then I’ll try not
to screw up then.
Wait three minutes.
‐ Are you really sure we
can attach the Y unit?
The Nadesico’s main
power grid is different
from the Shakayaku’s.
‐ I’m aware of that, Miss Won,
but the Shakayaku has been
crushed and it’s such a waste
to leave it.
We should conserve our
resources whenever possible.
Ruri, have the factory people
evacuated onto The Nadesico?
‐ Aye.
‐ Damn it!
If we could use the catapult,
we could help Tinkawa.
‐ Yes.
But it’s not the same now that
we’re fighting other humans.
(blasts)
‐ Justice will always prevail!
‐ Will you shut up
and die already?
‐ Akito!
‐ They’re not what
you think they are!
‐ They’re forcing
you to say that!
‐ [Megumi] You’re wrong, Akito!
Please stop attacking them!
‐ [Minato] I wanna make it clear
so this man’s honor
is not questioned.
We are not hostages, Akito.
‐ We’ve all been
tricked and lied to!
These people are
humans just like us!
‐ [Akito] We know that!
They’re descendants of people
banished from the moon!
‐ Please move out of the way.
Our only target is the
battleship equipped
with the phase
transition power plant.
‐ I know!
And you’ll never
touch The Nadesico!
‐ Why are we fighting
a war based on lies?
‐ Don’t you understand at all?
It’s too late to argue about
whose fault this war is!
It’s too late for forgiveness!
‐ [Megumi] Akito!
(screaming)
(exciting music)
‐ It’s a distortion field!
‐ It’s The Nadesico.
I don’t believe it.
‐ [Ruri] The enemy robot is
trapped inside our field.
‐ That certainly ought to
bring the odds against Akito
down a little bit.
‐ Except Akito can’t Boson
Jump and that Jovian spy can.
‐ He won’t.
‐ And what makes
you so sure of that?
‐ Because both Megumi and
Minato are onboard that robot
with him.
‐ That’s right.
Normal humans can’t
survive being Boson Jumped.
‐ So why should he care?
That man is our enemy.
He’ll sacrifice them both.
‐ I’m afraid I have greater
faith in the good in people.
‐ Hurry!
You’ve got to leave now!
‐ I can’t do that.
‐ I’ve never seen
such treachery.
How could you involve women
in a fight between men?
‐ Well, I’m a woman!
‐ What’s happening?
‐ This is for the
people on the moon!
And that’s for the people
you killed attacking Mars!
‐ Please, Akito,
you’ve got to stop!
‐ I’m not done with you!
‐ That Daimajin no longer
has the ability to fight!
I’ll let these two
off and then you
and I will settle this
on the field of battle.
‐ No!
Please, please stop this!
What’s the sense in doing
something senseless like this!
Akito!
‐ [Akito] I’m doing this to
protect the Earth, Megumi!
‐ And does doing it
to protect the Earth make
you incapable of being wrong?
Please listen to me!
If killing each other is the
only way to end this madness,
why are we all fighting
a war nobody wants?
Why can’t we all go home
and watch Gekiganger
for our space battles?
Please, Akito.
Stop fighting.
What happened to
the Akito I knew?
The Akito who hated war?
‐ Megumi, you know I never
wanted to be a soldier,
but I can’t ignore the
horrible things I see anymore.
It’s not like it seemed
when I was a kid watching
Gekiganger and dreaming
of being a pilot.
‐ The UEAF fleet is
approaching lunar orbit.
‐ Looks like they were watching
to see the outcome first.
‐ So, once again, blind
luck hands you the victory,
Captain.
But do you really
believe that you can keep
from dirtying your
hands forever?
‐ [Akito] Go.
‐ Thank you.
Could you tell me your name?
My name is‐‐
‐ No.
I don’t wanna learn the name
of the man I’m trying to kill.
‐ [Man] I see.
Then farewell.
‐ You know that I
did what I had to do.
‐ I know that you did.
I think that your passion
is what attracted me to you
in the first place.
It’s like that time you
had to rescue the captain
and me when we were
adrift in outer space.
You were more worried
about her than me,
but you were willing to
sacrifice her until you figured
out a better way.
‐ It’s not that simple.
‐ No.
If you weren’t the
kind of person you are,
I wouldn’t have fallen for you.
I’m sorry we ever met.
‐ Megumi!
‐ Don’t worry, kid.
There’s lots of other
fish in the sea.
‐ This isn’t some kind of
a game we’re talking about!
And I just let her go.
‐ [Ruri] Permission
has been granted
to transfer the evacuated
personnel, changing heading
to the specified colony.
We’re all idiots.
(foreign pop music)
(exciting music)
‐ Hello!
Admiral Nu‐mi‐ta‐ki here.
My head is about to
explode with everything
that’s been happening!
Can you believe that the
top brass is blaming me
for The Nadesico crew
finding out the truth
about the Jovians?
How could I when
they never told me?
The only thing that can save
my career is a brand new robot!
What?
No, not a plastic
metal kit, you idiot!
It’s the next episode
of Martian Nadesico!
It was a reunion
that came too late!
I’ve got a bad
feeling about this!