‐ [Narrator] Well, after
a whole lot of stumbling
and fussing about,
everyone seems to have
finally figured
out why they fight.
Actually, I’m not too clear
on why this is important.
But nobody asked me.
Whatever.
On the other hand, I
would like to know why we
keep getting stuck with all
these annoying hot shots.
(upbeat music)
(sings in a foreign language)
(peaceful guitar music)
(soft crying)
‐ Akito?
What’s wrong?
Does your tummy hurt, Akito?
‐ Shut up.
‐ [Yurika] Were you in a fight?
Go away.
(breeze blowing)
‐ Hey, Akito.
Do you want to see a magic trick
that’ll turn you back to normal?
(gasps)
Close your eyes, Akito.
(smacking)
(Akito moaning)
‐ Ew, gross!
What did you do that for?
‐ (laughs)
I told you it’d turn
you back to normal.
‐ Don’t you ever do
that to me again!
(laughs)
(smacking)
(screaming)
Not again.
But why?
That was over 10 years ago.
‐ The Admiral is waiting.
Why are you still
in your room, pilot?
‐ I’ll pass, thank you.
I’m not comfortable
around that little creep.
‐ You still think
he was involved
with Lieutenant Yamada’s death?
Weren’t you aware
that one of the
Admiral’s subordinates
has already
confessed and is
court‐martialed for that crime?
‐ Uh‐huh, yeah, sure.
‐ Well, if you don’t show,
the Captain might think
you were trying to
get her attention.
‐ What’s that mean?
‐ Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
‐ May I have your attention.
I have new orders
for you people.
‐ [Yurika] Excuse me, sir.
‐ Yes?
‐ Although Nergal
may have signed an
alliance with the armed forces,
our contract gives us the
right to refuse orders
that we deem to be unacceptable.
‐ Well, yes, technically.
‐ Then please submit
all new orders
directly to me so
I can determine
whether or not these
orders are in the
collective best
interests of the crew.
Is that clear?
‐ In other words,
you won’t be treated
like pawns in a war game.
Well, I don’t think
you’ll have anything
to complain about this
time since we’re not
asking you to fight.
‐ What?
‐ Our mission is to
elude enemy detection
and conduct a daring rescue.
‐ It’s a rescue mission?
‐ Yes, though I’m afraid
this assignment may
lack the glamor of
your attempt to rescue
the Martian settlers.
Still, it should be noble
enough for you, correct?
(pinging)
Our data indicates that
there are now 26,037 chulips
scattered across the
surface of the Earth.
As you know, their
presence has made standard
methods of transport
extremely vulnerable.
But the Nadesico will
be a match for them.
This is our destination.
Uchatsurawatosk Island
in the Bering Straits.
That’s where we’re going
to be making our pickup.
‐ A question please.
‐ Now what?
‐ Just how did this person get
left behind in the first place?
‐ Let’s just say
that our investigator
was sniffing around when
a fleet of Grasshoppers
attacked and eliminated
his support team.
Very messy.
‐ Oh.
At this time of year,
the straights are nearly
impassable with
snowstorms and blizzards.
The Nadesico is the
only ship available
that may be able to
slip in undetected and
rescue our investigator.
‐ There’s trouble
with the old flame.
‐ Their childhood friendship
has certainly gotten chilly.
‐ And since his relationship
with the chanteuse
has hit a sour note.
‐ Here’s your
chance, lover girl.
‐ Will you females stop
the romantic chit‐chat?
If we can’t rescue the
investigator in the
next two days we may
lose him to the enemy!
Time is of the essence!
Don’t you agree, Captain?
‐ Absolutely.
Let’s do it!
(engines roaring)
‐ [Narrator] And so the
Nadesico headed off toward
Uchatsurawatosk
Island in Destiny.
‐ There’s not much
for pilots to do
on this mission is there?
‐ I guess we’re supposed to
save our strength for later.
‐ Saving our strength
and wasting our time.
(laughs)
(groans)
‐ I think you need
some discipline.
You heard me, come on.
And it’s not for the reason
you perverts are thinking.
(snickering)
(rapid gunshots)
There’s something
I’ve been meaning to
ask you about, Akito.
‐ Ask me about what?
‐ About the Captain.
I need to know more about her.
‐ What about her?
‐ So, are you and she an item?
‐ Huh?
Are you kidding?
And anyway why do
you want to know?
‐ Because of something
she said to me.
‐ I’m sorry, but my
heart already belongs
to someone else.
He’s been my knight
in shining armor
ever since I was really small.
‐ She’s a nut ball.
‐ So you’re not interested.
Well, that works
out well for me.
‐ Huh?
Oh crap!
‐ Then she is mine
for the taking!
(laughs)
(mechanical whirring)
‐ What was that?
Since when was clubbing allowed?
‐ In real combat,
there are no rules.
‐ Oh is that so?
Well, let’s just
go another round,
no holds barred
then, you cheater!
‐ Yeah, all righty then.
(screams)
‐ Eat this.
(laughter)
You still have much to learn.
‐ [Yurika] We’re now
approaching the Bering Strait.
The blizzard has reduced
our visibility to zero.
‐ But still, this
means conditions for
the enemy are also horrible.
That is not necessarily
a bad thing.
‐ Optical scanning indicates
there are few reefs
that pose a danger to us.
We oughta be able to make it
through with a little luck.
‐ All right, let’s
go in low and slow.
‐ Oh, Miss Nanako,
you’re prettier than
a prairie dog’s ear.
‐ Oh, Cowboy Johnny!
‐ How dare he touch
Nanako that way.
‐ Geez, what a show off.
‐ You’re worried ’cause
Nanako likes him.
Shut up, Chupe!
What’s a brat like you know?
‐ Hello, Akito.
I have a surprise for you.
(door whirring)
Okay, here we are!
(groaning)
‐ Shouldn’t you be at your post?
‐ The weather
conditions are so bad
that the radio is
pretty much useless.
I don’t have much to do now.
‐ Oh, I see.
‐ And for that matter
I understand that
Izumi could handle any
piloting assignments
all by herself.
‐ Well, assuming the
Jovians don’t show up.
(mechanical whirring)
‐ Let’s see.
How century high school?
That sounds interesting.
Let’s leave the clothing at
the default settings
for now, okay?
‐ What?
‐ Welcome to the virtual
recreation center.
This room was created to relieve
the crew’s stress
while in space.
Each person’s brain waves
are automatically analyzed
in an appropriate scenario
for psychological‐
(computer buzzing)
‐ So are you ready to find out
what going to school
together might’ve been like?
Let’s go.
(machine beep)
(Akito screaming)
(children yelling)
‐ Whoa.
(giggling)
‐ Oh, Mr. Tenkawa.
So what do you think?
Do you like it?
(sputtering)
‐ Where’s the rest of it?
Yes, the skirts
were pretty short
back in those days.
Hey, you’ve never
been here before,
have you, Akito?
‐ Not really.
Well you see, in this scenario,
you’re my student advisor
for after‐school activities.
Oh, come on.
It’s time to relax.
How are we going to relieve
all that stress of yours
if you get all tensed up?
How am I not supposed to
be tense in this situation?
‐ Oh, Mr. Akito,
isn’t there something you
want to get off your chest?
‐ Off my chest?
I’m glad I tweaked the setting
to be a little more adult.
‐ Where has our
communications officer gone?
Are you sure you’re old
enough to know that, Ruri?
I think so.
‐ Are you certain?
I think she’s in the virtual
reality room with Akito.
‐ Are they on a date?
Yes, all alone together,
getting a head job,
so to speak (snickers).
That sounded dirty, didn’t it?
‐ Yeah.
(giggling)
‐ Captain!
Captain Misumaru!
‐ Huh?
‐ Why are you just
staring into space?
Don’t you have duties
to attend to right now?
‐ Yeah.
‐ If this is how
you normally act,
It’s no wonder you can’t
keep your boyfriend.
(gasping)
‐ You know, Erina’s pretty bossy
for someone who’s
just a houndswoman.
‐ Well, she used to be that
chairman of Nergal’s secretary.
And she’s also a bit of a‐
‐ You two.
Return to your places at once.
‐ Yes, ma’am.
‐ And you two belong
at your stations.
‐ Right.
Someone’s got to install some
order around here, captain.
(sighs)
Oh, Akito.
Do you really like
Megumi more than me?
(lock clicks)
‐ Huh?
Hey.
Hey, wait a minute.
Why did you just lock the door?
I thought you wanted to
talk to me about something.
‐ Yes, something very private.
‐ Something private?
‐ I know that you’re entering
the upcoming art competition.
‐ I am?
‐ And I was hoping that
you’d use me as your subject.
‐ Oh, okay.
Since this is all make believe,
I guess I can swallow that.
Well, I’m very
flattered by your offer.
‐ You know...
(clothes ruffling)
(bells chiming)
(gasping)
I wouldn’t do this
for anyone but you.
(gasps)
‐ No, you can’t do that, Megumi.
I mean, we’re still
high school students.
And we’re just not
old enough yet.
(wind harshly blowing)
‐ [Ruri] We’re all
clear, Captain.
No obstacles ahead.
Switching to Autopilot.
Um, Captain?
‐ Huh?
‐ Everyone’s gone to lunch.
Aren’t you feeling hungry, yet?
‐ Oh, I’m fine.
Why don’t you go ahead, Ruri.
‐ Sure.
‐ Akito, do you love her too?
‐ Stop it.
‐ Why are you so angry at me?
I know that you like me.
You took my first kiss.
‐ That’s just a
little different.
Will you please put
your clothes back on?
‐ Don’t you care about
me anymore, Akito?
‐ Huh?
Well...
I of course.
‐ Because the truth is
that I love you, Akito.
I do.
‐ Oh, Megumi...
‐ If the two of them...
If Akito and Megumi are...
If they...
(gasps)
I won’t believe it.
(machine beep)
(computer alarms)
(Captain gasps)
Oops.
(ship whirring)
‐ Please kiss me.
‐ Megumi, I...
‐ I just want something that
means there’s still hope.
‐ Yurika?
‐ Huh?
(Akito yells)
(alarms blaring)
‐ It’s a full squadron alert.
That means we must
be under attack!
(lasers blasting)
‐ Maintain our
shields and retreat.
‐ The distortion field
is holding steady.
‐ 10 more seconds ’till
we’re out of their range.
‐ [Ruri] Gravity
sensors indicate
numerous high
mobile enemy units.
‐ How far are we going
to pull back, Captain?
‐ Weigh our options.
(overlapping chatter)
(happy fanfare music)
(ships whirring)
(wind harshly blowing)
‐ [Rori] These are the
enemy numbers and positions
as indicated by our
magnetic resonance scan.
‐ Of course, they all know
where we are now, too.
Thanks to the captain
and that stupidity with
the gravity cannon.
‐ Well, there’s no sense
crying over spilled milk.
(scoffs)
‐ What was that?
‐ Why worry about something
you can’t change (chuckles)?
‐ Sysis my responsibility.
If someone is to be
help responsible,
it would be me for
leaving my post.
I apologize.
(guffaws)
‐ Could it be that
cool and logical Ruri
is actually covering
for the captain?
‐ Has she discovered
her human feelings?
‐ Idiots.
‐ Since we were detected
in the Western Passage,
we’ll have to try to sneak in
through the Eastern
Island Straits.
We’ll have to fly in
at a low altitude,
at a 72% chance of
running aground.
Unfortunately, I’m afraid
that that’s our best option.
‐ The Nadesico will
embark in 10 minutes
and will proceed through
the Eastern Passage.
Aestivalis units are to
stand by at alert status.
That’s all.
‐ I wonder what
happened to the Captain?
‐ Maybe she snuck off
some place to cry.
‐ I’ll be right back!
‐ Hey, wait up, Tenkawa!
Sheesh.
(solemn piano music)
‐ Yurika...
(groans)
(machine whirring)
(gasps)
‐ Akito!
‐ Yurika...
(buzzing)
This might sound kinda
strange coming from me,
but I get worried when
you’re not all spastic.
It’s just not like you to be
acting serious and responsible.
‐ Akito.
Help me.
‐ Huh?
‐ Help me, please.
I don’t know who else
to turn to anymore
except you, Akito.
I’m such a clutz
and I keep messing this
up for everyone else.
Or do you hate me now too?
(crying)
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t.
‐ I just want something that
means there’s still hope.
(gasps)
‐ I’m...
I know a trick that’ll help.
Yurika...
‐ Hold it.
You’re not doing this
because you feel
sorry for me, are you?
‐ Excuse me?
‐ I know that when
we were on Mars,
I asked for a kiss to
help me keep going.
But you didn’t kiss me
because you knew I had to
find the strength myself.
‐ Huh?
‐ At the time, I
didn’t understand why.
But afterwards,
it all made sense.
You know me better
than I know myself.
And I know you’d never waste
something this precious.
‐ Um, waste what?
‐ Oh, Akito.
I know you know I’ve
never been kissed before.
(gasps)
(bell chimes)
‐ Wait a second.
What do you mean,
"Never been kissed?"
‐ Mm‐hmm.
I’m waiting for true love.
‐ You don’t remember?
(gasps)
(alarms blaring)
‐ It’s another enemy attack!
I guess that means
we’ll have to continue
some other time.
Won’t we, Akito?
‐ Yeah, sure, whatever.
(ships roaring)
(tense music)
(lasers blasting)
‐ Well, look who’s back.
‐ I’m sorry I’m late.
May I have the status
report, please?
‐ We are currently passing
through the Island Reefs.
‐ You know, it
would be very nice
if you could just hurry
up and get on with it
so our investigator
won’t starve to death.
‐ So that he won’t
starve to death?
‐ But wouldn’t he be more
likely to freeze to death
under these kind of
weather conditions?
‐ No, not with all that
insulating body fat.
‐ Huh?
‐ Look, just hurry
up and get him.
(screams)
(rapid explosions)
‐ Yurika, can you give
me the coordinates
where the investigator’s
supposed to be?
‐ Coordinates?
‐ [Akito] Yurika, come on.
Proceed to map coordinates A‐13.
Ryoko, you and the others
will form a defensive screen.
‐ Rodger.
(machines blasting)
‐ Hey, try not to steal
all the good scenes, okay?
‐ If you’re so hung
up on the captain,
you should welcome escort duty.
(chuckles)
(heroic music)
(lasers blasting)
(machines whirring)
(gun fire)
‐ Here we go.
Buttercup formation.
(waves crashing)
(yelling)
(machine beeping)
‐ All right.
Where is he?
(gasps)
(ship engines roaring)
Damn it.
I’m almost at the edge of
the Nadesico’s energy range.
Oh, crap.
The blizzard must be
blocking the transmission.
(engine roaring)
(gun fire)
Man, I can’t see a thing
with all this snow
blowing around.
Hey, wait a second.
Let’s try something that
doesn’t have to be aimed.
Eat this!
(gun fire)
Flare!
(loud explosion)
‐ Akito?
‐ Akito...
‐ He’ll be back.
I’m sure of it.
(loud machine whirring)
‐ Where’s Tinkawa?
‐ He’s taking his sweet time.
He’ll be back.
‐ I see.
‐ Ryoko.
‐ Don’t give up yet, Ryoko.
‐ I won’t.
I know he wouldn’t dare
break this girl’s heart.
‐ I’m afraid that it’s hopeless.
‐ Even at full power,
he should be able to fly
for another 15 seconds.
‐ Electromagnetic
static lifting,
radio transmission
is now possible.
(wind howling)
‐ No Aestivalis I
dentification signal detected.
‐ No incoming transmissions.
‐ Akito.
‐ Oh, our poor investigator.
Oh well.
‐ He’s gone.
And it’s all my fault.
I sent him out to a
cold, lonely death!
‐ [Akito] Um, not really.
(Yurika gasps)
‐ Akito!
‐ [Akito] Can you come get me?
‐ But just where are you?
‐ [Akito] Down here.
(gasps)
(heroic music)
(Yurika giggles)
‐ You really are okay!
‐ [Akito] Well, I’m
in one piece, anyway.
But admiral,
please don’t tell me this
is the special investigator
you were talking about.
(bear roars)
‐ Well, I suppose you’re
wondering about that.
You see, the military
spent a lot of money
equipping that bear with all
those sensitive instruments.
But we knew that no one
would risk their life
to rescue a bear so we
named him, "Ambassador."
It was just a little white
lie, Captain (laughs).
(elevator whirring)
‐ Oh, that God, Akito.
I’m so glad you’re all right.
I was so worried about
what might’ve happened.
‐ I’m sorry,
but I need to report back
to the Captain first.
(footsteps)
(scoffs)
‐ Pilot Tenkawa
reporting, Captain.
‐ Well done, pilot.
(giggles)
I mean thank you, Akito, dear.
(gasps)
‐ Has she really
forgotten our first kiss?
‐ Hmm?
‐ Oh, nothing (chuckles).
(laughter)
(bright music in
foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] They say that
man cannot live on bread alone
But Akito may have to
if he wants to keep
his stomach in tact.
In the old days, men were
men and women were women.
But all this equality
of the sexes stuff
has really screwed things up.
Fortunately, there’s
plenty of the old Tabasco.
As we venture onto the meat
for our first swimsuit episode.
But our young hero may not
live long enough to enjoy it
when yet another mysterious
lady enters his life.
What is it with this guy?
It’s the next episode of
Martian Successor Nadesico,
the Dangers of Femininity.