(soft music)
‐ [Ruri] Time has
passed rather quickly
since the Nadesico broke
through the earth’s big barrier.
Our backup pilot’s
been like this
and our Captain’s
been like this.
The crews mutinied,
then changed their minds
and we’ve still made it to Mars.
Isn’t it amazing?
But now that we’re here,
will we be able to win?
("You get to Burning"
by Yumi Matsuzawa)
(singing in foreign language)
(whooshing)
‐ You wanna piece of me?
(computerized beeping)
Take this.
(yelling)
(triumphant music)
‐ Hikaru.
Connect the dots.
‐ Got it.
(explosions)
(triumphant music)
Now that’s a pretty picture.
(laughing)
(groans)
‐ Let’s keep our head,
or we’ll be dead.
‐ [Ryoko] Well who
brought that on?
‐ [Izumi] You were
kind of showing off.
‐ A ship is but a shell, it’s
hull lies in vacuum hell,
no robot, pug, nor alien
race chills my soul
as cold as space.
Or something like that.
I’m sorry, sometimes I
get moody.
(growls)
‐ And that’s the
understatement of ye year.
(whooshing)
(triumphant music)
‐ Jeez, is everyone in this
firefight screwing around
except me?
Hm?
(whoosh)
(triumphant music)
(yelling)
I hate inertia, I
hate it. (grunts)
(whooshing)
(sighs)
(triumphant music)
(shinging)
(lasers firing)
(zapping)
‐ Captain, I think you
should recall the Aestivalis.
‐ It’s not necessary, sir.
Come on, Akito.
‐ What?
‐ The enemy is equipped
with gravity blast cannons,
is that what’s
worrying you, Admiral?
There’s no need
to worry about it.
Our distortion fields
and offensive weapons
are far more powerful
than theirs are.
They can’t even touch us.
As long as we possess
the technological edge,
we are nearly invulnerable.
(whooshing)
‐ [Ruri] Enemy forcefields
are strengthening.
‐ [Ryoko] What?
(whooshing)
Damn, we can’t get
through that shield.
‐ [Izumi] Look like the
Reaver’s going to claim veal.
(all yelling)
‐ Come on.
(yelling)
(whooshing and yelling)
Damn, that’s a tough field.
‐ Watch where
you’re goin’, jerk.
‐ Sorry.
‐ That was great,
except for that bungled
ending, of course.
‐ Huh?
‐ We’ll bury you
with full honors.
‐ Bury?
‐ Izumi.
‐ So what are we gonna
do, we’re really stuck.
(sighs)
‐ I know.
(whooshing)
(triumphant music)
‐ Tenkawa, that’s crazy.
‐ It’s suicide.
‐ No it’s not,
it’s just a matter
of picking the right angle.
(groaning)
(whooshing)
(blasts)
Demigod lance.
(triumphant music)
(roaring and explosions)
‐ 80% of the enemy units
have been vaporized.
Atmospheric entry now
possible. (beeping)
Coordinates.
‐ Thank you, Ruri‐Ruri.
‐ Huh?
‐ Okay, is everybody
ready for this?
It might get a little
bumpy for a bit.
‐ Recall the Aestavalis.
‐ Already done.
(whirring)
(footsteps)
(chaching)
‐ Uh uh.
‐ Huh?
‐ I’ll buy.
‐ You left us with our
eyes bugging out. (sproing)
(startled skwawk)
‐ Don’t mind the junior geek.
You did good.
(whooshing)
(peaceful music)
‐ [Minato] Entering
Mars thermosphere,
phase transition engine
reaction power decreasing.
‐ [Megumi] What
are those things?
‐ Those are nanomachine
collectives.
‐ Nano?
‐ Machines.
Small, self replicating robots.
The mars colonists
seeded the clouds
with nanomachines to give
the planet an atmosphere
similar to earth’s.
‐ Hm.
‐ Yes, and the nanomachines
serve a dual purpose.
For even as they
continue to maintain
the stable atmospheric
composition,
they also function as shields
to protect the surface
from harmful space radiation.
‐ [Minato] Passing
through the first layer
of nanomachines.
‐ Isn’t it dangerous
to have something like that
passing through the Nadesico?
‐ There’s nothing
to worry about.
I remember people on Mars
were always swallowing
or inhaling nanomachines
by accident.
But if you wait a few days,
they just come
out the other end.
(gasps)
‐ That’s right, you were born
on Mars, weren’t you, Captain?
‐ Oh, is that so.
‐ [Yurika] Minato, stand by
on the gravity blast cannon.
‐ Yes, ma’am, but may I
ask why we didn’t use it
before this?
‐ Because I don’t think we’ve
seen their real force yet.
There’ll be a second wave.
Turn the bow toward the planet
and engage the batteries.
(yelling)
‐ How about some
gravity control here?
‐ I don’t get it.
Why is it that he always
gets all the chicks? (yells)
(whooshing)
(zapping and explosions)
‐ [Rurika] All enemy
units vaporized.
No signs of Jovian activity
within a 30 kilometer
radius of the Nadesico.
‐ Prepare the landing
ship immediately.
We’ll send a search team down
to scout out the surface.
‐ But sir, where should we land?
We’ve checked the satellite data
and there appear to
be no active colonies
remaining on the planet.
‐ Our first stop will be
the Derkal research facility
at Mount Olympus.
‐ It figures, business
first, is that it?
‐ Actually our research
facility was built to double
as a survival shelter.
‐ Now, for the landing party.
‐ Excuse me, I’d like
to borrow an Aestavalis.
‐ For what?
‐ I’d like to go see my home?
‐ You mean the Utopia colony?
‐ Hmm.
‐ [Seiya] I don’t know, that
area was completely devastated
and there’s a chulep lying
on the ground nearby.
‐ [Akito] I know, but I’d
just like to see it again.
(crosstalk)
‐ Let him go.
(gasps)
‐ But sir.
‐ I know I’m just a figurehead,
but I’m still technically in
charge here, isn’t that right?
Nobody should be denied
the chance to go back home.
Especially in times like these.
‐ Oh, thank you very much sir.
(beeping)
‐ Shaadow one, lifting off.
(whooshing)
(whirring)
(hisses)
(whoosh)
(whirring)
(footsteps)
‐ Huh?
Hey, what are you
doing, you’ll get hurt.
‐ Megumi, hi.
‐ I was wondering if I could
tag along with you. (chuckles)
‐ Um, but why?
‐ So I could see your roots?
‐ You can’t do that.
‐ I don’t get it,
why is it always him?
‐ I have no idea, I say that
those that look most unlikely.
‐ Unlikely?
(growling and yelling)
(thuds)
(whooshing)
‐ Wow, it’s gorgeous.
Is the place you live
very far from here?
‐ Huh, I (stammers).
‐ We could court
marshal her, right?
‐ I don’t really think it’s
such a big deal, Captain.
Do we need her right now?
‐ Well no, but it’s the
principle. (muttering)
(growling)
‐ Leaving, Captain?
(stammering)
‐ I know, Jun can take command
for just a little bit,
couldn’t you Jun, huh?
‐ Not without a good reason.
(sighs)
(gasps)
‐ That ought to do it,
Gekki, take command.
(growls)
‐ Are you nuts?
(baffs)
‐ You’d probably
do a better job.
(solemn music)
‐ This doesn’t look good, it
looks like it’s been abandoned
for months now.
‐ Yeah, whoever was here
left a long time ago.
‐ So anyway, what was
Nergal doing out here
in the middle of nowhere.
‐ [Seiya] Discovering
the Nadesico.
‐ What?
‐ This is where it began.
In this place, would
you like to see?
(triumphant music)
(quiet whirring)
Well, this is it.
(gasps)
It’s been nearly 30 years
since our research teams
discovered this.
That’s how long it took for us
to begin to decipher
its secrets.
(gentle harp music)
‐ Um, can I ask you something?
‐ Sure.
‐ The Captain’s family,
were you very close to them?
‐ Well they were in the military
and both of my parents
were scientists.
‐ But I guess stuff like that
didn’t matter much
to kids, did it?
‐ I guess. (gasps)
(giggling)
‐ [Child Yurika] Look at
me, Akido, I’m a pilot.
‐ [Child Akido]
What are you doing?
You’re not supposed to
be in there, Yurika.
‐ [Child Yurika] It’s
alright, firing engines.
Forward launch. (giggling)
(panicked crying)
(grunting)
‐ Come on. (grunting)
I can’t stop it.
(slap)
(whimper)
(crying)
‐ In the end, I was
the one who got blamed
for messing with the machine.
But what really
made me frustrated
was that I couldn’t
control the machine
in the first place.
I guess that’s why I got
this nanocontroller. (gasps)
‐ But you became a cook.
Why a cook and not a pilot?
‐ Oh, well it’s because
the food’s so bad.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Akito] Take a look, see them?
(gasps)
(screams in disgust)
‐ Just what are those things?
‐ They’re nanomachines.
‐ You mean like the ones
that make the atmosphere here?
‐ Uh huh, thanks to these guys,
we can breathe
without a respirator.
But cultivating the soil
will take a while yet.
Plants taste funny.
But a good cook can make
all of them taste wonderful.
That’s like magic to me.
I guess...
‐ And that’s why you wanted
to become a cook, right?
I see.
‐ Um yeah.
‐ That’s so sweet.
But I guess that you’re
a pilot now instead, huh?
‐ Uh, I guess it means
I don’t have much
resolve.
‐ No, that’s not true.
You’re not a quitter,
I know you’re not.
You work harder
than anyone else.
You never give up.
It’s true, you know.
(stammers)
Did I say something wrong?
Did I offend you somehow?
‐ But, no, it’s not that.
‐ Then what did I say?
Why did you pull away like that?
‐ It’s just that I
(distorted noises)
don’t know, I kind of
thought of something odd.
‐ You know, when I
quit my last job,
I was looking for something.
I was looking for someone
who was real responsible,
( grunting and crashing)
see, and focused on a goal.
Someone like you, Akito,
that’s why I, huh?
Akito, Akito?
(screams)
(rumbling)
(groans) That hurt.
Akito, where are you?
(groaning)
‐ He’s on the planet Mars.
(surprised grunts)
I think you should get
off your boyfriend now,
he’s turning blue.
(grunting)
(yells)
I"m not sure whether to welcome
you or to throw you out,
so I think I’ll compromise
by making you drink
some of my nasty coffee.
(suspenseful music)
I suppose I need to
explain a few things.
This is all that’s left.
Every single survivor from
all the Martian colonies
has gathered here.
Fortunately the Jovians don’t
really seem to be interested
in people.
‐ My god, you guys made it.
This is better than
I ever dreamed.
You can all go
back to earth now.
I was afraid there’d
be nothing left,
but you’re really here.
I’ve got to call our sup...
‐ We’re not leaving.
‐ Why not?
‐ That would require
a long explanation.
‐ I’ll settle for
the cliffs notes.
‐ [Figure] Because
here at least,
there’s a chance of survival.
Your ship will never
make it back to earth.
‐ Look, we’ve fought hard
to get back to this planet
to rescue you and
you have no idea
how powerful the Nadesico is.
‐ I know all about the Nadesico.
‐ You do?
‐ Of course I do.
I helped design the Nadesico’s
phase transition engines
and distortion field.
I’m Inez Fressange and I
know what I’m talking about.
‐ you worked for Nergal?
(surprised yelling and rumbles)
‐ Akito, Akito.
Oh, there you are, Akito.
I was worried about you,
so I came to find you.
‐ Worried about
what, I won’t ask.
Tenkawa landing party confirmed.
(shing)
(machinery chirping)
‐ In other words, go away
we don’t wanna be saved.
Is that what you’re saying?
‐ That’s correct, all of
the surviving colonists
wish to remain here on Mars.
It is their opinion that
boarding the Nadesico
for the journey back to
earth would be suicide.
And as this ship’s
designer, I agree with them.
The Nadesico will not
survive this mission.
‐ Please reconsider ma’am.
The Nadesico has
beaten the lizards
in every single exchange
of hostilities thus far.
You’ll be quite safe.
‐ (frustrated
groan) You’re wrong.
How much do you really know
about these Jovian
lizards, Mr. Hoary?
Have you any idea how
advanced their technology is?
What are their goals,
why are they here?
‐ So you’re just
going to give it up?
‐ We’re not, you’re the ones
who won’t face the facts.
Your actions are so predictable,
you may think you’ve had
a little success to date,
but have you really?
(stammers)
‐ You know you can
only analyze so much.
‐ Right now you’re
letting your hormones
cloud your judgment,
little girl.
Not everyone can be a hero.
‐ That’ll be enough.
‐ Hmm?
‐ [Ruri] Captain,
enemy forces incoming,
five large battleships,
30 smaller warships.
‐ Stand by on the
gravity blast cannon.
‐ Engaging power coils.
‐ Gravity blast energy charging.
(whooshing)
‐ Fire.
(zapping and explosions)
Yeah, we did it.
‐ [All] Huh?
(rumbling)
(ominous music)
‐ How could they survive
a full gravity blast?
‐ You see?
The enemy also has
distortion fields.
So much for a quick
and easy victory.
(anxious music)
‐ [Ruri] The enemy are
reinforcing their numbers
from a chulep 40
kilometers ahead.
‐ What’s going on, how
can it hold so many ships?
‐ They’re not coming out of it,
they’re coming through.
Those chuleps are actually
dimensional gates,
who knows how many
warships are still waiting
on the other side, waiting
for the order to advance.
‐ [Ruri] Enemy
continuing to reinforce.
‐ Their fields
can’t be invincible,
go to continuous fire.
‐ Huh, right.
Rearm the gravity blast cannon.
‐ We can’t.
‐ That’s right, we’re
not in a vacuum, Captain.
The phase transition engines
can’t generate enough power
to sustain continuous fire.
(tense music)
‐ So what now?
‐ There’s no way we can fight
that many of them is there?
‐ Bring up the distortion field.
‐ You can’t.
‐ If we raise
the distortion field now,
the ground underneath the
Nadesico is going to collapse
under the pressure.
If that happens, all
the survivors down there
will be crushed to death.
(dramatic music)
‐ Minato, take us up
and raise the shields.
‐ We can’t.
It’ll be 20 minutes until
we can divert enough power
from the fields for
sufficient thrust.
‐ Enemy fleet is taking up
position above the Nadesico.
The chulep continues to
reinforce the enemy’s numbers.
‐ [Inez] Either raise your field
or take on the enemy’s
attack without it.
‐ [Seiya] Well I’m
afraid this decision
may be too much for
our Captain to handle.
‐ [Hoary] (grunts)
We have no choice.
‐ But what about those
people, Akito and I told them
we were here to help them.
We said that we’d come back
to Mars in order to save them.
How can you betray
them like this?
They’re all going to die.
‐ Akito.
(tense music)
‐ Enemy in position.
Captain?
‐ [Prospector] This is
no time to be indecisive.
Activate the automatic
defenses now.
‐ [Ruri] The Captain has still
not given the order, sir.
They’re activating
their Graviton cannons.
(tense music)
(inaudible speaking)
(Zapping)
(explosions)
‐ Our fates were sealed when
the first chuleps appeared.
Even without the
fields the shelter
would have been destroyed
by that barrage.
At least this way,
it came quickly.
We all knew this day
would come, Captain.
Nobody really expected
you to be able to save us.
(tense music)
(gagging)
‐ Yurika.
‐ Ruri, maintain
dissociation field integrity.
(water running)
(sighs)
Why did we come here, Akito?
Why did we bother?
What’s the point, we
didn’t save anyone.
I couldn’t save them.
I failed.
‐ [Akito] Yurika.
(gasps)
(mournful music)
‐ This is the first time
you’ve been nice to me
since you came onboard the ship.
‐ Stop it, pull
yourself together.
‐ Akito.
‐ Huh?
‐ Please kiss me.
‐ Yurika.
I don’t think this is the time.
‐ Oh no, I didn’t mean
for you to kiss me
the way you kiss Megumi.
(squawks)
‐ What, you saw that?
Oh that was just something
something that...
‐ I don’t care.
It doesn’t matter, I just want
something that means
that there’s still hope.
‐ Uh. (stammers)
I’m sorry, I’m really sorry.
‐ Akito?
Megumi?
‐ Excuse me, Yurika.
But I don’t care if
you are the Captain.
I’m not going to lose.
‐ Uh huh.
And I’m not gonna lose either.
‐ Hm?
‐ We’re all going to beat
those Jovian lizards together.
‐ Uh. (chuckles nervously)
‐ That’s right, they’re
not gonna keep me down.
No siree, Bob, not me.
‐ That’s not what I meant
by what I was saying.
‐ We’re gonna fight.
‐ Oh, come on let me explain
what I meant.
("Watashi Rashiku"
by Houko Kuwashima)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] It was thought
that the battleship Nadesico
could withstand any attack,
but fate is a cruel mistress
and her cold embrace can
be fatal to the unwary.
As the diabolical might of
the mysterious battleships
encircles our heroes,
is the mighty Nadesico
about to embark upon
her final voyage?
In an epic saga
filled with limitless
soul stirring intensity and
beautiful romantic narrative,
the Nadesico may be
going down for the count.
Don’t miss the next
spectacular episode.
Because it could be my last.