‐ [Narrator] I know
we’re supposed to be
protecting the earth,
but our staff had a
really rough New Year
and everyone
decided to sleep in.
So since the animation’s
running a little late,
this time we present
a very special edition
of Martian Successor Nadesico.
‐ Darn, it’s gonna be a
show made of old clips.
‐ Dang.
(intense music)
(upbeat music)
(birds chirping)
‐ [Woman] So today’s
episode of Nadesico
is just a highlights episode?
‐ It looks more like an
introductory episode.
‐ Don’t you know that
they always do this
in the middle of animated series
so new viewers know
what’s happening?
‐ You’re pretty familiar
with this Jun Pay.
(chuckles)
‐ That’s not the only reason.
I’ll bet they were just
running behind schedule
and needed a quick
filler episode.
‐ You’re always such
a gloomy Guss, Joe.
‐ Hey, it’s starting!
‐ Yay!
‐ [Children Voiceover]
Three, two, one, kaboom!
Wee!
‐ It’s time to get
to know Nadesico.
Hey, kids, we’re back!
Come closer, it’s time to go
behind the scenes at Nadesico.
‐ Close up, please.
This special will be filled
with interesting facts
about the Nadesico.
‐ Oh, let me explain.
In 2195, Earth was confronting
the greatest threat
it had ever encountered.
‐ Abandon ship!
We’re gonna ram that thing!
‐ [Woman] To begin with,
a mysterious arm
of unmanned weapons
attacked and occupied Earth’s
colony on the planet Mars.
The aliens next
concurred the moon,
then advanced on
the Earth itself.
The United Earth Forces
were hopelessly outgunned
and unprepared for
such an attack.
Nothing we had could stop them,
not that is, until
Nergul Heavy Industries
created the high mobile
battleship Nadesico.
Her designation
is Nergul NDZ001,
total length 298 meters,
total height 106.8 meters,
total width 148 meters,
total weight 37,530 metric tons.
The ship is powered by
four nuclear pulse engines
and two face transition engines
and equipped with an
SVC‐2027 computer.
‐ Right, and now that you
know the basic specifications,
let’s take a tour of the ship,
beginning with the
bridge which is located
on the 12 and upper
most deck of the ship.
‐ [Yurica] As you can
see, our command staff
is ever vigilant
and alert and oops,
I forgot that everyone
has the day off today.
Nevermind.
‐ [Ruri] Directly
below the bridge
is the virtual reality room.
‐ I’ll explain.
The system automatically
analyzes the person’s brainwaves
and conducts a
psychological analysis.
It then creates a
virtual environment
calculated to help the
crew relieve themselves
of stress and
other primal urges.
For some reason, this
Japanese high school setting
is extremely popular.
‐ Hey, Akeyto, would
you like to pretend
that you’re my after
school advisor again?
‐ Huh?
‐ Come on, it’s time
to relax a little.
Don’t you want to
drop our inhibitions
and bare our inner souls?
(comical music)
(screaming)
I’m doing this for you.
‐ It’s not fair!
‐ [Woman] In addition to
the virtual reality suites,
we also have a meditation
room for zen meditation.
(bell rings)
‐ Owe.
‐ [Woman] The recreation
room, located on deck four,
is outfitted with a brand
new 2195 table tennis table.
Next to that is an
observation deck,
fitted with a
holographic projector
for adjustable scenery.
The air pressure
and oxygen levels
can also be adjusted at will.
Just below that is
the ships galley
where Mrs. Helmay
performs her magic.
‐ [Girl] Wow, doesn’t
that look wonderful?
‐ Hey, keep cooking, girls.
This is no time
for slacking off.
We’ve got a lot of hungry crew
members to feed, you know?
Pick up the pace if you
want to get off early
on New Years Eve.
‐ I don’t think I’m
such a bad cook myself,
but it’s amazing what
a real master can do.
‐ The Earth is small
but very diverse.
Every region has it’s own
different variety of flavors,
that’s why the
Nadesico cafeteria
has over 300 different
spices and seasonings.
I don’t like to boast but
that’s very impressive.
‐ [Man] They even stock
a nice selection of tea,
which tastes even better
with my special ingredient.
‐ [Mrs. Helmay] Emerald,
you leave that tea alone!
By the way, our most popular
dish is the Mars Bowl,
that’s rice with weenies
and stroganoff, mm!
‐ Personally, I like the
chicken fried rice the best.
Moving on, our next
stop is the Hanger Bay.
This is where we store
the Estovales robots
that defend our ship.
‐ [Yurica] Okay, let’s talk
about Estovales themselves.
‐ Hey, let me talk about
the Estovales, okay?
They’re the sexiest
robots you’ve ever seen!
We’ll start with the land
combat frame version.
Look at that amazing punch!
Behold it’s awesome mobility.
Oh, it’s so cool, I have
to take a sponge bath
every time it takes off.
Oh, and look at
the way it jumps!
But wait, there’s more.
Next there’s the
combat frame version.
‐ Hold on right there!
Leave this baby to me.
This is the robot for a
real hero to fight in.
Oh yeah, baby, check
out those thrusters.
But makes this hunk of heavy
metal so hot is the payload.
The one and only
indomitable me, Guy Digoji!
‐ [Ruri] Mr. Yamatta,
aren’t you supposed to be?
‐ Hey, it’s guy thing!
You wouldn’t understand.
Yeah, I haven’t had
this much fun in months!
And don’t forget the
Estabales’s special secret move.
Come on, everybody, let’s say
it all together with feeling,
Gragrat!
‐ We have the knowledge,
we have the technology,
world peace is at hand now.
‐ [Man] What in the hell
is that supposed to mean?
‐ You know, I’ve ridden on
Akeyto’s artillery frame.
‐ [Man] Oh, the artillery
frame, yes sir, baby.
This is build like a tank.
And then there’s
the zero G‐frame.
Those are for outer space work.
We have one for each
of our main pilots.
Akeyto Takowa, Reoko Subaru,
Ikaru Amatto and Azumi Maki.
Oh, that’s four right?
(triumphant music)
‐ Huh, I only know
three out of 10?
‐ It appears that
these grasshoppers
have a few legs up on us
in terms of defensive field.
‐ When did they get those?
‐ Who cares how
many legs they have?
We’re still one up on them
when it comes to
hand‐to‐hand combat!
All right, that takes
care of those lizards
but where in the
heck did they go?
Take cover!
‐ [Boy] The Estebales
that came to my rescue
was the very newest model.
‐ That’s a brand
new model Estebales,
a new frame, a new generator!
Look at that hand, look
at those thrusters!
Oh, it’s so smooth, I’m
in love, I’m in love.
‐ [Girls] Geez, what a loser!
‐ [Ruri] Nagarae Akatzki
joined us at the same time
that Arina Kinjowan came
onboad as Cohelm’s woman.
Personally, I think these
two are up to something.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Woman] We know next to
nothing about the Jovians,
their true nature, their goals.
Everything about them is
still cloaked in mystery.
And since they use
unmanned weapons,
we don’t even know
what they look like.
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
‐ [Woman] Yuko, it’s
coming your way!
(screaming)
It’s just a matter of
picking the right angle.
(screaming)
Get me again!
Lance!
‐ [Ruri] Somehow we’ve
managed to get by until now
but will we be able to deal
with the continued evolution
of the Jovian weapons?
‐ [Yurica] Oh, don’t
you just love anime?
It’s so imaginative.
‐ Wow, the fight sequences sure
are animated realistically.
‐ Eee, I wonder what’s
gonna happen to them next
do you suppose?
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
(dark music)
‐ What’s wrong, Prince Akara?
When will you have the
planet Earth conquered
as I have ordered?
‐ Very soon, sire.
I’m currently collecting
cultural information
regarding the earthlings.
‐ Data on the earthlings, aye?
Sounds interesting.
‐ Well, that’s enough
cold data for now.
How about some hot
gossip instead?
With 214 people living
and sleeping together
at all hours of the day,
things can be quite interesting!
For example, just
what’s going on
between the captain
and Akeyto Tinkowa.
Apparently, it’s been going on
e loncame onto this ship.
(screaming)
‐ I’m so sorry, I’m so
terribly, terribly sorry.
How could you
possibly forgive me?
Are you hurt, is
anything broken?
‐ Yes, it seems that
the relationship
between the captain
and Mrs. Tinkowa
goes back quite a ways.
‐ Don’t you feel like there’s
some kind of connection here?
(gentle music)
‐ Yes, there is.
‐ Aketo!
What’s wrong, does
your tummy hurt, Aketo?
‐ Shut up!
‐ Were you in a fight?
‐ Shut up, go away! (sobbing)
‐ Hey, wanna see a magic trick
that’ll turn you back to normal?
‐ Huh?
‐ Close your eyes, Aketo.
‐ Gross, what did
you do that for?
(laughing)
‐ I told that it would
turn you back to normal.
‐ Don’t ever do
that to me again.
(sobbing)
I can’t stop it.
‐ (sobbing) Aketo!
‐ Holy cow, I had no idea
all this was going on.
I’ve totally humiliated
myself for Eureka
and she’s still playing
around with the cook?
‐ Yes, yes, keep your shirt on.
‐ Oh, to be young
again sowing wild oats.
‐ And while they might
fight all the time,
sometimes they seem to
connect rather well.
‐ Why did we come here, Aketo?
Why did we bother?
What’s the point?
We didn’t save anyone.
I couldn’t save them, I failed.
‐ Eureka.
(dramatic music)
‐ You know, this is the first
time you’ve been nice to me
since you came aboard the ship.
‐ Stop it, please,
pull yourself together!
‐ Aketo, please, kiss me.
‐ Eureka, I don’t
think this is the time.
‐ I don’t care,
it doesn’t matter.
I just want something that
means there’s still hope.
Well?
Aren’t you in love
with me Aketo?
‐ Aketo, Aketo’s in
love with me, right?
‐ No, he’s in love
with me, you tramp!
‐ It’s me!
‐ No, it’s me!
‐ Poor Mr. Tinkowa,
it must be tough
having to act like an adult
with all those relationships.
It’s strange.
‐ Oh yes, it’s strange.
‐ But?
‐ But you’ll understand
once you’re grown up.
‐ Please, our ratings.
‐ By the way, those rabbit
ears, wear them tonight.
‐ How embarrassing.
‐ As I said, a lot
of interesting things
go on around here.
‐ (laughing) Lots
of naughty things.
‐ Naughty but nice things.
It’s on me.
(screaming)
Tinkoa!
‐ Tinkoa.
‐ Now, shut up you two!
I’ve had enough of this.
‐ Tinkoa, Tinkoa,
Tinkoa, Tinkoa, Tinkoa,
Tinkoa, Tinkoa, Tinkoa!
‐ Oh dear, what stress.
‐ Aketo!
‐ Aketo?
Aketo?
Aketo.
Aketo!
‐ [Narrator] With her hall full
of so many loves and passions,
the high mobile battleship
Nadesico sails on.
Were will she go?
What will be the fate of
the love between the two.
‐ How I wish to experience
this thing called love.
Will his royal
highness Prince Akara
never notice the way I
feel for him in my heart?
‐ Miyay, have you
finished collecting data
about earthling
culture for me yet?
‐ Oh, yes sire.
Please watch this screen.
This anime, Marian
Successor Nadesico
is the best source
of information
regarding earthlings.
‐ Anime, what is this anime?
‐ A form of entertainment
that uses pictures
to tell a story.
‐ What fools to be so infatuated
with tales of fantasy.
‐ Let’s do it, guys!
‐ Hm, so the earthlings allow
the genders to intermingle.
‐ Yes, many of their war stories
are mixed with stories of love.
It’s very romantic.
‐ What tripe, all
this love and romance.
How can one win battles when
preoccupied with such folly?
‐ Yes, my lord.
‐ Ah, by the great
gonzorks, what is that?
What kind of weapon
was that, MeaMea?
‐ Well, I am not sure, my lord.
But it appears to be a form
of inverted polarized
energy barrier
called a distortion field.
‐ Hm, I see.
Penetration by using the
force of repelling energy.
(chuckles) Oh, I like that.
And it gives me the perfect plan
for destroying Gecky
Ganger once and for all.
You have served me well MeaMea.
‐ Huh, oh, thank you.
I exist only to serve you.
‐ [Man] His royal highness
Akara’s custom robot,
The Big Akara, is ready.
‐ (chuckles) Just you
wait Gecky Ganger.
‐ Professor, an
unknown flying object
is closing in on the laboratory
at a ferociously fast pace.
‐ What, raise the force field!
‐ (laughing) That
won’t do you any good.
Distortion field on.
‐ What was that?
‐ It’s an earthquake!
‐ Ken, Ko, Akira,
a giant monster is
attacking the building.
You’ve got to destroy it.
‐ [All] Yes, sir!
‐ What’s wrong, Gecky Ganger?
If you don’t come
out and fight me,
I’ll destroy your secret base.
It’s judgment time!
‐ Come on, team!
‐ [All] Gecky Ganger, go!
(dramatic music)
‐ Gecky Gang beam!
‐ (laughing) No manner
of attack such as that
will have any affect on me.
Take this!
‐ Darn it, ugh!
Gecky Gang sword!
(gasping)
‐ Your little toys
will never be a match
for my brilliant
distortion field.
Die, Gecky Ganger!
‐ Father, Kanjo and
Akira are in danger.
You must do something.
‐ (laughing) And now you die!
‐ Must fight back!
‐ Ken!
‐ Professor?
‐ Yes, just configured
on it recently
and it hasn’t been tested
yet but we have no choice.
Ken, Jo, Akira, use
the Gekegan Flare!
‐ The Gekegan Flare!
‐ That’s right,
I anticipated that something
like this might happen
so I secretly developed
the Gekega Flare,
but be careful,
the three of you must be
perfectly synchronized
or the Gekaga will explode!
(dramatic music)
‐ But I guess we’ll
have to do it.
Watch out, here we go!
‐ Right!
‐ Gekegan Flare!
(upbeat music)
‐ What, what is
this blinding light?
‐ [Woman] Your highness!
‐ Damn you, earthlings,
you will rue this day!
‐ We did it, everyone.
But professor, how did you come
up with an attack like this?
‐ [Professor] Well, they
had it on Nadesico recently.
‐ What, you watch
it too, professor?
‐ [Professor] Yes, well in
any case, come right home.
We’ve got a special New
Years noodles to celebrate.
‐ Noodles, do you have
rice cakes ready too?
‐ [All] That’s for
tomorrows dinner. (laughing)
‐ Can we really release
an episode like that?
‐ Oh, one time is fine.
‐ Don’t worry, captain,
we’ll be back next time.
(upbeat music)
Hello, I’m Jennifer Earhart,
and I play Yurika Misumaru.
I hope you enjoyed
this special episode...
...of Martian
Successor Nadesico...
...as much as we
enjoyed making it.
Personally, the only thing
that I didn’t like...
...was that that
little tramp Megumi...
...made another
pass at my Akito!
I mean, just who does
she think she is?
And another... Huh?
Huh? All right..
In the next episode, we
finally find out who and
what the Jovian lizards are.
Hey, Yurika has a lot of good
lines in that one, doesn’t she?
She does? Good!
Anyway, don’t miss our
next thrilling episode...
..."The Significant Other
from a Star Far Away".