‐ [Yurika] Nobody expected
20‐year‐old Yurika Misamaru
to do well as the
captain of the Nadesico,
but thanks to her,
the world’s first
civilian space battleship has
overcome a takeover attempt
by Earth’s military.
Now, the high mobile battleship
is about to head to Mars.
(upbeat techno music)
To protect the Earth
from the Jovian invaders,
a series of defensive rings
has been placed
around our planet.
The first defensive line,
also known as the Big Barrier,
is composed of nuclear
fusion powered satellites.
Unfortunately, this
barrier works both ways,
and the Nadesico will have
to cross this obstacle
in order to leave
the Earth’s orbit.
I wouldn’t wanna die
in a place like this.
‐ We can’t afford to
overlook the existence
of the battleship
Nadesico any longer.
The time for wars between
individual nations is long gone.
The Earth has been
united by our struggle
to fight off these
mysterious attackers
from beyond Jupiter.
The crew of the
Nadesico, however,
seems to think that they
can have their own way.
How can we allow this
to go unpunished?
‐ Chief Commander,
we’re receiving
an emergency relay
via the White House.
‐ Now what?
‐ It’s the Nadesico, sir.
‐ Hi, happy New Year, everybody!
(shouting)
(indistinct talking)
Most of them don’t
understand our language.
Just let me chat a little while.
‐ However some of us
understand your language
quite well, Captain.
‐ Well, that makes things simple
which is good since we
don’t have much time.
The fact is that the
Nadesico will be able
to escape the Earth’s gravity
well in about three hours,
but unless you shoot the Big
Barrier down for a moment
to let us pass,
we’ll have to destroy
some of your barrier satellites.
So with that mind,
would you be nice and
shut the Big Barrier down
pretty please?
‐ You want us to
disable the Big Barrier?
Are you insane?
Forget it!
‐ Okay, we’ll just do
this the hard way then.
‐ That was the last straw.
If you cross the barrier,
you will all be outlaws.
‐ Is that so?
I guess we’ll have
to live with it.
‐ This is no longer
a time for debate.
This is the time for action.
In order to maintain order,
we must save the Nadesico.
‐ But if we destroy it,
we’ll lose the most
advanced weapon we have.
Over 70% of the Nadesico’s
crew are Japanese.
Admiral Misamaru, do you
have any thoughts here?
‐ Well, while she
is my daughter,
I’m taken aback by her boldness
and by the way she filled
out that kimono (giggles).
‐ [Female Soldier] Most
of our available forces
from the Pacific coastal
region are already in pursuit
are already in pursuit
of the Nadesico, sir.
‐ Good.
We should be able
to intercept her
before she makes it
to the stratosphere.
‐ In theory, however,
the sudden expansion
of the field operations
that we’ve employed
in order to collect the Nadesico
has caused the Jovians to
increase their own activities.
There are battles everywhere.
‐ I’ll never forgive
the Nadesico for this!
Launch the 3rd defensive line.
‐ Geki Gen Punch!
(screaming)
But the Geki Gen Punch is
made of yakigadian alloy.
‐ That is very
amusing, aren’t they?
However, action for you today!
‐ Oh not again!
‐ Yeah.
And just when it was
getting interesting too.
Why doesn’t Yurika do
something about those clowns?
‐ There’s not much she can do.
Our distortion
field was designed
as a countermeasure to
the lizard’s gravity blast
which means, grasshopper,
its use against
regular weapons is
compromised, comprende?
‐ Then why don’t you go fight
them with your Aestevalis?
‐ You still don’t get the
big picture, do you kid?
Robots aren’t for
fighting missiles.
They’re for fighting robots.
Wait till we get further out.
That’s when the real fun begins.
Oh yeah, baby.
We’ll be kicking
lizard butt galore
once we get past the
third defensive line!
And this time no cook
is gonna upstage me.
‐ Whatever floats
your boat, big guy.
‐ Yeah, right.
I’ll make sure that the
Nadesico reaches outer space
no matter what the
final cost might be,
and you better not get
in my way, fly cook boy,
or I won’t show you
the next episode.
‐ Wasn’t episode 26
the last episode?
‐ No, they changed the time slot
and did another full
season after that, dork.
‐ I’ve got to see
them pretty please.
‐ All right then,
but first promise
that you’ll stop
stealing my spotlight!
‐ [Hoary] As you know,
the Earth is shielded
by seven separate
lines of defense.
We’ll need to defeat
each of these barriers.
‐ Well we’ve already
gone beyond the range
of scram jet fighters,
and our reports say that
their airborne fleets
are all engaged in
multiple skirmishes
with the grasshoppers.
The current ground‐based
missile attacks
are a part of the third line,
and we should be
breaching the perimeter
at the fourth defense
line very shortly.
‐ This is so tedious.
Can’t we just blast our
way into outer space?
‐ Sorry, it’s not
that easy, I’m afraid.
‐ In order to break free of
the Earth’s gravity well,
we first have to reach
an escape velocity
of 11.2 kilometers a second.
To achieve escape velocity,
we’ll have to bring
the Nadesico’s space
transition engine online.
However, in order to
reach peak performance,
the engine needs to be
at a higher altitude.
Effective phase transition
cannot take place
below an altitude of
20,000 kilometers.
‐ But before we
can get that high,
we’ll have to get past the
third and second defense lines.
Now in theory our
shield should be able to
handle everything the
UF can throw at them.
‐ However, they do
seem to be weakening.
‐ Perhaps you should
change now, Captain.
‐ Oh yeah, good idea.
But before that.
My relationship
with Akito has been
on rather unsteady ground.
However.
Akito!
‐ [Ken] Joe!
‐ Huh?
What’s going on?
What are the two of
you doing in here?
‐ My poor Joe.
He sacrificed himself.
Oh the humanity.
‐ You see.
You see it, don’t you?
You understand?
‐ Huh?
‐ [Presenter] Thanks
to the sacrifices of‐‐
(voice drowned by sobbing)
But now Geki Gengar
3 is missing a pilot!
‐ Joe!
‐ Do you see?
This is the way a
man could go, man.
Dying in battle,
sacrificing himself
for the sake of friends.
‐ Thank you!
Thank you for
showing me the line!
‐ Oh you’re welcome.
‐ How can they pick that
over me in a kimono?
‐ Just how long do you
think you can get away
with locking us up like this?
This treatment is
clearly a breach
of all international
POW conventions.
‐ [Soldier] If you don’t quit
yapping about your rights,
I’m gonna have to introduce
an illegal hard mod
to your face.
Now shut up and
behave, soldier boy.
‐ Well?
‐ Almost too easy.
I can’t believe they use
rope in this day and age.
What a bunch of amateurs.
‐ I’m afraid I’m not
really in the mood
to go on Nadesico’s
little jog to Mars.
We’ll escape when the
fighting breaks out.
‐ You must listen to me, Aoi.
You are a junior officer with
a career in front of you.
‐ I’ve sworn to stop the
Nadesico at any cost, sir.
‐ But to receive
nanomachine treatment!
‐ He’s right.
There’s no reason why you
have to have this done.
‐ It’s of minor
consequence, Admiral.
Every pilot has to
do this eventually.
Without the nano injection,
the IFS won’t operate.
‐ I’ve completely
given up on Yurika,
so please don’t go.
‐ Gimme that!
(grunts)
‐ Stop wasting time!
Move it!
‐ Lieutenant, now that your
nano injection has taken hold,
you’ll be able to
control this delphinium
as if it was part of your body.
The attached external
fuel tanks will enable you
to stay alive for at
least one full hour.
Don’t forget to keep up
your thrust at all times.
‐ Thanks for your help.
‐ Sure, good luck, sir.
‐ Right.
(somber music)
Delphinium squadron,
intercept the Nadesico.
(dramatic music)
‐ Oh yeah!
Get out of my way.
Move it!
‐ Listen!
(indistinct talking)
‐ That idiot!
He’s not listening
to a word I’m saying.
I want the line to the bridge
disconnected right now.
‐ [Daigoji] Professor, lower
the laboratory’s force field
and let me at ’em!
‐ Hey, what happened to Tenkawa?
‐ [Daigoji] Tenkawa?
He’s in his room
crying like a baby.
Oh well, more for me.
‐ [Rumi] Nine Delphinium
fighters approaching
from 30 degrees to
port, as in left.
Elevation is 60 degrees,
distance is 8,000 meters.
‐ Enter danger, Geki Gengar.
Ah, and here come the bad guys.
Over in one big stinking pile!
‐ Here we go.
‐ [Yurika] How long until
we can have maximum thrust
from the PT engine?
‐ [Rumi] Another
19,750 kilometers.
‐ Stay on course, ma’am?
‐ Yes, stay on course.
‐ Oh yeah baby.
At long last, I can show
you how a real hero fights.
‐ Attack!
(screaming)
‐ You idiot!
‐ Hey, relax, pal.
(screaming)
All right, here they come.
Okay, Uribatake, drop
off the space Gengar
heavy armaments module.
‐ Mr. Yamada’s
requesting something.
‐ If he’s not willing
to listen to me,
I won’t listen to him.
‐ [Daigoji] Drop off
the Space Gengar heavy
armaments module, please?
‐ You can ask all you want,
but this ship doesn’t
stock any of these
Gengar geeky things.
‐ Maybe he means the
beam module for unit one?
‐ [Daigoji] Yeah,
yeah, that’s it.
‐ All right.
Here it comes.
Just make sure to catch it.
‐ This is great.
I’ll rush down below
them and lure them in.
The enemy thinks I
don’t have any weapons
but then I’ll combine
with the launched
heavy armaments
module in midair!
I’ll crush them
all in one sweep.
I call this plan
Operation Gengar Cross.
‐ [Uribatake] Whatever.
‐ Time to rock and roll.
All right!
Let’s go!
Gengar Crush!
‐ Hi!
Did the plan not work
out exactly right?
‐ Ain’t nothing.
Mind over matter.
Gai Super Upper!
(screaming)
This’ll do just fine.
‐ [Rumi] Mr. Yamada is
completely surrounded.
‐ [Hoary] It’s up
to you, Tenkawa.
‐ First he breaks
his leg, now this.
‐ Yurika, this is
your last chance.
Return the Nadesico to Earth.
‐ It’s Jun!
‐ You’re violating the
terms of our contract.
‐ Yurika, we’ll stop you
with force if we have to.
If you don’t turn around,
the third defensive line
will be focused on Nadesico.
‐ Uh‐oh.
‐ Please, I don’t
want to fight you!
‐ 19,650 kilometers
left to go, Captain.
‐ [Mr. Prospector] What
will it be, Captain?
‐ I’m sorry, Jun.
But I can’t turn back now.
‐ But why?
Why must you do this, Yurika?
‐ I’m doing it
because it’s my job.
I’m not just my
father’s daughter, Jun.
I’m a captain in my own right.
This is the only place
where I can be myself.
The real me.
‐ You mean?
Because of him?
All right then.
That’s that.
We’ll begin by
destroying that robot.
‐ Hey, let me go!
Stop it!
‐ Akito!
‐ What are you doing?
We were all friends just
a few hours ago, remember?
‐ You’re not my friend.
You’re my nemesis!
I challenge you, Akito Tenkawa.
One on one, man to man.
And if lose, I’ll have
my squadron withdraw.
‐ A duel?
‐ Not a bad deal, actually.
‐ Yeah, do it.
That’s the way real
men should fight!
‐ I don’t wanna fight you.
‐ You lousy coward!
Fight like a man.
‐ Stop it!
I don’t wanna fight you, Jun!
‐ [Soldier] We’re coming, sir.
‐ Oh no you don’t.
I’m your designated opponent.
And don’t you know
that interrupting
a duel of honor is nothing
short of really rude?
Right?
‐ [Rumi] Passing
third defensive line.
19,550 kilometers until we
can engage the PT engine.
‐ Phase transition engine at
50% and steadily increasing.
‐ What I don’t understand is
why Jun is so angry at Akito.
‐ Why, Captain, isn’t
this heart there
for everyone to see?
‐ Huh?
‐ It’s because Mr. Aoi is your‐‐
‐ He’s just a good friend.
‐ Uh‐huh.
‐ 19,400 kilometers
until PT engine burn.
‐ Wait a second, wait a second,
you’re getting this
all wrong, Jun.
I’m not even
interested in Yurika.
Cross my heart!
Space cook’s honor!
‐ I don’t believe you.
And besides this has nothing
to do with our personal lives!
‐ Then why do you wanna
fight so bad, you bone head?
It makes no sense!
‐ Since I was a child I’ve
dreamed of protecting the Earth.
That’s why I joined
the United Forces
to make those dreams
into a reality.
‐ I believed in the
same thing, Jun.
I believe that if you had faith,
you could make a
difference and be a hero.
I thought I could
change the world.
But I was wrong.
‐ I’m not like you.
‐ 19,000 kilometers
until PT engine burn.
‐ We’re now entering
the second line’s
missile envelope, Captain.
‐ I’m going to protect the
Earth no matter what it costs.
I’ve been ordered to stop you,
and that’s what I’m going to do.
I can’t let my personal feelings
come between me and my duty.
It’s a matter of honor.
It’s a matter of pride.
‐ You stupid moron!
‐ Oh!
‐ Yeah, way to go, Akito.
That’s the spirit.
That’s the way to fight
between a real man’s gotta be.
‐ Well, why did you stop?
‐ Because I’ve had
enough of this idiocy.
You don’t really think
that the two of us
hitting each other is
going to solve our problems
or win Yurika’s heart, do you?
‐ Don’t you understand?
I can’t let her become the
enemy of everything I hold dear.
I don’t have any
other choices left.
There’s no other way.
‐ The armed satellites
are now targeting the Nadesico.
‐ 18,000 kilometers until
ximumtransition engine burn.
‐ If the missiles come now,
we won’t be able to evade them.
(missiles firing)
‐ What’s going on?
I can’t move!
‐ I ran out of energy as well.
‐ [Rumi] Both Aestevalis
have gone beyond
our maximum energy
transfer range.
‐ Missiles launched
from armed satellites
approaching from
three directions.
‐ 10,000 kilometers
until PT engine burn.
‐ PT engine
accelerating smoothly.
‐ [Megumi] Armed
missiles approaching!
‐ He’s gonna block
’em with his robot.
‐ Jun!
‐ Jun, stop!
‐ I should’ve known.
I should’ve know that I
didn’t have what it takes
to be a real soldier.
The people in the military
are only interested
in fighting a war, not doing
what’s best for mankind.
I can see that now.
Yurika, maybe this
is what I was really
wishing for from the very start.
I would do anything
to protect you.
Wherever you are,
that’s where I belong.
‐ [Daigoji] For crying out loud,
quit trying to steal the show.
‐ I thought you
were immobilized.
‐ The Nadesico caught up to us.
‐ 300 kilometers until maximum
PT engine burn, Captain.
‐ Oh yeah, mama’s
really cooking now.
‐ Distortion field
at maximum strength.
‐ Get those fighters on board.
We’re going to breach
the Big Barrier.
‐ [Rumi] 100, 50, 10.
PT engine maximum thrust.
(dramatic music)
‐ Well you never know.
We may still be able to
become heroes after all.
And Jun, Yurika needs
someone to be her
knight in shining armor.
‐ You mean I can still
do that on the Nadesico?
‐ [Akito] You want
it, you got it.
‐ [Daigoji] Well, you
know, I was born a hero.
‐ Yeah, right.
‐ Don’t let them
breach the barrier.
I don’t care if the nuclear
power plants melt down!
(loud explosion)
‐ Well after that ...
‐ In order to keep the Big
Barrier up and running,
Earth had to use half the
power plants on the planet.
There are huge
blackouts everywhere.
‐ Yurika, I‐‐
‐ No, you have nothing
to apologize about.
I know that you did what you did
because you were worried
about me as a friend, right?
‐ Well actually‐‐
‐ And thank you, Akito.
Thank you for not hurting
my very best friend.
‐ Actually I didn’t
save him just because
he was your friend, you know.
‐ Come on, things are
bound to get better
as long as you’re alive.
Just make sure not to die
looking better than me,
all right, kid?
‐ What are those things?
‐ Oh these?
‐ [Akito] Geki Gengar stickers!
‐ [Daigoji] Yup, and I
took care of six buggies
so I’m gonna put six of
these on my Space Gengar.
‐ [Joe] Ken, finish him off!
‐ Joe, you must stop!
‐ [Ken] But, Joe,
what about you?
Joe!
‐ Don’t worry about me.
If we let them get away now,
they’ll demolish Tokyo.
Do it, Ken.
Ken!
Geki Gen Flare now!
‐ [Daigoji] Let me see.
I wonder where I
should put these now.
‐ [Soldier] Come on,
come on, come on.
‐ Hey!
Who are you?
(gun firing)
‐ [Ken] Geki Gen Flare!
‐ [Joe] Sorry, Miss Minako.
Looks like I won’t
be able to take you
to the beach like I promised.
(calm music)
‐ [Presenter] Don’t miss
our next exciting episode
as Akito takes his Aestevalis
out into the ever
expanding universe.
Don’t worry, Akito.
I’m covering your back.
What stellar dangers might
await our courageous adventurers
as they venture into
the vast sea of space?
Find out next time in
the next must see episode
of Martian Successor Nadesico.
Come, my sky blue space.
Oh yeah, and they’re adding
even cute girls to the cast.
Don’t miss it!