♪ You get me burning ♪
♪ It’s Christmas time
and I’m hot for you ♪
♪ I’ve got a present ♪
♪ Unwrap it baby ♪
♪ It’s a yule log ♪
(sighs)
(laughs)
♪ You get me burning ♪
(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
(hissing)
‐ Boson showing an exchange
reaction initiating.
‐ Test Aestivalis.
Are you ready?
‐ [Man] Roger.
‐ Lowering Aestivalis.
‐ [Man] Field expanding.
Massive amounts of photons,
gravitons and mesons
are being registered.
‐ [Man] Aestivalis
monitor, all stats nominal.
‐ All right, I’m about to
contact the jump field.
I am activating sensors now.
‐ [Man] Sensors on.
‐ [Pilot] Penetrating field
in three, two, one, contact.
‐ [Woman] May I inform
you that all attempts
at organic Boson Jumping
have ended in failure.
‐ Untrue.
In addition to the
proof provided by
the Nadesico’s jump from Mars,
our data indicates
that the croak
has appeared on Mars before
it disappeared on Earth.
Obviously, organic Boson Jumping
doesn’t adhere to your
existing theories, Professor.
‐ Perhaps.
However, your
theory that the CC’s
are the key to Boson Jumping
seems to have been disproved.
‐ I disagree.
The data that I
collected on the Nadesico
proves that organic
Boson Jumping
is possible with humans.
And we know how
the chairman feels.
Therefore, we will continue.
(bells jingling)
‐ [Woman] I’m so excited
about being invited
to Mr. Akatsuki’s party.
‐ [Woman] I never imagined
Christmas on a battleship
could be anything exciting.
‐ [Woman] Isn’t
Christmas wonderful?
‐ [Woman] Yeah, I’m glad I
got to go on the Nadesico.
‐ Come on, come on.
I see idle hands.
You’ve got to work
faster than that, girls.
If you want to get off
early for the party.
(laughing)
‐ Everyone, let’s
go out and party.
‐ And have a merry Christmas.
‐ Let’s not forget
what’s important.
This is a special time.
‐ It’s a time for
lords bearing presents.
‐ And for lords bearing flowers.
‐ And this lord comes
bearing the champagne.
(laughing)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ Christmas time for
just me and there.
That looks just
about perfect to me.
‐ I don’t know.
It looks a little crooked to me
and I think your eyes
aren’t big enough
and the perspective’s off.
‐ A Nergal Christmas party?
‐ [Yurika] That’s right.
I thought it would
be nice if we all
had a bash together
for a change.
‐ But you’re always making
others abash, Captain.
(snickers)
‐ But we’ve already been
invited to the party
Mr. Akatsuki’s giving.
‐ So what’s the
lineup for your party?
‐ The lineup?
‐ I mean, who have
you invited to come?
♪ I’ll be jolly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la la la ♪
‐ Hey, Megumi.
Are you coming?
‐ Oh I’m sorry, I don’t
think I’ll be there.
I plan on spending Christmas
with someone special
all by ourselves.
Under the mistletoe.
(laughs)
‐ I knew it.
Well if that’s the
way it’s gonna be,
I’ve got my angle.
After all, this is the time for
friendship and stuff, right?
Sorry, I’ll be busy.
Tenkawa, where are you, Tenkawa?
‐ Come to think of it,
where did Tenkawa run off to?
‐ [Women] Mm‐hmm.
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Akito] Maybe I’ll
just hide until Easter.
Do they ask how I feel?
‐ [Woman] Tenkawa, are
you in there, Tenkawa?
‐ [Narrator] What will
become of the future?
Scandals Q‐A‐Q.
This will be our last final‐‐
‐ The final episode.
I’ve watched every
episode through number 38.
But I just can’t
watch the last one.
‐ This is perfect.
Behold, my ultimate
party facility.
We’ve got three
dimensional Twister,
got that mistletoe and
see you spin the bottle.
‐ What?
‐ Okay ladies, come to papa.
‐ [Ruri] Didn’t you
know that everybody said
that they were going to
Mr. Akatsuki’s party?
(gasps)
(giggles)
‐ [Woman] There.
‐ I thought we were
being discreet.
‐ I don’t see anyone
else here, do you?
Let’s be bold and
daring for once.
Screens up.
What is this?
Are you telling me to
get off the Nadesico?
‐ I’m giving you the option.
‐ Don’t tell me that
you can’t handle
having me in the same
workplace as you.
‐ Don’t misunderstand.
This job is becoming dangerous.
‐ It’s been dangerous.
I think I can handle it.
‐ Once the crew is
officially drafted,
you won’t be able to
come and go so easily.
‐ I see.
So this is your
Christmas present.
(yelling)
‐ The UEAF can’t allow
a ship under its command
to be crewed by civilians.
Therefore, we’ve
reached a decision.
‐ Normally, all of
you would’ve been
booted off just like that,
but I went through
extraordinary steps
to request that the current crew
of the Nadesico be smoothly
incorporated into the military.
‐ Just whose idea was this?
‐ Well, this is very
difficult for me to say.
But after calculating
all the damages
that the UEAF
suffered as a result
of our little computer problem,
the damages we
would’ve had to pay
would’ve forced us to turn
to a military staff anyway.
‐ Two weeks ago, there
was a mysterious explosion
on the surface of the moon.
As a result, there’s
a distinct possibility
that the Nadesico
will be incorporated
into the lunar theater fleet.
‐ If anyone does decide
to leave the ship,
they’ll be subjected to
constant military surveillance.
So this is the best way.
‐ So what are you
going to do, Akito?
‐ Well, I wasn’t
really interested
in becoming a
career soldier but‐‐
‐ [Man] Oh, you
won’t have to worry.
‐ I won’t?
‐ The UEAF couldn’t
leave an Aestivalis
in the hands of
a novice forever,
so we’ve already obtained
a superb pilot as
your replacement.
‐ It’s nice to meet you, sir.
‐ [Ruri] So Akito will
return to being a cook?
‐ No, based on our
analysis of his past
performance and history,
we cannot regard Akito
Tenkawa as soldier material.
We feel he would better
serve the war effort
performing civilian
support duties.
Under our surveillance,
of course.
‐ You mean that you’re
going to fire me?
‐ I’m afraid this wasn’t
meant to be your place.
‐ You’ve done an excellent
job, Mr. Tenkawa.
It’s unfortunate that
you won’t be staying,
but I’m sure you’ll agree
that defeating the Jovians
is the most important thing.
I hope that we can
still be friends.
It’s too bad I won’t have a
chance to try your cooking.
(groans)
‐ I’m getting off too.
(singing in foreign language)
‐ Look Yurika, they’ve already
told me they don’t want me.
Being a soldier means
doing what you’re told,
so I’m going and you’re staying.
‐ Please don’t leave me, Akito.
How can you just
walk away like this
and leave your
girlfriend behind?
‐ You’re not my girlfriend.
Well, you’re my friend.
Huh?
‐ Did I keep you waiting, Akito?
‐ Kept me waiting?
‐ Thank you for everything,
Captain Misumaru.
Come on, let’s go, Akito.
‐ But we’re not finished yet.
(horn beeping)
‐ They look like newlyweds.
(groans)
‐ Please Akito, come back.
(horn beeps)
‐ So, what are you
going to do now, Megumi?
‐ No, you tell me first.
‐ Go back to cooking, I guess,
but I suppose everyone will just
call me a washed up pilot again.
But in the end,
it doesn’t matter.
Whatever it is that I try to do,
nobody ever really wants me.
‐ That’s not true, Akito.
‐ I agree.
Nergal still wants you, Akito.
‐ You’re just saying that
so you can keep him under
your thumb, aren’t you?
‐ No, we have a job
that only he can do.
‐ Only me?
‐ [Erina] As you know,
the Jovian lizards
are able to use the
tulips to conduct
a form of teleportation
that we call Boson Jumping.
Ever since its discovery,
Nergal has been trying to unlock
the secrets of the system
independently from the military.
‐ [Woman] The Jovians
use only unmanned weapons
and the accrual of the croaks
were all dead on arrival.
So, how was the Nadesico able
to Boson Jump successfully
with no harm to the
lifeforms on board?
‐ [Inez] I believe that the key
to this puzzle is Akito Tenkawa.
‐ Miss Fressange?
‐ Yes, Miss Fressange expressed
an interest in our research.
These people went to make
organic Boson Jumping a reality.
If we could send ships
to Mars and Jupiter,
the course of this war
could be reversed, Akito.
But as our unmanned
weapon technology
is nowhere near
that of the Jovians,
our ships will have
to carry pilots.
‐ True, however, to the
best of our knowledge,
not even the Jovians
have succeeded
in Boson Jumping lifeforms.
Therefore, we must develop
that technology at any cost.
No matter what the risk.
‐ We at Nergal believe
you have this ability.
Earth needs you, Mr. Tenkawa.
‐ Wait a second.
What makes you
think Akito can do
this thing you want him to?
‐ This is a tulip
crystal, a CC for short.
We found it on Mars.
Have you seen one?
You recognize it.
‐ My father gave one to me.
But I lost it on Mars.
(dramatic music)
‐ The first CC we discovered
when we began excavating
the Martian polar caps.
Nergal immediately took
over the entire operation.
This is a CC.
These are all CC’s.
So, are you surprised?
‐ More than that.
I thought I had the only one.
‐ [Erina] So tell me,
what happened to your CC?
‐ [Akito] Well‐‐
‐ Analysis proves the
crystal’s molecular structure
is identical to
that of the tulips.
It’s my hypothesis that the CC’s
can be used to
trigger Boson Jumping.
You’ve jumped
before, haven’t you?
From Mars to the Earth.
‐ I Boson Jumped?
To the Earth from Mars?
(eerie music)
‐ [Akito Voiceover] I
don’t know how I got here.
When I woke up, I
was on the Earth.
And the stone in my
pendant was gone.
‐ I knew it.
That’s why you have to help us.
You and Miss
Fressange can ensure
a bright future for all mankind.
‐ Excuse me, madam.
‐ [Erina] What?
‐ It’s back.
(crumbling)
‐ [Inez] So, Miss Won,
why didn’t you tell me
that you were conducting
live experiments?
‐ Hi, we kind of followed you.
(giggles)
‐ [Inez] You’re not
doing well, are you?
‐ Actually‐‐
‐ I understand.
You don’t want Miss
Fressange and I as coworkers.
What you want is guinea pigs.
‐ All right, damn it.
Yes it’s true and I refuse
to apologize for it.
You’re a nothing right now,
but at least this way,
you’d have some value.
‐ [Akito] You mean like that?
‐ But you can do it.
I know that you can.
You’ve got to help us.
Please?
‐ [Inez] Aren’t you
going to stop him?
‐ [Erina] He’ll be back.
Who’s gonna want
a loser like that?
‐ Obviously you do.
‐ What’s that mean?
(laughs)
‐ However, have you
stopped to consider
what the implications are
if the Jovians
don’t have organic
Boson Jumping technology either?
It could mean that
they, like us,
simply found the phase
transition engine and the tulip.
‐ [Man] The force field
generation is failing.
‐ [Man] No, there’s a more
powerful distortion field
coming from inside‐‐
‐ We’re registering massive
amounts of Boson particles.
‐ [Erina] What?
‐ It’s what I was afraid of.
If your research probes made
it to the enemy’s home planet,
then they know that
Earth has started
experimenting with the prospects
of organic Boson Jumping.
If I was in their place,
my first response would be
to stop our experiments,
and unfortunately, I’m right.
(rumbling)
‐ Oh my god, they’re here.
‐ I told Evelyn to
marry Christopher.
Merry Christmas Eve.
(cheering)
They arrested my brother
for stealing miniature cars.
He said he only
liked Hot Wheels.
(singing in foreign language)
‐ I’ve thought it over
and I can’t go back
to being just a secretary.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Captain, the Jovian lizards
are attacking Kawaski.
‐ It’s a big one!
(rumbling)
(speaking in foreign language)
‐ Looks like the
UEAF are wiped out.
‐ The hostile units
appear to possess
miniature gravity blast cannons.
Move in but be careful.
‐ [Announcer] Please
refrain from driving.
Sightseers and other
civilians are advised
to stay away from the
Kawasaki District,
as they will only interfere
with the efforts of the UEAF.
‐ Akito, you promised to
forget about the Nadesico
and spend a nice
Christmas with me.
‐ But I‐‐
‐ But you what, Akito?
‐ You know that I
don’t like fighting.
But now that Mars is gone,
the Nadesico was
like home to me.
I want to protect
the ones I love.
‐ Am I not enough?
Isn’t it enough to protect me?
Look at them.
Everyone looks so cheerful.
Do they look detached?
But they’re all
desperate inside.
They’re all trying desperately
to keep a smile on their face.
Trying to protect
each other’s happiness
by not letting their
fears show through.
You don’t have to fight a war
to be protecting
somebody, Akito.
Safeguarding one girl and
safeguarding the Earth
are only different
on a matter of scale.
(screams)
‐ Take this, you!
Die, damn it.
Huh?
(screaming)
‐ What is this, I don’t get it.
‐ Hold on, Hikaru.
Let me try something.
(intense music)
Teleporting won’t do
that thing any good
if I’m still attached to it.
‐ Oh my god.
If that thing jumps,
the Aestivalis pilot
will be killed instantly.
(gasping)
(intense music)
‐ Seiya, Seiya!
‐ He’s gone, the
cockpit’s crushed.
‐ I’ll straighten your fire
on the one that’s still moving.
(panting)
‐ You’re such a fool.
A fool.
‐ Open fire!
(intense music)
30 degrees to the
left in three seconds.
(gunshots)
With this jump
pattern figured out,
we can beat it.
(intense music)
‐ What’s that?
‐ Yes, I was afraid of this.
If all else failed,
they programmed its PT
engines to self‐destruct.
‐ You mean‐‐
‐ Yes.
The thing is trying
to phase transition
the entire adjacent
spatial sphere.
The energy generated
will vaporize
everything from miles around.
‐ [Erina] Perhaps, but I
wouldn’t worry too much.
‐ Huh?
Akito?
‐ All right, Erina.
The crystals.
‐ Hey, down there.
(beeping)
‐ What’s that idiot doing?
‐ Captain, look.
(gasps)
‐ Something I can do.
Something only I can do.
Okay, let’s find out.
I’m sending you back to hell.
(yells)
(intense music)
‐ [Megumi] Akito?
Akito?
Akito!
‐ [Man] Well, I
guess he turned into
a real warrior in the end.
‐ How can you say
something so insensitive?
I don’t believe you.
He sacrificed himself for us.
For all of us.
You, it’s all your fault
that Akito was killed.
‐ Please, control yourself.
And as for Tankawa.
‐ Hey, Nadesico.
Nadesico.
Oh, well it’s about time.
What’s going on?
It’s been two weeks.
I’ve been calling
you over and over.
‐ It’s the time variable.
He jumped to the
moon two weeks ago.
(sobbing)
‐ [Yurika] Akito.
‐ Yurika, are you crying?
‐ You’re a ghost.
‐ No.
‐ You’re alive?
Where are you now?
‐ I’m on the moon
someplace, why?
‐ So we can come get you.
‐ They might not let you.
I just wanted to
say, Merry Christmas.
‐ Akito really does love me.
‐ [Man] Hey, who is that
singing the Gangy Gankar theme?
‐ It’s not us, it’s
coming from inside.
‐ That’s impossible.
This is an unmanned weapon.
(gasps)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ Oh my god.
‐ [Ken] Hello everyone.
I’m Ken Tanku, pilot
of the Kakiga Jet.
In the next exciting
episode of Gangy Gankar,
we’re up against our
most dangerous enemy
and we have to use the new
top secret Gankegan flare.
It’s going to be a tough battle,
but we know we can
do it if you join in
to help us out.
‐ That’s not right.
Next week’s episode
will be Sail Forth,
The Glamorous Captain
Yurika Misumaru.
‐ [Man] No, it isn’t.
The next episode of
Martian Successor Nadesico
is Let’s Go With
Hot Blooded Anime.
Everyone be sure‐‐
‐ Let’s get in.
‐ Huh?
‐ Oops.