‐ [Ruri] Conventional
military wisdom says that
a superior combat vessel
must take on risks
that match the superior
capabilities of that ship.
Since the Nadesico
is the greatest ship
in the UEAF arsenal,
I guess that’s why we’re
always where we are.
In the midst of fighting.
You don’t want to know what
I think of military wisdom.
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ Once again, the Nadesico
was placed at the front
of the UEAF assault formation
and the enemy singled us out
as if we killed their parents.
It looks like the Jovians
want to play rough.
Well that’s fine with me.
‐ Onward comrades.
For the future of our planet
depends on our
gallantry in battle.
‐ Oh yeah whatever.
‐ Let’s do it.
‐ And not get shot.
‐ It’s time to make
the rent payment.
(upbeat music)
‐ [Intercom] All
Aestivalis have taken off.
All units engage at will.
‐ Launching missile barrage now.
Huh?
(yelling)
(dramatic music)
‐ Where are they going?
‐ [Intercom] They’re
going everywhere.
(explosions)
‐ Those damn slimy, lizard,
kill bastards got us.
I guess we’re done for.
‐ [Man] Um sir, we were
just shot by the Nadesico.
‐ Huh, say what?
Those bastards.
(dramatic music)
‐ Huh, huh, what’s
happening out there?
‐ [Ruri] Our
Aestivalis are shooting
at our own ships, Captain.
‐ They’re shooting
at friendlies?
‐ The attack guidance system
doesn’t seem to
be malfunctioning.
The Nadesico’s
Aestivalis are attacking
what it perceives
to be enemy units.
‐ But, but the
enemy’s over there.
‐ The Nadesico Aestivalis
are attacking both the enemy
and the UEAF units, Captain.
‐ Have they lost their minds?
Stop fighting immediately.
‐ [Ruri] The enemy is
too close, Captain.
If we stop firing now, our
entire side may be wiped out.
‐ Oh tell them to to
shoot at the Jovians.
Just at the Jovians.
‐ Don’t give up team.
Keep trying to engage the enemy.
‐ Even if we keep
shooting at our own side?
‐ At least we’re only shooting
at our own ships half the time.
‐ Yes I’m sure they
appreciate that.
(explosions)
‐ What in the hell
are you doing?
‐ Well at least none of
them have started shooting
at the Nadesico yet.
I guess the best we can do
is weather this one out.
Send out more Aestivalises
as reinforcements.
‐ [Ruri] We have no
more pilots, Captain.
(gasping)
‐ That’s not exactly true.
This is my time to shine.
I’m also a pilot.
And it is the duty of
an executive officer
to serve his captain.
That’s all I want to
do to serve my Yurika.
I will die to
protect you Yurika.
Attack!
(yelling)
(crashing)
‐ Mr. Aoi.
Please come in Mr. Aoi.
(explosions)
(yelling)
(dramatic music)
‐ [Ruri] The fighting that
day was a terrible mess.
Fortunately, the Jovians
were as confused as we were
and pulled out quickly.
Probacouldn’t figure out why
we’d attack ourselves
unless it was some part
of a brilliant trap.
‐ Well at least all of
you made it back safely.
‐ Well it looks like none of
Aestivalis were badly damaged.
(yelling)
Jumping jahosaphat.
What happened to that one?
(grunting)
‐ Jun, why were you
in that Aestivalis?
(grunting)
‐ What is that, sign language?
‐ Baseball hand
signals actually.
I believe he’s saying with
the Nadesico so undermanned,
it was his job to
fill in as a pilot.
‐ Well that’s fine but you
should have worn a pilot’s suit
to cushion you from the inertia.
(grunting)
What the hell’s that mean?
‐ I did it for Yurika.
Steal home.
‐ Doing it for Yurika is fine,
but you still should have
put on a pilot’s suit.
(grunting)
‐ I don’t want to start
bickering with you
at a time like this.
Yes, yes I think that’s more
than quite enough right now.
(grunting)
‐ What’s he saying?
‐ You should make sure
to put on your seatbelts
when you get in the Aestivalis.
Well except for the
whiplash to his neck,
he appears to be fine.
However he won’t be able to
speak normally for a while.
Idiots.
‐ Poor Jun.
Take care of yourself.
‐ Thank god no one was fatally
injured in all of this,
but do any of you realize
how much a battleship
like this costs?
‐ Um that one was my bad sir.
‐ Really?
That ship, the Fox
Glove, cost more to build
than the Nadesico.
‐ Uh I shot down 50.
‐ That’s pretty sharp
shooting Hikaru.
‐ Well yes but.
‐ But what?
‐ [Hikaru] Everything
is shot down
had a UEAF insignia on it.
‐ Please stop for
the love of god stop.
‐ I sure hope they
don’t have good lawyers.
‐ Well I set a new fleet
record with 78 units shot down.
That includes
friendly and enemy.
‐ [Mr. Prospector]
62 were friendly.
‐ Man what a bummer.
‐ Um you’ve been unusually
quiet over there Akito.
‐ Um well actually I kind of,
I didn’t shoot as many of
our ships as the others did,
but when I was aiming
for the enemy’s culup,
well I kind of blew up
the UEAF refueling depot.
‐ Do you have any idea how much
it cost to build that depot?
‐ I’m sure that all those
things must be insured.
Aren’t they?
‐ Of course they are.
In point of fact, Nergal
owns the insurance company.
At least no one was killed so
we won’t have to worry about
any wrongful death lawsuits.
(crying)
‐ [Yurika] Well there was
that one case of whiplash.
‐ So exactly how did all
of this end up happening.
Why did our Aestivalis
attack the UEAF fleet?
‐ It wasn’t like we
tried to attack them.
‐ We all dearly love our
beautiful blue mother earth
and would never betray the UEAF.
‐ Then was faulty
maintenance at fault?
‐ I’m going to pretend I
didn’t hear that haircut boy.
How dare you question
the ability of our
maintenance teams.
‐ The fact is that we’ve
been fighting continuously
for several months.
It’s possible that
there could have been
a maintenance error
due to fatigue.
‐ Look you blonde bimbo.
My men know that when
they screw up, people die.
That’s why every single
process is double
and triple checked
until it’s right.
Got that.
I’m a womanizer and
dead beat father,
but I do my job damn well.
So don’t blame your cherry
ass novice shortcomings on us.
‐ [Ruri] Please, wait a minute.
‐ Huh?
‐ There’s no indication
that either pilots
or maintenance crew
were at fault here.
‐ Then what was the cause Ruri?
‐ I don’t know, but
there’s a ship filled
with UEAF investigators
hailing us now.
‐ They’re sending a message
saying something about
how they think that the
Nadesico defense computer
maybe malfunctioning.
(sirens)
No don’t shoot at them Omoikane.
Those people aren’t our enemies.
‐ Huh?
(yelling)
(explosion)
(groaning)
‐ Oh no don’t look at me.
I didn’t touch a single button.
The escape pod from the research
is requesting assistance.
(explosion)
(groaning)
It’s being ordered
to fire again.
‐ But who is
issuing the command?
‐ I don’t know, Captain.
‐ Please stop firing.
Those people aren’t the enemy.
The UEAF investigation’s
vessel pod is now landing.
(dramatic music)
(sighing)
The investigators who were
accidentally fired upon
were predictably not very calm.
They immediately started
pointing their fingers
at every little minor
problem on the Nadesico.
Some people just like to condemn
the shortcomings of others.
‐ No!
‐ Obviously computers
have the capacity
to learn on their own,
accumulating knowledge
from experience
allows them to determine
the best options.
However, the
Nadesico’s computer.
‐ [Ruri] The Omoikane.
‐ That’s the name
of the computer.
‐ Attaching names to computers
is an idiotic practice
that ended in 20th century.
‐ But it identifies
itself as Omoikane.
‐ I don’t care if it
calls itself Orphan Annie.
‐ In any case, the
Nadesico’s computer
remembers the experience
of breaching the
Earth’s defense lines.
‐ Obviously Nad believes
that the UEAF is it’s enemy.
‐ Which is why it
targeted the UEAF armada
as well as the Jovians.
‐ So it’s behaving like
a disgruntled employee
who resents new management
afteby a competitor?
‐ That’s a nice
analogy Miss Fressange.
Believe I can sympathize
with how it feels.
‐ And that kind of
stress sometimes leads
to destructive behavior.
‐ Normally this stress
would make a system lock up.
If that were the case, we
could simply cut the power,
clear the RAM, and
reset the entire system.
‐ But Omoikane automatically
resets itself anyway.
‐ And that is what we believe
made the computer’s resentment
against the UEAF so strong.
Rather than purging
it each reboot
seems to have
increased its paranoia,
until it felt
compelled to attack.
The only solution now seems to
be a complete system rewrite.
We’ll have to wipe
the memory completely.
‐ Could I say something please?
‐ [Man] Yes.
‐ Resorting to such
jarkonian measures is stupid.
To purge the computer’s
memory in such a fashion
would mean a complete
loss of all the valuable
and still unanalyzed
information it acquired
during the Nadesico’s
mission to Mars.
‐ The Nadesico is operating
as part of the UEAF.
Any memories from when
the ship was alone
are more trouble
than they’re worth.
‐ The Admiral is right.
It’s humans that fight
to protect the Earth.
Not computers and machines.
Reprogram that thing.
‐ And after that last fiasco,
the ship will
belong to the UEAF.
Therefore, it makes
sense to have the system
purged completely.
We’ll wipe the slate
and start over.
‐ You’re wrong, but
it’s what I expected.
Why is it that adults think
that forgetting
something is a solution?
You can’t just throw
knowledge away.
‐ Ruri’s right.
(gonging)
(triumphant music)
(yelling)
(marching)
‐ Great crazy ball berries.
Is there a proctologist
convention in here?
‐ Switch control to
auxiliary computer.
Initiate installation now.
‐ All that data.
Do you really have
to erase everything?
‐ I’m afraid so.
‐ Yes, yes.
‐ We will eliminate self
awareness from this computer
and the Nadesico will be reborn.
‐ We’ll turn this civilian
zoo into a real battleship.
This overhaul was long overdue.
(jazz music)
‐ Akito.
(spitting)
‐ What’d you do that for?
‐ To get your
attention, of course.
Could I get you to do a
little favor for me please?
‐ No way, I’m not interested.
‐ But why not?
‐ Because I still
haven’t given up
my lifelong of becoming a chef.
And I’ve got to practice
whenever I’m not fighting.
Okay?
‐ But we really need
an Aestivalis pilot.
‐ Well why don’t you ask Ryoko,
Hikaru, Izumi, or Igatzki?
‐ Because we can’t.
‐ Huh?
‐ You’re the only one who
can do it Mr. Tenkawa.
Please help us.
‐ How can you resist that?
(sighing)
‐ Oh man it stinks in here.
‐ [Akito] You’ll get used to it.
‐ Are all men’s rooms like this?
‐ I don’t like it either.
‐ Well since the computer
center is occupied
and we can’t do this
from the bridge,
you’ll have to live
with it for a bit.
(yelling)
Watch where you’re stepping.
I’ve got a figure drying there.
‐ [Group] Huh?
‐ So can you really handle this
debugging from your PC unit?
‐ It just so happens
that I’ve accessed
the central computer
system several times
from this terminal already.
So popping back into the
system should be a snap.
And there we are.
(triumphant music)
‐ An Aestivalis.
‐ Why’s it wearing a smock?
‐ It’s a maintenance program.
It lives inside the
computer’s memory,
hunting down and
repairing broken parts
whenever it finds them.
It’s kind of like a
cyberspace, superhero janitor.
‐ That’s very strange.
‐ Excuse me, you got a
problem with my tastes?
Now then, by
hooking this program
into that virtual reality
simulator interface,
you’ll actually be
able to move around
like a cyberspace warrior.
‐ I’m ready sir.
‐ Alrighty then.
Let’s this show on the road.
Tenkawa Aestivalis online.
‐ Sure.
(loading noises)
Huh?
(gentle music)
This is the inside
of a computer.
‐ That’s correct.
This is the computer’s
graphical representation
of it’s own memory core.
Actually it’s modeled after
the central library at MIT,
which rejected me seven times.
‐ So where am I
supposed to go now?
‐ I’ll be your
guide Mr. Tenkawa.
‐ Just tell me where.
‐ Okay go up there.
Turn right.
Straight ahead.
Our destination is the
place where Omoikane’s
self consciousness is located.
That’s the military’s
new program.
It’s installing itself.
‐ I guess it’s time
to send it home, huh?
‐ No, not yet.
If we attack the
new program now,
the installation
will stop too soon
and the Nadesico will
continue to attack the UEAF.
‐ Then what do
you want me to do?
‐ We’ve got to keep moving on.
To the place Omoikane’s
consciousness is located.
‐ Roger.
Are you sure we
shouldn’t try to stop it?
‐ The Captain was right.
You’re very sensitive.
‐ Not to mention gullible.
Holy cow.
‐ That tree represents
the place where Omoikane’s
self consciousness resides.
It represents the ship’s
dreams and ambitions.
‐ I didn’t know that a
ship could have a dream.
‐ Aren’t dreams made
from pieces of memories?
It’s why they can’t
just be thrown away.
Why they must be cherished.
‐ Memories become dreams?
If that’s true, it
explains so many things.
But what about memories
that become nightmares?
‐ You can’t get rid of them,
but you can change them.
‐ How can you change a memory?
‐ Do you see that branch there?
It is only part of the tree
and the flowers on it
are even smaller still.
That branch cannot be cut,
but in time the tree
can grow new flowers.
It’s heart wrenching
to cut them,
but at least Omoikane will
remember who and what it is.
‐ I understand.
‐ Omoikane please
let yourself forget
and when your memories return,
do not let them rule you.
If you can learn how
to pretend to be a good
and obedient child, you can
still be true to yourself
in your own heart.
‐ Do you really think
this is working?
(yelling)
‐ Akito!
‐ What’s wrong Akito?
‐ It’s what we expected.
‐ What the heck was that?
‐ It’s the computer’s
automatic defense mechanism.
A sort of self
preservation program.
‐ Huh?
‐ The computer doesn’t
want to give up
what’s most precious to it.
(yelling)
‐ This is crazy.
What?
‐ Gekiganger Three.
‐ Gekiganger?
‐ Yes Omoikane has learned
to associate this image
with all that is good and
right in this universe.
Out of all the data
it has processed,
this is the entity
which it has chosen
as it’s avatar and defender.
That is why only you have a
chance to succeed at this task,
Mr. Tenkawa.
‐ But you can’t really expect
me to fight Gekiganger?
‐ Please Mr. Tenkawa.
You’re the only one
who can possibly do it.
‐ But Gekiganger is unbeatable.
‐ I’m begging you.
‐ Come on Akito.
You can beat that
Gekiganger piece of junk.
‐ What did you say?
‐ You can defeat, I
know that you can.
‐ Ruri please.
‐ I don’t think you’re going
to have much choice about it.
‐ Gekigang beam.
‐ Yikes.
(yelling)
‐ Gekigang cutter.
(punching)
(yelling)
‐ This is completely impossible.
I can’t defeat Gekiganger.
‐ But you can.
Think Mr. Tenkawa.
I know that you know
more about Gekiganger
than Omoikane does.
‐ I understand now.
It’s a virtual world.
Yeah.
Gekiganger charge!
(dramatic music)
Now we’re evenly
matched in power.
Gekigang beam.
(explosion)
Gekigang kick.
This is getting us nowhere.
‐ Actually the odds are against
us since you’re only human.
‐ No that’s his advantage.
Mr. Tenkawa has know
about and loved this robot
since he was just a child
and it must hold a very
special place in his heart.
That love can’t be defeated.
It can’t.
‐ Gee I like how you put that.
It really does hold
a very special place
in my heart, you know.
And!
(dramatic music)
Did you know that episode 28,
Gekiganger became
Gekiganger five.
And that’s not all.
Then there’s the
legendary unused sequence
to transform into Dragonganger.
(dramatic music)
Dragon blast!
(explosion)
(dramatic music)
‐ Omoikane’s self preservation
reflex has been defeated,
but now we’ve got to
hurry Mr. Tenkawa,
before the military program
finishes erasing
everything else.
‐ But what happens when we
take out the military program?
Won’t someone notice
what’s going on?
‐ Don’t worry about it kid.
I’ve been keeping
those military idiots
completely buffaloed with a
bunch of faked up read outs.
‐ Let’s blow that
thing to ash Akito.
‐ Roger that.
(explosion)
You know the Dragonganger
transformation
was never actually animated.
I only learned about
it by reading the books
that Gai left behind.
‐ Mr. Tenkawa.
I think it’s wonderful
that you still have
a child’s sense of wonder.
‐ Do I?
Well you should know.
‐ Yes I would.
After that, no
abnormalities appeared
in either Omoikane or
in the Nadesico itself.
At least not that the
military ever saw.
‐ Isn’t it beautiful?
My sweet new computer is
going to win this war.
Isn’t that right, Captain?
‐ Yes, of course it is.
‐ Well let’s be
off then, alright?
‐ Yes sir.
Slow speed ahead.
Rightful redder.
Take it away, Minato.
(gentle music)
‐ [Ruri] Yes how very true.
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] You won’t believe
what happens next, folks.
Akito says goodbye to Yurika.
My god can this
really be happening.
Your heart will
be torn to shreds
as a tragic twist of fate
causes a hero to leave the ship
and his lady love behind.
Is this the end or
a new beginning?
There’s a lot of action,
mystery, adventure,
and drama ahead,
as our saga steers a new course
towards an unexpected destiny.
In the next shocking episode
of Martian Successor Nadesico.
There is no single truth.