‐ [Narrator] Everyone
returned to the Nadesico.
As had I, they all realized
that this was their place to be.
We should’ve known that
from the beginning,
but instead we had to think
about it long and hard
until the truth came up
and hit us in the face.
What can I say,
we’re all idiots.
(upbeat trumpet music)
‐ I sure hope this was
the right thing to do.
‐ You can’t have doubts Eurika.
‐ We’ve got to believe that we
can bring an end to this war.
‐ That’s right.
If we asked for
both sides to show
they’re some of the blame,
that should be adequate.
‐ That’s not what’s
been worrying me.
I mean, there’s a
lot of water that’s
passed beneath the bridge.
Will the Earth and
Jupiter really be
able to forgive and forget?
I don’t know.
‐ You don’t think we made
the wrong choice, do you?
‐ Do you think we’d be
better off as virtual
prisoners back on Earth?
‐ No, but on the other hand,
I’m really not
that confident that
we’ll be able to convince
the people on either side
to believe in peace.
‐ Well I believe in myself
and in Mr. Shiratori.
‐ Why do you keep
trying to stop me?
‐ If you were only
leaving to be an
ambassador to the Earth slugs
I wouldn’t have to however,
I can’t believe
that you’ve fallen
prey to that earth
woman’s witchery.
How can you forsake
our ideal of womanhood?
The beautiful Miss Nanako.
‐ Miss Nanako is a wonderful
model of womanhood, but still.
‐ But what?
Just say it!
‐ She’s a cartoon you idiot!
(loud gasp)
Skumu!
(man growling)
‐ Bows and junk
detected off our bow.
It’s a Jovian
gekigen type captain.
‐ I’m Lieutenant
Commander Skomo Shiratori
of the Jovian Federation
Superior Male Forces
here to discuss
possible peace talks.
Requesting permission to
board the Nadesico ma’am.
‐ Permission is granted.
‐ Brother.
Big brother.
Big brother!
‐ Oh hi Yukina.
How’s the weather down here?
‐ Fine.
(brother and sister giggle)
‐ So, would you mind telling
me your name this time?
‐ Akito Tenkowa, Estivalis
pilot and ship’s cook.
‐ I brought you a little
something I’d like to show you.
‐ To show me?
Oh wow!
It’s the complete series
in octophonic sound!
‐ A videotape in
this day and age?
Unbelievable!
If it wasn’t for my
collection of obsolete decks,
you wouldn’t be
able to watch this.
You owe me big time.
‐ Yeah, yeah.
‐ Why do all of us have
to watch this stupid show?
‐ What can you do?
He’s a VIP so the
whole crew has to
join in to make this special.
‐ [Male Voice] Alright
then, power on, switch on.
(upbeat rock music)
‐ They’re idiots!
A bunch of grown ups all
watching a stupid cartoon.
It’s so idiotic!
What’s with you?
‐ Not a thing.
‐ Oh Akito, I finally
understand now.
Gekiganger is the answer.
I was so worried about who would
be willing to accept peace!
But now I see that
unlike the Earth,
the people of
Jupiter understand!
I know they must believe!
They must because
truth and honor
is the very essence
of Gekiganger!
‐ Now wait just a second here.
‐ She’s right!
Love, courage, and
passion are a thing
that will bring a true
peace to this universe,
and Gekiganger we
find the way to
achieve the true
potential of humanity!
(everyone cheers)
‐ I’m so ashamed of myself!
I call the show a cartoon for
little kids, but I was wrong!
‐ After all my years
in the industry,
I’ve never seen a show with such
respect for human feelings.
‐ It deserves to be
praised for it’s humanity.
‐ It touched my heart and
made me feel like a child.
‐ That’s it!
In order to find
the path to peace,
we have to set it Gekiganger!
(everyone cheers)
‐ I guess I never
thought of it that way.
‐ I need to know everything
about Gekiganger immediately!
‐ You want models, I got models.
‐ And here are the
production model sheets.
‐ No!
That’s not enough!
I want to live, slave,
and breathe Gekiganger!
‐ Oh boy.
‐ [Photographer] Give
me the sign Hikaru!
‐ Here!
‐ One inch scale aquamarines!
We made a special limited run
of 50 units for this show.
‐ Behold the mighty king
of garage kid heaven!
Pour a mold, pour a
mold, pour a mold!
(man laughing evilly)
‐ [Actor] Listen to
me foolish earthlings!
This room has been taken over
by the dark string universe!
‐ Not so fast Typerian!
Come on everyone!
Let’s fight in
the name of peace!
Let’s all Gekiganger!
‐ Well, we’re finally ready
to start our marathon.
‐ And tell them what
that means Akito.
‐ That’s right.
It’s time for the most eagerly
awaited event of Genkifest.
‐ We’re going to
screen the entire
Gekiganger series
from front to back!
(crowd cheers)
‐ Guy sure would
be happy right now
if he were still with us.
‐ So just exactly how does
Gekiganger end anyway Akito?
‐ Most giant robot
animes end with a
big fight and a happy ending.
‐ And peace and justice
triumph in the end.
That’s absolutely wonderful!
‐ Actually, I really
don’t know how it ends.
I’ve seen the whole series
except the last one.
‐ Really?
But why not?
‐ I was always afraid that
seeing the last episode
might somehow change the
way I feel about the show,
but this time I’m going to
watch it all the way through.
I’m going to finally
watch the last episode
and then we’re going to
make peace with the Jovians.
‐ Right.
‐ [Everyone] Let’s
go Gekiganger, speed!
‐ [Akito] Do you see the hand?
‐ Not yet.
‐ I wish people wouldn’t
play with my Gekiganger.
‐ [Female Voice] Maybe
you should keep it
attached with string.
‐ We have to find it first.
‐ Good.
There’s no one here.
At last, we’re finally alone.
‐ [Male Voice] Could
you step back a little?
‐ [Female Voice] Nope.
‐ Please, I’m not used to
being in situations like this
and although it’s not
completely unpleasurable,
I just find it a
little unsettling.
‐ You’re so cute!
‐ The male force
has rarely had the
opportunity to be in
contact with women
and I really don’t
know what to do next.
‐ You mean you’ve never
even kissed a girl?
‐ No ma’am.
‐ Would you like
me to teach you?
Was that a no?
Make up your mind please.
‐ I’m not against it.
‐ Then let me show you how.
First, close your eyes.
‐ [Male Voice] Okay.
‐ [Female Voice] Now,
tip your head forward.
‐ [Male Voice] Like this?
‐ [Female Voice] Yes, and
put your arms here and here.
‐ [Male Voice] There?
‐ [Female Voice]
Don’t open your eyes.
‐ [Male Voice] I’m sorry.
‐ [Female Voice] Don’t move.
Is your heart pounding?
‐ [Male Voice] Uh huh.
‐ Same here.
How do you feel?
‐ Hey, why are you
just standing there?
‐ Because this is the
door to my room Akito.
‐ Oh I guess it is, isn’t it?
Well, see ya!
‐ Akito.
I was just thinking that maybe
if you were ready to watch
the last episode of Gekiganger
that maybe you were ready
to make a decision about me.
(throat clears)
(yelping)
Why hello Yukino.
What are you doing here?
‐ I’m looking for
my big brother.
He hasn’t come back to our room.
‐ I think he’s in the cafeteria.
‐ No, wait, don’t!
‐ Oh is he now?
Sneak, sneak, sneak.
‐ Hey, now wait a second.
‐ Now that you mention it,
maybe you should
wait a little bit.
‐ Why is that?
‐ Oh, hi big brother!
‐ Yo!
‐ We’ll be back after the break.
‐ [Male Voice] You mean,
we’ve finally found it sir?
‐ That’s right.
At last, the lost city is
finally within our grasp.
Now not only will our dwindling
suppcivilization’s
artifacts be replenished,
but our original plans for the
ongoing war against
Earth can continue.
‐ And how is that
going to affect
the peace talks with Earth?
‐ The supreme war council is
debating that as we speak,
however this timely
discovery will no doubt
undermine the efforts of those
pushing for a peace settlement.
I will be conducting the
peace negotiations personally.
Commander, I have a very
special assignment for you.
‐ A special assignment sir?
‐ [Male Voice] Tomorrow’s
the last day of Gekifest.
I sure am gonna miss it.
‐ But the Gekiganger
festival doesn’t end here.
The way I see it, the peace
talks are a continuation,
another part of the same whole.
‐ I’ve gotta agree
with you there.
All hearts that long
for peace beat alike.
I’m planning on proposing to a
certain special person
when Gekifest is over.
So tell me, have you
given any thought
to what you’re gonna
do after the war?
‐ I haven’t thought that
far into the future.
‐ I wanna start raising a
family with the woman I love.
‐ You sound so sure of yourself.
‐ Someday you’ll
understand what it’s like.
No matter how
nebulous or difficult
the course to your
dreams may seem,
once you’ve discovered
your true love,
the path to happiness
is easy to follow.
‐ Once I’ve discovered
my true love?
(upbeat theme song music)
‐ [Female Voice] Well, it’s
the last episode Akito.
‐ Yeah.
(upbeat these song music)
‐ Emergency alert!
There’s a Jovian
fleet approaching!
‐ [Female Voice]
Incoming message from
the Jovian flagship.
‐ Patch it through please.
‐ I am Admiral Kusakare,
Jovian Federation.
‐ And I’m captain
Misumaru of the Nadesico.
‐ In the interest of
moving things forward,
I have been authorized to
begin peace negotiations.
‐ [Misumaru] Really?
‐ I would like to start
the talks in one hour.
We will forward you the details.
‐ Understood Admiral.
We are ready when you are.
I can’t believe
they were willing
to start peace
negotiations so quickly.
‐ We’re so lucky that
we’ve got Mr. Shiratori
acting as a go‐between.
‐ Let’s not let our
guard down just yet.
‐ Do I detect jealousy?
‐ I don’t mix business
with pleasure.
‐ Oh is that so Mr. Hori?
So you wouldn’t
tell someone that
you have been intimate with to
get off the ship, would you?
‐ What happened has
nothing to do with this.
‐ I’m not feeling very
comfortable right now.
‐ And so it begins.
‐ You make me proud big brother.
‐ What are these documents for?
‐ Just some preliminary
paperwork we prepared
in the interest of
expediting things.
‐ This isn’t a peace treaty.
It’s a terms of surrender.
You’re asking for a full
disarmament of Earth
and control of our
major industries.
There’s no way we
can agree to this.
‐ And all of these
are unnegotiable?
‐ That’s right.
‐ No.
No way.
‐ I demand these
terms be withdrawn!
‐ Shiratori.
‐ And why should we
withdraw them commander?
‐ Because they love
Gekiganger also.
Can’t you see sir?
‐ Shiratori.
‐ In Gekiganger, I’ve
discovered a common thread
that binds all men as brothers.
It’s the values we share,
courage; perseverance;
friendship; and love.
Together we’ve
watched Gekiganger
and embraced these
ideas that we share.
These people have
come seeking peace
because they’ve
learned the truth!
There is only one
true righteous path!
‐ I agree.
There is only one
true righteous path!
(loud gunshot)
(loud gasps)
‐ [Female Voice] Skomo!
‐ Damn, both of my
legs fell asleep.
‐ You bastard!
Why did you shoot him?
‐ The evil empire must be
destroyed by righteousness.
That is the central
theme of Gekiganger.
Gekiganger teaches
us that those who
would oppress others
must be destroyed.
Therefore, the
oppressive Earth regime
that banished us to
Jupiter must be vanquished!
‐ You’re crazy!
‐ Are you trying to say
that we’re the evil empire?
‐ Of course.
There is only one true righteous
path and that is our path.
‐ Who cares who’s
right and who’s wrong?
Please help him!
Can’t you see Skomo’s dying?
‐ Tenkowa!
(man yelling)
‐ Why are they shooting at us
while the diplomatic
team is on board?
‐ We’ve got to get
them out of there!
‐ Get out of here!
‐ [Male Voice] Right!
(loud explosion)
‐ Our shields can’t stand this!
Can’t we pull back?
‐ That would mean deserting
the captain and the away team.
(loud explosion)
‐ Damaged engineering!
We can’t continue
evasive action sir.
(loud explosions)
‐ Eureka.
(loud explosion)
‐ [Female Voice] It’s
Akito and the away team!
‐ [Robot] Okay, here we go!
(loud gunshots)
‐ Big brother!
‐ Protect that shuttle!
(loud explosions)
‐ This is bad.
(loud gunshots)
‐ Dammit!
‐ Well what goes
around, comes around.
It’s a good thing that
we’re here to bail you out.
‐ [Commander] You mean,
you’re going to help us?
‐ Like it or not,
we’re on the same side.
We’ll cover you while you
go retrieve your shuttle.
‐ Big brother!
Don’t die big brother!
‐ That’s right.
Prep for surgery and have the
anesthetic waiting for us.
‐ Big brother, big brother,
please hold on big brother!
Hold on!
‐ Arm the PT canon Rory.
‐ But if we use the PT canon,
all hopes for peace
will be destroyed.
‐ It’s too late.
‐ Are you sure?
Are you absolutely sure captain?
‐ [Radio] Recalling
all estovalis units.
‐ Big brother,
I brought you your favorite
Gekiganger model big brother.
If you get well,
I swear I will never
make fun of it again.
‐ I know you won’t Yukina.
Minato.
This is for you.
‐ The answer is yes.
‐ Hey Tenkowa.
I guess this means
I’m gonna miss
seeing the last
episode with you.
Please have faith.
Someone’s got to
keep up the flight.
‐ [Sister] Big brother!
‐ [Female Voice] No!
‐ [Male Voice] Do not
mourn Skomo Shiratori.
He was a spy and
Earth sympathizer.
‐ [Male Voice] Yes sir.
‐ However, his death
will be reported as
an assassination
planned by Earth.
That should ensure
that there will
be no further calls
for peace talks.
It seems that Shiratori
will serve our cause
better dead than alive.
Thank you for killing him.
‐ Right.
‐ Now that we’ve found
what we were looking for,
I’ll be damned if I
let peace stop us.
‐ Dammit all!
Dammit!
Stupid robots!
Go to hell!
I’m so blind.
Why didn’t I see?
It was always there
in front of me.
Idiot!
I saw what I liked and
ignored the rest of it.
I never thought about
how others might see it.
‐ Akito.
(upbeat dreamy music)
‐ [Narrator] Wind, fire,
tidal waves, explosions!
It’s been a real
rollercoaster of excitement
but now they’re
only two episodes
of Nadesico left to go!
Will all the
mysteries be revealed?
Will the romances
be consummated?
Will the war between Earth
and Jupiter come to an end?
Will sale figures on our
merchandise continue to climb?
Don’t miss out on the
action and thrills,
the tears and laughter,
the agony and the ecstasy,
The good, the bad, and the ugly
as the riders go berserk to
try to wrap everything up!