‐ [Female Speaker]
It may seem like
we weren’t taking
the war seriously.
In truth, most of our actions
were those of people
trying desperately
to forget something
that wouldn’t go away.
Like children who try to keep
playing after the sun sets,
we kept finding ourselves
surrounded by the darkness.
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ Okay, they’re all ready to go.
‐ Are you sure that
this will be safe?
‐ The rubber bicycle tires
should keep you
completely insulated
from the high voltage that’s
running through the corridors.
I’ve also installed an
independent gyro inside them
so if the gravity control goes
dead, you’ll still be okay.
‐ We have to regain control
over the Y‐Unit in 20 minutes.
Otherwise, the entire
operation will be in jeopardy.
‐ Right.
Let’s all go kick some ass!
‐ Spooks be gone,
spooks be gone.
Nevermore to bother me.
Spooks be gone, spooks be gone.
‐ Why is Izumi doing that?
‐ She says that she saw a ghost.
‐ You’re kidding, right?
‐ Spooks be gone!
‐ Brother, it can’t be.
I thought you were dead.
‐ What are these things?
It’s a mahjong tile.
‐ But it’s also a memory.
(dramatic orchestral music)
‐ Two Gekiganger type
units approaching.
All estobolus
launching to intercept.
‐ Aren’t we supposed
to rendezvous
with the lunar service
forces, commander?
‐ Don’t be ridiculous!
Not when that accursed
battleship is in my sight.
Let the young man force his
hand on the lunar surface.
This task group will
destroy the Nadesico.
‐ Aye aye, commander.
‐ Here they come!
What the?
We missed two!
‐ The Gekiganger type units
are compromising the integrity
of our distortion field.
‐ Ever since these
Gekiganger types appeared,
the protective value
of our distortion field
has been greatly diminished.
‐ Stop calling them
Gekiganger types, damn it!
(loud explosions)
‐ I’ve got him!
‐ [Female Speaker] Got him?
Isn’t that where Batman lives?
‐ Enemy vessel is accelerating.
‐ Are they in cannon range yet?
‐ We’re still outside their
firing range, Captain,
but they’re closing
the gap quickly.
‐ If we change our heading,
we won’t be able to
reach the position
for firing the cannon.
What should we do, Captain?
‐ Keep the Nadesico
advancing, Captain.
We’ll stop these Jovians.
‐ Alright, let’s begin the
briefing for this operation.
The second fleet
employing massive numbers
of lunar surface frames
and other vessels
is currently staging
a final offensive
on the dark side of the moon.
Our task is to lure
the Jovian’s boson
cannon equipped vessels
and robot forces here
and wipe them out.
‐ But if our distortion fields
can’t stop their boson cannon,
then what are we
gonna hit them with?
‐ Our PT cannon.
‐ [Everyone] PT cannon?!
‐ That’s right!
We’ll use the Y‐Unit, which
gives us three phase transition.
(yelling)
‐ We will use the
Y‐Unit’s PT engines
to project two opposed space
vault on the same point.
The resulting warp will cause
space to collapse on itself.
‐ If our PT cannon can eliminate
the Jovian vessels
in near lunar space,
the moon will be ours again.
And only the Nadesico can
complete this mission.
‐ The real question is
whether we’ll make it
to the intersection
point on time.
We have to be in position
and ready to fire the PT
cannon in less than 80 minutes!
‐ Tenkawa, wait!
I need you.
‐ An artificial
boson jump test?!
‐ We can create a
jump field using CC,
so all that we need is‐‐
‐ Someone who can survive
the jump process, right?
I’d like to be a part of
this experiment as well.
‐ Um.
‐ Let’s do it.
‐ The jump field appears
to be stable enough
for you to jump now,
but be advised that
chronological linearity
can be compromised if the
field’s integrity is violated‐‐
‐ If you’re having
second thoughts,
all you have to do is
say so and we’ll stop.
‐ Don’t push it
too hard, Tenkawa.
‐ Enemy vessels approaching.
Detecting phase transitions.
Boson cannon ready to fire.
‐ Right.
‐ [Female Speaker]
Visualize your target.
Think of the enemy battleships.
(growling)
(gasping)
‐ I did it! Fire!
(loud explosions)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
‐ Damn those evil earthlings.
Our precious leaf cannon
has been destroyed.
Prepare the Diomogen!
I go to fight!
‐ Hold it, (mumbling).
Pull back your forces.
‐ But Tsukumo, we can’t retreat!
‐ That was an order!
‐ Has anyone else noticed
that Akito hasn’t been
acting like himself lately?
‐ His success at boson jumping
seems to have unleashed
a repressed portion
of his personality.
Every little boy has dreams
of being a great hero
when he grows up,
and it seems Akito’s fantasies
were even stronger than usual.
However, for most of his life,
he has repressed
this part of himself.
This is why he keeps insisting
that he is just a cook
and has such a phobia about
accepting responsibilities.
‐ Stop peeking at
my memory tiles!
‐ It’s hard not to do that
when they’re all laid out
on the table in front of you.
Just look at them.
They’re just begging to
be examined and explained.
Which brings us back
to the original point.
Being the first earth human
to successfully
boson jump on his own
has paradoxically
made you a real hero.
‐ A hero, huh?
‐ You do seem to have gotten
more resilient, Tenkawa.
‐ I suppose I have,
but I don’t think that’s
what’s required to be a hero.
I’ve always thought a real hero
is someone who’s willing
to sacrifice everything
in order to keep other people
safe, somebody like Gai.
But if you’re going
to call me a hero
for doing what I did,
then I guess I just don’t
know what a hero really is.
‐ So I guess that you’ve got
what you always
wanted now, right?
Isn’t being a hero and
fighting alien monsters
like Gekiganger
the kind of life you’ve
always dreamed about?
‐ Except the enemy are humans.
(suspenseful music)
(yelling)
‐ In there too?
‐ It’s everywhere.
There’s no way we can get
through all that stuff.
(groaning)
‐ You’re saying
something’s wrong
with the connection
to the Y‐Unit?
‐ To be specific, the Y‐Unit’s
weapons control computer
is no longer responding to
the commands that I give it.
Also, the software
diagnostics have been blocked.
‐ Is this a hardware issue?
There must be a solution.
‐ We’re completely
screwed down here!
All passageways leading
from the Nadesico
to the Y‐Unit either have high
voltage flowing through them
or non‐functioning
gravity control.
It’s as if the Y‐Unit doesn’t
want to let anyone in!
‐ Will we be able to fire
the phase transition cannon
in 30 minutes?
‐ It won’t be
possible if the Y‐Unit
doesn’t start responding
to our commands.
‐ I think today’s
lesson might be
to not try to do
everything at once.
‐ We’ll have to send
a team into the Y‐Unit
to make it operational again.
‐ But our pilots
aren’t doing too well.
‐ Just what does that mean?
‐ They claim to
be seeing ghosts.
(gasping)
‐ Spooks be gone.
‐ Mister Yamada?
‐ Did you just say Yamada?
Are you sure?
‐ There are others
too, but who are they?
(ominous music)
‐ I never thought I’d
be leading an attack
inside a ship on a bicycle!
Come on, pump those pedals!
‐ I wish you were pumping
something besides those pedals.
‐ Hey, let’s have a
race, and the person
who gets to the computer
first wins a prize, okay?
You want to, huh?
‐ Why the hell not?
I could use a laugh.
‐ And the person
who gets there first
gets to claim his prize
from the losers, okay, okay?
‐ Okay, but what
if there’s a tie?
‐ There’s enough of me
to go around, you know.
‐ If I win, I get
to have the captain.
‐ Now, wait just a second there.
She’s not mine to give out
anyway, you little weenie.
Hey, come back here!
‐ These men sure
have strange tastes.
‐ You can sure say that again.
‐ This is all completely
inappropriate.
‐ I think someone’s jealous.
‐ Don’t be ridiculous!
That was simply my professional
opinion of the situation.
‐ What I’m worried
about right now
is how their personalities
seem to be changing.
‐ That is a point.
Akito seems much more
assertive than usual.
‐ I don’t think we should be
doing something this dangerous,
but I guess we have to.
‐ Um.
‐ (laughing) Don’t
worry, ladies.
I’ve got it.
(gunshots blasting)
(yelling)
(laughing)
Come on, get on your
bicycles, girls.
Right, there’s 100
obstacles up ahead
and I can’t wait for an
excuse to blow them all away!
(laughing)
(triumphant orchestral music)
‐ [Tsukumo] I thought
our goal was to establish
a true and lasting peace.
‐ [Male Speaker] Exactly.
That is why we fight.
‐ Then in that case,
isn’t it imperative
that we at least consider
a negotiated peace?
(groaning)
Of course, the earth
government must first apologize
for their past injustices.
‐ Our ancient phase transition
core fabrication plant
is on the verge
of breaking down,
and our excavations on Mars
havethe desired results.
Is peace possible?
‐ I have a plan that
should work, sir.
‐ Now!
Let’s (mumbling) in!
(thunder clapping)
(dramatic music)
‐ Darn you, Tsukumo!
Why did you pull me out when
victory was almost mine?
‐ To save your life.
‐ Big brother!
‐ Yukina!
What are you doing here?
‐ I heard what
you’ve been doing!
(yelling)
‐ [Male Speaker]
Miss, Miss Manoko.
Are you alright?
‐ [Female Speaker]
Ken would be alright
if it wasn’t for the mackerel
sushi I made for him.
I’ve got to pull through.
(yelling)
‐ Brother!
‐ Where are your manners?
I can’t believe you’re so rude
as to interrupt Gekiganger.
‐ I hate that cartoon.
Now, what’s this
I hear about you
and some stupid peace treaty?
‐ A peace treaty, Tsukumo?
‐ Well, actually,
I was gonna tell‐‐
‐ What is the meaning of this?
How can you think of forgiving
those subhuman brutes?
‐ If peace is truly
our objective,
then we’ve got to
try every path!
‐ It’s a bunch of bull!
The real truth is
that my big brother
has a thing for an earth woman.
Ew!
You disgust me, big brother!
‐ It appears that our memories
have somehow become
interconnected.
‐ Do you mean this isn’t all
just a really strange dream?
‐ If it was a dream, we couldn’t
see each other’s memories.
For example, you were a bed
wetter until you were 10.
‐ (gasping) But I’m
not one anymore.
(nervous giggling)
‐ Idiots.
‐ Bit if our personalities
are all here, Miss Fressange,
then who or what
is in our bodies?
‐ Other facets of our
personalities, I’m afraid.
The parts we normally repress.
‐ Keep pedaling!
(mumbling)
‐ Lookie, look.
It’s the hatch to the Y‐Unit!
‐ Come on, you wussies!
We’ve got a computer to blow!
‐ Estobolus has appeared in
front of the enemy flagship.
Mister Tenkawa has
successfully boson jumped.
‐ Oh.
‐ Alright, Irena.
It’s my turn to try it.
‐ Not yet.
‐ Just shut up and do it.
I can handle this baby
just as well as he can.
(mumbling)
(growling)
(yelling)
(heavy breathing)
What happened?
‐ It was obviously going to fail
so I aborted your jump attempt.
‐ But why?!
Look at yourself.
‐ Damn it.
Why can’t I jump?
Brother.
‐ Your brother was so
much older than you.
Your father was grooming him
as his successor, wasn’t he?
‐ So what does that have
to do with anything?
‐ He died.
‐ He was killed on the
way back from Mars.
‐ And you never wanted
the responsibility
your brother’s death put on you.
‐ What does it
matter what I want?!
‐ It’s not possible
for you to be here.
‐ Brother? It can’t be.
I thought you were dead.
‐ [Akito] Gai.
‐ What’s going on?
Why are they just
standing there?
‐ Pilots Tenkawa,
Izumi, Nakotski,
please respond to our
communications immediately.
Hello?
‐ Everyone’s acting
so strangely.
‐ Yes, you’re right.
‐ I’m afraid to ask
about the second team.
‐ (laughing) I love
to shoot things!
‐ (yelling) Somebody help me!
‐ So exactly what
is happening here?
The personalities of
our pilots have changed
and they’re all
acting very strangely.
‐ And Miss Fressange isn’t
here to explain everything.
(giggling)
‐ Gai, you’re dead.
(struggling)
But why?
Why are you trying to keep us
from reaching the computer, Gai?
Is there something
you’re trying to tell us?
‐ The dead aren’t trying
to tell you anything.
There are no such things
as ghosts in this world.
The phantoms you are seeing
are probably old memories
that are emotionally attached
to the suppressed portions
of your personality
that are resurfacing.
In short, it is yourself
that holds you back.
‐ When will you stop
pulling me back?
When will you finally
leave me in peace?
I’m not afraid, not anymore.
‐ Hey, Izumi.
Who is this a picture of?
‐ He’s one of your
fiances, isn’t he?
I know that you had two,
and both of them died pretty
tragically, didn’t they?
‐ One lost to disease,
the other in an accident.
Everyone who’s ever been
close to me has died.
Please tell me that the time’s
come for me to join you.
It’s alright, I’ve
been waiting for this.
There’s nothing left
to keep me here.
(melancholy music)
Don’t go.
Please don’t abandon me again.
Please.
‐ For Izumi and Nakotski, it
isn’t death itself they fear.
It’s the separation it’s
brought with their loved ones
that fills them
with such terror.
On the other hand, Akito’s
fear is much more direct.
You still haven’t come to terms
with the death of Jiro Yamada
because that would mean coming
to terms with your own fears.
‐ But I’m not afraid
of dying, I’m not!
‐ Oh really?
Are you sure?
‐ Well, maybe I am scared,
but I keep fighting.
I never give up when
it’s important anyway.
That’s why I fight,
’cause if I don’t‐‐
‐ (sighing) There you go getting
all full of yourself again.
There’s no rhyme or
reason for any of this.
‐ No reason?
It’s all like that time we
took our first bicycle ride.
We didn’t think, we just did it.
(gasping) And now I understand.
There are no reasons!
I understand.
Everything makes sense now, Gai!
‐ We’re approaching
the large enemy fleet
assembling behind the moon.
‐ Is the Y‐Unit online?
(heavy breathing)
(static screeching)
‐ Get off our ship,
you damn (mumbling)!
‐ [Captain] Standby
on the PT cannon.
‐ [Ruri] Expanding Y‐Unit.
‐ Y‐Unit phase
transition engines.
Raise power output
to maximum load.
‐ Maximum power.
Locking on enemy
fleet coordinates.
‐ Fire!
(loud explosion)
It’s actually destroying
the fabric of space itself.
‐ I’ve never seen
anything like it.
‐ We can’t use a weapon
like this against humans.
‐ Not unless all we want
to do is vaporize them.
‐ As you know, the
nanomachine devices
implanted in our pilots
create an auxiliary memory
storage area near the brain.
Apparently, the
Jovian hacker crab
mistook those storage areas
for a form of computer memory
and hacked into them.
‐ So how did our minds all get
stuck talking to each other?
‐ Through our communicators.
Since our personal communicators
are all interconnected,
the hacker crab perceived them
to be part of a larger network.
By downloading the
entire network,
the hermit crab linked
all our minds together.
‐ But what kind of
data was the enemy
looking to obtain from us?
‐ I don’t know yet.
‐ Oh, but you and I
have never gone through
nanomachine treatment,
have we, Miss Fressange?
‐ I can’t explain that either.
‐ Well, that’s
certainly unusual.
‐ [Tsukumo] What?! You’ve
already sent a peace emissary?!
‐ [Male Speaker] Yes, I
have sent the emissary
you suggested to this Nadesico.
‐ What are you talking about?!
Who did you send
to the Nadesico?!
‐ Oh, haven’t you figured
out that plot twist, yet?
‐ You tricked my big
brother, earth woman.
And for that treachery,
I swear you will pay!
‐ What do you mean you won’t
participate in the experiments?
You’re the only
person who can do it,
the only one who can
protect the Nadesico!
It’s just like that
cartoon Gekiganger.
You’re the only one who can
protect the blue planet earth!
‐ You can make it sound
as noble as you want,
but I don’t think you even know
what a real hero is, Irena.
This isn’t a game, you know?
I think knowing what to fight
for is what makes a real hero.
That’s weird.
What is this picture
of I doing here?
‐ Look at this wonderful memory
that Akito and I both share!
Look!
(relaxing music)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Oh, don’t go
breaking my heart ♪
♪ I wouldn’t if I tried ♪
‐ Oh yeah, sing it (mumbling).
♪ Strangers in the night ♪
♪ Exchanging glances ♪
♪ I don’t know the
lyrics to this song ♪
Excuse me, is this
getting serious?
♪ Strangers in the night ♪
♪ Two lonely people ♪
♪ We’re just strangers
in the night ♪
We’re in trouble!
Don’t miss our next exciting
episode, Protect The Visitor.
Hey, get a room you two!