‐ [Ruri Voiceover] The
Nadesico continues to fight on.
It’s strange, but whether
they like it or not,
everyone seems to think
that the only way
to stop the fighting
is to keep on fighting.
But just how much longer
will we have to fight?
Nobody knows.
(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
(water rushing)
That same dream again.
(beeping)
As I said, the Nadesico
continues to fight on,
and nobody knows
when it will all end.
(sighs)
‐ This sucks.
Will the fighting never end?
‐ [Ruri Voiceover]
In my spare time,
I’ve been reading about
the history of mankind.
It seems that most of
it is a history of wars.
More war than peace.
Assuming that I live to be 100,
does this mean that
90 years of my life
will be filled with
memories of war like these?
The saddest part
is that there were
no wars in the 10 years before
I came onboard the Nadesico.
But I don’t remember
them very well.
‐ Omikami, why can’t I remember?
(beeping)
Please display
all of my records.
Seven years ago, an
unidentified orphan named Ruri
was adopted by a
couple who worked
at a Nergal research laboratory.
Ruri’s foster
parents were charged
with training her
to be a crew member
of a new ship
called the Nadesico,
which was to be
completed in six years.
For the next six years,
she was intellectually nurtured
and trained for the
position of science officer.
At the end of this time,
they returned her to Nergal
for a large
financial settlement.
Yes, I remember that,
but what happened before?
(beeps)
But I still want to know.
(beeping)
The answer never changes.
Omikami doesn’t
know anything else.
And I remember so little.
(beeps)
What an idiot I am.
‐ Ruri.
I am your father, Ruri.
‐ That’s right, and I
am your mother, Ruri.
‐ Father, Mother.
‐ Ruri, I am your first teacher
of mathematics, Archimedes.
‐ Archimede.
‐ That’s Archimedes.
Pi.
‐ Archimedes, pi.
‐ Ruri, your father
is proud of you.
Very proud.
‐ That’s right, and your
mother is proud of you as well.
Extremely proud.
‐ [Both] Hurray, hurray, hurray!
‐ Archimedes!
‐ [Both] Very good, Ruri.
Wonderful, Ruri.
You’re adorable, Ruri.
‐ [Ruri Voiceover]
Those were the first
words that I learned.
Father, mother,
Archimedes, and pi.
Of course, that wasn’t
pie as in apple pie,
but the numeric value of pi.
‐ Goodbye, students.
‐ Thank you, goodbye teacher.
‐ Hello, are you ready
for your Japanese lesson?
This’ll be lesson
six for Hiragana.
Today we’re going to learn
some new words beginning
with the symbol for E,
words beginning with
the symbol for row,
and words beginning with
the symbol for ban‐ha.
Are you ready?
‐ May I ask a question, sensei?
‐ Yes, what is your
question, Miss Ruri?
‐ What’s the meaning
of this word?
Baka.
‐ It means idiot
and it is not a word
that should be used
in everyday life.
‐ Idiot?
‐ I am Einstein, and
I will be your teacher
for advanced quantum mechanics.
‐ Einstein, E equals MC squared.
Am I right?
‐ [Both] Very good, Ruri.
Wonderful, Ruri.
You’re adorable, Ruri.
‐ Idiots.
‐ [Ruri Voiceover] I
do remember having some
friends to play with.
(whining)
I had human friends as well.
They were the children
I studied with.
We all seemed very much alike,
except at night, when
the dreams would come.
That’s when I felt
very different.
‐ Father, Mother.
Papa, Mama.
‐ Thank you, Mama.
(laughs)
‐ Huh?
(rushing water)
‐ [Ruri Voiceover]
That dream again.
‐ Hello, Ruri.
‐ Hello.
‐ Could you please
come to the bridge
as soon as possible?
‐ Why, are we under attack?
‐ Well actually, no.
There’s someone here to see you.
‐ Somebody to see me?
What is Peace Land?
‐ Peace Land is a
very unusual country.
nation that is similar
to Switzerland in that
it is permanently neutral
in all Earth politics.
It began as a theme park
but now is a kingdom ruled by
the great grandson of
the original owner.
‐ Yes, I remember going there
when I was just a kid.
‐ It’s more than just an
amusement park for children.
Peace Land also has
legalized gambling.
That makes it the ideal
vacation spot for all ages.
More importantly,
they also maintain
the world’s most
discrete banking system,
which specializes
in money laundering.
That makes it very
popular with people
who need to hide extra income
in order to avoid paying taxes.
‐ You mean people like Nergal.
‐ Well, let’s just say that
the Peace Bank and Nergal
have had a few dealings
over the years.
‐ [Yurika] Then
why are they here?
Does someone onboard
have an account
in the Peace Land Bank?
‐ All I know is that they
asked for young Ruri here.
‐ But I don’t have an account
in the Peace Land Bank.
‐ Well whatever the case,
it’s prudent not to anger them.
The financial world revolves
around its banking practices.
So let’s all be on
our best behavior.
(soft music)
‐ I bring you an urgent
message, Princess Ruri.
‐ [Both] Princess?
‐ Yes, our King and
Queen spent many years
attempting to be
blessed with children.
Finally, they resorted
to a procedure
at a famous fertility clinic.
‐ You mean a test tube
fertilization, correct?
‐ Yes.
They longed desperately
for an heir.
Unfortunately, no
sooner had they returned
from making their first deposits
than they received word
that a band of terrorists
had blown up the clinic.
The vial containing
Your Royal Highness
was lost among the debris,
and we have been searching
for you ever since.
‐ But I was raised as an orphan.
‐ Yes, we are all aware of that.
But there is absolutely
no doubt in our minds
that you are the
missing royal zygote.
Although the Queen has
produced other heirs,
you are still Peace
Land’s princess.
‐ Then the King and
Queen are my parents.
Mother, Father.
How can I be a princess?
Omikami, I need a full
readout on princesses.
(speaking in foreign languages)
This is going to be too painful.
Start over, eliminating
anime characters.
(soft music)
‐ But why?
It’s not fair.
‐ Well, someone has to take her.
‐ That’s right, and please
watch her carefully.
We want to keep the
princess out of trouble.
‐ [Akito] I’ll do my best.
‐ But why, how come?
‐ In times of war,
a figure of state
should never be
allowed to travel
without an armed bodyguard.
‐ I know that.
But why does it
have to be Akito?
‐ So why did you pick me?
‐ Apparently princesses
aren’t supposed
to travel without a
knight to accompany them.
‐ Oh.
Did you read about that
in the computer files?
‐ [Ruri] Yes, I also
watched some videos.
(soft music)
‐ Oh Ruri, my dear child.
How long we have searched.
Thank the stars we found you.
‐ You’re my father?
‐ That’s right, I am
your papa, dear daughter.
And this is your mama.
‐ Oh, you’ve grown up to
be such a wonderful girl.
‐ And these are your
adoring little brothers.
‐ [Everyone] Welcome,
Princess Ruri.
Our dearest older sister.
(groans)
‐ This isn’t the place.
‐ We are all
together now at last.
And now you can stay and
be with us all you want.
(sighs)
‐ Father, can I request a favor?
‐ What is it you wish, my child?
‐ Time to think.
I would like some time.
(dramatic music)
(soft music)
‐ How much more shopping are
you going to do, Princess?
‐ I’ve got spanners
for Mr. Uri Pataki,
spices for Ms. Houmei,
a teddy bear for Miss‐‐
(groans)
(soft music)
‐ Whoa.
(speaks in foreign language)
‐ Pizza, it’s the
greatest of all
Peace Land’s native dishes.
‐ How can you call
it a native dish
when it was created in‐‐
‐ In Naples, in Italy.
(groans)
Everything in Peace Land
is borrowed from elsewhere.
‐ Why don’t you try
it and then you can
open your big mouth?
Try it, you’ll like it.
I guarantee.
‐ We’ll try.
‐ So what do you think
of our house specialty?
‐ Hey, well, I grew up on Mars,
so I can’t say for sure but‐‐
‐ It’s bad.
‐ Huh?
‐ It’s very bad.
In fact, it’s horrible.
‐ Huh, what did you say?
‐ He’s getting angry.
‐ You’ve used cheap olive oil,
the peppers, flour,
and mozzarella cheese
are all of mediocre quality,
the tomatoes weren’t ripe,
to compensate
you’ve over applied
cheap spices with the result
being a foul tasting mess.
‐ Is this new martian girl
brat gonna cuss on my cooking?
‐ It shouldn’t matter if
we’re from Mars or Jupiter.
Any rational human being
would find this pizza terrible,
unless they had no taste buds.
I won’t even mention the
carcinogens in the sausage.
‐ Where do you get your balls
to talk to me like that?
I’ll kill you.
‐ Hold it.
Leave her alone, you
lousy pasta maker.
(groans)
‐ Mr. Tenkawa.
(groaning)
‐ That ought to teach
you, martian food critic.
(groaning)
‐ Master.
‐ Our mentor.
‐ Our teacher.
‐ Muscle man.
‐ You got some nerve,
whacking on him like that.
‐ If he didn’t want to fight,
he shouldn’t have
thrown the first punch.
‐ Why you little‐‐
‐ Back off and
leave the kid alone.
I’m warning you.
‐ Trying to be her
knight in shining armor.
You’ve got some meatballs.
(yelling)
‐ Oh man, if I just wanted
to get into a fight,
I could’ve stayed home.
Who named this place Peace Land?
‐ It was all my fault.
I’m sorry you were hurt.
‐ Ruri, protecting the princess
is what a knight does.
Of course, I didn’t do very
well at that, now did I?
But that sure was some
nasty tasting pizza.
‐ [Ruri] Yes, it really was.
(roaring)
‐ A fjord in Scandinavia?
What do you want
to go there for?
‐ There’s a school up there.
My father said that’s where
his investigators discovered
that I had been brought up.
I’m looking for the
people who raised me.
(roaring)
‐ Wow, what a junk heap.
Where are you going?
(soft music)
‐ You must be Miss Ruri.
The King of Peace
Land sent me a message
that you would be coming here.
‐ I was looking for my parents.
‐ Your parents?
Now I see.
I’ll tell you what I know.
After the bombing, many
vials of unidentifiable
fertilized eggs were
brought to this facility.
Most of them were already dead,
but my associates and I decided
that those that had survived
had earned the right to live.
However, to justify the cost,
we had to use them
as test subjects.
‐ Test subjects?
‐ We believed that by
altering just a few genes,
we could improve
their viability.
‐ I thought that genetic
manipulation on humans
was against the law.
‐ There are always
those too backwards
to see the chosen path.
Genetic splicing promised
advanced intelligence.
Bodies free of disease,
able rigors of space travel.
We knew these things
were outlawed,
but we believed the gains
were worth the risks.
That is why we came to this
hidden spot in the wilderness.
Here where the air is clean
and the water untainted,
we could raise our
perfect children.
This school is where
we educated them.
Utilizing new
techniques to let them
absorb information in new ways.
‐ In other words, you
experimented on us.
‐ Humans learn too many
unnecessary things.
We only taught our children
what they needed to know.
We kept them from
wasting their young minds
with sports and games.
And you’re the result, Ruri.
The glorious culmination.
At your young age, for
all practical purposes,
you control the Nadesico.
Clearly, you are superior.
I am so proud of
what you’ve become.
‐ And what of the
other children?
‐ It’s very tragic,
but failures do happen.
Our teaching methods were banned
years ago because of that.
This institute has been
abandoned for years.
But you succeeded.
You proved our theories work.
For that, I thank you.
Now then, when you were four,
a man from Nergal came
and left a deposit
for your schooling.
I placed the money
in a savings account.
With that card, you will be able
to withdraw money
from an account
in the Peace Bank
whenever you like.
Of course, since
you’re now a princess,
you may never need to use it,
but a young girl can never have
too much spending
money, can she?
‐ And what about my parents?
‐ Hmm?
Oh, is this what you mean?
‐ [Man] Ruri.
I am your father, Ruri.
‐ [Woman] That’s right,
and I am your mother, Ruri.
‐ [Both] Very good, Ruri.
Wonderful, Ruri.
You’re adorable, Ruri.
‐ We knew our children
would need special parents.
‐ [Both] Hurray, hurray.
‐ Parents who would never scold
or traumatize our children.
Real people could
never fit the bill.
(soft music)
‐ [Ruri] Thank you
for letting me live.
‐ It wasn’t a hard thing to do.
‐ However, as for everything
else that you did to me‐‐
‐ Huh?
(gasps)
‐ If you want that
money, you can have it.
Idiot.
(trickling water)
(gasps)
(rushing water)
‐ Ruri, wait.
‐ [Ruri Voiceover] That
sound, that’s the sound.
(trickling water)
(rushing water)
(groaning)
‐ Oh wow.
Schools of salmon.
(rushing water)
They’re beautiful.
I’ve never seen
live ones before.
‐ [Ruri Voiceover] And so,
like a salmon returning
to the stream in
which it was spawned,
I went back to the Nadesico
and her complemented
idiots and fools.
(rushing water)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ As a child, I was in
love with the stars.
My idols were Lindbergh,
Gregorian, Glen, and Armstrong.
It’s been a long time since then
and I’ve come a long way.
I’ve achieved my dream
and flown in space.
But what I’ve never dared to do
is put my trust in
another human being.
Not until now.
But my sky blue eyes will change
to the color of the
darkest ocean depths
if I was to learn
I was being played
for a fool by someone I trusted.
The next episode of Martian
Successor Nadesico is
You’re The Next Captain
of the Nadesico.
Don’t you dare miss it, okay?
It’s gonna be very dramatic.