[muted, underwater ambiance]
[beams creak]
[exhales wearily]
Come here, Kyuichi.
[TOKIO] Kyuichi!
Come in, please.
We're all done
for the day.
[plane ascends]
[phone dings]
[phone dings urgently]
[explosion]
[immense explosion]
[horrified gasp]
[downpour]
[NARRATION] Hal is gone now.
He and Kurumi
were inseparable...
but there's an empty space
where he used to be.
Kurumi could
no longer smile...
She could no longer sleep...
could no longer listen...
could no longer eat...
could no longer cry.
[TOKIO] Kyuichi...
Help me, please.
This isn't a task I can do.
If you agree, you
will take on a face.
You will become human...
so that you can save the child.
[water drips]
[machines beep]
[NARRATION]
And so, I became human.
[hurried footsteps]
[heavy breathing]
[pants]
I'm here, Kyuichi, I'm here...
Sorry I'm late!
Hal, please...
From today on, that is my name.
Ah... that's right.
Of course it is.
So, Hal...
how does it feel?
Being human?
I'm sorry... but...
what does "feel" mean?
[ARANAMI] Well, when a person
has feelings, they, uh... Hmm...
Forget I said anything!
Now, hurry up,
young man...
Places to go!
Uh...
That takes me back,
all right...
May I?
Each face should be
only one color...
when you solve a face, the
wish that's written there
will come true.
The girls were particularly
into these things back when
I was a student...
If you've got one,
boys must like 'em too.
Oh! Forgive me... Forgot
who I was talking to.
You wouldn't know what
old Hal did, would you.
[footsteps, ARANAMI grunting]
[ARANAMI pants]
It's hot.
Sorry to leave you Hal, but
I need to check on the ladies
and make sure
they're all right...
You be okay going on
by yourself, won't you?
Oh, hold on!
Take this.
Something about
Kurumi... but what?
[ARANAMI] Hal must've
written that one.
[HAL] It says
"Live with Kurumi."
Well, look at that.
It could have been
Hal's final wish.
[NARRATION]
And so, I became human.
[BOY B]
Wait for me, guys!
[BOY C]
Hey, be careful!
[NARRATION] I became human
for her. For Kurumi...
So she could remember
what it was like to live...
Here... in this city...
I became Hal.
[beeping]
[RADIO DJ A] Man, I tell ya.
It sure has gotten hot
around here lately, hasn't it?
[RADIO DJ B] Yeah, this
is a brutal heat wave...
I hope everyone out there
is staying hydrated.
[RADIO DJ A] Drinking
water's important, all right...
I wish my son had
kept that in mind.
[HAL strains]
Hello, is anyone there?
[RADIO DJ A] He was running
around the park chasing bugs.
[RADIO DJ B] Well, sure!
That's a little boy's
favorite pastime!
[RADIO DJ A]
Don't get me wrong...
[door slides shut clumsily]
...a single water break!
[RADIO DJ B laughs] Maybe--
[bicycle rides past, bell rings]
[HAL's footsteps]
[HAL sits down]
[clatter]
[hurried footsteps]
[door slides shut]
[HAL's hurried footsteps]
If you could just tell me--
Forgive me, but
are you Kurumi?
[KURUMI] Who're you?
I'm from the care center.
They should've told
you I was coming...
if not... I'm sorry
for the surprise.
[KURUMI] I don't care
where you came from...
I didn't ask
for a robotic Hal.
I came to help.
At times like this,
it can be beneficial to--
[HAL grunts]
Okay, I understand.
I'll go, then.
[HAL] One thing though...
Could you look this over?
I need a signature
before I can go.
[washing machine rumbles]
[crash]
[HAL gasps]
This must be Kurumi's...
So, she has a puzzle cube, too.
[puzzle cube sides pivoting]
[HAL] Ha!
That's one side!
Look at your
puzzle cube...!
One face is solved...!
Now the wish that was written--
Awww!
[KURUMI] Just leave.
[HAL] I understand...
[wind instrument plays]
[dishes clang]
[dishes clang wildly]
[dish breaks]
[oil sizzles]
[fire erupts]
[HAL] Woah!
[HAL panics]
[approaching footsteps,
clanging dishes]
[dishes set down]
[HAL] You must be hungry...
I made some food for you.
I've never really
done this before...
Cooked, I mean.
So it may not be
exactly perfect.
I'm going...
but I'll leave the
tray out here for you.
I hope you'll
have some at least.
I'll be back
again tomorrow.
Goodbye until then.
[slow chopping]
[floorboards creak]
[dishes set down]
I'm back,
just like I promised!
[dishes clang]
I hope you're
feeling better.
I thought I'd go out for a
bit and do some shopping...
Is there anything
I can get for you?
Huh?!
[exasperated sigh]
[chicks chirp]
[oil sizzles]
[HAL] Whoa!
I'm sorry about the
wait. Here you go.
--[HAL] Thanks!
--[CHEF] Enjoy!
[HAL] Uh...
[KIDS eat frantically]
[BOY A] Ah!
I did it!
Cool, huh?
[chuckles]
[HAL] So, I just press
the "purchase" button...
[alarm]
[HAL] Huh? What went wrong?
[hurried footsteps]
[BOY C] Hey! Come
check it out!
[BOY B] This way!
Over here!
[BOY B] Hurry! Let's go!
[BOY C] Remember,
I'm the one that found it!
See it?
[approaching footsteps]
[HAL] Huh?!
[beeping]
[HAL] Huh?
[incredulous]
The price is zero!
[KIDS giggle]
[OLD MAN grumbles]
[ARANAMI] So you tried to take
the giraffe with you, huh?
[HAL] Yes, but I
didn't get far before
the storeowner yelled at me.
[ARANAMI] That happens
when you steal things.
I don't understand. The
price showed up as zero.
Well, that's your
problem right there...
Just because something
says zero doesn't mean
it's free to take.
In some cases it can mean
the object is priceless.
Hold the other side
for me, would you?
Explain "priceless."
It means it's so
important that no amount
of money can
equal its value.
Zero means priceless...
which means important.
[MAMI] If you really
want that giraffe,
you know what you gotta do?
Convince Sadao to
let you have it.
He's the man who sits
in front of the store...
the old one on the bench.
Huh.
It's time for that
giraffe to go...
It looks ridiculous,
if you ask me.
You're not alone in that.
I've heard plenty of
others saying as much.
Poor Sadao.
His glaucoma must be getting bad
if he thinks that looks good.
[MAMI] Maybe that sort of thing
was cool back in his day.
If he won't give it up,
I bet Tsukiko could
talk some sense into him.
That's right! She's
the one to ask.
Hey Tsukiko. Will
you talk to Sadao?
Well, will you?
[TSUKIKO] No, I will not.
Don't be such
a curmudgeon...
This young man really seems
to want that giraffe.
Why not help him?
[TSUKIKO grumbles]
The better question is,
why should I help him?
Why would I go out of my way
for this weak-chinned chump
I don't even know?
[TSUKIKO] For one thing, the
little idiot doesn't even know
better than to take something
that doesn't belong to him.
On top of that, this
spineless sissy needs
an old lady to help him
with his problems...?
And what's the pathetic
whimp wearing...?
Is that a brooch?
[TSUKIKO] Hold on...
I know that button.
Oh... Is this
what you mean...?
I just got it today...
It was from--
Hmmm...
Interesting... You know
Kurumi, do you, young man?
Uh-huh.
[TSUKIKO] Well, why didn't
you say so, you little idiot?
I'm not done yet... It
might not be safe for y--
Oh, shut your mouth,
baldie... You quack!
I'm sure Tsukiko
will help you now.
She feels indebted to Kurumi.
Huh?
[ERIKA] Before she
came here to the center,
she got into a huge
argument with her family.
They gave away all
of her belongings,
even her clothing!
Awful...!
How they could do
something like that?
I'll never understand.
But... Kurumi had a
word with the family
and tracked down
every last thing.
She fixed them up,
good as new...
There, take a look.
Tsukiko gave out
things to all of us.
[HAL] Kurumi did all that?
[RUMIKO] As for the
button you've got...
I'm pretty sure it was on one
of Tsukiko's dresses before...
A very special dress.
The one she wore
on her first date.
Right! With Sadao.
[TSUKIKO] Shut it,
you two old biddies!
[MAMI giggles]
It's all been
taken care of...
Now, get over there, young
chump. The giraffe is yours.
Really? That's kind of you!
Here. Let me give you
this button to say thanks.
[TSUKIKO] No, boy, you keep it.
Huh?
[TSUKIKO] Just take
care of it, all right...?
It's a nice thought,
you know...
that my memories could be
scattered around the world,
living on after I'm gone...
I'm a lucky woman.
Not everybody can say that.
[HAL] Zero can mean
free... or priceless.
[static feedback]
[HAL hums]
[GIRL giggles]
[static feedback]
--Uh! Quit filming me!
--[GIRL laughs]
[HAL] Hey, that's pretty.
[static feedback]
I love it, Grandpa! Thank you!
[HAL] Whatcha makin'?
[static feedback]
They're bears, can't you tell?
Made from the yarn I got
from Grandma Ohtake.
Aren't they cute?
[static feedback]
I think I finally got it right!
[intense static feedback]
[static feedback]
Thank you, Hal... It's pretty.
[HAL] Look at all this cash!
[static feedback]
[KURUMI] You weren't
supposed to sell them...!
[PASSENGERS scream,
alarms blare]
[static]
[ARANAMI] There's no
need to run, Hal!
[ARANAMI's haggard breathing]
Take pity on an
old man, will you?
If I don't get there
soon, they might give it
to somebody else.
I need that giraffe!
Trust me. No one else is
going to want that thing!
[door jiggles]
[CHILDREN scream and play]
[SADAO grumbles]
You know, Doctor...
Kurumi's sadness
seems so impervious.
Do you think I'll ever be able
to understand it completely?
No, my boy,
I'm afraid not.
Oh, I see.
Is it because I'm a robot?
Robot, human,
doesn't matter.
Not as I see it.
[ARANAMI] I don't think anybody
can ever totally understand
someone else's emotions,
whether happy or sad.
[warning bell]
Is complete
understanding
like that really
necessary?
I don't see how I can help
her get better without knowing.
What am I supposed
to do, Doctor?
Well, that's
just it.
You don't need
to do anything.
Just be there for her.
Is that it?
That sounds so simple.
[ARANAMI] Yep, that's it.
[train approaches]
[ARANAMI] That's all
we humans really need.
[yells] Who cares
if it's simple?
Not everything in this world has
to be complicated, you know.
[GIRL IN STROLLER]
Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe...!
It's big and it's tall
and it's got spots...
It's a gotta be a
giraffe! I know it!
I know it...! Mommy, can we
stop and pet the giraffe?
[GREEN DRESS MOM]
Sit down, dear... Please!
Sachiko is waiting
for us... There.
[GIRL IN STROLLER]
But, Mommy, the giraffe...!
Well, anyway,
that's what I think,
but it's not like
I'm a philosopher...
Hey, come on, what are you
doing just standing there...?
We've almost made it...!
Let's get this over with.
Right.
[electronic trills]
[ARANAMI] Okay... now look out
for the power line over there.
[gasps]
[ARANAMI] Good...
Go around and get the back.
[HAL] You got it.
[metal clang]
[ARANAMI] Awww, What now?
[metal clanging, ARANAMI sighs]
[HAL gasps]
[crash]
[ARANAMI] Hey...!
I think it's caught...
What are you doing back there?
[HAL] Uh...
[ARANAMI] Speak up,
boy. What is it...?
Oh...! It's on my end.
Gimme a sec...
Okay... Okay...
A little more.
There we go!
[ARANAMI groans]
[ARANAMI] That's a big scratch.
You ought to be more careful
when you move things...
Now you remember that...! Okay?
[HAL] Huh?
Don't "huh" me, boy...
Nod your head!
[KURUMI giggles]
[door closes]
There you go... Pay off!
Yeah.
Ha!
[door opens]
[dishes clatter]
[chuckles]
Little kitty has a
secret room, just for you...!
Want to come in and
see it? I don't bite.
Meow! Meow!
What's this "meow"?
[sighs]
Hey there, baby!
Little kitty has a secret
room just for you...!
Wouldn't you like
to see for yourself?
Meow!
[BUSINESSMAN STUTTERS]
I don't know...
What does little kitty
have in that secret room?
[MAN whistles]
[MAN] Hey, I was right!
It really is you, Hal!
Hey, buddy...!
Fill a guy in.
Where have you
been all this time?
You had that huge fight with
Kurumi, and then there was
all that other stuff,
and then I was...
Hey, there's
the rat...!
He's down there!
Let's get 'im!
[MAN jumps in water]
Get back here, Ryu!
[jumps in water]
[gasps]
[RYU] Hal! There's a
favor I need to ask you.
I'll track you down
again, okay...?
It was good to see you! Glad
you're hanging in there...!
Later!
[WHITE SUIT MAN A]
Damn you!
[WHITE SUIT MAN B]
He's getting away!
Hurry up!
[raindrops]
[downpour]
[door opens]
I'm sorry, but...
I have to ask.
Was Hal... violent toward you?
Not with me. He was
never like that...
but I... did hear about
it from other people.
Did you two...
get into a fight?
[gasps]
[hesitates]
[stutters] I'm sorry...! You
don't have to talk about it.
Thanks. I needed this.
[KURUMI] It was the buttons...
Huh?
He sold all my buttons.
Without bothering to ask me.
[KURUMI] How could you have
done something like this?!
[HAL] You said you were
collecting them in order
to sell them...
That's why you had so many
of the things laying around,
wasn't it?
[KURUMI] You had no right!
You weren't supposed to
sell them...! I don't know how
I'll ever forgive you, Hal!
[retreating footsteps]
I don't understand...
Why...?
[KURUMI] Listen...
I've always dreamed of a store
that's small and intimate...
not big and flashy.
[HAL] How many times
do I have to say it?
I'm sorry!
My customers
will all be regulars,
and I'll know them by name...
I'll personally
oversee each order...
every item will be handcrafted.
[HAL] Now you're
being ridiculous!
How do you expect to
make a living like that?
[KURUMI] We can do it
if we budget accordingly.
I know we can!
[HAL] Are you crazy...?! You
don't understand, Kurumi...!
You have no idea what
it's like to be poor!
I've heard enough!
[HAL] What are you going to do?
[KURUMI] I don't know...!
Get away from you?
[fumbles with lens]
[electonric trills]
Emotions are tricky...
If only they were
expressed numerically.
I see why you were
angry with me...
I did some pretty
bad things, huh?
I'm very sorry.
I think it
takes two people
to make this big
a mess of things.
I'm ashamed.
I never understood
Hal's past...
how difficult his
childhood must have been.
[HAL gasps]
[KURUMI] I should have
tried harder to understand...
I'm sorry.
[HAL] Tell me, Doctor...
Did you know me
before all of this?
Hmm?
You mean, did I
know the real Hal?
Uh-hmm.
Yeah...
I knew him for a few years
before it happened.
He liked living
his life on the edge.
Especially with
that friend of his, Ryu.
[gasps]
[WHITE SUIT MAN A]
Get back here, Ryu!
They knew each other
back when they were kids
working at an illegal site.
[MASKED WORKER A]
You idiot...!
What were you thinking?!
This red stuff isn't what
we told you to bring back!
[whimpers]
Don't hurt him!
Ryu...
[MASKED WORKER A] Damn it...!
You piece of trash...
Back in! And do it right!
[RYU] Hal...! Hal!
[whimpering]
[MASKED WORKER B]
Back in line with you...
Gutter rat!
[RYU screams]
[ARANAMI] They escaped
as soon as they could...
After that, they made
a living selling anything
they got their hands on.
Tough life for a kid,
or anyone...
It took a toll on him.
Which isn't to say
he was a bad guy...
Matter of fact, I liked Hal.
A lot of people did.
[ERIKA] Here.
[gasps] You solved
another face!
So surprised...!
I'm old, young man,
but I'm not senile yet!
"Put on a yukata...
and go to a festival!"
[HAL] Huh?
Go to a festival, huh...?
Well, if that
isn't good timing...
[LADIES giggle, ring bell]
The Gion Festival!
Yep...! The Gion Festival!
It's such an exciting
time of year!
A festival makes it seem
anything's possible!
It can be
such a romantic time!
Love is in the air!
All the food
and the people...!
It's so invigorating,
I almost can't take it!
[chuckles]
But, what do I do about
a yukata for Kurumi?
Well, that's easy enough.
Ask her grandfather.
Tokio will know what to do!
[ARANAMI] Yukata! Fireworks!
The beach! Swimsuits!
[ARANAMI cheers]
Just what I needed, thanks.
[TOKIO] And that isn't all.
...this one is for you to wear.
[HAL] For me?
[TOKIO] That's right...
Kurumi made this
yukata for Hal.
You may not know this,
but spider webs are supposed
to ward off bad luck.
A special design for luck.
She was worried
about Hal, wasn't she?
[HAL] Was I...
Or I suppose I should say,
was Hal a bad person?
His life was hard...
From the time he was
a child, he was burdened
with an enormous debt.
He was born with a weak,
failing heart, you see...
His parents had
to buy him a new one.
[TOKIO] It seemed they'd never
be able to pay off the loan...
So, ultimately, Hal's parents
ran off, leaving him behind.
An awful thing
to do to a child.
Terrible situation altogether.
[hammering]
[gasps]
[HAL] Hello, Kurumi.
Please, take this.
I brought it for you.
I mean, um...
You could wear it
to the Gion Festival.
We could go together...
Oh...! If you
don't want to...
What about you...?
Are you gonna to wear that?
Yeah...
I thought I would,
since you made it for Hal.
You look good in it.
May I ask a question...?
You wanted very badly
to help Hal, didn't you?
Tell me, what did
you want to save him from?
From the whole world...
From everything.
[HAL] Did you know,
when it comes to the
most dangerous work...
they have humans do it?
In school they said
robots do things like that.
It's what they're for.
[chuckles]
It costs a lot of money
to maintain robots,
especially if they
get damaged...
No big deal... They
can use humans instead.
We're nice and
expendable.
[gasps]
They just look
for guys like me--
ones who're up to their
eyeballs in debt, I mean.
We're not hard to find.
The trick is
to have money.
Then everybody's
nice to you.
The city's your playground.
The world is your oyster.
But if you're poor, you're
beneath everyone's notice.
No one gives a damn.
[KURUMI sobs]
I should shut up. Don't
listen to me, really!
I'm sorry!
I'm just babbling
on about nothing.
Hey, I've got an idea!
Why don't we go
do some shopping?
That's it! We'll
go to that store.
What was it called, again...?
The one you like so much?
[sobs]
Uhhh...
Gum! I've got a piece
in here somewhere...
[yells]
Hal...?!
Are you okay?
What's that?
Come in with me.
[nervous breathing]
[door closes]
This is it... The glowing
thing he carried.
[exhales]
When I--
first saw it...
I thought tha--
I actually thought
it was Hal's heart.
[KURUMI] Stay still, okay?
I was wrong,
Hal... I'm sorry!
[gasps]
I'm sorry I didn't
understand...
that I didn't try...
[BOTH cry]
Please, Hal... will you
stay with me forever?
I'll always be here.
I swear to you.
I will be with you forever!
[distant cymbals]
[flutes play,
cymbals crash rythmically]
[crowd cheers, applauds]
[POLICEMAN] Attention, please!
Everyone behind the white line!
Whew... it's hot!
[POLICEMAN] Step back
until you're behind the line!
Here.
Huh?
Thank you, kind lady!
I wonder how young Hal is
handling himself out there.
[giggles]
I'll tell you all
something--if I was only
fifty years younger...!
Then you'd still
be forty years old.
[crowd applauds,
cymbals start back up]
Here we go!
[LADIES]
Ohhh!
[traditional japanese music]
[crowds cheer]
[LADIES cheer]
Every year...
I wonder how many more
times I'll see this parade.
Y'know?
You know something?
You're beautiful.
That's sweet
of you... Thanks.
There's no
need to stare, though.
I'll stop! Sorry!
[wind chime]
♪
[DISGUISED, SING-SONGY VOICE]
Hello there, Hal!
Gotcha! Doing all
right...? Eh, buddy?
[sneer]
Sorry to bother you
on such a nice day,
but I'm in a bit of trouble.
The books don't seem
to be balancing, you see.
So, well...
I was hoping you might
be able to help a guy out.
[RYU] After all,
you were involved
in this particular
transaction, too.
I even know
what we could sell.
[RYU yells]
[KURUMI] Come on!
Let's go!
[THUG A]
H-Hey!
[snarls]
Hurry!
[cars honk]
[WOMAN gasps]
[growls]
[keys against metal]
It's open. Let's go!
[floorboards creak]
[KURUMI gasps, screams]
Kurumi...!
Where are you?!
[HAL] Can you hear me?
Sorry, but I'm on
the wrong side of this deal,
and I need to get right.
[gasps]
Don't touch her...!
Get your filthy
hands off of her!
What's the
matter with you?
Get it together!
Snap out of it!
Why can't
you remember?!
How much longer is this
gonna go on for, huh?
[hard punch]
[HAL] Now you're
being ridiculous!
How do you expect
to make a living like that?
[KURUMI] We can do it
if we budget accordingly.
I know we can!
[HAL] Are you crazy?
You don't understand Kurumi!
You have no idea what
it's like to be poor!
I've heard enough!
[HAL] What are you going to do?
[KURUMI] I don't know...!
Get away from you?
[HAL] Kurumi...
please don't go...
[HAL yelling] Fine!
Do whatever you want!
[HAL gasps]
[PASSENGERS panic, scream]
[KURUMI] Hal...! Hal!
[screams]
Kurumi!
I should have been on
that plane with her...!
If I was there...
maybe I could've done
something to stop it!
There's nothing
you could have done.
Not a damn thing, Hal!
[HAL, desperate] You don't
know! Maybe I--!
[HAL sobs]
Kurumi...
Kurumi!
Put it all together, damn you!
[HAL] Kurumi! Kurumi!
Think! That isn't her!
The real Kurumi is dead!
There... There you are,
you're awake!
Come on...
Let's go home now.
[HAL &amp; KURUMI fall into water]
What the hell
is he thinking...?!
Hal!
Hard to take in, I know...
But he truly does seem
to believe he's a robot.
He couldn't cope with
the reality of the situation...
So he had to find a way
to dissociate from it.
Can we help him?
Can anything be done?
[ARANAMI] What he needs
more than anything else now
is Kurumi.
Without her...
[TOKIO] I know,
but that's impossible...
She's gone.
[ARANAMI] This is one way.
It isn't standard practice yet.
but there is something
called robotic therapy.
Help me, please.
This isn't a task I can do.
If you agree, you
will take on a face.
You will become human...
so that you can save the child.
I'm glad you're here.
Kurumi.
You know, the
world's not so bad.
Really... I just didn't
realize it until I met you.
Everything I went
through before we met...
if that was the price for
finding someone like you...
well... then it was worth it.
I know, it's
taken me a long time...
but I finally understand.
No matter how much
pain there might be...
knowing you's still worth it.
Kurumi...
♪
Kurumi!
No, please! Don't go!
You can't leave me!
[cries]
Kurumi!
[grunts]
[water splashes]
[THUGS gasp]
Hal! Are you all right?!
Kurumi!
Stop it, Hal!
Please! Let it go!
Stay here... This
is where you belong.
Sorry for all this.
I know it's been hard,
but I'm telling you...!
Hal...! You deserve to live!
[RYU sobs]
[PEOPLE cheer, applaud]
Hey, Tokio...
Where do you believe the people
we love go when they die?
I don't think
they go anywhere at all.
They're with us forever,
just like they were in life...
In fact I often talk
to the ones I've lost.
Just little things,
you know...
"It's hot today," or
"What a delicious meal."
Things like that.
Isn't that an awful lot
like talking to yourself?
You think so, eh...?
Well, I guess you
could call it that.
Ha...
[RADIO DJ A] So, yesterday was
the bonfire to see off the
spirits that came calling
during the festival.
[RADIO DJ B] Yes, it was!
[RADIO DJ A] Did you know
they're saying that something
like a hundred thousand
people turned up for it?
[RADIO DJ B] That many?
Wow...! So, did you go?
[RADIO DJ A] No... I mean,
I was planning to,
but then something came up...
You know how it is...
[tires squeal]
[ARANAMI] Hey, Hal.
Glad I caught you...
Do you think you could find it
in your heart to do me a favor
and look after the ladies
for me tonight...?
I'd never ask normally,
but something came up.
You know how
things can be.
Excellent...! I
really appreciate it.
I owe you one, Hal!
[rings bell]
Thank you for this meal.
[exhales]
[HAL] This is really
a delicious meal... Kurumi.
♪