[YUTA] I was about to kick-off
my career as an artist,
and my solo debut was set
to be at the school I attended.
But Shishiku isn't your
run-of-the-mill institution.
It's the wildest
academy in the country.
It was a totally transparent
attempt to generate some buzz.
Although, to be honest,
I couldn't have
cared less about it.
Of course, that's
how I felt at the time.
And if it wasn't for who I met,
I'd still feel that way.
[FANGIRLS screech]
Huh?
The hell?
[HINAKO]
Where have I seen him before?
Girls, please.
I need to get to class,
or I'll be late.
Huh? Oh!
The guy from the posters!
Oh...
Hey. You a fan of
mine, too, babe?
Want an autograph?
No, I'm good, thanks!
Why are you here?
[YUTA]
Hmph.
You mean you don't know?
That hurts.
I'm a second-year student
in Cherryblossom Class.
Name's Yuta Mirako.
[FANGIRLS screech]
You're quite the little cutie.
You seem frail and naïve.
It kinda makes me
wanna take care of you.
Got a boyfriend I can replace?
No! I am a boy!
So, you are.
Can't believe
I missed the uniform,
though I'm not sure
I'm convinced.
[HINAKO]
Uh...
I don't make mistakes.
I pride myself on having
an especially keen eye.
And...
No guy has wrists like yours.
[FANGIRLS screech]
[photo snaps]
Huh?
[HINAKO]
I get that a lot, actually.
It's true I'm pretty short,
and I don't have the
most muscular build.
But, I really am a guy!
Uh-huh... Well, I'll actually
be attending class
for a change today.
I'll find you.
[HINAKO]
You'll find me?
Yup!
Maybe next time I can be a
little more thorough with you.
Then I'll know for sure whether
you're really a boy or not.
Huh?
[TOTOMARU]
Hey, Handsy!
Think you could give it a rest?
You're bothering Hikaru.
Not to mention
being a total creep.
[KONPARU]
He might be mild-mannered,
but he's the boss
of the first-years.
Back off, or we'll make you.
Yeah? A scrawny thing like you?
[HINAKO sighs]
And you are... who again?
We're his bros.
You got a problem with that?
[YUTA]
"Bros"?
What a load of crap.
Seriously.
Guess the first-years
don't amount to much.
[YUTA]
Been a while, Rintaro.
Didn't think you'd be
the one to reach out, first.
It's not like you at all.
[KIRA] Stop messing with
the first-years, understand?
[YUTA]
Ah, yes.
So, you saw that?
He's quite interesting,
isn't he?
I thought he was
a girl, at first.
Maybe, I'll...
[chuckles]
All right, kill the scary look.
I'll leave him be, okay?
Besides, he's got a
couple "friends" with him.
What a loser.
[KIRA]
There's that pathetic attitude.
You haven't changed
at all, Yuta.
You're still letting ancient
history tear you apart.
[TOSHIYA]
Hey, did ya hear the news?
You know that guy, Mirako?
Rival to the top
of the second-years?
He's putting on
a solo concert here.
Hell yeah! Ha!
A punk and an idol, huh?
Must be exhausting.
I heard something else.
Mirako was messin' with Hikaru.
His lieutenants are pissed.
That's right.
It won't be much longer until...
A power play!
[HINAKO moans]
[YUTA] Can't believe
I missed the uniform,
though I'm not sure
I'm convinced.
I don't make mistakes.
I pride myself on having
an especially keen eye.
And...
You're so thin,
I can't help but wonder.
Are you actually
who you say you are?
Huh... He definitely looks
like a girl from this angle.
You conquered
the first-year class?
Really?
[HINAKO]
Hmm?
[HINAKO gasps]
Mirako, what are you--?
[YUTA] No need to shout,
I'm right here.
Good morning, sleepy head.
[HINAKO]
Uh... Yeah, good morning to--
What am I saying?!
Get off me!
[YUTA]
Fine, jeez.
Don't be embarrassed.
We're both guys after all.
Unless, of course,
you're admitting
you're actually a girl?
[HINAKO]
You want me to prove I'm a guy?
Then quit messing
around and fight me.
You're one of the top
second-years, right?
Well, if I'm a girl it
should be no contest.
You've got fire.
And your punch
is nothing to scoff at.
Hmph! You sure you wanna do this
without your "bros"
here to help you?
My friends have nothing
to do with this!
You're right,
they'd only get in the way.
Besides, what's
the point of friends?
They'll just let you down
when you need them.
Huh? They really bother you.
What is it about my friends
that makes you so angry?
[YUTA gasps]
Know what, you sound like
Rintaro when you talk like that.
[HINAKO]
Rintaro?
[YUTA]
Damn it.
Everyone acts like
they know things.
Heh! Six months,
nine days and no challenge.
I'm getting bored.