[KIRA] The moment we met
I could feel something was off.
And, as time went by, that
feeling became total certainty.
More than anything,
there was the resemblance.
It was uncanny.
[HINAKO]
At some point in time,
I had just forgotten
all about him.
But I was little,
and it was years ago.
I guess it shouldn't
have surprised me.
My protector, he inspired me
to become strong on my own.
So, of course,
I would call him "Brother."
[gasps]
Huh?
You're so thin,
I can't help but wonder.
Are you actually
who you say you are?
I want to help him.
[KIRA]
It's simple.
This is not Hikaru Onigashima.
[HINAKO gasps]
If anything happens,
I'll be there to protect you.
After all...
After all, Hinako,
you're my little sister.
[approaching footsteps]
The next time you ask someone
to meet you, show up on time.
Yeah?
[sighs]
[approaching footsteps]
Huh?
[HOUOU]
S'been awhile, Hikaru.
How are ya?
Have we met before?
Seriously?
D'you forget what your
own brother looks like?
[HINAKO]
So this is Houou Onigashima!
Um, 'sup, Big Bro?
[HOUOU]
Hmm?
Uh, Houou?
Hikaru!
Yes?
Must be a cold day in hell.
I never thought
you'd call me "Big Bro"
or anything close to it.
Really?
Well, can you blame me?
All I ever got from
you was "Buzz off!"
or "You're in my way!
I hate your guts!"
What is wrong with you, Hikaru.
[KIRA] So, you gonna
tell me why I'm here?
[YUTA] Thought I might beat
some sense into your ass.
Don't be ridiculous.
[YUTA] Well, you've been
getting on my nerves lately.
Watching you sulk about
isn't all that entertaining.
Do me a solid and get over it.
It's got nothing to do with you.
[HOUOU]
There are two guys
running Shishiku's
second-years.
But I'm the one sittin'
at the top of the dog pile.
See, thanks to some trouble,
I ended up repeating.
Whoa. Must be rough.
[HOUOU] Heh!
So, word through the grapevine
is you already took
over the first-years.
Is that true?
Yeah.
I guess.
Heard the fish were a
pretty rowdy bunch, too.
You having trouble
keeping 'em in line?
Well, at first
Totomaru, Konparu,
and I didn't really get along,
but now they're the best
friends I've ever had.
Got ya.
Found yourself some bros?
Uh-huh!
Totamaru can be pretty
straightforward at times,
but he's the best
student in Shishiku!
So much so, the teachers
actually cried over his grades!
And Konparu's about as
stubborn and moody as they come,
but he's super sweet and
cares a lot for his siblings.
Exactly like an
older brother should!
Uhm...!
Uh...
Ah! Not what I meant!
You're great just
the way you are!
[HOUOU chuckles]
Goofball.
Look at you,
actin' all grown up.
That'll help here, but let your
guard down for an instant,
and it's game over.
Understand?
[HOUOU] If anything happens,
just come to me.
I know I haven't been the best
brother to you over the years,
but we're family,
no matter what.
You can always count on me.
[HINAKO]
Thanks.
Anyway, if you can get used
to this school's atmosphere,
everything else
will go smoothly.
That's the problem.
I don't know how.
It's simple.
Stick to what you believe in
and face every foe head on.
Whatever you care
about, fight for it,
with every ounce of
strength you can muster.
Do that,
and you'll be just fine.
[YUTA] You think I haven't
changed at all, right?
But I'm pretty sure you have!
Now which one of us is "letting
ancient history tear him apart"?
Shut up!
I'm sick of watching
you brooding!
Quit running away
from your feelings!
It's pathetic!
And it's pissing me off!
[KIRA]
That's enough!
[YUTA] Since they saved me,
I haven't had the right
to call myself the top
of the second-years!
It's you now.
So get your act together or
we'll never keep them in line!
Got it?
[KIRA] I never asked
to be top of our class.
I didn't want it, or to have
anything to do with them.
That's your excuse?
[KIRA] But, I'll admit,
you have a point.
These feelings,
I can't run from them anymore.
I'll fight.
[YUTA chuckles]
[HINAKO]
That's right.
I need to face my foe head on.
It's time we settled this!