I'm not interested in fighting.
It's pointless.
[HINAKO]
Konparu.
You coward!
Huh...?
Give back my brother!
[HINAKO]
Your brother?
What are you talking about?
I'm here because I got this
letter of challenge from you.
[KONPARU] You're the
one who sent a letter,
you sorry son of a bitch.
[HINAKO]
Huh?
This doesn't make any sense.
[KONPARU]
Don't play dumb!
You've tried to pick a fight
with me every day for weeks.
What? You resort to kidnapping
when you don't get your way?
Bastard!
Just how rotten are you?
What? Kidnapping?
Look man, you're
confused or something.
Hikaru doesn't roll like that.
Now, are you gonna
fight him or keep babbling?
[GOON LEADER]
Hey, Boss!
[TOTOMARU, HINAKO]
Hmm?
Don't worry!
We picked up Konparu's
little brat of a brother,
like you said!
[MINORU muffled cries]
Minoru!
[gasps]
I know that boy!
Wait, seriously?
[GOONS laugh]
[HINAKO] I-I met him on the
way to school the other day.
But those other guys...?
Whatever goes down here,
I got your back, Bro.
I trust you wouldn't stoop to
pulling dirty tricks like that.
Totomaru.
Don't worry, Minoru!
I'll get you out of this!
[GOON LEADER]
Whoa, now.
One more step and the brat
will have a permanent smile.
Better cool it.
[KONPARU grunts]
You sick, demented psychopath!
What kind of monster
threatens a child
just so they can
have a street fight?
[HINAKO] This is a
misunderstanding, I swear!
[gasps]
[HINAKO]
Mm.
If you want a fight,
you've got one pal!
[KONPARU]
You won't get away with this!
I swear, by the time
I'm done with you.
You'll be crippled!
[KONPARU]
At the time,
Minoru was in danger,
so I just sorta lost it.
Thinking back to that day,
Hikaru was just trying
to talk some sense into me,
so he was slow
to react, at first.
All right.
Guess I have to do this.
[HINAKO]
Yeah. I realized...
...if I wanted any hope of
getting through to Konparu,
I'd have to snap him out
of it with a few punches.
[gasps]
Huh...?
Now, will you listen, Konparu?
I had nothing to do
with the kidnapping.
Just the thought of doing
something like that
turns my stomach.
I could never--
You're still acting innocent?
Stop, I don't buy it!
Just leave him alone!
[gasps]
[HINAKO]
Konparu...
[MINORU]
Big Bro!
[KONPARU]
Huh? Minoru?
[GOONS groan]
[KONPARU]
Thank goodness.
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't there.
[MINORU]
I... I can't breathe.
Oh! Oops.
[MINORU]
That's him, Bro!
Huh?
He's the cute boy that helped me
when those bullies tried
to take my lunch money!
He was just as cool then, too!
Isn't he awesome?
[KONPARU]
That was you?
[MINORU]
Thanks, cute boy!
I owe you!
No. Really!
[chuckles]
[KONPARU]
Sorry about this.
Huh?
[TOTOMARU]
Hm?
I was in the wrong here.
I threw punches
without thinking.
I'm ashamed of myself.
I was angry.
You didn't deserve any of this.
Hey, I get it.
I mean, I've been trying to pick
a fight with you for so long.
I'm just sorry your
brother got involved.
[KONPARU]
I don't get it.
Why would those guys
do this in the first place?
[TOTOMARU]
Who knows?
Maybe they thought,
if you two duked it out,
you'd destroy each other.
Freakin' cowards.
[HINAKO]
Hmm...
[TOTOMARU]
Hm?
[KONPARU]
I learned a lot about you today.
Huh?
Not only are you
incredibly strong,
but you've got a kind heart
and look out for the weak,
like you've done
for my little brother.
After all this,
I think you'd make a great
leader for the first-years.
Do you mean that?
I do.
And, you'll have
my full support,
Hikaru Onigashima.
[gasps]
[HINAKO]
Thank you, Konparu.
[TOTOMARU chuckles]
Hell yeah!
All our problems just
flew out the window!
Hikaru's at the
top of the first-years,
and Headphones is a
bonified member of the gang.
Uh... I didn't agree to that.
Sure.
Gah, you're annoying.
Huh? Hikaru?
What's up?
[HINAKO]
Nothing!
[HINAKO laughs]
[ALL laugh]