[THUG A growls]
[THUGS growl]
[TOSHIYA]
Hey, did you hear the rumor?
They're saying Hikaru
Onigashima's a chick.
[TORA]
Hell yeah, I did!
It's the biggest scandal
in Shishiku's history!
[SAKUYA] But, could a
girl really be that tough?
If he is a chick, she still beat
the first- and second-years.
[KENTA]
Whatever the case,
the flyers and internet
chatter are bad news.
The whole school's on edge.
[ALL 4]
This'll be one hell of a storm.
[KIRA] There's a lot
of talk going around.
You okay?
[HINAKO]
I think so.
Sorry for making you all worry.
[TOTOMARU]
Why are you apologizing, dude?
[KONPARU]
You did nothing wrong.
[HINAKO]
But...
[PUNK A]
What the hell is all this?
We're a laughing stock!
[PUNK B]
Explain yourself!
Are you really a chick?
[PUNK C]
We're waiting, Onigashima!
Guys, chill out
and think for a second.
Shishiku's a boy's school.
Why would a girl even come here?
[PUNK D] 'Sup?
Too embarrassed to talk?
[TOTOMARU]
Jeez, what a bunch of dumbasses.
If they'd cool their jets,
they'd realize it was fake.
[KIRA] Do we have any idea
who started the rumor?
[YUTA]
It's my fault.
Huh?
Care to explain? Now?
It was some of my fans.
They started it on
my message board.
They might've thought I was
in a relationship with Hikaru.
[TOTOMARU] You were kind of
creepin' on him for a bit there.
[KONPARU]
Damn, girls are terrifying.
[YUTA]
My bad. Sorry.
Uh! Come on, please don't
bow to me like that, Mirako!
This is my responsibility!
I should've just worked harder.
If I had,
maybe things wouldn't have
gotten out of hand like this.
Don't be stupid, Bro.
The fault is with the losers
freaking out over this BS.
Those trolls are
just making noise.
They'll get bored, eventually.
[TOTOMARU] So keep your head up
and ride this out, okay?
No matter what anyone says,
you're our boss
and we respect you.
Right, guys?
You know it.
[KIRA]
Mm.
Thank you.
[TOTOMARU]
If push comes to shove,
just strip!
That'll do it! Real quick!
[KONPARU] Only you would
get naked in front of people
for no reason.
[TOTOMARU]
Whatever dude.
[YUTA]
What do you expect?
He's got no sense of decorum.
[KIRA]
Agreed.
[TOTOMARU]
Oh, I get it.
Gangin' up on ol' Totomaru.
Well, turnabout's
fair play you know!
[PUNK LEADER] The guys at
Shishiku are freakin' pissed!
This is too good!
[GOON LEADER]
Just like we were hoping.
Good work, Oyamada.
[OYAMADA]
Heh. It was easy.
They're punks, but they still
have their own set of rules.
They stick to a hierarchy.
Now, we just gotta
push a little harder.
It was naïve of us to think
everything would just blow over.
The rumors kept getting worse,
and tension at the school
was rising like mad.
What are you gonna do
if they find out
your true identity, huh?
All of my efforts would
have been for nothing!
A brilliant plan, wasted!
Even as Hikaru said that,
I wasn't sure what
I could do to change things.
So I kept quiet,
like I had since the
whole thing had started.
And then, finally,
the day I had dreaded arrived.
[PUNK E]
Prove you're a man! Right now!
[PUNK F]
You owe us that much at least!
[PUNK G]
Yeah! Whip it out!
[PUNK H]
We want proof!
[TOTOMARU]
How stupid are you guys?
You gonna let gossip
get you riled up like this?
[KONPARU] Everyone in
here knows how strong he is.
No way he's a girl.
Chick's aren't built that way.
Heh...
[PUNK I]
Enough excuses!
Show us your junk!
[PUNK J]
We want visible proof!
[PUNK K]
Yeah! Visible!
[PUNK L] Take it off,
then we'll know for sure.
[PUNK K]
Yeah! Take it off!
[PUNK M] If you're not a girl,
you won't mind stripping!
[PUNK N] That's the only
way to prove you're a man!
[PUNK K]
Yeah! Prove it!
Take it off! Take it off!
[STUDENTS] Take it off!
[PUNK O]
You're kidding me.
[PUNK P]
For real?
[PUNK Q]
He really is a chick!
[PUNK R] She was lying
to us the whole freakin' time!
[PUNK S]
Tricky bitch!
[PUNK T]
She's gotta pay!
Make her pay!
[PUNK U]
No chick's gonna be my boss!
[OYAMADA laughs]
I heard Shishiku had
a skirt running things
but didn't believe it.
Looks like all
the rumors had merit.
[KIRA, YUTA]
Huh?
[PUNK V]
Oyamada?
[PUNK W] The hell is Saka
Third High School doing here?
[OYAMADA chuckles] It'd be
hilarious if it weren't so sad.
Don't worry, fellas,
we'll expose this
fraud for what she really is.
You just stand back
and enjoy the show.
[PUNK, GOON LEADER laugh]
You guys...
You ain't layin' a finger on
him, unless you get through us.
By all means, try it.
[OYAMADA growls]