[YUTA grunts]
[YUTA]
Friends, huh?
So much for that.
[HINAKO]
Can you help me Kira?
It's about Yuta Mirako.
I thought you might
have the answer.
You know him, right?
Then tell me, why does he
hate friendship so much?
Know what?
You sound like Rintaro
when you talk like that.
I'll say this once.
It's got nothing to do with you.
[HINAKO]
True.
It's just I feel like
I should do something.
He seems so sad.
I want to help him.
[KIRA gasps]
[HINAKO] I think I understand
what he's feeling.
The loneliness and the hurt.
Because for a time, I felt
the same way that he does.
[cries]
I'm really glad I asked Kira.
What he said after that was
more than enough to motivate me.
Tomorrow?
Sure, I got nothin'
better to do.
You owe me, Hikaru.
Tomorrow, we train
for the whole damn day!
My wonderfully accepting friends
were gracious enough to help me.
When it came time
for the concert,
we volunteered as event staff.
--[FAN A] Yuta, baby!
--[FAN B] Come on out!
[FAN C]
Don't be shy!
[FAN D]
Where is he?
[CROWD cheers]
--[FAN E] He's so hot!
--[FAN F] Notice me!
[FAN G]
Kiss me, gorgeous!
Good evening!
Thanks so much
for coming out to see me!
I'm flattered.
I'm gonna make it hot tonight.
I hope you can keep up with me.
[cheering]
I've poured my soul
into these songs.
The first one of the night
is one that's
particularly personal.
I hope you enjoy it.
[GOON, PUNK LEADER]
Hold it!
Huh?
Sorry, fellas. No autographs.
Do we look like your
loser fans, pretty boy?
Don't make me laugh.
The thought of a punk
pretending to be an idol
makes me wanna puke.
It's pathetic.
So, uhh...
Is this part of the show?
Doubt it.
We know these guys.
Huh?
Ha! I get it now.
You're jealous of me.
Nothing's more pitiful
than a man sick with envy.
Poor babies.
Hey! Better watch that mouth.
Hear that, boys?
The pop star says we're pitiful.
Get him!
[PUNK LEADER] What? You gonna
fight back or somethin'?
[GOON LEADER]
Think about this.
Your little show's being
broadcast nationally.
Could get ugly.
[HINAKO]
Stop right there!
[PUNK LEADER]
Who're these chumps?
Wannabe heroes?
[GOON LEADER]
Mind your own damn business.
What is this?
I couldn't just leave you to
deal with things on your own.
Huh? What are you,
stupid or something?
Yeah.
A big stupid softie with great
friends who tolerate me.
The boss says fight for you,
so that's what we'll do.
End of story.
Shishiku is our turf.
They can't waltz in here
like they own the place.
Really?
[HINAKO]
Let's go!
[TOTOMARU, KONPARU]
Right!
[KIRA] Mirako used to
be a good-natured guy.
He cared a lot
about his friends.
In middle school
he started to rise up,
and he trusted them to back him.
But then, one day,
his friends betrayed that trust.
It taught him that comradery,
like being top of the school,
meant next to nothing.
[KIRA]
After that, he saw friendship
between guys as a fantasy.
A game of pretend
that led to regret.
[PUNK LEADER]
You'll be sorry!
[FAN H]
Awesome!
[FAN I]
Yuta's entourage kicks ass!
[OYAMADA]
Tsch! Damn it all.
Ha! I give up.
You have me beat.
You're as light as a feather.
Like a little princess.
Come on.
You can share your secrets.
I won't kiss and tell.
I told you. I'm a boy!
Yeah, about that.
I've decided I don't care
if you're a boy or girl.
Oh. Then, would you
mind putting me down?
[TOTOMARU]
Hey, that's enough, weirdo!
[KONPARU]
Let go of him! Or else!
[HIKARU]
Stupid Hinako!
She doesn't even
care about Yuta,
but I'm the one stuck out
here with the rabble!
Damn!
Boss...
[YUTA]
It's all right, everyone!
Thanks to my
powerful friends here,
those creeps won't be
bothering us again!
And now just for you, I'll share
our bond through my music!
[FANGIRLS screech]
[FAN J]
Bond with me!
[FAN K]
Let's get married!
[FAN L]
He's so hot!