[HARUO]
Hmm.
[HIKARU, HINAKO cry out]
[HINAKO]
Oh, no, are you okay?
[HIKARU moans]
[HARUO] I'm a doctor,
conveniently passing by.
Gracious!
This is a compound fracture!
Really? Can you
call 119 for him?
[HIKARU]
Wait!
I was heading to my school's
entrance ceremony.
[HINAKO] I don't think you
should worry about that.
[HIKARU]
You don't understand.
My school is Shishiku Academy.
[gasps]
You're me.
Uncanny.
Y'know. If this is a miracle,
then we have to
make good use of it!
Good use?
[HIKARU]
That's right!
Since I'm clearly too
injured to make it, you'll go
to the Shishiku Academy
entrance ceremony in my place.
Wait. Are you serious?
Yes. Not a bad idea.
It could actually work.
Huh?
The Shishiku Academy
he's talking about
is a unique boy's school.
If he misses the ceremony, it's
grounds for immediate expulsion.
But if you were to
attend class in his place
for a little while--
Attend class?
There's no way that would work.
I'd miss out on my own classes!
That won't be a problem.
I'll be going to
your school instead.
Huh?!
[HIKARU]
So don't sweat it.
Just go to Shishiku.
But... I can't.
I'm a girl, and you're a...
Think this through.
If your actions get him
expelled, then you'll be
financially responsible for
his enormous medical bills.
More like gargantuan.
[HINAKO]
Uh...?
[HIKARU]
Guess it's settled.
For now, you'll go to
Shishiku Academy as a boy,
and you'll rise to
the top of the school!
Simple as pie!
[HINAKO]
You just added a condition!
[HIKARU] My name's Hikaru
Onigashima, by the way.
But, starting today, that's
the name you'll be going by.
[HINAKO] Turns out.
That little "accident"
was actually staged to get me
to attend Shishiku Academy.
But that wasn't the half of it.
Sorry.
When the young boss gets
an idea, he stops listening.
[chuckles]
I do.
Young boss?
The surprises didn't stop there.
Uh... Wha... This is...
Uh-huh!
We had everything in
the orphanage shipped
to this apartment.
Get comfy, this is where
you're living from now on.
[HINAKO]
You must be joking!
[HIKARU]
Don't freak out.
We smoothed it over
with that Suzukaze place
you were staying in.
It's fine.
Huh?
It was so easy.
All I had to tell them
was that we were long-lost
twins, and presto!
I mean, look at us.
I don't think
there's anyone alive
who wouldn't think
we were siblings.
HUH?! Siblings?
No way!
Yep.
You and I are
practically family, now.
[HINAKO]
Uh...
[HIKARU]
And...
As the second son of
the Onigashima Group,
I have an obligation
to take the top spot
at Shishiku for my family.
Wait, are you... yakuza?
Jeez, are you gonna freak
out about everything?
Look... It's Onigashima
family policy.
Every son has to
attend Shishiku Academy,
take it over,
and make it a breeding
ground for future gangsters.
But I've suffered from illness
ever since I was a child.
[coughs]
And I doubt I could manage it.
[HIKARU] On the other hand,
you've been healthy
and studying various
martial arts all this time.
Conquering Shishiku
should be a breeze!
[HINAKO]
When I was growing up.
I didn't have anyone.
I was pretty much alone.
He was the first family
that I'd ever known.
And before I realized it,
I'd agreed to help him.
Hey, did you hear the rumor?
Apparently, Totomaru
from Samejima
got his ass handed to him.
Hell yeah, he did!
That's what happens
when you take on
an Onigashima mano-a-mano!
[SAKUYA] Well, I think he lost
on purpose out of respect.
Hikaru didn't look
like much of a fighter.
[KENTA]
For real?
If that's true it means Hikaru's
status as number one is:
[ALL 4]
A lie!
Uh... 'Scuse me?
[TOTOMARU] Dammit!
I thought I was past this.
I mulled it over a
thousand times yesterday,
but I still can't
face the music.
Talk about lame, huh?
[HINAKO]
Not sure I follow.
[TOTOMARU sighs]
Really, dude?
I'm tryin' to say you
beat me fair and square.
No other way to slice it.
I accept it.
No bull.
It's the truth.
I respect your strength
and your skill as a fighter,
not to mention your family name.
[TOTOMARU] There's no
turning back at this point.
By beating me, you're now the
acting boss of the first-years.
I'll be your right hand.
If anyone challenges you,
I'll back you up with
everything I've got.
Hold on, Minowa.
I didn't mean to do that.
Don't call me that.
"Totomaru" will do just fine.
[HINAKO]
Uh... Really?
Isn't that kind of
overly familiar?
Huh?
I don't think it's a big deal.
I mean, we're bros now.
Bros?
That means "friend," right?
Well, yeah, you punch it
out with a guy, and you're bros!
That means a lot to me.
Uh...
To... Totomaru.
Uh! Sure, whatever.
[TOTOMARU]
Y'know.
I used to dream 'bout takin'
over Shishiku Academy.
Well...
Until that fight, anyway.
It's frustrating.
But he's the real deal,
so I can't really complain.
Hikaru Onigashima is a badass.
I respect the hell out of him.
[gasps]
[KIRA]
You're unnaturally thin.
[gasps]
[KIRA]
Makes me wonder.
Are you really
who you say you are?
[HINAKO]
Huh?!