[NARRATION] It was a season
in which the war banners
blossomed across the land.
They were planted by men
who thirsted for power.
Men who wanted dominion
over this divided country.
[NARRATION]
Shingen Takeda, also known as
the "Tiger of Kai."
At his command, the largest
cavalry of the age.
He rode them hard.
To the very edge of victory.
[NARRATION]
However...
[NARRATION] Before he could
claim absolute rule,
he crossed the Sanzu
river, into death.
As his sun set, we reached
the dawn of a new era,
led by Oda and Tokugawa.
[NARRATION] Though leaderless,
the Takeda cavalry
pressed on.
They put all they had
into a single battle:
Nagashino.
[NARRATION]
They were met on the field
by row upon row of soldiers,
Each loyal to the
Oda and Tokugawa.
Three thousand of them
carrying matchlocks,
their swords and spears,
things of the past.
[RED WARRIORS yelling]
Fire!
[RED WARRIORS screaming]
[yelping]
[groaning]
[RED WARRIOR E groans]
To think that an
army of that size
could be taken down so easily.
This will change everything.
Yes.
Who's that?
Cut off Nobunaga's head
and this is over!
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[NOBUNAGA]
We have but one life.
One march from birth to rot.
So it goes.
[yelling]
[YUKIMURA gasps]
Who might you be?
Takeda's retainer!
Nobuyuki Sanada.
[grunts] I'm his brother.
Yukimura Sanada!
Oh. Brothers, are you?
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA yell]
[NARRATION]
They put forth a valiant effort,
but the Takeda
forces were defeated
on the bloody
fields of Nagashino.
And with the death
of Katsuyori Takeda
at Mt. Tenmoku, the clan
was effectively wiped out.
Though they once
raced towards death,
the Sanada brothers were
now forced to flee from it.
We gave everything we had.
But still, Takeda fell.
[NOBUYUKI]
Yukimura.
How could the house
not survive the master?
I feel like our failure means
we've betrayed his legacy!
[NOBUYUKI] Takeda is no more,
but still, we must walk on.
Yes, but what path do we
follow now, brother?
We have lost our way!
Without Takeda to lead us,
where will the Sanada go?
We will find our way.
We'll have to forge--
The Oda forces are
beginning to close in on us.
We have to run, quickly!
[RED WARRIORS gasp]
[groans]
We must flee!
[YUKIMURA grunts]
Where are you going?
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
--[YUKIMURA grunting]
--[BLUE WARRIORS groaning]
[grunting]
[BLUE WARRIOR AA sputters]
[pants, gasps]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
--[gunshot]
--[gasps]
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI panting]
[grunts]
Yukimura!
How could you have
been so foolish?
You charged in blindly,
with no regard for our wounded,
nor consideration for
how many enemies
may have been waiting!
Are you trying to
get yourself killed?
Listen, brother.
I don't know if I can
carry the shame with me.
We failed our master,
and living without
honor goes against
the code of the Sanada!
Have you forgotten why
we always have these
six coins at the ready?
It's so we are prepared to give
the boatman of
the Sanzu his toll,
and cross into the underworld.
You're a fool!
They represent living
without fear of death,
not a desire for it!
They signify our strong heart,
our will to face challenges!
They are a pittance!
The true cost of crossing that
river is the Soul of the Sanada!
Takeda's dreams must
go on living with us.
That means our struggles
cannot end here.
For now, we must live on
shouldering the burdens
of those we've lost.
But, brother, how?
Side by side.
You and I will
weather the storm.
We'll never stop fighting
to keep the soul
of the Sanada alive.
I was reckless. You're right.
Forgive me.
"Where will the
Sanada go," you ask?
I say we go back
to our homeland.
[YUKIMURA]
But what's there for us?
We must go and ensure that
there is a place for us.
We'll build our castle there.
For the Sanada. Our home.
[NARRATION] Not long after,
at the Honnoji Temple
in Kyoto, Nobunaga fell
victim to betrayal.
A coup led by Mitsuhide Akechi,
one of his inner circle,
who held many
grievances against him.
[NARRATION]
In power for a mere 13 days,
Mitsuhide was
defeated at Yamazaki
by Hideyoshi Hashiba,
a man that had his own
dreams of ruling the land.
I'm starting to
feel at rest here.
You as well?
That's why we built it.
And for the people.
Their smiles are
a balm to our wounds.
Our worries.
I know. It's true.
[gasps]
[YUKIMURA]
He still has worries.
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[sighs]
[KUNOICHI] Is that all
the training for today?
[YUKIMURA]
Perhaps.
You seem a wee bit
distracted, my lord.
We've finally completed building
our family castle,
but I can't seem to get
the image of Nobuyuki's
worried face out of my mind.
Since Nobunaga went up
in flames like that,
everybody I've talked to
has been acting suspicious
and on edge.
It's because we're surrounded by
the Tokugawa, the Hojo,
and the Uesugi.
It seems it would be
easy to choke us out.
My brother works so hard
for our survival,
but sees there's
more to be done.
[YUKIMURA]
It's his nature.
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA yell]
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA yell, grunt]
[yells]
[NOBUYUKI yelps]
You've grown strong.
I'm impressed.
[YUKIMURA]
Thanks, brother. I'm trying.
My dream is to become
such a good warrior that I
can teach the Uesugi a lesson.
The Uesugi are pretty
strong, too, ya know.
Yeah, I know they are,
but they're not stronger
than Lord Takeda!
[NOBUYUKI]
Maybe not.
But do you remember when
the Imagawa and Hojo
cut off our supplies of salt?
The Uesugi made sure that
people of Takeda still
had access to it.
But they are our
enemy, aren't they?
[NOBUYUKI]
They are,
but they treat their enemies
with respect and humanity.
They don't take their grievances
out on the regular folk.
That kind of strength
is rare in the world.
Do you see, Yukimura?
Yeah! Definitely!
I know. That's it.
[KUNOICHI gasps] Lord Yukimura,
where are you going?
Always running off!
[YUKIMURA]
Brother.
[gasps]
What is it? Something wrong?
Hear me out.
I have made up my mind
to go to the Uesugi.
[NOBUYUKI]
What do you mean?
I love our home,
but as it is now,
we're surrounded on
all sides by our enemies.
We can never truly
be at ease here.
So what I'm proposing
is a defensive strategy
that would make the Uesugi
our allies instead.
If I offer myself up
to them as a hostage,
we should have some protection
on that front, at least.
A hostage?
You know what you're
saying, don't you?
[YUKIMURA]
I do.
[NOBUYUKI]
But you'll be putting your life
in our enemy's hands!
I'm aware of that.
I'll do it to
protect the Sanada.
Right now it's the best
option that we have.
[YUKIMURA]
We have our disputes,
but they're not monsters.
Even when we fought,
they made sure
some of our needs were met.
Yukimura...
[YUKIMURA]
I may be gone for a long time.
But my heart will remain
here with you, brother.
This is it. I shall
take my leave.
Best of luck. Farewell, brother.
[YUKIMURA]
Farewell.
Yukimura!
Though the cherry
blossoms may fall,
they bloom again
in spring every year.
Promise me
we'll see them bloom
in Ueda once more.
[gasps]
Together.
I promise!
Please stay strong.
[KUNOICHI] "This will be
the last time I see
these mountains." That's what
you're thinking, right?
I overheard the vow you swore
to your brother back there.
It means that you can't
do anything reckless.
Of course. I know that.
The castle you're going to
is pretty impressive.
Up on Mt Kasuga and
very well defended.
But that's not gonna stop me
from getting inside, ya know?
You can't be reckless either.
[KUNOICHI]
Lord Yukimura!
As your loyal ninja, have I
ever let you down before?
Can't think of a time.
Ya see?
[NARRATION] Once regarded
as the living embodiment
of the God of War,
Kenshin Uesugi
was taken down by illness.
Rule over Echigo and
command of his forces
has fallen to his
adopted son, Kagekatsu,
who cuts an intimidating figure.
Kanetsugu. Will you handle this?
Yes.
[KANETSUGU] Lord Kagekatsu
has taken a liking to you.
[gasps]
What makes you say that?
He's quiet,
but his heart is
overflowing with love.
It is?
My name is Kanetsugu Naoe.
[YUKIMURA]
There's so much fog here.
That's due to our
mountainous perch.
A demon?
It's clear.
I've wondered where you've been,
Mitsunari.
[gasps] He's one of
Lord Hideyoshi's
most trusted advisors, isn't he?
That's right. He is.
So what brings you
to Mt. Kasuga?
I believe that would be
none of your concern.
[KANETSUGU] He came all
the way here to see me.
No!
Yes you did!
[MITSUNARI]
I didn't!
Anyway.
Let me introduce you.
This young man--
[MITSUNARI]
Sanada, right?
I'm Yukimura Sanada.
I'd expected that the Sanada
would align with the Uesugi.
[YUKIMURA]
Oh. You did?
Your family was loyal
to the Takeda, after all.
After they fell, siding
with Uesugi makes sense.
That's because we
have an abundance
of salt and love!
Enough with the "love" okay?
Oh, come on.
What man can truly
have enough love?
[MITSUNARI] I've certainly had
enough of you touching me!
[KANETSUGU]
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
[MITSUNARI]
I'm not!
[KANETSUGU laughs]
These guys are really strange.
So, Tadakatsu.
I hear the Sanada have
made some sort of move?
Yes.
It seems as though the
second son, Yukimura,
has gone to the Uesugi.
[gasps]
We witnessed both
Sanada brothers in action
during the Battle of Nagashino.
Do you remember that, Ina?
Yes, my lord.
I must admit, I'm
extremely curious to know
just how strong those
brothers truly are.
[TOKUGAWA VASSAL A]
By the order of
Lord Ieyasu Tokugawa.
We request that the
region of Numata
be handed over to
the Hojo immediately.
What? Hand over Numata?
My lord has granted you
ten days to consider your reply.
You'd be wise not
to force his hand.
How can the Tokugawa be
so unreasonable, my lord?
During the Battle of Nagakute,
the Hojo forces sided with them.
This must be their payment.
But there's more.
[NOBUYUKI] A few years ago,
at the battle of Mikatagahara,
Lord Shingen's cavalry soundly
defeated Ieyasu's forces.
[RED WARRIORS yelling]
[NOBUYUKI]
With our soldiers in pursuit,
the Tokugawa's men
gave their lives
to allow their
lord's safe retreat.
[NOBUYUKI] Countless souls
were lost that day,
all given so Ieyasu
could live on.
But he fled without
ever looking back.
[NOBUYUKI]
Ieyasu Tokugawa.
Is he a villain who lacks
mercy and respect for life?
Or something else entirely?
A tanuki .
Yes. I see the resemblance.
You realize that
I'm not talking about
his appearance.
Of course. I was joking!
If I may ask.
What exactly do you mean
by calling him that?
I mean, I see him
as a shape shifter
and a trickster.
He's close to Lord
Hideyoshi only because
he's waiting for the
chance to steal from him.
[MITSUNARI]
Like a sly, conniving tanuki .
Yes.
He's taken Shinano, and he'll
surely want Echigo as well.
I wonder how the
Sanada will choose
to deal with him.
It'll be quite interesting.
Our family won control
of Numata in battle,
and we have governed
it well ever since.
There's no way
that we would ever
just hand it over to the Hojo.
Perhaps.
But the Tokugawa clearly
have the advantage
in this situation.
Ieyasu commands a massive army.
This is not a fight
the Sanada can win.
Please forgive his bluntness.
He can come off as a
little abrasive at times.
It's lead to a
few misunderstandings.
In truth,
his heart is
practically bursting
with love and compassion.
Don't go telling lies about me.
No lies here!
What did I say?
Tell me. What will
the Sanada do?
Those six coins you carry.
Do you plan to spend them?
I don't.
I plan on holding onto them
for another day, in fact.
Huh.
The Sanada are
not afraid of death,
but that does not mean
that we desire for it.
We must keep the soul
of our family alive.
So I will do just that.
[NOBUYUKI] We could give in
to the Tokugawa's demands
and no blood may be spilled.
But is justice not worth lives?
[LITTLE GIRL A]
It's Lord Nobuyuki!
I hope you're having
a good day, my lord!
Oh! It really is him.
[LITTLE GIRL A giggles]
[ALL laugh]
[NOBUYUKI] If we fight,
our people will suffer.
Their fields could be destroyed.
[NOBUYUKI]
However...
[whinnies]
[gasps]
[INA]
Halt! Who goes there?
[NOBUYUKI]
My apologies, ma'am.
I didn't realize
there was anyone here.
[gasps] The six coins. Sanada.
Nobuyuki Sanada.
And I think I've
seen you before.
You were with the
Tokugawa at Nagashino.
In fact, I was there.
My father's Tadakatsu
Honda. I'm Ina.
I've heard you haven't replied
to my lord's request
concerning Numata.
Why is that?
There are many
factors to consider.
Like our people.
I want them to remain safe.
If you honor
my lord's request,
then your people
will be very safe.
Or is that not
your true concern?
Would you give up control
of your land that easily?
[INA] If my family's
life depended on it.
I see. But if we do
as your lord requests
and give our land to the Hojo,
we risk losing our
family's soul instead.
Refuse and we'll have no
choice but to take it by force.
[gasps]
I am well aware of that.
But we can't lose what
gives our lives meaning.
The Sanada name
does not mean "surrender."
Ieyasu's thinking
on a grand scale.
You just don't see it.
And what do you mean by that?
[INA] My lord does not
fight solely for the sake
of the Tokugawa, or any
single house for that matter.
[NOBUYUKI]
So then, why does he fight?
What's his goal in all this?
[INA] That's as much as
I can say on his behalf.
If you really want
to know, submit,
and he'll likely
discuss it with you.
I'm sorry. But I can't do that.
Why not?
If Lord Ieyasu is thinking
on such "a grand scale,"
I'd love to discuss his plans,
but not be subjugated by them.
It's my duty to protect
the Sanada's soul.
So you can inform your lord
that we will not be
handing over Numata.
[INA]
Then the Sanada will perish.
[NOBUYUKI]
No, we won't.
We will never let that happen.
[INA]
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
My brother and I won't relent.
[hooves thumping]
[NOBUYUKI] Lord Ieyasu is
willing to sacrifice his men
for the sake of his ambition.
If they truly understood
the scale of it,
would they have so
willingly given their lives?
I cannot say.
[horse whinnies]
[YUKIMURA]
What?
The Tokugawa army is on
their way towards Ueda?
Yes. With over 7,000 soldiers.
Which is more than triple
the size of our forces.
Yah!
[KANETSUGU]
Yukimura! Wait!
Where are you going?
Back to Ueda.
You realize it's
a fool's errand?
I know that we're
greatly outnumbered.
But once Numata is
taken without a fight,
do you think Ieyasu
will stop there?
[MITSUNARI] If you leave,
Uesugi may choose to attack
the Sanada as well.
You're a hostage.
Wasn't the point
of that to be used
as a bargaining tool?
I must honor
the vow that I made
to my brother.
I said I would fight
alongside him to protect
the soul of the Sanada.
But still. You'll die!
No I won't!
I will live, fighting
to protect what I value
more than anything else.
Your mind's made up.
Then go.
I'm glad that I came
here and got to meet
both of you. And Lord Kagekatsu.
Go on. And I hope
we'll meet again.
We will.
Yah!
That man... is a fool.
You're wrong.
[MITSUNARI]
He's a fool beyond compare.
[YUKIMURA]
I'm coming, brother.
Just hold on until I get there.
[NOBUYUKI]
I knew they were a large force,
but seeing them is
something else entirely.
[RED WARRIOR E]
Indeed.
However,
numbers alone do
not equal supremacy.
The army we face is vast,
but so is our spirit!
We will not back down!
We'll defend our
home with honor!
[RED WARRIORS cheer]
Let's ride out!
[RED WARRIORS yell]
Matchlocks. Ready!
But, sir, don't you
think we should fire
on them in two separate waves?
No. I'm confident that
one will be enough.
[NOBUYUKI, RED WARRIORS yelling]
Fire away!
What?
[yelling]
[BLUE WARRIOR BB groans]
[BLUE WARRIORS yelp]
[RED WARRIOR D]
This is worth spending the night
down here!
[RED WARRIORS yell]
No! Get back in your ranks!
That's an order!
Mobilize left and right wings!
Crush the Sanada
forces between you!
Retreat, men!
Now! Retreat!
[NOBUYUKI]
Retreat, retreat!
They're running to the castle!
Strike them down!
[BLUE WARRIORS yelling]
On through the gate!
[RED WARRIOR E]
My lord.
That was a perfectly
timed retreat.
One wrong move and we
could have been annihilated.
That's the reason why
I had to give the order myself.
They followed us into
the tertiary ward.
Everything is going exactly
as you'd said it would.
Then let us end this fight.
Are our men in place?
[RED WARRIORS]
Yes, my lord!
[BLUE WARRIORS]
Heave-ho!
[BLUE WARRIORS cheer]
Now, forward march!
Break through that one, too!
Yes, perfect. Let them go!
[RED WARRIORS grunting]
[BLUE WARRIORS gasp]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[SOLDIER gasps, yelps]
[gasps]
[BLUE WARRIORS screaming]
[screams]
Fall back, men! Retreat!
The enemy is pulling out
of the secondary ward now.
That's good.
So is everything ready
in the tertiary ward?
Of course, my lord!
[BLUE WARRIORS screaming]
We can't get out this way.
Go back!
[groans]
[BLUE WARRIOR JJ]
Retreat!
[groans]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[NARRATION] The Tokugawa
forces tried in vain
to make their retreat
from the tertiary ward.
Every way out was blocked,
and Sanada soldiers
were there to see
them to the underworld.
[groans]
Most of the invaders
in the tertiary ward
have been slain, my lord.
A small number made it out,
and are fleeing to their camp.
Good.
Send a division
from the north gate!
Overwhelm all that remain!
[RED WARRIORS]
Yes, my lord!
[NOBUYUKI] Hopefully,
they can push through.
But if not...
I'll use my last breath
to slay Ieyasu myself.
Our vanguard force
is retreating, my lord!
But it appears that
most of our men were killed.
--[INA] What?
--[TADAKATSU gasps]
My lord.
Take it down!
Yes, my lord!
[NARRATION] Sanada infantry
engaged the Tokugawa
and forced them to
retreat to a precipice
over the Chikuma River.
Again, there was no escape.
Many more lost their
lives in the battle.
However...
[TADAKATSU] Let us ride!
And claim our victory!
[BLUE WARRIORS yelling]
[groans]
[RED WARRIORS groan]
[yelling]
[RED WARRIOR PP groans]
[NARRATION]
The arrival of Tadakatsu Honda
turned the tide of battle
in the Tokugawa's favor.
We've deployed a wave
of reinforcements, my lord,
but we can't seem to stall
the enemy's momentum.
[NOBUYUKI]
Then I have no choice.
[YUKIMURA]
Brother!
[gasps] That's Yukimura!
[yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[yells]
Come and face me!
Lord Yukimura's here!
I knew that he'd
come back to help us!
They may have a lot of soldiers,
but we're all true warriors!
Let's show them what that means!
Are you with me?
[RED WARRIORS cheer]
[NOBUYUKI]
There's our soul.
[YUKIMURA yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS yell]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[YUKIMURA yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[RED WARRIORS yell]
[BLUE WARRIOR PP groans]
[YUKIMURA grunting]
[BLUE WARRIOR TT panting]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
My lord, I'm here.
I've got this.
Go and help them
defend the main gate!
Right!
[SOLDIER C]
Yukimura Sanada!
I will have your head!
[yells]
[SOLDIER C groans]
[WARRIOR F] There is a new
enemy on the battlefield,
my lord! I'm afraid our
men may be overwhelmed.
A new enemy? How many?
In truth, my lady,
it's just one single man.
Only one soldier?
[BLUE WARRIOR F]
Yes, but it's the younger
Sanada brother, Yukimura.
[gasps]
My brother and I
will never relent.
This one man.
He's no match for Tadakatsu!
Hear my words!
We will take Ueda!
[yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[gasps]
[TADAKATSU]
You are a true warrior.
But now you test your mettle
against Tadakatsu Hoenda,
chief retainer of the Tokugawa!
And you against Yukimura Sanada!
[yells]
[TADAKATSU, YUKIMURA grunting]
Don't just stand there!
Our mission is to
take Ueda Castle!
[BLUE WARRIORS]
Sir!
[YUKIMURA gasps]
You will not reach the gate!
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
Mitsunari!
And Kanetsugu!
We've come here
to show our love
and solidarity with the Sanada!
Thank you!
[KANETSUGU]
Ha!
[MITSUNARI grunts]
[BLUE WARRIORS groaning]
[KANETSUGU yells]
[yelling]
[groans]
--[KUNOICHI] Ha!
--[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[NOBUYUKI]
Lord Ieyasu is on the move.
This may be my only
chance to take his head!
[NOBUYUKI] Killing him
will ensure our victory
and the future of the Sanada!
I must not falter!
[TADAKATSU grunts]
[grunts]
[YUKIMURA]
He's strong!
[TADAKATSU yells]
[grunts]
What stokes the fire
of your warrior's spirit?
[gasps]
I fight to realize
the grand ambition
of my lord! A vision
that we share!
Tell me! Why do you fight?
[gasps]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
For righteousness
against the ambitions
of one man!
A man who takes what is not his!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[YUKIMURA] The Sanada will
always fight against injustice!
We are warriors at heart,
and our will is ironclad.
[YUKIMURA]
As mighty as a tree that dares
to touch the heavens--
we will stand for righteousness!
That's the soul of the Sanada!
[TADAKATSU grunts]
[yells]
[grunts]
[YUKIMURA growls]
[gasps]
It's him!
Have no fear, my lord!
[RED WARRIORS groan]
[yells]
Ieyasu!
[BLUE WARRIORS, INA gasp]
We Sanada have
never wronged you!
Why do you want to take from us?
My actions are
dictated by the age
in which we live.
And your actions cry for rebuke!
You will not have our soul!
[IEYASU, NOBUYUKI grunting]
When this battle's
reached its end,
tell me, what is it
that awaits you?
[gasps]
Do you truly see an end
to the constant state
of warfare and
chaos of our time?
Do you?
Well, I have a clear vision
of the end of war
and that is why I fight!
The end?
This dark age of suffering
cannot be allowed
to continue!
[gasps]
And I'm willing to turn
my heart to stone
to see its demise!
My dream is for a land of peace.
How will you keep it?
I cannot do it alone.
I'll need the next
generation of leaders
to sustain it with me.
Leaders that embody
the type of strength
that is evident inside you.
[NOBUYUKI]
He truly has a grand vision.
A vision beyond compare.
Those flags!
Uesugi.
We have come
to render aid to our
allies the Sanada!
Lord Kagekatsu!
So they have chosen
to walk against the
currents of history.
[gasps]
Let's retreat.
Yes, my lord!
[horn sounds]
Farewell, Yukimura. Perhaps our
swords will cross yet again.
My only request is that you
survive this era of chaos.
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI]
A land of peace.
[RED WARRIOR TT]
The Tokugawa Army.
[RED WARRIOR UU]
They're pulling out.
[RED WARRIOR VV]
It's a full retreat!
We beat 'em.
Victory for the Sanada!
[RED WARRIORS cheering]
[KUNOICHI sighs]
[NARRATION]
So concludes the battle of Ueda,
which pitted the
small Sanada forces
against the massive
Tokugawa army.
Though outnumbered, the
defenders lost only 40 men,
the invaders, 1,300.
[YUKIMURA] You risked your lives
for us without hesitation.
You have my gratitude.
We were in the right
place at the right time.
So don't go reading
too much into it, okay?
My heart's bursting
for the Sanada.
Your clan knows love!
Love? What do you mean?
Standing up for the
weak and becoming
the strength that they need.
That spirit
illustrates immaculate
love and righteousness!
[gasps]
Now, friends.
Let us swear our oath
of devotion together!
Kanetsugu Naoe!
[YUKIMURA]
Yukimura Sanada!
Huh?
[MITSUNARI]
Mitsunari Ishida.
[IEYASU]
The Sanada.
They are warriors like
none I've encountered.
Indeed.
It's good to see you.
[MITSUNARI]
That must be Nobuyuki Sanada.
And you.
But why have you returned here?
I came back
to offer my assistance
to you, brother.
That defeats your
purpose as a hostage.
Part of your surrender
to the Uesugi,
was the promise you'd
remain with them.
Please forgive me, Nobuyuki.
But when I learned
Ueda was in danger,
I couldn't stand idly by.
I didn't fully consider
the pledge I'd made
to the Uesugi.
[NOBUYUKI]
It's in your nature to help.
I'm glad.
Thanks to you,
the Soul of the
Sanada will live on.
Yes, it will.
Promise me.
That you will fight alongside
me to ensure that it does.
Yes. I promise.
That's why we must survive.
[RED WARRIORS laughing]
[KANETSUGU chuckles]
[giggles]
[gasps]
Yukimura.
I want to see the
world that awaits us
once this dark age
of chaos is over.
Is there such a world?
One without chaos?
There is.
But I fear that the path
to reach it may be darker still.
[NARRATION] The land was
unified by Hideyoshi Toyotomi,
but his sudden death plunges
it into chaos once again.
This fracture leads
to the Bloody Battle
of Sekigahara, which rocks
the nation to its core.
The path to peace
would grow dark indeed.
Its only light from the
flames of war that burned
with a righteous fury.
Will the soul of the Sanada
survive this conflagration?