Preserve the Toyotomi.
Ensure that my legacy lives on.
Hideyori.
My... son.
Protect him. Please.
You're like my brother,
but you are not my master.
This is goodbye Mitsunari.
[MASANORI]
Kiyomasa.
We're gone!
[YUKIMURA]
Please, wait!
Master Kiyomasa!
Master Masanori!
We must remain stalwart.
And never lose heart.
For in our hands rests
the fate of countless lives.
May I ask why you are saying
such things to me, my lord?
[KANETSUGU] We three shall
fight together as one.
And share a righteous victory!
To preserve the
soul of the Sanada.
I shall wage war
on behalf of peace.
Fighting alongside the Tokugawa.
I shall wage war on
behalf of righteousness
and fight alongside Mitsunari.
[NOBUYUKI]
I knew this day would come.
[YUKIMURA] Be it victory
or death, I'm ready!
[BOTH shout]
[NARRATION]
The summer grasses
rise from where brave warriors
dared to dream a dream.
It was a dream
many warriors shared.
To unite this fractured
land under their banner.
Shingen Takeda.
Kenshin Uesugi.
Nobunaga Oda.
At last. The dream
that eluded so many
was within the grasp of
one extraordinary man.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi,
the emperor's Chief Advisor
and Grand Minister, was only one
step away from uniting the land.
All that blocked his path
was Sagami province.
Ujiyasu Hojo ruled this,
and the entire Kanto region
from his stronghold in Odawara.
Although a massive force
besieged the castle there,
Hojo remained firmly
ensconced within its walls.
The battle was
at a stalemate.
Seemingly without end.
[MASANORI]
It has been three months!
We wait much longer and
we'll be dead of old age!
We could have sat on
our asses at home!
There is a reason
we're all here, right?
So if you have
a plan, Mitsunari,
now would be a good
time to share it with us!
Calm down, Masanori.
I'm just wondering if there's
any kind of strategy
floating around in
that big head of his!
We should've taken this
castle from the very beginning!
[YOSHITSUGU]
Yes, that is correct.
And we could have
done just that,
had you not broken
formation and charged in.
[gasps] I'm not gonna take
all the blame for that day!
Anyway, that's in the past.
Aren't we talking about
what we're gonna do now?
[KANETSUGU]
Shouting won't win the war.
I think we should
trust Mitsunari.
After all, he is the
one put in charge here.
[MASANORI grunts]
Fine!
[BOTH gasp]
This castle seems
impossible to breach.
The bones of that
fortress are strong indeed,
but its heart is the
key to its resilience.
Hojo and his vassals are
willing to sacrifice their lives
for the sake of survival.
That resolve is their defense.
[YUKIMURA]
Defense by will alone.
[IEYASU] Master Mitsunari
has been laying siege
for three months now, my lord.
Ujiyasu Hojo has
proven his reputation
as a warrior is
well earned indeed.
He's known as "The Lion
of Sagaki" for good reason.
Let me take command, my lord.
The castle will be rubble
by this time tomorrow.
Naomasa. Be quiet.
[NAOMASA scoffs]
[laughs]
That quickly, eh?
While I do appreciate
your vigor,
Mitsunari will claim
victory in due time.
Right, Nene?
[NENE chuckles]
He will indeed, darling.
The boy's never let us down.
So. Let us discuss
what is to become
of the Kanto region
after Hojo's defeat.
I think that should fall under
the aegis of Master Ieyasu.
[gasps]
[HIDEYOSHI]
The land is vast,
and Hojo has controlled
it for many years.
A great man like
master Ieyasu
could maintain order in
the wake of his departure.
Agreed?
[IEYASU grunts]
It would be an honor, my lord.
[HIDEYOSHI grunts]
Now! The time for
unification is upon us!
[WARRIORS]
Yes, my lord!
[HIDETADA] Father.
I'm afraid that Hideyoshi
is merely trying to placate you
with that worthless offer!
Kanto may be
"vast" as he said,
but it's also completely
inconsequential!
We are Tokugawa!
Not some back-country daimyo!
Father!
[SOLDIER 1]
Delicious!
You know, your cooking
really isn't half-bad!
[UJIYASU] Ha! And here
I thought Hideyoshi's men
would pack up and leave
after a month or two.
They're patient little buggers!
Perhaps they still believe that
they can simply wait us out.
If they think they can outlast
Hojo in a test of endurance,
they're a bunch of damned fools.
That's putting it mildly.
Hideyoshi is definitely
hard-headed.
I'll give him credit,
but he'll never have Kanto.
[UJIYASU] That said. I feel
the endgame is soon to come.
[MITSUNARI]
The wait is over.
All forces,
prepare to engage.
We will crush Odawara
with a full on assault.
[BOTH gasp]
Master Mitsunari!
Why now? I mean...
What?!
It took you this long to come up
with "let's storm the castle"?!
Isn't that risky?
You do realize Odawara
won't go down easily.
[YOSHITSUGU]
Don't you see?
[BOTH gasp]
[YOSHITSUGU]
Since the siege began,
The smoke from cooking
fires has risen from
all over the castle at
this hour. Without fail.
[KIYOMASA gasps]
[YOSHITSUGU] But today
the plumes are sparse.
You're right! They must
be running out of food!
So you were just biding time
until their morale dropped?
Perhaps you should
consider letting us know
what's on your mind,
lest ours drop as well.
[NOBUYUKI]
Please, wait!
Such a massacre would
surely leave an indelible
stain on our image in Kanto.
Your point being?
What our lord seeks is
peace and unification.
Needless bloodshed is
contrary to that aim.
That's love.
Huh?!
It's soft. Our image
must be that of
decisiveness and
strength to rule.
The glorious
might of Toyotomi
shall be what unifies the land.
[KANETSUGU] Hm. Love that
spawns from admiration.
The soldiers may be fatigued,
but their fortifications
remain strong.
Both sides are sure to
suffer massive casualties.
[KIYOMASA]
He's right.
We spoke of the Hojo's bravery
in the face of crisis.
Careless actions could
spell our demise.
[MASANORI] So you
wanna wait even longer?
What? Do you think the castle's
just gonna fall down by itself?
[horse neighs]
[KUNOICHI grunts]
Yukimura, my lord.
[grunts]
That hurt, Tsukimaru.
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
Where are you going?
Are you leaving the camp?
I can no longer just sit idly by
when I know I can do something.
[shouts]
It's dangerous to go alone!
Lets follow him there!
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
[MASANORI]
This is ridiculous!
If we won't attack,
we might as well leave!
You know that's not
a viable option.
Perhaps we should send an
envoy to assess their position.
We will not negotiate with them!
[INA]
But...
[SAKON sighs]
Well, it would appear that
our envoy has sent himself.
[NOBUYUKI]
Hm?
[BOTH gasp]
[screams]
He left?
He must be extremely motivated
to talk things through.
[NOBUYUKI exhales]
Nobuyuki, my lord.
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
--[YUKIMURA shouts]
--[horse neighs]
[SOLDIER 2]
Look there! Do you see that?
The enemy!
Is he trying to raid
us all by himself?
Don't let him get closer!
Fire!
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[MALE SOLDIERS yell]
Damn. They have so
many matchlocks.
Well then...
[YUKIMURA shouts]
Fire!
What? Impossible!
I swear I did not come
here today to fight you!
[SOLDIER 3]
You can't be serious!
[SOLDIERS yell]
I know you can hear me, Hojo!
I respectfully challenge
you to a duel!
A duel?
Please accept. I implore you!
[KAI]
Are you really that stupid?
You're not getting
past me! Let's go!
[KAI grunts]
[shouts]
[grunts]
The six coins? You're a Sanada!
[YUKIMURA]
My fight is not with you,
I'm here to duel Ujiyasu Hojo
alone, so please back away!
[LADY HAYAKAWA grunts]
[KAI shouts]
[KUNOICHI grunts]
[LADY HAYAKAWA gasps]
You won't touch him!
Now that is very impressive.
How could one man get past
so many of my soldiers?
[gunshots, explosions]
I guess he means business.
[KAI grunting]
[LADY HAYAKAWA]
Kai!
[shouts]
[gasps, growls]
Not bad.
You've got guts, kid.
Careful, Father!
You must be Ujiyasu Hojo!
Yeah, the one and only.
I am Yukimura Sanada.
And I've come to
challenge you to a duel!
[UJIYASU chuckels] That seems
to be a good way to settle this
mess once and for all.
I accept, Yukimura Sanada!
Have at you!
[shouts]
[UJIYASU, YUKIMURA grunting]
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[BOTH grunting]
[KUNOICHI yelps]
[shouts]
[gasps]
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
[KAI grunts]
Nice work, Tsukimaru!
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
[shouts]
[YUKIMURA groans]
[UJIYASU]
Huh?
[shouts]
[UJIYASU grunts]
You actually made me
unsheathe my sword.
Good job, boy!
[grunts]
[KOTARO grunts]
You need to stay
out of this, Kotaro!
Was that Kotaro Fuma?
[YUKIMURA grunting]
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
Who are you?
Nobuyuki Sanada!
[UJIYASU] So both Sanada
brothers have come calling.
Yukimura. I have come here
to offer you my support.
Thank you. Now...
Let us unleash the
Soul of the Sanada!
[BOTH shout]
[shouts]
[BOTH grunting]
[UJIYASU] He burns with
such a righteous conviction.
If this is the kind of man
that fights for the Toyotomi,
maybe they're not all that bad.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
They're still as
tough as we thought!
We're in too far
to turn back now!
Yeah!
Forward. And do not falter!
[YUKIMURA, UJIYASU grunting]
Father no!
Yukimura!
[UJIYASU grunts]
[UJIYASU, YUKIMURA shouting]
Yukimura, my lord!
--[LADY HAYAKAWA gasps]
--He's been defeated!
[chuckles]
I guess that settles it.
[gasps]
[UJIYASU]
This war is officially over!
--[LADY HAYAKAWA whimpers]
--[KAI gasps]
[KOTARO laughs]
How unfortunate.
Hey, Sanadas. Listen.
[NOBUYUKI]
Yes, sir?
Do me a favor and
pass on this message
to the next ruler of Kanto.
Treat the people here right.
With honor and love.
Or he'll rue the
day he came here.
They are my family.
Every last one is precious.
Yes, sir.
I swear it.
[chuckles]
[HIDEYOSHI] At last this
fractured land is one!
I'm proud of you, Mitsunari.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
I've never seen you
look so despondent.
My command was ineffective.
Bogged down by doubt.
And plodding.
We claimed victory.
Due solely to Yukimura
Sanada's decisive actions.
[YUKIMURA gasps]
I, for one, commend
your patience, Mitsunari.
Waiting for the enemy to
weaken means fewer graves dug.
Violence does
not equal valor.
[MASANORI gasps]
Strength of mind. Sitting back
and watching that smoke
diminish over time
takes mental fortitude.
Now, that's leadership.
[gasps]
[HIDEYOSHI] People will say
what they will about you,
without thought.
But I understand you.
Perhaps better than anyone else.
That's love.
Thank you.
Without you, there would be
neither victory, nor peace.
Hideyoshi, my lord.
[NENE chuckles]
I'm proud of you.
That goes for all my boys.
I'm sorry. I should say,
"my strong young men."
--[NENE chuckles]
--[MASANORI groans]
[NENE]
You've all grown so much!
You've done well!
You've dreamed of a world
where everyone can smile,
haven't you, dear?
Indeed I have.
Let us be counted among them.
Drink and be merry!
[ALL]
Yes, my lord!
[NENE, HIDEYOSHI chuckle]
You always knew that
the day would come
when we would all live
in a peaceful world.
It's true.
Dear brother. Let us work
together to maintain that peace.
That is our family's purpose.
Our name shall be
synonymous with harmony.
Yes. It shall.
But that can only happen
if you stop making your
poor brother worry so much.
Right, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA gasps]
I mean, I...
Wow!
So now you're not only a wife,
but a bossy big sister as well?
--How cute!
--[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
Uh... Beg pardon?
It seems like only yesterday
you were the Sanada's
sworn enemy, and now you're
just one big happy family.
Yes! But I am not bossy!
[KUNOICHI giggles]
Look, I made her blush!
I have a strong feeling
Ina will regret marrying
into that silly little
clan before too long.
Careful not to
underestimate them.
Sanada's star is on the rise.
I don't know about that.
Master Ieyasu.
[IEYASU]
Yes, my lord.
Mitsunari.
[MITSUNARI]
Yes, my lord.
[HIDEYOSHI]
I consider the two of you
as pillars of this empire.
And I ask that you work
together to support it.
[BOTH]
Yes, my lord!
Nobuyuki Sanada and Yukimura!
[ALL gasp]
[YUKIMURA, NOBUYUKI]
Lord!
My praise!
You're the embodiment
of warriors for peace!
[BOTH chuckle]
[HIDEYOSHI] And I shall need
your strength to preserve it.
[BOTH]
Lord!
[BOTH chuckle]
My dream has come true.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors High School!
[TADAKATSU] Social studies
teacher: Tadakatsu Honda!
You must learn
this for the exam!
Unification!
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
[TADAKATSU]
Now pay attention!
Nobu--
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
[TADAKATSU]
Battle of Nagash--
Honno--
Get it right or you fail!
[YUKIMURA, KUNOICHI]
Huh?
[NARRATION] Seeds of mistrust
and resentment have been sown
amongst the summer grasses.
Fed by blood, they grow,
tearing apart the
strongest of bonds.
Will they flower into
total dissolution?
Next episode:
"Separation at Inubushi."