[NARRATION] The country
is broken, yet mountains
and rivers remain.
Spring comes to the castle,
and the grass is green again.
Poisoned by blood,
Hideyoshi's dream
of unity now rests
on its own deathbed.
The winds of destiny blow,
carrying both seeds
of peace and war.
Which will sprout from this
ground, fed by fallen bodies?
Once again,
Nobuyuki was sent out
as the Tokugawa envoy.
This time to Osaka to meet
with Hideyori and deliver
the message that Hidetada
was to be the next Shogun.
On Mt. Kudo,
Yukimura was challenged
by Naomasa, but before
they could duel,
the village was set
ablaze by Kotaro Fuma.
By protecting the people there,
Yukimura realized his purpose:
To be a righteous warrior.
[YUKIMURA]
Yah! Hah!
Yah!
[chirps]
[BLUE SOLDIER 8A]
Halt at once, Yukimura Sanada!
[grunts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS gasp]
Kill him now!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelling]
So how do you guys
like my pepper bomb?
It's homemade!
[YUKIMURA]
Master Mitsunari. I promise,
I will uphold the oath
I swore with you.
[IEYASU]
Then... Naomasa perished.
[TADAKATSU]
Yes, my lord.
He died with honor,
as a warrior fighting
for the Tokugawa Shogunate.
Rest his soul.
[TADAKATSU] It seems
Yukimura has rediscovered
his warrior's spirit.
Yes.
The wheels of fate are set
in motion, albeit early.
And the time that
you spoke about
has come to pass.
Indeed.
For peace to truly prosper,
we must first be sure
to cut away all
of the dead wood.
Dead wood?
[MALE VASSAL 8A]
I beg your pardon, my lord.
What is it?
[VASSAL 8A] Master Kato
and Master Fukushima.
[KIYOMASA]
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to Osaka.
I can't pretend what I'm
doing now honors the pledge
I made to preserve the Toyotomi.
I hear ya.
But are you really sure that
Lord Hideyori will forgive us?
I will beg for his forgiveness!
If I have to bloody my head
against the ground groveling,
so be it!
You're right.
Let's go! Off to Osaka!
I see.
[HIDEYORI] Please go back
and tell your master.
That I agree to meet with him.
--[VASSALS gasp]
--[VASSAL 7C] My lord!
Are you certain?
If he truly desires
to confer with me
about the future of our nation,
then I must honor that request.
Yes.
We have many things to discuss,
Ieyasu and I.
I look forward to it.
[NOBUYUKI]
Lady Kai was right.
I still have no idea
who Hideyori really is
or what he's planning.
[gasps]
This road is dangerous, ya know?
Give up your money and
you'll keep your life.
[BANDITS cackle]
[NOBUYUKI]
These are no ordinary bandits.
More like actors trying
to play the part.
[NOBUYUKI] If I pay you,
you'll let me pass?
[laughs] Yeah, that's
how this works!
Now, men! Let's cut him down!
[BANDITS yell]
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
After him!
[KEIJI] What the hell's
with all the noise?
[BANDITS gasping]
[KEIJI] Can't you see
I'm tryin' to take a nap?
Why should we care? Who are you?
[KEIJI]
I could tell ya.
But then...
I'd have to kill ya.
You stay outta this.
Just go back to your nap, okay?
Who could sleep with
all this excitement
goin' on around 'em?
I'm sure Lord Hideyori
would be too interested
to close his eyes.
[gasps] What's he
got to do with this?
We're just bandits on the road.
It's pretty damn obvious
that you're Toyotomi vassals
pretending to be outlaws.
I mean, seriously.
Just look at those fancy
swords you got there.
The outfits are close,
but those katanas
just give it all away.
[sputters]
[KEIJI] Do you think
Lord Hideyori wants his men
harassing people on
the road like this?
If word were to get out,
that would not be good for you.
Enough! Shut your mouth!
Run along home and we'll forget
that the whole thing
ever happened. Okay?
[BANDITS whimpering]
[KEIJI] One of you
tough guys gonna make me
"shut my mouth?"
[BANDIT 8A growls]
[KEIJI]
'Cause I'd love to see you try.
[grunts]
You're goin' down!
[BANDIT 8A yells]
[BANDIT 8A gasps]
I think you need to cool off!
In ya go!
[KEIJI]
Who's next?
[BANDITS whimper]
[BANDITS yell]
[NOBUYUKI]
Thank you.
No sweat. That was kinda fun.
I know you.
You're Master
Keiji Maeda, right?
[KEIJI] That's correct,
my friend. Good job.
I guess my
reputation precedes me.
[laughs]
[NARRATION] Keiji is the adopted
nephew of Toshiie Maeda,
who was a confidant
and trusted advisor
to Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
Keiji left the Maeda household
to become a Ronin in Kyoto.
A samurai with no
master but himself.
And I think I know who you are.
Six coins at the ready.
Nobuyuki Sanada.
[KAI] Why did you agree
to meet with Ieyasu?
I don't understand.
You are well aware
that many of our vassals
are chomping at the bit
to go to war with the Tokugawa.
And that is precisely
why I believe
it is imperative that we try
to resolve our differences
before the fighting begins anew.
[VASSAL 7B]
This is unforgivable!
[VASSAL 7A]
We cannot allow him to strip you
of your birthright!
So, in other words,
this is your advice:
That we should prepare for war.
Personally, I have
no thirst for bloodshed.
But still.
I know that our
nation cannot live
in a house divided much longer.
Two horses pulling us
in two directions.
To take us down
the road of peace,
we have to choose
which one to follow.
[TADAKATSU] I'm certain that
all of you have heard by now.
Yukimura Sanada has
broken his exile
and escaped from Mount Kudo.
What's more,
Kiyomasa Kato and
Masanori Fukushima
have left the castle here
in Edo to go to Osaka.
Takatora Todo, I order you
to locate and
eliminate Yukimura.
Lord.
Masamune Date.
You will take down
Kato and Fukushima.
Lord.
Forgive me, my lord.
But I would like
to make a request.
Allow me to hunt
down the deserters.
With all due respect.
I would prefer to find Yukimura
and defeat him instead.
Are you refusing to follow
Lord Ieyasu's orders?
[TAKATORA]
No, sir, I am not. But...
Those two have pledged
allegiance to the Toyotomi.
And as a former vassal myself,
I must prove my loyalty.
As for me: I am a warrior.
The chance to fight
a man like Yukimura,
who has defeated whole armies
singlehandedly, is irresistible.
Denied.
My lord--
[IEYASU] No! Accept your
missions, and leave at once.
Is that clear?
[TADAKATSU]
Tell me, my lord.
Why did you not allow them
to change their missions?
It was because I
understand all too well
the motivations behind
why they requested
that I switch their
initial assignments.
They stem from an
unslakable thirst for blood
and vengeance that must
not be allowed to continue
in the era of peace
we're about to enter.
It has no place.
Samurai must learn how
to exist in this new world
that decries war and
strives for harmony.
Adaptation is the
key to the survival
of any species,
including warriors.
To move forward,
we must unburden ourselves
of these bloody desires.
So are you saying
we must leave behind
our fighting spirit?
I am.
And that is exactly the reason
why I am denying them
the battles they believe
will satisfy them.
What then?
If samurai abandon fighting,
what will they do instead?
As I said, they'll adapt.
They've all honed very
useful skills over the years:
The ability to read the flow
of battle, strategize,
and command troops
must now be applied
to governing this nation.
But if they give in to
their violent tendencies,
peace will have no chance,
and we may never
crawl out of the chaos of war.
It is a lofty
and difficult goal.
[IEYASU]
Hm. Indeed it is.
Pretty relaxing, don't ya think?
Very much.
Look there.
Even in the most gentle
of streams, there can still
be pockets of turbulence.
What a metaphor, huh?
[NOBUYUKI]
Indeed.
If those bandits were
in fact Toyotomi vassals,
it shows that there
are those among them
ready to resort to violence.
They knew I was merely
the Tokugawa's messenger,
and still they attacked.
[KEIJI] It's obvious why
they feel that way.
Lord Hideyoshi was the
man who originally united
the nation under one banner,
but after the battle
between the Eastern
and Western armies,
Tokugawa is running the show.
All the Toyotomi are doing
is trying to save face.
Perhaps. But still.
Oh, yeah. I heard
about your brother.
[KEIJI] He was exiled.
But now he's escaped.
I don't know the
details, but apparently,
there was some kinda
trouble up there.
[NOBUYUKI]
Yukimura has broken his exile?
He must be on his way to Osaka.
Right now! I can't let
him reach the castle!
Hold on!
He's not even gonna say goodbye?
Guess things are about
to get really wild.
[horse whinnies]
[NOBUYUKI]
Ha!
I must stop him!
We better watch out.
Yes, I'm aware.
Keep your eyes and
ears open, you hear?
Yes, sir!
What was that?
Here they come!
Ready, men.
Let's go!
Fire away!
[groans]
Damnit, no!
I knew they'd try to keep us
from getting to Osaka!
[groans]
[KIYOMASA growls]
[KIYOMASA grunts]
Damn fools. Now you're all mine!
[NOBUYUKI] I beg you.
Please let me help you.
I can find Yukimura!
Not a chance.
Your bond with him
is too strong.
You two are sure to join
forces and fight against us.
That isn't true! I swear--
Silence! Now,
arrest this traitor!
[BLUE SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[gasps] Takatora! This is wrong!
[TAKATORA] You will wait here,
while I kill your brother.
Come men! We're riding out!
[BLUE SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MASAMUNE yells]
[GOLD SOLDIERS groan]
One-eyed rat!
Silence!
I've always been loyal
to the Tokugawa!
But the nation
belongs to Toyotomi!
That may have been the case,
but those days are over!
[KUNOICHI] This water is
so cold and refreshing!
We're almost to Osaka, right?
Yes.
[KUNOICHI gasps]
Master Takatora.
Yukimura Sanada!
By the order of Lord Ieyasu,
I've come...
...to strike you down!
[gasps]
Now, fire!
[yells]
--[KUNOICHI grunts]
--[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelp]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
[yelling]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
--[YUKIMURA grunting]
--[BLUE SOLDIERS groaning]
[squeaks]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelping]
No! There're too many!
--[explosion]
--[BLUE SOLDIERS yelling]
[gasps]
[BLUE SOLDIERS screaming]
[YUKIMURA, KUNOICHI gasp]
[KEIJI yelling]
You mind if I cut in?
You look like you
could use a hand!
I know that flashy
outfit! It's him!
Master Keiji Maeda?
Seems like I'm more
famous than I ever
imagined I'd be!
This is not your fight!
I know you were
merely following orders.
Forgive me.
But still, I must stop Yukimura.
[yelling]
[YUKIMURA grunting]
[yells]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
[YUKIMURA, TAKATORA grunting]
[yells]
[YUKIMURA growls, yells]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelling]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
Stop him! Right now!
[grunts] Too late for that!
[yells]
[BLUE SOLDIER 8C]
A wall!
[yells]
[TAKATORA growls]
Damn them.
You just saved
my life back there.
Glad to be of help!
[gasps]
Brother.
I've found you.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[yells]
[KOJURO, MASANORI grunting]
Damn. I think this is it!
[BOTH gasp]
What's this?
What's going on?
[gasps]
It's Lady Nene!
Let's go!
[BOTH]
Follow us!
Bastards!
[KIYOMASA, MASANORI]
Please forgive me, my lady!
For what?
We broke our vow.
We promised we'd
protect the Toyotomi,
fight with Mitsunari.
But at the battle of Sekigahara,
we met as enemies.
[NENE]
Don't worry yourself.
Each one of you boys
was just acting on
what you believed
in your hearts to be
the right thing to do.
So no promises were broken.
Lady Nene!
That was quite
a scene back there.
Why all the fighting?
Because we left Edo castle
and the Tokugawa to go to Osaka
and serve Lord Hideyori,
and they were trying to stop us.
I knew you were good boys.
I'm so proud of you.
Now go and help the Toyotomi.
Yes, my lady.
[NOBUYUKI] Yukimura. Why did
you leave Mount Kudo?
[YUKIMURA]
Because it was time.
I took your advice,
and finally found the answer
I had been searching for.
Do you remember what
you said to me that day,
before I left for exile?
[NOBUYUKI]
I can't.
You are the only one
with that answer.
Look inside yourself,
and discover what that is.
The heart of a righteous warrior
still pounds inside of my chest.
As long as I live,
I'll fight for what's right.
So, you're going to Osaka.
[YUKIMURA]
Yes.
And you will never serve
the Tokugawa Shogunate
alongside me.
[YUKIMURA] I swore an oath
with Master Mitsunari
to fight for what I believe in.
He's gone, but my vow remains.
As does my belief
in the Toyotomi.
[NOBUYUKI]
I see.
And I can't change your mind.
You had once said to me
that you wanted to be
the trunk that supports
the Sanada house.
I want to be the warrior
who preserves the Sanada Spirit.
It's a shame that the two of us
cannot come together as one.
[YUKIMURA] But that is
the sad fact we face.
From this moment forward,
I am no longer your brother.
Understood.
And if we're fated to
meet again in battle...
If that day comes...
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA]
I will not back down.
[YUKIMURA]
This is farewell.
Best of luck.
[NARRATION] The parting
of these two brothers
paralleled the conflict
between the two houses
that vied for control
of the nation itself.
War would tear the
land asunder yet again.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
I hear the bean paste buns
are the best in Japan!
[gasps]
It's mine!
No, it's mine!
[MOTOCHIKA]
Hm.
[gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
It's not fair!
I was dreaming about
those sweet bean buns.
[NARRATION] Osaka castle
houses what remains
of the Toyotomi.
Their banner once flew over
warriors of every stripe.
Now it waves over only
those who walk against
the current of destiny,
grasping for control.
[NARRATION]
Next episode: "Winds of Osaka."