[NARRATION]
The summer grasses
rise from where brave warriors
dared to dream a dream.
It was a dream many
warriors shared.
To unite this fractured
land under their banner.
Shingen Takeda.
Kenshin Uesugi.
Nobunaga Oda.
But now, one warrior has made
that elusive dream a reality.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
It would seem that he,
has sown peace in the land
by the tip of his spear.
However...
After his sudden passing,
chaos began to grow again.
Threatening to
disrupt the balance
so many others died to achieve.
Ieyasu Tokugawa
seized this opportunity
to expand his influence.
Mitsunari Ishida vowed to
halt his quest for power.
The two met on the
field at Sekigahara.
The outcome of this battle would
determine who holds the reigns
on the land once and for all.
Having sworn an oath of
righteousness and solidarity
with Mitsunari, Kanetsugu Naoe
attempted to lead Uesugi's
forces and bring Tokugawa's
march to a halt.
They were met by The One-Eyed
Dragon, Masamune Date.
He and his men saw to
it that the Uesugi army
did not reach Sekigahara.
With Hidetada's failed
siege on Ueda castle
costing Tokugawa
soldiers and arms,
fortune appeared to
smile on Mitsunari.
Many things shift with the
winds of war, however.
Betrayal and soft-hearted
decisions wreaked havoc
on the Western Army,
and in the end,
Mitsunari lost his life
on the battlefield.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
He was defeated? This can't be!
[KANETSUGU sobs]
We must fall back.
I shall lead the rear guard.
Hurry, my lord!
Understood.
[KANETSUGU grunts]
[KANETSUGU]
You kept your oath.
[NARRATION]
Once the Eastern Army
claimed their bloody victory,
Nobuyuki returned to the castle
in Ueda to disarm his brother.
Yukimura was held in
confinement there.
His home, now his prison.
[KUNOICHI]
Lord Yukimura.
Look, I found these in
the hills out back.
I've always loved chestnuts!
Remember how we used to cook
these over a nice open flame?
They'd pop and I got
burned so many times.
My reflexes are much better now.
[KUNOICHI, TSUKIMARU giggles]
So, uh... I know!
I'll steam 'em and
serve 'em with rice!
That'll be delicious.
Don't you think?
[YUKIMURA]
Hm...
Okay! I'll be back with dinner.
[YUKIMURA] You should
give them to Tsukimaru.
[KUNOICHI]
Huh?
Can you eat all
those by yourself?
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
[YUKIMURA]
I've no need for food.
[KUNOICHI]
Uh?
[YUKIMURA] Tokugawa will
ask I pay the ultimate price.
You sure?
As my final act of kindness,
I shall grant you your freedom.
[KUNOICHI]
No! Forgive me, my lord,
but I can't accept that!
I swore I would be
forever at your side!
[YUKIMURA] I'll need no
servants in the afterlife.
[KUNOICHI]
My lord.
If you die, I'm more than
willing to perish alongside you!
[YUKIMURA]
No.
[KUNOICHI]
Huh?
My life will end soon.
You must begin yours!
To live as you see fit.
Following your own life's path.
That's all I ask.
No! I can't!
[VASSAL 1] What shall
become of Yukimura Sanada?
[COUNCIL murmurs]
There's only one answer!
Justice demands he
become food for worms!
Because of his
barbaric interference,
we nearly lost the war!
No Sanada can be trusted!
[TADAKATSU]
On the contrary, my lord.
[HIDETADA gasps]
I have it on good authority
that the siege of Ueda
was a rogue decision made
solely by Lord Hidetada.
[HIDETADA gasps]
[TADAKATSU]
He squandered resources
and the lives of hundreds of
men on a useless skirmish.
And as a result of
this foolishness,
he arrived late to the battle.
No! I won't stand for this!
Yukimura was in
league with Mitsunari
and tried to prevent us from
crossing the mountain pass!
[INA]
That's not true.
We pleaded with him
to honor the mission
that you'd entrusted to us.
But he insisted on
laying siege to Ueda!
That unprovoked attack is
why our mission failed!
Yukimura did not bring
an army to the fields
of Sekigahara to do battle,
he was merely defending
his own castle.
Reason would dictate that had
nothing to do with Mitsunari.
[TAKATORA]
Is that so?
Perhaps we should
listen to reason.
The fact is, despite being
outnumbered ten to one,
Yukimura was still able to send
an army running for their lives.
We can't allow him to live.
He's too dangerous.
Agreed.
Exactly my point!
But we would have
surely taken the castle,
were it not for the
traitorous rat in our ranks!
[MASANORI]
Huh?
Who do you mean, my lord?
[HIDETADA]
It was Sanada!
He and his brother
were working together!
He told him our plans and helped
him set ambushes on our men!
How can you betray him?
Although you regarded
him with contempt,
he saved your life on
more than one occasion!
[TADAKATSU] My lord, I ask you
treat Yukimura magnanimously.
With warrior's grace.
Spare his life!
[INA]
I beg you, my lord!
[NOBUYUKI exhales]
Wait! They're lying!
Don't fall prey
to their deception!
Nobuyuki.
Will you share your
thoughts on this matter?
[NOBUYUKI]
My lord.
Though it pains
me to say this,
his life is forfeit.
[IEYASU]
I understand.
[NENE]
I miss you, my sweet monkey.
But I suppose you have
a lot of company now.
To think that so
many have joined you
so soon after
you've passed over.
I know that's not what
you were hoping for.
And it leaves me
feeling more lonely.
[gasps] I can't believe it.
[gasps]
[NENE]
I can't believe it.
Poor Mitsunari.
[VASSAL 2]
Master Mitsunari, was defeated?
[VILLAGERS murmur]
[VASSAL 3] What will become of
us who are loyal to Toyotomi?
They'll kill us!
Burn us to the ground!
[MAIDS]
My lady! My lady!
Something wrong?
What's all the fuss about?
We've been hearing some very
troubling rumors, my lady.
They're saying Tokugawa
will attack us any day now!
That's nothing but idle chatter.
And even if that
scenario were to happen,
Osaka castle won't fall to
such a blowhard like Ieyasu.
But still...
And he wouldn't dare
challenge Lord Hideyori.
So calm your fears.
[MAIDS]
Yes ma'am.
[NARRATION] Kai, the woman
who once crossed blades
with Yukimura in Odawara,
now calls Osaka castle her home.
She is a fearsome warrior
faithful to the Toyotomi.
I thought that I
might find you here.
Lord Hideyori.
My lady, Kai.
Is there a problem?
[NARRATION]
His father no longer alive,
Hideyori claimed his birthright
and assumed rule
over the Toyotomi.
There is much uneasy talk
amongst your vassals.
Perhaps they need to hear
your calm and reassuring voice
to relieve their tensions.
My voice?
What's wrong?
You know Mitsunari
was defeated.
The people fear that Tokugawa
has his sights on
our house next?
They do. Should they my lord?
[HIDEYORI] Tokugawa swore
fealty to the house of Toyotomi.
Nothing will change
but the seasons.
The chrysanthemums
all lose their blooms.
The sky darkens and
the ground grows cold.
[KAI]
What?
[HIDEYORI chuckles]
[giggles]
[KAI] Wow, he must have
his father's charm.
[NOBUYUKI] I will read
the sentence aloud.
Yukimura Sanada,
you shall be exiled to
the Mount Koya region.
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI] Confined indefinitely
to Mount Kudo.
[NARRATION] Yukimura's life may
have been spared by Tokugawa,
but it was no longer his own.
This punishment, known as
"Chikkyo," or house arrest,
was a way to isolate
and render an insubordinate
samurai powerless.
Chikkyo?
That's the sentence? Not death?
[YUKIMURA] Why would
he allow me to live?
I sided with his enemy!
I threatened the life
of his favorite son!
I was willing to die in my
fight against the Tokugawa
and I still am!
Wait... Tell the truth.
Brother, did you beg
forgiveness on my behalf?
You have a right to know.
I did not.
Though it pains me say this,
his life is forfeit.
I understand.
Sanada will be sentenced...
[HIDETADA chuckles]
...to exile in Mount Koya.
[VASSALS murmur]
[ALL gasp]
Seriously?
[INA gasps]
[NOBUYUKI gasps]
No... Why?
Father, are you mad?
His very existence is a
threat to the Tokugawa--
[IEYASU]
Silence!
[gasps]
You brought shame
upon our house!
You were to join us
on the battlefield!
But your frivolous distraction
nearly cost us the war!
[HIDETADA]
Father, please!
Hidetada.
I shall sentence you to
confinement as well!
But father, have mercy!
That's mercy!
[HIDETADA]
Yes, my lord.
And Nobuyuki.
I order you to deliver
Yukimura's sentence
to him personally.
[NOBUYUKI]
Yes, my lord.
So you see.
It was Lord Ieyasu's charity and
honor that spared your life,
not I.
[YUKIMURA]
Honor?
[YUKIMURA gasps]
How can you speak of honor
when I've had mine taken?
Am I supposed to spend my
days beholden to his pity?
[YUKIMURA grunts]
A warrior like me walks his
path staring death in the face,
not living in shame!
You know that!
Yes, I do.
What will I say when
we meet again?
When I see Master Mitsunari
in the afterlife?
I'll commit seppuku to save
face if that's the only way!
[NOBUYUKI]
You fool!
[gasps]
Look, you can believe life
will be nothing but shame,
if that's what you choose.
However, you can also believe
you live for a reason.
And what reason would that be?
Tell me!
[NOBUYUKI]
I can't.
You are the only one
with that answer.
Look inside yourself and
discover what that is.
From now on, I will guard
both our family castles.
I will ensure the
Sanada's survival.
That's what I'm living for.
You will find your next purpose
in this life, I know it.
And your survival means
that I have fulfilled
the purpose given me.
I accept, brother.
Tomorrow you will
travel to Mount Koya.
And you will remain
there indefinitely.
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[YUKIMURA]
How can I live like that?
After losing who I am?
[KUNOICHI]
You said it to me yourself.
By living as you see fit
and following your own path.
That's all you have to do.
Live the life you want
to live from here on.
But please... promise that
you'll cherish it.
I beg you.
This is our new home.
Yes. It is.
[NOBUYUKI]
We'll build our castle here.
[INA]
There you are.
I'm happy that your dear
brother's life was spared.
Truly.
[NOBUYUKI]
I'm not heartless.
[INA]
No.
But I advised that my
brother be put to death.
[INA chuckles]
I know that is not what
you believe in your heart.
Advocating mercy in this case
would make you appear soft
in front of the Tokugawa.
I understand the
factors in play.
You did it to save your family.
Remember what you
said to me that night?
"Branches will fall, but no tree
survives without its trunk."
That's what you
are for the Sanada.
[NOBUYUKI]
But I did not follow my heart.
I wanted to put my own
life at stake to save his.
In the end, I gave
in to political pressure.
I did what I believed
would end the war.
I couldn't risk having
my loyalty questioned.
I chose to serve Lord Ieyasu,
no matter what the cost.
[NOBUYUKI] But those words
will resonate in my mind
for as long as I live.
I'm a fool.
A fool who'd sacrifice
his own brother.
That's not true.
You're an honorable man.
I can't believe he was
merely sent to exile.
[grunts]
Curse this wound.
It's insignificant.
I let it keep me
from the sentencing.
I would have demanded his head.
[MASANORI]
You know what?
[KIYOMASA]
Hm?
I'm actually kinda relieved
about what happened.
You mean Yukimura's sentencing?
[MASANORI]
Yeah.
I dunno, he's...
He's just really solid.
He does whatever
he thinks is right
no matter what the cost may be.
To be honest with ya,
we need more guys like him.
[TADAKATSU] I must
confess my surprise, my lord.
I didn't expect you
to spare his life.
[IEYASU]
Tell me.
Why did you advocate
against death for him?
Because my daughter is
his older brother's wife.
Nobuyuki has been
a devoted husband.
I didn't wish to bring more
unhappiness to the family.
[TADAKATSU]
That, and...
Honestly, I'd like to
face Yukimura again
in battle one day.
I remember when he and I
clashed for the first time.
My blood was boiling
from the intensity.
It had been an eternity
since fighting gave me
that kind of feeling.
[IEYASU] Doubtless, there will
be more fighting to come.
[gasps]
To create this world of
peace to which we aspire,
we must first destroy the
world of warfare.
You mean...
We must destroy the
world as it is now?
[IEYASU]
I do.
To end this era of conflict
with an act so univocal,
no one could deny
its termination.
That requires a sacrifice.
One lone death to save
innumerable lives.
This man needs to be
a valiant warrior.
We must exhibit him as
samurai among samurai
and cut him down for all to see.
The exile is just to bide
time until his death.
[IEYASU] We all must pay a
price for peace in this world.
[HIDETADA shouts]
It's not fair!
I don't deserve to be treated
like some common criminal!
They did this to me!
Those vile Sanadas
were never to be trusted!
They... made a fool of me!
[KOTARO]
Then, they must be eliminated.
[HIDETADA gasps]
[yelps]
[KOTARO]
Cherish your hatred.
[HIDETADA gasps]
[KOTARO]
Imagine your vengeance.
I can make your blood-soaked
dreams a murderous reality.
[KOTARO laughs]
[gasps]
Beloved brother and sister.
I bid you farewell.
These dark days will soon pass.
I know.
Still, the cherry
blossoms bloom and fall.
Keep our home safe.
Godspeed brother.
[SOLDIER 1]
Lord Yukimura! Please!
Let me go with you!
[VASSAL 4] Me too!
I will follow you there!
[SOLDIER 1]
I beg you!
[SOLDIER 2]
Lord Yukimura!
You will stay!
But, my lord!
We all swore an oath of
eternal loyalty to you!
That's true!
[VASSAL 5]
I beseech you my lord!
Listen well, all of you.
From this moment on, my brother
Nobuyuki will be lord of Ueda.
[VASSALS chatter]
I leave you with
one final order.
You all must swear that
you'll remain in Ueda
and serve my brother.
Defend the Sanada.
[VASSAL 6]
But we serve you!
My lord!
Do you understand?
[ALL]
Yes! My lord!
I shall keep you
all in my thoughts.
[shouts]
[KUNOICHI] I swore I would
never leave your side, my lord.
Wherever you go,
I shall be your shadow.
[squeaks]
[INA]
Please, watch over him.
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
Yukimura!
[NARRATION]
Not long after this,
emperor Go-Yozei appointed
Ieyasu to Seii Taishogun,
the "great unifying leader."
A title paid for by the
blood of warriors.
Ieyasu.
Well played, indeed.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
My sweet sister-in-law
made me lunch today.
I hope it's something good!
[BOTH gasp]
She loves you!
Aw man. She must've
given me the wrong lunch!
What did my sweet
Ina pack for me?
[NOBUYKUI chuckles]
[NARRATION] Aizu and
Mount Kudo are the stages
for this next act.
Nobuyuki hurries
towards Uesugi, now his enemy.
Yukimura searches for a life
beyond the warrior's calling.
Once again, the brothers
must reshape their destiny.
Next episode:
"Prison of the heart."