[NARRATOR]
The country is broken,
yet mountains and rivers remain.
Spring comes to the castle,
and the grass is green again.
Poisoned by blood,
Hideyoshi's dream of unity
now rests on its own deathbed.
The winds of destiny blow,
carrying both seeds
of peace and war.
Which will sprout from this
ground, fed by fallen bodies?
Not satisfied with blood alone,
Tokugawa demands more from
those who sided with his enemy.
The Uesugi, a powerful
Toyotomi ally,
were to be stripped of most
of their wealth and their land.
Rather than suffer
this humiliation,
they were willing to give
their lives for honor.
However, Nobuyuki
again made the point
that survival was paramount,
and the Uesugi agreed
to Tokugawa's terms.
Meanwhile Yukimura
was living in exile,
his warrior's path cut off
by the Shogunate.
Seemingly devoid of purpose,
he spent his days
engaged in idle reflection.
When offered Mitsunari's
keepsake, he refused.
A symbolic act of
turning away from
the life of violence
and warfare.
An encounter with Suzu,
a child of the village,
lifted his spirits, somewhat.
Although he was known
as a "bad man,"
she was still willing to
share food with him.
Unfortunately, she fell ill.
Yukimura broke through
the guards and rushed her
to a doctor in a village
at the mountain's base,
directly violating the
terms of his exile.
As a result, his punishment
was intensified.
He now found himself
under house arrest,
unable to leave the confines
of his modest dwelling.
[NARRATOR] Regarded as a mad
dog by the Tokugawa Shogunate,
Yukimura was penned
up in Mount Kudo.
That selfless gesture seen
as a threatening outburst,
his leash was
tightened even further.
Denied interaction with
the world around him,
all he could do now
was simply exist.
What's wrong?
Why can't Yukimura come
out and play with me?
[SUZU'S MOTHER] I haven't even
had the chance to thank him yet.
I feel this is all my fault.
You never asked him
to do anything.
[KUNOICHI]
He can't change who he is.
Wait up, Tsukimaru!
[KUNOICHI]
Please, come back!
Ina's here!
[INA] Although I'm happy
the girl was saved,
that was still a very reckless
thing for him to do.
If given the chance,
I'm sure he would make the
same decision over again.
[INA] There's no doubt about it,
but I'm afraid his punishment
would be far more
severe the next time.
Not just house arrest.
Indeed, he may be forced
to pay the ultimate price.
I know.
Once we reach the peace
we've all been striving for,
I believe he'll be forgiven.
But to see that day,
he must abide by the rules
as they stand now.
Please look after
Yukimura for us.
You're the only one who can.
I will.
Oh yes. I brought a
few gifts with me.
I imagine it's difficult to
get many things out here.
[KUNOICHI] Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
It's so sweet of you
to think of us!
[KUNOICHI] Goodbye!
Hope to see you soon!
It's nice, but...
How in the world am
I supposed to carry
all of these heavy boxes
up the mountain by myself?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Nobuyuki was once again
sent as Tokugawa's envoy.
This time to the
castle in Osaka,
from where Lord Hideyori
leads the Toyotomi.
[NOBUYUKI] I'm here to
inform you that Lord Ieyasu
has stepped down from his
position as Seii Taishogun.
In his place, the Imperial
court has chosen his son,
Lord Hidetada, as his successor.
They feel he has the
experience and leadership
to maintain peace in the land.
This is an outrage.
That title rightfully belongs
to Lord Hideyori!
[HIDEYORI]
You should relax.
I know that you're not
the one to blame for this.
[NOBUYUKI]
Apologies, my lord.
Yes. Thank you.
The situation is
rather troubling.
So he's appointed
his favorite son...
The Toyotomi rule is over
now. This makes it final.
[HIDEYORI]
Anything else?
Yes.
He'd like to speak with you.
About the future of the empire.
He wishes to hear your thoughts
on how to preserve peace
in the land.
[HIDEYORI]
Does he now?
Indeed, my lord.
I will not go to Edo.
[NOBUYUKI]
You needn't.
Lord Ieyasu will
visit the capital
to receive the imperial
proclamation
regarding the transfer of power.
As part of his journey
he wishes to meet
at Nijo castle to facilitate
this discussion.
That power-hungry
fool has no right
to treat Lord Hideyori
as an afterthought!
He's just a vassal himself!
Settle down.
Of course, my lord.
Please forgive me,
but I cannot make this
agreement at the moment.
I shall need some
time to think.
The implications are far too
vast for a hasty decision.
Kai. Please prepare a
room for Master Nobuyuki.
[KAI]
Yes, my lord.
[HIDEYORI]
By the way,
I hope that Yukimura is
doing well these days.
[KAI]
Ugh.
I was afraid that things
would someday come to this.
What do you mean by that?
That Tokugawa would
try to assume
absolute power, obviously.
It really breaks my heart
for Lord Hideyori.
Does Lord Hideyori always
carry himself in such a way?
What way would that be?
[NOBUYUKI]
How do I put this?
Perhaps "lackadaisical"
is the right word?
I think he behaves like
that to mask his true feelings.
Honestly, sometimes I find
it absolutely adorable!
But what is in his mind?
What does he really think?
That's hard to discern.
He's quite an enigma.
He wears many faces.
The stern leader.
The innocent young man.
The poet.
And the one full of mystery.
For the life of me, I can never
tell which one is truly him.
But no matter the face,
he's always paying attention.
Lord Hideyori,
I strongly urge you
not to agree to this meeting!
[VASSAL B] Your father
brought peace to this land
and it was his wish for you to
be its shepherd, not Tokugawa.
This is a slap in the face!
[VASSAL C]
His job was to see us through
until you could continue
your father's legacy!
[VASSAL B]
This is unforgivable!
[VASSAL A] We cannot allow him
to strip you of your birthright!
So in other words,
this is your advice:
That we should prepare for war.
And soon.
[KIYOMASA]
Everyone in town was smiling.
[MASANORI]
Huh?
[KIYOMASA]
Remember?
Lord Hideyoshi said
he wanted a world
where everyone could smile.
Yeah, he did say that a lot.
[KIYOMASA]
This was his dream.
And it seems to me that Ieyasu
always wanted to take
what Lord Hideyoshi
worked so hard to build.
And claim it as his own.
[MASANORI]
That's probably what's going on.
And now Hidetada
will be the Shogun?
We were loyal to the Toyotomi.
And so was Tokugawa.
We swore no such oath to Ieyasu.
[MASANORI yells]
Just say it already, that the
Tokugawa are lousy thieves!
[TAKATORA]
Did I hear that right?
Takatora.
[TAKATORA] That's quite an
inflammatory statement.
Were you spying on us?
Yeah, so what if I said it?
[TAKATORA] I have heard quite
a bit of this kind of talk
from the two of you,
this support for Toyotomi.
[TAKATORA]
These words,
will they lead you to
betray the Tokugawa?
There is no betrayal.
We've always served
the same lord as Ieyasu.
And what exactly do
you mean by that?
Tokugawa are Toyotomi
vassals just like we are!
We're not the type to switch
masters for our convenience.
[yelling]
Stop now!
[TADAKATSU]
All of you, calm down!
[TAKATORA]
Yes, Master Tadakatsu.
[TADAKATSU] I will let you go
with a warning this time only.
Do you understand?
[TAKATORA, MASANORI, KIYOMASA]
Yes, sir.
[GUARD A] Stop! No one
is allowed to enter!
[GUARD B] By order of the
Shogun, you must keep out!
Yukimura Sanada.
Master Naomasa Ii.
What's wrong?
Who's in there?
Do not interfere.
Leave him alone!
Do as he says.
My lord.
Yukimura.
Pick up the spear.
What Lord Ieyasu wants
is a long-lasting peace.
One that extends beyond
our lifetimes.
That said,
it cannot come to fruition as
long as you are allowed to live.
You are a warrior
through and through,
one worthy of honor and respect.
Thus, I will give you the
opportunity to die as a warrior.
Now pick up the
spear. And fight!
I will not disturb this peaceful
world with an act of violence.
So you choose to
die as a coward?
I'll not die by
violence, either.
A life of shame is
your choice then.
That is unacceptable!
Look, you can believe life
will be nothing but shame
if that's what you choose.
However, you can also believe
you live for a reason.
It may be considered shameful
for me to live in this way,
but I must continue to do so.
I promised my brother
that I would.
Alas, Nobuyuki himself
told Lord Ieyasu
that your life was forfeit.
That maybe true, but
I made a vow to him to live.
I'll honor it.
I swore to think
about why I live.
To find my purpose.
Until I've made that
discovery, I cannot die.
But I know you can't
be allowed to live.
You threaten the Tokugawa
regime and peace itself!
How can I pose such
a threat to the world
when I'm exiled from it?
By simply being alive!
Possessing your
warrior's spirit!
It's time you accepted
your fate.
I told you that I will
never wield a spear again.
Then I shall honor that pledge.
Now you die!
No! Please don't kill him!
You have a serious injury!
What's that smell? Smoke?
--The village!
--What?
[GUARD A]
What's going on?
[GUARD B]
The village is burning!
Let me see what's
happening out there!
Don't run from me!
[VILLAGERS screaming]
Run! This way!
Just who in the hell are you?
It's Kotaro Fuma!
Lead the villagers to safety!
[YUKIMURA]
I must protect the people!
Please, you have to run!
You came to save us!
Hurry!
Get out of here, now!
[yelling]
Oh no!
Now descend into chaos!
[YUKIMURA screaming]
Lord Yukimura, no!
The scary man killed him!
Yukimura!
You have to pick up
the spear, Yukimura!
A warrior does what
is in his heart!
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[yelling]
That's the Yukimura I know!
I live... in order
to protect the people!
That is the true
meaning of my life!
[yelling]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
Master Naomasa!
Get on my back, Suzu!
[yells]
Master Naomasa!
You must stop him!
[yelling]
And once you're done,
we fight...
...and die...
...with honor.
I won't fall for
that trick again!
Now die!
[yells]
[chuckling]
[HIDETADA snoring]
[KOTARO]
Wake up.
It's you!
War shall rule the land again.
What the hell are you saying?
[laughing]
[YUKIMURA]
He died honorably.
All my life I have
used my strength
to protect other people.
Whether they be
at my home in Ueda
or in the village of my exile,
I strived to keep them safe.
That's why I must leave.
Because they'd be
safer without you here.
This place helped me discover
my true reason for living.
My path will now and forever
be the way of the
righteous warrior.
[KUNOICHI]
I think you should take this.
I believe that you're finally
ready to accept it, my lord.
Mitsunari.
I swore to fight for
righteousness with you.
And I'll never stop fighting.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
[NENE]
Here ya go!
Now, your change
is one million yen!
Don't forget,
smiles are always free!
[KUNOICHI]
Uhh...
[CLERK]
For you, sir.
What kinda crazy burger is this?
It's the bomb.
[NARRATOR] When one follows
their true life's path,
they will encounter
many crossroads.
Decisions must be made
to reach the destination.
There is no map,
save one found inside
the chambers of the heart.
[NARRATION] Next episode:
"Way of No Return"