[NARRATION]
The summer grasses
rise from where brave warriors
dared to dream a dream.
It was a dream many
warriors shared.
To unite this fractured
land under their banner.
Shingen Takeda.
Kenshin Uesugi.
Nobunaga Oda.
But now, one warrior has made
that elusive dream a reality.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
It would seem that he
has sown peace in the land
by the tip of his spear.
However...
The seeds of war are
beginning to germinate.
[HIDEYOSHI breathes weakly]
Stay strong darling.
Everyone is here with you.
Hideyoshi, my lord.
[MASANORI sobs]
Please... Mitsunari.
Master Ieyasu.
[BOTH gasp]
What is it my lord?
Preserve the Toyotomi.
Ensure that my legacy lives on.
Hideyori...
[IEYASU gasps]
[HIDEYOSHI]
My son...
He is safe, my lord.
And I swear on my honor
that he will remain so.
[sighs]
[HIDEYOSHI]
His fate's with you.
Protect him... Please.
[ALL gasp]
[NENE] Darling, no!
Please stay with us!
My sweet little monkey!
[NENE sobs]
[IEYASU sobs]
No!
[MASANORI screams]
Hideyoshi, my lord!
[KIYOMASA]
Where are you going?
I have important
business to attend.
Oh yeah?!
I'm sure it's so important!
The world doesn't revolve
around your big fat head!
[KIYOMASA]
Masanori!
Our uncle just died, you know?
Don't you have a heart?
A... Soul?
You should be in
tears right now!
This is horrible.
How could he die
at a time like this?
[MASANORI sobs]
[gasps]
[MITSUNARI sobs]
Master Mitsunari.
[SHINGEN]
Promise me.
You'll take care of Katsuyori.
[YUKIMURA grunts]
We gave everything we had.
But still, Takeda fell.
How could the house
not survive the master?
I feel like our failure means
we've betrayed his legacy!
What comes next?
Can this nascent peace
survive losing its master?
Listen. No matter
what is to come,
You and I will devote our lives
to ensure the
Sanada clan survives.
Understand?
Yes. No matter what.
[YUKIMURA]
I vow...
...to keep the same fate from
befalling Master Mitsunari.
[NOBUYUKI] I cannot make the
same mistakes I made back then.
[NARRATION] The unity that had
so recently come to the land,
so torn by generations of war,
was dealt a crippling blow
by Hideyoshi's passing.
Shortly thereafter his
ally Toshiie Maeda,
joined him in the afterlife.
With these two pillars gone,
will the peace remain standing?
[IEYASU] Will someone explain
to me why Master Kagekatsu
is no longer here with us?
Lord Uesugi deemed
it necessary to return.
He's on his way to Aizu.
The entire purpose of
our meeting today
is to discuss what the
future holds for Toyotomi
after Master Toshiie's
untimely passing.
Your lord's involvement
in such matters
is crucial to
maintaining the peace.
As you're well aware,
our house has been
transferred from Echigo
to Aizu very recently.
So it is crucial for us to
establish a foothold there.
[IEYASU] Yes, and there is
talk of Master Kagekatsu
building a new
fortress to that end.
"To establish a foothold."
But some may see it as
a preparation for war.
[BOTH gasp]
To start another war?!
Surely you've heard
these same rumblings.
There are those that say
your lord is planning
a rebellion against
the Toyotomi.
So are the rumors
true or not, Kanetsugu?
They're false. Nothing but
unfounded gossip!
What truly needs clarification
is why Master Ieyasu is
gathering up Daimyo in Edo.
One may suspect, that you
are beginning to assemble
your forces to take
over the Toyotomi
in the wake of these
recent tragedies.
That's Nonsense.
Lord Hideyoshi himself entrusted
me to preserve his legacy,
and honoring the vow I made
to him is my sacred duty.
Preserve the Toyotomi.
Ensure that my legacy lives on.
Hideyori...
I assure you that I am merely
doing my best to see that peace,
which he devoted
his life to establish,
continues to flourish
and grow strong.
[MITSUNARI] You seem to forget
that was not your task alone.
We were all entrusted
to preserve that legacy,
were we not?
Such brazen arrogance carries
with it a considerable price.
Odd that you would be the
one to invoke such a term.
You knew Master Kagekatsu
would be absent today,
but chose to keep that
knowledge to yourself, correct?
Indeed.
Of course I did.
Because I determined that his
absence was acceptable.
Oh, is that so?
Are you the one to
make such decisions?
I have a feeling that your
head has gotten even bigger
than it was before!
I'm beginning to grow rather
weary of your insinuations.
What did you say?!
You speak of sharing our duty,
but your actions betray you.
[KIYOMASA]
Mitsunari! Wait!
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKIMURA]
What's going on?
[MITSUNARI]
Kiyomasa. Go to Kyushu.
But why Kyushu?
Because I asked
you to go there.
I have no intention of
leaving Osaka anytime soon!
What the hell are
you talking about?
We've been together ever
since we were all little kids
and now you wanna send us away?
We are much stronger
together than we are apart.
Toyotomi needs that
strength more than ever!
[MITSUNARI]
That may be what you believe,
but I have my own plan.
[BOTH gasp]
You mean you're planning to
take Uncle Hideyoshi's place.
Do as I ask. That's an order.
[MASANORI growls]
You bastard!
[MASANORI grunts]
[MASANORI pants]
Master Masanori!
Calm down!
That was a mistake.
How unfortunate.
Oh, come on!
Mitsunari!
[SAKON] Haven't you two known
him long enough to realize
that he has all of our
best interests at heart?
[MASANORI, KIYOMASA gasp]
[YOSHITSUGU]
Kiyomasa.
You are his most trusted friend.
That's the sole reason he's
asked you protect Kyushu.
If that's the case why
doesn't he say it himself?
Ordering me around like a vassal
is an insult to our friendship.
[MASANORI] All our lives,
we've gotten into fights.
But we never took it as anything
more than letting off steam!
What the hell happened to you?
[MITSUNARI scoffs]
I have realized that we
are no longer children.
[MASANORI, KIYOMASA grunt]
You're like my brother,
but you are not my master.
This is goodbye Mitsunari.
[MASANORI]
Kiyomasa...
We're gone!
[YUKIMURA]
Please, wait!
Master Kiyomasa!
Master Masanori!
[MASANORI]
Lady Nene,
do you really have to
leave all by yourself?
His spirit will
keep me company,
but there are simply too
many memories lingering here.
Aww...
You're such good boys.
Part of our family.
Always there for us.
Promise me you won't grow apart.
This peace is his legacy.
But now it is in your hands.
Take care of it.
[ALL]
Yes!
What will we do without you?
[MITSUNARI exhales]
[SAKON sighs]
This is troubling.
[NOBUYUKI]
I see.
So Lord Ieyasu
has returned to Edo.
[INA]
Yes.
You seem pensive. Is there
something that's troubling you?
My family dutifully supported
the Takeda clan for many years.
But still, the house
fell so quickly
after Lord Shingen's passing.
It left me with a
sense of failure
the likes of which
I'd never experienced.
And I vowed to never forget.
Branches will fall, but no
tree survives without its trunk.
You're worried that the
Toyotomi and the union itself
will suffer the same fate that
befell the house of Takeda.
That it will not
survive this loss.
All I know is I must be
the trunk for the Sanada.
One that will withstand
the axes of war.
One that will not fall.
[YUKIMURA]
You should know, Master Kiyomasa
and Master Masanori
have left the castle.
[KANETSUGU]
I see.
Although he may hide it,
Mitsunari's heart aches after
Lord Hideyoshi's sudden death.
I know.
You know the fate that
befell the Takeda clan.
Without their master they could
neither endure, nor be saved.
Master Mitsunari is painfully
aware that peace in the land
rests solely on the
survival of the Toyotomi.
And he seeks to
carry that burden
squarely on his
own shoulders.
I'm afraid he
doesn't realize...
...it's too much for
one man to bear alone.
Then it is our duty to see
he doesn't bear it alone.
[KANETSUGU]
Indeed, it is.
[YOSHITSUGU]
Mitsunari.
Work shouldn't keep you from
the necessities of living.
I haven't seen you sleep or
eat a decent meal in days.
Don't you thin- -
Although he's no longer
with us in a physical sense,
my lord needs my
service more than ever.
[SAKON sighs]
So, in other words,
there's no rest for the weary.
[YOSHITSUGU] Careful you
don't exhaust yourself.
I appreciate your concern.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Those sentimental fools.
So unrefined.
A telltale sign that Sakon
must have made these.
[MITSUNARI chuckles]
That, and the saltiness.
[NOBUYUKI] It's time
I returned to Numata.
Please forgive me,
but I've been away from
the castle for far too long.
[YUKIMURA]
I understand.
Safe travels, brother.
I bid you farewell, Yukimura.
[YUKIMURA]
Farewell.
We'll meet again soon,
in Shinano!
[INA gasps]
[INA]
Father?
Lord Ieyasu requires
your presence.
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
Apologies for the delay.
[IEYASU grunts]
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI]
Takatora Todo.
Kiyomasa Kato.
Masanori Fukushima.
So many Toyotomi Daimyo in
one place. What is this?
I appreciate you all
joining me here today.
[ALL]
Yes, my lord!
[IEYASU]
I'm sure you're all aware
of Lord Hideyoshi's
tragic passing.
Were he still alive,
I would be in Kanto now.
Establishing a new province
under the Toyotomi banner
in the spirit of unity.
Alas, the circumstances
have sadly changed.
Lord Hideyori, his heir,
Is still quite young.
Too young to defend the peace
his father brought to this land.
Thus, We must do
everything in our power
to ensure this peace remains.
Even as we speak, Kagekatsu
Uesugi is rattling his sabers
and plotting against
the Toyotomi
from his stronghold
in the Aizu province.
We shall brook no
threat to peace,
and punish those
who dare disturb it!
War may be over, but our
vigilance must never end!
I ask you, join me to
quell this insurrection!
[ALL]
Aye!
Could it be true?
Have you forgotten the
allegiance Sanada has
to the house of Uesugi?
They joined forces to fight
against us before, you know?
And I wouldn't put it
past them to do it again!
Please, father!
They were our enemies!
We can't risk their
inevitable betrayal!
Master Mitsunari.
Have you reached
your decision?
[MITSUNARI]
Ieyasu plans to attack our lord.
I believe he's trying
to usurp Lord Hideyori
as leader of the Toyotomi.
The man has no honor.
Only blatant ambition.
This I swear. I will
strike him down.
Then I shall join you
and face Ieyasu in Aizu
to defend the Uesugi!
The house of Sanada
will repay our debt
and lend our swords to
the battle alongside you!
[MITSUNARI]
It's too late.
[YUKIMURA grunts]
Your brother's already
sided with the Tokugawa.
[YUKIMURA gasps]
That can't be true!
I found it hard
to believe myself,
but I'm afraid it is true.
But why?
Our family would never abandon
an ally in their time of need.
This must be
a misunderstanding
and I will clear it up once I
remind him of our obligation
to the Uesugi.
You need not ask for
my support in this battle,
I pledge it without
any hesitation!
In the battle of Ueda, both of
you willingly risked your lives
to save mine and if I
should happen to die
while repaying that debt
to you, then so be it!
As long as there's breath in my
lungs, I'll fight on your side.
[MITSUNARI]
Fools.
Let us swear our oath
of devotion together!
[YUKIMURA]
Yes!
Kanetsugu Naoe!
Yukimura Sanada!
[MITSUNARI exhales]
Mitsunari Ishida.
[KANETSUGU] We three shall
fight together as one.
And share a righteous victory!
[KUNOICHI]
Nobuyuki my lord.
[NOBUYUKI gasps]
[NOBUYUKI]
What is it?
Lord Yukimura would like to
have a word with you in private.
He's waiting for you.
In Inubushi.
[NOBUYUKI sighs]
[NOBUYUKI]
I understand.
[NARRATION] With each
hoping to convince the other
of the proper way forward.
The brothers ride off
to meet in a small village
in the Shimotsuke province.
[NOBUYUKI]
Yukimura, your line's pulling!
[YUKIMURA grunts]
Yes! I got it!
[YOUNG NOBUYUKI]
Let me help you!
Are you ready?
Go!
[BOTH grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH shout, grunt]
[BOTH laugh]
[YUKIMURA]
You're here!
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI]
Yukimura.
[YUKIMURA] I come bearing a
letter from Master Mitsunari.
I ask that you please read it.
[NOBUYUKI]
I already know what it says.
He wants us to join him.
To take up arms against Ieyasu.
I'm afraid I don't
understand your hesitation.
Then I refuse
without hesitation.
You do?
[NOBUYUKI]
Yukimura.
Please listen.
I side with Tokugawa.
[YUKIMURA] Why?!
Explain yourself, brother!
[NOBUYUKI] Because I remember
what happened to the Takeda clan
after Lord Shingen's passing.
History cannot be
allowed to repeat itself.
The stakes are much too high.
[YUKIMURA]
That is exactly why
we have to be on
the right side of it!
Why we need to
fight with Mitsunari!
I understand your feelings,
but Mitsunari is
in no way capable
of holding up the Toyotomi!
He can if we give him the full
support of the Sanada family!
[NOBUYUKI exhales]
You're wrong.
I have thought this through.
And I've come to the conclusion
that only Lord Ieyasu is
capable of keeping the peace.
[YUKIMURA] Peace, maybe.
But what about righteousness?
[NOBUYUKI gasps]
Please join me!
[YUKIMURA gasps]
[NOBUYUKI] My wish is
to be our family's trunk.
And so I must not
permit myself to bend.
To preserve the
Soul of the Sanada,
I shall wage war
on behalf of peace.
Fighting alongside the Tokugawa.
Let's fight for peace!
As brothers!
I'm sorry, brother.
But I can't do that.
[NOBUYUKI gasps]
[YUKIMURA] Even if it means
that you and I are destined
to part ways, I will honor
my debt to the Uesugi
and throw in my lot
against the Tokugawa.
I shall wage war on
behalf of righteousness
and fight alongside Mitsunari.
[YUKIMURA]
I wish you luck, brother.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors High School!
[MITSUNARI grunting]
[MITSUNARI gasps]
[MITSUNARI gasps, grunts]
--[clicking]
--[MITSUNARI] Hm?
[MITSUNARI gasps]
I guess typing isn't
exactly your strong suit?
Ah, shut up!
--[craking]
--[BOTH] Huh?
[MITSUNARI groans]
[SAKON]
Smooth.
[NARRATION]
Ueda castle.
The Sanada's home
away from home,
Is no longer a place of refuge.
The cherry blossoms are no
longer a symbol of unity.
They now set the stage
for war between brothers.
Next episode:
"Storm at Ueda Castle."