[NARRATION] Once the epicenter
of Japan's unification,
Osaka castle was now
the site of its fracture.
Tokugawa laid siege
from all sides.
Takatora Todo led the south,
while Yukimura watched
perched atop his namesake ward.
[WARRIORS yelling]
They're getting close!
Just wait.
[NARRATION]
Yamatoboshi Bridge on the east
was stormed by Uesugi soldiers,
led by his trusted
retainer Kanetsugu Naoe.
Keiji Maeda manned
the defenses there.
Let's make it rain down hard
on those Tokugawa bastards.
[NARRATION] The west side had
many bridges crossing the river
to the outer wall.
The Date army tried
to push their men
through these openings.
Kiyomasa and Masanori were
there to beat them away.
[NARRATION]
The dragon's invaders
unleashed a massive salvo
of gunfire from
their matchlocks.
[yells]
[WARRIORS scream]
[NARRATION] The Toyotomi
attempted to slow the offensive
by destroying every bridge
leading to the fortress,
leaving no easy way in.
How d'ya like that?
I thought that we might see
those stray dogs again.
[NARRATION] Farther to
the south of Osaka castle,
at the foot of Mount Chausu,
Ieyasu Tokugawa commanded
from his primary camp.
Their fortress
seems impregnable.
There has to be some
way to breach it.
[WARRIORS yelling]
Don't you think they've gotten
close enough by now?
Not just yet.
[WARRIORS yelling]
Now fire!
[WARRIORS screaming]
Launch another volley!
Press on, men!
Our cavalry will surely
force a breach!
Matchlocks! Ready!
And Fire!
[WARRIORS screaming]
[groans]
[BLUE WARRIOR 10E groans]
[growls]
[NARRATION] Relying on sheer
numbers and brute strength
to overwhelm their foe,
the Tokugawa were staved off
by the Toyotomi's
natural defenses
and fierce determination.
The newly constructed
Sanada ward
also served as a major deterrent
on the previously
vulnerable south side.
[KEIJI] Yukimura, you're as
good a warrior as they say!
I appreciate the sentiment,
but my soldiers
deserve all the praise.
But thanks to you,
morale in our ranks
is higher than ever before.
And the ward you
created is invincible.
That's the whole reason why
I named it the Sanada ward!
Looks like it's
startin' to snow.
[KEIJI] A good fight
should heat things up.
Aw, thank you, Tsukimaru.
They're calling it
the Sanada ward?
How utterly ridiculous!
This battle...
has only just begun.
The Toyotomi are trapped
inside their castle.
If we stay the course,
victory is ours.
[KANETSUGU] Seems Yukimura
is playing a central role
in the castle's defense.
I imagined that once
he came to Osaka
that would be the case.
We are truly enemies now.
[LEAD MUSKETEER 10A]
Next rotation! Hurry!
Why are we not
firing back at them?
Because the angle and elevation
from which they're shooting
gives them an advantage
on their range. For our
guns to reach them,
we must get much closer.
So then order your
men to push forward!
The enemy is rotating
their gunners,
but not very quickly.
We are taking advantage
of this by moving forward
while they reload.
Their front line is
advancing, my lord.
Unfortunately, many
of our soldiers
lack experience
using matchlocks.
However, we do have
a contingency plan.
Lord Yukimura. Is it time?
Take my post!
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 10A]
Yes, my lord!
Are we close enough yet?
Very soon.
[YUKIMURA yells]
[KUNOICHI grunts]
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 10B
grunts, yells]
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIERS grunting]
[YUKIMURA yells]
Wait! What's that?
[yelling]
What's going on here?
It looks like an ambush!
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIERS yelling]
[BLUE WARRIOR 10H groans]
[BLUE WARRIORS groan]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
[NARRATION] Yukimura's surprise
attack from behind
the lines confused the enemy,
and drew them in closer
to the Sanada ward.
The Toyotomi forces
stationed atop it
viciously rained fire
down from above.
[NARRATION]
The seasons have changed,
but the struggle for
dominance continues,
as December heralds
winter's arrival.
[YUKIMURA]
Lord Hideyori.
This battle is taking
quite a toll on our forces
and fatigue is setting in.
We must try to put
an end to this before
we lose more lives.
The same is true for our enemy.
And In addition to that,
they are on foreign soil.
Now is the time
to launch our offensive.
[TADAKATSU] Our progress
seems to have stalled.
[IEYASU] They have a
geographic advantage.
[TADAKATSU]
Indeed, that is one factor.
But there are many more.
Most notably among them
is this new "Sanada ward."
Yukimura Sanada.
His very existence is a threat.
Many men in our ranks
believe that his presence
means the fortress
is invincible.
Thus, morale is suffering.
Surely you aren't
suggesting that we retreat?
[TADAKATSU] The entire fortress
was brilliantly designed.
If we do get past
the Sanada ward,
there is still the outer
wards and inner moat.
Reaching the castle
keep will prove
to be extremely difficult.
[IEYASU]
Don't lose heart.
I have plans in place.
[NOBUYUKI]
This bitter cold--
it's been severely detrimental
to our soldiers' health.
Their wounds aren't healing,
and many are
beginning to fall ill.
They have simply been pushed
beyond their limits.
This can't go on much longer.
Now fire!
They have cannons?
[KUNOICHI]
They hit the main ward!
[YUKIMURA]
But they're so far away!
I don't believe it.
How can they possibly
reach us from their position?
They couldn't get
through the Sanada ward,
so they're just going over it.
[HIDEYORI grunts]
Lord Hideyori, you must
escape at once!
I will not leave while
asking others to stay!
The cannons are hitting
the main ward!
How is that even possible?
Where are you going?
[YUKIMURA]
I must destroy those cannons.
--No, please! Let me go instead!
--[BLUE WARRIORS yelling]
Your soldiers need you here!
You have to stay behind with
them and lead as only you can!
I understand.
I'm going then!
Prepare yourselves!
The enemy's here!
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIERS grunting]
[YELLOW WARRIORS scream]
Sir. They've struck
the main ward!
I didn't think that
they had it in 'em.
Kiyomasa, what should we do?
Stay focused on who
we're fighting now.
Bastards!
[BLUE WARRIORS gasp, groan]
[BOTH growl]
[grunts]
[BLUE WARRIORS screaming]
[TAKATORA]
Stop right there!
[KUNOICHI gasps]
[yells]
[yelps]
She's gone!
Vanished into the smoke!
Never mind. She's been injured.
Get back to your
stations and keep firing!
[BLUE WARRIORS]
Lord!
[pants]
I'm sorry.
I should've done a lot
more damage with that.
[TSUKIMARU whines]
[KUNOICHI grunts]
[NARRATION] Those cannons
fired by the Tokugawa
were known as "Kuni Kuzushi"
or "country destroyers."
They continued to release
their destructive payloads
for many more days.
The unceasing barrage
of cannon fire
and the devastation they
brought upon the castle
also took their toll
on the morale of those
who bravely fought
for the Toyotomi.
Lord Yukimura.
Please forgive me.
I've failed you.
No, you haven't.
How is your wound?
I'll be all right.
I never could've even imagined
that the Tokugawa had such
nasty toys to play with.
[IEYASU]
You want me to stop firing?
Has it not achieved
its desired effect?
It is my belief
that if we continue,
both sides will perish.
What in the hell
do you mean by that?
We will kill the Toyotomi,
and nature... will kill us.
[growls]
[NOBUYUKI] The cold and lack
of resources are unforgiving.
We're losing countless
men by the day.
And more will be lost
without our cannons.
That means we must
call for a truce.
You can't be serious!
[NOBUYUKI] Serious enough
to carry the message myself.
--Damn fool!
I will not cease firing!
[NOBUYUKI]
So be it.
And what if the enemy
rejects this notion
of a truce?
[NOBUYUKI]
Then more graves will be dug.
[INA] How large of
a squad will you bring?
[NOBUYUKI]
I'll be going alone.
Are you certain?
Lord Ieyasu has said
he will not stop
the cannons. I refuse to put
my men in the line of fire.
And I can move faster on my own.
I admire the love that you
show for your soldiers.
Getting inside will be
difficult, even by yourself.
You must approach
from the south.
So that means the only way
to enter the main fortress
is through the Sanada ward.
I shall create a
diversion for Yukimura.
I'd appreciate that.
Your courage and
devotion to saving lives
is inspiring.
We should move out.
Yes.
[INA gasps]
[HIDETADA] Heh. He truly is
going out of his way
to impress father and I.
Lord Hidetada. What are you...?
Well...
I mean he already
betrayed his own brother
to garner favor from us.
[HIDETADA gasps]
[HIDETADA grunts]
I beg your pardon, my lord.
That was reckless.
Onward, men!
That's Kanetsugu!
[yells]
[BLUE WARRIORS scream]
You will not get past me!
Is that so?
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
We need to get more
ammunition to this wall!
Hold on, was that...?
[WARRIORS yelling]
[yelling]
I thought you had some
real men among your ranks!
[TADAKATSU yells]
Like Tadakatsu Honda.
Keiji Maeda.
[KEIJI yells]
[TADAKATSU yells]
[BOTH yell]
We shall be over the
moat shortly, my lord.
[MASAMUNE]
Excellent!
What in the hell are they doing?
I have an idea.
[GREEN WARRIORS grunting]
They're using their
turrets as bridges!
We must stop them!
Yeah!
[MASANORI grunts]
[KIYOMASA grunts]
[yells]
[KOJURO]
It would appear that you two
form the core of
the western defense.
Then Hideyori must
be truly desperate.
I'll knock out that other eye!
You will not pass!
[MASANORI grunts]
[MASAMUNE yells]
[yells]
[MASAMUNE grunts]
[gasps]
Masanori!
[yells]
[YUKIMURA, KANETSUGU grunting]
Lord Yukimura!
You need to stand back!
Lord Nobuyuki is in the castle!
He is?
He has come to
deliver a truce offer.
Is that true?
I've heard a lot about you.
But I think you may
be a better fighter
than the rumors say!
You as well.
Good. Yeah.
This is gonna be a real treat!
Lord Maeda!
Can't you see I'm busy here?
Nobuyuki Sanada
is in the main ward!
Say what?
Now I can see what's going on.
[HIDEYORI]
Nobuyuki Sanada.
Lord Hideyori.
I bring an urgent message
from Lord Ieyasu.
If this battle continues,
both the Tokugawa
and Toyotomi will suffer
losses far too great to bear.
We ask that you
consider a truce.
Nobuyuki!
[NOBUYUKI]
Stay out of this.
[YUKIMURA] If Lord Hideyori
refuses your offer,
tell me. What will you do, then?
[NOBUYUKI]
You know what I will do.
Please lower your
spear, Yukimura.
[gasps]
I will speak with him
about our terms.
You have made a wise decision.
Are you certain, my lord?
Look. All this destruction.
If I have a chance to
stop it, I must take it.
[growls]
[horn sounds]
Nobuyuki.
You've truly done it.
Heh.
Cease your fire!
[MASANORI sobs]
[MASANORI]
Kiyomasa. Kiyomasa.
Kiyomasa!
This will not satisfy
the Tokugawa for long.
[NOBUYUKI] The next battle
will end all fighting.
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
This will be
covered on the exam!
[YUKIMURA]
Be... covered... on... exam...
[gasps]
[NOBUYUKI] Yukimura,
I'm watching out for you.
[YUKIMURA]
Brother.
Nobuyuki Sanada!
Go back to class!
[YUKIMURA]
And he can't even hide well!
[NOBUYUKI chuckles]
[NARRATION] The seeds of war
have grown into thorny vines,
ensnaring all who
tread among them.
Will they reach the peace
on the other side?
Or be strangled by
the bloody brambles?
The final battle
is on the horizon.
Next episode:
"Castle of Solitude."