[NARRATION]
The summer grasses
rise from where brave warriors
dared to dream a dream.
It was a dream many
warriors shared.
To unite this fractured
land under their banner.
Shingen Takeda.
Kenshin Uesugi.
Nobunaga Oda.
But now, one warrior has made
that elusive dream a reality.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
It would seem that he,
has sown peace in the land
by the tip of his spear.
However...
After his sudden passing,
chaos begins to grow again.
Threatening to
disrupt the balance
so many others died to achieve.
Ieyasu Tokugawa seizes
this opportunity
to expand his influence.
Mitsunari Ishida vows to
halt his quest for power.
The two men lead their
respective armies
in what will prove to be a
historic clash at Sekigahara.
Although the Sanada brothers
both desire to keep their
family name alive,
they take separate paths
in the hopes of someday merging
once again under one banner.
But those paths cross
in Hidetada Tokugawa's
ill-advised siege on Ueda.
The castle they
once called home.
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
You saved my life!
That is what I have
sworn to do, my lord!
Move, brother.
I refuse.
Lord Hidetada,
please retreat at once!
I'll ask you one more
time to get out of my way!
I will not.
I see. Then you leave
me with no choice!
[grunts]
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[NOBUYUKI shouts]
[BOTH shouting]
[NARRATION] Meanwhile, swords
also clanged in Northern Aizu,
where Kagekatsu was locked in
combat with Masamune Date,
The One-Eyed Dragon of Osho.
[SILVER SOLDIERS groan]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[KANETSUGU]
Mitsunari, please. Wait for me!
[NARRATION]
Covered in a dense fog,
Sekigahara was eerily silent.
This silence would soon be
broken by the call to arms.
Followed by the savage
cacophony of combat.
Tranquility would not
return without a price.
Ieyasu Tokugawa's Eastern Army
had both Masanori Fukushima
and Kiyomasa Kato leading
the charge at the front line.
With Tokugawa's main
camp at their backs.
This was the Gyorin,
or fish scale formation.
Across the Sekigahara Basin,
Mitsunari Ishida led his
Western army from his
primary camp on Mount Sasao.
His forces were
more dispersed.
Spread out to surround
the Eastern army.
This was the Kakuyoku,
or Crane Formation.
Due to Hidetada's
misguided attack on Ueda,
the Tokugawa forces seemed
to be at a disadvantage.
Mitsunari was able to establish
a superior footing, and had a
large array of soldiers
and arms at his disposal.
From this view, victory appears
to be his for the taking.
[MASANORI]
Are we ever gonna fight?
I can't stand all
this waiting around!
We will fight in due time.
Lord Ieyasu is simply allowing
this thick fog to clear.
And when that happens,
we'll see the enemy coming
right for us while
we just sit here.
Still we must wait.
We were trusted by our lord
to lead the vanguard
and not act rashly.
There's plenty of time to earn
our valor on the battlefield.
--horse neighs]
--[MASANORI gasps]
Impossible!
[KIYOMASA]
Naomasa!
That bastard! No fair! Damn!
[NAOMASA]
This war is for Tokugawa!
I will not allow Hideyoshi's
followers to draw first blood!
It is truly
no surprise, my lord.
[IEYASU]
Hm.
What's that?
I, Naomasa Ii, bring the first
strike from the Tokugawa!
[shouts]
[GOLDEN SOLDIERS grunting]
[GOLDEN SOLDIERS gasp]
That... red armor!
It's the Crimson Ogre of Ii!
The time has come.
Now! Front line, into battle!
The signal!
Well, finally!
I thought I was gonna
explode over here!
Let's ride out!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
Steady.
Just hold steady!
[yelling continues]
Now men! Fire cannons!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelling]
[gasps]
What do we do?
[BLUE SOLDIERS whimper]
That's some serious firepower!
Maintain your formation!
[NARRATION] The Eastern
Army began its advance,
but the Western Army's
cannons caused much panic
and confusion in their ranks.
Now in disarray, they were
easily outflanked,
and the crane began
to devour the fish!
Attack!
[GOLDEN SOLDIERS shout]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[YOSHITSUGU]
We have them surrounded!
Leave none standing!
[YOSHITSUGU]
Kobayakawa...
Everything is
falling into place.
We have lost the advantage.
Had our cannons arrived, that
might not have been the case.
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[BOTH grunting]
I implore you
to run, my lord!
Uh... You're right!
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA grunting]
This is our home!
I can't let it be destroyed!
I will defend Ueda.
And strike down any threat!
No matter the foe,
my support for
Tokugawa will not waver!
Don't betray me!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell
[SOLDIERS screaming]
The cannons are
causing massive chaos
in the enemy's ranks, my lord.
Between this onslaught
and the Kobayakawa forces,
we're sure to claim victory.
It looks like they've
completely lost the ability
to maintain their formation and
organize any kind of
defense against our attacks.
[MITSUNARI]
Hm.
I must put an end to this soon.
If their reserves
get past Yukimura,
the tides could turn against me.
We need to push further.
Alert the Kobayakawa squad, now!
[GOLDEN VASSAL 1]
Yes, my lord!
[NARRATION]
With his enemy surrounded,
Mitsunari decided that now
was the time to make his
last strike, and end the battle.
A signal was sent to the
Kobayakawa squad
on Mount Matsuo,
to deliver the final blow.
[YOSHITSUGU] Kobayakawa,
will you make your move?
The Western Army has
raised a smoke signal.
[YOSHITSUGU]
Maintain a tight perimeter!
[GOLDEN VASSAL 2]
Yes my lord.
[YOSHITSUGU] There is something
I must do. I'm riding out.
[YOSHITSUGU] It's as I feared.
They're connected to Tokugawa.
[GOLDEN VASSAL 1] My lord, the
Kobayakawa squad is not moving!
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[MITSUNARI]
Ieyasu. Is this your doing?
[GOLDEN VASSAL 3] Lord Otani
is approaching Lord Kobayakawa.
Was this part of
your strategy, my lord?
I was hopeful, but uncertain
that he would cooperate
with us and turn against
the Western Army.
It's not over. We can
still claim victory.
[NOBUYUKI, YUKIMURA grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[gunshots]
Lord Hidetada,
what are you doing?
Fire!
[RED SOLDIERS groan]
[KUNOICHI grunts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS grunt]
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
Wait. Who did that?
--[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
--[BLUE SOLDIER 1 grunts]
Please retreat!
Quickly! While we can!
Fall back, men!
[YUKIMURA gasps]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[YUKIMURA]
Ueda...
Are you hurt, my lord?
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[NAOMASA shouts]
You've fought well,
Crimson Ogre.
Seeing you in action,
will make taking your
life far more satisfying.
Your bloody wounds
betray your empty words.
They will heal after
I've claimed victory.
Have at you!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[KIYOMASA]
I see now.
What is it?
He's only using his
cannons to scare us.
He's purposely missing us!
That idiot's
shooting at nothing!
Huh. Still so soft. How typical.
Let's go beat some
sense into him.
Yeah!
[GOLDEN MESSENGER 1]
My lord, the enemy front line
is pushing forward.
Kiyomasa. Masanori. It's you.
They'll be upon us soon.
We can not allow their
forces to advance.
I'm aware of that!
[MITSUNARI]
I must target them.
[GOLDEN VASSAL 1,2]
My lord!
Draw them in closer,
then wait for my signal.
Stop there!
[TAKATORA grunts]
No farther.
[YOSHITSUGU]
I was expecting to see you.
Curse you, Sanada!
Forgive me, my lord, but my
clan is not our target.
We're fighting Mitsunari.
Without the men and
supplies we still have.
Your father's chances of
victory are far less assured.
Stop running your damn mouth.
Do you think we'll
arrive in time?
I don't know.
But we must not delay.
[GOLDEN SOLDIERS shout]
[KIYOMASA shouts]
My lord! The enemy's
forces are getting closer!
Please! Your orders!
[GOLDEN MESSENGER 2] Tokugawa's
main forces are advancing.
[NARRATION] Kiyomasa and
Masanori had led their soldiers
toward the Western Army's
primary camp on Mount Sasao,
and were now within
striking distance.
The strategically placed
Kobayakawa squad,
had not yet responded
to Mitsunari's signal.
They remained still.
Ieyasu moved his troops to
assist his right and left flank.
My lord!
Fire now.
[GOLDEN MESSENGER 2]
And our aim?
[MITSUNARI]
The soldiers.
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
He's aiming at us now!
He's desperate.
Time to move in!
[IEYASU]
Hm.
[BOTH grunting]
Do you truly believe Mitsunari
can defeat Tokugawa?
You have chosen the losing side!
There is no doubt!
I've let respect be my
lodestar and therefore have
chosen to fight behind the
man who burns the brightest.
[NAOMASA]
What?
[NAOMASA grunts]
[SAKON shouts]
Believe whatever
you will. But I...
...have no regrets for
what side I've chosen.
I'd die for him.
That's good.
[shouts]
[yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[NAOMASA grunts]
My lord.
I pray these changing winds
speed your way towards victory.
[NAOMASA grunts]
[NAOMASA gasps]
[TAKATORA, YOSHITSUGU grunting]
It's not too late to
side with us!
Yoshitsugu! Join me!
[YOSHITSUGU] And betray my
lord in the midst of battle?
But can't you see that the flow
of destiny favors Tokugawa?
Come on!
[YOSHITSUGU] Believe me, I have
seen the flow very clearly.
And I chose to go against it.
Then that means you're
going against me as well.
[YOSHITSUGU]
True, our paths have diverged.
[YOSHITSUGU grunts]
[gasps]
[YOSHITSUGU groans]
Yoshitsugu!
You and I will
follow our dreams.
[YOSHITSUGU]
To see where they lead.
Please, talk!
[YOSHITSUGU grunts]
I knew that my journey...
...would end here.
Forgive me... Mitsunari.
[gasps]
Our dreams. Were they just
leading us towards death?
Yoshitsugu!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yelling]
[growls]
What are we gonna do now?
[TADAKATSU shouts]
[BOTH gasp]
[KIYOMASA]
Master Tadakatsu?
[TADAKATSU shouts]
--[TADAKATSU shouts]
--[MITSUNARI gasps]
[TADAKATSU grunts]
[GOLDEN SOLDIERS groan]
[TADAKATSU shouts]
Tadakatsu Honda!
[GOLDEN VASSAL 4]
My lord!
[MITSUNARI]
Hm?
Lord Kobayakawa has betrayed us!
[gasps]
[GOLDEN VASSAL 5]
My lord!
The Otani and Shima
squads have fallen!
[growls]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
[NARRATION] With Yoshitsugu
and Sakon defeated,
the Western Army's Crane
Formation was broken.
Kobayakawa led his force
against Mitsunari's main camp,
and thus, the outcome
of the war was decided.
[MITSUNARI shouts]
[MITSUNARI yells]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
[MITSUNARI] I am the last
defender of the Toyotomi!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
[MITSUNARI shouts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
Mitsunari!
Concede defeat or you'll die!
You will not stop me!
[MITSUNARI grunts]
[growls]
[MITSUNARI inhales]
Ieyasu!
[IEYASU grunts]
[MITSUNARI growls]
I'll kill you!
[VILLAGERS murmur]
Lord Yukimura!
[YUKIMURA]
Hm?
Your brother is approaching
with Tokugawa soldiers!
He is?
[YUKIMURA]
Why have you returned?
We stand firm behind
master Mitsunari!
[NOBUYUKI]
The war is over!
[YUKIMURA gasps]
Mitsunari has fallen.
No... No!
I refuse to believe that!
[NOBUYUKI]
He lost!
Our presence here more
than proves his failure!
[gasps]
So... where is he now?
[MITSUNARI groans]
You... I'll kill you.
[MITSUNARI gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[MITSUNARI grunts]
[HIDEYOSHI]
Mitsunari.
People will say what
they will about you,
without any thought.
But I understand you.
Perhaps better than anyone else.
[MITSUNARI]
Forgive me, my lord.
[sobs]
Mitsunari!
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
[YOSHITSUGU] I choose
to go against this flow.
[YOSHITSUGU grunts]
[YOSHITSUGU]
Well...
Maybe next time.
[NARRATION] For his stance
against the Tokugawa,
Yukimura stands trial.
Calls for his head are met
with arguments for mercy.
But will his brother's voice
be the loudest to condemn him?
Next episode:
"Where Life Shall Go."