[NARRATION]
The summer grasses
rise from where brave warriors
dared to dream a dream.
It was a dream many
warriors shared.
To unite this fractured
land under their banner.
Shingen Takeda.
Kenshin Uesugi.
Nobunaga Oda.
But now, one warrior has made
that elusive dream a reality.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
It would seem that he,
has sown peace in the land
by the tip of his spear.
However...
After his sudden passing,
chaos begins to grow again.
Threatening to
disrupt the balance
so many others died to achieve.
To preserve the
Soul of the Sanada,
I shall wage war
on behalf of peace.
Fighting alongside the Tokugawa.
I shall wage war on
behalf of righteousness
and fight alongside Mitsunari.
[MITSUNARI] The Tokugawa
have gathered their forces.
Their aim is to take the
union away from the Toyotomi,
our rightful leaders!
This will not stand!
So. We draw our
swords for virtue!
[ARMY cheers]
Move out!
[IEYASU]
Mitsunari has begun to mobilize.
Interfering with our
attack against Uesugi
is a blatant act of
war on Toyotomi.
One that begs
dire consequences.
We shall send our soldiers
west and strike him down!
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
To secure victory, I believe
we should split up our forces.
I will lead our main battalion
along the ocean side.
Hidetada, you will command
troops of your own.
And lead them through
the mountain pass.
Yes.
Your mission is to carry
arms and ammunition to us.
Your promptness
will be essential.
I understand, my lord.
[HIDETADA]
The mountains, eh?
[HIDETADA chuckles]
One question.
How soon shall we depart?
Not before you are ready.
Yes.
[IEYASU]
Nobuyuki.
Yes?
You will provide
support to Hidetada.
[scoffs]
Father, are you sure of that?
[gasps]
[IEYASU]
Is that understood?
Yes, my lord.
[HIDETADA groans]
And what about the Uesugi?
We will crush them.
But first, this battle.
Tomorrow morning, we march!
Mitsunari must not
set foot in Kanto.
We will head him off.
And clash in Sekigahara.
[ALL]
Yes, my lord!
[NARRATION] News of Tokugawa's
forces marching westward
has reached Uesugi.
His advisors are gathered,
to devise their strategy.
[KANETSUGU] My lord, I say
we take this opportunity
and strike Tokugawa
from the rear.
I believe that will be
the most effective way
to support Mitsunari.
[KAGEKATSU grunts]
My lord! Masamune Date from
Osho has launched an attack.
What are your orders?
[gasps]
Masamune approaches?
Ieyasu sent him.
[NARRATION] Ueda fortress,
a Sanada stronghold.
These walls are no strangers
to a Tokugawa assault.
A force of over
seven thousand men
could not raze it to the ground.
Its iron will is reflected
in the master, Yukimura.
His brother, Nobuyuki,
calls another fortress,
in Numata, his home.
It too, has seen its fair
share of bloodshed
due to its location along
the north-south corridor.
Listen up! We Sanada
are true to our word.
Therefore we will
support Master Mitsunari!
My lord, where is your brother?
Will he join us?
He will fight.
Backing Tokugawa.
[VASSALS murmur]
[YUKIMURA]
Do not be discouraged.
This separation is temporary.
Master Mitsunari
will claim victory
and we Sanada will be reunited.
[VASSALS]
Right!
I have a message
for you my lord.
[YUKIMURA]
Thank you.
[TSUKIMARU squeaks]
[KUNOICHI giggles]
[gasps] The Tokugawa are
splitting their forces in two.
They're beginning to move west.
We are to engage the battalion
headed over the mountain pass.
They shall not move forward!
Now! Pick up your weapons
and let's move out!
[VASSALS cheer]
[NARRATION] Hidetada's men
have separated from the larger
Tokugawa army led by
his father, Ieyasu.
They now make camp in Komoro,
south of the Ueda fortress.
[HIDETADA] Soon, we shall
begin our siege on Ueda.
We'll split into four squads,
thus boxing those traitors in.
Their fortress is
very well defended,
and they will try to
draw us inside its walls.
But they would never predict
such a bold assault
from all sides.
Our forces outnumber the
Sanada by tenfold, at least.
They don't stand a chance
against us, my lord!
Word has gotten around
that you're planning to
launch an attack on Ueda.
[HIDETADA]
Hm?
I strongly urge
you to reconsider.
Our mission is to deliver
supplies and ammunition
to your father's
forces in Sekigahara.
This assault was in
no way authorized!
[HIDETADA] Hmph! Neither
was this pathetic attempt
to spare your little brother.
Pardon me?
Isn't that precisely what
you're attempting to do here?
My lord. I say this with
all due respect, but...
Ina, look.
I can understand Lord Hidetada's
mistrust of my motives.
But I assure you, my lord,
what I am attempting to do
here is fight for peace,
which I believe only the
Tokugawa can sustain.
[HIDETADA grunts]
Such lovely words.
If only I believed them.
The Tokugawa forces
have turned to the north.
They're marching towards Ueda!
I see.
Just as I had hoped.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[KANETSUGU shouts]
[DATE SOLDIERS groan]
--[KANETSUGU grunting]
--[DATE SOLDIERS yelling]
[MASAMUNE shouts]
[MASAMUNE] Idiot!
Do you really believe these
little katana fodder soldiers
are going to stop me?
It's Masamune!
I earned the name
"heavenly dragon,"
but I'm sure you know that!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Shame that you won't
survive the introduction.
[KANETSUGU]
You will not advance!
[KANETSUGU grunts]
And there stands
the man himself.
[KANETSUGU] Mitsunari!
Hold on a bit longer!
[NARRATION] Hidetada enacts his
plan and begins his four-pronged
assault on the Ueda fortress.
However...
[NARRATION] The Sanada were
prepared with traps and ambushes
to beat them back,
causing massive casualties
to the invading army.
The Tokugawa forces split
up and tried to surround us.
It's just as you had predicted.
The strategy worked perfectly!
I can't take credit for it.
[KUNOICHI, TSUKIMARU]
Huh?
You see? That's why
you can't be careless.
And if you choose to
underestimate your enemy,
you will lose.
[YUKIMURA] I never
expected those traps
to be waiting for me.
[NOBUYUKI] So, you should
change your strategy.
But what will you do?
[YUKIMURA]
Hm...
Well...
[YUKIMURA gasps]
I don't understand.
I never told you that
I was going to split
up my army like that.
Is there some
kind of secret?
It's like you were reading
my mind or something.
I wasn't reading your mind.
But I was reading the battle
and that told me everything.
Battles tell their own stories.
You can read them from
one part to the next.
So, look at the bigger picture.
If you know what's
happened before,
you can likely see
what'll happen next.
Never forget what
I've told you.
If you read the battle, pay
attention to the way it flows,
and know the lay of the land
you will always have a major
strategic advantage
over any opponent
you may face in the future.
[YUKIMURA] Brother, I haven't
forgotten the lessons
you taught me all
those years ago.
That's how I will
win the fight today.
[HIDETADA]
What is this?
Where are my other squads?
Why aren't they attacking?
[MESSENGER 1]
My lord!
I'm sorry but, It appears the
other squadrons have all been
pinned down by ambushes
set up by Sanada's men!
That's ridiculous!
What are your orders, my lord?
The remaining force still
massively outnumbers
the Sanadas'. Do you
think we should attack?
I have no desire to make the
same mistake as last time.
I know.
We shall just have to
stay outside their walls.
At a safe distance.
Flaming arrows, then.
I'd like to see them
defend a pile of ashes.
My lord, the forces that
went through the mountains
were all met with ambushes.
I'm afraid the casualties
were quite significant.
Just as I thought.
We must get back to camp.
What about the mission?
I cannot let Lord
Hidetada perish.
[NOBUYUKI] That fool walked
directly into Yukimura's trap.
[TOKUGAWA VASSAL 1]
Ready arrows!
[HIDETADA chuckles]
And fire!
What the...?
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
[gasps]
[RED SOLDIERS shout]
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
Don't just stand there!
Get your matchlocks ready
and shoot them down!
[YUKIMURA]
Tokugawa sent his spineless heir
to attack our home?
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
[HIDETADA grunts]
Prepare to die!
[gasps]
Nobuyuki!
Hidetada, my lord!
We must retreat, at once!
How dare you? I'm the
one giving orders here!
Listen to reason!
[HIDETADA growls]
[YUKIMURA growls]
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
[YUKIMURA grunts]
[YUKIMURA]
They're gone!
Yukimura, my lord.
The enemies coming from the
mountain have retreated.
Understood. We should
fall back as well.
It's strange.
I didn't expect to see
your brother here today.
I thought he'd be with them.
But for once, I wish
I had been wrong.
[MESSENGER 1] All squads
reporting heavy losses, my lord.
Damn you, Sanada!
He may have somehow
survived the battle today,
but mark my words I will crush
him like the insect he is!
Something on your mind?
Thoughts of
my brother. That's all.
He's quite formidable.
That's true.
Because he's using our
age-old Sanada strategies.
The same ones that I taught him
while we were both children.
[YUKIMURA] When Nobuyuki
and I built this fortress,
I never dreamed I'd have
to defend it from him.
[YUKIMURA] Although our bond is
strong, my will is far stronger.
I must continue to walk
the path of righteousness.
To repay my debts and keep
my word to Master Mitsunari.
We shall protect
this sacred land
from those who view
it as a mere prize.
Master Mitsunari,
I will hold them here for
as many days as you need.
I will wait for you to claim
your rightful victory.
[NARRATION] Sekigahara, in the
Mino province is a small,
picturesque basin surrounded
by verdant mountains.
Mitsunari Ishida had set
up camp on Mount Sasao.
Just to the northwest
of this area.
[YOSHITSUGU] Word has
come in from Ueda.
Yukimura is holding his ground.
It seems the winds
blow in our favor.
[MITSUNARI]
Hm.
From here it feels
more like a head wind.
Then so be it.
That will not stop us.
[YOSHITSUGU]
Well then, shall we?
[YOSHITSUGU] Mitsunari,
you changed me forever.
When my character was
brought into question,
when I was treated as a pariah,
you alone stood up
to defend my honor.
I won't forget that.
Your rectitude is what ensures
your victory in this fight.
[YOSHITSUGU] And whoever
dares go against you
can count me as
an enemy as well.
[SAKON]
I didn't see this coming.
Kiyomasa and Masanori
were like brothers to my lord.
Practically inseparable.
I suppose I underestimated
his stubborn nature.
[SAKON]
But that's my failure.
He'll stop at nothing
when it comes to righting
what he sees as wrong.
He definitely doesn't
make things easy for me,
but here I am.
The winds have changed.
[NARRATION] Led by Ieyasu,
the main battalion of the
Tokugawa army has made their
camp on Mount Momokubari.
Which is to the east of
the Sekigahara basin.
[TADAKATSU]
My lord.
This battle is unfolding
just as you foretold.
[IEYASU]
Hm.
But Lord Hidetada
and his provisions
have still yet to
arrive, my lord.
Until they appear, we will be
low on arms and ammunition.
My lord, should we
wait for their arrival?
[IEYASU] The human
mind is easily swayed.
However, I will
remain resolute.
We will launch our
attack at sunrise.
[TADAKATSU]
Yes, my lord.
I have an uneasy feeling.
About what?
About our vanguard forces.
Every last one of them
served under Hideyoshi.
Who knows what other
alliances may come into play.
Has Tokugawa considered
this side of things?
Then, what would
you propose he do?
[NAOMASA gasps]
Were it I...
Do you think we'll
see Mitsunari?
I can't say for certain.
The only thing I'm sure about,
Is fate brought us to the
battlefield and there's nothing
we could have done to avoid it.
I'm right there with you!
This is what you and me
were supposed to do!
But still I wonder.
Does Mitsunari
feel the same way?
If we do see him...
...I'm gonna give him a punch
right between the eyes and
knock some sense into him.
Well, I hope it turns
out to be that simple.
[YUKIMURA] This is where
we Sanada call home.
[YUKIMURA] When our lord passed
away, we had no place to go.
We were fugitives
in our own land.
But the cherry blossoms
were waiting to greet us.
They welcomed us here.
The beauty of that
moment was breathtaking.
We knew this was
where we belonged.
This is our new home.
Yes. It is.
We'll build our
castle here.
[YUKIMURA]
Right.
[YUKIMURA] I must protect
this place with my life.
So one day...
My brother will have a
place to call home again.
--[explosions]
--[gasps]
[RED SOLDIERS yell]
[YUKIMURA gasps]
[NOBUYUKI]
Hidetada, my lord.
I beg you to stop!
Your father is waiting on
us to deliver these supplies
and you're putting
his life in jeopardy!
[scoffs] After shelling this
tiny hut you call a fortress,
I will still have plenty of
supplies and a victory
under my belt.
[NOBUYUKI grunts]
[VILLAGERS scream]
[VASSAL 1]
Take the women and children
to the back of the castle!
Lord Yukimura, you have
to get out of here, now!
I'm going directly
to the enemy's camp!
Are they still putting
up resistance?
[VASSAL 2] We see no action
in the fortress, my lord.
They've lost the will
to fight. How pitiful.
[gasps]
Ready the defenses!
The enemy is approaching!
[scoffs]
Such utter nonsense.
Wait! What's happening?
[NOBUYUKI gasps]
The gunpowder stash!
[BLUE SOLDIERS yell]
They're blowing up our supplies?
Do not lose focus!
The enemy is upon us!
[RED SOLDIERS shout]
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[BLUE SOLDIERS groan]
But how?
[YUKIMURA shouts]
[WARRIORS]
Samurai Warriors Highschool!
Once again Nobunaga
Oda proves he's no dummy.
After winning this battle,
he takes over all the
land he could grab.
This will definitely
be on the exam!
[YOSHITSUGU whispers]
Mitsunari.
What are you doing?
Wait. Are you crying
over your notes?
[YOSHITSUGU]
Oh. It's just drool.
Wake up!
[MITSUNARI]
Huh?
[NARRATION] The forces
collide at Sekigahara,
where a momentous clash could
turn the tide of history.
Guided by their own ideals,
one must follow their own path.
But many of those paths
end on the field of battle.
Next episode:
"Sunset at Sekigahara."