Just like us,
they were all fighting
for what they believed in.
[OKITA]
Our goals keep us at war,
but we pray these fallen
soldiers on both sides
may know peace.
And that their souls
may find their way back to the
planets which they call home.
Salute!
[inaudible]
[SHIMA]
Yurisha Iscandar, huh?
[MISAKI] When you were shot,
I wanted to be there for you.
Something changed.
It's like inside of me,
I was screaming to get out.
And then I did. Yurisha left me.
Well, that's good.
I'm glad you're back.
This deck was breeched.
A lot of them may have been
sucked outside the ship.
Ito may be dead, but I'm
starting to think he was right.
Come on, don't be stupid!
[TOKI]
But how else do you explain it?
That Iscandarian. They told
us she had possessed Yuria!
But now she shows up,
looking like Yuki.
Don't ask me.
I mean, she's an alien.
Who knows what she can do?
[YABU]
Hey, look! Jackpot!
Idiot! Do you want
'em to find us?
[grunts]
[YABU]
Sorry.
[sighs]
[YABU]
What do we do now?
I don't know, I'm thinking.
[YABU yelps]
[ITO]
Would you shut up?
[YABU]
See?
[gasps]
Are you feeling better now?
My Iscandarian's pretty lousy.
I put that on you
so we could talk.
Welcome. I'm Banner Holder
Noran Ortschett, Your Grace.
I'll be looking after you.
What's wrong?
Are you a Gamilan?
[HEINI]
Attention: We will be arriving
at the prison planet
Leptapoda shortly.
All crew, prepare for landing.
Prison planet?
Don't worry.
We're only going there
to transfer you
to a different ship.
[MORI]
Where are you taking me?
I'm taking you to Lord Desler.
Wait. What happened
to the Yamato ?
The Teron ship was destroyed.
[gunshots]
[BOZEN] Someone of high
birth is on the way here.
That means you will
have to chaperone her.
All you barbarians do
is waste our food.
[PRISONER A speaking Gamilan]
[BOZEN]
She's Iscandarian royalty.
Someone from Iscandar?
I hate to rely on you,
but you're the only one who
knows the proper etiquette.
[PRISONER B speaking Gamilan]
[PRISONER B screams]
[knocking]
[DITZ] What do you expect
an old man like me to do?
[UX-01 CM A] UX-01 linked
up and birthing now.
Extending jetty.
Port crew, prepare to receive.
[HEINI] Look at those tin
cans standing guard.
[FLAKEN]
They use them everywhere now.
The empire could never maintain
its sprawling territory
without the mechanical
toy soldiers.
That's the downside
of expansionism.
Whatever happened to the
"invincible Gamilas Empire"?
Welcome to Leptapoda, gentlemen!
My name is Bozen, Warden of
Prison Planet Seventeen.
Glad to have you!
You can put the
Iscandarian in the car.
I've brought a special inmate
to make sure she's cared for.
But that's General
Domel's wife, isn't it?
Yes.
[ELISA]
This way, Your Grace.
[ORTSCHETT] Thank you, Captain.
This is where we part.
And where are you going?
I'm on assignment, sir.
I'm here to make sure
she gets home safely.
That's my job.
I'll take it from here.
I don't need any help from
a second-class citizen.
I'm a Gamilan,
same as you, sir.
Shut your mouth!
You Zaltzi scum!
That bastard.
Your people are
nothing but parasites.
How dare you call
yourself a Gamilan!
Fine then. Take this!
[MORI]
Stop!
He will complete his mission.
That is an Iscandarian order.
[ELISA]
My father served as a diplomat.
So I was taught proper
Iscandarian etiquette
as a child.
[ELISA]
If you please.
It suits you well.
You're too kind.
Oh. Hold on!
Almost forgot.
[ELISA]
What is that?
A parting gift from my sister.
The ultimate salvation of
all intelligent life-forms
in the Universe.
That's the true meaning
of the "path to Iscandar."
And it is the duty of our family
to be the guides on that path.
[gasps]
My dear sister.
We've scanned the nearest system
for the materials we need
for repairs, Captain.
Out of all the
planets and moons,
this is the one match.
[HIRATA] I've assembled an
away team for extraction.
Good.
[SANADA]
But let's remember,
we seem to be in
Gamilan territory.
They may have recognized the
planet's value themselves,
and could have operations
there already.
Maybe even a base.
Kodai.
Sir?
I want you to carry out
a recon mission yourself.
Me?
But I can't leave the
Yamato right now,
there's so much more work to do.
Maybe fresh air will do you
some good, Lieutenant.
Sir, yes, sir.
I'll carry out recon on
the planet's surface.
Sir, with the scanning finished,
I'll return to the brig.
No, Niimi. No more brig.
I want you back on
duty full time.
Yes, sir.
[YAMATO CM A] All guidance
crew to their stations,
and prepare for Seagull launch.
Repeat: All guidance
crew to their stations,
and prepare for Seagull launch.
You wish to save her,
don't you, Kodai?
[KODAI yelps]
What are you doing in here?
Do you wish to save
Yuki Mori or not?
Sure I do. But I've
been given orders.
I want to save Yuki Mori.
[KODAI] No offense, lady,
but would you mind getting out?
I don't have time to talk.
And so when will you have time?
Look, I--
[YAMATO CM A] Seagull ,
are you ready to launch?
[KODAI] I'd save her if I knew
where she was, but I don't.
Now will you please get out?
She's on this planet here.
Now you know.
[KODAI gasps]
[YAMATO CM A]
Seagull , is there a problem?
Please respond.
[KODAI]
Negative.
[YAMATO CM A]
Ten-four. Opening hatch.
[KODAI]
Is that true? You're sure of it?
[YURISHA] Yes, of course.
She's on this world.
[KODAI]
How do you know?
Because I love her.
Don't you love her as well?
[KODAI]
Um.
[YURISHA]
Don't you?
[KODAI]
I...
Is this really the right time
to be gossiping about love?
Ito. You're still alive?
Yes, I am. Is that a problem?
No.
Well, it's nice to see you
can be so relaxed, Kodai.
Even after so many have died
on this doomed quest.
And it looks like
Mori's cosplaying.
I kinda feel jealous.
[KODAI] You wouldn't know this
since you've been locked away,
but that's not Mori
you're pointing a gun at.
[ITO]
Oh, I know all too well.
That's an alien.
Mori was a false identity.
Her true name is
Yurisha Iscandar.
[KODAI]
You're wrong!
I mean, you're part right, but--
Hey! Freeze!
Sit down!
[ITO]
Wrong choice.
[BOTH yell]
You moron!
I'm sorry!
Damn it!
[KODAI] Everyone,
grab hold of something!
An imperial inspection ship?
[PRISON GUARD A] Yes, Warden.
It will arrive shortly.
Do you think they know
what we've been selling
on the black market, sir?
Damn!
This could wreck my plan to get
back home, and I was so close!
Wait, I still have a play.
Ah. I hardly recognized you!
You finally look like an
Iscandarian princess!
[BOZEN laughs]
[PRISON GUARD A]
Warden.
[BOZEN]
What?
[PRISON GUARD A] One of
our patrols has discovered
what appear to be
escaped prisoners.
Can't you see I'm busy?
[grunts]
We'll get to the bottom
of this! Let's go!
That's the ship.
Out of the frying pan and
into the fire. Lovely.
It's your fault.
All that's happened...
...it's your fault!
If I hadn't bought into your
damn scheme, I'd still be--
Yabu!
[PRISON GUARD A]
Attention!
We have urgent orders
from the warden!
Bring the Zaltzi woman
to him at once!
[PRISONERS yelling]
[alarm blares]
What's this?
[PRISONERS yelling]
Hey. Wait!
Kodai!
[KODAI]
Run!
[PRISONERS yelling]
[PRISONER C speaking Gamilan]
[PRISONERS yells]
[chuckles nervously]
A riot here? Impossible.
But, sir.
[BOZEN] Oh, hello,
Inspector, and welcome!
We're handling a little
issue right now.
Whoa.
[AGENT A]
This way.
Melda!
We've come to set
you free, Admiral.
[PRISON GUARD A]
Security, status report!
[PRISON GUARD B] We can't hold
them off! There's too many! Uh!
Let's get outta here.
[MORI gasps]
[GAMILOID B]
Return to your quarters.
We'll take back our freedom!
Get down!
You okay?
[MORI]
Yes.
[MORI gasps]
Wait, his blood's red.
[ORTSCHETT] He's a Zaltzi,
like me. My own kind.
[BOZEN] I won't lose
all I've worked for!
Hey! Can anyone hear
me? Open this door!
Thank goodness.
I'm right over here.
[PRISONERS yelling]
[PRISONER H speaking Gamilan]
[screams]
You wanna tell me where you're
going, "Lieutenant Mori,"
or is that an alien secret?
I'm going to save Yuki.
I just don't get you.
Interesting, I guess her
kind mourn the dead, too.
Can you do mine?
All right, "Lieutenant
Mori." Maybe--
[gunshot]
Ito!
[ITO]
Well, I guess that's what I get
for acting outta character.
[ITO chuckles]
Listen... Mori, or
Yurisha, whatever.
If I'm right about you,
then promise me...
Get the Yamato back
to your home world.
Save us. Okay?
Save the Earth.
[PRISONERS yelling]
[GAMILOID C]
It appears subversive elements
were aboard Inspector's ship.
[GAMILOID D] Confusion has
occurred along chain of command.
Yuki!
Get us ready!
Prepare ship for launch, now!
No. Not again!
Yuki! Yuki!
[DITZ]
Attention all personnel.
This is Admiral Ditz, Supreme
Commander of the Astrofleets.
Prison Planet Seventeen
is now under our control.
There is no point in resisting.
Surrender now if
you want to live.
[KODAI]
Yuki.
[YURISHA]
I know where she's going.
[gasps]
[KODAI]
Yurisha!
Then tell me, quick!
Where are they taking her next?
To their home planet. Gamilas.
Two planets?
Gamilas has a twin planet.
The other is the one you seek.
The home of my people.
Mother Iscandar.
[KODAI]
No... That's impossible.