[SANADA] The ship itself
sustained only minimal damage
in our last fight, and our
return will not be affected.
Seventeen crewmembers died.
Thirty-four were wounded.
Damn it!
[SANADA] Chief of Operations,
Lieutenant Mori was shot
and is in a coma.
[OKITA] Any chance
she'll recover, Doctor?
I'm not optimistic.
I'm afraid we'd need
a miracle, Captain.
[OKITA]
Hmm...
[SANADA]
Miracles don't just happen.
We should all know that by now.
Huh?
You have to... make them happen.
[AIHARA] Earth channel open!
It's working, sir!
[gasping]
[TODO] This is Director Todo,
at Yamato Plan HQ.
Yamato , do you copy?
[gasping]
[SANADA]
This is the Yamato .
We have received the Cosmo
Reverse System from Iscandar.
We are approaching our
system on the way to Earth.
[TODO sighs]
I see.
Then the salvation
the Iscandarians
offered us was real.
You did it.
My god, you actually did it.
We've been gritting
our teeth for a year.
Watching the skies.
Counting the days.
Resting all our hopes
on the Yamato 's return.
[TODO sighs]
But where's your captain?
Where's Admiral Okita?
He's led bravely.
But his Planet Bomb Syndrome's
returned and intensified.
He's not in good shape.
I see...
Tell me, Sanada,
is Yuki all right?
[KODAI gasps]
Lieutenant Mori
has been wounded in combat.
She's alive,
but her condition is...
[TODO] Your transmission's
breaking up, can you hear me?
Yamato , do you copy?
[AIHARA] The relays we're
using are still unstable.
I'll keep working on them, but I
think we'll need more time, sir.
[NANBU]
It's fine.
The point is that we're close.
We're back home!
[OTA]
Yeah. We've done it.
[KODAI]
Hey.
Just 'cause we're near our own
solar system doesn't mean
we can drop our guard!
[NANBU gasps]
'Least we know
Earth's still there.
Hopefully, that means our
families are safe, too.
[CIC OFFICER 15A]
Did you hear?
Rumor is there's another
ghost on the Yamato now!
[NIIMI]
Mm?
Heard this one's in
a Cosmo Navy uniform!
[HAYASHI] But what I saw wasn't
really a ghost, remember?
It was Yurisha.
[CIC OFFICER 15A] I think
this is different, though.
--[NIIMI gasps]
--I heard it's a guy.
--[HAYASHI] Huh?
--Well, that's no fun.
And there's more.
It's a uniform but
not from our own ship!
[HAYASHI]
What? How does that make sense?
[SAWAMURA]
Seriously.
Why would a ghost from another
ship be on the Yamato ?
[CIC OFFICER 15A]
That's the big mystery.
Spooky, huh?
[CIC OFFICER 15A]
Speaking of ship drama,
you guys hear anything more
about Lieutenant Mori?
--[HAYASHI] No.
--[gasps]
[SAWAMURA] I heard the
X.O. wants to put her in there.
[DR. SADO]
Best case scenario,
we get her back to Earth
and into a real hospital.
But... I'm afraid her
probability of survival,
is still likely to
be less than 0.1%.
[KODAI] Okay. Well, that's
better than nothing, right?
The immediate problem is
I don't think her body
can hold out long enough
for us to reach Earth.
[DR. SADO]
Which is why we'll intervene.
Uh?
[SANADA] There is a way
we can stabilize her.
At least, we hope.
[gasps]
[SANADA] The capsule
that kept Yurisha alive
during her coma
is still functional.
We believe it can
work on Mori, as well.
[TOKUGAWA]
Captain. Captain!
[OKITA]
Hmm...?
I came in to check on you.
Looks like you were
having a nightmare.
I'm fine, just a harmless dream.
It was about
Mamoru Kodai actually.
You know, I've been
thinking about him, too,
about how he served
with us on the Kirishima .
You were captain of that crew
and I was running the engines.
He was a new
Weapons Officer, wasn't he?
That was during the
Second Battle of Mars.
As if I could ever forget that.
Before this ship,
it's the one battle
against the Gamilans we won.
That success allowed us
to push back their invasion, and
made the rest of this possible.
[OKITA] But we lost a great
deal in that battle, too.
Tokugawa.
Yes, Captain?
You believe this is
a good ship, don't you?
You think we've done well?
I do. No doubt in my mind
[OKITA]
I'm proud of this ship.
Proud of her crew.
I have no illusions.
The flame of my life
won't burn much longer.
--[gasps]
--I'll die,
but this ship will live on.
I hope the younger generation
can keep her good soul intact.
All this morbid talk
is worrying me.
Relax, Chief, I'm not dying yet.
Not until I've seen the Earth
again with my own eyes.
[TOKUGAWA chuckles]
[TOKUGAWA] Well, speaking
of passing the torch.
I think I should get back
to the engine room.
Yamazaki's talented, but I've
still got a lot to teach him.
[TOKUGAWA]
Oh, one more thing.
Mamoru Kodai.
He was meant to be here, right?
[OKITA] Yes, but his
younger brother is
filling his shoes just fine.
--[ANALYZER] Excuse me, Nanbu.
--Uh, yeah?
[ANALYZER] Can you tell me
what is wrong with Aihara?
You know that last transmission
we got from Earth?
[ANALYZER]
Yes?
[NANBU] Let's just say
he got some bad news.
My father is dead.
That means my mother
has to take care of herself.
And while we've been away,
the Earth's turned into
a total mess. No one's safe.
I'm not sure she can last.
Things are bad.
Our world's barely hanging on.
But crying about it
won't save anyone.
The Yamato will make it.
We'll get there in time!
We just have to
stay strong, all right?
Oh, wow. He's kinda
acting like the Captain.
Yeah, Earth'll be fine,
leave it to me!
I've got the helm and
I won't let us down!
I'll get us home
ahead of schedule!
[SHIMA]
Excuse me, who's got the helm?
--[OTA gulps]
--Uh?
Time for a shift change.
[OTA gasps]
I've been waiting for you, sir!
The X.O?
He went to the Wave
Motion Gun control room,
to check on the
Cosmo Reverse System.
I see.
--[KODAI] Shima.
--[gasps]
Kodai.
Here you go. This one's for you.
Whaddaya know?
So it finally happened, huh?
It wasn't easy persuading Kato
to turn it into a party.
That guy is so old fashioned.
But I think it's for the best.
We could all use
something to smile about.
[SHIMA sighs]
Is this okay?
[HARADA] The dress?
I thought I looked good!
No. I mean the party.
Are we rubbing it in?
Is this about Kodai?
It's an act. He's forcing
himself to be cheerful,
for the sake of everyone else.
But the truth is,
he's falling apart.
Even so! Let's do this!
If he's trying
to lift people's spirits
then so should we!
Makoto.
We're staying positive.
For Earth, and for
our little one, too.
[KATO]
Hmph. Yeah, you're right.
That's the spirit, now tell me
which one you like best!
[KATO] I still vote for
the traditional kimono.
No way!
[DR. SADO] New life's born
as the old passes away.
Guess I should find
that inspiring. Right?
[ANALYZER] To what are
you referring, Doctor?
[DR. SADO]
I don't know.
Hey, since we left Iscandar,
you've been coming here a lot.
What gives?
[ANALYZER] I find this
environment calms me.
Ah. I see.
Then you might as well
stick around, tin-man.
[ANALYZER]
You mean that?
[DR. SADO growls]
Don't make me say it again!
[HARADA] So, Yuki. Kato and I
are about to get married.
Can you believe that?
Oh, and hey, get this.
When Kodai found out,
he went straight to Kato,
and was all like, "You have to
have a party. For all of us!"
I mean he actually said that!
And Kato--being Kato--was
totally mortified, of course.
But in the end, he agreed to it.
Guys are cute, aren't they?
They get frazzled by
the weirdest things.
Ah.
[gasps]
Yuki!
[HARADA gasps]
Finally. Just hold on.
I'll get the doctor, okay?
Doctor! Get in here, now!
Get in where?
To automatic navigation,
you old dummy!
[SANADA]
What's your analysis?
It appears to be an interlocking
recursive structure.
The System, it's behaving
like a brain's neural network.
We know it needed
matter from the ship itself.
But there's something
else making it act like
a living creature.
Like something intelligent.
Right. So this
wave motion pattern--
It's the memory that
can rebuild the Earth.
[SANADA] Interesting theory.
But the question is:
If a mind is shaping the
memory, whose mind is it?
[KIRYU] Could it be...
a collective subconscious,
using the minds of the crew
to make this memory of Earth?
Is that possible?
[SANADA]
Or is it one mind instead?
[KIRYU gasps]
[SANADA]
Could it be... you?
[NIIMI sighs]
[SANO]
Wave Motion Control Room.
I-I can't understand you
when you're yelling, Doctor!
[NIIMI gasps]
[SANO]
Yes, the X.O. is here.
I'll send him immediately,
but what's going on with
Lieutenant Mori? Is it bad?
[ringing]
[KODAI gasps]
[KODAI]
Yeah.
[gasps]
[heart monitor flat lines]
[pants]
Oh, no...
[HARADA sobs]
[KODAI grunts]
[screams]
[KODAI sobs]
[DR. SADO] Before she died,
she somehow found the strength
to open her eyes. I'm sorry.
The last thing she said
was your name, Kodai.
She said she... wanted
to see you again...
So did I... [sobs]
I wanted to see you, too...
I wanted it more
than anything...
[HARADA sobbing]
[KODAI]
X.O. I have a request...
Don't tell anyone
else about this.
They don't need to know.
[gasping]
[KODAI whimpers]
We've almost made it home...
I don't want them to
hear any more sad news...
They've been through enough.
[applause, cheering]
[chattering, laughing]
[SHINOHARA chuckles] What do you
think, Ace? Maybe it's our turn.
Gah.
Congratulations.
Uh. Thanks.
[KODAI]
And you, too, Harada.
[HARADA]
Thank you very much.
[KATO] Kodai, remember
when we were first assigned
to this ship?
What I said to you?
[KODAI]
Hmm?
I thought you were
just some reckless punk.
I said that if you ever issued a
command that got my men killed
for nothing,
I would make you pay.
And well... You delivered
on every mission we had.
No one could have led us better.
You deserve to
have something good.
And Mori's gonna be just fine.
[gasps]
Sabu!
[KATO]
Eh? What? I say something wrong?
--[KODAI] Kato.
--[BOTH] Huh?
Thank you. Make her happy, okay?
[NIIMI]
Mamoru Kodai?
You think he's the core of
the Cosmo Reverse System?
[SANADA]
I've considered it carefully,
and it's the most
logical conclusion.
[NIIMI]
Doctor.
Have you heard?
There've been rumors circulating
around the Yamato crew
about a new ghost.
[SANADA]
Hmm?
I've been afraid you
would laugh, and tell me
I was being unscientific.
But I saw him myself.
It was Mamoru!
I'm sure of it!
It's like Clarke's third law:
"Any sufficiently
advanced technology
is indistinguishable
from magic. Heh.
[NIIMI]
Huh?
Iscandar has technology
far more advanced than ours.
My theory is that after he died,
Starsha had some way
to preserve his consciousness.
We're almost close enough to see
the Earth with our own eyes!
[TECH OFFICER 26A]
Aw, man, I can't wait!
[SANADA] His mind has
been used as the core,
the key to activate the wave
motion record of Earth
locked in the
matter of this ship.
In a sense, right now,
Mamoru Kodai is
the Cosmo Reverse System.
Extrapolated further,
he's now the Yamato itself.
[KODAI] Yuki. Do you remember
the first time we met?
[KODAI]
A rocky start.
[KODAI] Back then, I was so
angry about losing my brother.
I was lashing out.
It wasn't the best way
to meet someone.
[KODAI]
Then, before we knew it,
we were onboard
the Yamato together.
We were so different,
and fought all the time.
[KODAI] But eventually, you took
a chance and opened up to me.
Told me how you lost
your memories.
[KODAI] How, despite
all you'd been through,
you kept trying
to stay positive.
I didn't even understand
what was happening.
But I just...
I was so drawn to you.
[gasps]
When you were kidnapped...
...and I found you in space...
...that's when I finally
realized how I actually felt.
[whimpers] I love you.
I love you so much.
More than anyone
else in the world.
[sobs] We went through
all this to save our world...
But what's the point of
me living in that world
if you won't be in it...?
What's the point?!
[sobs]
Susumu. I couldn't
come back home
like I promised.
But I can do this.
I'm returning the ship
to you now, Captain Okita.
The system is
starting up on its own!
It's what? But why?!
[SANO]
I don't know!
[BOTH grunt, gasp]
[KIRYU]
Output is dropping fast!
[SANO] This is bad! If it keeps
discharging at this rate.
[SANADA]
Keep it going!
Don't let the Cosmo Reverse
System shut down!
[SANO]
It's no use, sir!
It's not accepting
any of my commands!
[NIIMI grunts]
Oh, no. Doctor!
[SANADA]
Why...?
Why?! Kodai!
Why did you start it now?!
What the...?
[KODAI gasps]
[MORI sighs]
[gasps]
Kodai? What...
Yuki!
Ah!
[sobs]
[MORI]
What am I... doing here?
I was shot. And then I...
Did I die...?
[KODAI sighs]
Just a dream.
A dream?
Yeah, a bad nightmare.
That's all. I was
having one, too.
Kodai!
[SANADA] Inspect every
part of the system!
Prepare to reboot!
[NIIMI] His mind fired
a massive activation pulse.
Now, it's almost entirely
lost in the quantum sea.
Without it, we can't reactivate.
So... Even if the
Yamato makes it to Earth...
...we won't be able to save it?
It's over?
Kodai. No. How could you?
[ALL gasp]
After everything
we went through.
Is this your will?!
Is this what you really wanted?!
[NANBU] There she is!
We can see the Earth!
[OKITA]
Doctor Sado.
[DR. SADO]
Hmm?
Would you... mind
leaving me for a moment?
I'd like to be alone.
[OKITA]
One more thing, Doctor.
[DR. SADO]
Ah?
[OKITA]
Thank you.
[DR. SADO whimpers]
[door creaks, shuts]
[OKITA]
My dear mother Earth.
How I've missed you.
Seeing you brings back
so many memories.
The Cosmo Reverse
System rebooted.
And I think it's reactivating.
What do you think happened, sir?
I don't know. Perhaps...
We're witnessing a miracle.
[NIIMI]
Mamoru!
[MAMORU]
Goodbye, Sanada.
Goodbye, Kaoru.
[gasps, yells]
[gasping]
Guess stuff like this
really does happen.
I'm so happy!
[sobs]
And so am I.
[SHIMA]
Welcome back.
Or make that welcome home.
--Mori!
--[laughter]
[YAMAMOTO] I think
I can speak for all of us.
[gasps]
Welcome back, Lieutenant Mori.
[MISAKI whimpers]
Thank you all.
[gasps]
[DR. SADO whimpers]
[sobs]