[DESLER] What point is there
in clinging to this planet?
[GHADER] We'll be entering
the atmosphere shortly, sir.
Please return inside.
[clang, creak]
[GIMLEH] My secret police
are confident they've found
all subversive elements who were
allied with Zoellik, my lord.
[CELESTRA] The purging
will be completed very soon.
I'm sorry for what
I had to put you through,
my loyal space wolf.
Don't be.
Well, the important thing is
your rule is once again
secure, my lord.
Do you honestly think
we can call it "secure"
when the bulk
of our fleet has been
stranded 90 days away?
Oh! That's not what I--
So there's nothing we can do?
It will take them three
months to get back home?
Balun is located at the center
of the Geschtam Gates--
the hub that connected the two
sides of the network together.
The enemy's attack has
caused the gates on our side
to stop functioning,
and with most of our ships
still out there.
[DOMEL grunts]
[GHADER] Since the Yamato
made it through before
the gates shut down,
it is now impossible
for our primary fleet
to catch up to them
with normal Geschtam navigation.
My lord.
Issue the order,
and I'll leave at once.
I will sink that ship myself.
You really think you can?
Even if it kills me.
We can give you the ideal
crew for this mission, General.
If you succeed in
destroying the Yamato ,
we'll see to it that
your wife's punishment
is significantly reduced.
Thank you for the offer,
sir. I will not fail.
Now then, there's just
one more thing, Elk.
Call it a personal request.
[DOMEL]
Mm.
[YAMAMOTO]
I see you snuck out of medical.
Makoto's looking
all over for you.
[SHINOHARA] That's where you
launch from, huh? Pretty cool.
So what, you come up here
to retrieve me?
Heh. More or less.
[YAMAMOTO] Shinohara,
you were in the same squadron
as my brother Akio, right?
[SHINOHARA]
Yeah. He was a good man.
That "Sword Three" call sign.
I know it's what
he used to use, too.
Uh!
[chuckles]
Did he? Oh, yeah.
Then I guess it was
a subtle tribute.
Subtle was always his style.
Some things are better implied.
[YAMAMOTO]
A different galaxy.
We've come a long way,
haven't we.
[SHINOHARA]
Yeah. We have.
[NIIMI] Congratulations.
You were right.
I never expected
we'd get this far.
[SHIMA] I don't know if
"right" is the way I'd put it.
People could view
that different ways.
But there is only one reality.
And the reality is that
yes, we made it.
[HOSHINA]
What are you looking at?
The stars.
[HOSHINA] That's the Tarantula
Nebula. Impressive, huh?
[MISAKI]
Beyond it lies Iscandar.
I thought I'd be
coming home with Sasha,
but now she's gone.
Yurisha.
[gasps]
It's dangerous out here.
I'm sorry, Hoshina.
[HOSHINA gasps]
Yuria Misaki is thinking
about how much she wishes
you would hug her
in this moment.
Can you explain this "hug"?
[HEYDELN] An Iscandarian
onboard the Yamato ?
Do you really believe that?
[DOMEL] Remember when
Celestra went to Balun?
[HEYDELN]
Yes, wasn't she investigating
the Aquarius ruins?
Somehow she used them
to infiltrate the Yamato
and come back with that intel.
She did what? Is that possible?
Well, she is a
Jirel witch, after all.
Point is, I've been given
another mission because of it.
We're landing the ship.
Prepare to roll out!
♪
[HEYDELN] Looks like nothin'
but a bunch of children
and old men to me.
This is what Hyss
calls the ideal crew?
They're only supplying us
with four carriers?
No whining, Berger.
Imperial Guard controls
the Homeland Defense Fleets
and claims they're
already stretched thin.
They won't give us any more.
--Yeah, yeah.
--[gasps] Barlen!
Uh! Heydeln!
[chuckles]
I figured you were
dead by now!
Same to you, pal.
You look like hell!
[DOMEL] You fought
in the Gorni Campaign.
Yes, and proudly, sir.
We have old ships and
young recruits. Can they fight?
You once said there's
nothing like a battlefield
to turn children into men.
They'll learn quick, sir.
Yes, true enough.
[BARLEN]
Zar Belk!
[HEYDELN]
Attention!
[SOLDIERS stomp]
[DOMEL] Flaken. I may need
your help once again.
The air in Baleras
is like poison.
I would jump at the chance.
Thank you.
[BERGER gasps]
Second-class Gamilan troops?
They're volunteers
from planet Zaltz.
Which means losing's
in their blood.
They're from the same
planet as Commander Shultz.
We're from the 442nd.
Specialized Warfare
Group B, General.
This mission is vital to
the empire and comes with
a great deal of risk, soldier.
You understand that, yes?
Yes, we do, General.
We live to serve Gamilas.
Ha! Can we really
trust these savages?
[gasps]
Heh.
[ORTSCHETT] ♪ Our home, noble,
mighty, strong and true, ♪
[ALL] ♪ World of majesty
with her blossoms blue! ♪
♪ Sing with joy and overcome! ♪
♪ May the grace of the gods
who look down from above ♪
♪ Ever march to our drum! ♪
[ALL]
♪ Garle Gamilas! ♪
♪ Glory be with us! ♪
♪ Eternal glory! ♪
[NANBU] Wave Motion Gun
inspection complete.
All weapons personnel
report to superior officer.
[OKITA]
Mm.
[NANBU] Keeping this pristine
is your top priority.
We'll beat the Gamilans every
time as long as we have this.
Oh! Captain.
Can we help with something, sir?
[OKITA]
No. It's nothing.
What's wrong with him?
Beats me.
Huh?
[door hisses]
We need to talk
about that device.
You have created a tool of war.
Wave Motion Energy was not
meant to be a weapon.
You're corrupting its purpose.
It is meant as a bridge of hope.
When we gave you the plans,
our intention was that
you would use it
to cross the stars to Iscandar,
and nothing more.
[OKITA] It's a journey of
168,000 light-years.
We had no chance of making it
without protection
from the Gamilans.
[MISAKI]
And so, from our gift of peace,
Sanada forged this weapon.
Huh?
[MISAKI] But that's the same
justification the Gamilans use.
You claim the Wave Motion Gun
is only for protection.
But will it always be?
Have faith in our people.
We'll prove it.
[MISAKI] "Why?"
You must be eager to ask.
Why did we bring you
plans for the engine,
instead of bringing you
the Cosmo Reverser itself?
Maybe because you
wanted to see if we're
worthy of salvation.
It's a test.
That's why you're here.
My role is to aid.
And to observe you.
My sister, Starsha.
She is the one who will decide.
[OKITA] Then I hope you'll
watch us closely, Yurisha.
See if this crew--
no, if the human race
is worth saving
based on everything that we do.
[MALE CARRIER OPERATOR 19A]
Once the weapons are aboard
the Domelaze, Seventh
Maintenance Company is to
immediately begin loading
fighters onto the Balgrey.
[VELTE] It's only a prototype,
and a top-secret one at that.
It wasn't easy convincing
Weapons Research
to let you have it.
[DOMEL]
I'm grateful for it.
[VELTE chuckles]
It's fine.
By now I'm used to
your requests.
My biggest struggle is
simply trying to figure out
what you're
planning to do with it.
Whoa, look at that thing!
I thought it was a drill
for asteroid mining. Why are we
loading it in like a bomb?
Beats me. I'll never
understand the higher-ups.
[AFC OFFICER 19C]
This is ridiculous!
[AFC OFFICER 19A]
Lieutenant Commander!
[AFC OFFICER 19D]
...hero, not a criminal!
Stay calm, soldiers, it's fine.
I've done nothing wrong,
and they'll see that
as soon as they finish
their investigation.
They've got Helder! Ugh!
[AFC OFFICER 19A]
Where are you taking him?
Ugh!
[AFC OFFICER 19B]
Lieutenant Commander!
While we're out risking our
lives to keep the empire safe,
this is what's really
going on back home.
Who are you people?
You're Lower Storm
Leader Ditz, correct?
[SANADA] The Tarantula Nebula,
on the edge of
the Large Magellanic
Cloud galaxy.
It's a vast and
perilous expanse filled with
interstellar medium
and strong ion storms.
These seven stars
are in an open cluster
at the nebula's heart.
For brevity's sake we're calling
them the Rainbow Cluster,
and weaving around their gravity
wells is our fastest course.
Down side? Navigating
through this cluster
would also mean dealing
with degenerate stars.
And strong relativistic jets
that are hard to predict.
It's the fastest way
and the most dangerous.
We're already
running into issues
with the Cosmo Radar, Captain.
Can't we just
warp past this mess?
[OTA] Even at our
maximum warp distance,
we couldn't jump past it.
It's too big.
[KODAI] Hm. Another crucible.
It could wreck the ship.
Yes. That's why I've
charted a longer course
that goes around it.
[GETTO] This is the path we
believe the Yamato will take
to reach the Salezar sytem.
[KRAITZE]
The quickest route would be
that nebula's central cluster.
But heading through those
storms and interference
would be suicide. The Terons
can't be that stupid.
If they do plan
to avoid the cluster,
there are only a handful of
other routes that make sense.
[OKITA] No. Our Balun
maneuver bought us time,
but that doesn't mean
we're safe.
We can't afford to take
the longer route.
We'd lose what we gained.
And give the Gamilans time
to hit us with a counterattack.
And the enemy is highly
unlikely to anticipate us
taking this path, which would
play in our favor as well.
[OKITA]
Mm.
We'll continue through
this Rainbow Cluster
and onward to Iscandar.
Maintain ship-wide alert status
until we've made it
to the other side.
And I want eyes on
the anti-air scanners.
♪
[BALGREY CM 19A]
Balgrey ready to launch.
[LAMBEA CM 19A]
Lambea ready to launch.
[SCHDERG CM 19A]
Shderg ready to launch.
[DAUROLD CM 19A]
Daurold ready to launch.
General. All ships
ready to roll out.
Launch all ships now.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 19A]
Fleet is passing second Baleras.
This is General Domel,
announcing course for fleet.
Flight plan 728. We're going
to the central cluster.
He can't be serious?
Come on!
[HEYDELN]
You really think they'll risk
flying through
those hazards, General?
[DOMEL]
Oh, they'll risk it.
This is the same captain
who chose to charge
through our fleet
not once, but twice.
If he's the man I think he is,
he won't be stopped by a storm.
[ALL grunt]
High-density ionized gas!
Switching helm to manual!
Interference causing
radar and sensors to fail!
Switching to optic mode!
So we'll have to
rely on optics, huh?
Yeah, that's right, buddy--
just like the old sailing ships.
[OKITA] If the enemy is the same
commander we faced before...
[beeping]
[FLAKEN]
Nasty storm up there, Heini.
Too bad for them!
[KIEL]
Ship detected at nine o'clock.
[FLAKEN]
There you are.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 19A]
Message from the Hound:
"The prey is in
the lost forest."
[HEYDELN] Seems you were
right about them, sir.
Yes.
Commence operation immediately.
Attack Force Group One,
prepare fighters
and launch when ready.
[GETTO] Captain.
I'll be counting on you.
Good luck, Deputy Commander.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 19C]
Seventy gek to operation area.
[KOBASHI] You think they'll
attack in a storm like this?
We won't have Shino
backing us up.
[DAIKUHARA]
Don't be scared, Kobashi.
[KOBASHI]
I'm not scared!
[DAIKUHARA]
Well, you shouldn't be.
If there's a fight,
I'll fly so pretty
you won't even notice he's gone.
Heh. I'm gonna hold you
to that, Daikuhara.
[KATO]
Can it, Sawamura.
Sorry, sir.
[KATO] If the Gamis attack
under these conditions,
we'll be the only ones
who can protect the ship.
[SAWAMURA] Are we still leaving
Lady Bull's-Eye behind?
[KATO]
Yeah. She's our ace in the hole.
Why are they
trusting those aliens?
It's a trap, and we'll die.
We're all gonna die!
[OTA] Breaking through
turbulence layer.
[sighs]
It's actually
smooth sailing up here.
There's something
on radar, sir.
It looks like an enemy
fighter formation,
27 light-seconds away.
All crew to battle stations!
To battle stations! Fighter
group, proceed with launch!
Of course they're coming.
And with them comes war.
One Hundred, Kato.
Launching now.
Fighter squadron
has launched, sir.