[DESLER]
I see.
So the Iscandarians had it.
[chirps]
Yes.
Mirenel gave up her life
for that information.
[DESLER]
Another Jirel has fallen.
That makes you the last one.
[BLUE BIRD chirps]
And I've not forgotten you saved
me from sharing their fate.
Even if I am the last of us.
[chirps]
I shall always remain
loyal to you, my lord.
Loyalty is a precious thing.
[GIMLEH] So you're telling me
you chose to retreat,
because you were unable to deal
with a single, native rebellion?
[DROPPE]
They surrounded the capital!
W-We had to leave, there was
nothing else we could do!
Director-General Gimleh,
please use your fleet
to protect our people
who couldn't evacuate!
Heh. We will bathe
this planet in fire.
[gasps]
[GIMLEH] A world that
rebels against our Lord
sets a dangerous example.
We cannot allow such a blight
to exist in our Empire.
No more than we can allow
the existence of a governor
who lets that blight spread.
Is that some kind of joke?
[DROPPE gasps, groans]
[GIMLEH sips]
I've never been a fan of comedy.
Now, then. Let the
symphony of death begin!
[TECH OFFICER 15A]
That's the recoil brake
for the gravity anchor.
Make sure it's fastened tight.
[TECH OFFICER 15B]
Hey.
What are you doin'
all the way down here?
[MISAKI]
This mechanism. What is it?
Uh, what?
Uh, what are you talkin' about?
It's the Wave Motion Gun.
[MISAKI]
Uh...
But what is that?
[SHINOHARA]
Complex stuff, huh?
Leave it to the mechanics
to figure out.
I'm her pilot.
I wanna make sure
she's taken care of.
It sounds like you're
forming quite the bond.
[YAMAMOTO]
That doesn't look right.
--[footsteps]
--[SHINOHARA] Uh?
Hey, Kodai!
Still haven't let that go, huh?
Of course not!
Next time maybe
I'll fly a fighter
and you'll wish that
I was in the wing, too!
[KODAI] We thought leaving the
Milky Way would help,
but we're seeing
the enemy even more.
There's no time to play around.
[MORI]
Who's playing? I'm serious!
Teach me to fly,
then maybe I can help!
[KODAI]
Mm?
[SHINOHARA groaning]
Ow.
[KODAI]
Shinohara!
[SHINOHARA groans]
[KODAI]
What's goin' on with her?
Actually she's got
a lot going on, sir.
Which you'd notice, if you
ever took off your blinders.
[KODAI]
Uh? What's he talking about?
--[alarm blares]
--[BOTH gasp]
[AIHARA]
All crew to battle stations.
Again?
[AIHARA] Repeat, all crew
to battle stations.
--[COMBAT OFFICER 15A] Go!
--[NAV. OFFICER 15A] Hurry!
[AIHARA]
Scramble all available fighters.
All pilots to cockpits.
Catapult crew,
prepare to launch.
Repeat: catapult crew,
Two enemy cruisers, sir.
I'll take over.
Uh, of course, ma'am.
Do you think it's another
reconnaissance team?
You'll have to ask the enemy.
All crew, stand by at battle
stations and prepare for attack.
[MORI]
Distance: nine megameters.
Speed: unchanged.
Closing to eight.
[MORI gasps]
[MORI]
They're turning around!
It's been one cancelled
alarm after another!
How are we supposed to
get any rest if we don't--
--[thud]
--[GROUP] Huh?
[NEMOTO]
What's with her?
Well I can hardly blame
her for being upset.
[SHINOHARA chuckles]
She's goin' through some stuff.
[HIRATA] It's still going
to take more time
to get the O.M.C.S. back online.
We need to find
more food and water.
Or we'll be at risk of
running out of our supplies.
Yeah, but where are we
supposed to do that?
We're between galaxies.
There aren't any systems
anywhere close.
[NIIMI]
There's one.
According to the map
provided by Iscandar,
there's an inter-galactic
star system roughly
four light-years ahead of
our current position.
The star's name: Beemela.
Beemela, huh?
Observation indicates
the system's fourth planet
is likely an Earth-type world,
well within the habitable zone.
Sounds perfect.
[NIIMI] We've been stuck
in this ship for too long.
Many of our crew are
showing signs of stress,
which negatively
affects performance.
I think landing there
might be good
for their mental health as well.
[SANADA]
Hm.
[KODAI] Shima. You're the
navigator, what do you think?
Yeah. We could swing it.
[KODAI] It's not gonna
mess up our schedule?
[SHIMA]
No. We'll be okay.
[KODAI]
All right, then.
[ITO chuckles]
[OBAMA]
This is rough.
I'm gonna go mad if we have to
keep eating this every day.
My sleep has been
pretty crummy, too.
You think Iscandar
really exists,
or are we going through
this for nothing?
Gimme a break.
[HARADA]
It's true!
--[YABU] Huh?
--[KATO] What?
Everyone's talking about
this beautiful ghost lady
who keeps popping up
on the ship!
That Hayashi guy from
navigation saw her, too!
Then it must be true.
But wait, it gets even juicier!
Some people think she's
really an alien lifeform!
[sighs]
[HARADA]
Mm.
Hey, what are you doing?
You look exhausted.
I was just seeing
if you have a fever.
[SAOTOME] I can't live on this!
I need more food!
I'm sorry but the
O.M.C.S. is down.
It's the best we can do for now.
[sighs] I think
we're all exhausted.
[sighs]
[CIC OFFICER 15A]
Food directly affects morale.
[YABU]
Honestly, guys,
I'm starting to wonder
if we're gonna make it.
[coughs]
Oh, Misaki!
You haven't broadcast
your show lately--
Okay. Nevermind then.
[MISAKI]
Tell me.
Is the Wave Motion Gun based
on a specific solution
of the Buchinsky
Wave Motion formula?
[SANADA] Huh?
You've done your homework.
Yes, that's right. Using a
specific solution allows us to
release part of a miniaturized
Calabi-Yau manifold.
And have you created
safeguards to guarantee
that this released
energy is proportional
to the space-time
supersymmetry moduli?
[SANADA]
Mm-mm. No.
There's no need for
any safeguards.
It's not linked to the
supersymmetry moduli.
At the gun's core,
we're dealing with
a miniaturized
superstring landscape.
But if that's the case,
couldn't that cause the
superstring vacuum to dissipate?
And that could tear
the universe apart.
[gasps]
[HOSHINA]
Yuria!
Come on, let's go.
[OTA chuckles]
[whimpers]
The collapse of a Euclidean
two-dimensional black hole, huh.
Never even considered that.
[OTA]
I'm lovin' her new hairstyle.
She looks great!
Uh, wait, did she do
something to her hair?
It's the way he thinks.
I'm certain of it.
[HOSHINA]
Uh?
If a weapon of mass destruction
like the Wave Motion Gun
is possible, then he
must have designed it.
[GOER] Our Lord Supreme
is coming here, to Balun,
for an inspection?
[DOMEL]
Yes.
Admiral Ditz tells me
he's coming in secret.
Well! Then we'll have to
organize a proper reception!
If we really want to
demonstrate our loyalty to him,
we should focus on
destroying the Yamato .
Our force recon's probably
run them ragged by now
with all their prodding.
Then it's the perfect
time to strike!
According to the intel reports,
the Yamato has changed course
and is headed for
the Beemela system.
[DOMEL]
Indeed.
And this neutron star,
Carell One-Six-Three,
stands between them and Beemela.
They'll have to jump
again to get there,
and when they do the
neutron star's gravity well
will interfere with
their navigation.
That will cause them to Geschtam
out at one of these five points.
And that's when
we'll launch our attack.
We'll divide the fleet
to these five locations,
then as soon as one of us
engages the Yamato ,
we'll reassemble
and destroy them.
Questions?
[GROUP]
Zar Belk!
[MONK gasps]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 15A]
Stop! Running is useless!
Don't even think of
the rebels as people.
They're a pestilence,
nothing more.
If they resist, kill them!
[REBEL 15A pants]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 15B]
This is it.
[IMPERIAL GUARD 15A]
I saw them run in here.
Prepare an assault.
[IMPERIAL GUARD 15B] Sir!
Look who's house this is!
[BRIDGE OFFICER 11A] All
ships ready to launch, General.
Very well. Move out!
[NIIMI] Before this, she worked
in the Joint Staff Operations,
Division Nine.
Notable, considering
that's where they
came up with
the Yamato Plan.
This says she joined
the department
on September Seventh of '98.
Admiral Hijikata
recommended her.
[ITO]
Hijikata...
Both of her parents
are deceased,
and for the year
before we launched
the admiral had been
serving as her guardian.
He helped her while she
convalesced from an injury.
For the past year, huh?
No siblings listed.
Her father was
the Undersecretary
of Foreign Affairs.
[ITO]
Hijikata?
Yeah, I can seem him doing it.
[NIIMI]
Huh?
[ITO]
Altering her records.
[NIIMI]
You're not serious!
Yes. In fact I am.
Got another hunch?
[ITO]
Something like that.
Why are you interested
in her, anyway?
Maybe it's a crush?
[ITO]
You don't need to know why.
[NIIMI grunts]
In other news, our next
stop looks promising.
[ITO] If that's true, then we're
going to be very busy soon.
Now here's another
hunch for you.
Keep your distance from the XO,
he won't be sympathetic.
But we do need someone else
on the bridge as insurance.
Leave that to me.
I know just where to go.
[door opens]
[SHIMA] That you, Hayashi?
I've got that data input.
Huh?
Thought you'd like some.
[SHIMA]
Thanks.
Of course.
So how are things looking?
Can we still make it in time?
[SHIMA sips]
Yeah. We'll be fine.
Just barely.
You're a terrible liar.
I'd know.
I am a counselor.
The success of this voyage
depends on you, Lieutenant.
You're the most important
person on this ship.
[HOSHINA]
Chief of Navigation.
[gasps]
Please, sir.
May I have a word with you?
[BRIDGE OFFICER 15A]
Linking with system satellites,
and opening
Geschtam Gates to Balun.
Commencing entry in 20 gek.
[CAPTAIN 15A]
Lord Desler.
Our vessels are about to
enter the Geschtam Gate,
right on schedule, sir.
We'll arrive at Balun shortly.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 15A]
Problem in main engine.
Pressure is rising fast.
At this rate it will
overboost, sir!
Isolate chamber and stabilize!
[ZOELLIK] What do you mean
our great leader isn't here?!
How are we supposed to
draw our plans without him?!
And you, Ditz!
Why are you the only one
in Imperial Command
who knew about
this foolhardy trip?
It's hardly the first time
our Supreme Lord
has acted on a whim.
Sounds to me like
the Inspector-General
has hurt feelings because
he wasn't in on the secret.
You sound rather pleased
with yourself, Gimleh.
You handle one rebellion and now
you think you can mouth off?
I more than "handled" Alteria.
I destroyed it.
Your Imperial Guard
goes too far!
[CELESTRA]
I disagree.
We cannot maintain peace
throughout the empire
unless the systems
are afraid of us.
[GIMLEH]
Hm...
It's true that rebellions have
cropped up everywhere
since the Yamato appeared and
news of its defiance has spread.
But this makes it worse!
We pure bloods are
the only ones who matter!
I won't waste my time
worrying about
the happiness of the barbarians.
No more than I'm going to listen
to their advice on this counsel.
[door hisses]
[HYSS] Silence, everyone!
Something terrible's happened!
Our leader's command vessel has
just exploded at the Gate!
Lord Desler has
been assassinated!
[BRIDGE OFFICER 11A]
Message from a scout ship.
They've got the Yamato
in their sights, sir.
Order the scouts to launch
an attack against the Yamato .
See if we can force
them to jump.
[OTA] No obstacles
detected in warp path.
And what about
that neutron star?
It'll affect our course,
but we should still get closer.
All crewmembers prepare to warp.
[gasps] Radar activity sir.
It appears to be
two enemy vessels
approaching from the rear.
Their speed is
seven space knots.
[NANBU chuckles]
Sounds like more recon trying
to mess with our heads.
Damage to port side!
Should we return fire, sir?
Negative, we will
proceed with warp.
But sir!
What are we going to do if
they damage our warp engine?
Without sufficient supplies
it would be folly to engage.
[SHIMA]
XO!
That neutron star
will affect our warp.
I'm not sure where
we're going to end up!
Compensate as best you can,
just get us out of here!
Navigation, report!
[OTA] Neutron star
is at 10 o'clock, sir!
[SANADA]
So it did affect us.
[MORI gasps]
We have multiple sightings!
There's an enemy
fleet off our bow!
They're behind us, too!
They've got us completely
surrounded, sir!
[GOER] So that's
where it dumped them!
With their feeble minds
they prob'ly had no idea
such predictions were possible!
Fell right into our trap.
Order all ships to rendezvous.
Scramble all available fighters.
--[OKITA] Wait.
--Uh?
[OKITA] There's not enough
time to use the falcons.
The enemy guns would
just pick them off
while they're trying to launch.
Captain!
We'll fire up the Wave Motion
Shields at maximum power.
And then charge straight ahead
at combat speed two.
We'll break through their line.
Sir!
Sir! There's a
Super-Dreadnought Class ship
positioned directly ahead of us!
No one said it would be easy,
but we'll never make it out
if we don't take the risk!
[OTA]
Keel shield under attack!
Open all torpedo
tubes on the bow!
Deflection ability of
shields decreasing!
If we keep taking these hits,
they're gonna break through!
We'll strike at the
center of their line
and try to punch a hole in it.
Concentrate all fire
to the front!
Let's give 'em all we've got!
[BRIDGE OFFICER 11A]
16-0-4 has been hit.
Have them fall back and switch
positions with the next ship.
Wave Motion Shields
are now critical!
We're about to lose them!
[OKITA grunts]
The Yamato has just broken
through our front line, sir!
They're approaching us now!
Impressive.
A truly worthy opponent.
What now, Commander?
Open all forward gunports!
Destroy the Yamato !
Come on, come on!
[CREW grunts]
Engine Room!
What just happened?
--Why did we lose our thrust?
--Gunport One is down, Captain!
Radar is offline!
[OKITA] Switch over to
inertial navigation!
We can't slow down!
Right now we're only
focused on one ship!
Ram it if you have to,
just get passed!
Right. Here goes!
[SHIMA grunts]
Evasive maneuvers!
Hold position!
The Domelaze does not retreat!
Fire!
Now full speed ahead!
It's time to shake them off!
Battle stations!
[BERGER] There she is!
There's our beautiful prey.
[HEYDELN]
Cut the chatter, fool!
Second squad. In position sir!
The next move will be checkmate.
[DOMEL] Flying Squadron Three,
strike their right side.
Commander Domel.
There's a message
from the home world.
I'll hear it later.
[GOER] But it's a message
from Lord Desler's office,
priority class one!
From Lord Desler's office?
Secondary Gunport Two, report!
What's going on?
[OTA]
We can't take much more!
[TOKUGAWA]
Engine output is dropping!
[KODAI] Torpedoes! What are
you doing? Return fire!
[DOMEL]
Come home?
But, what kind of
order is that, sir?
The Yamato is in my grasp.
Do not question me, Commander.
Withdraw the full fleet
and return to the home
planet immediately.
This takes precedence
over all else.
You will obey.
[DOMEL growls]
[GOER chuckles]
[NANBU]
We've lost another cannon!
[OTA]
Damage control can't keep up!
[NANBU]
Agh! It's hopeless!
Damn it!
We're gonna die out here!
Control yourself!
We can't give up!
[OKITA]
Hmm?
What the--?
[ANALYZER]
Enemy vessels are warping away.
[ANALYZER] All enemies
have evacuated the area.
What's going on?
They were so close
to destroying us.
Why stop?
[OKITA] Something must've
happened to pull them back.
But the question is... what?