[DESLER speaking Gamilan]
[cheering]
[CITIZENS speaking Gamilan]
[speaking Gamilan]
[DESLER]
You wrote a good speech.
[CELESTRA]
You honor me, my lord.
[DESLER] My people are such
foolish, submissive creatures.
And they bore me to death.
That's their gravest flaw.
Well, your post-speech
entertainment
should be a cure for that.
[DESLER]
You mean that ship?
Yes, sir.
[DESLER]
Hmph.
[applause]
Your lordship,
on behalf of everyone here,
I congratulate you.
Today marks 1,000 years
of Gamilan history
and the 103 year of your reign.
Why thank you, Viceroy Hyss.
The Great Gamilas Empire
has successfully united
the Large and Small
Magellanic Cloud galaxies,
and now reaches
into the Milky Way,
expanding your territory
with each new day.
Your glory shines bright, like
a beacon across the Universe.
Your unification policy
is working as well, sir.
Thanks to your wisdom,
those who submit have
been allowed to join us
instead of facing eradication.
And now they contribute to the
cause as second-class citizens.
[ZOELLIK]
Glory to our supreme lord!
His deeds are more fit for a
righteous god than a mortal!
I praise him!
No enemy in the cosmos can
withstand our military power!
Gamilas is invincible!
We will never be defeated!
[DITZ]
Arrogance is a mistake!
We must always remain vigilant.
We still have invaders
in the Small Cloud.
Boasts won't stop them.
Admiral!
Am I mistaken, or did
you just call me a braggart?
As leader of the fleets,
I merely speak the truth.
Take it however you want.
Your lordship.
We have come up with a plan
to eliminate the
barbarian invaders.
Senior General Domel
is headed there now.
Oh really, you've
sent the Space Wolf?
That's good; he can show
the rest of you how it's done.
Now, let's move on to the fun.
I've prepared some entertainment
to help with morale.
I know your jobs
can be so stressful.
Tonight, comrades,
you'll be watching video
from the front lines
of our war in the
galactic hinterlands.
And what are we
going to see there?
[CELESTRA]
Our lord has devised a trap.
And you will have the privilege
of watching as it's sprung.
All right, shall we?
Let the little game begin.
[MISAKI] Like the old
refrain tells us, listeners,
when you wish upon a star,
you really can ask for anything.
All that matters is
how much you want it.
If your heart is
truly committed,
then the heavens will look
down on you, and be kind.
No matter how impossible it
seems, fate can show us a way.
[sighs]
And that's it for Radio Yamato!
Our next broadcast
will be at ship time 2030.
so make sure you tune in!
Signing off.
This has been Yuria Misaki!
[ENGINEER]
And that's a wrap!
[MISAKI] You sure it's cool
for you to be killing time
with me like this?
Yeah.
I'm off duty right now.
[MISAKI]
Mm-hmm
[HOSHINA]
Hey, you hear the rumor?
Huh?
There's a door up
here that never opens.
And supposedly the ghost
of a beautiful woman lives
on the other side of it.
Pretty spooky, right?
Big deal.
I've seen plenty of ghosts.
Huh?
Back on Earth, they
appeared to me all the time.
Ah! Ah! Um... Seriously?
[OTA]
Current position.
Eight light years from Earth
in the Sirius star system.
Cruising at 18 space-knots.
We'll be attempting 12 more
light years with our next warp.
That would get us
to Gliese 581, Captain.
Twelve more light years huh?
That would make this
our last chance to see Earth
through the Yamato 's
deep-space telescope
before we're out of range.
Put her up.
[SANADA]
Yes, sir.
[KODAI]
Whoa.
[NANBU]
That's Earth?
That's right.
We're now eight-point-six
light years away.
So actually,
that's how the Earth
looked over eight years ago.
Before she was massacred
when the Gamilans attacked.
[OKITA]
Take a long look, everyone.
This is what we're fighting for.
The Earth that used to be.
The Earth we can reclaim.
Shima.
Prepare the ship for warp.
[SHIMA]
Aye-aye, Captain.
Preparing now.
[OPERATOR B]
The Yamato has jumped.
Identify the jump coordinates!
[OPERATOR B] Calculating
space-time wave motion.
[OPERATOR C]
Tracing space wake.
[OPERATOR A]
Deputy Commander!
One of our own resupply ships
is requesting a rendezvous.
Daddy, hi!
Finish your assignment soon.
I can't wait to see you!
Mom's worried, as usual,
but you know Mom.
I'm sure you're just fine.
My choices are clear.
Our only options
are victory or death.
Sorry, Hilde. This is it.
[GANZ] Commander! General Goer
has sent a resupply!
[SHULTZ]
Huh... Huh?!
A resupply?
You're sure?
[GANZ]
Yes, Commander!
We're not abandoned after all!
Lord Desler!
As your chosen commander
of this galactic theater.
It is my highest honor
to be supervising this
grand operation that you,
in your infinite brilliance
and glory, have designed!
That's quite enough.
Just tell me.
Did you get the special
package I sent you, Goer?
Yes! I was just getting to that!
You mean the new torpedo, sir?
The Desler Torpedo.
Yes, the Desler Torpedo!
We've already deployed it
to the front, just as you asked!
[MORI]
Warp complete.
We are now in the
Gliese 581 system, sir.
Perfect.
We're now 20.4 light years out.
And there's Gliese 581,
an M-class red dwarf.
[DR. SADO]
Hm...
Looks like that warp didn't
have any negative effects.
But don't get complacent,
this doesn't mean
you're in the clear.
[NIIMI]
This is Lieutenant Niimi.
I'm coming in.
[DR. SADO]
Well, take care.
On to the next patient, Doctor.
Is this a good time?
Good as any.
How can I help?
As I'm sure you know, sir,
this system has a planet
suitable for human colonization.
I'd like to deploy a ground team
to investigate it
more extensively.
We don't have time
for that, Lieutenant.
I'm well aware of our
misson's time constraints.
But we're humankind's last hope.
Captain, don't you
think it's our duty
to keep all options
on the table?
Look, Niimi.
The Izumo Plan was scrapped;
we're moving on.
But, sir! If we...
[NANBU]
The port side has taken a hit!
[SHIMA]
Righting the ship.
Fifteen degrees!
Some electrical systems offline!
[ANALYZER] Detecting powerful
charged-particle wave motion.
[SHIMA]
Slowing speed.
Red 20!
That's odd.
[OKITA]
XO, report!
It appears that we've run into
a hyper-dense plasma
filament field, Captain.
Filament field? What's that?
He's describing a
thick stream of plasma flares
emitted by a star.
[SANADA]
A solar storm, in other words.
It looks like our ship has run
into the edge of
a plasma corridor.
But it doesn't seem normal.
Birkeland currents are
several hundred million times
their predicted values.
And what does this mean?
It means this
didn't occur naturally.
Someone created it.
[GOER]
The vermin is in the trap!
I'm astonished you
could predict the Terons
would come to this
system, Lord Desler!
Your genius is
as impressive as ever!
Please.
Analyzing their ship's course
was an amusing
distraction for me.
But the real fun
is just starting.
My dear comrades,
let us toast to the Terons
and wish them well
in this challenge.
[GOEHIN chortles]
Hilarious, sir!
Set a trap and then goad
your prey on as they squirm!
I've always enjoyed playing
with my food, as well!
[chortles]
[screams]
Gamilas has no need
for such disgusting men.
[ALL]
Garle Desler!
Hail our Supreme Lord!
[SANADA] All of our electrical
systems are back online.
But, sir, we can't bear much
more contact with those fields.
[OKITA] Analyze the
field around the ship.
Let's find a weak point
in that corridor.
There's bound to
be a gap somewhere.
Huh?!
[MORI]
I've got something.
The plasma reading is
lower at three o'clock.
It looks like
a weak point to me.
Picking up a distortion in
the gravity field behind us.
Something's warping out!
[OKITA]
Hmm?
[OPERATOR A]
Tube is loaded!
Desler Torpedo Fire!
[MORI]
Enemy ship has fired torpedo!
It will be too close to
intercept in 20 seconds!
[KODAI]
Target locked.
AA Systems armed!
[AIHARA]
Prepare to intercept torpedo!
[MORI] Thirteen seconds
remaining to intercept
and counting down.
Ten, nine, eight...
Captain, quick!
[MORI]
...six, five, four, three...
Return fire using
stern side cannons!
Fire!
Confirmed.
Target has been hit
and destroyed.
[MORI]
Wait a minute!
What the...?
[SHULTZ]
What's happening out there?
[OPERATOR A] Transmitting
video to Imperial Command.
[gasping]
[ZOELLIK]
What in the world is that?
Do you like it?
That is the Desler
Torpedo in action.
Bizarre.
Is that gas, Lord Desler?
It's indigenous
to the Mirbelia system.
It's not just a gas
but a gas-based life form.
It's self-replicating
and thrives in space,
converting and absorbing
material energy
to fuel it's
indefinite expansion.
The ultimate,
natural chemical weapon.
Now that the rat's in the trap.
Let's see what happens if we
should throw in a cat as well.
[OTA] Whatever that is,
it's expanding sir!
Just keep tracking it, ensign.
[SANADA]
It's breaking down the plasma
and absorbing it like fuel.
If we can't outrun it,
there's a good chance
it'll do the same to us.
[OKITA]
Hmmm...
[MORI] Unidentified
object gaining on us!
It seems your trapped prey's
about to reach a dead end.
Now we simply wait for the
cat to catch it in its claws.
No.
I've prepared an exit for them.
Shima, can you make
it through that weak point
we found in the plasma?
[SHIMA]
I think so, Captain.
Wait a minute.
If we keep going
in that direction...
You're kidding me.
[DESLER] However, a tenacious
little star waits at that exit,
its fiery jaws open wide.
So will they be
consumed by the gas?
Or disintegrated in
a burning fusion reactor?
Or might they surprise me
and find a third path?
There is no third path, sir.
It's perfect.
Well done.
Comrades.
Let us all applaud the brave
decision they're about to make.
I'm sure it won't be
easy for them.
Can't go back; can't go forward.
So what are we
supposed to do now?
Shima.
Full speed ahead
toward the star, hurry!
But, sir, that's suicide!
Full speed ahead, sir!
Steady as she goes!
[DESLER]
That didn't take them long.
It appears the Terons
have chosen death by fire.
[applause]
[OTA] Temperature outside:
1150 degrees.
Inside: 90 and rising, sir!
Climate control failing.
The system can't take it!
Captain.
I suggest engaging the
Wave Motion Shields.
We're quickly
approaching the limit
of what the Yamato can handle.
We can't afford shields.
Order all crew into space suits.
Reduce energy output to
bare minimum as we advance.
Seal bulkheads,
blast shields down.
What about that Gamilan ship?
It's staying behind the gas.
Eight megameters.
It's following us, sir.
[OKITA]
Hmm...
Keep a close eye on it.
[OKITA groans]
[MORI]
Huh?
Captain!
[DR. SADO]
This is bad!
[HARADA]
Doctor, you need to wear this!
[DR. SADO]
Where's the captain?
Huh?!
Who the heck flies into a star?
Turn us around, morons!
Or are you trying to
get the captain killed?
[OKITA]
It's okay.
My old battle wounds
are just flaring up.
I'm just fine.
Right, doc?
[DR. SADO]
Uhh...
Yeah!
I'm sure that's what it is!
I'll just take a quick look,
due diligence and all.
Let's check that pulse.
Yup, like I thought,
no problem here!
Just a little fatigue.
Guess I'll give you a nutrient
injection and call it a day!
Close call.
I've been instructed
to keep you alive
and you're making
that very difficult.
You need to listen to me
and manage your condition!
If you keep this up, you'll--!
I know the stakes. Trust me.
[OTA] Solar prominence
straight ahead, SK-223.
Steer to port!
Captain.
That gas is having
some kind of reaction!
[SANADA] It's trying
to absorb the star,
but the star's absorbing it.
I see.
So this is why you brought
us here, isn't it, Captain?
Incompetent fools!
You just floated
there and watched
while Lord Desler's magnificent
weapon was devoured!
You're a useless, inferior race!
This is on your head,
you understand me?
Yours and yours alone!
I won't be dragged down by this!
I'll make sure Lord De--
Prepare for battle!
We'll give the Yamato
everything we've got left!
We follow Commander Shultz!
[CREW]
There's trouble ahead!
A massive solar flare!
[KODAI]
Shima, can we get around it?
Negative!
It's too big!
There's no way!
Full speed, ahead!
Kodai.
We'll use the Wave Motion Gun.
Yes, sir.
Wait, you mean
on the solar flare?
[OKITA]
That's an order!
Yes, sir!
Prepare to fire at solar flare!
Circuit to Wave Motion Gun open.
Vents sealed.
Force injector: Activating.
Safety lock released.
Confirming: Force
injector active.
Tachyon particle pressure
is rising in chamber.
Eighty.
Eighty-five.
Ninety percent.
Enemy ship! Approaching quickly!
[OTA]
Hit to starboard side!
[OKITA]
Ignore them!
[MORI] Ten seconds
before we're too close!
Energy charge complete,
120 percent!
Wave Motion Gun. Fire!
Now straight through
that opening!
Full speed ahead!
[OPERATOR B] Sir!
The Yamato 's broken through!
[OPERATOR A] Ship
temperature: three million bek!
Impossible.
[OPERATOR A]
Our ship can't handle this heat!
Stern is melting!
[OPERATOR B]
We've lost control!
[GANZ]
Glory to Zaltz!
[CREW]
[GAMILAN OPERATOR]
Video signal lost.
My Lord Supreme.
Clearly that inferior
Shultz has failed you!
And failed me as well.
A splendid battle.
Packed with drama
until the very last shot.
You're welcome, men.
I trust you were all
as entertained as I.
Now, Hyss.
Yes, Sir!
[DESLER] Award all our
dead a two-rank promotion.
Furthermore, give their
families honorary status
as first-class Gamilans.
Zar Beluk!
All right.
That concludes
tonight's festivities.
Good night, comrades.
[ALL]
Garle Desler!
[DESLER]
Oh, one more thing, Celestra.
What's the name of that Teron
ship that performed so well?
They call it the
Yamato , your lordship.
[DESLER]
Hmph...
The Yamato ?
I'll have to remember that.
[VELTE]
Hmm...
Is something wrong?
That massive weapon that
broke through the flare.
It appeared to be similar
to one of our prototypes
in Weapons Development.
Are you sure, Velte?
That can't be.
[MISAKI] I don't know
about you, listeners,
but I'll sure be making
another wish tonight.
Remember: All that matters
is what's in your heart.
If you are truly committed,
then the heavens will look
down on you, and be kind.
No matter how
impossible it seems,
fate can show us a way.
[MISAKI] This is your host,
Yuria Misaki, signing off.
[OKITA] Gamilloids,
the artificial soldiers
and vanguard of the enemy.
We've captured one
still capable of speech,
but how can we know
if his words are truth, or lies?
Can a conversation
between automatons give us
that answer, or only
lead to more questions?
Where is the line
between life and machine?
Next time: "Clockwork Prisoner."
There are 339 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.