[MORI]
Yamato , do you copy?
Mayday! Mayday!
[GOER] Interesting.
Now we know what they call
that pest of a ship. Look at it.
What an ugly heap of metal.
Not at all graceful.
They've left their moon, sir.
And it will
most likely come here.
We'll lure their ship in
and then destroy it.
And what makes you so confident
they'll walk into your trap?
This is the launch site
for the planet bombs
that are turning
their world red.
We're too tempting
a target to resist.
I see, Shultz. It's a grand
opportunity for your race.
You can prove that
despite your weak genes
and that regrettable skin color,
your loyalty to
the empire is true.
We're every bit as loyal
as pure-blooded Gamilans,
Major General,
and just as capable.
[laughing]
That's the spirit I like
in a Gamilan soldier!
Don't let me down.
Garle Desler! Our Great Leader!
[SHULTZ]
Garle Desler!
Makes one long for the old days
when we fought
under General Domel.
Indeed.
How are the preparations
for our next strike?
We're ready, sir.
Planet bomb 301 will launch
shortly, just as you commanded.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5X
speaking Gamilan]
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Correcting for target errors,
minus 3.7.
Target sighted and locked.
Reflecting Satellite Cannon
charging up now.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
Chamber pressure rising.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Reflecting Satellite Cannon
charging complete.
Then fire!
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
103 contact imminent.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
103 ignition successful.
Angle correct.
Accelerating at 17 gat speed.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
Trajectory confirmed.
103 on collision course
with planet Teron.
That system has
more uses than we think.
[SHULTZ chuckles]
Edgeworth-Kuiper Belt
object 637 has deviated
from its course, sir.
It's a planet bomb.
Damn those demons.
[MISAKI]
No enemy ships detected
within two light-seconds
of the Yamato .
Ah. So you're sitting in
for Lieutenant Mori, huh?
Nice! I like the view!
She's a fellow sailor.
Show some respect.
[OTA chuckles]
Lieutenant Kodai
and the XO left, too.
You think we're missing
a party or something?
Those two are in
the laboratory looking at
that Gamilan soldier
they brought back with them.
[OTA]
Oh. I bet Mori's there, too.
So Nanbu. How's that chair?
Uh. It's fine I guess.
[NIIMI] This technology
is astonishing.
Nanomachines seem
to be functioning
as artificial organelles.
[SANADA] Have you analyzed
it's epidermal composition yet?
[ANALYZER] Body exterior chiefly
composed of soft tektite rubber.
They're using a race of
machines as ground troops?
You're jumping to conclusions.
How so?
Come on, what else
would you call that thing?
[SANADA]
An android.
Exactly. That's what I said!
[NIIMI]
You said "race of machines,"
which implies autonomy and
the ability to self-replicate,
and we don't know
if they're that or
programmed drone weapons
with a humanoid design.
That's what the XO is saying.
Yes, thank you.
Look. My point--
Okay. We've given them
our report, Lieutenant.
Time for us to go.
--But.
--I don't want to hear it,
all right? Go.
[KODAI grunts]
So you did search the
whole Yukikaze , correct?
And you're sure
there were no survivors?
[KODAI]
Yes, sir.
[SANADA]
Thank you. That is all.
I wish it weren't, sir.
You're concerned
about him, aren't you.
I can tell.
You care, sir.
And I like that about you.
[KODAI] Who's the bigger
android, that thing or him?
Jeez. He was all like,
[imitates robot]
"Thank you, that is all."
Freaking computer.
You know we don't all
wear our hearts
on our sleeves like you.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
--So, Kodai.
--Now what?
Thanks for all you did.
On that moon.
You were great down there.
You kept us safe.
Yeah, of course.
I mean that was
my assignment, right?
That's true.
Oh hey, I almost forgot.
You know that Cosmo Zero pilot
who helped us out?
Well, it turns out it was
this girl from accounting.
She's not even in the wing!
[KATO]
Since when are you a pilot?
I'm letting it slide
just this once.
But never try that again.
Under those circumstances
it was the optimal course.
[KATO grunts]
Listen. I want to be
transferred to the squadron.
So you can die
trying to avenge Akio?
No damn way!
[grunts]
Even if I were
that crazy, I couldn't.
That would be
the Captain's call.
And there he goes again.
[HARADA]
So, a locker this time?
Had to. She just
won't listen to reason.
Yeah? Stubborn locker, huh?
[HARADA]
Lieutenant Kato!
[KATO]
Hm?
So, listen. That tank.
It really had us
pinned down on Enceladus.
A few seconds later and
it would've been too late.
So can you say thank you
for me? To that pilot.
[KATO chuckles]
All right, fine.
Uh, what?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Attention all chief officers,
please report to the
central operations room.
[HARADA] Did I...
just say something wrong?
Ha! Don't ask me!
[laughing]
It was my plan to avoid
all unnecessary combat
in order to reach Iscandar
as soon as possible.
However, this latest
planet bomb suggests
the enemy is not only continuing
their assaults on Earth,
they're accelerating them.
And we cannot stand for that.
We'll cripple their base
so they can never attack again!
After the Gamilans took Pluto,
they altered its
environment considerably,
turning it from a frozen rock
to a habitable dwarf planet
with liquid seas.
UN Cosmo Force intel has
been analyzing the movement
of surface hot spots
for some time now.
And determined
the base is most likely
at one of these 18 points.
What? We can't narrow it
down any more than that?
No, I'm afraid not.
We suspect they're using
some kind of cloaking shield.
And that it's
preventing our sensors
from locating their base.
Tricky lot, aren't they.
It's a major outpost for them.
So, if we do find it they're
gonna put up a real fight.
The Yamato is equipped
with advanced
Iscandarian defense technology
called the Wave Motion Shields.
They only last 20 minutes
per charge of course.
But we believe that
they will give us
more than ample protection
from the enemy's positron beams.
[KODAI] We plan to launch
the squadron early,
before the Yamato
sets off their alarm bells.
She'll serve as a decoy.
Drawing the bulk of the enemy
fleet that we're expecting.
The fighters will set a stealth
course through Nyx's orbit,
loop around Charon then
onto Pluto, staying low.
There they'll split up
and search for the base.
And once they locate it.
They'll destroy it.
Meanwhile, the Yamato
will try to break through
the enemy fleet and get close
enough to Pluto's surface
to give suppressing fire
for the squadron.
Providing cover from above.
If I may speak, sir.
Can't we just as easily
destroy their base
from long range
with the Wave Motion Gun?
Most likely, but we won't.
Why not? This puts us at risk
for no reason at all, sir!
It would destroy Pluto.
We'd wreak even more havoc
on our solar system
just to avoid a fight.
And I won't do that.
It's for our species!
What's a planet or two, huh?
Nanbu.
--I said no!
--[NANBU grunts]
That's your commanding officer,
so you'd better fall in line.
Oh, come on,
you know I'm right.
That gun would keep your pilots
from taking any losses, too.
Though honestly,
now that we have this weapon
I don't see why we need
a fighter squadron at all.
What did you say?
Did that bruise your ego?
--Why, you--
--[OKITA] Enough!
We will destroy
their base without using
the Wave Motion Gun.
And that decision is final.
Sir.
We'll rely on our squadron.
Kodai. You will lead them.
Uh. So you want me
in a cockpit, sir?
[OKITA]
That's right.
Sir! You can
count on me, sir!
It would be an honor
to fly for you!
[OKITA]
We'll oversee the operation
from the combat bridge's CIC.
You'll be on the bridge
as well, Chief,
running engineering by comm.
Understood, sir.
That will be all.
Do you have a moment
to talk, sir?
Remind me. Who're you?
Yamamoto from accounting.
I'll try to
make this brief, sir.
Yamamoto, huh?
Hey, you flew
the Zero, didn't you?
Look, I don't really care if
he's the ace of the squadron,
a raging jerk in a bomber jacket
is still a raging jerk.
[MORI gasps]
Ah!
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Team Five, report immediately
to Hanger One.
[NANBU]
Well, say no more.
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Team Five report to Hanger One.
[door squeaks]
Thank you very much, Captain.
Oh, hey, Shima!
Now you can get revenge
without risking the whole brig.
[KODAI]
I'll do my best.
Take care of our ship
till I get back.
[knock, knock]
[OKITA]
Come in.
[SHIMA] It's your
Chief of Navigation, sir.
[SHIMA] We've almost reached
the operation zone.
You're needed in the CIC.
[OKITA]
That's not why you're here.
It's just that... you're a
legend for what you did
back on Mars.
And, well, I've always really
admired you as a sailor, sir.
And I-I lost my dad in this
war when they first attacked us.
We've all lost good people.
Captain. I want you to know
that I fully support
your plan to attack Pluto.
And as Chief of Navigation,
I swear I will make up
the lost time.
I see.
[FIGHTER SQUAD murmuring]
[MALE FIGHTER SQUAD 5A whistles]
Lieutenant Kodai. I realize
we're about to launch,
but is there time
for us to talk?
Yeah, sure.
But first things first.
There's some news I think
you all need to hear.
We have a personnel transfer
from Accounting Division
to the fighter squadron that
goes into effect immediately.
[KATO]
Huh?
[FIGHTER SQUAD gasping]
--[FIGHTER SQUAD 5A] Oh!
--[FIGHTER SQUAD 5B] Yeah!
Name's Yamamoto and
I'm glad to join the wing.
It's an honor.
Let's go kick some tail.
[SAWAMURA]
Yeah, all right!
[NOBUHIKO] I feel like working
twice as hard now.
[KOBASHI] Yeah, working
twice as hard at what?
[FIGHTER SQUAD 5C]
Glad to have ya, babe!
Akira! But, how did you--?
Akira? I thought it was Rei.
That's a nickname.
There, you see?
Akira Yamamoto.
Oh, gotchya.
Well, my mistake.
[YAMAMOTO]
Rei's fine, anyway.
Lots of people call me that.
All right, then.
Looks like Captain Okita
already approved this.
[KATO]
Hm. She's good.
I'll run the squadron side
of this operation.
Alpha will start up north
and Bravo will start
from the south.
Once we've entered Pluto,
we'll all split up
into pairs for the search.
You're with me. We'll be
flying in the Alpha team,
--understood?
--Yes, sir.
I know the score. I'm sure
that most if not all of you
have lost friends
and family to the enemy.
That said. Don't even think
of dying to avenge them.
Survive and keep fighting!
[KOBASHI]
'Bout time we saw some action.
So you wanted to talk
to me about something?
Nah. Thanks.
Now it's a moot point.
[KODAI]
Hm?
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A] Cosmo
Falcons launching in sequence.
Ready keel track ramp
for imminent deployment.
You're up, Lieutenant.
[HANGAR OFFICER 4A]
Let's move!
--Good luck out there.
--[KATO] Don't need it.
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Ready catapults for
Cosmo Zeroes One and Two.
[YAMAMOTO]
Lieutenant Kodai.
Thanks for the chance.
I won't let you down.
Don't thank me, pilot,
you earned it on Enceladus.
Just stay alive. I mean that.
Sir.
Good luck, sir. Give 'em
a big thumping for all of us.
[OTA]
Approaching operation zone.
Deploy the Wave Motion Shields.
[OTA]
Wave Motion Shields deployed.
Output at 80%.
[MORI] Fighter squadron
standing by for launch.
Now commencing Operation M-2.
Deploy the Falcons!
♪
[MALE ATC 5A]
Cosmo Zeroes Alpha 1 and 2,
you are cleared for takeoff.
Alpha 1, roger!
Clear for takeoff!
Alpha 2, roger.
We're clear for takeoff.
[KODAI]
Alpha 1 to all fighters.
Maintain radio silence
until target located.
Activate ECM.
Good luck out there.
We're passing through
Nyx's orbit now, all clear.
It's so quiet. It's hard to
believe we're in enemy space.
Anything on the radar?
Negative, sir. No sightings.
Who knows. Maybe they saw
the Yamato and ran.
No. If you ask me,
this feels more like
we're walking into a trap.
[OKITA]
Mmm. Mori.
Keep an eye on that radar.
Report every blip.
Yes, sir.
Captain, if we make it
past Charon's orbit,
and get Pluto in our sights,
we'd just need one shot.
So it's not too late yet.
I told you we'll depend
on our fighters
and that's the
end of it, Lieutenant.
We'll wait until Kodai's here.
[ALL yell]
That flash. What was that?
[alarm beeping]
What just hit us? Report!
It must be some kind
of long range attack.
It seemed like it
came out of nowhere!
[SANADA]
Damage report coming in now.
Still no sign of enemy ships.
And the angle's wrong for Pluto.
Damage to Deck Three, portside.
Seems the Wave Motion Shields
were penetrated, Captain.
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Closing bulkheads!
[DR. SADO yells]
What's going on? Ah!
No peeking!
Inertial control system
is offline.
And, the ship interior
is at zero-g.
[SHIMA] No damage
to navigation controls.
Source of attack
calculated to approximately
ten o'clock on the portside.
Take evasive maneuvers.
Maintain speed and
turn hard to port,
try to move
into their blind spot.
Starting evasive maneuvers.
Turning the ship
hard to port, sir.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
First shot landed.
Impact confirmed.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5C]
Yamato engaging in
evasive maneuvers.
It's a brilliant tactic,
Commander Shultz.
As versed as I am
in this base's technology,
it never would have
occurred to me
to use the planet bomb launching
system as a weapon itself.
You have to consider
all the angles.
The ability to adapt and
improvise during battle
is the key to victory.
Yes, General Domel
taught us that.
Shame, though. The first
shot didn't finish them off
like I was hoping it would.
Relax, Jarletora.
Don't you know hunts
are meant to be savored?
Adjust the reflectors
for the next volley.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5Y
speaking Gamilan]
Based on the attack analysis,
we should have entered
its blind spot by now.
--[AIHARA sighs]
--Guess we're safe now.
Stay on guard, crew.
They know where we are and
it's possible they're mobile.
They'll strike again
if they get the chance.
Maintain geostationary orbit.
[SANADA] There's a lot
of debris out here.
[SHULTZ]
Do they imagine they're hidden?
New flight path calculated.
Satellites 7, 13,
and 28 deploying reflectors.
Reflecting Satellite
Cannon. Fire!
[ALL yell]
It's the same attack
as before, Captain.
I thought they couldn't
reach us out here!
Radar, what's the source?
Still no blips, sir.
I can't explain it.
Maintain our position!
We can't, sir! Propulsion's
dropping too fast!
I've lost all control!
We've got a significant fluid
leak from the point of impact.
[OKITA] Shima. Prepare for
emergency landing
in the seas of Pluto.
Uh, yes sir!
Now raise the bow
till we're level!
Preparing to land, sir.
All crewmen, brace for impact!
The ship is still afloat.
Landing complete.
Stay on guard!
Captain. We're nearing
the Wave Motion Shields'
max time before recharge.
If we take one of
those shots without them.
Understood. Just get the ship
repaired as fast as possible.
Aihara, any word from
the fighter squadron?
No, nothing yet, sir.
--If I may.
--[OKITA] Mm?
I'd like to offer
a tactical suggestion?
[SHULTZ]
Stubborn little bastards.
Don't give them
a chance to recoop.
Calibrate the reflectors
for the next attack!
Reflecting Satellites
are in position.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5C]
Reflecting Satellite
Cannon charged.
[SHULTZ] It was
a valiant effort, Terons.
You fought well.
However, all battles must end.
Farewell, Yamato .
[MORI] Powerful energy
reading. Overhead!
[OKITA] The space battleship
sinks into a Pluto sea.
But failure is not an option
for this vessel.
You must rise, Yamato,
because you're the last
desperate hope for
the people of Earth.
Open the vents, raise her up!
Target the hidden enemy base,
and fire a decisive shot
into the strange,
aurora-filled skies.
Next time:
"The Sun Sets on Pluto."
There are 361 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.