[MISAKI]
Today, on Yamato Radio Theater,
a request from a crewmember
going under the
name Shiro Shinta.
It's a famous tale from
the late 21st century,
called The Heart
of Agent Number Nine.
[MISAKI] In the early
days of life on Mars,
before there
were towns at all,
a single observation
post stood alone
at the edge of Mare Sirenum.
No one ever came to visit
this forgotten tower
in the silent, barren land,
where a lone young man
spent his days keeping watch,
much like a lighthouse
keeper of old.
He had no name.
In his solitude,
he didn't need one.
He only had his number.
[ANALYZER]
Transplanting visual sensors
from Gamiloid A to Gamiloid B.
[ANALYZER]
Transplant successful.
[SANADA] The three Gamiloid
soldiers we recovered
from Enceladus all
share the same design,
and what we
consider orthodox AI.
We think they're automata.
What's that mean?
[MORI]
Like mechanical dolls, right?
[SANADA]
By running a massive number
of simple programs in parallel,
it can perform complex actions,
replicating many
human capabilities.
They share the same
fundamental architecture
as our own artificial
intelligence systems.
Their programming
tells us Gamilans
use the same mathematics.
And understand physics
much like we do.
This means our cultures
should be capable
of at least some communication.
When encountering an
alien civilization in space,
this has long been
theorized to be important.
Vital, when it comes
down to matters of war.
It means we can play shogi
by the same rules.
And that's a start.
Yeah, I guess.
So, could you pull any useful
data from their hard drives?
Like intel, that might help us?
[SANADA]
Hmm.
Well, we tried.
But two of them were
damaged beyond repair.
The third unit is still intact.
But we can't get
access to its data.
As far as we can tell it
would only be accessible
from a Gamilan terminal.
It sounds like we've struck out.
But there is another option.
We turn it back on.
And then we ask it to talk.
[ANALYZER]
Local mainframe restored.
Gamiloid Alternative rebooting.
[ANALYZER]
Can you hear me?
Greetings.
I am Type AU09, autonomous
sub-frame of this vessel.
Please call me Analyzer.
[ALTER]
A... A-Ana-Ana... Analyzer?
[ANALYZER] You are a rebooted,
alternative configuration
of an alien civilization's
servant android.
Suggestion!
I can call you Alter!
[ALTER]
Al... Alter?
[SANADA]
Warp complete.
[MORI] No enemies
detected in the vicinity.
[ANALYZER] Sir, permission
to resume analyzing Alter?
Yes, go ahead.
[ANALYZER]
Aye-aye!
Analyzer seems to
be enjoying himself.
Yeah, I'm sure he is.
He's finally got another
robot to talk to now.
[ANALYZER]
Identify.
[ALTER]
A cat.
[ANALYZER]
Negative.
This is a dog.
Subgroup of mammal.
Subgroup of animal.
Can you repeat?
[ALTER]
A dog.
Mammal.
Animal.
[ANALYZER]
Identify.
[ALTER]
A dog.
[ANALYZER]
Negative.
This is a cat.
[NIIMI]
Hello, Analyzer.
Am I interrupting
some machine gossip?
[ANALYZER]
Negative.
I do not gossip.
I am currently
teaching Alter to speak.
Oh, is that a fact?
But you've already figured out
how to link operating systems,
so why not just upload
a dictionary to it?
[ANALYZER] Vocabulary alone
does not equal mastery.
To understand linguistic
structure and concepts,
a large number of
exchanges are required.
In addition...
Yes, I know.
For security reasons,
you can't connect it
to the ship's network.
So I was right, we should
have investigated further.
This still doesn't tell me
if we could colonize.
[MISAKI] One day at
the observation post,
an old mechanical engineer
named Houdin arrived with
a girl named Eve at his side.
For Number Nine,
this led to an encounter
he found nothing
short of magical.
Hearing a sound in the distance,
Number Nine followed
it to the new Martian sea,
and found the girl
sitting on a rock,
singing with a haunting voice.
[ALTER]
Who are you?
[MISAKI]
Hearing his approach,
the girl stopped
and turned to him.
"Who are you?" she asked.
[MISAKI] "And what are you
doing all the way out here?"
[ALTER]
Yesterday, I met a goddess.
[ANALYZER]
A goddess?
[ALTER]
The goddess of this vessel.
[ANALYZER]
Can you please elaborate?
[ALTER] The goddess asked,
"Who are you?"
I answered, "I am Alter."
"No," she replied.
"Your identity.
I am not asking for your name."
[ANALYZER]
Lieutenant Mori, perhaps?
Or Lieutenant Niimi?
Negative.
That seems unlikely.
[ALTER] Can you answer
this question, Analyzer?
Who are you?
[ANALYZER]
Who am I?
[SHINOHARA]
Shinohara to Yamato .
Investigation of the
spatial wake complete.
Confirming it is
safe for passage.
[AIHARA]
Roger that.
Captain, the scout team
is completing patrol
and will return to ship.
[OKITA]
Mm.
We'll jump as soon
as they're back on board.
Schedule the next warp
navigation for oh-two-hundred.
[MORI]
Yes, sir.
Preparing dock now.
Hey, Analyzer.
Can you go and give them a hand?
[ANALYZER]
Figuratively, yes.
Sorry, man, you're dead meat.
[ringing alarm]
[IWATA]
They're back.
Let's go!
Hey, no fair!
I had a straight flush!
Guys!
Navi-baby.
Be a doll and take it
from here, would ya?
[SID VOICE]
Switching to automatic control.
Aw, you get me now!
Huh?
Huh? Let me guess,
you think I'm nuts?
[YAMAMOTO]
No comment.
Give 'em a name
and show 'em you care.
Then they'll take care of you.
Just like anybody else.
[MAINTENANCE]
Open port side hatch.
[IWATA]
Aye-aye.
Let's do this.
[MAINTENANCE] Guidance team,
prepare to pull them in.
Okay!
Looks good!
[ANALYZER]
Huh? Alter?
[SANADA]
Hmm?
[IWATA]
Huh?
Toyama.
Are you seeing an error
on the control display?
[TOYAMA]
The screen just went blank!
[IWATA]
What?
Force release!
[SID VOICE]
Executing command.
What the hell?
[IWATA]
Look out!
[YAMAMOTO]
Get her steady!
I'm trying!
What is wrong with you?
You've could've
gotten us killed!
[IWATA]
I don't know what happened.
We can't explain it.
That crane.
Doesn't it have
an auto-control program?
And we were using it.
But then something went wrong.
My control display went blank
and the crane just went haywire.
If there's an issue, it's
supposed to shut itself down.
I've never seen anything
like this before.
Morons!
Just because it never
happened before
doesn't mean it
won't happen today!
That's why you're
both down there,
in case the machines
do screw it up!
Yes, sir!
No excuses.
I'm sorry.
We let you all down.
It's fine.
We can see you're on top of it.
Right?
[YAMAMOTO]
Uh. Yeah.
Looks like you talked to Alter.
By your own sub-network before
the accident, is that right?
[ANALYZER]
Correct.
There was a very minor
lag in the data relay
between the hangar equipment
and the ship's mainframe.
But those
nanoseconds were vital.
And that's what caused
the dock crane to malfunction.
[ANALYZER]
I am sorry for the issue.
Your sessions with Alter may be
stressing the ship's processors
in ways we didn't expect.
So if this continues, I'll have
to reformat you as a safeguard.
[ANALYZER]
That would be...
...the correct and
logical decision to make.
Analyzer.
I'm going to put a
hold on the Alter project.
For now you're forbidden
from coming here
or communicating with
Alter by your sub-network.
Let us keep
an eye on it for now.
You got it?
[ANALYZER]
Aye-aye.
[MISAKI] The old engineer
sent Eve back to their ship,
and Agent Number Nine
desired nothing more
than to see her again.
Despite his prior solitude,
this was the first time in his
life he truly knew loneliness.
So he decided to venture out to
the ship, and see Eve once more.
He felt, with a sudden
conviction in his heart,
this was the only way he
could learn who he truly was.
[ANALYZER]
XO, I learned something
from my communication
with Alter.
[SANADA]
Hmm?
[ANALYZER] The Gamiloid
machines are just like me.
That so?
[ANALYZER] Alter asked me
to define who I am.
[SANADA]
What did you say?
[ANALYZER]
I said a friend.
[SANADA]
A friend, huh?
I think that's a good answer.
[ALTER]
Where is the goddess?
[MISAKI]
Huh?
[ANALYZER]
Computer, what is happening?
[MORI] The lock to the
main lab has been destroyed.
Looks like that
Gamiloid's missing.
Send in security, now!
Weapons use is approved,
so shoot it down if you have to!
[SHIMA] Ship has moved
to Alert Status One.
Repeat: Ship has moved
Recovered Gamiloid has escaped
main lab on deck four,
and is assumed to be
hiding somewhere on ship.
Security teams are
to capture or destroy.
[SECURITY B]
Is that it?
[SECURITY A]
Freeze!
[SHIMA] Security are
to capture or destroy.
[SECURITY A]
Don't move. Stay right there!
Target spotted!
In pursuit on
port side of deck three!
[ANALYZER] Alter wanted
to know how to define
who he was, as well.
He likely believes
if he finds the goddess,
he will resolve that question.
Wait, what goddess?
[ANALYZER] Alter said
that he had encountered
the goddess of this ship.
And I have learned
one additional,
important fact
about the Gamiloids,
which I believe we must
take into consideration.
[HOSHINA]
Don't let it escape!
Close the bulkheads!
[HOSHINA]
Don't move!
Huh?!
Mori.
Where's the Gamiloid now?
[MORI]
In the ducts on deck two.
Looks like it's moving
toward the bow.
[HOSHINA] We're heading
for that sealed room, right?
The automatic guidance
systems leading us
to Iscandar are housed in there.
Do you think
that's what it's after?
There it is!
We have to stop it!
Open fire, now!
[ALTER]
Enemy.
Terror.
Alive.
Goddess!
That's the second
turret loading room.
Looks like it just went inside!
[ITO]
Well?
[HOSHINA]
No good.
It's locked from inside.
Team to bridge!
We need you
to override this lock!
Stand by to open fire.
[AIHARA]
This is the bridge.
The Gamiloid infiltrated
our system and locked us out.
It's going to take us some time
to make our way back in.
Tsch!
[ANALYZER]
I can assist.
AU09, perfect timing.
Come open this door.
[ANALYZER] First, your team
must holster their weapons.
[ITO]
Why?
[ANALYZER] I do not want
him to think we are enemies.
Have you blown a fuse?
Of course that
thing's our enemy!
[MISAKI] We do not fire
on unarmed prisoners.
What do you mean?
A prisoner?
Don't be stupid.
That thing's just a
big hunk of metal and wires.
It thinks and feels.
So it should be treated
as a prisoner like us!
Wait, feel?
So now it has a heart?
I thought it was an automaton.
Isn't that what you've
been calling that thing
in your reports, XO?
It's true the Gamiloids
are automata that function
through a massive array
of response programs.
So, that much we know.
Exactly.
Like I said.
They're just brainless machines.
[SANADA]
However...
Some would say the human brain
is essentially no different.
A network of parallel processors
programmed by our DNA.
Your attitude is a common one.
You want to believe that
our consciousness is special.
And could never be
achieved by circuitry.
And yet...
your belief is irrelevant.
You cannot actually
prove that's the case.
[ITO]
Hmph!
You've got a real way
with words, sir.
[ANALYZER] I have retaken
control of security.
Bottom line.
You do not fire
unless I say you can.
[ITO]
All right, XO, you're the boss.
[ANALYZER]
Opening door now.
[HOSHINA]
Misaki?
[ANALYZER]
XO...
When Alter is found,
I recommend immediate forced
shut down with maximum caution.
[ITO]
Oh yeah, and why's that?
For safety.
So he won't blow himself up.
[ANALYZER] Gamiloids have a
root program that is designed
to self-destruct if isolated
and surrounded by what they
perceive to be their enemies.
Go! Just be careful!
Yes, sir!
Analyzer, let's go.
One question.
What's your take on it?
You don't really think that
machine has a heart, do you?
[SANADA]
To be honest: At the moment,
it's not even clear to me
whether you have a heart.
There are some in our species
who lack all empathy,
and only fake it
to get what they want.
Perhaps you're
simulating your humanity.
It's exiting the ship!
To the upper deck, sir!
I think it's making its
way toward the bridge
from the outside!
[OKITA]
We can't allow the Gamiloid
to reach the automatic
guidance system.
We'll destroy it if we must.
[ANALYZER]
Shell block destroyed.
Infiltrating kernel.
[ALTER]
Dog. Cat. Alive. Goddess. Death.
Friend. Friend. Friend...
[ANALYZER] Gamiloid Alternative
forced shut down complete.
Mainframe reformatted.
Reboot impossible.
[SANADA]
Recover its task log.
[ANALYZER]
Roger that.
[SANADA]
I've completed the analysis.
There's nothing in
Alter's task log to indicate
the self-destruct defense
program was activated.
[ANALYZER]
Therefore...
Yes. If nothing else,
he believed he still had at
least one friend on this ship.
You performed
your duty well, Analyzer.
[MISAKI]
Eve's skin was peeled away,
her joints ratcheted apart,
revealing the intricate
system of gears and silicon
that had been hidden inside.
From the tower's window, Number
Nine watched in perfect silence
as her body sank
into the Mare Sirenum.
[MISAKI] "I no longer
feel pity for that doll.
For her plight is not
some unfathomable mystery."
"Because I know I am
also one," he thought.
"A servant. A doll.
A creation of Houdin."
[MISAKI]
And then Number Nine thought.
Alone in his small room,
in the observation post.
He thought that ultimately,
whether or not that
beautiful doll had a heart,
he did not need to know.
It was not his
question to answer.
[MISAKI] And then he thought,
as Martian day turned to night:
The fact that I do have
a heart is a secret.
A secret that
belongs only to me.
[OKITA] The Yamato plunges
through a dimensional gap
into a ship graveyard,
a cruel space devoid
of life or salvation.
But in that bleakness falls
the shadow of an enemy ship.
Will they aid,
or impede each other?
Will stranded crews
work together,
or doom them all to death?
Next time:
"Graveyard of the Universe."
There are 325 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.