[NANBU]
So Balun's on the other side?
That's what you were calling a
"lighthouse in space," right?
[OTA]
That's right.
[SHIMA]
We're surprised, too.
We had no idea it was the hub
of a whole subspace
gate network.
But that's great--
we can jump to
the Large Magellanic
without issue!
Sure, if we're lucky.
The enemy controls
this network, remember?
Yeah, I know.
Well, I'd say Misaki
was the bigger surprise.
Who knew Iscandarians
could possess people?
It's crazy. Do you think
she'll ever go back to normal?
[SANADA]
The gate's back online.
And with her help,
we've learned how to use
the control system
from our ship.
Mm.
We appreciate you assisting us.
[MISAKI]
Show gratitude with action.
Not with your words.
[SANADA] We're loading
a simplified version of
the control program
onto a Gamilan fighter
we recovered from the satellite.
Scouting Balun will be
a dangerous assignment.
Who are you planning
to send as the pilot?
Well, the Fighter Squad
Captain will choose.
I'll notify you as soon
as it's been decided.
[OKITA]
Mmm.
[KOBASHI]
I wish he'd picked me.
[FIGHTER SQUAD 15B] Yeah, yeah,
you just want the glory.
[FIGHTER SQUAD 18A]
Come back in one piece, buddy.
All right, that's enough!
I've made my decision.
Now clear out!
--Guess I'll see ya.
--[DAIKUHARA] Good luck.
Don't screw up.
Back to your stations,
you gossipy imbeciles!
--[SAWAMURA] All right! Jeez.
--[KOBASHI] We're going.
--Shinohara.
--Yes, sir.
Try to relax, would ya?
[chuckles]
[YAMAMOTO]
I'm surprised.
Volunteering for work
doesn't seem like your style.
Why now? Why this mission?
[SHINOHARA] A long time ago,
back when I was still
in flight school, I saw one
of our planes passing over,
and it was a spectacular sight.
Hard to put into words, really.
Just something about the way
it cut across the sky.
Noble and strong.
And when I saw it I thought,
"There. That's the most
beautiful thing in the world."
Later someone I.D.'d it for me.
It was a recon plane.
You know, I actually wanted
to be in recon myself.
Uh.
Listen to me, Shinohara.
The first rule of reacon
is that you have to return.
So make sure you
come back to us. Got it?
[COMM OFFICER 18A]
Goergametsch launching now.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 10E]
Inspector-General Zoellik
will be arriving shortly.
Escort fleet,
proceed to your positions.
Repeat:
Inspector-General Zoellik
will be arriving shortly.
[COMM OFFICER 18B] Five seconds
until Geschtam Jump.
Three, two, one.
[MONK] We've arrived
at Balun on schedule.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 10E]
The Goergametsch is requesting
permission to dock, sir.
That must be Goer.
Yes, right on cue.
Inspector-General,
thank you for gracing us
with your presence
all the way out here.
I mean the sheer honor of
this-this huge naval review
at Balun is indescribable
for all of us stationed here.
And of course as acting
commander I can't help
but feel especially proud.
The sight of so many ships
here fulfills a dream
I've long held
for this vital theater--
The Empire is in greater
peril now than ever before.
Treasonous forces
are trying to divide us.
And so it falls on me
to bring us back together!
I will save the glory
of our people!
[grunts]
Three hours?
That's right.
[YAMAMOTO] He's supposed
to recon the area and locate
the Magellanic gate
all in three hours?
[KATO]
He's agreed to the stakes.
[YAMAMOTO]
And what does that mean?
[KATO]
It's an enemy network.
We could be leading them
straight to us.
If we can't use the gate,
we need to get out fast.
So what, when that
stupid clock runs out
we're just gonna leave
whether he's back or not?
[SHINOHARA]
Sword Three to control.
I'm ready to launch.
--You're clear to go.
--[SHINOHARA] Roger that.
See you soon.
Leave the light on for me.
I'm launching now.
[FEMALE S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Beginning phase one.
[MORI] Sword Three's
physical signal lost.
It's no longer
in normal space, sir.
Navigation. Let's ready a plan
if we can use the gate.
Yes, sir.
[OKITA] When time's up,
we evacuate immediately.
If Sword Three isn't back
by then, we leave him behind.
I need you all to
come to terms with that.
[SHINOHARA] This subspace
business is pretty crazy.
[SHINOHARA]
Gamilans?
That's weird.
[clicking]
[SHINOHARA] Guess the radar's
not gonna help.
That limits my options.
I can only rely on this.
[YAMAMOTO]
And that call sign?
He picked it out himself.
I guess it's his way
of paying tribute.
"Sword Three" is an old
call sign we used in the 343rd.
I never thought
I'd hear it out here.
[YAMAMOTO] You always said
the first rule of reacon
is you have to return.
But that didn't save my brother.
Did it?
[KATO]
Shinohara's gonna be fine.
He will come back.
[KATO]
There's no doubt in my mind.
[FEMALE S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Approaching gate.
Entering phase two.
Brace for extreme turbulence.
[SHINOHARA] Huh?
What do you mean, "extreme"?
[SHINOHARA groaning]
[COMM OFFICER 18A]
Forty-third Milky Way Theater
Carrier Strike Group,
proceed to designated area.
[BRIDGE OFFICER 10E]
One hundred twenty-fourth
Torpedo Squadron arriving now.
[COMM OFFICER 18A]
Upon arrival, all ships proceed
to designated positions. Repeat:
upon arrival, all ships
to designated positions.
[SHINOHARA panting]
That was close. Uh!
[SHINOHARA]
Am I really seeing this?
Are these all Gamilans?
[CELESTRA]
How would you describe
the Inspector-General's
state of mind?
[GIMLEH] He's so ecstatic, I can
read it in his coded message.
The man's feeling like a king.
[CELESTRA] So, this is no
mere review of the fleet.
Contact me if there are issues.
But of course. I live
only to serve the empire.
[GOER] Another wave of forces
from the Delheid theater
are arriving now,
Inspector-General.
It's the 66th Astrocorps
from Zelloom.
[ZOELLIK] Soak it in,
Goer, you'll never see
anything greater
in all your life.
This dignity. This power.
This is Gamilas!
[SHINOHARA]
Talk about a head trip.
What are all these
ships doing here?
There must be 10,000, at least!
[SHINOHARA] Uh! Is that
the Magellanic gate?
Whoa. An artificial structure?
In the planet's core?
Okay.
[GAMILAN COMM 18A,
speaking Gamilan]
[SHINOHARA]
Sounds like I ticked him off.
Sorry, Gamis,
I hate to upset you,
but I've got somewhere to be.
Fire secondary engines.
But, sir!
[SANADA]
It's not a discussion.
Prepare to leave the area.
[SHINOHARA yells]
[GAMILAN PATROL 18A,
speaking Gamilan]
[SHINOHARA]
Get outta my way!
Just do it like they did.
Fly strong. Fly noble.
Fly beautiful!
[SHINOHARA]
Just fly.
[FEMALE S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Moving to phase three.
[NEMOTO]
It's totally shredded.
[KODAI]
So how's he doing?
[HARADA] Luckily, there wasn't
any permanent damage,
and his wounds
are surprisingly minor
considering the shape
of that ship.
We'll give him a physical
when he wakes up,
but the doctor's prognosis:
[immitates Dr. Sado] "Relax,
the guy's got a strong ticker!"
He'll be just fine.
We've analyzed the data
from his onboard computer.
[SHIMA]
Whoa, that's no natural core.
Indeed. Balun is
an artificial planet
with a massive energy
generator at its core
that powers the subspace gates.
The good news is
we've confirmed
the Magellanic gate
is functional.
Which brings us to the bad news.
We don't know why,
but the Gamilans
have assembled
an enormous armada of over
10,000 military vessels
around the planet.
[gasps]
Ten thousand ships?
Impossible.
[SANADA] We've already plotted
our contingency warp course.
Captain. We should switch to
plan B and set out immediately.
[OKITA] No. We go through
the gate as planned.
The best chance we've got is
to charge right through them.
Proud soldiers of Gamilas
and my courageous comrades.
Your ongoing bravery and
sacrifice are the foundation
on which this towering
empire stands.
You deserve to
be uplifted by glory,
not burdened by despair.
And so, it is with great pain
that I deliver this news.
[GOER]
Uh?
[ZOELLIK] My friends in arms,
our empire's mighty ruler,
the supreme leader
Lord Abelt Desler.
He has been taken away
by the cruel hand of death
and is with us no more.
--[GOER gasps]
--[GAMILAN OFFICERS gasp]
[GAMILAN OFFICERS
gasp, murmur]
With this peril
comes a question.
Who can lead us next?
I must confess that my soul
trembles under the weight
of such a task. For what mortal
man can replace a star?
But as I share in this
sorrow with you,
knowing my heart
will never heal,
it's my duty to be strong!
Here and now I swear to you all
that I shall carry out
our great leader's will,
and bring swift justice
to the criminals responsible!
We must purge the traitors
in Imperial Command!
If you love Gamilas as I do,
then rise with me and fight!
We will wipe out the evil
scourge infesting our government
in Baleras,
and save our empire!
There's a disturbance
in one of the gates, sir.
We must take these traitors
by the throat and crush them.
We'll show no mercy!
--[VANDEVEL] What?
--[GOER gasps]
What's going on?
Sir. We're picking up activity
from the galactic theater gate.
A foreign vessel appears
to be coming through.
[ZOELLIK]
Huh?
[VANDEVEL]
The gate is opening now.
To combat speed one!
Open fire when ready!
Sir! Opening fire now!
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18A]
The Teron ship is smashing
through the sixth
on a course for Balun!
What an auspicious
stroke of fortune.
It's a message from the gods
that I am destined
to destroy the Yamato .
Open fire!
[ZOELLIK] As a tribute to
our fallen leader, I will sink
the vile Teron ship before
we march home. Garle Gamilas!
[OKITA] Maintain course.
Increase our speed.
Sir! Black 20!
This is classic Okita.
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18B]
We're blocked by ally ships.
We can't engage!
[GAMILAN FLEET CAPTAIN 18A]
Agreed. Everyone,
hold your fire!
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18A]
We're losing more ships, sir!
What are you waiting for?
We're grouped too close
together! Scatter the fleet!
[ZOELLIK] No! We will swarm
the Yamato and destroy it.
But sir, then our ships
won't be able to maneuver!
--[ZOELLIK] I don't care.
--[GOER] Uh!
Let them fall.
True glory can only
be achieved through sacrifice.
But the fleet.
[ZOELLIK]
All ships, change course!
Do not be afraid!
Our numbers make us strong!
Move all cannons
to forward position.
[OKITA]
Now punch through!
[MORI] Enemy ships closing in,
sir--too many to count!
[OTA] Port side shield
has been breached!
Lower bulkheads.
--[NANBU] Gun turrets, report!
--[SANADA] Damage control!
[OTA]
We're caught in Balun's gravity!
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18A]
Teron ship has been sunk.
It's crashing on Balun.
Calculating crash point.
[ZOELLIK laughing]
The Yamato has been
crushed at Balun.
It must have been
so devastating for you
when you couldn't
do it yourself, Domel.
You'll be remembered not only as
a traitor but as a failure, too.
My, how tragic.
[laughing]
[DESLER]
You're in high spirits, Zoellik.
What? Uh! B-But how?!
I was so very moved by
your speech to the troops.
You're quite the poet.
Lord Desler lives!
[ZOELLIK]
No, that's impossible!
No one could have
survived that explosion!
I know you can't be
that stupid, Zoellik.
Then it-it was just
a double who died?
You were too clumsy, Zoellik.
Celestra was well aware
of your plot to kill me.
But on the bright side
you did save me
from an insufferably
boring trip.
Now, then.
Your guilt is too obvious
to even feign a trial.
Do you have any last words,
comrade? Or...?
[gunshots]
No. I-It's not true.
It's not true!
My fellow brothers in arms,
it's not what you think.
I only took on
the mantle of traitor
out of love for my country!
There are plans in motion
you don't know about
that threaten the empire!
--[gunshot]
--[groans]
[GOER panting]
[ZOELLIK]
Goer, you fool.
No, Zoellik!
Traitorous scum.
[beeping]
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18C]
General Goer!
What is it?
There's something rising up
near Balun's equator, sir!
♪
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18A]
It's the Yamato !
And it's moving fast!
You morons!
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18C]
All crew to battle stations!
Wave Motion Gun
is now online, sir.
[TOKUGAWA] Increase engine
power. Seal emergency vents.
Adjust course 180 degrees.
And open the firing vent.
[TOKUGAWA]
Activating force injector.
Activation confirmed.
Releasing safety.
[NANBU]
Pressure, rising in chamber.
[KODAI]
Adjusting ship heading.
Target locked.
Anchor. Ready to disable.
Wave Motion Gun, fire!
[GOER]
That cursed gun of theirs.
They're missing all our ships!
What are they aiming at?
[GAMILAN BRIDGE OFFICER 18C]
Emergency! That beam's causing
a chain reaction
in Balun's energy core.
It's spiraling out of control.
It's gonna explode!
What? Explode?!
Retreat! Get us out
of this system now!
Disable the gravity anchor.
All crew, brace yourselves
for impact!
[KODAI grunting]
[beeping]
[KODAI]
The Large Magellanic Cloud.
[SHIMA]
Yeah. We actually made it.
After all that,
we're finally here.
I've returned
to my own sea of stars.