[KODAI] Why would the enemy care
about this ancient battleship?
[distant aircraft noise]
[SHIMA gasps]
[KODAI gasps]
It's them!
This doesn't make any sense.
Why would they be attacking it?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT VOICE 2A]
Enemy bombardment
near Cape Bonomisaki.
All personnel, remain
on standby in the shelter.
Are we okay here?
We're supposed to
be launching any day now!
I don't want to die in a tunnel!
What the hell? Where are
they all coming from?
[KODAI gasps]
A carrier.
[ALL yell]
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[SHIMA]
It's the Air Defense Force!
[KATO]
This is Alpha Leader.
Our party guests
have been served the punch.
[MALE UNCF WING DISPATCHER 2A]
Confirmed, Alpha Leader.
Threat has been neutralized.
Return to base.
[KATO]
Roger that.
[KATO sighs]
Idiots.
[SHIMA] Hey, are you kidding me?
Don't leave us here!
[KODAI] She's alive.
This rusted old ship.
[MAN 1 speaking Gamilan]
[speaking Gamilan]
[continues speaking Gamilan]
There. Just don't punch
anything else for a while.
Man. I thought he'd
calmed down. Guess not.
[DR. SADO laughing]
Ah the great joys
of youth, am I right?
You boys did take some radiation
but you should be fine.
Oh, come here, Mew.
I'm not going to be around
for a while. Actually,
you kids won't be either.
Didn't you get
the standby orders, too?
Uh, yeah.
[meows]
[FEMALE EUROPEAN REP. 2A]
The situation is deteriorating,
with energy supplies dwindling
all across the globe.
We're dealing with
famine and riots
in almost every sector,
and poisonous spores
from those alien plants
are still wreaking havoc.
All attempts to curb
the destruction have failed.
Even underground we're
not going to last for long.
That's abundantly clear.
Now that the enemy's
discovered the ship,
how soon can we
execute the launch?
We've moved it up.
We're planning
to embark in 72 hours.
How can you?
I've been told you lost
a great deal of experienced
crewmen in that bombing.
Your information is wrong.
We suffered no casualties.
That's not what we heard either,
but if the hero of the Second
Battle of Mars says it,
I am inclined to believe him.
[SERIZAWA]
Hm!
This plan is being executed
under the UN's authority.
But under the circumstances,
we can't even be there.
The sectors are cut off.
Realistically there's little
we can do to help you now.
[MALE USA REP. 2A]
Same for us.
We're only hanging on
by a thread.
Vice-Admiral,
the Yamato Plan has to succeed,
the hopes of the entire
world are resting on it.
[alarm blaring]
[LAUNCH CONTROLLER 2A
speaking Gamilan]
What is this? You think
we're finally gonna launch?
Must be, that's what the
Izumo Plan's all about, right?
Feels weird leaving
everyone else behind, though.
[OKITA] Soldiers.
The long wait is over.
Each one of you
is here today because
you were selected and trained
for a vital space mission.
Now, your mission will commence.
And I will have the honor of
serving as your ship's captain.
However. The Izumo Plan,
to escape the earth
and resettle in space,
has been shelved.
[CROWD gasping]
[OKITA]
I'll explain your assignment.
But first there's something
I want to show you.
The following, is a video
message we recovered
from an interstellar vessel
as part of Operation M.
[STARSHA] I am Starsha
of the planet Iscandar.
Is that--?
[STARSHA]
Your world as you know it
is on the verge of ruin,
due to the relentless
attacks of the Gamilans.
The Gamilans.
[STARSHA]
I learned of this one year ago,
and dispatched
my sister, Yurisha,
to Earth to bring you
plans for a technology
we call the Dimensional
Wave Motion Engine.
Looks like the vessel
we saw on Mars.
[STARSHA] If you can
understand these plans
and successfully
build your own ship,
then come to Iscandar.
On our planet we have
engineered a system
that can cleanse
the Gamilan pollution,
and restore your home world
to its former state.
No way!
You think that's even possible?
[STARSHA] Unfortunately, I can
no longer take this system
to Earth myself. The journey
will have to be yours.
So that's her? The Iscandarian?
Wow, she's beautiful.
[STARSHA]
Now, along with this message,
I have sent you
the Wave Motion Core,
the activation device for the
Dimensional Wave Motion Engine,
which I entrusted to
my other sister, Sasha.
I believe you will
overcome unknown dangers
and reach my planet, Earthlings.
I believe you will
find salvation.
I am Starsha of Iscandar,
and I believe in you.
One year ago,
Earth received technological
cooperation from Iscandar,
just as she said.
We poured everything into this,
and we've now completed
a spaceship capable
of interstellar flight.
That tech must be incredible.
I had no idea.
That ship's name:
Yamato !
[CROWD murmuring]
Yamato ?
[OKITA]
She also sent us coordinates.
According to the capsule,
Iscandar is 168,000
light-years from Earth.
In the Large
Magellanic Cloud galaxy.
This journey, 336,000
light-years in total,
is farther than mankind
ever dreamed possible.
And of course there's risk.
I won't force you to come.
Any who wish to
stay here may do so.
You have until
we launch tomorrow
at 0600 hours. So think hard.
I'll assume those
who don't report by then
have chosen to stay.
That will be all.
It's a real shame
Yamamoto is dead.
He'd love this.
Shut up.
Onto personnel.
The following officers
will be in charge
of each division.
Engineering:
Hikozaemon Tokugawa.
Technology Division:
Shiro Sanada.
Lieutenant Commander Sanada
will also serve
as the Yamato 's
second-in-command.
Next division is Tactical.
Susumu Kodai.
[KODAI gasp]
Whoa! Seriously?
He's younger than me!
[MORI]
Navigation: Daisuke Shima.
[doorbell buzzes]
[HIJIKATA]
I'm coming in.
[OKITA]
I know what you're going to say.
[HIJIKATA]
Then that makes this easy.
So you're dead-set on going?
Yes.
Despite your condition?
I may be old, but I'm not blind.
How many years have we
known each other now, Juuzo?
Let me go instead.
That takes courage, too.
[OKITA] This voyage
of 168,000 light-years,
may take every bit
of life that I have left.
But I will lead my crew.
And, I will return.
Understood. I won't argue.
Not with a wall.
Take care of Earth.
Give 'em hell.
♪
[ambulance siren blaring]
[bell dings]
So, I hear you'll be
serving on the Yamato , too.
I requested pilot. I want to
be in the wing like my brother.
Well, I'm sorry,
but you're going to be
assigned to accounting.
[scissors snip]
[HIKOSHICHI]
You don't have to go, Dad.
[KIKUKO]
You're retiring in two months!
He asked me to go and take care
of this new engine for him.
That's all the reason I need.
[TASUKE]
Well, it's time, Aiko.
Say goodbye to
your grandpa, okay?
[AIKO]
Grandpa!
Oh, come here, sweetheart.
[chuckles]
I'll be back.
Not even light-years
could keep me from you.
[FEMALE STATION ANNOUNCEMENT 2A]
All embarking personnel,
please have your
identification ready...
[JIRO]
Daisuke!
Jiro! Hey, what's the matter?
Mom asked me
to give this to you.
She said she forgot
to give it to Dad,
so she wanted to make sure
that you have it for good luck.
[SHIMA]
I see.
She worries way too much.
But that's Mom.
Well, don't you worry.
I'm making it back
no matter what.
So you just take good care
of Mom until then.
You promise?
[JIRO]
Mhmm.
Rioting continues day
and night in District Six,
while in District Seven the
Management Center Building
has been leveled by a bomb,
with rioters
claiming responsibility.
The Far East Sector government
is asking all citizens
to remain calm while
resources can be distrib--
I'm coming back. You'll see.
I'm so worried I'm nauseous.
The ship's OMCS should
be perfectly capable
of producing alcohol, sir.
No, for Mew!
Oh, I'm sure she'll be fine.
[MALE LOADING OPERATOR 2A]
Inspections completed.
All systems go.
[MALE LOADING OPERATOR 2B]
Direct all personnel transports
to Deck Three for boarding.
[MALE LOADING OPERATOR 2A]
Maintenance and repair teams,
you are clear
to load the planes.
[REPAIRMAN 2A]
I guess this one goes
to the autopilot room, right?
[ENOMOTO]
Hm?
[ENOMOTO chuckles]
[MALE LOADING OPERATOR 2B]
All reporting personnel...
What's this?
[MALE LOADING OPERATOR 2B]
...and check in for onboard
orientation and
receipt of uniforms.
All crewmembers
have reported, sir.
No one chose to stay.
[OKITA] Mm. So all that's
left now is the engine.
[SANADA] This is it,
the Wave Motion Core.
And that's the last
part we need
to get her up and running, huh?
[SANADA]
Engine response is confirmed.
[TOKUGAWA] Does that mean
we can start her now?
[SANADA]
No. That's going to take
more power than we have
at our disposal.
That's kind of mean of
our goddess, don't you think?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT VOICE 1A]
All personnel are to change
into their crew uniforms
immediately after checking in.
Follow your superior's orders
and remain on standby
at your station.
[KATO]
So you're in charge of Tactical.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT VOICE 1A]
All personnel are to change
into their crew uniforms
immediately after checking in.
Follow your superior's orders
and remain on standby
at your station.
Well, that makes you
my commanding officer now.
So, I'll obey your orders.
That said, if you
ever issue a command
that gets my men
killed for nothing...
...then trust me,
you'll pay for it.
You don't have to
worry about that.
[KATO]
We're all counting on you.
I'll make it.
I'm coming home for sure.
--[digital beep]
--[gasps]
[gasps] I didn't realize
you were part of the crew.
Yes. You're running Tactical.
Kodai, right?
Lieutenant Yuki Mori,
Chief Operations Officer.
Welcome aboard.
So where's our Captain?
[knock, knock]
Who is it?
[KODAI]
Susumu Kodai, sir.
Come in.
[KODAI]
Thank you.
What is it?
Well, it's about my role
as Chief Tactical Officer.
I just don't...
I don't think
I'm qualified, sir.
[OKITA] Most of our top
candidates for Division Leaders
were making on-site
preparations for the launch,
and were killed
in yesterday's bombing.
[KODAI]
But, sir.
[OKITA] And the soldier
who was supposed to
sit in your chair, Lieutenant.
Well, I'm responsible
for his death, too.
[KODAI gasps]
[OKITA] Mamoru Kodai,
your older brother.
[KODAI gasps]
I've examined your
service record myself.
And I've decided you're more
than capable of the position,
or at least worthy
of the chance.
From now on, it's up to you
to prove me right.
What's his problem, anyway?
He's got no manners.
[SHIMA]
Hey!
This is the First Bridge, huh?
It's really something.
I'm Lieutenant Daisuke Shima,
our Chief Navigation Officer.
We've met before, haven't we?
The captain's upstairs, okay!
[SHIMA]
Uh--
Oh. Hey, Kodai.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
So this is the
first bridge crew.
I'm Lieutenant Commander Sanada.
Is everyone ready?
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
[siren blaring]
To your stations, on the
double-- This is no drill.
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
Confirm the situation
with Command.
Receiving message now, sir.
Interplanetary ballistic missile
sited on path to Earth.
Assessed target.
[gasps]
Battleship Yamato !
But we can't launch yet, can we?
[ANALYZER] Negative.
Significantly more energy
required to reach
escape velocity.
The problem is where
we get that energy,
our grid is completely taxed.
Oh, man.
But we are gonna
make it, right, sir?
[OKITA]
Stay focused!
Go Comms. Get command
on the line, main screen.
Oh. Hello, Admiral.
We making any progress with
the power supply, Director?
We'll see. We've begun
routing all power from
the Far East Sector
into the Yamato 's main line.
But since we had no time
to test the activator
we have no way to know
if it's enough--
[OKITA]
Mmmm.
[siren blares]
Power in Far East
Sector is down.
All districts!
Switch to backup generators!
[MALE UNCF CONTROLLER 2A]
Switch to backup, confirmed.
If that's not enough power
we'll have to call off
the launch, and she'll be
a sitting duck out there.
[MALE UNCF CONTROLLER 2E]
Director,
you'll want to see this, sir.
[YABU]
Lieutenant, look!
I'll be.
[MALE UNCF CONTROLLER 2E]
North America, Africa, Eurasia,
all sectors are rerouting power!
The whole world
is answering the call,
giving the ship every
kilowatt they can spare.
How's it look?
[YAMAZAKI] It worked, Chief.
We can fire her up.
[OKITA] Mm!
Activate Wave Motion Engine!
[TOKUGAWA] Activating now.
Connecting flywheel.
Pressure rising.
Ninety. Ninety-six.
One hundred percent.
Energy charge at 120!
Wave Motion Engine live.
RPMs looking good.
Here we go!
[MORI] Interplanetary
ballistic missile spotted!
Straighten the ship for launch!
Remove camouflage!
[KODAI]
What is this?
[ANALYZER] Prototype built
within existing vessel,
providing camouflage
to deceive enemy.
Camouflage. That explains it--
the sunken battleship
in that dried sea bed!
Yes, Lieutenant.
We're on board her now.
The Space Battleship Yamato !
If we want her to see space,
we need to blow that missile
out of the sky.
Prepare to fire the cannons!
Prepare the main cannons.
Let's go!
[MALE OFFICER 2D]
Man your positions!
Open the throttle!
Let's get her airborne!
[SHIMA] Aye-aye, Captain!
Launching Yamato now!
♪
Shock cannons live.
The engine has charged them
to maximum power.
Target is sighted.
Engage the automatic tracking.
[NANBU]
Automatic tracking engaged.
Locking on target.
Correcting for errors,
minus 1.3.
[KODAI]
Target lock.
Open fire, full bore!
Fire!
[MALE UNCF CONTROLLER 2A] Power
coming back on line, sir.
[SERIZAWA, TODO gasp]
Where's the Yamato ?
If that missile struck,
it may have been incinerated.
[MALE UNCF CONTROLLER 2A]
No damage, sir!
The Yamato is fine!
[SANADA]
Releasing Wave Motion Shields.
That didn't even
leave a scratch.
[OTA exhales]
Kodai.
Yes, sir?
That was well done.
[SHIMA]
Would it kill you to smile?
[OKITA]
The time has come to embark,
and the Space Battleship
Yamato sets course
for Iscandar,
the planet of hope.
This vessel and her crew
are the only ones
who can journey across the stars
and save our civilization.
But we don't even
fully understand
the new power we hold.
Now the Yamato 's true
strength will be revealed.
Is it too much for us?
Next time: "Escape from
the Jupiter Sphere."
There are 364 days left
before humanity becomes extinct.