[SHIMA] This is the Yamato 's
current location.
Our next warp should take us out
here, past the protostar cluster
that marks the edge
of the Milky Way.
Forty-one kiloparsecs
separate our galaxy
and the Large Magellanic Cloud.
In other words,
we still have over
130,000 more light years
of unknown space ahead of us.
[OKITA]
Mm.
We're expecting far fewer
run-ins with the enemy
once we leave the Milky Way.
Oh, what makes you think that?
It's a guess.
When you consider the
requirements for life,
it's a numbers game.
The Milky Way is larger, with
many more potential systems,
meaning it's most probable
the Gamilas System
is in our own galaxy.
[NANBU]
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
[OKITA]
Hm...
[KODAI]
I'll leave the math to you guys,
I'll just be glad to have them
off our backs for a while.
I'm shocked you're so relaxed.
Is this all a game to you?
[gasps]
Hey, what's your problem?
My problem is you're
losing your edge, Kodai.
[KODAI]
"Losing my edge"?
What are you talking about?
I work every bit
as hard as you do.
You're being too idealistic, and
forgetting who the enemy is!
Oh, I see, so this
is about Melda!
[SHIMA]
The enemy Gamilan pilot, yeah!
[KODAI] And what does she
have to do with any of this?
Everything, because
if you respect her
you must believe her!
You think we fired first and
started the war, just admit it!
Don't put words in
my mouth, Shima!
You aren't denying it!
[NANBU]
Guys, just breathe, okay?
[SHIMA, KODAI]
Shut the hell up, Nanbu!
Enough, you idiots!
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH gasp]
[DR. SADO] Your blood pressure's
a little high, Captain.
[OKITA]
Duly noted.
[DR. SADO]
I heard about the drama.
The young ones have tempers
like sticks of dynamite.
Ya better watch
your own fuse, too.
[OKITA chuckles]
You can always read my mind.
[KODAI]
Curse that old man.
"You lack the self-awareness
required of an officer."
This is how they punish
little grade school kids!
Hey.
Can we wrap this up and
move to the next one?
[SHIMA]
I'm done.
[KODAI] I hear they're offering
a "Milky Way Lunch"
in the galley.
Limited time only!
Wanna check it out?
[sighs] Whatever.
[TOKUGAWA] Hm...
You told all that to Shima?
[YAMAZAKI]
Yeah.
I see.
That explains why
he was so upset.
So, do you regret telling him?
I don't.
He's Daigo Shima's son, he
can handle the hard truth.
He just needs more time
to come to terms with it.
At least, that's how I see it.
[YABU] I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Those higher ups can be
surprisingly fragile.
All right, see you
next shift, sir.
[gasps]
I see.
Thanks, Yabu.
It helps immensely.
[YABU gasps]
You're welcome, Lieutenant.
[DESLER'S COURTESANS]
One moment, please.
Our Supreme Lord is
using the hotline
and is not to be interrupted.
The hotline...?
Get out of the way!
--But ma'am--
--[CELESTRA] I said move!
[DESLER laughs]
Well forgive me
if I've jumped to
erroneous conclusions.
But you can understand why
I'd suspect such a thing.
I thought you had gone
back to your old tricks
out of pity for them.
You're my empire's
heart and soul.
So, I worry about anything
coming between us.
Peace across the galaxies
will only be possible
through our
enduring friendship.
Agreed?
I think a conversation in
person is long overdue.
Let's make it happen, shall we?
And what brings you
two to my chambers?
Preparations for
Senior General Domel's
medal ceremony
are complete.
Glad to hear it.
And what about you, Gimleh?
I've come to report the Imperial
Guard's latest findings
about rogue elements
within the Empire, sir.
My secret police have
much to address.
I'm going to let you
make those calls.
You're free to handle
things however you wish.
Thank you, my lord, I
will not let you down.
[DESLER]
More importantly...
[CELESTRA] That's the Teron
vessel, isn't it, my lord?
The obvious question has always
been: where are they heading?
Where do they hope
their journey will end?
It now appears I've
found the answer.
[GAMILAN CITIZENS]
Garle Domel!
Garle Domel! Garle Domel!
Hold on.
These are for you, sir!
Thank you.
[GAMILAN CITIZENS]
Garle Domel!
Garle Domel! Garle Domel!
Garle Phezeron!
Perhaps you've been
wondering why
I've recalled you from
the front lines, General.
I imagine it was
hard to swallow.
The border of the
Small Magellanic Cloud
is the lynchpin of our defenses.
The absence of the commanding
officer aids the enemy, sir.
Perhaps, but sadly
we've encountered
another problem in the
Milky Way Theater.
[DOMEL]
Yes, I've heard the rumors.
A Teron ship has broken through
our line and evaded our grasp.
I understand we also
lost Shultz to them.
You've done so admirably
against the other barbarians,
I'd like you to handle
this new breed, as well.
What say you, General?
I am a soldier, loyal to you and
the almighty Gamilas Empire,
my lord. I do as you command.
[applause]
All hail the shining
star of Gamilas!
All hail Lord Desler!
[VELTE] A promotion
to High Chief General?
I'm happy for you, Space Wolf,
but what concerns me is your
popularity among the people.
Keep your guard up.
Imperial Command's full
of ambitious climbers,
and many of them resent your
meteoric rise to the top.
I know for a fact that your
new direct superior Goer
is one of "Sideburns"
Zoellik's lackeys.
Thank you, Admiral, but I have
no interest in politics.
[DITZ, VELTE grunt]
Baleras has changed
a great deal.
Oh, I forgot to tell you, I'm
glad to hear your Melda's safe.
She must have come home
with quite a juicy story.
Ha! My daughter has
been impossible!
She refuses to share a single
detail about the ordeal
or how she survived!
It's torture!
Are you paying attention
to this, Elk?
Even the fearsome Admiral Ditz
has a chink in his armor.
Shut up, Talan.
If I may, Admiral.
I have a request.
[DITZ grunts]
Your special operations vessel--
could you lend it
to me for a while?
Tell me why.
[IMPERIAL GUARD 12A]
Halt.
[DITZ]
What's wrong?
[DRIVER 12A]
Imperial Guard checkpoint.
Your ID.
[IMPERIAL GUARDS chattering]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 12B]
Forgive me, officers!
What's going on here, soldier?
[IMPERIAL GUARD 12B] Sabotage
at the Floating Plant, sir.
[DOMEL]
Who are they?
They're rebel forces
we rooted out.
They look like ordinary
citizens to me.
Better safe than sorry.
Director Gimleh has
ordered they all be sent
to the prison planet
immediately.
[REBELS groan]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 12B]
You're free to pass.
Garle Desler!
[DITZ]
Curse that Gimleh.
[VELTE] What you said earlier
was right, General.
Baleras has most
certainly changed.
[VELTE] Sure you want
to be dropped off here?
[DOMEL]
Yes.
As for your request, Domel.
I'll make the
arrangements tonight.
Thank you, Admiral.
[VELTE]
Is this wise?
Doesn't that ship need approval
from Lord Desler himself?
I'm the Supreme Commander
of the Astrofleets.
All right, all right,
just forget I asked.
The Inspector-General
continues to expand
our territory at
a reckless speed,
while that Jirel witch spreads
her blatantly false propaganda.
The Viceroy is nothing more
than a useless figurehead,
while the Guard's
excessive cruelties
are only matched by
their arrogance.
And then there's our leader.
Did you know he fully intends
to move the capital?
[DITZ]
Away from Baleras?
It's his Great Unification.
How did we get here?
And where exactly are we going?
[DITZ]
Don't play philosopher.
It doesn't suit you.
[ROKROHK squawks]
Honestly, I didn't think you'd
remember it was today.
I'm glad you did.
I'm back briefly at
our lord's request.
[ELISA]
Oh.
[ROKROHK croaks]
[BOY 12A]
Look, it's a rokrhok!
Let's catch it!
Come down!
[BOY 12B grunts]
[ELISA] That's how old he'd
be if he were alive.
What did our Supreme Lord
want from you this time?
[DOMEL] He ordered me to command
the Milky Way Theater.
[gasps]
Hey!
Look!
The Milky Way is far from here.
Indeed.
[ELISA]
So very, very far.
I know.
[DOMEL]
Before long we will be united,
with nothing between us.
Now watch from your perch.
As the Space Wolf I've
released catches his prey
and crushes them with his
fierce and deadly jaws.
[MISAKI]
Uh!
Dr. Sado!
They did survive it but
with massive trauma.
One of them seems to
have severe amnesia.
[DR. SADO] An accident like
that, what are the odds?
[MALE DOCTOR 12B] Some are
saying it was terrorism.
[MISAKI gasps]
[HAYASHI humming]
[HAYASHI]
Auto-nav system check complete.
All good.
[gasps]
[MISAKI gasping]
[MISAKI yelps]
[panting]
[HARADA]
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you havin' a nightmare
or somethin'?
[MISAKI]
Mm-hm. Uh, yeah.
There was this beautiful woman.
[HARADA] Doesn't sound like a
nightmare to me.
[MISAKI]
No! Wait, you don't understand!
[sighs]
[HARADA]
No way, Hayashi!
You saw her too!
That's right.
It was a beautiful woman.
By the auto-navigation
room, huh?
She looked just like
the Lieutenant!
You're working too much.
But! Dr. Sado, everyone
says that room's haunted!
She's the ghost of the ship!
Hey, she's not like a spooky
ghost in a bed sheet!
How should I know
what she wears?
She doesn't wear anything, okay!
Don't be a pervert!
[DR. SADO]
Knock it off!
Just take this and sleep!
[HAYASHI]
A tranquilizer?
[HAYASHI] She looked
just like Mori, I swear.
[HARADA] Maybe Lieutenant Niimi
should be treating him instead.
--[DR. SADO groans]
--[door hisses]
--[KODAI] Doctor.
--[DR. SADO] Hm?
I'm done cleaning the exam room.
Perfect! Good work, kid!
[HOSHINA] Ensign Yamamoto, you
are now released from the brig.
Six days is a lot.
Hope it wasn't too rough!
[YAMAMOTO gasping]
Just don't do anything
else stupid.
Hm?
But I lost a valuable
fighter plane.
I don't deserve to fly.
A good squadron values
the pilot over the plane.
[gasps]
Heh. Yeah, you're stuck with us.
[harmonica plays]
[MORI]
So, you finish your punishment?
That's right.
Shined and polished.
So, you like playing, huh?
Yeah, I do. It's therapy.
It just helps me relax.
I see.
Hey, do you think I'd
ever be able to pilot
one of these things like
Yamamoto does?
[KODAI]
No way.
[gasps] Oh yeah,
and why's that?!
You came down to talk
to me about her, right?
[gasps]
[KODAI]
I understand how she feels.
A big part of me doesn't
want to believe it, either.
After all,
I lost my family to
the Gamilans, too.
[KODAI]
But our side isn't blameless.
My brother died never
knowing he was a decoy.
I'm sorry.
[KODAI]
Don't frown on my account.
[gasps]
I think I've finally
made peace with it all.
I'm just putting my trust
in the Captain.
But it's different for Shima.
He still has a family
back home to protect.
And to tell you the truth
maybe I'm jealous
of him for that.
Well don't be.
You can make a new family now.
Everyone on board
is your family.
I guess you're right.
[TOKUGAWA] You've still
got a mom and brother
back home, don't you?
[TOKUGAWA]
I'm lucky.
My eldest has a wife and child,
and I've got a second son, too.
Oh yeah?
[TOKUGAWA] The younger
one says he actually wants
to follow in his old man's
footsteps one day.
As a sailor?
A rather fanciful dream now
that we've lost our fleet.
But still, it must be
nice to hear, right?
Eh. No, I don't need
to pass the torch.
[SHIMA]
Uh?
I'm more concerned
about my grandkid.
She deserves to be happy
and I can't die
until I find her a good match!
It's not gonna be
easy finding someone
who meets your high
standards, Chief!
Oh, I know, maybe you'll
want to marry her!
Aiko's going to be a
magnificent woman,
you'd be a perfect couple!
No! I'm not really looking to--
[gasps]
I'll get back to you
in twenty years.
[BOTH laugh]
Listen, Shima.
[SHIMA]
Huh?
We don't always
come to the table
with the same set of facts.
You act on what
you think is true.
And the other side may see it
a completely different way.
But in the end,
there's only one reality.
War did start, and now we all
have to suffer through it.
Yet despite all the
painful losses,
you and I still
have family left.
That makes us pretty damn lucky,
don't you think?
[knocking]
[KODAI]
It's Lieutenant Kodai.
Excuse me, sir.
This room's last on my list.
Uh!
[OKITA] Your timing's excellent.
I was just thinking that I would
like to talk to you, Lieutenant.
[KODAI gasps]
[YAMAMOTO grunting]
[SHIMA]
So, you finished your sentence.
Six days staring at a wall.
Since when are you
on cleaning detail?
[SHIMA]
Huh? Oh.
Some get the brig
and some get the mop.
[OKITA] That day,
I disobeyed orders, too.
[gasps]
[OKITA]
I opposed the preemptive attack,
and was removed from command.
So that's what really happened?
Do you think what
I did was right?
Of course I do!
I second-guessed my superior.
A good soldier is never supposed
to disobey an order.
No matter what.
[KODAI]
Yeah, but Captain--
And yet, there are extreme
times when a soldier must
remember a higher duty and be
a good human being instead.
People make mistakes
regardless of rank.
You need the courage to disobey
an order you believe is wrong,
especially when
lives are at stake.
In war, it's the only way
you can live with yourself
once the bloodshed is over.
I understand how you felt.
You wanted to shoot her down
to avenge your family.
And yet my sworn enemy
ended up saving my life.
For all we know that was a
trick, the point is you were
staying true to yourself
and our side!
Maybe Kodai's being too
naive about Melda Ditz,
thinking we can
understand each other.
That said,
I do understand a little now.
[gasps]
[DAIGO]
Don't worry.
Your old man isn't
going there to fight.
I'm sure we can forge a
friendship with this alien race.
But she's the enemy.
Don't you hate her?
I did at first,
but not anymore.
[SHIMA]
You think so?
I do.
Never lose hope, son.
[YAMAMOTO] I had plenty of
time to cool my head.
[SHIMA] I see.
[ding]
Kodai's been worried about you.
I'm heading up there soon.
[SHIMA]
Akira.
Thank you for the chat.
[SHIMA grunts]
I'll cool my head, too.
So, that Milky Way Lunch in
the galley, still goin' on?
It ends next week.
At least, I think.
Are you free tomorrow?
You bet.
[gasps]
Report!
[OTA]
Hit to port side!
Looks like a torpedo!
[OKITA]
The Yamato hides,
like wounded prey, while an
invisible hunter searches
with eyes that penetrate
normal space,
sharpening its fangs
for a lethal strike.
Is there any escape from
that dreaded bite?
Listen across the cold expanse,
and you might just
hear the howl.
Next time: The Wolf
from Another Dimension.
There are three 317 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.