[COMMS. 13A] Space-time
fluctuation has increased
from zel 0-5-0 to zel 0-7-0.
ETA unchanged.
[COMMS. 13A] Seventh Squadron,
proceed to dock five.
Sixth and Thirteenth Destroyer
Groups, proceed to dock nine.
[COMMS. 13A] Port crew,
begin anchoring procedures.
Mechanic team,
stand by for further orders.
Official orders straight
from Lord Desler.
Effective tam 12-0-8.
Domel, Commander of
SMC Defense Forces.
Appointed Commander of Milky
Way Theater Operations.
His predecessor,
Major General Goer,
will serve as his
second in command.
End of orders.
[GOER grunts]
[HEYDELN]
General.
A message from Flaken.
"The great dance between the
hunter and hunted, begins."
What does that mean,
has something happened?
It seems The Hound has
tracked down his prey.
[MORI] Two enemy torpedoes
have struck a planetesimal.
Distance: three megameters.
No doubt it's another
attempt to find us.
[SANADA] The interstellar medium
around this protostar
is immense, with hundreds
of places to hide.
As long as we don't move, it's
going to be hard to find us.
It was an excellent
tactical choice, Captain.
The question is, where did
those torpedoes come from?
Anything on radar?
Negative. I tried to back-trace
but nothing's there.
Must be some kinda
stealth ship.
We've already spent four
hours on this rock.
We can't hide here forever.
[MORI]
Another incoming!
[NANBU]
Huh?
[MORI] Explosion, ten o'clock,
distance: 200 kilometers!
[sonar pings]
[KIEL] Close subspace vents and
adjust course from 22 to 30.
Dimensional pressure normal.
Phase displacement
in normal range.
We aren't detecting their
ship's Wave Motion pattern.
I thought we'd have
flushed them out by now.
With all the noise from
that interstellar medium
we can't pinpoint
their spatial wake
until they rev their engine.
Intelligent little vermin,
aren't they?
[HEINI]
Huh?
[FLAKEN] Good. Smarter
prey means a better hunt.
Cheer up, Heini.
If we have to be at war,
might as well enjoy it.
Small dimensional quakes?
Captain, this is only a theory,
but these readings from
our sensors remind me
of that dimensional fault
we were trapped in.
Maybe they have a ship that
can tunnel into subspace
similar to how we tunneled out.
[OKITA groans]
Captain?
[thud]
[KODAI]
Captain!
Doctor, what is this?
There's not much time.
Go get the operation room ready.
[HARADA]
Yes, sir.
[SANADA] As the XO,
I'll be taking command of
the Yamato until Captain Okita
is fit to return to duty.
We'll assume the enemy ship
is capable of controlled
and sustained
inter-dimensional travel
as a means of stealth assault.
Niimi and Mori, try to find
a way to track them.
[NIIMI]
Yes, sir.
[KODAI] A ship that can hide
in other dimensions?
[GOER]
Dimensional Submarine UX-01
is under our supreme
lord's direct control.
I'm shocked his office gave
you permission to bring it
all the way out to the
galactic hinterlands.
[DOMEL] They didn't,
because I didn't bother to ask.
You can't be serious!
[BERGER]
Don't worry, Major General.
[GOER growls]
Lord Desler has
official control,
but it's still the
Admiral's vessel.
That's right.
If old man Ditz
signed off on it,
there's nothing to worry about.
The real problem is
that beast at the helm,
not the ship itself.
Yeah, no doubt about that.
Captain Flaken's a
hard man to control.
[GOER growling]
[DOMEL]
Keep this in mind, Goer.
We either adapt or die.
[GOER grunts]
Right. Zar... Belk.
[caws]
[MEDIC STAFF 13A]
Blood pressure 120 over 75.
Pulse 60.
[DR. SADO]
Hang in there.
I'm gonna take care
of ya, Captain.
Begin the operation.
[MEDIC STAFF 13A]
Activating medical drone.
[HARADA]
Medical nanomachines on standby.
[HEINI]
Anything?
[HEINI growls]
Now what, Captain?
Our prey is clever,
but they're also too
frightened to take action.
[HEINI grunts]
[FLAKEN] They fear the
hunter in the darkness.
They're waiting for us
to make the next move.
Come on!
How long are we gonna sit
here twiddling our thumbs?
This sucks!
Look, the officers know what
they're doing, is that clear?
[YABU] But I heard that Captain
Okita collapsed and had to be
carried off the bridge. What
are we gonna do if he dies?
Yabu!
[gasps]
[YABU]
Huh? Oh, hey Chief!
When did you get here?
You don't have to worry
about that, Yabu.
The Captain will survive.
He'll get us through this.
You hear me?
Yes, sir!
[DR. SADO]
Sweat.
[SHIMA]
Any sign of 'em?
No, but even if dimensional
submersion is possible
there'd be a limit to how
long they could stay there.
They're bound to
surface eventually.
[SHIMA] So, we just have
to keep waiting, huh?
Great.
[footsteps]
Uh?
I've never seen you
this tense before, Kodai.
Waiting's hard for
a soldier, isn't it?
Yeah.
[HEINI]
Haven't we waited long enough?
For all we know, one of
our torpedoes got lucky
and already blew them up, sir.
I agree with you.
[HEINI]
Huh?
[FLAKEN]
We have waited long enough.
No more hide and seek.
We're going to give
something else a try.
[DR. SADO]
Four hundred more cc's of blood.
And that's a wrap.
[sighs]
[KODAI]
XO.
If you know more,
then please tell us.
Kodai.
What's wrong with
Captain Okita, sir?
[ping]
[MORI]
Ship on radar!
Four o'clock, distance:
23 megameters.
The wavelength they're emitting
is specific to Gamilan ships.
That must be it!
[MORI] Sir. They appear
to be leaving the system.
So, they're retreating?
They must've given up
on trying to find us.
Hold on.
We shouldn't assume that.
It's possible that's a decoy.
Are you basing that on evidence?
There's nothing I can point to.
I suppose you could
just call it a hunch.
I see. It runs in
the family, then.
I was just saying that I agree
with you, Lieutenant Kodai.
Here's a thought. We could use
the warp engine's subsystems
as a transducer to convert a
signal beyond normal space.
We can use the dimensional fault
data to set the parameters,
and see what bounces back.
It would be like firing
a sonar ping
across the dimensional
phase boundary.
Dimensional active
sonar! Brilliant!
That would tell us if a ship
is still hiding in
another dimension!
Yeah, but that's a
double-edged sword.
Firing a ping from our ship
would reveal our position, too.
If you allow your
fear to paralyze you
then you'll never take action.
I suggest flying a
Seagull to patrol
for hostiles instead, sir.
You mean with the new
subspace sonar buoys?
Yes. That could basically
work the same way, right?
They would show us
if something's hiding
in another dimension.
Theoretically, yes.
But trying to navigate
a Seagull through all this
interstellar medium
would be far too dangerous.
It's a death sentence!
Better than risking
the whole crew!
It's a way to search
without revealing
the Yamato 's position!
And which unlucky pilot
are you going to send out
into that minefield, Kodai?
I'll fly it myself!
No, you won't.
[KODAI]
What?
We've seen a ship leaving,
this is only confirmation.
Niimi's correct.
It would be far too dangerous
just to follow a hunch.
But XO!
[SANADA]
That's final.
Niimi, prepare transduction
for dimensional ping.
[NIIMI]
Yes, sir.
[beeping]
[DR. SADO]
Doctor Sado to CIC.
[CREW gasps]
[DR. SADO]
The Captain's operation is over.
It's looking good.
[ALL sigh]
Can I make a suggestion, XO?
Send one of us to check
on the Captain,
it might help with morale.
We can handle things here.
[KODAI]
Uh?
[OKITA] You need the courage
to disobey an order
you believe is wrong, especially
when lives are at stake.
In war, it's the only way
you can live with yourself
once the bloodshed is over.
You came to see him, huh?
[KODAI]
Take good care of him, Doc.
Don't do anything stupid.
[NANBU] Inputting Wave
Motion parameters.
[NIIMI]
Parameters confirmed...
[KITANO]
Kitano reporting.
It's about time!
[KITANO]
Sorry, sir.
[ANALYZER]
Charging is now complete.
Prepare to ping.
Subspace transducer
is standing by, sir.
You're asking us to load
up the buoys now, sir?
That's right.
I'll launch as soon
as they're ready.
But they're ready
right now, sir,
we already put them on board.
[gasps]
[ENOMOTO] A good sailor
stays one step ahead.
[KODAI]
Enomoto!
You remember that from
training, don't ya?
All right clowns, let's go!
We're launchin' the Seagull!
Uh! But don't we have to
wait for the order, sir?
Yeah, we haven't
received it yet.
[ENOMOTO]
Let me worry about that.
So, let's get moving.
And to make sure our Chief of
Tactical has what he needs,
you two are coming with us.
[IWATA, TOYAMA gasping]
[NANBU]
Dimensional sonar ping ready.
Prepare to track the enemy.
Fire the sonar ping.
[KITANO]
Firing!
[sonar ping]
And there she goes!
Ha! They fell for the decoy
just like we hoped, sir.
If those fools really thought
we were still here
they wouldn't have
betrayed their position!
I take it we were able
to back-trace that ping?
[MEZZE]
Affirmative, sir.
[HEINI]
Can we finally strike now?
Before I go mad?
Bring the vessel up to
periscope depth and stand by.
[HEINI] You heard 'im,
blow the dimensional tanks!
Let the real hunt begin.
We've got something, sir.
It's a ship.
Looks like they're moving closer
to the phase boundary.
[gasps]
[MORI]
They must have traced our ping!
Start engine! Get us out of
here as fast as possible!
Raise the anchor!
[FLAKEN]
Look what I found.
Prepare to fire torpedoes.
Open torpedo tubes one and two!
[gasps] XO. A hangar door
just opened on portside!
What?
[AIHARA] Seagull, you are
not authorized to launch.
We told you, sir!
Seagull launching now.
[IWATA]
Huh?!
Uh, sir? Are you disobeying
them on purpose?
Quit your bellyaching
and get to work!
--[TOYAMA] Yes, sir!
--[IWATA] What?!
Torpedo parameters
are set, Captain.
Fire torpedo tubes one and two.
Let's see them escape from that.
[HEINI]
Tubes one and two, fire!
[FLAKEN]
Heh, heh.
Yamato to Seagull,
please respond!
Who's on board?!
[ping]
[MORI gasps]
Two objects approaching
the Yamato at high speed!
[ALL gasp]
Computing...
They're torpedoes, sir!
He was right.
Shima!
Taking evasive action!
[SHIMA grunts]
[MORI]
Second torpedo approaching!
[COMBAT OFFICERS scream]
Not too shabby kid.
What can I say, I had
one hell of a teacher.
Ah, don't make me blush.
Hey, what's wrong
with the Yamato ?
[KITANO] Armor plating
has been penetrated.
Effectiveness down to 18%.
[TOKUGAWA]
Engine output dropping.
[SANADA]
Seal deck ten!
[NANBU]
That ping came back to bite us.
Send in damage control.
[KODAI]
Seagull to Yamato . Do you copy?
That's Kodai!
[KODAI] Please be advised.
We're about to drop the buoys.
They already found us!
What do you think you're doing?!
Ooh, scary.
All right, let's do this.
Drop the buoys now!
[BOTH]
Aye-aye, lieutenant!
Dropping them now!
[FLAKEN]
Our prey's hide is thick.
Tube Three. Tube Four.
Open fire!
[KODAI]
Seagull to Yamato .
I'll use the buoys to send you
estimated emergence points
for the torpedoes,
so you can shoot them down.
Listen to me!
Let's try it.
Prepare weapons to intercept.
Understood.
Prepare to intercept!
[KITANO]
Preparing now, sir!
[TOYAMA]
Looks like it's working.
We found them!
[IWATA]
Two torpedoes!
Transmit to the Yamato .
[IWATA]
Roger!
Target coordinates received
and entered, sir.
Intercept torpedoes.
Yes sir, firing now!
[FLAKEN grunts] They anticipated
our firing angle?
[HEINI]
But how?
--[ping]
--[HEINI gasps] More sonar?
Tenacious little vermin,
aren't they.
They may be able to see us,
but we're still in
another dimension.
They won't be able
to touch us here.
[gasps]
[FLAKEN]
So that's their trick.
[IWATA]
Whoa.
What is that thing?
Something else just emerged from
the phase boundary, lieutenant!
Where is it?
[IWATA]
Close!
Okay, got it. Turning now.
Tell me when you have a visual.
Ah-ha. Gotcha!
Heh.
[KODAI]
Seagull to Yamato .
We've found an apparent
enemy probe behind you,
at four o'clock.
Sending you the coordinates now.
If you can knock it out,
you'll blind them.
Evidently recklessness
runs in the family, as well.
[SANADA]
Prepare to fire!
[KITANO]
Inputting coordinates!
Locked on target!
All right, fire
the shock cannons!
[gasps] They got us.
[KODAI]
Approaching the Yamato .
Pre-landing check.
Preparing Seagull to dock.
Navigation, as soon as he's
secure in the hangar,
get us out of here at
maximum possible speed.
Once we're clear of this rubble
we're going to warp
to lose them.
No sign of them on radar.
Then those slippery mongrels
must have already jumped.
What's our next move, sir?
For now, we're going
to let them go.
You sure, Captain?
Good hunters don't
need to chase.
We'll pick up their
scent again eventually.
[OKITA grunting]
Hey, Captain.
Hello, Kodai.
This is quite the
welcoming party.
Is the ship all right?
It was close, but we made
it through, Captain.
Thanks to the moxie of
some of our young sailors.
You pushed the envelope a bit
too far, if you ask me.
[HARADA, KODAI gasp]
But despite your disobedience,
Sanada's gonna let you
off the hook this time.
Don't let that stern
look of his fool ya.
He's not a bad guy.
Oh, I see.
[NIIMI]
You didn't want him
to risk his life out there
in the Seagull, did you?
That's why you didn't
agree to his plan
even though he had a point.
But he believed he was doing
the right thing, for all of us,
and acted anyway.
And what would he have done,
if he were in command?
[gasps] Well, sir.
It's just a guess,
but I think he would've done
the exact same thing.
[SANADA]
I think you're right.
[OKITA] A siren's song lures
ships to their doom,
and a mysterious prowler
lurks in the shadows,
making mischief with
her victims' memories.
The Yamato is shipwrecked, but
what has happened to her crew?
Can Kodai and Mori make sense
of the madness they see?
Next time:
The Whisper of the Witch.
There are 310 left before the
extinction of the human race.