You would demote me?
But why do I deserve that?
You have brought
shame on Lord Desler
and his great campaign
in the hinterlands.
You seem to be incapable of
dealing with the Yamato problem.
And since I recommended you to
command that galactic theater,
that puts me in
jeopardy, as well.
You have nothing
to worry about, sir!
I can take care of
one measly Teron vessel!
Perhaps you've spent too long
commanding off-worlders,
but we true Gamilans
do not tolerate failure.
And I won't tolerate
it from you.
Sir! Yes, sir!
I shall await the
good news, Goer.
[GOER]
Zar Belk!
Commander.
There's still no sign of
that ship that vanished.
It's been several days now!
So?
But that ship was carrying
an Information Officer
from the Imperial Guard, sir!
The only ship that matters
right now is the Yamato !
We have to find those
Terons and crush them!
[MONK]
Their predicted trajectory.
They should be within the
seven-korm sector by now.
[GOER]
I'm assuming command!
Launch the fleet, now!
[FIGHTER SQUAD B]
Ha! Full house strikes again!
[SAWAMURA]
Man, you're on a tear!
Well, be careful,
Bro, and good luck.
[NIIMI] Attention: Ship now
entering warp navigation.
All crew, prepare
for warp procedures.
I've gotten used to this.
Yeah what can we
say, we're a bunch of old pros.
[SHIMA]
Coordinates entered.
Galactic longitude is 274.76.
Galactic latitude
is minus 12.73.
Distance: 63.7 parsecs, confirm.
Confirmed.
Coordinate axis fixed.
[TOKUGAWA] Wave Motion Engine
chamber pressure rising.
Critical pressure
has now been achieved.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
And warp!
Aye-aye!
What is this?
Yeah, it's not
usually like this.
What's going on, ensign?
The ship doesn't seem to
be coming out of warp, sir.
I see.
We're currently inhabiting
the single nanosecond
of space time the ship passes
through during warp travel.
This has never
happened before, has it?
[OKITA]
Could it be the auto-nav?
Lieutenant, go check the
automatic navigation room.
Sir.
Attention all crew,
this is the XO.
Look, you guys.
If you're having blurry vision,
then you've probably
got a case of the jitters.
[SHINOHARA]
I don't think so, pal.
That's odd, what's
happening to me?
[gasps]
[MISAKI]
Huh?
[MISAKI sighs]
[groans]
[MORI]
Misaki?
Can you hear me?
[gasps]
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Where'd we come out?
And how?
Inspect systems for damage.
Radar and scanner online,
but they're blank.
Long-range transmission
seems to be working, too.
But we most likely can't
communicate very far.
Those signals won't
resonate beyond this space
to reach the outside.
Captain.
I think the most
likely explanation
is we've fallen into
a dimensional fault.
You mean where
dimensions intersect.
A gap space
created between them.
[TOKUGAWA]
Engine room to bridge.
I don't know what's causing
it or where it's going.
But the Wave Motion Engine
is leaking energy, Captain.
Then shut her down.
[OKITA] This fault seems to be
causing an inverse reaction.
Normally, energy flows
from other dimensions
into the Wave Motion Engine
for a nearly infinite supply.
But here, energy is leaking
from the engine to the outside.
[ANALYZER]
Warning.
Multiple unidentified
objects ahead.
[gasps]
What the hell?
This place is
like a ship graveyard.
[SANADA]
They probably couldn't escape.
Doomed to wander this
dimensional fault for eternity.
It's like a
Sargasso Sea in space.
Nothing unusual, sir.
[SANADA]
Understood.
[ANALYZER] Gamilan ship
detected at eleven o'clock.
Identified as L-Class cruiser.
It's online!
The Gamilan vessel appears
to be armed and on high alert!
It looks like they're alone.
Should we attack?
We clearly have the
advantage in firepower!
If two lions chest-deep
in quicksand
choose to fight each other
instead of trying to escape,
both will sink and perish.
I'm betting the
Gamilans understand that
just as well as we do.
Captain, we're being
hailed by the enemy ship.
Let's open a channel.
[AIHARA]
Alpha Two, stand by in catapult.
Cosmo Zero now
ready for takeoff.
Fighter spotted, sir.
They've launched it.
Launch the Cosmo Zero.
[AIHARA]
Yamato to Alpha Two.
You are instructed to escort
the Gamilan plane
safely to Hangar Three.
I don't buy this "envoy"
business, it's a trap.
They claim they know how
to get out of this place,
so it's a risk we have to take.
Yeah, but it doesn't
make any sense.
If they know how to escape,
then why are they still here?
We're gonna
find out soon enough.
[MAINTENANCE]
Pressurize Hangar Three.
Stay on your toes, everyone
[IWATA]
Pressure rising.
Oxygen in hangar now
approaching normal levels.
[MORI]
So that's a Gamilan?
[AIHARA] Man, what do
you think they look like?
[NANBU] They're trying to
exterminate the human race!
They're prob'ly fanged,
bug-eyed monsters!
Hey, look!
[NANBU]
What?
But, that's impossible!
No way.
They look just like humans!
They're humanoid;
we can certainly say that much.
Crazy.
[OTA]
That's a female, right?
Her skin. It's blue.
[ANALYZER speaking Gamilan]
[speaking Gamilan]
There's no need for it.
I can translate your
language with this device.
Now to start, I want
to confirm something.
Is this a Teron vessel?
Teron?
You call her the
Yamato , yes or no?
[KODAI]
Huh?
[BRIDGE OFFICER A] Lower
Storm Leader Ditz is docked
with the Yamato .
[NERGE]
If that is the Yamato .
It would be quite
a fortunate break
for a ship full of second-class
Gamilans like yourself, Captain.
You fell into this.
But Director-General Gimleh
will be pleased, nonetheless.
Imperial Guard.
[MELDA]
I'm a Gamilan pilot
of the 707th
Galactic Theater Air Corps.
Name is Melda Ditz.
Lower Storm Leader.
Lieutenant Susumu Kodai.
Chief of Tactical.
You may be interested to
know that within the empire
there are other humanoid
species like your own
without blue skin.
You don't say.
They are inferior races
from planets
we've colonized or
systems we've absorbed.
We call them
second-class Gamilans.
You always start
negotiations with insults?
Well do your people
always start them
by bringing a
weapon to the table?
[gasps]
But, of course,
I shouldn't be surprised,
considering you Terons love war
so much you attacked us
without a formal declaration.
Don't feed us lies,
you started this!
For generations my
family's served the empire
with honor and integrity.
And I swear on that honor
I'm speaking the truth.
Nonsense!
They attacked us first,
how can they dispute that?
What's he doing?
Now, what's your proposal?
[OKITA]
The Wave Motion Gun?
Yeah.
Interesting and quite
possible, theoretically.
As the name implies,
the gun creates Dimensional Wave
Motion along its line of fire.
If we aim the bow
at the phase boundary
of this dimensional
fault and fire it.
The resulting wave
of interference
should open a hole
we can pass through.
But how do they know what
the Wave Motion Gun can do?
They were probably
watching when we broke through
that stellar prominence
from Gleise 581.
But the Wave Motion Engine
can't recharge here,
and the gun would deplete
most of our remaining energy.
So, your little plan would
knock the Yamato off-line!
And that's where we come in.
Use your gun and we promise
to use our ship
to tow yours to safety.
We need your help to create
a passageway out of this
dimensional fault.
And you need our help to get
out once that passage is open.
Unless we work together both
ships will be lost.
[SHIMA]
How can we trust them?
After we fire the gun
there's nothing to stop them
from leaving us here to die!
Why wouldn't they betray us?
These are the same demons
who blame us for the war.
While we stand around talking,
the engine continues
to leak energy.
So, whatever we do
we need to decide quickly,
or the Wave Motion Gun
won't even be an option.
I agree, Chief.
We don't have time to hesitate.
Okay. So what do we do now?
I mean is there
anything we can do?
There is.
We can choose to
believe the Gamilans.
We've all decided.
That we're going
to agree to your plan.
I'm glad to hear it.
Thank you, Terons.
[LANG] This is Captain
Vars Lang, of the EX-178.
This is the Yamato 's
Captain, Juzo Okita.
Captain Lang, I want to
thank you for your proposal.
[LANG] Just like you, we've
been trapped in this space,
with no means to escape.
I thank you as well,
for agreeing to our plan.
Lower Storm Leader Ditz
will remain on your vessel
until we've both
made it to safety,
serving as a point of contact
and a gesture of goodwill.
[NERGE]
Hmph!
I guess it never hurts
to have a hostage.
[LANG] But once we return to
normal space, our truce ends.
I understand.
[LANG] I look forward
to our battle, Captain.
They've ended
the transmission, sir.
Once it's done,
we'll be too drained to
even use our Shock Cannons.
I'm well aware.
This is a promise from
one soldier to another.
[NERGE] So Admiral Ditz's
daughter stays with them?
A clever way to
buy their trust. Heh!
[MELDA]
That's a beautiful stone.
Not nearly as precious
as noble blue, of course,
but red is still a lovely color.
[YAMAMOTO]
Red is the color of my home.
And my color, too.
It seems to be quite
important to you.
It's the same as Kodai's gun.
And what does that mean?
[YAMAMOTO] Both are mementos
our loved ones left behind.
They're gone.
Because you murdered them.
Gamilan ship firing tow beams.
Switch to emergency power.
It looks like it's begun.
Prepare to fire Wave Motion Gun!
Safety lock released, Captain.
Activating the force injector.
Releasing final safety.
[NANBU] Tachyon particle
pressure rising in chamber.
Path is clear.
Gamilan ship out of firing line.
Engage anti-shock
and anti-flare defenses.
Activating the targeting scope.
Electronic cross-gauge,
brightness twenty.
Five seconds 'til go.
Four. Three. Two. One.
And fire.
Fire!
It's working, there's a passage!
[SHIMA]
But now we're dead in the water.
Will those demons
really save us?
[BRIDGE OFFICER C] Phase
boundary fissure confirmed.
It's an exit.
Continue towing operation
through the passage.
Let me know as soon
as we're both out.
Gamilan ship moving into
breech, beams holding.
Captain Lang.
This is the perfect chance!
I'm in command of this ship.
You're along for the ride.
Hail our Lord Supreme!
[EX-178 VOICE]
Tow beam output normalized.
Performance optimal.
Tow beams receding,
they cut us loose!
[KODAI]
Huh?
The Gamilan ship
is transmitting a signal
through the opening
and out to normal space, sir!
It's encrypted,
I can't decipher!
Just like I thought,
they are gonna leave us here!
That's what we get
for trusting them.
[MELDA]
That can't be!
[YAMAMOTO]
I knew it.
You were just
the sacrificial lamb.
[LANG]
What is this?
[TOW BEAM CONTROLLER]
Captain, he made me!
You severed the tow beams
and alerted Commander Goer
we found the Yamato .
I'm going to report this
treason to Imperial Command.
You accuse me of treason?
You're the traitor, Captain.
They're Terons!
They're our sworn enemy!
[YAMAMOTO]
You were playing us all along.
If you think I'm
the enemy, shoot.
Don't hesitate.
Gamilan tow beams have
been redeployed, sir.
Huh?
I don't understand.
Stay on alert.
Right now our
only focus is escape.
Three minutes to reentry
into normal space.
This passageway is
becoming unstable, sir.
Maintaining distance
to Gamilan ship.
One more minute.
[BRIDGE OFFICER C]
Detecting phase fluctuation.
Accelerating to 12 gat.
You're a pilot, aren't you?
We don't need a little pistol,
we'll settle this
in our cockpits.
[SHIMA]
Tow beams released.
[MORI]
Coordinates confirmed.
Ship has returned
to normal space.
Yeah!
Looks like we
threaded another needle.
Yeah, guess we're safe for now.
Oh, man.
[LANG]
All crew to battle stations.
Order Ditz to return.
All right, Yamato .
You should make a good foe.
[BRIDGE OFFICER C]
Detecting Geschtam Jumps!
Gamilan vessels!
Warping in off port bow!
So, it was a trap.
You're in our
line of fire, Captain.
And I won't risk
my glorious victory
just to spare
your crew of inferiors.
But Commander Goer!
Admiral Ditz's daughter is
still on board that Teron ship!
Sir.
I don't care. Fire!
[BRIDGE OFFICER C]
Our ships are firing!
Evasive maneuver!
[OTA]
EX-178 has been destroyed!
[BRIDGE OFFICER E]
Confirmed destruction of EX-178.
[GOER] We'll report the Yamato
shot down our missing ship
with the Admiral's
daughter on board.
That clear?
Yes, sir.
Now then!
All ships, open fire
on that Yamato pest!
[OTA]
Hit to portside armor plating!
[SANADA]
Damage control, get down there!
Permission to attack, sir!
Turn the ship to their flank.
We're running, sir?
Just trust me.
Don't let them escape!
Hunt them down!
[MORI] The enemy fleet is being
sucked into the breech!
[BRIDGE OFFICER E]
Dimensional quake!
Looks like there's a dimensional
fault at the epicenter, sir!
Get us out of here!
Execute emergency Geschtam Jump!
Sir!
We're the flagship, we can't
leave until we've issued orders!
Do you think I want to die here?
Enemy threat neutralized.
The phase boundary
we distorted tried to collapse
to its original position,
leading the fault to temporarily
expand and suck them in.
Yes. Yes, understood, sir.
We just encountered
a Gamilan fleet.
Your ship.
It's gone.
[OKITA]
Every heart harbors secrets.
Feelings we're unwilling or
unready to share.
Facing the nightmares
and mistakes of our
pasts takes courage,
but it's crucial before we
can turn toward the future,
and blaze ahead.
The Yamato must blaze
toward that future now,
on a trail too long
to comprehend.
Next time: "A World I Once Saw."
There are 323 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.