You're a brilliant woman,
Lieutenant.
So why would you
try something so stupid?
I was wrong.
I have to answer for that.
Huh?
Let's get moving, ma'am.
[NIIMI]
Thank you for the help.
Doctor. Do you think Lieutenant
Mori's an Iscandarian,
like they said?
That's the dumbest thing
I've heard all day.
[HIJIKATA] This was her final
message to her sister
as she entrusted her
with a dangerous mission
across the stars.
Some things I can't
explain now may become
more clear on your journey.
Just don't lose hope.
Stay safe out there.
And come back in one piece.
[STARSHA]
The ultimate salvation of
all intelligent life-forms
in the universe.
That is the true meaning
of the "path to Iscandar."
After all our various setbacks,
we're now 35 days
behind schedule for getting
back to Earth on time.
However, if the intel
from Beemela-Four is true,
we can use this subspace
gate to instantly jump
30,000 light-years.
According to the data, there's
a system satellite nearby
that controls the gate.
The real question is can we find
a way to hijack the satellite.
[OKITA]
Mm.
The Wave Motion Core we
recovered contains records
of two different alien races
involved with the gate.
One that originally built it,
and a second race
that controls the system now.
Who controls it?
[SANADA] That took some digging,
but we finally found a name.
All right, enough suspense--
tell us who they are.
It's the Gamilans.
[DOMEL] I was seconds away
from destroying the Yamato .
Why did you recall the fleet?
What's going on?
We brought you back
because early this morning
our supreme leader's vessel
was destroyed
through a cowardly act
of sabotage.
The great Lord Desler
has been assassinated.
[gasps]
Before the attack, only two
members of Imperial Command
knew he would be
visiting you on Balun.
The first was Admiral Ditz,
our Supreme Commander
of the Astrofleets.
And the other
was yourself, General.
You are here in manacles
because I'm accusing you
of plotting our leader's
assassination.
Are you mad?
[GIMLEH] You and Ditz conspired
together to murder Lord Desler
and seize control of the Empire.
Do you dare deny it?
I don't have time
for these fantasies.
Fantasies? You think so?
And is your wife's arrest
for treason a fantasy as well?
What, Elisa? What are
you talking about--
what has she done?
[GIMLEH] You didn't know?
She's been caught red-handed
supporting
anti-government rebels.
[DOMEL]
There must be some mistake!
[GIMLEH]
That's what they all say.
Order is the foundation
of empire,
and it must be maintained
above all else.
That means those
suspected of wrongdoing
must be judged swiftly.
No matter how
high they've climbed.
Gimleh.
[GIMLEH]
Hm.
[HYSS] We shall take a vote.
Gentlemen of the jury?
[GAMILAS MAGISTRATES]
Death!
By unanimous verdict,
the tribunal sentences
General Domel to death
for the assassination
of our Supreme Lord.
[ZOELLIK laughing]
Sir. Preparations for
naval review are complete
and we are ready to embark.
I take it something
good has happened?
The tribunal has just given
Elk Domel a death sentence.
[VANDEVEL]
Congratulations, sir!
[laughing]
Inform the fleet
we're launching now!
Set course for planet Balun!
♪
[IMPERIAL GUARD 17B]
All right, scum, keep moving.
[IMPERIAL GUARD 17A]
No talking.
Eyes down. Stay in line!
[IMPERIAL GUARD 17B]
Stop!
--[MALE REBEL 17A grunts]
--[IMPERIAL GUARD 17C groans]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 17A]
Uh!
[groans]
[gasps]
[IMPERIAL GUARD 17B]
Get up.
[MALE ASTROPORT PA VOICE 17A]
There's your example.
Anyone attempting to run
will be shot on the spot.
[LARKIN]
That the one?
[DOLMEN]
Yeah.
[KITANO]
That's the subspace gate?
[NANBU]
Hardly looks functional.
So do you really think
it can transport us
30,000 light-years
in a single warp?
[MISAKI]
Yes it can.
[DR. SADO]
No. There's no way.
I thought I'd seen everything
but I can't help you with this.
If we don't
figure out something,
at this rate it's going to
become a serious problem for us.
My job is to take care of
the crew, not the frickin' ship!
--I'm well aware.
--[DR. SADO] Hm.
I think I deserve
an explanation, Captain.
It's not like you to go along
with somethin' like this.
And keeping it a secret
from the crew?
That's not the Okita I know.
We had strict orders
from Central Command.
I don't care
about orders, damn it!
[OKITA] "You need the courage
to disobey an order
you believe is wrong, especially
when lives are at stake.
In war, it's the only way
you can live with yourself."
Huh?
I told Kodai that but haven't
lived up to my own words.
We should've been honest
with ourselves and the crew
about what we've done.
X.O. I will assume
full responsibility.
[DR. SADO]
Mmm.
[door hisses]
[IWATA] All I'm saying is Mori
being an alien is a huge bummer.
Yeah, no kidding. Oh!
I was her biggest fan,
but I guess she's--
Sir! The Type One-Hundred is
fueled and ready to go, sir!
Good, thanks.
I'm ready to go.
[AIHARA] I know Kodai's flying
and going for protection,
but why do you think
the X.O. would take Mori?
I don't know, maybe because
she's an Iscandarian?
Hey! She's not an alien, okay?
But how else do you
explain her having
a private message from Starsha?
And she only remembers
a year before we launched.
It does fit.
That's all just speculation!
We're in the middle
of a mission here.
Cut the chatter, crewmen!
[SAIJO] Type One-Hundred has
landed on system satellite, sir.
[clinking]
[SANADA] I don't see any
evidence of booby traps.
Looks like it was
used as a base,
but it's been abandoned
a long time.
The inertial mass system
is online, though,
so the rest is most likely
still functional.
This fighter could be
useful to us in the future.
We'll tow it back
with us when we leave.
What do you say
we get this done, sir.
[KODAI]
Hard to know which way to go.
[SANADA]
Indeed.
[MORI] X.O. Didn't you say
an alien civilization
older than the Gamilans
built this gate?
[SANADA]
We think so.
They would be horrified.
The Gamilans took a beautiful
thing and they tainted it.
Well, "The sorrow
of being tainted
makes the snow fall
once more." Yes?
What's that?
It's by Chuya Nakahara.
I used to know someone who
was obsessed with that poem.
It's a classic. From the
twentieth century, right?
A poem from 200 years ago, huh?
--Uh. Hey, wait a minute!
--Uh, what's wrong?
Do you really think
the Iscandarians would know
about this
Nakahara guy's poetry?
[KODAI]
He's ancient. Why would they?
And if Iscandarians
don't know about him...
[MORI gasps]
Be quiet!
Looks like they left
their guard dog behind.
That may not be
the only one. This way.
[NIIMI] He was always like
a guiding star for me.
Whenever I didn't know what
to do, he'd point the way.
[NIIMI] Here are those
papers you requested.
Thank you.
Hm. Word is the alien fleet
is on the outskirts of Mars
and could reach orbit
any moment now.
Yes, I heard that, too.
Apparently they've
upgraded the shelters
from the Inner Planet War.
And now the entire surface
is being evacuated.
[door knob clicks]
[MAMORU KODAI]
Don't worry.
[NIIMI]
Kodai?
Our side's about to launch
a big operation at Mars
to show those invaders
who they're messing with.
And where did you
hear that from?
I can't say.
[sighs]
So, what are you doing here?
It's against regulation
for anyone to be
in this lab without approval.
And do you have
approval, Niimi?
That's different. I'm bringing
Sanada materials he asked for.
[SANADA chuckles]
Yeah, so am I.
--Here.
--[SANADA] Hm?
You said you'd like to
check it out sometime, remember?
A book of poems? Really?
That's right.
All this time I thought
he only cared about equations!
Hm. I mean, don't be rude!
I don't mean to cut this short,
but you've got a visitor.
[MAMORU KODAI] Oh, yeah!
I promised I'd meet my brother!
Bye.
He does whatever he wants.
Because he's honest
with himself, Niimi.
You know, you could learn
a thing or two from him.
Mamoru.
Being more honest
with ourselves, huh?
[KODAI]
This is great!
I'm glad I was able
to prove you're an Earthling!
It's the only way
to explain it, right?
But-- then, what about
my amnesia--
not remembering anything
beyond that year?
Can it really be just a
coincidence that I lost
my memory the same time
Yurisha disappeared?
--[KODAI] Well.
--[SANADA] No, it's not.
We should have told you
the truth from the start.
You and Yurisha were together.
Victims of the same crash.
Maybe it was an accident,
or maybe an act of terror.
The investigators
could never say.
All we know is
there was an explosion,
and you lost your memory.
And Yurisha fell into a coma.
We had the best doctors
in the world working on her,
but she never woke up.
[KODAI]
Why didn't you tell us that?
We know Iscandar is in the
Large Magellanic Cloud galaxy,
but we don't know exactly where.
[KODAI, MORI gasp]
What? But aren't the
coordinates on the map?
Yeah, that's right.
You entered the data
in the Auto-Nav,
and that's what it's using
to point us there.
--It wasn't on the map.
--[KODAI, MORI gasp]
She said she would reveal
"the path to Iscandar" to us
as we journeyed.
Or that was the plan.
[KODAI]
W-Wait a minute!
Then what's the
Auto-Nav been using?
We've been following
Yurisha's memories.
Her what? You don't mean that.
[SANADA] Mm. The core of the
Automatic Navigation System
is Yurisha herself.
[BOTH gasp]
[SANADA] We've been physically
tapping into her brain
to point the way to Iscandar.
[MORI]
But, sir.
[SANADA]
I know it's ethically wrong,
and we have to take
responsibility
for what's happened.
That's why we're going to take
her back home to Iscandar,
where she can hopefully get
the help she needs to recover.
That's a key element
of the Yamato 's mission.
But sir, what about
Yurisha's message capsule?
Why do I have it?
The truth is...
[KODAI yells]
[SANADA]
Nice shooting.
Now let's get inside
while we can.
[KODAI]
Inside what?
That should be a chamber door.
It leads to the system
satellite's control area.
♪
At least the door works.
I should be able to handle
the rest of it myself.
You two wait for me here.
[MORI gasps]
[KODAI]
X.O! Hey!
[beeping]
[KODAI]
X.O!
[SANADA]
Just as I thought.
If I reboot the
system satellite,
then the subspace gate
should open automatically.
[gasps]
It's been locked
from the inside.
[KODAI gasps]
[SANADA]
Kodai, listen to me.
To use the gate,
we need to reboot the system,
but there's a catch.
Doing so is going to cause
a massive neutron burst
in this chamber.
--[MORI] Huh?
--[KODAI] But, sir.
[SANADA] The door and walls
in here are specially shielded.
So there's no need to worry.
You'll be safe out there.
But what about you, sir?
Is that terminal shielded,
or are you gonna be exposed?
What are you planning to do?
[MORI]
You can't, sir! It's suicide!
No! Please don't do this!
I'll see if I can
override the lock!
[KODAI]
Sanada, open the door!
Kodai. Listen. I told you
I used to know someone
who loved Chuya Nakahara's
poetry, right?
It was my friend, Mamoru.
That's right.
Mamoru Kodai. Your brother.
[KODAI] Wait, what? You and
my brother were friends?
Yes. Best friends, in fact.
[door knob clicks]
If you're looking
for Niimi, she left.
Another meteorite.
This one landed
on Rio de Janeiro.
Clearly, the enemy
is launching them
as catastrophic weapons.
After Mars, the aliens have
changed their strategy.
Hey, you want to go get some
actual fresh air for a change?
Huh?
[MAMORU KODAI]
Sky looks terrible.
It could be the beginning
of a nuclear winter.
Are you still planning to enlist
in the Cosmo Navy
when you graduate?
Yeah. And you?
Not sure. I don't think
I'm cut out for the military.
That said, there's got to be
something I can do
to help us in this war.
That's all there is now.
You'll find your true calling.
You'll end up helping
the cause in a way
I could never dream of.
That's my bet.
A poem and an equation.
That's what we are.
[SANADA]
Hm?
[MAMORU KODAI]
We can bring order to this world
in completely different ways.
But in the end,
our intentions are the same.
Yeah.
Chuya wrote, "The sorrow
of being tainted..."
"...causes the snow
to fall once more."
[KODAI]
Sanada!
He's the best friend I ever had,
but I sent him to his death.
[KODAI gasps]
[SANADA] I couldn't tell him
that Operation M was a decoy.
That the whole fleet was a decoy
to get the Wave Motion Core.
[YUKIKAZE PA VOICE 17A]
The operation will begin today
as scheduled at...
Well, good luck, Captain.
[YUKIKAZE PA VOICE 17A]
...loading procedures for
prototype torpedoes.
[MAMORU KODAI]
We're launching this morning.
--[SANADA] Mm.
--[MAMORU KODAI] I don't know
how many ships
are gonna make it through.
But we'll shut down their Pluto
base, no matter what it takes.
[SANADA]
Did you get to see Niimi?
No, we broke up. Real shame.
[SANADA]
I see.
Here, I never got a chance
to bring this back to you.
You keep it. Please.
You need it more than I do.
[SANADA] I've read it twice.
And I still don't understand
why anyone likes poetry.
Wow, tell me what
you really think!
[SANADA]
Hm.
♪
[SANADA] The fact it was
a decoy was top secret.
I didn't have the courage
to tell my friend.
I just obeyed my orders.
That tells you
what kind of a man I am.
Even if he had known
he was a decoy,
it wouldn't have mattered.
He still would've gone.
No matter the odds,
or how unreasonable the order,
he would've believed
he could find a way.
That's just how my brother was.
Yes, you're right.
That does sound like him.
Kodai. Your brother
would be proud
that you've followed
in his footsteps.
Sanada. What else?
Keep talking, I didn't even
know he liked poetry!
I'm almost in.
[SANADA] "The sorrow of being
tainted longs for nothing.
At dusk the sun
can do nothing more,
and sets helplessly with
the sadness of being tainted."
Sanada, wait!
Please, tell me what made
my brother happy!
What made him sad?
Just talk to me!
Neutrons have flooded
the control room, Kodai.
He couldn't survive that.
Nobody could.
Sanada!
[MISAKI]
The door is open. This is it.
This is the path that leads
to the mother world.
[beeping]
[MORI gasps]
Where is he?
[KODAI]
No! Sanada!
There's so much more
I wanted to know.
I wanted to learn more
about my brother.
And more about you.
You're alive.
Neutrons don't pass through
water so easily, Lieutenant.
[gasps]
Honestly, sir,
you amaze me.
[OKITA]
Attention all crew:
The gate is now online.
Very soon, the Yamato
will be warping
30,000 light-years
closer to our goal.
But first, I need to
make something clear.
Something I should have
said at the start.
There is a rumor circulating
about an Iscandarian
aboard this ship.
That much is true.
But make no mistake,
she is not a crewmember.
She is in a coma in the
automatic navigation room.
[MORI] So, I guess
you're Yurisha Iscandar.
[MISAKI]
Actually, that would be me.
Greetings friend.
I am Yurisha of Iscandar.