[YUKIKAZE CM 1A]
Entering orbit,
200 megameters from Pluto.
--Battle stations!
--[alarm blares]
[YUKIKAZE CM 1B]
Enemy sightings
are negative, sir.
Seas are calm today.
It's kind of eerie.
Send up a signal round--
Do it now.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1A]
Signal round sighted
from vanguard ship Yukikaze .
Message: We have
entered operation area.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B] Spotters
report enemy sighted, sir.
Multiple contacts.
Starboard, four o'clock.
EM Wave blackout cleared.
Identify those vessels.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B] One
Super-Dreadnaught Class Warship,
7 battleships, 22 cruisers,
70 destroyers and counting, sir.
All ships to combat positions.
Thirty degrees starboard.
Ready the torpedoes.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1C]
Turning starboard.
[alarm blaring]
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B]
Distance: 7.5 megameters.
Incoming message
from the enemy.
"Attention all Earth vessels.
Surrender or be destroyed."
How should we respond, sir?
[OKITA]
Tell them, "Nuts."
[KIRISHIMA CM 1A]
Sir?
Go on. Send it.
Aye-aye. Earth fleet
responding: "Nuts!"
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D]
The Yuguri is destroyed!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B]
The Kurama is leaving formation.
--Now, sir?
--Not yet.
Enemy ship is
within firing range.
Target locked.
Open up all the gun ports--fire!
[MALE ABUKUMA OFFICER 1A]
Evasive maneuver!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D] Two more
of our cruisers are down!
[OKITA] Still no word
from the Amaterasu?
[KIRISHIMA CM 1A]
No message received, sir.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B] Another
Space Cruiser has been hit...
You really believe
they'll come, Admiral?
We have to believe.
--[KIRISHIMA CM 1F gasps]
--[OKITA] Uh!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D]
Damage report:
we're leaking cyanide gas.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1E] Engine
output dropping!
Damage control. Get those
bulkheads down, now!
[alarm blaring]
[KIRISHIMA CM 1G, 1H yell]
Hang on, kid,
do you hear me!
Don't you dare die on me!
[gasps]
Mom. Mom, is that you?
Damn it!
[FLEET CAPTAIN 1A]
We've lost control.
We're leaving formation!
[FLEET CAPTAIN 1B] Our main
cannon isn't powerful enough!
The enemy's advantage
is overwhelming, sir.
[MAMORU KODAI]
This was an ambush?
Turn the ship, reverse course!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1K]
Fire team, where are you?
Keep working! We can't
lose any more output.
And keep an eye out
for those plasma leaks!
[YABU] Chief. We've got things
stabilized for now.
But if we keep
taking these hits...
[TOKUGAWA]
I told you, we'll be fine.
Have faith.
The Admiral's at the helm.
He'll get us through this.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B]
Eighty percent of our fleet
is out of commission, sir.
[OKITA]
Mmm.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1M]
Signal from Amaterasu confirmed!
They're on course
at interstellar speed.
They'll be passing
Neptune shortly, sir!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1M]
Package will reach Mars
in 10 minutes, sir!
Send encrypted message to HQ.
"The Stone Door
of Heaven is open."
[MALE HQ CM 1A]
Battle report: at 1200,
the First Fleet engaged the
enemy 380 megameters from Pluto.
State of combat
currently unknown.
Message received from
Admiral Okita on the Kirishima .
"The Stone Door
of Heaven is open."
[TODO] Then so far,
everything is going as planned.
When is the rendezvous
with the package?
There's a two-man
recovery squad,
waiting at the old Arcadia Port.
[SHIMA] Today makes 3 weeks
since we were dropped here.
You think Operation M
is going our way?
Beats the hell out of me.
All I know is my brother's
fighting at Pluto.
While I'm staring at red dirt.
[radio beeping]
Yeah?
Roger that.
That ends the staring.
That's it?
[KODAI, SHIMA gasp]
Hey, where you going?
There's an escape pod.
[footsteps]
[KODAI gasps]
That's it.
Well?
[SHIMA]
She's who we're here to meet?
[KODAI] Don't know.
She sure is beautiful.
[SHIMA gasps]
[SHIMA]
This must be it.
[FLEET CM 1A]
The Isokaze's gone!
[FLEET CAPTAIN 1C]
Keep fighting! Fire!
The recovery team has confirmed
package in hand, sir.
Mm. Then the First Fleet's
operation is complete.
Turn this ship around.
Full retreat.
--Huh?
--[beeping]
Enemy destroyer approaching
quickly from above, sir!
[YUKIKAZE CM 1D]
Target sighted!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1M]
They're trying to lock on!
Tubes one and two, fire!
[YUKIKAZE CM 1D]
Confirmed hit, target destroyed!
Gotcha!
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D]
Enemy destroyer is down, sir.
They're reorganizing
their fleet.
Order remaining vessels
to retreat.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1A]
Sending order now, sir!
[OKITA]
How many of us survived?
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D]
Just us and one other ship.
That assault destroyer.
[OKITA]
Who is she?
[KIRISHIMA CM 1D]
Captain Kodai's Yukikaze .
[YUKIKAZE CM 1E]
Incoming retreat order
from the Kirishima .
Retreat?
[YUKIKAZE CM 1E] Message:
"Disengage and withdraw.
Follow us home."
[KIRISHIMA CM 1C]
Exiting battlefield.
Turning hard to starboard.
They ignored us!
They're not turning!
They're what?
Kodai. Follow my lead!
Negative, sir.
We're not going anywhere.
[OKITA]
That's an order!
The Yukikaze will stay
on the battlefield.
We'll support
the Kirishima 's withdrawal.
Don't do this! We've made
great sacrifices
but the operation was a success!
Now let's go home!
[MAMORU KODAI]
If we don't play this right,
our whole fleet
will be wiped out!
And with no one left
to protect Earth
there won't be a home
to go back to!
[OKITA]
Kodai!
Listen, Admiral.
You can't die here.
You have to escape!
Earth needs you. You may be
the best chance we've got.
[OKITA]
I could say the same about you.
We need you, Captain!
Thank you for
saying that, sir.
I'm going to take
those words to the grave.
[OKITA] No, stop!
You don't understand!
Give 'em hell. I'm leaving
the earth in your care.
[OKITA]
Kodai!
Well, all right.
Let's take it to 'em.
Ha. We're only
outnumbered 50 to 1.
[MAMORU KODAI]
Mm.
♪ Crossing the waves
drifting out ♪
♪ on the galactic sea, ♪
♪ fixing our sights
on Alpha Centauri! ♪
[YUKIKAZE CMs]
♪ Bright be the fiery glow, ♪
♪ of the stars celestial. ♪
♪ Lighting the way
ahead to capture destiny! ♪
[YUKIKAZE CM, FIRST MATE]
♪ Set sail! ♪
♪ We're leaving shore! ♪
♪ Raise the anchor!
Home no more! ♪
♪ Hold steady, crewman brother.
Onward past Mars! ♪
I'm sorry everyone.
[YUKIKAZE CMs continue singing]
[KIRISHIMA CM 1C]
They're flying directly
into the enemy fleet.
Admiral?
[OKITA] Maintain course.
Full speed ahead.
Maintain course, full speed!
[OKITA]
Stay alive, Kodai. Stay alive.
♪
[KODAI] This is the Uzume,
requesting permission to dock.
What's going on?
Where's my brother,
and the rest of the fleet?
[HIRATA] Package secured.
Well done, soldiers.
[KODAI]
Hirata. We're in the dark here.
What happened?
Where's my brother's ship,
is he okay?
[GUY ON SHIP] Our flagship
has secured the capsule
from the Amaterasu,
and set a course for Earth.
It cost many lives
and many ships.
But the main objective of
Operation M has been achieved.
That means the path is clear
for the Yamato Plan.
The gambit worked.
[HIJIKATA]
No. This is just the start.
There's too much we don't
know about our enemy,
and how they'll counter.
All we can say for sure
is they're monsters.
Demons who call
themselves Gamilans.
Beyond that, we're in the dark.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1C]
Now entering Earth's orbit.
[KIRISHIMA CM 1B]
Two planet bombs sighted,
type MN3. Passing on
the starboard side,
on a collision course
with Earth.
Passing satellite orbit.
Speed is unchanged.
[OKITA] Firing's pointless.
Just a waste of rounds.
We don't have the power
to stop them.
♪
[OKITA]
Hard to believe this ugly,
red rock is Mother Earth.
Just you wait, devils.
I'll fight you
all the way to the end.
I'll never despair.
I won't give you that.
Even if I'm the last one
breathing, I'll never despair.
♪
[MORI]
The year is 2199 A.D.
The human race is on
the verge of extinction.
Our planet as we know it
nearly destroyed.
Eight years ago, Earth made
first contact with alien life.
The celebrations
did not last long.
Attempts at peace
were quickly met with war,
and merciless,
indiscriminate attacks.
The scale of devastation and
the power of their weaponry
was beyond anything
we'd ever seen.
At the second battle of Mars,
we won a Pyrrhic victory,
managing to narrowly
fend off their direct assault.
But then, they shifted
their strategy,
relying on an onslaught
of long-range planet bombs.
With no way
to defend the surface,
humankind was
forced underground.
We built underground cities and
retreated into the darkness.
We devoted our greatest
minds and resources into
the Earth Defense Fleet,
only to see it almost
completely wiped out
by the enemy.
Their planet bombs
have dried up the land,
polluted the atmosphere,
and eradicated
all life on the surface.
And still the cruel shadow
of death is growing,
spreading downward
to our underground cities,
the last fortress of humankind.
The facts are inescapable.
We are headed toward our end.
Our scientists estimate
that the human race
could be extinct within a year.
The enemy has re-engineered
the environment of Pluto.
And continues to launch
their horrific weapons
from a base there.
So do we know why the aliens
are doing this to our planet?
We don't know.
But we have theories.
Just as we terraformed Mars,
they may be terraforming Earth,
so that they can live here.
[NANBU] Must be tough teaching
kids on top of your HQ job.
I mean, what do you say?
Jeez, another riot?
The unrest is inevitable now.
All hail the ice queen,
unemotional as ever.
[NANBU] Lots of gossip
flying around lately.
People are saying
the only survivors
from the First Fleet
were on the Kirishima .
That's right.
That's not all. Rumor is
the whole thing was a ruse.
Sounds crazy,
but they say Operation M
was just a diversion
for the enemy.
And the real
mission's classified
so only the top brass knew,
leaving everyone else
to go blind to the slaughter.
[KODAI]
Hey. You!
That talk about a diversion,
is that true?
[NANBU] I don't know.
It's just something I heard.
How should I know?
Well, you guys work
at Headquarters, right?
Where's Commander Okita,
is he here?
[MORI]
Hey! What's your name, pilot?
You're way out of line!
Oh, well, uh.
Cut him some slack, ma'am.
We're back from battle.
[MORI]
The Vice-Admiral's in the ward
recovering from his injuries.
Lieutenant, let's go.
Uh, yes, ma'am.
[SHIMA] That's a trip.
She looks just like her.
You're imagining things.
Where do you think
you're going?
[KODAI]
The hospital zone.
[SHIMA] You're seriously
gonna talk to him?
We're supposed to be
on standby, you know.
I need to hear it
straight from him.
Uncanny. Sometimes
I think you're immortal.
No, Dr. Sado, I just
have the best physician
in the fleet treating me.
[DR. SADO]
Don't flatter me, I am not!
Heh. Well, maybe.
Where do they have the capsule?
[HIJIKATA] Tech team's
looking at it now.
They should be done
analyzing it soon.
[door hisses, scrapes]
[HARADA]
Hey, this is a private room.
You can't just come in!
Back off, I need to
talk to the Admiral!
But sir, you--!
Is it true Operation M
was nothing more
than a damn diversion?
Did my brother and everyone else
know what they were flying into?
[HIJIKATA]
Shut up, soldier!
[KODAI]
Admiral Hijikata!
[SHIMA groans]
I'm sorry. That's Susumu Kodai,
a former student of mine.
[OKITA] Kodai. Then you
must be Mamoru Kodai's...
That's right, Captain Kodai
of the Yukikaze .
He was my brother.
Mamoru Kodai was a great man.
One of the best to ever serve.
He bravely sacrificed
everything for the cause.
And I'm the one
who led him to his death.
I'm sorry.
[SHIMA]
So now what?
[KODAI] We follow orders
and go back to standby.
What else?
[SHIMA]
Works for me.
[DR. SADO]
Hey!
[KODAI gasps]
Sorry, Doctor.
I meant no disrespect.
I get it,
emotions are running high.
But you're sure as hell
not the only one here
to lose friends and family
in this war, kid.
Just try to remember that.
I just can't believe we got to
see Admiral Hijikata in person.
Those two have been
good friends since
they were young recruits
in Officer Training.
Just like you two right now,
from the looks of it.
Give me a break,
we're nothing like them.
I guess time will tell.
But more importantly,
who wants a drink?
Doctor!
This isn't that
jet fuel hooch, either!
This is real saké--
it's hard to find!
[giggles]
Nice try. But they're gone, sir.
Their loss.
[phone beeping]
[phone handset clicks]
[OKITA]
Go ahead.
[FEMALE HQ CM 1A] Test
preparations are ready, sir.
On my way.
[phone handset clicks]
[HIJIKATA] Seems our faith
was well-placed.
At least so far, she's delivered
on everything she said.
It's been a year since we
switched from the Izumo Plan.
And now the Yamato Plan
is finally bearing fruit.
What about the crew?
They're on standby
according to plan.
We can activate them...
It's a damn shame about Kodai.
[TODO]
Very good.
[MALE DECK CM 1A]
All right, team, let's move!
[KODAI] I've never seen
a ship like this.
Me neither. You think it's
an air defense prototype?
[KATO] Type-Zero
Space Model 52.
Cosmo Zero for short.
She's a ship-based fighter
meant for space deployment,
not for air defense.
You sightseeing?
We were ordered to
report here for standby.
[KATO]
Is that right? Same as me.
[MALE DECK CM 1B]
Lieutenant Kato!
Yeah! Be right there.
Don't touch her.
Lieutenant Kato?
Saburo Kato,
the best ace in the fleet.
Yeah?
[KODAI]
Funny, isn't it?
When someone says
not to do something...
Can't resist.
[alarm blarring]
[MALE HQ CM 1B] Enemy mobile
squadron has broken through
our defenses, entering
atmosphere now.
[MALE HQ CM 1D] Alarms sounded
in fighter hanger.
Prepare to engage! Code Red!
I guess they noticed.
[FEMALE HQ CM 1B]
Enemy approaching dry sea zone
off Cape Bonomisaki.
Estimated target...
Well, that was good timing.
Yeah, we can use this beauty
to shoot 'em down.
[KATO] We don't have time
to wait for orders, just do it!
[KATO]
Hey, what are you doing?
That's my fighter!
Hold on, you idiots!
Get back here!
♪
[KODAI]
Closing in.
Up there! Looks like
a recon plane.
Can ya' do this?
Oh, yeah.
This is for my brother.
[KODAI]
You're mine.
[BOTH gasp]
[SHIMA] The deck crew must
have unloaded the weapons!
[beeping]
Ah! Damn it!
[KODAI grunts]
[KODAI]
A system error! Hang on!
[KODAI grunting]
You okay?
[SHIMA]
Yeah. I guess.
But in these lightweight suits
we may not last long enough
for an extraction team
to get here.
Kodai! Where are you going?
[SHIMA]
You see something?
--[SHIMA] What is that?
--[KODAI] Not sure.
[KODAI] You think that's
what they were looking for?
[SHIMA] Can't be. It's just
a sunken battleship.
Must be over 200 years old!
[KODAI]
Yeah.
[OKITA]
The year is 2199.
Earth is on the verge
of destruction.
And now, humanity's
last hope slips past
the outstretched claws of
the enemy and takes flight.
The name of this hope:
Space Battleship Yamato .
Its crew will leave
our home world behind
and set a course
for unexplored space.
Next time:
"Toward a Sea of Stars."
There are 365 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.