[GOER] You expect me
to believe a Teron ship
made a hyperspace jump?
And somehow destroyed
a resupply base?
Are you mad?
Yes, I realize how it sounds.
But Major General, there's no
other explanation for it.
Shut your mouth!
I'm in charge of this
whole galactic theater!
Do you think I rose
to this rank by relaying
such drivel to imperial command?
Of course not!
Our leader has
no time for nonsense.
I'll just have to wait
until you have
something appropriate to report.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
Yes, sir.
[GOER] Fix this, and I may
speak to command about
promoting all of you from
second to first-class citizens,
despite your inferior blood.
[gasps]
So go on! Come up with a report
that's good for all of us.
He doesn't understand anything.
Bring up the Zupist footage.
[SHULTZ] The first question,
is what sort of weapon
causes that much damage?
How is destruction on
that scale even possible?
[SANADA] The UN's Yamato Plan
was painstakingly drawn,
and we have no margin
for error on Pluto.
That said, we have
operational control,
so the decision about
the M-2 contingency
ultimately lies with us.
We have to do it!
We have the firepower
to destroy their Pluto base
and prevent future attacks!
Navigation? Your thoughts?
Well, from our coordinates,
we've determined this is
now the quickest route
out of our solar system.
[SHIMA]
As you can see, it's--
The wrong way!
You're kidding me!
You want to leave
their base here
just to shave off some time!
I can understand how you feel.
But if we're going to succeed,
we can't afford any detours.
--Detours?
--[beeping]
[AIHARA]
Main Bridge to Captain.
We've picked up
a distress signal.
UN Cosmo Force Standard Code.
It's weak, but there's
no doubt it's real.
[OKITA]
What's the ship's name?
We can't make it out.
All we know: It's coming from
the Saturn moon Enceladus,
near its southern pole.
Saturn, huh?
That would still be the
opposite direction from Pluto.
And it would delay
your precious schedule.
[OTA]
Heh.
If we go to Enceladus
and send a rescue team,
how many days are lost?
I'd estimate two altogether.
[KODAI] Well, here's
the view from Tactical.
If we spend time on a mission,
it shouldn't be on that moon!
How can you say that, Kodai?
True sailors never abandon
one of their own!
We don't even know
if there are survivors!
We can't waste time on detours!
Isn't that what
you just said to me?
We have to think
big picture here!
Our mission's to reach Iscandar.
It's not to strike
the Pluto base!
But a distress call
is different. We have to go.
Even if the chance
of survivors is miniscule!
[ALL grunt]
[MORI yells]
[NANBU]
What was that?
Engine room,
I need a status report.
[TOKUGAWA] This is bad.
That blast partly melted one of
the condensors, and it's
caused a chain reaction
that's threatening
the whole condenser system.
[TOKUGAWA]
If we don't fix this soon,
it could paralyze
the entire ship.
[SANADA]
How long to repair?
That's hard to say, sir.
First, there's the
question of materials.
[BOTH yell]
What's cosmonite 90?
[SANADA]
It's a rare material.
They need it to
repair that condenser.
Lieutenant. Did we bring any?
Yes sir, but not nearly enough
for repairs on that scale.
Bingo. We're in luck.
Enceladus actually has
a cosmonite mine
that was abandoned
before full extraction,
so it should have
all that we need.
So, we can resupply there.
Mm. We're changing course.
We'll go to Enceladus and
get the required cosmonite.
We'll investigate the signal,
but only until
the mining's done. Understood?
[BOTH]
Sir!
[SHULTZ] The Teron ship
has changed course?
[JARLETORA] Our recon vessels
report they're heading
for planet six, Zedan.
Jarletora, don't we have
a recon landing ship
stationed near Zedan
for rapid deployment?
Sir.
Then let's use it.
Take prisoners if possible.
I want to find out
what they're up to.
[CREW chattering]
[OTA]
The Yamato 's OMCS is amazing!
It can produce as much
food as you want!
[AIHARA] Yeah, but what's
it produce it from?
[OTA chuckles]
Beats me, I just eat it.
No way. Commander Sanada, is
that really all you're having?
[SANADA]
Yes. This is a military vessel,
not a cruise ship.
XO, I was wondering,
what's the OMCS use
as raw material to make
all the food it creates?
I think you're better
off not knowing
the answer to that,
ensign. Mm?
[KODAI]
Mind if I sit?
No of course not.
[KODAI] I'm not against
the rescue mission itself,
it's just...
complicated, you know?
You lost your brother in
that operation around Pluto.
So I understand why you would
want vengeance for that.
It's personal for me, too.
My dad was a sailor.
Have I told you that before?
And there's one thing
he hammered into me.
[DAIGO]
It's a rule we live by, Daisuke.
Sailors don't abandon
their own, no matter what.
That's what it means
to wear the anchor.
To be a true man of the fleet.
[SHIMA] I always wanted
to be just like him.
And that's why I enlisted, too.
[HOSHINA] They're real
peas in a pod those two.
I hear they even got
promoted at the same time,
'cause the people who did have
their assignments got killed.
That's kinda weird.
What's weird about friendship?
I mean, their jobs!
[MORI]
They're simple-minded boys.
Immature and completely
self-absorbed.
They are not role models!
--[laughing]
--Yes, ma'am!
Understood!
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
After inspection, Team Five
is to gather
in the briefing room.
Repeat: after inspection,
Team Five to the briefing room.
We will discuss our maintenance
and operation plans.
Over and out.
Wow, is the inertial control
in here turned off on purpose?
Lots of pricey machinery.
We're better off
without gravity.
You need something?
You know that request you
submitted for extra ammunition?
--It's your lucky day. Here.
--Awesome, thanks.
So how's the accounting job
treating you?
Fine. It has its moments.
[GAMILOID speaking Gamilan]
[OTA] That moon looks more like
a messed-up golf ball to me.
As satellites go, it's quite
fascinating, actually.
Its surface is frozen,
yet tidal pull from Saturn
and the moon cause geysers
which shoot comet-like
plumes into space.
Prepare for landing on
Enceladus. Begin our descent.
Approach angle set.
Forward at minimum speed.
Red 15. Descent angle 16.
Preparing to level bow.
Ready for docking routine.
All ready.
[OKITA]
Let's get right to it, XO.
I'm putting you in charge
of the mining site.
Sir.
Operations.
You'll lead the rescue.
Take Analyzer and a medic to the
source of the distress signal.
See if there's anyone
you can help.
Sir.
[OKITA] Kodai, you'll serve
as Mori's escort.
Okay, and what does that mean?
[ANALYZER] I interpret
you are meant to protect.
[MORI]
That won't be necessary.
[ENOMOTO humming]
[MALE MINE CREW 4A]
That's it, keep backing up.
We need to get the truck...
[ENOMOTO] This place
is a real treasure trove.
Boatswain, I need this done
as fast as you can.
Aye-aye, sir.
I hear Kodai's
escorting the princess,
that should be interesting.
[SANADA]
Hm?
I know him. I was
one of his instructors
back in training school,
so I was around him a lot.
And that guy was always
clueless when it came to women.
I hope he comes back
in one piece!
[laughs]
Two girls and a robot
on their own?
It's a good thing the captain
overruled your objection.
I meant what I said.
I'm not going to need
your help down there.
[ANALYZER] I am quite capable of
executing this mission as well.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Babysitting was never my thing.
[MORI] You may be the escort,
but on the ground
you obey my orders,
is that clear, Lieutenant?
Ma'am, yes ma'am.
Drop the attitude.
One ma'am's fine.
[KODAI grunts]
Ma'am, yes ma'am.
What did I say?
Look at them.
I'm sensing some chemistry.
[ANALYZER] I detect no unusual
chemical reactions on board.
Ugh. You're such a bore,
you know that?
[MORI] It's strange.
This distress signal.
Who in the world
could have sent it?
What's wrong?
Can I ask you...
something weird?
I guess so.
Aah. Yes! Here it comes!
It's just... Well, are you
related to any aliens?
--[MORI] Huh?
--[HARADA groans]
Never mind. Sorry.
[ANALYZER] Now approaching
source of distress signal.
[laughing]
[MORI]
This is definitely one of ours.
And with that
distinctive conning tower.
[KODAI] It's an Isokaze-class
assault destroyer.
My brother captained
one of these.
I can't read the ship's
name through the ice.
[HARADA] Lieutenant Mori!
Lieutenant Kodai!
We can enter the ship
from down here!
♪
[continuous beeping]
There's the source of the call.
Looks like the only
system running.
[KODAI]
Yeah.
I'll go look around
a little more.
Okay, I'll try to find
the ship's log.
Thank you.
[KODAI]
It's no good.
Uh?
--We've got company!
--[MORI] Huh?
They got the Seagull!
Hey. Did something
happen out there?
[HARADA groans]
Go use that console
to call the Yamato !
[MORI]
Good idea.
Hey, Harada!
[HARADA]
Help me, I'm locked in!
[KODAI grunting]
[MORI]
Medical team to Yamato ...
Aww, damn it!
Analyzer! I thought you
were Mr. Capable, huh?
Ship down! We are currently
under Gamilan attack!
We require immediate help!
[AIHARA]
This is the Yamato .
We are currently under attack
by an enemy armored unit.
Please standby!
[gasps]
[OTA] Hit to starboard!
Assessing damage now!
[NANBU]
Engine is off line,
so main and secondary
guns are down.
[FIGHTER SQUAD 4A]
Hurry up!
[FIGHTER SQUAD 3A]
Time to swat some flies!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Repeat, all available fighters--
[MALE MINE CREW 4A]
All crew, withdraw now!
[ENOMOTO]
Bring it on, fools!
They don't have the numbers
to attack the Yamato .
Not a chance.
[KODAI]
Looking good, keep it up.
Guess you are useful.
[ANALYZER]
Naturally.
That's odd.
They've stopped attacking us.
[MORI] Kodai, the Yamato
is under fire, too!
[KODAI]
Huh?
[KATO]
We can't launch?
[MALE HANGAR OFFICER 4A]
We're still waiting for
the mine team to board!
Your fighters
won't be able to launch
until we get
to a higher altitude.
[SHINOHARA]
Ah. Well that's great.
So what, we just
stand here looking pretty?
[KATO] Guess we'll
have to borrow them .
Which them?
[MALE HANGAR OFFICER 4B]
Hey!
Did they give
a launch order for that?
Who's in that cockpit?
[MALE HANGAR OFFICER 4B]
Wait. It's not one of you guys?
[KATO] Hey! You!
State your name and rank!
Well, whoever the hell you are,
get back to
the medical team, pronto!
[MORI] This is the medical team.
Yamato , please respond.
[WOMAN] Cosmo Zero Two
to medical team. I'm on my way.
--[MORI] Huh?
--[thud, clang]
--[KODAI] Nice work.
--[HARADA] All right!
[MORI screams]
Mori!
[speaking Gamilan]
--What now?
--Just take cover!
[KODAI]
Uh!
[KODAI grunts]
I should treat him!
[ANALYZER]
That is an enemy.
I don't care!
[gasps]
Take this, Gami!
[KODAI grunts]
[MORI grunting]
[groans]
Nice shooting.
Hey, look out!
[KODAI grunts]
Get down!
Pretty impressive work there.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You've just saved my life.
Yeah, well. This old thing
deserves most of the credit.
[KODAI gasps]
What's the matter?
Hey! What's wrong?
[MORI]
Huh?
♪
[KODAI]
It was his, all along.
His gun. His crew.
That's my brother's ship,
the Yukikaze !
♪
Lose the helmet, soldier.
Hey...!
Son of a-- I shoulda known.
Hold on. Where's Kodai?
[SHIMA] Oh, he's giving
your team's report.
Is that okay?
[KODAI] Reporting, sir.
Origin of distress call
was the assault
destroyer Yukikaze
of the UN Cosmo Force,
First Fleet.
We conducted a thorough search,
but found no survivors on board.
[OKITA] No survivors.
That dreaded phrase.
Kodai.
Let's make sure
the earth doesn't share
the Yukikaze 's fate.
Yes, sir.
[OKITA] The planet named after
the god of the dead
now stands before the Yamato ,
and unless its
weaponry is overcome,
our civilization has no future.
All crew to battle stations!
Target: Pluto.
Can the Yamato overcome the
deadly trap that lies in wait?
Our biggest battle yet--
our ordeal to leave
the solar system begins now.
Next time:
"The Trap on All Sides."
There are 362 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.