[CLONE GUARD A] Attack from
Second Baleras complete.
[MORI]
What have you done?
[DESLER]
Oh, just a little idea of mine.
I've tried using Wave
Motion Energy as a weapon.
A Wave Motion Gun?
[CLONE GUARD A] The Yamato
appears to be destroyed.
After a long journey,
they were killed just
before reaching their goal.
There's beauty in its perfectly
tragic end, don't you think?
I wonder what the Teron
captain was like.
I'd love to have met the man,
to thank him for giving me
such a rousing challenge.
Our dear Princess Yurisha
seems to be feeling unwell.
Perhaps she needs fresh air.
Let's go.
[CLONE GUARD B] Something on
radar near point of impact.
It's the Yamato !
[NANBU]
AA guns badly damaged!
[OTA]
Sensors malfunctioning!
[MISAKI]
The planet's collapsing!
Epidra is lost.
A weapon that can destroy
planets with one shot?
A Wave Motion Gun.
Picking up fluctuations in
the gravitational gradient.
This waveform is consistent
with a wave motion attack.
We are not retreating.
We'll continue
to the inner system.
Any wave motion weapon
should have difficulty
targeting a ship moving
at sub-light-speed.
And without moving
deep into their range,
we have no way to win.
Full speed ahead.
New target, Gamilas!
[CLONE GUARD B] Yamato heading
toward us at sub-light-speed!
[DESLER]
Interesting.
[CLONE GUARD C] Minister Talan
hailing from Second Baleras.
My lord, as anticipated, firing
at maximum available power
has damaged the system.
Complete the repairs
as soon as you can.
They're at sub-light-speed.
Targeting with the Desler Cannon
will be close to impossible!
It won't work!
Patience, Talan, they'll
be slowing down soon.
[CLONE GUARD C]
My lord.
Her Royal Highness Queen
Starsha is on the hotline.
She wants to speak
to you directly.
[STARSHA] Lord Desler, how
could you even consider this?
Weaponizing Wave Motion
Energy is madness.
And in our own system no less!
--Are you here to complain?
--I am.
You're always complaining.
Have you noticed
that's the only reason
you ever grace me with
your presence anymore?
Well if you're so incensed,
then why don't you go
complain to the Terons?
And what does that mean?
[DESLER]
That ship you brought here
also weaponizes
Wave Motion Energy.
They've used it for some time.
That can't be.
While you're here,
I assume you noticed
your little sister is with us.
She's doing quite well.
[STARSHA gasps]
I've ordered that she be
kept here, safe and secure.
How far are you going to
take this? To what end?
[DESLER]
But I'm doing it all for you.
Stop it.
[DESLER]
Starsha.
Please, don't!
I see. That's too bad.
[STARSHA]
Please, Abelt. Don't do this.
[MISAKI] Three ships at
ten o'clock. Carriers!
[SANADA]
Deploy Wave Motion Shields.
[OKITA]
No.
Not yet.
Yes, sir.
Slow down to half speed.
Then send out the Falcons!
[KILLMENHEIM CM A] Front carrier
fleet will soon encounter enemy.
Have them attack.
Launch the Melancas now.
[KATO] Don't let 'em near the
Yamato . Shoot 'em down!
Turn us hard to starboard.
I want the bow pointing
straight at Gamilas!
[CLONE GUARD D] Major damage
to forward carrier fleet.
[CLONE GUARD B]
The Yamato is descending.
Ultimately, our goal is
protecting the new capital.
But I still want to give
our leader a good show.
[MELDA] That's Baleras ahead,
the Imperial capital.
Cross this ravine and you'll
have a clear path to the palace.
Mm. That sounds good to me.
Head for the palace. We'll
strike right at their heart.
[HYSS] We've allowed the
enemy in to our home world?
What is the Imperial
Guard doing?
Gimleh. I told you
he was useless.
♪
Deploy Wave Motion Shields.
[OKITA]
We're going to ram the palace.
All crew, brace for impact!
[MORI gasps]
[OKITA groans]
Captain. Are you okay?
I want all crew
armed with weapons.
Kodai, assemble a strike
team with you in command.
We'd better get out of here.
Uh!
That's exactly what
I thought you'd say.
[OPERATOR D]
Damage report, now!
[OPERATOR C] The palace
wall has been breached!
[HYSS]
Impossible.
[CELESTRA]
Is our leader safe?
Send in soldiers
to find him, now!
Let's not panic.
[PA VOICE A] Initiating
Deusura decoupling sequence.
The Deusura ?
[CELESTRA]
Out of the way!
[PA VOICE A speaking Gamilan]
What? We're accelerating.
[MISAKI] Something's
launched from the palace!
I can tell.
Yuki is onboard.
My lord, you left me behind?
But why? Why would you leave
me?!
My lord. We should
acquire full control
of Second Baleras momentarily.
Everything is going as planned.
Yes, sir.
Then it is time to
begin the operation!
Zar Belk.
[BALERAS II OFFICER A]
Minister Talan,
our central control system is
being taken over from outside!
[VELTE]
Find the origin.
What the--? It's coming
from the Deusura !
--Lord Desler?
--Ah! Minister, sir!
Industrial Sector 633
is decoupling!
Uh. That can't be.
[YURISHA]
Forget this palace.
Go after that vessel
and rescue Yuki!
Strike team is ready to go!
Kodai!
[MISAKI]
I've found something on radar!
Magnify it!
[MISAKI] It's a massive
object falling from orbit!
[ANALYZER] Estimated mass:
60 million tons.
Descending from
Lagrange point L-One.
Estimated impact
point is the palace.
In other words: Here.
[OPERATOR C]
It's continuing to drop.
[OPERATOR D]
The decoupling command
came from Lord Desler himself.
From Lord Desler?
[OPERATOR B] Impact at
approximately 2,400 gek.
But this doesn't make any sense.
Everyone, evacuate! Declare
an emergency in the capital!
[PA VOICE A]
This is not a drill.
All personnel must evacuate
palace immediately.
Repeat: all personnel must
evacuate palace immediately.
We can't stay here, sir!
How could he? How could
our leader do this?
Desler!
[OPERATOR E]
Guidance beacon, locked.
[OPERATOR F]
Docking complete.
Connected to Desler
Cannon circuit.
[LECTER]
Minister Talan is here.
My lord, tell me why
you're doing this, please.
Why are you dropping Sector
633 on Baleras? Why?
[DESLER]
It's a rite of passage, Talan.
A rite of passage?
[DESLER] Baleras and the Yamato
will be annihilated together.
And from the smoldering ashes
of this noble sacrifice.
A more perfect
Gamilas will be born.
When this operation is done,
Second Baleras will
descend to Iscandar.
As of this moment
by imperial decree,
this mobile
city fortress,
this grand achievement we
have built in the heavens,
will be the new
capital of Gamilas.
A new center! A new Baleras!
Splendid, my lord.
[DESLER] This Second Baleras
shall be the ultimate bridge,
uniting Gamilas and Iscandar
for our glorious future!
[ANALYZER] Estimated impact
on palace: 20 minutes.
Prepare to fire the
Wave Motion Gun.
Okita.
It's the only hope we have
for destroying a
structure that massive.
With the gun,
we can save this city.
Proving it with actions,
not with your words. Mm.
This is a moment when
we all must do our best.
As our hearts compel us.
What we alone can achieve.
--I'm going after Yuki!
--[KODAI] No.
Sorry. But it should be me.
Captain, please, sir.
Requesting use of a Zero.
Kodai. I hereby
relieve you of your duties
as Yamato 's Chief of Tactical.
As of now, I'm giving
you another mission.
Rescue Lieutenant Mori,
whatever it takes.
Yes, sir!
[OKITA] You may take one
more person to assist.
Thanks, Captain.
[KODAI gasps]
Yes, Captain. I promise
I won't let you down.
I've got this, sir. Just
please. Bring her back.
Melda.
[MELDA] Just protecting
Princess Yurisha.
You leave them to me, Kodai.
[MELDA]
She means to us.
Everyone.
We're doing our best,
what we alone can achieve.
Ready?
Yeah. Yeah!
Take care of Her Grace.
Go, Kodai. Good luck.
[PA VOICE B]
After linking with core ship,
Company Six is to
load Deusura II
and make primed for launch.
[GAMILAN TECH A]
Get that resupply ready!
[MORI]
Looks like the control room.
[ORTSCHETT]
Aren't we trying to escape?
[MORI] This craft has
a Wave Motion Gun,
and if they use it, the Yamato
will never reach Iscandar.
What are you trying to do?
I'm gonna try to destroy it.
Sealing emergency vents.
[NANBU]
Releasing safety lock.
[KITANO]
Target in range.
[SHIMA] Adjusting angle
of incline. Raising bow.
Stabilize the hull.
[PA VOICE A]
All citizens must evacuate.
Impact is imminent.
Proceed to nearest transport.
[TOKUGAWA] Tachyon particle
pressure rising in chamber.
Energy charge 120%.
Anti-shock and
anti-flare defenses.
[NANBU]
Four. Three. Two. One.
Fire!
The Yamato . They saved us all.
Yamato ?
[OKITA groaning]
[thud]
[SANADA]
Captain!
[OPERATOR D] Six-Three-Three
engaged in route.
[LECTER]
Very well.
My lord, Desler Cannon is
back online and ready to fire.
[VELTE gasps]
[DESLER]
Hm.
[ORTSCHETT]
It's preparing to fire!
[MORI]
Don't worry.
[PA VOICE A]
Firing sequence...
[MORI]
It's done.
[PA VOICE A] ...prepare
for Wave Motion sequence.
This will destabilize
the Wave Motion Core.
Yuki.
Thanks for all your
help. Now go.
You don't need to stick
around for the rest.
There's still time--
Why are you willing to
make this sacrifice?
Because it's finally clear.
I understand it now.
I'm doing what my
heart tells me to do.
What I want most of all.
--We do this...
--I do this...
To keep you safe!
Let's go, Zero!
[YURISHA]
Ever faster! Ever higher!
[PA VOICE A]
Begin routing all...
No.
Why, Norran?
I thought that would be obvious.
This is my chance to show
what I'm made of, too.
If my lord learns I saved this
secret weapon from sabotage,
he might even make me
a first-class Gamilan.
You're not thinking! Ugh!
[ORTSCHETT]
Oh, trust me, I am!
I've never been more certain.
And that's why this
is our goodbye.
[MORI yells]
No, wait! Norran!
You take care.
[MORI]
Norran!
[ORTSCHETT]
Farewell.
[LECTER]
Firing hammer system activated.
[DESLER]
Focus on the Yamato .
Channel all the energy we have.
My lord, you can't do this!
You're about to fire
on your own people!
Think of how many will die!
[PA VOICE A] Desler Cannon final
firing sequence set to begin.
[DESLER] That's why it must be
my hand that pulls the trigger.
I must be the one
who commits the sin
of sacrificing so many noble
lives for the future of Gamilas.
It will haunt me. But for
the sake of the empire,
I will bear this
burden on my soul.
What the--?
[PA VOICE A]
Warning. Warning.
Wave Motion Core failing.
Safety limits exceeded.
Explosive compression immin...
[ORTSCHETT] It's funny.
I was willing to go this far.
But never learned her real name.
[OPERATOR 23D]
The core's about to blow!
--Jump now!
--Yes, sir!
No. Goodbye, Norran.
You're a terrible liar.
[KILLMENHEIM CM A]
The other ships are gone!
Explosion incoming!
[GAMILAN OFFICER A]
Evasive action! Get away!
[KILLMENHEIM CM A]
There's no time!
My, what a shame.
So this is how it ends.
[MISAKI] Enemy station appears
to be collapsing, sir.
What in the world
happened out there?
In the end, I lost her.
[gasps]
♪
[MORI]
I'm not dreaming, am I?
No. This is real.