[BRIDGE OFFICER 11A
speaking Gamilan]
[speaking Gamilan]
[BERGER speaking Gamilan]
[BERGER]
This is Deputy Commander Berger,
leading the 7th Strike Group.
The enemy is 70% eliminated
and in full retreat.
These Gatlantis are
nothing to fear.
[DOMEL]
Don't underestimate them.
Uh. Yes, sir.
The 7th Strike Group will
pursue and destroy
all remaining hostiles.
[BERGER]
Zar Belk!
Berger's getting too cocky,
but it is a good victory.
Yes.
Those barbarians should be off
our backs for a while.
[DOMEL]
Heh. You've been enjoying
this fight, haven't you?
You're damn right!
[laughs]
[BRIDGE OFFICER 11A]
General Domel,
incoming message from
Imperial Command.
From Baleras?
Who is it?
Admiral Ditz sir, Supreme
Commander of the Astrofleets.
You look well, Space Wolf.
[DOMEL] I'm pleased to see
that you do as well, sir.
I have news.
You've been ordered to
return to the home world.
You will be awarded the Desler
Cross, Special First Class.
[BRIDGE OFFICERS gasp]
I'm honored, sir.
But this border's critical
to our defenses.
As the commanding officer,
I cannot leave the front
lines for mere pomp!
I understand.
You have no taste for
political performance.
But our Supreme Lord
is planning something
and it's not our place to doubt.
I've sent the 8th to the
front as reinforcements.
And Gudell's Gross Space Armored
Forces are on the way as well.
You can leave the rest to them.
Understood, sir.
[DITZ] Good. Then I'll
see you at Baleras.
Zar Belk!
Good! You can suit back up,
thanks for agreeing to this.
[OKITA]
Their DNA looks like ours?
You're sure?
I know it's shocking, Captain,
but other than the skin color,
she's essentially
the same as us.
[OKITA]
Hm...
Captain. It's safe to assume
she has information that
would be useful to us.
She could be interrogated
in a number of ways.
No. I think that we
should let her go.
Her fighter plane
has no warp drive,
which means interstellar flight
would be impossible.
We would be condemning her
to an almost certain death.
[gasps] But, sir!
We can't just keep her
locked up like a prisoner.
Come on! She helped us
escape that dimensional fault.
Sir, she's earned the right
to be treated as an ally.
An ally?
Many if not most of
our crewmembers
have lost loved ones
in the Gamilan attacks.
How do you think they
would feel about her
strolling through the ship?
I've lost family too, okay?
Like my brother.
Those monsters sent him
to an icy grave.
I hate them. More than anyone.
And we need to keep her
locked up to protect her
from feelings just like
that, Lieutenant.
We don't want our crew
seeking vengeance.
[KODAI gasps] None of us
would ever stoop to that!
I know it for a fact!
[SANADA sighs]
It's impossible to know that.
Your argument lacks all logic.
Yeah? Well that's still better
than lacking in humanity, sir.
[OKITA]
Enough. I've made my decision.
She'll remain in custody
at least for the time being.
Kodai. I want you
to question her.
Uh?
Hey. Did you hear the rumor?
What that Gamilan
pilot lady told us?
[YAMAZAKI]
No, enlighten me.
She said we attacked them
first and started the war.
Nuts, right?
You survived the first contact,
didn't you, Yama?
You would know
better than anyone.
Yeah.
It's an unconscionable lie.
[TOKUGAWA]
My goodness.
The whole ship's talking about
what that Gamilan pilot said.
Yabu! I thought you
were scheduled
for a counseling session
with Lieutenant Niimi today?
[gasps] Yes, sir!
Thanks for reminding me!
[footsteps]
[TOKUGAWA sighs]
[TOKUGAWA]
You look troubled.
Something on your mind?
♪♪♪
[VIDEO NARRATOR]
The date is April 1, 2191!
A remote observation
post on Uranus
captures shocking
video of spaceships
from another civilization
entering our solar system
for the first time.
The UN Cosmo Force immediately
gathers the brave
inner planet fleet,
ordering the first defensive
action against alien life forms
in the history of humankind.
[VIDEO NARRATOR] Twenty-seven
Japanese battleships
participate in the
harrowing operation,
led by their fleet commander,
Vice-Admiral Juzo Okita,
famous for his heroics
during the Second
Inner Planet War.
The first ship to encounter the
mysterious enemy vessels
near Pluto is the Japanese
cruiser Murasame .
[DAIGO]
Don't worry.
Your old man isn't
going there to fight.
I'm sure we can forge a
friendship with this alien race.
You think so?
I do. Never lose hope, son.
[VIDEO NARRATOR] But
without warning or provocation,
the aliens open fire on the
Murasame, ripping it apart.
With the exception of
one very fortunate man,
the entire crew of the Murasame,
led by Captain Daigo Shima,
is killed, making them the
first casualties in this
terrible war for survival.
[SHIMA]
That's my father.
They fired first.
Those shameless, sneaky cowards.
They decided our entire race
should be exterminated
without ever giving us a chance.
The Gamilans may have faces like
us, but inside they're demons!
Kodai believes in
fair treatment,
but I know we feel the same way.
They're enemies we
can never forgive.
[VIDEO NARRATOR]
We must stand against a threat
greater than any
have ever known!
Your father was a valiant
man, Lieutenant Shima.
Don't ever doubt that.
[SHIMA]
Thank you, Captain.
[VIDEO NARRATOR]
Remember the countless fallen,
and their battle for justice!
We must never forgive
these demonic invaders
from outer space!
My captain wants to
know if you can answer
some questions for us.
[ITO]
Heh. This should be amusing.
I can't wait to see
how this goes.
[door opens]
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, hey. Your shift's not
for another three hours.
For what it's worth, I'm sorry
for how things went down.
Lower Storm Leader Ditz.
I.D. number 3817529.
It sounds like you're taking
the same approach we would.
All of the old war films
I used to watch as a kid
had prisoner scenes
just like this.
Do you have films?
Does Gamilas have any laws
about POW treatment?
We treat all who
surrender to the Empire
with perfect fairness
and civility.
Those who refuse to
surrender, we annihilate.
So that's why you've been trying
to destroy our planet, huh?
Because we dare to fight back?!
And yet...
...we did manage
to work together.
That's gotta mean something.
[MELDA] It means we don't
break our promises.
[KODAI]
Neither do we.
[gasps]
Call me crazy,
but I'm getting this feeling
that we can trust each other.
My XO would probably
call that illogical,
but sometimes you
gotta go with your gut.
[ITO]
He calls that interrogation?
Looks to me like he's trying
to establish trust, sir.
Well, all I'm saying is I hope
he doesn't get any cozier
than he has to.
[HOSHINA]
Huh?
Our Chief of Tactical
is a man, after all.
[ITO] "Establishing trust"
with an alien.
That's a naïve fantasy.
Once the Yamato gets out
of the Milky Way galaxy,
we'll be navigating
toward the planet Balun.
It's a halfway point between us
and the Large Magellanic Cloud.
Sort of a lighthouse
in space to show the way.
So, Lieutenant.
I've never heard of Balun
before, did H.Q. name it
while drawing up
the Yamato Plan?
No, it's not from us.
Apparently it was in the plans
Yurisha gave us a year ago.
Yamazaki.
Lieutenant Shima.
Sorry, but may we have
a word in private?
[gasps] Okay.
[panting]
[exhales]
[YAMAMOTO panting]
You're working hard.
Only way to get stronger.
True. But pushing yourself
too hard can be bad, ya know?
What are you talking about?
No offense, but I think
you're taking this situation
a little too personally.
Oh, I know what'll
cheer you up.
So, what is it you
wanted to talk about?
[YAMAZAKI]
Look,
I was on board the ship your
father captained that day.
[gasps]
Command issued a gag order.
I'm strictly forbidden to ever
discuss what happened.
I've kept quiet
all these years.
But no more.
[gasps]
[SERIZAWA]
We dispatched a military envoy
and attempted peaceful contact.
But the aliens chose
to ignore our overtures
and fired on us without warning.
The UN Space Defense Committee
had no choice but to
take this aggression
as a clear act of war
against planet Earth.
In response, we issued
an emergency order
to defend our system...
[SERIZAWA]
Open fire, Okita!
[OKITA] It's our first contact
with an alien civilization.
We can't jump to conclusions!
[SERIZAWA] This is Central
Command's decision!
If we don't act decisively
it could be too late.
That's nonsense!
Incoming message
from the Murasame.
"We have encountered alien
vessels. Please advise."
We don't have time
to debate this
and it's clear you won't obey.
By my authority as
Military Director,
I hereby remove
you from command!
[gasps]
[SERIZAWA] This is General
Serizawa from Central Command.
The Murasame is instructed
to immediately open fire
on the alien vessels.
But, sir! Admiral Okita--
[SERIZAWA]
Has been removed from command.
You have your orders, Captain!
[YAMAZAKI]
And so, we did as we were told.
We opened fire first
on the Gamilan ships.
[SHIMA gasping]
[MURASAME CM 11A]
Critical hit to deck four, sir!
[MURASAME CM 11B]
Second main gun is down!
Main engine output
reduced by 80%!
All crew, abandon ship!
You sure, Captain?
This ship is too far gone
to survive. Go, Chief.
Admiral Owen,
manage the evacuation.
But, Captain...
Forging a friendship with
the aliens is possible.
I made that promise to my son.
Instead, we've chosen war.
Captain...
Go quickly!
That's an order, Chief!
Yes, sir.
[alarm blaring]
Get to the lifeboats, hurry!
[MURASAME CM 11A groans]
[MURASAME VOICE]
Emergency.
Sealing all bulkheads.
Captain!
[DAIGO]
Daisuke, never lose hope.
[YAMAZAKI] I don't remember
what happened next.
Or how I escaped.
I just... woke up.
[YAMAZAKI]
The battle was already over,
with no sign of
the fellow sailors
I thought had gotten
out with me.
Liar! That can't be true!
[KODAI]
Ah, there you are.
Did you learn anything?
Serving her empire with honor
means everything to her.
She'll never give information
that betrays that.
[OKITA] Those who close
their eyes to the past
become blind to the future.
Perhaps she's already told
us what we needed to hear.
What is this?
Does sullying my father's honor
give you some kind
of twisted thrill?!
Your father was a man
of utmost integrity.
He would want you to know.
I refuse to accept this!
You're making it all up!
I know you are!
[door closes]
[MORI sighs]
There!
Don't you feel better?
This was your plan
for cheering me up?
[MORI]
Well, sure!
After exercise, you stretch
and have a nice, hot bath.
That's Relaxation 101!
It's surprising, that's all.
Huh?
[YAMAMOTO]
Everyone says you're so guarded.
Basically, I didn't think
Ice Queens took hot baths.
That name. I can't shake it.
[YAMAMOTO]
Can I ask you something?
Huh?
[What'd you mean?
In the gym, when you said I was
taking things too personally.
[sighs]
[YAMAMOTO]
Are you scared to tell me?
A little.
I know your brother lost
his life fighting Gamilans
and I don't want
to minimize that.
But I still don't
think it's fair
to direct all your anger at her.
You mean that pilot.
Why don't we wait until
you lose family in this war
and then you can talk
to me about what's fair.
[MORI]
That may not be possible.
Huh?
[MORI]
Truth is,
I don't have any memories
beyond this last year.
There's a good chance my
family's dead already,
I just can't remember
who they were,
or what they meant to me.
It's all just empty space.
Then you're right, you can't
possibly understand.
[door hisses]
[SANADA]
Based on our analysis,
this system shows strong
signs of enemy activity.
It's highly probable
there's a Gamilan base
on one of these planets
very close to our route.
We've already charted a detour
to keep our distance.
[OKITA]
No. We'll maintain our course.
[gasps]
It's the perfect place
to drop off our passenger.
[door hisses]
Okay, time to change shifts.
[SHIMA]
I have to object!
What if she's been spying on us?
Shima...
My decision stands, Lieutenant.
How can you trust that demon
when she lied to our faces,
and said we attacked them first?
Would you relax?
This isn't like you.
They killed your brother
like they killed my father!
Don't tell me you trust her
just because she helped
us out one time!
[KODAI grunts]
[gasps] Do you?
[beeping]
[AIHARA]
Bridge to Captain.
The Gamilan fighter plane
has launched, sir!
--[SHIMA gasps]
--And who's flying it?
[AIHARA]
Melda Ditz.
How could she have escaped?
[AIHARA] Wait, did someone
issue a pursuit order?
One of the Cosmo Falcons
just launched, too!
Hold on, what?
[AIHARA]
Yamato to Falcon. Do you copy?
I repeat. Falcon, do you copy?
All right, who's piloting that
thing?! What is going on?
[KODAI]
Come in!
Don't you ignore me!
[YAMAMOTO]
Out here it's just you and me.
[S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Enemy locked on.
[YAMAMOTO gasps]
[S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Warning! Warning!
Engine failure.
Vessel cannot maintain
functionality
in these conditions.
[S.I.D. VOICE 6A]
Engine pressure rising.
Ten seconds until critical.
[MELDA]
You need to eject! Now!
[YAMAMOTO growls]
[YAMAMOTO]
Akio...
Oh, look who's awake.
[YAMAMOTO]
Where am I?
Onboard the Yamato .
Melda brought you
back in her ship.
[YAMAMOTO]
Melda did?
You're kidding, right?
I'm not. And by the way,
she'll be leaving us soon.
I'm sorry, Yuki.
Your punishment is six
days in the brig.
I'd say I got off light.
But... I do think I'm
feeling better now.
[KODAI]
This is goodbye.
This food should
last you four days.
So tell me,
when she crashed,
did you think I would abandon
her and try to escape?
No, I thought we could
trust in your honor.
And I was right.
I want her to know she showed
real talent out there.
[KODAI gasps]
I'll trust you to
pass that along.
[MAINTENANCE 9A] Gamilan fighter
disembarking shortly.
You know, it keeps on surprising
me how much we think alike.
Change course, Lieutenant.
Get us out of this sector.
Roger that.
[OKITA] Separated by the
vast expanse of space,
two worlds are locked
in a bitter war,
with two ideas of the "truth"
and what defines
a righteous act.
[OKITA]
Is there any hope
of reconciling these
disparate truths,
as the Yamato pushes onward,
across the galactic seas?
Next time: What Lies Beyond.
There are 318 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.