[GAMILIAN RECON
speaking Gamilan]
[KOBASHI] So we're
restricted to visual range?
Talk about old school!
[KOBASHI]
Captain!
[KATO] Yeah, I see 'em.
Time to greet our guests.
Don't let them kill you.
You kill them!
[FALCON PILOTS]
Yes, sir!
[SNUKA PILOT speaking Gamilan]
[BRIDGE OFFICER A] Attack Force
Group Two, launch immediately.
Repeat: Attack Force Group Two,
launch immediately.
[BERGER]
Fomt Berger, launching.
[BRIDGE OFFICER A] Attack Force
Group Two is in position.
Activating Matter
Transfer System!
Inputting recon data now, sir.
Coordinates: Over their ship.
Matter Transfer Waves
calibrated and ready.
Then fire!
[BERGER]
There they are.
[gasps] They're
right over us, sir!
[OKITA]
Huh?
[NAV. OFFICER A]
Direct hit!
--[SHIMA] Damage control!
--[OTA] Torpedoes coming fast!
Gunners, AA formation!
Maintain a wall of fire!
Secondary Gunport One is hit!
Damn it!
[YAMAMOTO]
Yamamoto to Bridge.
Alpha Two launching now.
[BERGER]
Melhi, you target the catapult.
I'll knock out their eyes.
[BERGER]
We don't want to sink it. Yet.
[CO-PILOT A]
Enemy behind us!
[BERGER]
Huh?
I won't let you get
away with this!
[OTA] Port-side catapult
has been destroyed!
[SAIJO]
Radar, system hit!
[KODAI]
Gunners, keep firing!
[AIHARA] Yamato to all
fighters! Do you copy?
This is the Yamato
with a change of orders.
We are under surprise attack!
All fighters are to return
immediately to close perimeter
and defend the Yamato !
[KATO]
What? We're chasing decoys?
[KOBASHI]
Captain, what do we do?
[PILOT screams]
[DAIKUHARA] Don't lose
your nerve, Kobashi.
I'll shoot down
anyone on your tail!
[KOBASHI]
Daikuhara's down!
[gasps]
[KATO]
Akira, keep 'em busy!
[CO-PILOT A]
That was one Fighter?
[BERGER] Doesn't matter.
Our job's done. Withdraw.
Their fighter
group's retreating.
[ENOMOTO]
Bridge Three to Bridge One.
Our converter's shot.
We cannot deploy
Wave Motion Shields.
If we don't patch this,
it's going to affect
inertial control.
I'll go supervise repairs.
But those fighters came
down out of nowhere.
How'd they do that?
[OKITA]
They warped.
There's no way.
Those small fighters could
never hold a warp drive.
You can't win if you only rely
on what you think you know.
They've got one hell
of a commander.
Excellent bit of flying, Berger.
Surface the ship and
release our guests.
[BELLGER]
Remember that face, soldiers.
I gotta say, she's beautiful.
Well, that's nobility for you.
[RAITSCH]
Hm.
Don't fall in love, Norran.
[ORTSCHETT grunts]
[ORTSCHETT]
I'm not!
[AIHARA]
All damage teams,
full priority to Bridge
Three converter...
Norran, stay here and
keep that airlock secure
until we get back.
Zar Belk.
[HEYDELN]
So tell me, Barlen.
How does it feel sittin'
in the pilot seat again?
[BARLEN]
Feels wonderful.
I may be all scars and
wrinkles on the outside,
but I'm still as sharp
as the day I enlisted.
[HEYDELN laughs]
Garlent primed and launching.
[OKITA]
That was only the start.
Their commander will
have more surprises.
Everyone stay on the
lookout for the next one.
How can we, sir?
Our sensors are down.
With the Yamato flying
blind and deaf now,
our human senses are
all we can rely on.
That and our wits.
There should be a current
of ion turbulence nearby.
Use the data we've already
gathered to find it.
[OTA, KIRYU]
Yes, sir.
Hostile! Dead ahead!
[BARLEN]
Here's your gift, Terons!
Hope you like it!
[KODAI]
A dud?
[BARLEN]
The present has been delivered.
We're on our way back--
You're finished!
[ALL yell]
[IWATA]
Okay! To the windows!
[TACTICAL OFFICERS]
Right!
Yurisha!
[YURISHA]
Hoshina.
They could come from
any direction...
It's dangerous here.
They could attack.
[TACTICAL OFFICERS]
Yes, sir!
Be careful.
What is that? A bomb?
[KIRYU] Sending report
on dud to Bridge Three.
[NANBU] Wave Motion Gun
Control Room, report.
Captain! It's moving
towards the gun's chamber!
[WAVE GUN CM A]
Chamber pressure dropping!
[WAVE GUN CM B]
Close the safety valves, now!
[WAVE GUN CM C]
Watch out! Hurry!
[BRIDGE 3 OFFICER A]
Inertial control is down.
[ENOMOTO] I guess it
wasn't a dud, after all.
[SANADA]
Most likely a delay fuse.
[ENOMOTO]
This is bad.
[SANADA]
This is Sanada, on Bridge Three.
Go ahead.
I have a suggestion.
[AIHARA] All available
crewmembers not assigned
to damage teams or
active battle stations
are needed for
emergency watch duty.
Position yourselves at
stations with exterior...
[HOSHINA]
Hey. Hold up.
Don't think we've met before.
Where're you stationed?
[BELLGER]
Oh, uh. Me?
[gasps]
[KIRYU]
Gunfire on Deck Six!
Sound print matches
Gamilan weapon, sir!
Send security to investigate.
Kodai, take command.
Yes, sir!
[YURISHA]
Hoshina!
No!
They've seen our faces.
[MORI]
Hey, what's going on here?
It's the Iscandarian.
[RAITSCH]
Sorry about this.
Got her.
[ANALYZER]
I am surprised that this weapon
could be infiltrated so easily.
[NIIMI] Probably because it
wasn't built as a weapon.
I think they converted
existing tech
that wasn't designed
for warfare.
[ANALYZER]
A logical conclusion.
Seems the enemy's
starting to get desperate.
[chuckles]
But then, so are we.
[yells]
Stop it! Get off me!
[SAWAMURA]
You okay, rookie?
Sawamura?
[SAWAMURA]
Don't push yourself.
Enemy ship, ten o'clock!
[KOBASHI]
That's a carrier.
[SAWAMURA]
Kobashi, wait!
[KOBASHI]
I've got this!
[SAWAMURA]
Kobashi! Abort!
I'm no coward,
and I'm gonna prove it!
[BRIDGE OFFICER C]
Enemy approaching portside!
Fire anti-air weapons!
Mother!
Kobashi!
Damn it!
[KATO]
Not bad.
[GETTO speaking Gamilan]
[SNUKA PILOT B speaking Gamilan]
[KATO]
You're mine!
[GETTO speaking Gamilan]
I can help.
[KODAI]
Gamilan soldiers?
[KODAI gasps]
Mori!
Get her to the ship!
[ORTSCHETT]
Yes, sir!
[SECURITY C] Security to Bridge,
Gamilans are onboard!
Captain!
Uh! No!
Captain Gelt!
Go, Norran. Escape!
Fulfill our mission,
and make Zaltz proud!
Long live, Zaltz!
Yuki!
No, Yuki! Yuki!
[FLAKEN] Surface. Let's pick
up our little suckerfish.
What do I do? What do I do?
[KODAI]
Yuki!
[BRIDGE OFFICER A] Encrypted
message from the Hound .
The suckerfish has our target.
Schderg requesting permission
to launch the attack teams.
Shall we, sir?
[DOMEL]
When that drill explodes,
the Yamato should
be ripped apart.
But there are no
certainties in battle.
We'll send out the bombers
in case they need
to finish the job.
Attack Force Group Three.
Launch when ready!
[NIIMI] Niimi to Bridge. The
detonator has been disabled.
Well done. You may
have saved the ship.
[ANALYZER]
Good job.
Die, Gamilans!
[SCIENCE DIV. OFFICERS scream]
[KATO] Damn it.
You'll all pay for this!
[KRAITZE] Attack Force Group
Three requesting reinforcements!
Enemy fighters have engaged,
they're coming down strong!
You're dead!
General?
Evidently the gods want me
to finish the Yamato myself.
Then I shall do their bidding.
Order fleet to strike!
Mooring Cosmo Zero!
[SAIJO]
The fighters have returned, sir.
Twelve were lost.
Get them ready for re-launch.
Ota, did you find
that ion current?
[OTA]
Yes, sir.
[IWATA] Watch Team to Bridge.
Enemy ships to starboard!
[OKITA]
So they've come.
[NIIMI]
Analyzer!
[ANALYZER]
Go on.
Turn the ship! Forty
to port! Combat Speed!
But, sir! That'll take
us to the ion current!
If the storm sucks us in,
we'll be helpless!
That's an order, Lieutenant!
Uh. Right!
Changing course
40 degrees to port.
[OKITA] Ota, send that
drill's flight path
to the weapons officer.
[OTA]
Aye-aye!
[OKITA] Nanbu, when its axis
lines up with the enemy fleet,
light it up.
Sir!
It's a tough shot,
sir. Don't miss!
Don't you worry.
Guns are my specialty.
[BARECK]
Evade!
[LAMBEA CM A]
The Schderg is down!
Just stay calm!
[LAMBEA OFFICER A]
Enemy is firing!
[BERGER]
Send me out there! Now!
Don't be a fool!
I want revenge!
Damn it! It can't
end this way!
[HEYDELN]
Berger!
All cannons fire!
Fire!
[BRIDGE OFFICER A]
Direct hit!
Keep calm, and fire!
Concentrate everything
we've got left on that ship!
I told you, keep
firing! Now what?
Right the ship, now!
[BRIDGE OFFICER A]
We can't, sir!
We're caught in the ion current!
That was their plan?
The ion storm current
has caught them, sir!
[DOMEL]
Of course.
They lured me into this trap.
I let my arrogance consume me
and tried to destroy
the Yamato myself.
It's my fault.
In the final hour,
I made a fatal mistake.
[BRIDGE OFFICER B]
Engine output dropping!
[HEYDELN]
Turn to port!
[BRIDGE OFFICER B]
The helm's not responding!
We've lost control of the ship!
[DOMEL]
Elk Domel, ID-17492-Zeku.
[HEYDELN]
General, don't.
This is now a battle
between them and me.
All crew abandon ship!
[chuckles]
Looks like we're all going
to be court-martialed
for disobeying orders, sir.
[HEYDELN]
Prepare to fire anchors!
It sounds like we
have a new problem.
I'm almost finished.
[KIRYU] An enemy vessel
has latched onto us.
[beeping]
The enemy ship
is hailing us, sir.
Video transmission.
On screen.
Let me speak to your captain.
You're speaking to the captain
right now. Juzo Okita.
Greetings.
I'm Commander of the Milky
Way Galactic Theater,
Elk Domel.
I've been looking
forward to this moment.
Glad to hear it.
Because I feel the same way.
Captain Okita, allow me
to express my admiration
for your exemplary command.
Commander Domel,
this battle is over.
I'd like to avoid more
bloodshed if we can.
Let us pass, and we will
not fire on your ship.
I can't do that.
As a fellow leader,
I'd think you'd understand.
If I allow the
Yamato safe passage,
then all my men who have
given their lives today
will have done so in vain.
Captain Okita, as a soldier--
no, more than that--as a man,
I'm proud to have faced
an opponent like you
before my death.
It was a true honor.
Bless the Terons,
and Gamilans alike,
as we die in this battle.
The enemy's going
to self-destruct.
All crew on the lower
decks evacuate!
Oh, Elk.
Did we really make it?