[MORI] Powerful energy
reading. Overhead!
[GANZ]
Splendid work, Commander.
When we report this
to Major General Goer
we can hold our heads high.
[SHULTZ]
I don't think so.
If that shameless
opportunist hears this,
he'll report to Lord Desler as
if he'd conceived this himself.
This is our victory and
we're going to make sure
we claim the spoils.
♪
Ilun Phezeron.
We have an incoming call.
Commander Shultz wishes
to give you a direct report.
Who is Shultz?
I believe you placed him
in command of
the forward base on Plat
in the galactic hinterlands'
Zol system, my lord.
[DESLER]
Ah yes. I left a brigade of
second-class Gamilans in charge
of Teron's conquest, didn't I.
[footsteps]
[SHULTZ] I am Walke Shultz,
Commander of the forces
besieging Teron, my lord.
You are contacting us
without the approval
of your commanding officer,
Major General Goer,
a grave offense--!
Now, now, Hyss,
I would like to hear him.
Yes, sir.
Go on, Commander.
Please give your report.
Oh, yes sir.
This morning, at Tahm 1006
Gamilan Standard Time,
after fierce engagement,
we destroyed the
Teron FTL-capable
spaceship Yamato using our
RSC as an improvised weapon.
And you called to tell
me this why, Commander?
Well, sir. I-I wanted
to let you know
immediately about our victory.
So, you requested
a direct audience with me
in order to say that?
An outcome so obvious
it was implied?
I simply wished to add some
small measure of further glory
for the Great Gamilas Empire's
founding celebration.
I shall remember
your loyalty, Commander.
That's enough!
Now get back to work!
Garle Desler!
Hail to our leader!
So, Celestra. Is it true
a Teron ship has actually
managed to break
the light speed barrier?
That's the first I've
heard of it, Ilun Phezeron.
How about you,
Viceroy Hyss, did you know?
Uh, I did not. This is
news to me as well, sir.
I assumed as much.
[FEMALES giggle]
[GANZ] Commander, what did
Lord Desler have to say?
He told me he would
remember our loyalty, Ganz.
[gasps]
It's a shame about the Terons.
If they had chosen
not to fight back,
they could have lived
under the Gamilan thumb,
just as we have.
[YAMAMOTO humming]
Hey SID. Tell me
everything you can
about our search zone.
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A]
Executing command.
I've linked geographic data
with observed heat sources
projected as possible
sites of Gamilan base.
[ENOMOTO] Balance control,
are those vents closed?
We're working on it, sir!
[ENOMOTO]
Work faster!
Who wants to drown
on a spaceship?
Not me, damn it!
Hey! Prime the Extractor Pumps!
[MALE COMBAT OFFICER 6A]
We're closing this section off!
Get out of here! Aah!
[ENGINE ROOM OFFICER 4A]
Okay, it's contained over here.
[WOUNDED OFFICERS moaning]
[DR. SADO]
This wound's nothing.
With a little spit
he'll be fine.
Hey, Makoto!
She's helping patients
in another section, Doctor.
[HARADA]
Hey, you still with me?
Just stay strong, okay?
We'll patch you up right now,
you'll be fine.
All right, this one is stable.
Good. Give me a hand.
Yes, ma'am!
[HARADA]
See? You're all right.
So, were they able
to figure out how
the enemy was attacking us?
From what I've heard
they still don't know yet.
[MALE ANNOUNCEMENT 4A]
Damage Control Team Three
report to Deck Four.
[YABU] Finished the check.
No problems yet.
That's good to hear.
What do you think, sir?
What's the plan?
How long are we
gonna have to sit here
hiding on the ocean floor?
We haven't even made it
out of our own solar system.
Do you really think
we'll be able to make it
all the way to Iscandar?
I will never let another ship
go down on my watch.
Since the first moment
I set sail from the earth,
my life's been in
old man Okita's hands,
and he's kept me alive.
If there's a way through,
then he'll find it.
That's all I know.
[SHIMA]
You're positive, sir?
[SANADA] Yes, a
satellite-assisted beam weapon.
The large amount of orbital
debris made me curious.
So intel did more
thorough scanning.
[NIIMI]
They're not debris at all.
They're enemy satellites.
We believe they're using
this immense network
to precisely relay a beam
which is fired from the surface.
If that's true...
They could hit any
coordinate around Pluto
and from any angle.
But that means there's
no way to escape.
If we surface
they'll hit us again!
[OKITA] Can we approximate
how much time we'd have?
I'll try, sir.
I hope our little fireworks
and acrobatic performance
were enough to
convince them we sank.
They're going to figure out
the truth eventually.
But for now, we sit tight
and put our faith in Kodai
and the rest of the pilots.
And when the time is right,
the Yamato will strike back.
And strike back hard.
[SHINOHARA]
Hey, Nemoto.
That rookie pilot's
a real babe, huh?
She sure can rock a flight suit.
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A]
EM restrictions in effect.
Communication not sent.
I know that, Navi-sweet!
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A]
Sorry, command not recognized.
Loosen up,
we're just havin' fun.
♪ Protect me at night and
protect me during the day ♪
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A] Sorry,
command not recognized.
Search target
in three megameters.
[KATO] EM restrictions lifted.
Come on Sugiyama, follow me.
[NOBUHIKO]
Roger! Ugh!
Sugiyama!
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A]
Bravo 3 destroyed.
[KATO]
I guess we chose a winner, huh?
What do you mean
Teron fighters? Impossible.
Just outside the
Unmanned Environmental
Modification Plant
number 137, sir.
What are they doing out there?
Anti-Aircraft System
engaging them now, sir.
It appears there are
several others coming out
of hiding as well, Commander.
Most likely survivors
from the Yamato .
Launch the interceptors
to finish them off.
Sir!
♪
[YAMAMOTO]
Beautiful.
[KATO] This is Bravo 1.
EM restrictions lifted.
I've found the Gamilan base.
[KODAI]
Yamamoto, let's go.
[YAMAMOTO]
Wait!
[KODAI]
Is there a problem?
[YAMAMOTO]
Two o'clock.
Two o'clock?
[AIHARA]
Message from Bravo 1.
Lieutenant Kato under fire
at Target Five.
He found it.
That didn't take long.
[OTA]
Coordinates confirmed.
--Good.
--Something's there, sir.
But we aren't certain
it's the enemy base yet.
Like any battle it's a gamble.
But you can't win the pot
without placing a bet first.
Hm. Weapons Officer,
load the missiles and prepare
to launch them on our command.
Loading missiles for launch.
Engine status?
[TOKUGAWA]
Engine online.
We can reach maximum speed
on request, sir.
Bridge to Boatswain. Are the
Wave Motion Shields charged yet?
[ENOMOTO]
Close enough, Captain.
Inertial Control's
back on line, too.
Should be a lot easier to fight
with our feet on the floor.
Attention, all crew.
This is your Captain.
We will now convert to
undersea operations mode,
and engage in a
missile-based counterattack.
All crew to number three
battle stations!
Fire the engine!
[SAOTOME, YABU, YOSHIDA]
Yes, sir!
Blow the main tank
and start raising the bow.
New angle, 35 degrees.
Turn us over!
[KODAI] Those enemy fighters
came from within the auroras.
That means...
[FEMALE SID VOICE 6A]
Warning! Warning!
Sensors detecting
unidentified energy emission.
Effect on ship unknown.
[rapid beeping]
[KODAI gasps]
[YAMAMOTO gasps]
[rapid beeping continues]
[KODAI grunting]
[gasps]
Incredible.
[YAMAMOTO]
Lieutenant Kodai!
I think we found it. This is
definitely the enemy base.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Movement on radar.
Enemy fighters
directly above base.
What's that?
How is the
concealment field offline?
It's functioning properly.
What do we do?
There's no need to panic, Ganz.
A few support planes
are nothing to fear.
[YAMAMOTO]
Come on.
Direct hits to generators.
Concealment field dissipating.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Concealment field offline.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
Something is surfacing
near Yamato sink site.
On main screen!
[GANZ]
What is that? A submarine?
Use your head, you idiot!
That's the Yamato !
[GANZ]
Uh?
[SHULTZ grunts] This is bad.
I already told Lord Desler
that ship was destroyed.
Now what are we supposed to do?
You won't win, Yamato .
Ready Reflecting
Satellite Cannon!
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 6A]
Preparing Reflecting
Satellite Cannon.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 6B]
Calculating trajectory.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 6A]
Selecting satellites for relay.
Number 6. Number 33.
In the end,
this will all be irrelevant.
We will simply sink them again.
My report was merely
a bit early.
Nothing more.
The outcome won't change.
[AIHARA]
Preparing for missile strike.
Bravo 1, immediately
withdraw from the target area.
[KATO]
Easier said than done.
Bravo 1, do you copy?
[KODAI] This is Alpha 1.
Requesting combat support
from the Yamato .
Alpha 1 and 2 have discovered
camouflaged enemy base.
We don't have the payload
to destroy it ourselves.
So that's the real base, huh?
[OKITA]
Good work, Kodai.
[KODAI]
Captain.
[OKITA]
You see anything down there
that resembles a beam weapon?
[KODAI]
Negative, sir, not from here.
They may have hidden it below
the surface or in the sea
to make it harder
to locate, Captain.
[AIHARA]
Searching now.
We can't engage
in a full on assault
until we've got
that threat off our back.
Alpha team, you are to
stay in the proximity
of the enemy base and stand by
to locate the source
of the beam.
How are we supposed to do that?
This base is gigantic.
[OKITA]
Just keep your eyes open.
[KODAI]
I don't see it!
Trust me. You will.
[KATO] Damn it! They've got me
pinned at the wrong target!
[SHINOHARA]
Stop complaining.
That's right.
The cavalry's arrived.
[KATO]
Shinohara! Nemoto!
And don't forget us!
Let 'em have it!
[FIGHTER SQUAD cheering]
[SHINOHARA] They fly like
a bunch of thugs.
Let's go!
[FIGHTER SQUAD]
Roger!
Deploying reflectors on
satellites Number 6 and 33.
[NIIMI]
Got 'em!
Signals to satellites
have been intercepted!
Analyzer, now!
[ANALYZER]
Beginning signal analysis.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Now deploying on satellites
Number 28 and 57.
[ANALYZER]
Relay satellites identified.
Locking on nearest target.
AA interceptor missiles
ready for launch.
[OKITA]
AA interceptor missiles, fire!
You've been lucky so far.
But you won't survive this.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
Energy charging complete.
Reflecting Satellite Cannon.
Fire!
[OKITA]
Well done.
[YAMAMOTO] Alpha 2 to Yamato .
I've spotted beam weapon.
Location is a frozen bay.
Copy that. Transmit the
--coordinates now.
--[YAMAMOTO] Roger.
Prepare to fire main guns
at the enemy beam weapon.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Satellite 57 lost,
shot down from the surface.
[SHULTZ]
Looks like the Yamato
finally figured out
what we're up to.
Prepare the cannon to
fire again, on the double!
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Charging cannon now.
Our beam can
outdistance their missiles.
This time we'll change angles
and fire from
outside their range.
Level the Yamato .
Main guns topside!
Adjusting inertial control.
Reversing the space gyros.
And dropping starboard ballast.
Leveling ship, now!
Leveling complete.
Inspection teams report
all systems are go.
Teams have set Type-3
rounds with timed fuses.
Our target is
the enemy beam weapon.
Load main gun
with Type-3 rounds.
Ranging complete.
Fire!
Countdown to impact.
Ten. Nine. Eight.
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5B]
Charging complete!
[NANBU]
Seven. Six. Five. Four.
Ready to discharge beam!
Fire!
♪
Alpha 1 to the Yamato .
Enemy beam weapon
has been destroyed.
We did it!
We're not finished yet, crew.
Now we will advance
and destroy the enemy base.
Raise the bow by 20 degrees.
Take us into the sky!
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
No signal from
Reflecting Satellite Cannon.
This can't be true.
[sirens blaring]
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
Yamato rapidly approaching!
Quick, sir. It's not safe here!
You have to leave the base!
You want me to retreat?
As long as you survive,
you'll have a chance
to redeem us!
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5C]
All crew to battle stations!
Targets are locked
and ranging complete.
Air-to-surface missiles,
ready to launch!
Open fire, full bore!
Four enemy vessels.
It looks like they're running.
Pursue those ships.
And convert the main guns
to shock cannons.
We will stay here and
cover your escape, Commander.
Please be safe.
Prepare for Geschtam
Navigation! Hurry!
Enemy ship heading
straight for us!
Draw their fire!
[yells]
[PLUTO BASE OPERATOR 5A]
The Destoria is lost!
Geschtam Jump, now!
[MORI]
Enemy appears to have warped.
What matters is the Gamilan
base on Pluto is destroyed.
The days of those
demonic planet bombs
striking the Earth are done.
[KODAI] Alpha 1 to Yamato .
We're headed home.
[DESLER]
Plat has fallen?
Tell me, Hyss,
was I having some sort of
perverse dream earlier today?
I could have sworn I was told
the Teron ship
had been destroyed.
It was no dream, sir,
that's what he said.
So Shultz abandoned his base?
And retreated
in the midst of battle?
Yes, sir, he did.
Remind him retreat
is not a Gamilan concept.
It's "Victory. And if not
victory, then death."
Sir!
Terons, huh?
[OTA] The Yamato
has left Pluto's orbit.
Well, we pulled it off, Kodai.
Yeah. We did.
[KODAI]
That was for you, brother.
Get us back on the fastest
course to Iscandar,
set engines to combat speed one.
[SHIMA]
Course adjusted, Captain.
Combat speed one.
[OKITA] With different emotions
in each of their hearts,
the crew of the Yamato
leave the solar system behind,
entering a galaxy which
human eyes have never seen.
Say a prayer
for those who set sail,
and a solemn goodbye
to those left behind.
Let your feelings be heard.
We leave you, Earth,
but not for long.
We will return!
Next time:
"Farewell to the Solar System."
There are 355 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.