[MISAKI] It's been two months
since the Yamato acquired
the Cosmo Reverse System,
and left planet Iscandar.
And it's been eight months
since we left planet Earth.
[MISAKI] On our journey,
we've lost many friends,
faced many hardships,
and shed many tears.
[MISAKI] But through it all,
we've never lost hope.
That's because we knew
the people of Earth
believed in us,
and were waiting.
Counting on our return.
[MISAKI] The first time we made
this trip across the galaxies,
deep down, I think we
were all pretty scared.
But this time, it's different.
We've proven it's possible.
Now, the Yamato is heading home
on a path we've already cut,
and carrying hope with it.
[sighs]
Uh?
[giggles]
[NIIMI sighs]
Using Balun? What do you mean?
I see. You mean we're
using the subspace gate.
That's right.
You think it still works?
But I thought we shut down
the gates with that blast.
[SHIMA]
For all we know,
different gates could have
different power sources.
The one to our galaxy
might still be running.
That gate would take us
60,000 light-years
in a single warp.
We can access it
with the same controller
we built last time.
Yeah, let's hope.
If this does work,
we can compensate
for all the time we've lost.
[AIHARA]
Chief of Tactical!
I'm picking up
a possible mayday!
And sir... I'm pretty
sure it's Gamilan!
[DITZ]
We're finally back.
[GHADER]
Allied fleet approaching.
It's Minister Talan.
[DITZ] We've been anxiously
awaiting your return.
What about your brother?
[DITZ]
I see...
Despite his flaws,
Desler was the glue
holding this empire together;
keeping the various
factions united to
rebuild will be difficult.
[GHADER]
Indeed.
Hope still remains.
[gasps]
[squawks]
My immediate concern
are the ships rebelling
against your fleet-wide order.
They're refusing to return home.
[DITZ]
I'm well aware.
[DITZ] I've sent someone
I trust to deal with that.
[GOER] All this time,
I have served dutifully,
leading a fleet of
3,000 stranded ships
across the sea of space!
Along the way,
we've had to abandon those
who allied with
the traitor Ditz.
But our 30 greatest
ships remain!
Now. I have braved
the cold, vast expanse
to finally meet you again!
And your loyal soldier Goer
is overjoyed at this chance!
It's the pinnacle of my--
[VELTE groans]
If I may, sir.
Why do you continue to
obsess over that one ship?
[DESLER] Simple. Because
I want what it has.
[gasps]
[DESLER] To use the ship
that drove me to the brink
to power my triumphant return.
Can you imagine
anything more splendid?
The glory of Great Gamilas
shall bring order
and salvation to
all the Universe.
Only I can make it happen.
And realize the dream.
[MALE RECON VOICE 25A]
Looks like the engine went out.
It can't fly.
[MALE MEDIC 25A]
Medic to bridge.
We've located a survivor.
Approaching vessel
now for rescue.
[MORI sighs]
[NANBU]
She's a Gamilan officer, right?
Mori says she knows her,
but are you sure this is safe?
She'll be just fine.
She's proven she can
take care of herself.
Yeah. You're right.
[MORI] Well, well. This
feels familiar, doesn't it?
Though now we've
switched positions.
There's nothing to worry about.
We're going to fix your ship.
So you can get home to Gamilas.
[CELESTRA]
That's not my home.
[MORI]
Hmm?
[CELESTRA] I have no intention
of returning to that planet.
My home has been gone
for a long time.
The people of Jirel
had unique powers.
We all possessed a
natural telepathic ability.
Civilizations from
neighboring worlds feared,
envied, and ultimately
destroyed us.
Mirenel and I would have
been lost, too, but...
I know. But Desler saved you.
I understand how you feel.
But he died in that battle.
You're lying!
I know my lord's still out
there and he needs my help.
He can't die. He can't...
Not without me there...
I'm supposed to be at his side.
Warp complete. We've arrived.
That's Balun?
Or what's left of it.
The planet most likely
couldn't withstand
the gravitational shift
after our attack destroyed
the energy plant at its core.
There's a good deal of debris.
Shima. Careful
with the navigation.
Roger that.
[SHIMA]
Decelerate. Red 20.
[MALE COMM. OFFICER 18B]
We've sighted the Yamato .
[MALE BRIDGE OFFICER 10E] It's
heading for the Geschtam Gate.
[GOER chuckles]
And how are the engineers doing?
[MALE GAMILAN ENGINEER 25A]
Transmitting power to system
satellite, but the energy
drain is immense!
We can't do this
for much longer!
Relax. You only have to
keep it up long enough
to convince the Yamato
to enter the gate.
Those ignorant vermin don't
realize we're leading them
into a trap.
[OTA] We've sighted the
subspace gate to our galaxy.
Detecting no external
damage to structure.
Activate the gate controller.
[ANALYZER] Activating gate
controller, phase one.
It's online!
Yeah, I think this could work.
Radar, what was that?
Sir! Enemy ships!
They must've been
hiding in the debris.
It's an ambush!
Weapons team! Counterattack!
No. Deploy the shields.
We'll head straight through
them. More power to engines.
[SHIMA]
Yes, sir!
[MALE COMM. OFFICER 18B]
Enemy is accelerating!
[MALE BRIDGE OFFICER 10E]
They're attempting to
reach the gate.
You've fallen for it, Yamato .
Maintain fire and chase them in!
[OTA] Point-two light-seconds
until we reach the gate!
[SAIJO]
Torpedoes from the front!
They're headed straight for us!
[MALE BRIDGE OFFICER 10E]
Gamilan torpedoes!
[gasps]
But that doesn't make sense!
What's happening?!
[FLAKEN]
This is what's happening.
[gasps] That's the
dimensional submarine!
[FLAKEN] You ignored Admiral
Ditz's command to return home
at once, and moved
your fleet without orders.
And now I have
the privilege of placing you
under arrest, General Goer.
A military tribunal is
awaiting you on Balerus.
The Captain seems
to be enjoying himself.
[snarls]
It's Ditz's little mongrels!
Fire! Tear that ship apart!
[HEINI]
Captain, we're ready to dive!
[FLAKEN] Not just yet.
Draw their fire a little longer.
[SAIJO] Enemy submarine
has passed our port side.
[SHIMA] Gamilans fighting
against each other?
What's going on here?
Let's not miss this chance!
Yes, sir! To speed two!
[SANADA]
Open gate! Begin Phase Two!
All right, Heini, commence
dimensional dive.
What's wrong?
There's trouble with the engine.
We can't dive now.
Aw, and it was
just getting good.
[YABU]
Engine room to bridge.
We opened the dimensional
emergency valves
as a workaround. We're good!
[MALE COMM. OFFICER 18B] We've
lost dimensional submarine!
Dirty mutts come out
to nip at my heels
and then scurry back
into the shadows!
Why don't you show
yourselves and fight with honor,
you cowards?!
[FLAKEN]
He's calling us cowards.
That's pretty funny coming from
the biggest craven in the fleet.
My thoughts exactly.
[GOER]
Don't you know who I am?!
I've commanded
a whole galactic theater!
I am Garemud Goer!
[FLAKEN]
Mission complete.
Woo-hoo! I'll admit. I was
sweating there for a second.
Our new recruit is proving out.
Who? You mean
that kid from Zaltz?
--[laughs]
--Well done, buddy!
I guess there's a method
to your madness, Captain.
You do always love
to take in the strays.
[giggles]
[FLAKEN chuckles]
We'll return to base.
[HEINI]
Zar Belk!
[ANALYZER]
We are inside subspace corridor.
Forward. Nice and steady!
[KODAI]
We lose our surprise guests?
I can't tell, sir.
It's like last time.
Radar doesn't work
inside the gate.
Ah!
Shima, what is that?!
I have no idea.
I've lost control!
Switch to optical combat mode.
[gasping]
[gasps]
[TACTICAL OFFICERS scream]
Launch hangar to bridge,
we're under attack!
Enemy troops onboard!
Ah!
[SAIJO]
Multiple hostiles on deck two!
[AIHARA]
No response from launch hangar!
[SAIJO] Air pressure
dropping inside ship!
Seal the bulkheads. Kodai!
I'll command
the defense force, sir.
[SAIJO] Alert! All crew,
we are being boarded.
Arm yourselves, and prepare
to engage the invaders.
[MORI] I'm sorry, but this is
the best we can do right now.
You just sit tight, okay?
[KATO] Damn it! [grunts]
There's too many of 'em!
Take this, Gamis!
--[ALL gasp]
--All right!
[ALL]
Huh? Uh.
Oh, crap, run!
[TOYAMA]
That really... hurts...
Toyama? Toyama! Hey!
Toyama! [grunts]
[ENOMOTO]
Iwata! Toyama! Damn it all!
[snarls]
[LECTER] Teams one and two
will take over the engine room.
Then I want you to send any
remaining troops to the bridge.
[CLONE GUARD 23B]
Yes, sir.
[DESLER] Everything appears
to be going smoothly, Talan.
Well done. Then I shall
leave the rest to you.
[VELTE] Ah. My lord.
What are you planning to do?
[DESLER] I'm boarding,
to speak with their Captain.
It's long overdue.
Well, go on, protect him!
[ANALYZER] X.O. Sanada,
I am detecting no life signs
among the enemy troops
that have boarded.
So we're fighting
a deployment of Gamiloids.
I see.
If that's true,
then sir... It's time.
I think you're right.
Let's do it.
Analyzer, come with me.
[SECURITY 25A]
Die, Gamis!
--[rapid gun fire]
--[SECURITY 25 A groans]
[CELESTRA speaks Gamilan]
[KODAI grunts]
[HOSHINA]
Lieutenant!
[KODAI]
You guys okay?
Well, we are now, sir.
[comm beeps]
[AIHARA] Kodai! More
intruders on deck four!
On my way.
[AIHARA] Additional enemy
troops are attacking deck four.
Security, reposition
to engage and eliminate.
--[gunfire]
--[gasps]
[MORI gasps]
[DESLER speaks Gamilan]
Or no. I guess it's safe to
call you "false princess" now.
You're alive.
[CELESTRA]
I knew it. He's safe! He's safe!
[MORI grunts]
[DESLER] Such a special honor
to see you again, my dear.
Now why don't you be
a good little royal hostess
and take me to your captain.
Captain Okita would never
meet with the likes of you.
Strong-willed, just like
the real princess.
My lord!
[DESLER gasps]
[MORI grunts]
[CELESTRA whimpers]
My lord...
[CLONE GUARD 25A]
It's that uppity Jirel woman.
[CLONE GUARD 25B]
She released sympathetic waves
when she saw him.
How disrespectful.
[CLONE GUARD 25A]
That's the problem with Jirels.
[MORI sobs]
[TOKUGAWA]
[KAMO] Come on, Chief!
He can cover you!
Stop shooting!
Use your head!
What if you hit the engine?!
[MORI]
Why? She loved you so much.
Why did you...?
There was no need for this.
There's no need
for our worlds to fight.
We could have
taken care of each other.
We could have chosen love.
But instead...
there's just more pain.
[DESLER]
War, my dear, is necessary.
War makes worlds obey.
War alone can bring
salvation to the universe.
And realize the ultimate,
beautiful dream.
Of the woman I love.
Wait, the what?
[KODAI pants]
Yuki?!
[yelps]
[KODAI]
Yuki! Are you okay?!
Kodai!
[DESLER grunts]
[CLONE GUARD 25B]
Ah! My lord!
Are you all right?
[DESLER grunts]
[CELESTRA]
Stop this, my lord. It must end.
Always, my lord.
Always and forever.
[CLONE GUARDS gasp]
Witchcraft!
No!!
Yu-- Yuki!
[ANALYZER]
Setup complete.
Activate!
[TOKUGAWA]
They're releasing the lock!
They're close
to reaching the Core!
Damn robot soldiers!
[ALL whimper]
[LECTER] A virus! The
mechanical soldiers are failing!
[VELTE growls]
Move!
Ah!
[SANADA] The data we extracted
before made it possible.
We have Alter to thank for this.
This way, sir.
Yuki! Yuki!
Don't shoot them.
[KODAI grunts]
My lord, let's hurry!
Wait, "my lord"?
That's him...?
[LECTER]
Lord Desler has returned.
Prepare to embark.
[VELTE] You fool!
Who ordered you to attack?!
I... I'm sorry, sir.
You're sorry?!
Don't you realize
we're in subspace?
[door hisses]
[DESLER] Meaning normal beam
weapons won't work, correct?
You're okay, sir!
Beams won't.
But what about
the Desler cannon?
[AIHARA]
Enemy ship is falling back!
At 6 o'clock!
[SANADA] They've seen normal
beams won't work in here.
That's a Wave Motion Gun!
[CLONE GUARD 23B]
Charging energy!
Ninety belas until criticality!
[VELTE] Stop, my lord! We can't
use the Desler Canon here!
It's suicidal!
[DESLER]
Do not interfere, Talan.
But, Lord Desler...
Victory at war will never
come to the faint of heart.
[CLONE GUARD 23D]
Target is turning around.
[CLONE GUARD 23B]
Energy charge complete.
[DESLER]
Prepare to fire Desler Cannon.
[DESLER growls]
[CLONE GUARD 23D]
Target locked!
[VELTE]
How are they hitting us?!
[CLONE GUARD 23D]
They're shells, sir!
They're firing
physical cannon shells!
Teron barbarians!
[DESLER] I will bring
peace to all worlds,
in our galaxy and beyond.
I will...
Just as I promised
you back then.
[DESLER]
It's all for you.
[OTA]
We made it through the gate!
We're at the
Milky Way's outer rim!
[CREW groaning]
[KODAI]
Yuki! Wake up! Don't die on me!
Kodai...
Come on, please. Yuki.
We made it.
Just come back to me.