[beeping]
[AIHARA]
Message from Director Todo.
[TODO] So you've already
made it to the outer edge
of the solar system, Admiral.
It may seem like
a giant leap to us.
But on the long road to Iscandar
it's only the first small step.
True enough.
But news of the
Yamato destroying
the enemy's Pluto base has
spread all across the globe.
The planet bomb barrage is over.
You have no idea how
much relief that's brought.
And how much hope.
Just knowing you're headed for
Iscandar helps us keep going.
We can believe there's a way.
So find that way, Admiral.
Retrieve the Cosmo
Reverse System.
All of Earth is behind you.
And the Yamato 's
successful return home.
[AIHARA] The heliopause
is disrupting our transmission.
I'll need five minutes to set up
the long-range
signal boosters, sir.
[OKITA]
Mm.
[ITO]
Oh, you're actually alone.
The XO's gone for once.
More free time?
Well, unless crewmen
are fighting over cards.
There's really not much
for security to do right now.
Hmm. So how are things for you?
[NIIMI]
Not much for me to do either,
at least, until we reach
a new star system.
Huh.
[ITO] I hear you're offering
counseling sessions to the crew.
I could use some
one-on-one therapy myself.
Please, take your
hand off of me.
[ITO]
Once we cross the heliopause,
we won't be able
to talk to Earth.
Wouldn't it be nice if
the captain let everyone
onboard make one last call home?
Wait.
Or would that just
make us all homesick?
I guess I'll have to leave
that to the counselor.
[ITO]
Hmph.
Okay.
Call me if you
need some security.
This is the
updated duty list, huh?
Hey, Kodai.
Huh?
On our way down to Enceladus.
You asked me something
strange, remember?
It's just.
Well are you related
to any aliens?
You were talking
about Sasha, weren't you?
[KODAI]
Huh?
When you asked I had no
idea what you meant by that.
But then I remembered,
you saw her on Mars.
That is why you asked me, right?
[KODAI]
Yeah, she did look like you.
Heh... Sasha Iscandar.
The brave traveler
who gave her life to bring us
the engine's activation core.
And the captain.
Didn't he tell us another
Iscandarian came a year ago?
The one who gave us the plans
for the engine
in the first place?
[MORI]
Yurisha Iscandar.
That was her name.
[SHIMA]
Final calls home, sir?
Huh?
[OKITA]
Hmm...
Beyond the heliopause,
a rise in galactic cosmic rays
and other interference
will severely impede our
communication with Earth.
So we're going to give our
crew the opportunity to speak
to their families now
before we're cut off.
Whoa, seriously?
And we'll be having
a line-crossing ceremony
as we leave our system, too.
[gasps]
A line-crossing?
Isn't that for the equator?
[OKITA]
That's right.
Earth's sailors began the
tradition a long time ago.
Asking for safe passage as
they crossed that great divide.
And now we're going
to do the same.
[HARADA shrieks]
But Ota said everyone wears
costumes to a line-crossing!
He said it's tradition!
He really pranked you good!
[laughs]
You define the word "gullible."
[HARADA growls]
Where are you hiding, Ota?
You'll pay!
For future reference,
don't listen to a word he says.
[jangling metal]
[HARADA]
Hmm?
[gasps]
Relax. I think that
outfit looks good on you.
[giggles]
Thanks.
Crewmen,
because of your fearless
and heroic efforts,
Operation M-2 was
a resounding success.
The Pluto base no longer stands
to rain down terror on Earth.
I want to thank you
all for that.
This ceremony marks our
exit from our solar system.
But the long voyage
has only begun.
When we cross this line,
do not look back.
Look ahead.
Keep your eyes on
the path to Iscandar.
We pray for safety as
we cross the great line!
To the stars!
[ALL]
Ahh...!
Hm? Hey, pal.
Want a swig of the good stuff?
[ANALYZER] I am not
designed for fluid intake.
What a tragic existence.
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh?
Lieutenant Hirata.
You know I was in officer school
with your new wing buddy.
[YAMAMOTO]
I've been meaning to thank you
for agreeing to my transfer.
[HIRATA] If flying gets old,
you can always come back.
[IWATA] The deck crew
definitely got the short straw.
[TOYAMA] Look, I want
to call, same as you.
But ship repairs
are top priority.
We're taking one for the team.
My sweet Akemi!
[ENOMOTO]
Cut the chatter and focus!
[IWATA]
Yes, sir, but, never mind.
Enomoto!
[ENOMOTO]
Hmm?
Hey there, Kodai.
What's up?
You need something?
I mean.
Welcome, sir!
If anyone wants to call home.
I can take a shift.
You sure about that, kid?
Oh! Oh, sorry.
Is that an order, Lieutenant?
Enomoto!
[ENOMOTO laughs]
Well, at least that
means one person
will get to make
a call back home.
[YAMAMOTO]
Make that two.
[ENOMOTO]
Hmm?
Isn't that, uh...?
Uh-huh. That's her.
She took out the Gamilan base
with Lieutenant Kodai.
Nice work, pilot.
It looks like our
Chief of Tactical
is getting a little less
clueless with the ladies.
What was that?
Kishima! Saeki!
You both just
got hitched, right?
Go call your wives.
Really?
[KISHIMA, SAEKI]
Thank you, sir!
Oh, Captain.
Do you need me for something?
Uh, no.
Looks like you're working.
I won't interrupt.
[SATO]
Oh, no!
What's there to smile about?
So naïve.
[MISAKI] Warning: as the Yamato
approaches the heliopause,
some turbulence is expected.
All crew at
line-crossing ceremony,
please locate the
nearest safety hand rails.
Oh, is something wrong, Captain?
All is well.
You need something, sir?
No, no, I'm just
inspecting the ship.
I won't interrupt.
As you were.
[NAV. OFFICER A]
It's almost my turn.
What do I say?
[NAV. OFFICER B]
It's fine.
They just want
to know you're all right.
So who are you talking to?
Just my mom and my brother.
My dad...
[TOKUGAWA]
Hmm...
Yes, that's right.
He gave his life
during the first battle
with the Gamilan fleet.
My kid was just born!
That was great!
We spent the whole
time on the name!
Ha! But it was worth it!
[TOKUGAWA chuckles]
[MORI]
Chief of Engineering, you're up.
Huh? All right!
Lookey! Grandpa!
[TOKUGAWA chuckles]
Aiko! Hello!
But Tasuke, where's
the rest of the family?
[TASUKE]
Sorry, Dad.
[TOKUGAWA]
Hmm?
They all wanted to talk but they
had to stand in line for food.
Tasuke, I'm hungry, can we eat?
Just a little longer, okay?
Food's gotten more
scarce since you left.
So they're trying the
black market, but it's chaos.
They're what?
I warned all of you
to stay away!
We know.
But we had no choice,
it was either that or starve!
[gasps]
Hey. When will you
be coming home?
[TOKUGAWA] A little less
than a year, sweetheart.
Then I'll bring
back presents, okay?
Tasuke, look after your niece.
When we come back
it's going to be up
to your generation to rebuild.
[TASUKE]
Mm.
[TOKUGAWA]
Come on, son.
You have to be strong.
Tasuke, Grandpa's crying!
[SHIMA]
Jiro?
Daisuke!
[SHIMA]
Where's Mom?
[JIRO] She's with
Auntie at the hospital.
She'll be back soon.
Really? Okay.
Well time's short.
And this is going to be my last
message for a long while, okay?
What? You shouldn't say that!
[SHIMA]
Don't be selfish.
Tell Mom I love her.
And that I'll see this
mission all the way through,
just like Dad would have wanted.
And I'll come back to Earth,
no matter what.
Take care of Mom for me, Jiro.
You have to.
[JIRO]
Mm.
[SHIMA]
Time's almost up.
[SAORI]
I'm home.
Mom! Daisuke is calling!
[SAORI]
What? Right now?
Hurry! Mom! Hurry.
Get to the screen!
Just a few more seconds!
Mom!
Daisuke!
[KODAI] So, you already
made your call back home?
[YAMAMOTO]
No.
[KODAI]
You didn't?
[YAMAMOTO]
There's no need.
Trust me.
It's fine.
Are you...?
I mean, were your parents, uh...
Were they settlers on Mars?
My eye color's a dead giveaway.
My grandmother was born on Mars.
When I was born it was chaos.
During the
Second Inner Planet War.
After that, we were forced
to resettle on Earth.
Oh...
So you do still have family?
Not now.
Planet bombs got them.
I had one brother who survived.
Then he died while
shooting them down.
So like I said there's no need.
Same goes for me.
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh?
[KODAI]
Heh.
[NANBU]
Are you kidding me with this?
[TOKIKO]
She's a good match.
Her family owns Morita
Pharmaceuticals.
Your father knows a high-ranking
official with a daughter,
so we could try her.
But I think--
[NANBU]
Mother, stop!
You're in complete denial
of what's going on!
You're the one who
doesn't grasp reality, Son!
You will take over this company!
No, I'm going to
fight for the Earth!
And I'll choose my own wife!
You will come to your senses
and do what I tell you!
[TOKIKO]
Kozo!
Look honey.
Just get home safely.
We'll talk then.
[NANBU]
Forgive me, Mom.
But... I already know
who I want to marry.
Nanbu's done,
let's move to the next one.
There's 28 more
who still need to talk.
[AIHARA]
Right on schedule.
By the way, congratulations.
Huh?
Your request.
It got approved.
[MISAKI]
Thank you so much!
Good luck.
I'll be listening!
That's great!
What a day.
It was really nice of the
captain to let us all call home,
I'll have to tell him,
"Thank you."
Actually, calling
home wasn't his idea.
Who, me?
[ITO] Well I didn't
talk to the captain.
So did you suggest
it to him or not?
Are you interrogating me now?
[ITO]
I didn't see you in the line.
If you're going to take part,
you'd better hurry.
I'm well aware.
Oh and by the way.
Look, you have an admirer.
[MISAKI]
Attention, all crew:
Once the Yamato
crosses the heliopause,
calls to Earth will
no longer be possible.
Anyone wishing to talk...
That guy needs
to learn how to relax.
Hey, you know I don't drink.
[chuckles]
You sure you don't
want to call home?
[KATO] Why, so I can
hear another lecture?
My dad will just tell me to quit
and take over the temple again.
[sighs]
My old man is gone.
He died like so many, in the
first wave of planet bombs.
Honestly, I hated him.
All he ever did was yell.
It's weird, though.
Now I think about him a lot.
And I'd give anything
to hear that yell again.
Oh well.
[YAMAMOTO]
This is a lot of work.
[KODAI]
Well, yeah.
It's a pretty big ship.
Can I ask you something?
[YAMAMOTO]
Huh?
[KODAI] Why didn't you volunteer
for the wing from the start?
Well, I tried to.
But the CAG said no.
Putting me in a cockpit
wasn't happening.
[KODAI]
You mean Kato?
Why not?
[YAMAMOTO] You wouldn't know
it from how he struts around,
but when it comes
to life and death,
let's just say he's sensitive.
Just come back alive!
Sir!
Thank you.
[YAMAMOTO]
My take?
He doesn't want me to die.
Not in combat,
the way my brother did.
Kato and my brother
were thick as thieves.
He took it really hard.
[ENOMOTO clears throat]
Well, I'm sorry to
interrupt the bonding session.
But if you don't mind,
Lieutenant,
we could use some
help on the portside.
Very funny.
[YAMAMOTO giggles]
Yes, sir!
No!
You won't get off that easy!
[laughs]
Look Ota.
I told you not to
let my glass get empty.
And what do we have here?
Please let me go!
[HARADA] You'd better drink too,
Mister, it'll make this easier.
[sighs]
[MISAKI]
Attention, all crew...
Help me!
Hey, come back here!
Huh? Where'd she go?
[HIJIKATA]
You look well.
How's your captain?
Is doctor Sado
taking care of him?
He seems a bit
calmer since Pluto.
That's good.
[MORI] I'm grateful
for you taking care of me
this past year, Admiral.
[HIJIKATA]
Mm. Come back alive.
All right?
Yes, sir.
[knocking]
Come in.
[OKITA]
Can I help you, Chief?
Well, that's my question.
Hard to believe
it's already been a year.
[TOKUGAWA]
Talked to Yamazaki.
He said you dropped
by the engine room.
Well, uh, yes.
I don't suppose you
were looking for this? Hmm?
Tokugawa.
[TOKUGAWA] Do you remember
the first ship we ever crewed?
[OKITA laughs]
Defense Ship Number 36.
She was so tiny they didn't
even give her a proper name.
We were almost too
young to shave.
[OKITA laughs]
And how many brave
young sailors have died
since then while
we just keep hanging on?
Far too many to count.
Truth is... I don't
let myself try.
Lives are more
than just numbers.
As survivors, there's
only one thing to do.
Keep on fighting until we give
the young a reason to hope.
It's the only atonement
for us living this long.
On the backs of all those dead.
[MORI]
Good job on those repairs.
Huh?
[MORI]
I saw you out there.
I didn't have
anything else to do.
Why didn't you
make a call to Earth?
[KODAI]
My family's dead.
It's okay.
It's just the way it is.
Did you talk to yours?
I'm like you.
An orphan.
Oh, sorry.
[MORI]
At least, as far as I know.
You see...
I have no memories of my past.
I can recall this last year
with perfect clarity.
But beyond that there's nothing.
I see.
[MISAKI]
Attention, all crew:
In a few minutes the Yamato
will go beyond the heliopause
and the line-crossing
will be complete.
So let's usher in
this new era in style!
And we're live!
Hello, listeners!
Welcome to Radio Yamato!
I'm Yuria Misaki,
hostess with the most-ess!
We're kicking things off
with a great first song!
An oldie but a goodie,
perfect to wrap up the
line-crossing ceremony!
Farewell, Earth.
We'll see you again soon.
Do you hear me, we'll be back!
[SERIZAWA] Glad to hear
you're performing well.
You're the last real
hope our civilization has.
I'm counting on you,
Lieutenant Niimi.
[OKITA] We sail
on to interstellar space,
an enemy trap on one side,
and on the other,
a furious star.
Its mouth a smoldering pit, and
its arms Hell's crimson flames.
We only have one shot.
Will it be enough
to break through this snare
and complete
our unlikely escape?
Next time: "Wish Upon a Star."
There are 343 days left
before the extinction
of the human race.