♪
[OTA] Speed: 28,000,
altitude: 2,400, Earth-relative.
Exiting Earth's
atmosphere now.
Initializing Space Speed Two.
Do you really think
saving the Earth is possible?
You getting cold feet,
Tactical Officer?
I didn't say that.
Vessel off our starboard bow.
She's a friendly.
[AIHARA] Message received:
"Safe travels.
You're in our prayers."
[OKITA]
Our journey's begun, crewmen.
We'll pass through lunar orbit,
and head for Mars
at cruising speed.
Upon arrival, chief officers
are to report immediately
to the central operations room.
There will be a full
briefing on the warp test.
That is all.
[MALE SPY PILOT 3A] This is the
impact observation team.
A Teron ship has left orbit.
[SHULTZ]
Hmm.
Should we send the fleet
to intercept, sir?
Not yet. First, we'll observe.
They're a technologically
inferior race
who can't even
leave their own star.
What do they plan to do
with one ship?
I'd like to watch and find out.
Crewmen. As you know,
the trip to Iscandar and back
would take 336,000 years
traveling at light speed,
a feat our race up to now has
not come close to achieving.
And yet to save the earth
and our civilization,
we must complete that voyage
within a single year.
Accomplishing this
Herculean task requires us
to circumvent the light barrier,
using what the Iscandarians
call warp navigation.
[SANADA] Warp navigation
generates an artificial wormhole
around us, skipping our ship
through folded space
at an effective speed
far beyond light.
People speculated
about this for ages,
now you're telling me
we have the means to do this?
Theoretically, we can do it.
But if we botch the timing,
we'll create a distortion
in the space-time continuum.
And it's possible
that could trigger
a phase transition
of the entire universe.
Meaning what, exactly?
It means we have to be
very careful with
the Wave Motion Engine,
or else the earth
and reality itself
could be lost.
Are you getting cold
feet now, officer?
I didn't say that.
[OKITA]
That's not all.
I'm Lieutenant Niimi,
Chief of Intelligence.
We've also completed a weapon,
which harnesses the power output
of the Wave Motion Engine.
It takes up most of
the Yamato's bow,
but we felt it was
worth the load.
A weapon? What kind?
Oh, a Dimensional Wave
Motion Explosion Emitter.
We call it the
Wave Motion Gun for short.
The Wave Motion Gun?
So how does it work?
It's complicated.
Basically, it channels
the higher dimensions the Wave
Motion Engine interacts with,
folding them down
these conducting tubes.
Super gravity creates
micro black holes,
which in turn release
Hawking radiation.
Looks to me like you've
turned the entire ship
into one gigantic cannon.
A flawed metaphor,
but close enough.
Afraid you lost me
at higher dimensions.
Captain, now that we're
up and running,
when there's time we'll need
to test fire the gun.
Now pay attention.
We'll use the low gravity
interference zone
beyond Mars to test the warp.
The test will begin
precisely at 0130.
I want everyone on board
suited up, just in case.
Dismissed!
[MORI] Sasha. She's down there
on Mars, isn't she?
She's all alone.
[KODAI] It wasn't in vain.
I'll show you.
We will reach your home world.
You crossed this
great expanse already.
168,000 light-years.
Our minds can't even
comprehend that distance,
and you did it all by yourself.
With that journey, you gave us
the courage and hope to survive.
We won't let that go to waste.
[KODAI] Tactical Division,
all pre-test routines complete.
[YABU]
What do you think, Chief?
Even with plans
from that goddess,
you really think
we can bend space-time?
No idea! But sometimes,
all you can do is try.
Two minutes until warp test.
Confirm our post-warp
coordinates, ensign.
Checked and confirmed.
[SHIMA]
Point S8630, Uranus orbit.
Coordinate axis set.
Increasing speed
from 12 to 33 space-knots.
[OKITATOKUGAWA]
Increase engine output.
[TOKUGAWA]
Raising output from 40 to 99.
Wave Motion Engine's
internal pressure rising.
[OTA]
Speed: 30 space-knots.
Thirty-two. Thirty-three!
[MORI]
One minute until warp test.
[DR. SADO]
Yay-eeeeh!
♪ Off the boat takes,
with smoke in its wake, ♪
♪ and smoky wake makes,
my croaky throat ache! ♪
Oooh. Uh! Ha-ha!
I get he's from a family
of priests and all, but still.
Yeah, I know. The chanting
always creeps me out.
[KATO]
...together we petition,
and with reverent awe,
this we respectfully declare.
[OTA]
Speed: 36 space-knots!
[MORI]
Commencing countdown.
Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven.
Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One.
Warp!
♪
Yeah! Bull's-eye!
[BOTH gasp]
[KODAI]
Where did we come out?
--Jupiter.
--But why?
Hey, Shima!
Navigation. Can you explain?
I don't know
what happened, sir.
The coordinates were right,
but we came out early!
Sensors detected an unknown
obstacle in our path.
The system may have
overridden us to avoid it.
[OTA] The Yamato is caught
in Jupiter's gravity!
We're too close!
We can't even achieve orbit!
[SHIMA]
I can't control the ship!
Stay calm, Lieutenant!
Engine room,
what's going on down there?
[TOKUGAWA] Something's off
with the main engine.
It's not transferring energy.
I'm going to try redirecting
the sub-engines now!
Power is flowing
to the sub-engines.
Stabilizer wings out!
We're falling, Shima!
Yeah, I know!
[MORI]
Something on the radar!
It's 65 megameters ahead of us!
No way that's a ship.
It looks way too big!
On screen and magnify!
[NANBUSANADA]
Switching to infrared.
What is that?
[OTA] I don't know how to
describe it, Captain.
It's like a floating continent!
It's nearly the same
size as Australia!
Shima, I want you
to attempt a soft landing
on that floating continent.
Yes, sir!
[SHIMA grunting]
You've got this, Shima!
--Fire the anchor!
--[OTA] Firing!
[engines powering down]
[inhales, exhales]
[TOKUGAWA] Captain, we've
tracked down the source
of our engine trouble.
The main coolant
system's malfunctioning,
but we can fix that.
Understood.
Begin repairs immediately.
Mr. Kodai. Assemble a team
from the deck crew
and collect samples. I want
to know what we landed on.
Yes, sir!
AU09. You're up.
[ANALYZER]
Do not address me by my number.
I am a free-thinking individual.
[AIHARA, NANBU gasp]
Hold on,
this thing is autonomous?
Yes, AU09 is the Yamato 's
self-directing sub-computer.
[ANALYZER]
Please, call me Analyzer.
[HILDE] Daddy, finish
your assignment soon
and come back home.
I can't wait to see you!
Mom's worried, as usual.
[GANZ]
Commander Shultz.
What is it now, Ganz?
Sir. There's a message
from Larleta
on the floating continent.
[SHULTZ] The one on Zupist,
planet number five?
Yes. And if the message
is to be believed,
that Teron ship we were
watching just landed there.
Ridiculous.
With their crude tech,
they're still crawling through
the inner solar system.
There's more, sir.
It would appear that
the sensors at the outpost
have picked up traces
of a Geschtam Jump.
Impossible! Are you
trying to tell me
that they actually jumped?
[GANZ] I'm just relaying
the message, sir.
[SHULTZ] Mmm. And what about
the floating continents fleet?
[GANZ]
It's a resupply base.
There are only
four ships at present.
[SHULTZ]
That'll be plenty.
Order Deputy Commander
Larleta to destroy them.
[GANZ]
Yes, sir.
[LARLETA]
Understood.
I shall dispatch the
combat fleet immediately, sir.
[meows]
[LARLETA] Teron weapons are mere
pinpricks for these vessels.
Four's overkill,
but I like to indulge.
Can't believe we're out
collecting plants.
It feels like elementary school.
[ENOMOTO]
Stop whining.
[IWATA]
Huh?
[ANALYZER] Temperature and
pressure differ considerably
from native Jupiter environment.
Atmospheric composition:
Methane, 67%.
Carbon dioxide, 21%.
Nitrogen, 6%.
Detecting traces of acetaldehyde
and ethanol, as well.
Alcohol, huh?
I don't feel so good.
[DR. SADO]
Warp sickness! What a drag!
Is that a thing?
Eh, I just coined it!
Seems to resemble a hangover!
Want a little saké
to dull the pain?
Nah. I'll pass.
[ANALYZER] DNA match with
extraterrestrial species
of flora currently spreading
on Earth surface: 99.98%.
[SANADA]
After analyzing the samples,
our best guess is
this environment was imported
from outside our solar system.
Seems the Gamilans
moved this whole continent
to Jupiter to help them
re-engineer the earth.
Like a huge supply nursery.
If that's true,
then they're probably not far--
[MORI]
I'm picking up ships!
Gamilan vessels!
All crew to your
battle stations!
Prepare to fire main guns!
[SHIMA]
Kodai, wait!
We won't be able to route
energy to the weapon systems
until the main engine
is repaired!
The Type-3 rounds
are physical shells,
so we can fire them immediately!
But the Type-3 are
only for short-range!
We can't let them
get that close, sir.
We need the shock cannons!
[SANADA] Captain, we could use
a bypass to launch a few shots
from the shock cannons
while we wait.
[TOKUGAWA] The repairs will be
done in five minutes.
If we can hold out,
we'll have full strength!
We don't have any more
time to wait for repairs.
Connect the bypass and
route power to the main guns.
Load Type-3 artillery
into the secondaries!
[NANBU]
Energy transferred to primaries.
The shock cannons are ready!
Turrets one and two,
aim for the destroyers
approaching port side!
Turret three,
you take that heavy cruiser
circling from aft!
One through three,
targets locked.
Auto-tracking enabled.
Open fire now!
[MORI] Torpedoes
approaching from port!
AA defenses!
[OTA]
All torpedoes downed!
[NANBU]
Enemy ships within Type-3 range!
Secondary guns
may fire when ready!
Fire!
Last destroyer retreating!
[TOKUGAWA]
This is the engine room.
Repairs are complete, Captain.
Activate engine.
Raise the anchor!
[OTA] We're approaching
the continent's edge!
[OTA] Twenty-three megameters
from floating continent, sir!
Kodai. Prepare to fire
the Wave Motion Gun.
We'll use this opportunity
to test our new weapon
on the enemy's base.
We aren't even sure
how powerful that gun is.
Using it on a real target
without knowing the effects?
I think it's too risky, Captain.
Everything's a risk--
we're trying to survive.
If we don't test it now,
we may not get another chance.
All crew, stand by
to open fire.
Turn the ship around,
and point the bow
at the floating continent.
[SANADA] Switching ship
to emergency power
in preparation
for energy redirect.
Chief of Navigation.
Transfer helm
to Chief of Tactical.
Transferring to
Chief of Tactical.
Chief of Tactical
has the helm, sir.
Mori, you detecting
any heat sources?
They're concentrated
in the basin,
at the continent's center.
Fine. Then send
the coordinates. Kodai?
On it, sir. Pointing bow at
the center of the continent.
Open the circuit to
the Wave Motion Gun.
Opening circuit now.
Sealing the emergency vents.
Activating force injector.
Release trigger safety lock.
[KODAI]
Safety lock released.
Confirming force
injector active.
Releasing final safety.
I'm activating
the targeting scope.
Tachyon particle pressure
is rising in chamber.
Eighty-six, 97, 100, 120%.
Floating continent is
23 megameters off the bow
and we're holding steady,
with relative speed of 36.
Bow set. On firing axis.
Correcting for target errors,
plus two degrees.
[rapid beeping]
Wave Motion Gun
safeguards up.
Engage anti-shock
and anti-flare defenses.
[rapid beeping]
[KODAI] Electronic cross-gauge
display brightness 20.
Locking on to target.
[NANBU] Ten seconds to go.
Nine. Eight. Seven. Six.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Fire!
[LARLETA] What is this?
What is that light?
What's happening? No!
This power, it's unbelievable.
This weapon is amazing!
Now we'll be able to fight
the Gamilans toe-to-toe!
Heck, who knows, we may even
have the advantage!
There's no denying its power,
but let's not forget
we were only targeting
the Gamilan base.
Yet the Wave Motion Gun
completely obliterated
the whole continent.
Duly noted, XO.
Our mission is not
to exterminate the enemy.
The Yamato 's weaponry
should be used
solely for the purposes
of self-defense.
[OKITA] A power that could
destroy the universe itself.
Have we attained the
forbidden fire of divinity?
Are we sailing
towards Armageddon?
No, I won't think of that now.
If this is a trial
of human character,
we won't build
our case with words.
Our actions will
speak for themselves.
May our course be true.
[OKITA] The horrific power
of the Wave Motion Gun
has damaged the Yamato herself,
while a mysterious distress
call divides the crew.
On this mission where one wrong
choice could doom Earth,
how should the ship proceed?
Meanwhile, Lieutenant Kodai
finds the traces of a hero
on a frozen satellite,
and offers a requiem
in the vacuum of space.
Next time:
"Gravestone on a Frozen Field."
There are 363 days left
until the extinction
of the human race.