(fireworks exploding)
(crowd cheering)
What a day for a cardfight!
It's hard to believe,
but it's already
that time again.
Now, tell me.
Are you ready to
kick off the start
of the Vanguard
National Championship?
(flares popping)
(crowd screaming)
Before we begin,
let me remind everyone
how the day's
schedule will work.
We start by dividing
the 32 participating teams
into eight blocks,
at which point‐‐
‐Choo‐choo!
‐Huh?
Ultra Rare is comin' through!
(giggling)
What are you doing?
I was just starting my intro.
Back off, onion breath!
Hi, it's so nice
to see all of you again.
It's been too long.
♪
Hey there, a question.
Are you just gonna
tell 'em all the same stuff
you did last time?
Yeah.
That was the plan.
And it's not good to
turn your back onstage.
(gasps, chuckles)
Do you think it's really
necessary for us to explain
how the national
tournament works?
No!
Boo!
‐Told ya.
‐Aww.
We'll let the audience decide.
Do you wanna skip
all the talking
and go straight
to the cardfights?
(cheering)
(sighs)
We're skipping it?
Yeah.
The people have spoken.
I guess you're right.
We don't need to waste time
with the stinking rules!
On with the lottery, let's go!
(cheers)
Don't you dare start!
Huh?
What's the problem?
You can't start till
Kourin gets here!
Seriously, man?
Just sit down.
Oh, that's right.
Kourin isn't feeling well today.
Oh no, what do you mean?
Is she gonna get better?
Oh, lighten up.
My life won't be
the same without her!
She's gonna be fine.
Ultra Rare has a
super‐busy schedule
and Kourin's just
a little tired out.
But Suiko and I are
gonna do our best
to cheer you all on.
You bet your booties we are!
(cheering)
Oh, why'd she have to miss this?
I just need to see her!
That's weird.
Miwa hasn't shown up either.
Hold on, I wouldn't
wanna lose you.
(engine roars)
Wait, Kourin, my darling!
Take me for a ride instead!
I hope those two are okay.
(weeping)
♪
Now, the computer
is finally ready
to choose the pairings
for our elimination round.
So let's check it out!
♪
It's Block C for us.
Looks like we're up
against Jurassic Army again,
as well as Team Spyder
and, um...
Team Asteroid.
It can't be.
No way, they're facing
Ren Suzugamori's team.
Huh?
That's just not fair.
Game over, yo!
Take a close look, guys.
It's not the same team
we fought before.
Ren's team is in Block F.
Huh?
If you take a look at Block A,
you'll see Team Caesar,
and the rest of the big
teams from last time
are spread through
the other groupings.
♪
Well.
Without Ren to stop us,
Block C is ours
for the taking.
‐Big talk, little man.
‐Huh?
Who are you, gingersnaps?
Oh, we're just
one of those teams
you'll be fighting in
the elimination round.
We play for Team Asteroid,
though everyone calls us
the Brilliant Stars.
My name's Kiriya Bidou
and I'm the captain.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
Uh...thank you.
He didn't mean anything
by what he said.
Yeah, sorry, I was
a little meager.
Don't you mean "eager"?
Hm...
You call yourselves
Brill and the Stars.
Which one of you
is Brill, anyway?
He said "Brilliant Stars."
Yeah, Kamui, as in
"twinkle, twinkle"?
That's a way better name.
Isn't it, though?
Huh?
In the depths
of the night sky,
it's the brilliant stars
that shine brightest of all.
When we find ourselves
under cover of darkness...
The cosmos pales
in comparison to us.
See, the biggest stars
of all are here on Earth.
Hey, Morikawa, did you
get a load of this team?
Are you listening?
Hmph.
Well, I've heard enough.
All of their bragging is
making my skin crawl over here!
Argh!
My teammates probably
don't want me to say this,
but we're gonna have no
problem kicking your butts.
After all, you're just the
rejects that couldn't make it
on the real Team Asteroid.
Rejects?
Hm.
I guess I can see how
you would think like that.
Tell me, little man.
Do you have any idea
how many skilled cardfighters
are competing for our spots?
Huh?
I've never really
thought about it before.
Um, maybe somewhere around 30?
Way off.
‐There are 500.
‐What?
No way.
With that many people training
and challenging each other
all the time, the atmosphere
is intense, to say the least.
That's the price we pay.
We fight our hardest
to impress Ren.
And the few people that can
handle the struggle to the top
are given a place on his teams.
This is how the Brilliant
Stars were formed.
♪
So you might want to
reconsider referring to us
as rejects.
♪
We've been looking
everywhere for you, Kiriya.
Hm?
♪
Hm.
Team Q4 again.
I was expecting to see
Kai here with you.
Huh, yeah, well,
we could say the same
for your fearless leader.
What's the matter, did
he get scared and run away?
Don't talk about him like that.
Asaka, he's just a kid.
Whatever.
Hm.
Hm?
Ren's ready to see you now.
Of course.
Well, it was nice to
meet you all, Team Q4.
♪
Especially you, Aichi Sendou.
Yeah.
Hold on, you never told
him your name, did you?
Nope.
But I can't wait to battle him.
Heh, yeah!
Hm.
(knocking)
Leave us, Tetsu.
Sir.
(doors slide open, closed)
So, what did you think
of Aichi Sendou?
We hardly spoke, so
I couldn't gather much.
Really?
But it upsets you, doesn't it?
Hm?
There's no need to pretend.
You can't stand the fact that
I gave the Shadow Paladin deck
to someone else, am I right?
‐Arrgh!
‐(Ren chuckles)
Why?
What did he do to earn
your faith like this?
I saw the way he played
in last year's nationals
and he cost his team their shot.
They lost in the preliminaries
and went home empty‐handed.
So why did you entrust
that deck to a guy like him?
To give you more of
a challenge, of course.
Even if you don't get
to use the Shadow Paladins,
you're capable of taking
him out, aren't you?
Huh?
You know I am.
Succeeding in this task
will show me that
you're finally ready to fill
the last remaining
spot on my team.
It's yours for the taking.
Consider it done.
I swear, I won't
let you down, sir.
♪
Heh‐heh, the stage is
set for my little game.
Now, show me the next step
in the evolution
of your Psyqualia,
Aichi Sendou.
Oh, Kourin's still not here!
Oh, wow, we've got amazing
cardfights in progress
at all our exhibition sites!
Over in Block A, one of our
favorites in this tournament,
Team Caesar, is
currently‐‐oh, whoops.
Looks like they've
already won their matches.
The winner is Kenji Mitsusada,
with two wins and no losses.
Team Caesar has aced
their first opponents.
Next time, let's report
the action while it happens.
Ohh.
Huh?
Team Caesar!
Hey, it's good to see you again.
Are you here to
cheer us on or what?
Yeah, something
like that, I guess.
You sure made short work
of your first match‐up.
Good job.
Thanks, but we've got
a long road ahead
to the tournament final.
Well, Aichi, all set?
Yeah.
So, were you able to
improve your deck since camp?
Yes.
I've got the perfect deck now.
(gasping)
Wow.
You sure are confident.
C Block teams,
please get ready.
Huh?
I repeat, C Block teams,
please get ready.
All right!
It's our turn!
Well, good luck, you guys.
We look forward to
facing off against you
in the final round.
"Good luck"?
Huh?
No one's gonna stop us
from making the finals.
Luck isn't necessary.
Uh...
Bye!
Oh.
♪
There's something
different about him now.
♪
Well, we meet again,
Aichi Sendou.
Yes we do.
It's interesting that you
and I are facing each other
in the first match
of the very first round,
just like last time.
Victory was mine
in our meeting.
But how 'bout now?
Have you gotten any stronger?
That question bores me.
Hm?
Seems like everyone's asking
me the exact same thing
and I'm tired of it.
What?
I think people were expecting me
to be the scared kid I was
in the last tournament.
It looks like I'm gonna have
to make an example out of you
to prove how much I've grown
as a cardfighter since then.
Huh?
Hm.
I'm not gonna hold back,
Ryuudou, so get ready
to feel me at full power.
Believe me,
I'd be disappointed
if you came at me
with anything less.
Now, how 'bout you
show me what you got?
Fate gave us a
shot at a rematch,
so let's not waste it.
(whirring)
♪
Stand up, my...
Vanguard!
♪
Huh?
Fullbau?
He must have
a new deck entirely.
Shadow Paladins?
But why?
He used to take such good care
of those Royal Paladins of his.
♪
(chuckling)
Welcome back, folks.
The action in the preliminaries
is coming fast and furious
here at the Vanguard
National Championship.
Let's take a look at the
battle over in Block C
as Team Jurassic Army
looks to get one game up
on Team Q4.
We've got Q4's Aichi Sendou
versus Gungi Ryuudou
of the Jurassic Army,
and it looks like this
cardfight is really heating up.
♪
Go, Gigarex!
No need to guard.
♪
I check for a Damage Trigger.
Whoa, boy!
With five in the damage zone,
we might be nearing
the end of this game.
Luckily, for Aichi Sendou,
his opponent has no more
units to attack with.
♪
Well, it looks like
that's the end of my turn.
Hm.
He's done a really
impressive job
of withstanding his
adversary's relentless attacks.
Sadly for Ryuudou,
he also has five cards
sitting in the damage zone.
By the looks of it,
this next turn could prove
to be very interesting.
Final turn.
What?
Shazam!
Aichi lays it on the line
with that declaration.
Again?
Why, bro?
♪
(sighing)
I stand and draw.
Spreading its black wings
to cast a shadow
over this battlefield,
I ride...
Phantom Blaster Dragon!
♪
(gasps)
I call Dark Mage, Badhabh Caar.
♪
Hm.
Badhabh Caar's skill.
I call Abyss Freezer.
♪
And now...
Yes, unleash the power, Aichi.
Phantom Blaster
Dragon's counterblast.
Corrupted Charging Lance!
(sounds of struggle)
♪
Sacrificing the rear guard?
A commander has to know
when to make sacrifices
for the win, don't you think?
Yes, of course.
But I never thought
you'd be the type
to use such brutal tactics.
And next, I'm going
to call Blaster Dark
and Witch of Nostrum, Arianrhod!
♪
Now with a boost
from Arianrhod...
fly, Phantom Blaster Dragon.
Finish Deathrex!
♪
Oh, this won't be enough.
I don't guard.
Twin‐drive check.
♪
Good, then I've
still got a chance.
Oh?
But you're already at
five damage, aren't you?
The only possible way for
you to survive this attack
is to draw two Heal
Triggers back to back.
If I must.
This reminds me of our
first battle together.
A lucky draw
saved you last time,
but now, I think your
luck has just run out.
(growls)
Damage Trigger, first check!
♪
Oh, Heal Trigger activated!
Oh, this can't be happening!
No kidding.
♪
What a nightmare!
Someone should wake us up.
Aichi...
You're oh so close.
The pressure's on
to pull a second one.
♪
Uh...
(murmuring)
♪
I'm not defeated yet.
This is only the beginning.
♪
Oh...
The winner, Aichi Sendou!
There you have it.
Team Q4 has prevailed
in the first match
of the opening round.
Hm.
(cheering)
Excellent work, Aichi.
But you've got a long way yet.
Fully embrace that power
and who knows what
you'll be capable of?
(evil chuckle)
Check it out, he just
keeps getting stronger!
I know, but he...
But what?
Hm...
♪
My units were defeated.
You've changed so much
since last time.
Your strength is amazing.
So you finally understand.
I'm not the same person
you met last time.
(chuckling)
♪
Only honorable fighters
deserve a salute.
And that's not you anymore.
Way to get us off
to a good start, bro.
(gasping)
(all gasp)
Not again!
Come on, Aichi.
Wake up.
I've gotten so...
so much stronger.
♪
Where am I?
Oh...huh?
Oh!
Kai?
Wait for me, Kai!
Listen!
I finally did it!
I'm stronger than
I was before!
I'll show you.
(panting)
Why are you leaving?
Huh?
♪
(Aichi screams)
(panting)
♪
Oh good, you're awake.
Emi.
That's it, I...collapsed.
Who's playing now?
Kamui.
You can watch the end of it.
Let's see you stop
Stern Blaukluger's attack!
Stardust Blaster!
♪
Thanks to Kamui Katsuragi's
ferocious attacks,
Jurassic Army is defeated.
There it is.
Team Q4 wins their
first pairing.
Drink up.
Thanks a lot.
(crowd cheers)
Yes, we're off to a great start!
You guys rock!
Looks like Q4's really gonna
make a run of it this time.
Hey, Morikawa,
why don't we...
Huh?
♪
I claim this Kourin
merchandise in the name of love!
♪
(engine roars)
There she is now.
♪
She came back‐‐Kourin!
Outta my way, I can't
see, Kourin‐‐wait!
(thunk)
♪
Kourin's over here...
and she's over there, too.
♪
Kourin!
Hello?
Oh, wow, a private room.
Well, yeah, but you're
allowed to come visit.
Hey, guys, how's it going?
Fine‐‐it's you
we're worried about.
Thanks, but I just
needed a little rest.
I'll be fine for
the next round.
Why am I...
You can't get up so soon,
you've gotta lay down.
But I told you,
I feel great right now.
♪
Hm.
This is bad.
Yeah.
Ever since we got
back from training camp,
he's been passing out
after all his fights.
It happened after his
battle with Team Fragrance,
and again when he fought Kyou.
♪
I don't know why it happens,
but it can't be good.
It's our job to make sure
that Aichi doesn't need
to play another match today.
That means you and I
are gonna have to win
the remaining battles.
‐Got it?
‐Yeah, I got it.
Hm.
♪
There's no time to waste.
Hurry up, Kai.
♪
We can't let Aichi fight
in the condition he's in.
Yeah, he really
seems worn out today.
All right, here's the deal.
You and I are
gonna win our way
out of the preliminary round
for Aichi's sake.
No problem.
We're gonna be the most
fearsome duo out there.
I know you two are
worried about me,
but are you sure it's
okay for me to sit out?
Our next opponents
might be tough.
I picture Team Q4
winning with ease.
We can do it.