♪
Well, gang,
let's get going.
Regionals await!
Yeah.
Alright!
Mm‐hmm.
♪
(meows)
(Shin humming)
♪ We're on our way now ♪
After losing
my temper at Kai,
I ran out on my team leaving
them to fend for themselves.
♪
They lost in the
first round of Nationals
and I wasn't
there for them.
♪
This time I'm gonna do
everything in my power
to makes sure we win.
♪
Listen up.
There's no way
you'll be able to beat me.
Not with that deck
you're using.
Hmm.
♪
Next time I face her,
it'll be different.
I've got to make
sure we win Regionals.
♪
I couldn't beat Tetsu
when we battled each other.
Looking back, it
seems like ages ago.
I used to be happy regardless
of whether I won or lost.
After that battle,
I felt so helpless.
Like I was hopelessly lost,
but Kai helped me
believe in myself again.
♪
You are the one to blame.
With your skills,
you're not gonna beat
anyone on that team...
yet.
Does that mean he thinks
I'll get better?
♪
I am getting stronger.
Losing doesn't feel good,
but I know in the long run,
it's what I need to
develop as a card fighter.
While we were training
with Team Caesar,
I learned so much
about the game.
Now I love it
more than ever.
I'm much more confident
going into this tournament,
and of course,
there's that‐‐
That feeling I get.
Like my cards
are talking to me.
I'm picturing the battle
just like Kai said.
Since camp, every time
I card fight I can feel it.
The cards want me to win
and it's getting more
intense with each game.
Like the cards and I have
a shared vision of victory.
♪
Miwa was impressed with
how much I've improved.
I wonder.
♪
If I keep at it, I know
I can get even stronger
than I am right now.
Then Kai will finally
accept me as an equal.
I can do it.
♪
Though he did say something
kinda weird to me.
That he felt like his cards
were telling him what to do.
Hmm.
♪
(crowd chattering)
Why's everybody
staring at us?
Isn't it obvious?
Team Q4 won the last
Regional qualifiers
so now, we're
a big deal, bro.
Or rather, now
we're a big target.
Oh.
That's it.
Take a look around.
Everyone here wants
a piece of you guys.
(snickering)
Hey, Gouki.
Oh, no!
I forgot all about
Team Handsome.
Which means that
somewhere around here‐‐
(giggling)
(screams)
Kamui, yah!
♪
You can't avoid me, Kamui!
(giggles)
Told ya!
Why can't you
just leave me alone?
You're too cute
to leave alone.
Isn't she a firecracker?
(laughing)
Well, it's sure nice to see
you guys haven't changed much.
Yeah, well, looks
can be deceiving.
If you think you're
gonna beat us again,
you've got
another think coming.
In order to
defeat you guys,
every member
of Team Handsome
has gone through a strict,
super special training regimen.
♪
So underestimating
any of us
will be the last
mistake you ever make.
Well since
you mention it,
our team also
underwent some training.
In fact, I wouldn't
be surprised
if all the other teams
here had done the same.
Really?
I think you've
got a point.
Yeah, I bet they have.
Take a good look, Kamui.
See? I've changed
a lot, haven't I?
Not really.
What do you mean,
"not really"?
I'm way stronger than the
last time, and you know it!
You're supposed to notice
these kinds of things
about the girl you love!
Haven't I been clear?
I don't love you!
Why does your beautiful
mouth tell filthy lies?
(chuckles)
What are you looking at?
Huh?
He belongs to Nagisa,
and don't you forget it.
She can keep him
for all I care.
Listen up, guys,
we didn't appreciate
missing out on Nationals,
so we're totally
gonna beat you this time.
We're not gonna lose to you.
We've still got unfinished
business with Team Asteroid.
Is that so?
Yeah.
♪
Team Q4.
Alright ladies
and gentlemen,
the Vanguard regional
qualifying tournament
is about to start.
This time around, we've
got 16 teams competing,
but only one of them
will have what it takes
to move on to the
national tournament.
All of your training
and hard work
comes down to
these next few battles.
Hey, Aichi!
We're here to
cheer you guys on!
You better not lose
or we'll look silly!
We already do.
Hang in there.
Morikawa, how dare you
make Emi embarrass herself!
Hmm?
Huh, huh?
(crowd chattering)
♪
And now, we're
proud to present
the Vanguard
super group Ultra‐Rare
with their new song.
This is the‐‐
A new song?
"Stand Up Dream".
I love you!
♪ (indistinct lyrics) ♪
♪ You spill on your face ♪
♪ Just a feeling more ♪
♪ Far from any league ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Don't hold
anything back ♪
♪ You just might ♪
♪
♪ Even if you're
making fun of yourself ♪
♪ I can see the fire
burning in your eyes ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ And you'll be flying
again as sun in the sky ♪
♪ Why don't you
stand up and act ♪
♪ Only if you wish
to touch the sky ♪
Yeah!
‐Are you okay?
Look up here!
I think next time we should
just leave Morikawa at home.
(chuckling nervously)
(groans)
♪ Only a sunny sky for you ♪
♪ Good things come in two ♪
♪
(crowd cheers)
And that was Ultra‐Rare
with "Stand Up Dream".
Let's give them a big round
of applause, everyone.
We love you!
Encore, encore!
I wonder if he knows
how annoying he is.
I kinda doubt it.
Well, it's time.
Now, let's imagine.
Let's play...
‐Vanguard!
That was so fun.
Hey, Suiko, I thought
we were finished
with this ridiculous
pop star nonsense.
I never told you that.
Besides, we haven't found
what we're looking for yet.
Yeah, that's right.
While we're here, we might as
well watch some card fights.
Yeah!
I just don't understand
why we have to come out
to this silly
regional tournament.
Besides, he's not
who we're looking for.
But there is someone
else to watch here.
Huh?
That girl?
Exactly.
She might just be the one.
You really think
she has that ability?
♪
Wow, so it's
a girl this time?
♪
I don't see anything
special about her.
♪
We're finally ready
to begin the battles
here at the Vanguard
regional tournament.
I've got more energy than I
know what to do with right now,
and that's cause I've been
drinking coffee all morning.
You know me as MC Miya,
and would you like
to introduce yourself?
You'll remember
me from Vanguard TV
and my delightful
color commentary
at the national tournament,
but I love card fighting
so much, I'm back again.
The one and only Dr. O.
Our first match
features Team Handsome.
An impressive
group that suffered
a heartbreaking defeat in
the last regional tournament.
Hey, Kamui!
Just watch,
I'm gonna win!
(snickers)
Without further ado,
let's play Vanguard!
♪
Ready?
Let's start.
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
♪
Feels like we were
just at Regionals.
Yeah, let's do our best
to win this one too.
Right.
With the mane of courage
and the roar of justice,
Nagisa, the Great,
rides Lion Heat!
(roars)
So she's Nagisa,
the Great, now?
Oh, man.
You can't stop
the power of love!
Boosted by Shining Lady,
Lion Heat attacks.
♪
(roaring, grunts)
What an ugly loss.
Winner of the first match.
Team Handsome's
Nagisa Daimonji!
Hey, Kamui!
Your love helped me
win that battle.
Oh, boy!
(chuckles)
♪
Using Basskirk's soul blast.
Pirates, return to battle
in the name of the Demon King.
I call two
Commodore Bluebloods
and two Dandy Guy Ramarios
to the rear guard circle.
(shuddering)
How do you like my ultimate
resurrection technique?
(gasps)
(shouts)
♪
The winner of this match
is Gouki Daimonji!
What a quick victory
for Team Handsome!
As former contenders
at the national level,
I think they've just
sent everyone a message.
The future is handsome.
They weren't kidding.
They really have
gotten stronger.
Yeah, their play in both
games was near perfect.
I guess now we know
who we're gonna be up
against in the final round,
and it's not gonna be easy.
Don't worry.
‐Huh?
We'll beat them,
no problem.
Sorry, did I say
something strange?
No.
You got it, bro.
Let's do this!
I've never heard
Aichi say something
with that much
confidence before.
♪
(singing in Japanese)
We're already seeing
a lot of intense battles
here in the first round.
With all of our teams determined
to keep their eye on the prize!
But there's no telling which
two will make it to the finals.
A few first‐timers
have done a good job
of upsetting the hopes
of regional veterans.
The world of Vanguard fights
is very unpredictable.
One day, you're
the cat's pajamas
and next you know,
you're slipping on bananas.
That's what makes
card fighting so thrilling.
Are you excited, Doctor?
You bet your
sweet patootie, I am.
By the sound of it,
we'll have our work cut out
for us in the first round.
That may be so, but I'm not
gonna let these other teams win.
It doesn't matter
who we're up against.
I won't lose.
I'm just getting one last look
at my deck before the fight.
♪
I heard it.
The cards said...
"Hey, use me if
you want to win.
I can help you."
♪
Huh? What's up?
Kai was watching me
look through my deck.
Normally, he ignores
everything I do.
Like it bothers him
just to be nearby.
Is he finally starting
to pay attention to me?
♪
I've got to keep
getting stronger.
We're nearing the end
of the first round
and what an amazing number
of upsets we've seen.
The new teams
are really putting
our veterans
through the gauntlet.
Oh, and how!
Our first match
is coming up next.
That means we'll need
to decide on turn order.
Who'll start us off?
♪
You want to go first?
Well, if it's all right
with the rest of you.
I have this feeling right now,
like I know I can win.
♪
Is that all right?
Yeah, for sure.
You're normally super shy,
but now all of a sudden,
you've got tons of confidence.
It's pretty inspiring!
Bro, get out there
and kick some butt!
Guys, you agree?
Mm‐hmm.
All of our training has
really had an effect on him.
I don't mind
if you go first.
Should be interesting.
Well, you heard them, Aichi.
This is your
big opportunity.
Right!
Then that just leaves the
second and third matches.
I really want to fight!
Is that okay?
Yeah.
I'd rather sit back
and watch anyway.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You guys can win
this round without me.
Trying to look
cool again, huh?
Well, save me
for the third battle.
Guess that makes me second.
Better be careful, Kai,
or you might not
get a chance to play
in this tournament at all.
You say that like
it's a bad thing.
Could you possibly be
more full of yourself?
Is he stronger or
is it something else?
If Kai's offering to sit out,
it must be because
he trusts me
to get the win we need.
This is it!
He's finally
starting to see
I'm not as weak
as I was before.
We've got this,
right, Kamui?
Misaki?
‐Hmm.
‐You better believe it!
And now it's the moment
we've all been waiting for.
The next matchup
features the champions
from the last regional
tournament: Team Q4.
Alright!
It's finally time.
Q4 rules!
This is gonna be great!
Aichi!
C'mon, Kamui,
you're the greatest!
Q4, yo!
And facing off against
Team Quadrifoglio:
Team Fragrance.
This will be their
debut at Regionals,
but from what
I've heard,
they've dominated
their shop tournament
and are focused on making
the finals here today.
Both groups are powerful.
Which will win?
This is going
to be classic.
Team Q4 defeated in
the very first round.
Say what?
You must be completely
out of your mind
saying something
that brownless!
Groundless.
Alright,
let's calm down.
(grunts)
Hey, I can smell
that from over here.
What is that?
It's lavender.
Yes, in our line of work,
it's a well known fact
that lavender has a calming
effect on the nerves.
The three of us
are perfumers.
You mean performers?
Perfumers.
Explains the
spray bottle.
And we all have
expertly trained noses.
Able to analyze and
reproduce any aroma.
Bet you didn't know
that every person
has their own unique scent.
And a person's scent changes
based on their emotions,
so if you're scared
or angry, we'll smell it.
No way.
Way!
You won't be able
to hide your feelings
and we'll use
that against you.
If we smell fear,
it's time to attack.
If we detect confidence,
we'll defend.
Now do you see how
hopeless your chances are?
We are gonna beat you.
Man, what is
with these guys?
‐They‐‐
‐Oh, my!
I'm smelling
fear already!
That's my deodorant.
Well, you may be skilled...
‐Hmm?
But we don't need
a gimmick to win.
What?
Nice one, bro.
You sure showed them.
♪
Aichi is in
the zone today!
What did you expect?
He's my student after all.
Go get 'em, Aichi!
And Kamui!
Q4, yo!
Can't leave her out!
Go Misaki!
♪
I smell it.
Hmm?
You're nervous right now.
How can you win if you
don't believe in yourself?
(growls)
♪
Thought he could
make a fool out of me.
♪
‐Stand up, vanguard!
The Vanguard
regional tournament.
It's finally back!
I don't mind letting
you guys compete here.
My talents are
wasted at this level.
‐You never change.
‐Oh, really?
I didn't used to make
wicked awesome banners.
Help me hold
this thing up.
Fine!
Which side
is the front?
Next time,
"Dangerous Scent".
Thanks for your
support, everyone.
My winning image is
coming in loud and clear.
You guys are gonna make it to
the final match, no problem.
Hold on a sec, this
person looks familiar.