Team Asteroid versus Team Q4!
The third and final match.
After the second turn,
we've got Team Q4
at 3 damage with
Asteroid untouched.
Aichi better have
something big planned for us.
Hopefully, otherwise this
card fight is as good as over.
Indeed.
♪
Here goes.
I activate Barcgal's skill
and superior call
Future Knight Llew.
♪
Counterblast.
Llew, Barcgal, and
Flogal move to the soul.
Hm.
♪
Now stand up, my avatar.
Superior ride Blaster Blade.
♪
Hm.
Oh, I get it.
He took all that damage
so he could superior ride
and still have
enough left over to...
Blaster Blade's counterblast.
♪
...use this ability.
(grunts)
It's time for your
Prisoner Beast to retire.
♪
Hm.
Everything I've
learned about Vanguard,
I'll need to use it all
if I'm gonna win this match.
♪
I call Gordon and Wingal.
Hm.
With a boost from Wingal,
my blaster blade
attacks your Vanguard.
(grunts)
I check for a drive trigger.
Damage trigger check.
I've activated
a stand trigger.
That's 5,000 power
to Prisoner Beast.
Succubus stands up.
♪
Gordon's attack
isn't strong enough
to damage that
Prisoner Beast.
Fine.
Then Gordon, take his
succubus off the field.
♪
(battle cry)
(shrieks)
If Aichi can limit
Tetsu's attacking capacity,
it'll be easier to make
it to his next turn.
And then he should be
able to set himself up
to deal the finishing blow.
I ride Werwolf Sieger.
♪
(snarling)
And I call Blue Dust.
♪
With support from
Nightmare Baby,
he attacks you.
Thanks to
Nightmare Baby's skill,
another 4,000 points
is added to his power.
(grunts)
I'm activating
Blue Dust's ability.
Soul charge.
He's really building that up.
He has to be careful because
the Dark Irregulars deck
can do a lot of nasty things
using the power in the soul.
Werwolf Sieger
attacks your Vanguard.
(roars)
Gordon, I need your
Especial Intercept.
♪
(snarling)
I check for a drive trigger
and end my turn.
Look at the
difference in damage.
Does Aichi even
stand a chance?
I need to hit him with
everything I've got.
Enter the fray,
your paladins await.
I ride King of
Knights Alfred.
♪
Alfred gains strength with Royal
Paladins in the rear‐guard.
by considering
the situation.
♪
I call...
Gigantic Charger.
With his skill, I superior
call Future Knight Llew.
♪
And I call these two.
I need your help
now more than ever.
I need you to lend your
strength to the king.
♪
(snarling)
Impressive.
Gigantic Charger attacks.
With the boost from Llew,
he's after your Vanguard.
♪
I defend with
Hades Puppet Master.
Next I'm attacking with Alfred.
(whinnying)
♪
Now I'm checking
the Twin Drive.
First check.
And the second check.
Heal trigger active.
That's 5,000
power to Gallatin.
I also recover one damage.
♪
Now feel the power of
my sacred great sword,
Divine Punishment.
Hyah!
(grunts)
Damage check.
Gallatin, with
Marron's support,
attacks you.
♪
(grunts)
Damage trigger check.
And just when you thought
you'd seen everything,
Team Q4 ties up the damage
rates with Team Asteroid.
Looks like Aichi could
be setting himself up
for the best come
from behind victory ever!
Watching you play,
it's pretty obvious
you know what you're
doing on the battlefield.
But still, you lack
the experience required
to defeat someone
at my level.
I draw.
Crawling up
from the Underworld
to unleash
his evil power,
I ride Demon
World Marquis Amon.
♪
(groans)
I use his skill.
Utilizing the
power of darkness,
Amon receives an additional
1,000 attack power
for each card in the soul.
I call Alluring Succubus
and use her skill
to soul charge.
He's actually
adding another card?
♪
Finally, we're seeing the true
cunning of the Dark Irregulars
as he turns the
soul into strength.
Oh my!
Yes, Tetsu commands the units
of darkness within his soul.
That's why everyone
calls him The General.
♪
With Nightmare Baby's support,
Blue Dust attacks.
♪
Elaine will guard that.
Demon World Marquis Amon,
crush this kid with support
from Alluring Succubus.
♪
Twin Drive.
First check.
Second check.
You got a critical trigger?
I'm giving the 5,000 power bonus
and critical effect to Amon.
♪
(gasps)
What should I do?
How can I possibly compete
with someone this strong?
♪
Picture it.
Imagine you're as powerful
as the warrior on that card.
That's right.
I just need to picture myself
being stronger than I am.
Imagine it.
♪
My friends.
That's right.
I haven't reached
full strength yet.
I draw.
♪
Here I go.
Sacred Dragon, bring your
judgment to this battlefield.
I ride Soul Saver Dragon.
♪
Activating my soul blast.
My Vanguard's ultimate move.
Holy Charging Roar!
♪
That's 5,000 power to three
of my rear‐guard units.
This is the most
powerful attack
that I can manage right now.
Paladins, we ride.
It's about to get good!
Can Aichi still win this?
I don't know, but at
least with that soul blast
he's got a fighting chance.
With support from
Marron, Gallatin attacks.
♪
Damage trigger check.
Stand trigger activated.
I'm giving the
5,000 power to Amon
and Blue Dust will
stand up once more.
You're gonna
need more than that.
♪
Soul Saver Dragon attacks
with support from Wingal.
♪
The March Rabbit
of Nightmareland
blocks your attempt.
Agh!
This can't be.
Aichi finally
got some momentum
and that guy stopped
his best attack?
Kamui!
(grunts)
What gives?
Why'd you have
to hit me so hard?
That was for running
from your teammates.
Now your friend is out
there giving his all.
How do you know I ran away?
Huh?
Emi's here?
And Goki?
Aichi's stuck in the
toughest fight of his life
because you deserted
your friends.
Huh?
We had a little
talk with the people
from Team Caesar.
They told us what
Aichi's got planned.
They said he wants
to fight alongside you
in the tournament
finals next week.
That's why he's trying to
win the elimination round,
so you can be part
of the team again.
Don't cry.
Gigantic Charger attacking
with support from Llew.
(explosion)
Aichi.
With that, our teams are
now tied at 5 damage each.
Hm.
How could you
abandon your teammates
when they needed you most?
You're not the same
Kamui I fell in love with.
I guess being on this team
doesn't mean anything to you,
does it?
Hm.
Unfortunately
for Aichi Sendou,
his opponent is
still standing.
Indeed, that boy just put
on an excellent display
of Royal Paladin
battle tactics,
but it looks like
it wasn't enough.
I'm sure he must be really
feeling the pressure now.
When things get rough,
you stick by your teammates,
especially when
they're your friends.
♪
Kamui, I'm sure if Aichi heard
you cheering for him right now,
it would give him the
hope he needs to win.
Hm.
♪
Your Royal Paladins
are impressive
with that Soul Saver
Dragon leading them,
but I hate to tell
you the bad news.
You're going down.
I draw.
It's time for me to teach
you an important lesson.
A team is only as strong
as its weakest link.
The wings of destruction are
echoing through the night.
Stil Vampir.
♪
Soul charge.
Raising Stil Vampir's
power by 2,000,
and I call Werwolf Sieger.
My Vanguard has an ability
that might interest you.
Counterblast and soul blast.
♪
Stil Vampir
replaces your Vanguard
with Future Knight Llew.
♪
(gasps)
Oh no.
Is he joking?
I wish.
No way.
♪
This just can't be.
What about Soul Saver Dragon?
Witness the power
of the Stil Vampir.
For this turn, I
replace your Vanguard
with a rear‐guard
of my choosing,
and I chose the weakest one.
♪
Your enthusiasm for
the game is impressive,
but you've still
got a lot to learn
before you're ready to
stand up to the challenge
of defeating a
Team Asteroid player.
Future Knight Llew,
the warrior boy
who dreams of
becoming a real knight.
That's the Vanguard
you should be using,
considering how puny
you really are.
♪
(growls)
Aichi!
♪
You can do it, bro,
just hang in there!
♪
You're still here?
Hm.
♪
I'll never give up.
He turned me into
Llew for this turn only,
so if I can survive
until next turn
I get my Soul Saver Dragon back.
All I need is one more
attack to win this game.
Thanks, Kamui,
for giving me strength.
Werwolf Sieger, attack.
♪
(shouts)
Epona will guard that.
♪
My succubus gives me
the boost I need.
(grunts)
♪
I guard with Iseult.
Llew is a Grade 0.
That means I can't
guard him with any units
that are above Grade 0.
(Tetsu chuckles)
With Soul Saver Dragon, you
would have a lot more options.
You probably could
have stopped my attacks,
but not with that pitiful
boy in the Vanguard circle.
It's like I said, Aichi,
a team is only as strong
as its weakest link
and Llew is the weak
link on your team.
He's about to crush his
opponent with this attack.
The way Tetsu is
commanding his units
is almost as though he wants to
eradicate all hope of recovery
before landing that
final destructive blow.
Is this why his Asteroid
teammates refer to him
as The General?
♪
Hm.
Twin Drive.
♪
Hm!
(barks)
(laughs)
(shouts)
(whimpers)
♪
I'm sorry, bro.
There it is!
Team Asteroid has
defeated Team Q4,
and in doing so have
secured the three wins
they need to move on
to next week's finals.
(cheering)
We didn't get to
face off today, Kai,
but just you wait.
(cheering)
(applause)
At last, it's Block
A's final card fight.
Team Jurassic Army
versus Team Muscle Brain.
In the first match,
it's Gunji Ryuudou
versus Kicking Shoe.
♪
The heated Block A fights
have all been completed.
The final results
for Block A teams are...
Here!
♪
Hey, look.
Three teams are tied with
one win and two losses?
Huh?
Just two of these teams
are moving on to the finals.
Team Asteroid was the only
one to secure a spot next week.
How will they
decide a runner‐up?
So then Team Q4 still
has a chance to make it?
Hey, everybody,
Ultra‐Rare here!
Looks like the final
scores for A Block
are all lined up
and ready to go.
Since three teams are tied,
we're gonna have to take a
closer look at the outcomes
to determine second place.
Let's show you
the final records.
First, Q4.
♪
Here's how it works.
In calculating
the total scores,
we add a point
for every game won
and take one away
for every game lost.
The team with the
highest number of points
will go to the finals.
Now check out the results!
(giggles)
♪
Hm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the team moving on
to the finals next week
will be none other
than Jurassic Army.
(cheering)
♪
(clapping)
Well, we did our best, right?
I have to finish some
paperwork before we can leave.
Wait here, okay?
Listen, guys.
This is...
It's my...
Oh, there you are, Kai.
Huh?
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Ever since you ran
away from Team Asteroid.
It's been a long, long time.
It's hard to
believe you wound up
tied to a bunch of weaklings.
You can't possibly enjoy
playing with these people,
so why don't you just
find something better?
With the amount of
amazing players you know,
I was sure you'd
form your own team.
Maybe you're just hoping to
be invited back to Asteroid.
Is that it?
The team I'm on doesn't matter.
As long as I don't
have to play for you.
Ooh, kitty's got claws.
Kai, wait.
All you had to do
was win one match.
One win from you
would have changed
the way the scores
were calculated
and you would have been
the team moving forward.
Your friend Kai, he would
have made it to the finals
with a chance to
fight against me.
Ha, it's your fault.
Now how does it feel?
That's enough out of you.
It's okay, Misaki.
I don't like to hear it,
but it's true.
♪
(laughs)
There now, that must have
taken quite a load off.
So why are you
playing on this team
if you're just
gonna bring them down?
(laughs)
Where's Kyou?
He's back at headquarters
to start his retraining.
He got the only
loss of the day.
As far as the other two
Asteroid teams are concerned,
there wasn't a single defeat
in any of their pairings.
We're all going
to the finals.
Once we win the tournament
for the second year in a row,
people will finally realize
the strength of Asteroid.
Looks like we're a
force to be reckoned with.
Watch us in
the finals, Kai,
and you'll see
what you're missing.
♪
Kai.
He could tell
just by looking at me.
And we all know who the
weakest link is going to be.
I don't mind.
♪
Oh.
Aichi!
♪
Come on, bro,
snap out of it!
It's all my fault
the team lost.
Because I'm so weak,
I don't belong with Q4.
I'm not fit to be on
the same team as Kai.
♪
I can't believe it.
Team Q4 lost because of me.
That's right, you're
not good enough for them.
It's like having a turtle
on a team of rabbits.
You'll never catch up.
Shut your mouth!
Nobody calls my bro a turtle.
How careless of me.
I guess there aren't any
rabbits on your team at all.
Next time,
Blaster of Darkness.
Picture it, Team Asteroid
hunting down the competition.
Run, little rabbits,
from our fangs.