♪
Take this.
I want you to have it.
Huh?
♪
Listen up, you can do it.
Picture yourself
big and strong
like the warrior
on that card.
Mm.
You've got to
believe in yourself,
that way nobody can ever
stop you from becoming
the stronger person
you want to be.
You think I'll get stronger?
♪
Hmm?
It's an odd request,
using my table.
♪
But I'm not about to
say no to a friend.
Knock yourself out.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Huh?
Hmm.
♪
I can picture it.
I've finally obtained
the strength I require
to defeat that power.
♪
(birds chirping)
Blaster Dark.
I can always count on you
to get me through my fights.
My dependable avatar.
(gasping)
Hello?
Who said that?
♪
Hmm, come on, Aichi.
I know you heard it.
And what exactly
are you doing here?
We didn't invite
you to the shop.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm just waiting for
a friend to come by.
I don't think so.
If you're gonna stand around,
you can do it
out in the mall.
Is this how PSY Shop
treats its customers?
Anyway, miss, could you
please grab me a drink?
I am not the maid.
You are if you want
to keep my business.
(groans)
Here's your coffee.
(sniffs)
Ah, this garbage is
the best you've got?
(grunts)
♪
Who does he think he is
criticizing my coffee?
Now, now.
Hey, how about we close up
the store early today?
He says he's meeting someone,
but I don't want to see
any of his friends.
Oh?
Well, I wouldn't mind if
that boy came by to visit us.
Huh?
You know who
he's waiting for?
He's the only
one it could be.
Though, it's pretty unlikely
that he'll actually get here.
What do you mean?
Well, he won't make it
if Kourin has
anything to say about it.
Hold on, she was just‐‐
Now that you mention it,
she's been out
since this morning.
♪
That voice.
I hear it calling me.
Huh?
Kourin, what...
(gasps)
(engine starts)
You're coming with me,
Aichi Sendou.
(gasps)
(footsteps)
You're becoming
too predictable.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
What do you want?
This isn't an easy
question to ask, all right,
but you've got to do
something about Aichi.
Kai, we need your help.
You must have noticed
he's been acting really
strange these days.
None of us are blaming you,
but it's gotten a lot
worse since you left.
Aichi, I'm sorry, but I'm
not going to fight you.
Huh?
It's been a nightmare.
He's like a different person.
♪
Come on!
If you can beat him,
maybe he'll go back
to the way he was!
You think I don't know that?
‐Huh?
‐Hmm.
I'm gonna take care of
this little problem of ours
once and for all.
The man of the hour is here.
Hmm?
(engine putters)
♪
(sighs)
Hey, Kai.
Here, go on.
Uh, sure.
♪
Got that new deck with you?
Uh...
I challenge you to a fight.
Really?
Last time, you said you
didn't want to battle me.
Yeah, things have changed.
Then does this mean
you've finally recognized
how strong I've gotten?
No.
You've gotten weaker.
That's rough.
Battle me and you'll
see for yourself.
I see.
You still think I'm
the player I used to be.
Well, if that's
the case then,
I'll have to prove to you
how powerful I really am.
(worried sighs)
♪
It's in your hands.
You can't fail.
Pretty hard to admit that
I'm stronger than you.
Huh, Kai?
Why do we have to watch
from way back here?
Uh, this battle is
between the two of them.
I think it's best if we
give them a lot of space.
And, trust me,
the battlefield can get
pretty intense at times.
Hmm.
Having us out there
would just be distracting.
Okay.
♪
‐Now stand up, the...
‐Now stand up‐‐
‐Vanguard!
(whooshing)
Whoa!
I didn't know that was
a motion figure system.
I know you can
pull this off, Kai.
Good luck.
Go, Fullbau!
Barcgal.
♪
You're kidding.
That deck.
‐Huh?
‐Yeah.
He's gonna battle him
using the Royal Paladin deck,
the same one Aichi abandoned.
I get it.
A cute trick.
You may think
this deck is weak,
but I'm gonna show you how
wrong you are to doubt it.
There's no way you'll
beat the Shadow Paladins.
I draw.
I ride Blaster Javelin.
♪
Activating Fullbau's skill
to search for my avatar.
Meet Blaster Dark.
So you've really given
up on Blaster Blade?
♪
Then I've got no choice
but to hit you with
everything I've got.
I won't make the
same mistake twice.
Four years ago, my parents
went away on a trip,
and never came back.
Losing them didn't just hurt,
it shattered my
entire life to pieces.
Everything changed after that.
I was too young
to fend for myself,
so my uncle took me in.
I moved away from this town
and left everything behind.
It was a fresh start.
♪
And then I met him.
Huh?
(sighs)
♪
(footsteps)
This is the guy?
That lazy sack of bones
on the ground here
is the new Vanguard
fighter from your class?
That's right.
What's your name?
It's Ren, you know.
Not you, dummy, that guy.
That guy?
No, they wrote his
name on the board,
and it was way
longer than "that guy."
Remind me to never
ask you anything again.
New guy, what's
your name, huh?
You don't need
to know my name.
‐What?
‐I'm guessing you woke me up
because you and I
have business, right?
Hmm, you certainly don't
beat around the bush.
‐Stand up, the Vanguard.
Wow, cool!
The Vanguard.
♪
Is that it, Tetsu?
‐Well...
‐It's my turn.
Now I ride Dragonic Overlord.
Burn this world to ashes!
Eternal flame!
Hey.
Looks like I lost.
Hm, you're not so tough.
Getting pushed around
by the new kid?
Be quiet.
So, what do you
think of this guy?
I figure he could
fill the final spot.
Works for me.
Hmm?
You hear that?
You're gonna be a
member of Asteroid.
What's Asteroid?
It's our card fighting team.
Though we only started
a little while ago,
so it's just me
and Ren right now.
Have you heard of the
Vanguard Championships?
It's a team battle.
In order to compete
at the national level,
you have to have a group
of at least three players.
Now that you're here, we've
finally got enough to compete.
So you guys want
me on your team?
Yeah, I'm Tetsu Shinjou,
and this here is...
Your name's Ren, right?
Yeah, Ren Suzugamori
at your service.
Come on.
You wanna join the team?
Are you sure that I'm...
Look, you were strong
enough to defeat me,
and more importantly,
Ren seems to have
taking a liking to you.
Why does that matter?
Ren's a bit weird,
but he's also a good
judge of character,
so you must be a cool guy.
Hmm.
Do you mind if I take
a look at your deck?
Uh, sure.
So you want to go to the
Vanguard Championship?
Then count me in.
‐Nice.
‐My name's Kai.
Toshiki Kai.
Put her there, teammate.
Ha, sure.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Shouldn't that be
a team handshake?
♪
We set our sights
on the championship,
but back then, Team Asteroid
was still in the
learning stages.
Tetsu's play was
really undisciplined,
and he made
a lot of mistakes.
Ren would keep our spirits up
with the ridiculous
things he said.
He was always
good for a laugh.
♪
They were the best
friends I'd ever had.
Being with them
made me feel at home.
Those were good times.
Sadly, it didn't last.
Wasn't I clear?
Guarding isn't going
to help you at all.
I told you at
the very beginning
that I would beat
you with this card
no matter what you do.
Huh?
(sighs)
(shouts)
Hey!
Are you okay?
Yeah, don't worry.
Huh?
Shows you for resisting.
♪
It's a shame, Tetsu.
I thought you were
a better player.
You disappoint me.
Stop it!
Yeah, you were
able to beat him,
but you don't
need to be a jerk.
I was able to?
I don't think you understand.
What?
Well, why don't you let him
know what's happening to me?
Ren is stronger, and it's
almost scary at this point.
Scary, how come?
You see, I've been
reborn as a card fighter.
I don't like this.
I can hear them speak.
The cards are talking.
Talking?
But how?
It's all thanks to this
incredible new power
I've obtained, Kai.
Now no one will be able
to stand in my way.
You're looking at the
strongest card fighter on earth.
(laughing)
♪
What was this power
Ren had discovered?
At the time, I had no idea.
But what was clear was
that Ren was no longer
the same guy I once knew.
(drilling)
What is this place?
Asteroid's new headquarters.
Hmm?
I'm gonna gather and
train fighters here
until we're the best
team in the whole world.
But why?
We've already got a team.
Ren's got some new plans
for the future of our group.
Hmm?
The top players
in the country
will be brought here
to battle each other
with the winners moving on
to bigger, better fights.
Only those few that can prove
themselves by going undefeated
will earn the honor of
playing for Team Asteroid.
This all seems like
a waste of time,
considering that we
have a full roster.
There's no free rides here.
You've got to fight for a
spot just like everyone else.
But I'm sure you
can handle it.
Oh, yeah?
You're very talented, Kai.
You and I, together with
our army of elite fighters,
can conquer the
world of Vanguard!
No chance.
Huh?
‐Get your deck.
‐But...
I'll show you who's
the strongest right now.
(grunts)
All right, stand
up the Vanguard.
♪
I wanted to beat Ren
to show him that Vanguard
wasn't about being the best.
It was about
enjoying the game
and the friendship
we'd created, only...
Final turn.
Can you see it?
You're broken and
utterly defeated
on the surface of
the Planet Cray.
It's pathetic.
(gasps)
Huh?
♪
Th‐‐this is...
So, Kai, like my winning image?
Ren, get me out of here!
No.
I want you to fully
understand my new powers,
and I want you to appreciate
how helpless you really are.
This is the end of the line.
Now, say hello to my
avatar, Blaster Dark!
Oh!
♪
You're not the same
person I used to know.
Rising from the shadows
to cut down my enemies.
Go, I'll destroy anyone
that interferes with me!
(laughs)
(grunts)
(groans)
Ren!
(grunts)
Careful!
What's wrong with you?
Kai, I‐‐I've gotten
much stronger.
Oh.
♪
Leaving?
You can come with
me if you want.
I'll never turn
my back on him.
Yeah.
I left.
Unable to stop Ren,
I decided to get as far
away from him as I could.
♪
So I moved back home
for another fresh start.
Kai!
Kai, is that you?
Oh, man, it really is!
Remember, it's me, Miwa.
How you been?
Leave me alone.
Hold on, hey!
We used to be pals!
I couldn't forgive myself.
I'd lost my best friends
because I wasn't strong
enough to stop Ren,
and it ate me up inside.
I thought about
it constantly,
how different things
might have been
if I wasn't so weak.
If only I'd been
able to overwhelm
that Psyqualia of his.
All I cared about was becoming
a stronger card fighter,
always searching
for the next challenge.
Then, one day...
Um, that card
means a lot to me.
Look, I just won this
in a game of Vanguard,
so there's no way that
I'm gonna give it up easily.
Mm, fine then!
I'll fight you
to get it back!
Okay, kid, it's a deal.
‐Now stand up, the Vanguard.
♪
He didn't stand a
chance against me,
but I took it slow and
I taught him the rules.
Normally, I wouldn't
even waste my time
playing someone so weak.
But...
Now stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade.
♪
Hmm.
I realized I was actually
enjoying Vanguard again.
The game had become such
a struggle for power.
(laughing)
♪
I'd forgotten.
Card fights were
supposed to be fun.
♪
You made it possible for me
to see that again, Aichi.
Only now...
♪
I'm stronger now, right?
Then why don't you fight me,
and I'll prove to you exactly
how strong I've become!
You know that if
we play, I'll win.
♪
I lost a friend
once to Psyqualia,
but this time
will be different.
I'm gonna stop you.
I won't let it happen again.
♪
I'll start by riding
Young Pegasus Knight,
then I move Barcgal and use
his ability to call Flogal.
♪
Gancelot's skill,
I search for Blaster Blade
and add it to my hand.
Blaster Blade, huh?
Don't you remember?
It's your avatar.
Oh, I know, but I don't
care about that card anymore
because now I've got a
much stronger avatar.
Wrong.
Hm?
It doesn't matter if
you threw it away or not,
your avatar is always
going to be Blaster Blade.
Hm!
Aichi, the time has come
for me to teach you
what true strength really is.
All right!
Your quest for
power ends now!
♪
I'll force you to acknowledge
my strength if I have to.
Aichi, it's my fault
you care so much
about getting stronger.
Don't say that.
You taught me everything
I know about card fighting.
And you helped me remember
how fun this game really is.
I've come so far to stand
across from you as an equal.
I'm ready to destroy you.
Next time, "At the
End of the Battle..."
I see Kai broken on the
surface of the Planet Cray.
♪