♪
Raise the sails
and swab the decks.
The pirates are gonna
make you walk the plank.
♪
Arrgh.
He's got two grade 3s
in the front row.
That's a lot more
power all of a sudden.
Come on, man, you just
need to survive this attack.
Ugh.
Aichi.
♪
‐Please, bro.
‐Mmm.
♪
(undersea bubbles gurgling)
Hmm.
Two grade 3s.
If this had happened
a few weeks ago,
I would have been too
scared to think straight.
But this is nothing
I can't handle.
Watch this.
Ruin Shade attacks Alfred.
I active her skill
to increase her power.
♪
Look, two more cards
into the drop zone.
For an attack power boost.
Is that bad?
♪
I guard with Wingal.
Grr.
Ya!
♪
Huh.
Spirit Exceed
boosted by Evil Shade
attacks your Vanguard.
Activating Evil Shade's skill
to increase Exceed's power.
♪
Rawr!
Now for the
twin drive check.
First.
Second check.
Rawr!
I check for
a damage trigger.
♪
Ah, he's been hit for four.
Guiding Zombie supports
my other Spirit Exceed
for this last attack
against Alfred.
I send Elaine in to guard.
♪
Hrrr, hrrr, ha!
(scream)
♪
That's about it for now.
Nice, I held him
to one damage
through that whole assault.
Okay.
It's time to strike back!
♪
Are you guys ready?
We are.
Draw!
I call the Solitary
Knight, Gancelot.
♪
He's filled up
his rear guard.
Alfred's coming in
at full strength!
With support from Wingal,
Gallatin's power goes up
and he attacks your Vanguard.
Spirit Exceed.
My Samurai Spirit
will guard that.
♪
Arrgh!
That's not all.
Ruin Shade will intercept.
♪
Let's see how
your Vanguard deals
with an attack from Alfred.
King of Knights charging up!
♪
I know it's him,
but it's like
he's over‐flushing
with confidence.
I'm pretty sure you
meant to say overflowing.
Eh heh.
Something's different
about the way he's playing.
I think you're right.
All it takes is one look
and you know he's excited
to be out there fighting.
This isn't the same Aichi
we're used to playing with.
Face your punishment!
♪
Now twin drive.
The first check.
The second.
Arrgh!
Ugh, damage check.
♪
Lastly, I'll have Marron
lend support to Gordon.
He attacks your
Spirit Exceed once more.
Yeah!
Argh!
Checking damage trigger.
♪
With that, I end my turn.
That's five damage
for the captain.
And the other
guy's only got four.
Ah, kaboom.
♪
How's he beating
my big brother?
(sigh)
Yes, I got him cornered
with one point to go.
(evil laughter)
Huh?
Well, kid, you sure
are a tough fighter.
Pushing me all
the way to five damage
like you just did.
You deserve a reward.
Say hello to the
fearsome new face
of the Abyssal Pirate Van.
Granblue!
♪
That card must be from
the new expansion set!
♪
Scourge of the
seven seas arise.
Master of tyranny, ride!
King of Demonic
Seas, Basskirk.
♪
(groaning)
Basskirk.
Soul charge.
When Basskirk soul charges,
he gets an extra 2,000 attack
power until end of turn.
Next, I activate
Guiding Zombie's skill.
I send him to the soul
and take three cards
from the top of my deck
and place them
in the drop zone.
You don't think...
Oh, he's gonna...
Told ya.
Here it comes,
something big.
♪
That makes eight
units in the soul.
Now witness the
ultimate resurrection.
Counter blast!
I follow that up with
a soul blast for eight!
Sleeping warriors
of the watery deep,
rise to action in the
name of the demon lord.
Wrath of the sea king!
♪
Two Commodore Bluebloods
and two Dandy Guy, Romarios
to the rear guard circles.
I retire Spirit Exceed.
♪
Four units out of the
drop zone at the same time.
With this skill, I can
resurrect up to five units.
But these four
are all I need.
Show them the power of the
Granblue Pirates, captain.
Teach those kids a lesson
for taking the
champions too lightly.
You've got them all
trembling in fear, kaboom!
Amazing.
With this level of play
it's impossible
to guess the winner.
It's looking like whoever
runs out of options first
will lose.
Ah!
Don't forget.
Uh.
Please, bro, you've got
to win this one for me!
I have to defend
these attacks.
Here goes‐‐with
Romario's support,
I'll have Blueblood
attack Alfred.
♪
I guard with Epona.
Basskirk gain support from
Evil Shade and attacks Alfred.
I activate Evil Shade's skill.
♪
I stop that with
Flash Shield, Iseult.
What?
♪
I activate Iseult's skill.
By discarding a Royal
Paladin card from my hand,
Iseult completely
nullifies the attack.
Grr.
Rawr!
♪
Uh, checking twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
Critical, huh?
Let's see.
Commodore Blueblood.
I give him an
additional 5,000 power
as well as the
plus one critical.
And now with the added
support from Romario,
he attacks Alfred!
I guard with Wingal.
This attack is too powerful
to be stopped that easily.
That's why I'm using Gordon
to intercept as well.
Huh?
♪
As long as there's a Royal
Paladin in the Vanguard circle
when Gordon intercepts,
5,000 power gets
added to his shield.
♪
Huh.
Grrr.
I end my turn.
No way, you mean the captain
couldn't even get one damage
with that amazing attack?
Ka‐‐kaboom.
Hmm.
Wow, look at Aichi go!
Hey, Emi, does your
brother have a secret twin
that none of us have
ever met before or what?
Can you please
not sit so close?
How come?
That boy, I wonder if he
could actually win this match?
Yeah, his opponent is
sitting at five damage.
Too close to call.
At first glance it looks
like he has a chance to win,
but we can't underestimate
the pirate's determination.
(bubbles gurgling)
My last attack
forced him to use up
almost all the
cards in his hand.
I just need to
get back to my turn
and he'll be
totally defenseless.
Then the game is mine.
I've got to give
myself that chance,
no matter what the cost!
This is it.
If I want to defeat Gouki
it's gonna have
to be on this turn.
I just need to
deal one more damage
and I'll do whatever
it takes to win.
My Royal Paladins and
my friends in Team Q4.
Everyone's counting on me.
I won't let them down.
♪
Uh?
Hmm?
What is this
strange feeling?
♪
Why is he just
standing there?
There's no way.
It's like a card
was calling to me,
telling me to use it.
♪
And there's never
been a better time.
Yes!
Beacon of hope, bring
judgment to the battlefield!
I ride Soul Saver Dragon!
♪
Uh, Soul Saver Dragon?
Why, I thought...
What's the matter?
I stopped him from
putting that into his deck.
It was one of the new cards
he got in his booster pack.
Uh.
Um, that card
is really powerful
but I don't think you
should use it right away.
With all its
different abilities
it might be too tough
to master in time.
♪
Kamui tried to stop me.
But then on the way in...
♪
I got a feeling.
And it's because I
believed in that feeling
that I now have
a chance to win.
♪
Time for me to see what
this new Vanguard can do.
Soul Saver Dragon's
Soul Blast activated!
♪
Are you ready for the power
of the Royal Paladins?
♪
I add 5,000 power to Gallatin.
5,000 to Marron.
And 5,000 to Wingal, too.
You're raising the power
of your units just like that?
It's Soul Saver Dragon's
ultimate ability,
Holy Charging Roar.
(gasp)
Marron moves to the front.
Gancelot is retired and
I call one more Marron.
I attack Basskirk with
Gallatin supported by Wingal.
I guard with
Rough Seas Banshee.
And I intercept
with two Bluebloods.
♪
Grrr, all this
power of his
means I've got to
be extra careful.
♪
With support from Marron,
I boost Soul Saver Dragon
and attack Basskirk.
Also, I activate Soul Saver
Dragon's battle skill.
Soul Saver Dragon gets
3,000 added to its power
whenever it
attacks a Vanguard.
♪
Wha?
I defend with Gust Jinn.
♪
By discarding one
Granblue unit from my hand,
I can nullify your attack.
It's the same skill
that Iseult has.
♪
Twin drive first check.
As long as he doesn't
draw a trigger here,
I can still win this.
Second check.
♪
Ah!
I activate
the stand trigger.
Gallatin stands once more.
Now with an extra
5,000 attack power.
That's just too much.
♪
Good defending, it's not easy
to stop an attack like that.
It doesn't matter what
comes over the horizon,
a pirate never gives up.
Marron attacks your Vanguard.
Ha!
Knight Spirit will guard!
♪
‐Oh, so close!
‐Oh, man!
Grrr, rawr!
Yeah, captain!
He stopped that
punk flat, kaboom!
‐No, you're wrong.
‐Huh?
The kid still has
one more attack.
But the captain
won't be able to‐‐
He's used up all his cards
and he doesn't have
any more intercepts.
He's out of options.
Here it is, Gouki.
I attack.
There's nothing I can do.
It looks like I'm
gonna meet my maker.
But that doesn't matter
'cause pirates never give up!
Gallatin, our opponent
battled us with honor.
Give him a swift ending.
Attack!
Grrrr.
Grrrr, rawr!
♪
Damage check.
This pirate is sunk.
(gasps)
He did it!
Aichi!
♪
It's all over.
The winner is Aichi Sendou!
There you have it, folks,
our champions for this year's
Vanguard Regional Qualifying
Tournament are Team Q4!
(cheering)
Kai, I couldn't have
done it without you
and the support of Team Q4.
♪
Oh yeah, my Royal Paladins
were a big help, too.
Thanks, you guys.
You did it, bro!
That was awesome!
You beat Gouki,
we're champions!
All right!
Then that means‐‐
Our team is going
to the nationals.
I don't think
anyone expected
that kind
of performance, Aichi.
He's great, huh?
♪
Ha ha ha, my savior,
thank goodness!
♪
Did he just‐‐no, nonsense.
Hey, what are you
calling nonsense?
Oh no, I'm sure
he didn't mean that.
Listen up, if you've
got a problem with Aichi,
you've got a problem with me
and I don't like guys that‐‐
Calm down.
Hmm.
Oh, sure, act cool when the
shop manager's holding me back.
Why I oughta...
Ease off, Kamui.
That weird feeling
I got during the game...
What was it?
Captain, my captain.
Stay away from me!
Huh?
Do I look like I mope
around after a loss?
I'm a pirate.
Just watch, the pirate
spirit flows through me.
Argh.
Now that's the guy I admire.
I'm proud to be
on your crew.
Same goes for
me, boss, kaboom.
(sobbing)
‐Gouki?
‐Huh?
I wanted to say thank you.
That was the best
battle I've ever had.
I underestimated you.
But I finally understand
why Kamui looks up
to you so much.
But hey, I've
got to warn you,
nationals are a lot tougher.
You'll have to train
real hard for it, got me?
Yes, sir.
♪
Gouki.
Kamui.
Argh!
♪
Nagisa.
It looks like Team Q4 won,
so I'll give up on making
you my husband for now.
Wow, that's great news!
I've decided...
that if you
won't be my husband
then I'll just be your wife!
Arrgh!
Ah!
Aw, they look so
happy together.
Kamui's not gonna be
a free man after all.
Poor guy, yo.
No!
Emi, it's not
what it looks like!
♪
Come on, you need to stop!
Why should I?
Kamui has the national
tournament coming up.
You can't be bothering
him about marriage.
Thank you.
The wedding can wait
until after nationals.
Huh?
You're the best, big brother.
No!
♪
Congrats.
Thank you.
Keep it up, the nationals
are right around the corner.
Uh, sure.
Who does he think he is
talking to my girlfriend?
I'll show him
a thing or two!
‐(giggle)
‐Home wrecker!
How 'bout we ignore him?
Sound good?
‐Okay.
We all wish you
the best of luck.
♪
You too.
Uh, thank you.
You're welcome to
visit us at Psy anytime.
All right, Team Q4
has earned the right
to go off and compete at the
National Vanguard Tournament.
Now join me in
congratulating them.
(clapping)
(giggling)
I won't clap for Kamui.
This is all
because of you, bro.
Huh?
If you hadn't beaten Gouki,
we'd be second
place right now.
But we're champions.
And we're gonna win
at the nationals
no matter who
our opponents are.
Then we're
gonna get married.
No, we're not!
The strongest cardfighters
from all over the country.
There are huge
challenges ahead of us.
But I won't run away,
even if I'm scared.
I've got my clan
to back me up
and all my
friends in Team Q4.
♪
I'm gonna give it my all.
We won the
regional championship!
You're amazing, bro!
Thanks, we all worked
so hard to get there.
That's true, but you
only just started playing,
so beating Gouki
is a huge deal.
That's it, I'm
gonna set my sights
on training harder.
Could you take me to that card
shop you're talking about?
Uh, sure, sounds like Morikawa
wasn't able to find it, but...
Next time,
Fateful Encounter.
What, whose image
is this in my head?