This is it, everybody.
The moment you've
all been waiting for.
The final match
is about to start.
Who would've thought
we'd have our two‐time
returning champions
going to sudden death
against a group of
relative new‐comers.
I may have made
the prediction earlier
that Team Asteroid
would win without
having to play
in this third game.
For once, I'm
glad to be wrong.
Well, that makes
two of us, Doctor O.
It's the Shadow Paladins
versus the Royal Paladins.
Who will reign supreme?
It's o‐verwhelming.
♪
(crowd cheers)
Well, isn't it nice?
I'll destroy this kid
and Team Asteroid will
have its third
straight championship.
That's right.
Claiming another title
should bring a massive
new wave of recruits with it.
The organization
needs to expand.
Asteroid is ready
to take the world
by storm.
♪
Hm?
(growls)
And there's no one
that can stop us.
(mischievous laugh)
(groans)
♪
What's with that look?
You're still afraid, huh?
No, it's just‐‐
A big guy like you
shouldn't get scared.
My powers have
done so much for us,
and yet I can still see
the resentment in your eyes.
My eyes?
♪
(shudders)
Huh?
♪
(struggling)
Hmm.
Don't force me to question
where your loyalties lie.
♪
Psyqualia,
it'll help me
bring the earth
to its knees
one person at a time.
(mischievous laugh)
♪
Ren's Psyqualia.
I can feel it from here.
It's the only reason
he was able to beat Kai.
Let's finish what we
started all those years ago!
♪
Kai did everything he could,
hoping to reach out to
the friend he used to know.
But Ren was...
too strong.
♪
You okay?
This isn't a good
time to get nervous.
Don't sweat it, bro.
You gotta believe in yourself.
I bet that weirdo
thinks he's gonna
win this match.
I can't wait
to see him lose!
Kamui's got
a good point.
You've become
so much stronger
in the last little while.
I know you can
handle this guy.
Are you sure?
You got it!
The Aichi Sendou here
isn't the same one
that walked into my store
those long months ago.
All the training you've
done this last year
was to prepare
for this moment.
My number one student.
Thanks, guys.
♪
Get him.
Kai.
Aichi, it's important
to remember that you're
not going out
there by yourself,
your friends,
everyone you've battled
will be right behind you.
Believe it!
We've got your
back, bro.
Hmm.
Okay, then.
I'm ready.
That's weird.
Ren's already activated
his Psyqualia.
I know.
And it feels like
it's stronger than ever.
Seems so.
But I've yet to sense
anything from Aichi Sendou.
Do you think he'll
actually try to use it?
'Cause yesterday...
Hmm.
He was able to beat
Team Caesar without
relying on that power.
Go, Enigman Storm!
Glory Maker's skill
pumps him up to 33,000.
I fought my hardest
alongside my rightful clan.
Thanks to them,
I'll never give up.
You...
you've come to save me?
See the king
as he once was.
I ride...
Alfred Early!
♪
(shouts)
Only he's facing
Ren Suzugamori.
He'll have to use it
if he wants to win.
I don't think he has
any other option.
Hmm.
Uh‐oh.
Kourin's getting
that angry look
on her face again.
Right, and you
think I care?
After how long it took
us to find two people
with that power,
I hope they do
use it on each other.
We've waited for this.
Indeed.
Soon enough, these
two chosen card fighters
will leave everything
to the mercy of the cards,
then we'll finally
understand the true
nature of their
mysterious ability.
♪
People, are you ready?
'Cause we're about
to kick off the deciding
match of the final round!
Q4 versus Team Asteroid!
Now, let me hear it!
Are you pumped to watch
card fighting history
in the making?
(crowd cheers)
♪
Go get 'em, Aichi.
Watch yourself.
Hm?
♪
Enjoy this moment.
You can remember it
as the day you lost
the biggest fight
of your life.
Talk all you want, Ren,
it's not gonna work.
You can't win.
You knew that even
before I said it.
The strength that
burns in my eyes
will ensure that this
battle goes my way.
The world of Vanguard
belongs to me.
Faithful card fighters
flock to my side
from around the globe.
It's like I said,
the powerless will
fall to their knees,
and the chosen shall
reap the spoils!
You've got a really
messed up way
of treating people!
You fool.
You could have anything,
and yet you
reject it, Aichi.
Maybe you just need
me to show you what
you're missing out on.
Decks are shuffled and ready.
Let's get this
game started!
♪
Let the match begin!
‐Now stand up, my vanguard!
♪
(laughs)
(Aichi pants)
♪
Did you see it?
My path to victory.
The cards have
already shown it to me.
♪
And once this is over,
we'll finally be able to put
this whole mess behind us.
But first, I wanna
see you realize
the foolish mistake you
made by shunning this gift.
As though I need
help remembering.
I know too well
what it can do,
and I don't need it.
♪
Blaster Javelin ride!
Using Fullbau's skill.
♪
It's your turn.
I draw
and ride Marron.
♪
Wingal Brave
moves to rear guard
with Gancelot's skill.
♪
Call!
Attacking Blaster Javelin!
♪
I don't guard.
I check for
a drive trigger.
(groans)
♪
Next, the Knight
of Friendship, Kay
will attack with a
boost from Wingal Brave.
Abyss Freezer will guard that.
(grunts)
♪
And with that,
it's my turn.
♪
The darkness that
swallows the light.
My avatar!
I ride,
Blaster Dark is here.
(screams)
♪
I call...
Skull Witch, Nemain.
♪
CounterBlast.
Call.
♪
Demon World Castle,
DonnerSchlag attacks
the Knight of Friendship, Kay.
♪
That Knight of Friendship,
Kay, would've gotten
a lot stronger once Aichi
got Blaster Blade into play.
I guess Ren's gonna
mess with his plans
from the get‐go.
♪
Attacking your vanguard
with Blaster Dark.
♪
I don't guard.
I check the drive trigger.
♪
Afraid having it
in front of you again?
♪
The clan you threw away?
Now then...
see if you can
picture it.
Blaster Dark is
coming for you...
slashing forward
with his shadow blade.
(screams)
♪
This can't be.
Huh?
♪
(screams)
(Ren chuckles)
♪
I‐‐I check for
a damage trigger.
♪
This is amazing.
I could feel myself
swinging the sword.
Power surging through me.
I'm unstoppable.
It's come to this.
♪
Boosted by Gururubau,
Skull Witch, Nemain, attacks.
I don't guard.
♪
(groans)
(Ren chuckles)
It's hard to believe,
but my Psyqualia
is stronger than
it's ever been before.
Can you feel what
you're missing?
This is a card fight,
so spare me the mind games!
Oh, but it's just
so enjoyable making
you feel humiliated
and helpless like that.
(chuckles)
The chance to make
my dreams a reality.
It's the greatest
gift a man could get.
What reason could you
possibly have for rejecting
such an advantage?
(chuckles)
You're wrong.
I didn't reject Psyqualia.
Hmph?
It was way too strong
for me to handle.
When I used it,
I actually felt powerful
for the first
time in my life.
But it isn't real.
And you've become
addicted to that lie.
This is it.
My strength.
(gasps)
Is that‐‐
All right!
You know what time it is.
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade!
I won't let myself turn
into what you've become.
Not now, not ever.
This is the path I chose, Ren.
♪
Hmm.
CounterBlast.
♪
Hey, DonnerSchlag!
Beat it!
♪
I call.
Marron, let's go.
♪
Drive trigger check.
Critical trigger.
5,000 power to Bedivere.
A critical
to Blaster Blade!
Two damage about
to go through.
Oh, yeah!
(grunts)
♪
You fool.
You'll never be able
to beat me unless
you give in to Psyqualia.
Like you did?
That's not my style.
Face the facts, Ren.
You're so blind you can't
even tell who your friends are.
This power will give me
everything I could ever want.
And there's not a person
on earth who can stop me.
Not one.
Ren, wait!
♪
Again!
Kai?
Stay away!
Leave me alone.
Even after everything
Kai did to reach you‐‐
What's that?
That power's
driven you insane!
Why else would you be trying
to take over the world?
Here's a lesson
you can't ignore.
True strength
comes from within!
(grunts)
♪
With a boost from
Wingal Brave,
Bedivere attacks next.
♪
Inspired by Blaster Blade,
he gains 3,000 power.
♪
Would you look at that?
I recover one point of damage.
What a shame,
you were about to take
a commanding lead there.
Unfortunately, the outcome
of this game isn't yours
to decide.
I couldn't figure
it out until just now
why you would
walk away from
a once‐in‐a‐lifetime chance.
But then I realized...
it's me that
you're denying.
Aichi's really standing
his ground out there.
Is he seriously
not gonna use it?
We'll have to wait and see.
Cursed Black Dragon.
Pain will flow
through this battlefield.
I ride...
Phantom Blaster Dragon!
♪
(roars)
With his passive skill,
because Blaster Dark
is in the soul...
He gains a thousand power.
♪
Come on, Aichi!
And I call.
♪
This is bad.
Real bad.
What's that
called again?
Oh yeah,
Corruption Charged Dance.
It's the Corrupted
Charging Lance.
Do you think
before you talk?
Careful!
♪
You know what
happens next.
Phantom Blaster
Dragon's ultimate skill.
♪
Corrupted Charging Lance,
Nemain, Gururubau,
Darkside Trumpeter.
There it is.
We knew this moment
was about to come.
Sendou's in a lot
of trouble here.
Indeed.
These next decisions
are crucial as the challenger
could quickly find
himself heading home.
So true!
And you'd need a laser
to cut through the tension
in this place.
Huh?
(crowd cheers)
♪
He'll be fine.
If anyone can do this,
Aichi can!
I don't know.
(growls)
♪
Lives paid in tribute
to the cursed dragon.
(screams)
♪
This is incredible.
When I used his skill,
I could feel myself
getting stronger.
The strength
of my vanguard
surges through me.
(laughs)
♪
He's pushing himself
to the limit and beyond.
♪
Hm?
(doors whooshing closed)
Hm.
♪
(laughs)
I'll end this right now.
Someone like you
could never stop me.
♪
Humiliating you
isn't enough anymore.
I'll destroy you
and transform you
back into the thing
you hate the most.
(laughs)
♪
(groans)
(mischievous laugh)
♪
Psyqualia.
An ability given
to the fortunate few.
The power to reshape
the world as we see fit.
Why do you deny it, Aichi?
It isn't real.
I won't abuse it
and lose sight
of myself ever again!
(mischievous laugh)
Is that what you fear?
Then I'd better
end this quick
and save you
from yourself.
Next time,
The Truth of Psyqualia.
It's still within me.
I don't want it
to come back,
but I can hear
it calling.