That's the last draw.
Straw?
Bro, I hate
to do this to you,
but there's just no way
I can bring myself
to fight alongside
a jerk like him anymore.
Sorry!
I quit!
No, Kamui, wait!
You know that this
is just the first day
of the tournament,
and the big games
don't happen until
next week, right?
Uh, yeah.
Well, the games you're
about to play are
elimination matches.
I know you wanna chase
after your friend right now,
but if you
don't play today,
there won't be
a team for him
to come back to.
Sometimes doing what's
right isn't easy.
I guess so.
♪
Hold on, Kamui.
I know how badly
you wanted to play
in this tournament.
That's why I'll do
everything in my power
to get us to the finals.
Your team will be
waiting for you.
♪
It's time for me‐‐
Let's take a moment to explain
how the elimination
matches work!
For the Vanguard...
National Championships!
(crowd cheers)
♪
We finally made it.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Kourin, love!
You don't mean...
That's right, it's time
for the super fan dance.
Everybody this way!
We love you,
Ultra Rare!
Simmer down.
♪
In preparation for
next week's finals,
we're gonna be forced
to eliminate half
our competitors.
To ensure this process is fair,
we'll be dividing
the 32 participating teams
into eight blocks.
♪
Each block will be
made up of four teams.
All teams in a given block
will play each other
Round Robin style
with the top two teams
moving on to compete
in the finals next week.
But how exactly
do we decide
which teams are moving on?
Let's imagine the
outcome looked like this.
♪
Looking here,
we can clearly see
that Team A has done
the best with three wins
and no losses.
Team B has two
wins, one loss.
In this case,
it's easy to tell
which two teams are
going on to the finals.
But Suiko, couldn't
two teams wind up
with the same record?
If that happens,
our judges will look
at the individual
game stats to reach
their decision.
Sounds like we put
a lot of thought into it.
(chuckles)
This is a competition
where only the strongest
will survive.
Do your best to win
all your matches
so there's no question
who's the best team
in your block.
Uh‐huh, because there's
no other way to get
to the finals.
Right!
Good luck, everyone!
Play hard and have fun!
(cheers)
If we have to win
all our matches
to get past
the preliminaries,
that's what we'll do.
Failure isn't an option.
Kamui's counting on us.
Is it okay with you guys
if I go first?
Huh?
Hmm?
You heard them.
Only the strongest
will move on,
and I know I can win.
Then you're up first.
I'm with him,
count me in
for the second battle.
Huh?
I missed out
on Regionals,
it's about time I got
the chance to fight.
Sounds good, Misaki.
Are you ready
to find out
what block you're in?
'Cause here we go!
Our computer is in
the process of selecting
the first four teams.
There, it's block A.
Nice!
Team Q4 is first on the list.
That must be good luck, right?
Oh, no.
Huh?
♪
Is that...
who's Team Asteroid?
This is bad.
Team Asteroid
is gonna be tough.
Those guys are
the defending champions
from last year.
Aichi and I met
their leader
the day we went
over to PSY Shop.
What?!
Oh.
♪
Yeah, it's Ren Suzugamori.
‐Huh?
‐You've gotta see
the way he plays.
It looks like I will.
Well, then we're gonna
have to battle hard
if we want a chance
of making it to
the top two
in our block.
What a pain in the neck.
(groans)
Oh!
The team is in A block
against... oh no!
There you are!
We've been looking for you.
Ah!
I think there's been
a mistake, you guys.
Nice try, Kamui,
but you can't fool me.
You wear the same
clothes every day.
Even if you were
trying to play it cool,
it's no use.
We can spot our
hot‐headed friend
a mile away.
Hot‐headed?
Ah, uh‐oh.
That's Kamui!
No doubt.
Thinking he could hide
with a dopey disguise.
Sorry, that just slipped out.
I think it's
a great disguise!
A for effort, yo.
You know, Kamui,
you don't really
seem like your usual self.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Isn't it obvious?
You wanna go back
to your team.
You wanted to play in
the National Tournament
more than anyone, and now
you don't get the chance.
Uh, hardly.
I mean, yeah,
I did wanna play,
but now that I'm here,
I'm not impressed.
I don't buy it.
This has been your dream
as long as I've known you.
Now, suck up your pride,
rejoin your team,
and win the whole thing!
You guys are wasting
your breath trying
to convince me.
There's no way
I'm going back.
‐But Kamui...
I know you guys
wanted to cheer me on,
but now you'll just have
to cheer on Aichi, okay?
That's all I can
ask of you two!
(cries)
Don't do this!
What's gotten into him today?
Huh.
‐Kamui!
‐Don't go!
All right, teams,
now that you know
which blocks you're all in,
please proceed
to your designated
qualification area.
Oh, looks like
A block is gonna
be playing right here.
Everything's
coming up Morikawa!
Yeah, 'cause moving
seats would be hard.
Once all of our
teams have arrived
at the correct locations,
we'll be kicking off
the first matches
of the National
Vanguard Tournament!
(crowd cheers)
Our message to
the country's
greatest cardfighters...
Try your hardest and show
us what you're made of.
And good luck, everyone!
Let's play some Vanguard!
(cheers continue)
I'm glad we're not facing
them in the first round.
Hmm?
(chuckles)
That's weird.
Huh?
I don't see him anywhere.
You'd think that
since they're playing,
Ren Suzugamori would be
somewhere around here.
Yeah.
Huh, hmm.
‐It's been a long time, Kai.
‐Huh?
♪
Tetsu.
Who's this guy, Tetsu?
Friend of yours?
Just someone
I used to know.
♪
Huh?
I think I've seen his
picture in a magazine.
Huh?
Those are Ren's teammates.
(gasps)
So, Kai, I thought
you were avoiding us.
(scoffs)
Why hasn't Ren
shown his face yet?
He's not playing in
the preliminary round.
Ren doesn't enjoy
wasting his time.
You should remember
that at least.
Should I?
The past isn't something
I tend to dwell on.
Then Kai knows
Ren and that
other guy as well?
Huh?
My past is none
of your business.
Sorry.
So, he'll be playing
in the final rounds?
Couldn't tell you,
guess you'll have
to make it that far
if you wanna find out.
(chuckles)
This year Ren was
able to qualify
three separate teams
into the Nationals,
and I doubt you guys
are capable of getting
past any one of them.
It'll be two
of Ren's teams
in the final match.
I can guarantee that.
He's on‐‐
Three different teams?
It's like he's
amassing an army
of cardfighters.
Who are these guys?
And what is
Ren Suzugamori after?
♪
Our teams are in
the same block,
so it looks like
we'll be fighting soon,
just like old times.
(chuckles)
Hmph.
Well, Kai...
You heard me right.
The past isn't something
I like to discuss.
Wait!
Just let him be.
But Misaki‐‐
Everyone has something
they'd rather not talk about.
(Aichi groans)
Attention, please!
‐Huh?
Our teams are in place,
and it's time to get
started with the first
matches of the
National Championship.
(cheers)
Let's take a look
at the pairings
for blocks A and B.
Team Q4 versus
Jurassic Army.
No time like the present.
I'm just happy we don't
have to face Ren's team
right away.
Yeah.
Hey, Aichi.
What?
I'm sure that one day
we'll all understand
a little bit more
about Ren and Kai,
but until then...
let's focus on
the match ahead.
We've gotta win this match!
(grunts)
You still wanna
go first, Aichi?
(groans)
Yeah!
(cheers)
♪
This is the calm
before the storm.
♪
Vanguard
National Championship
first match block A.
Now, would the fighters
please step out on the field.
(cheers)
Aichi Sendou
versus Gunji Rukudo.
♪
Come on, bro.
I've never seen you before,
so I'm going to assume
this is your first time
at the National Tournament?
Yeah.
I see.
Well, I like
the look about you.
You're calm
and you're confident.
Thanks, that's really nice.
Now, you listen
to me, boy.
Confidence alone won't
help you win against
the Jurassic Army.
Cardfighters
to your console.
Oh, man.
This setup is a bit
different than the one
at Regionals.
I just hope I'm
in the right spot.
♪
Jurassic Army.
A team that's been to
the Nationals before.
This is our first challenge.
♪
But I won't lose!
My friends are all
counting on me.
Good luck.
(whirring)
Huh?
♪
And now let's battle!
Hmm.
♪
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
‐Oh!
‐Don't close your eyes.
(grunts)
♪
Whoa!
Wow!
♪
Barcgal!
Dragon Egg.
There, the starting units
are out on the battlefield.
I'm your host MC Mya.
Joining me today
is our guest commentator,
the amazing and
talented Doctor O.
When it comes to Vanguard,
nobody knows more
than the man
who dedicated his life
to the game, Doctor O.
Let's have some fun.
Our block A match
has just kicked off
with team Q4
facing off
against the Jurassic Army.
Predictions, Doctor?
This is my first
time seeing team Q4.
So I'm not sure
how they'll play,
but I'm excited
to find out!
My turn.
I draw and ride Sonic Noa.
Next I activate
Dragon Egg's skill
moving it to
the rear guard.
My turn's over.
You're up.
Here goes.
I ride Wingal.
♪
I move Barcgal back.
And now I call
the Little Sage Marron.
♪
With support from Barcgal,
Wingal attacks Sonic Noa.
♪
Trigger check.
Checking for damage.
♪
I attack with Marron too.
Hm.
Aichi Sandou has managed to
get in for a quick two damage.
A good start for sure.
But here at the
National Championships,
you can never let
your guard down.
Right you are, Doctor.
‐It's my turn.
‐Hm?
I ride the Ravenous
Dragon, Megarex.
I call Cannon Fire
Dragon, Cannon Gear.
This unit has an extra
cost I have to pay.
When he comes into play,
I'm forced to retire
one of my other rear
guard units.
What?
Dragon Egg,
you are being sacrificed.
You destroyed one
of your own units.
It's unfortunate,
but it's the only
way I can get Cannon Gear
onto the battlefield.
He's a powerful soldier.
Well worth losing
others to obtain.
But Dragon Egg's sacrifice
is never in vain.
Paying one counter blast.
Dragon Egg
returns to my hand.
You see, now I can hold
this card for defending
or return it to
the battlefield
to fight once again.
Thus I'm able to call
in my most powerful units
without suffering
their negative effects.
Behold the unparalleled
strength of the Tachikaze clan.
Oh!
See that?
The Tachikaze clan has
so much power it's crazy.
Why are you acting
so happy about it?
That's right, you use
a Tachikaze deck.
Uh‐huh.
Watch out.
The Jurassic Army's
about to launch
a massive attack.
I call Wing Dragon, Skyptero,
and Pack Dragon, Tinyrex.
♪
Bring it.
I attack Wingal
with Cannon Gear.
♪
I don't guard.
Damage trigger check.
I attack with Megarex.
♪
No guard.
Hmm.
Drive check.
♪
With support
from Tinyrex
I'll have Skyptero attack.
I don't guard.
What?
Do you mean
all his attacks
were able to get through?
What's Aichi doing down there?
♪
That attack
ends my turn.
I knew Aichi didn't
have the chops to play
at the national level.
Hmm.
I doubt he's declaring
no guard just for fun.
Aichi must have
a big move in the works.
It looks like the player
for team Q4 has forgotten
how to guard!
I'm interested to see
what he does next.
I didn't guard
those attacks
'cause I needed
the damage...
for this move!
Now stand up my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade.
♪
I strike back.
Counter blast active.
Huh?
Cannon Gear, retired!
♪
So that's it!
All those attacks
you let through
were just helping
you build up damage
for this moment.
It was the best thing
I could think of
to deal with that
powerful unit of yours.
And that's just
the beginning.
Marron, move to
the back row.
Now I call the Knight
of Truth, Gordon.
And the Knight of Rose, Morgana.
♪
Morgana's only
got 6,000 power.
And there's no
unit to boost it.
Striking at Megarex
with that unit
would be a wasted move.
Attack one of his
rear guard units
and slow him down!
I'll have Morgana
attack Skyptero.
♪
Activating Skyptero's
defense skill.
Counter blast.
And now I'm returning
Skyptero back to my hand.
Jurassic Army doesn't
let our soldiers fall
to enemy fire.
Gaining support
from Barcgal.
My Blaster Blade
attacks your Megarex.
♪
Checking for
a drive trigger.
♪
With Marron's support,
Gordon attacks.
♪
Fire in the hole!
I defend with Dragon Egg.
♪
I end my turn.
I only got one
damage through.
But I managed to get
rid of Cannon Gear.
That really wasn't
the most impressive turn.
What?
Aichi's doing well down there.
And this is where
the real game begins.
Huh?
All the pressure of
the National Tournament
is weighing
on Aichi's head.
In the first few
turns of this battle,
we've seen both players
take a very cautious approach.
Neither willing
to over commit.
Going forward from here,
the units these players
send out could have a huge
impact on the outcome.
Mm‐hmm.
Any predictions on
what's gonna happen next,
Doctor O?
I hope it's exciting!
Is that all
you're gonna say?
Yeah, the best thing
we can do right now
is sit back and enjoy.
Now that's an idea
I'll get behind!
♪
Hey Shin, what are you
doing with your hands there?
My hands?
Oh, that's weird.
Hey, you just
called me Shin.
You know that when
we're out at Vanguard events,
you have to address me
as Coach or Manager.
Whatever you say, Coach Shin.
No, just Coach!
Well, I'll give you this,
you did take down
that Cannon Gear.
Huh?
Still, you never rest
on the battlefield.
I may have lost a unit...
but my army is
as tough as ever.
Watch as I declare war
with the strongest
soldier in my army.
Thundering
Mechanical Dinosaur.
Trample him underfoot.
I ride Tyrant, Deathrex.
♪
Tyrant, Deathrex.
That's a very
powerful unit.
But no matter how
strong his units are,
I'm not about to lose,
for Kamui's sake,
for the sake of
all my teammates,
I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to win this battle!
♪
Deathrex, I had
trouble with that unit
when I fought against Izaki.
Aichi, stay focused,
he's got a Tachikaze deck
and it's full of
creatures from
the recent expansion set.
I wonder how many
Grade Threes he has.
Morikawa!
Oh, go Aichi, you're the man!
He sacrificed his own
units to increase his power?
Now, that's intense.
Next time,
aggressive movement.
Tachikaze deck.
I won't lose!
I‐‐no we,
are winning
this battle for Kamui.
Imagine it.