♪
I didn't come
for a lecture, Ren.
I came cause I'm finally
strong enough to beat you.
I'm gonna bring back
the person you used to be.
I swear it to you.
And that's perfectly
fine by me.
You'll need all
the help you can get.
I'm gonna destroy you
with the power that
you hate so much.
♪
I never thought
I'd see the day
when the three of us
were back together again,
but things have changed
a lot since then, Kai.
You have no
chance of winning.
Ren's power level
is terrifying.
The Overlord has
reached his ultimate form!
Cross ride!
Dragonic Overlord, The End!
♪
I've never seen that
used before in my life.
What do you think of my Dragonic
Overlord's final evolution?
It's true form?
Alright, let's see if we
can't find the old you, huh?
♪
Well, what do you think of
Dragonic Overlord, The End?
When ridden on top of Dragonic
Overlord, an ability triggers.
Giving it 13,000 power
at all times.
A cross ride?
I've never even
heard of units
that could do
something like that.
It's just what Kai needed!
♪
Did you know?
Is that why you brought us
here to watch the fight?
Actually, I'm as
surprised as you.
He's one of the most amazing
Vanguard players I've ever seen.
Not only did he rescue
Aichi from Psyqualia's grip,
but he has no problem mastering
the most difficult units.
♪
Considering how skillful
a card fighter he is,
you have to wonder why he
wasn't chosen by Psyqualia.
Interesting.
♪
There was a time when nothing
could tear these two apart.
Now, nothing but Vanguard
can bring them back together.
What a moment.
I bet I'm the only
person in this room
that's happy to
see them like this.
Who they are,
what they stand for.
They've changed a lot, but
the essence of this fight,
the heart of this battle.
It feels like old times.
Or maybe that's
how I want to see it.
It's obvious.
Things can't go back
to the way they were.
I should know better.
♪
Leaving?
You can come
with me if you want.
I'll never turn
my back on him.
Yeah.
♪
Everything got worse
the day Kai quit the team.
Ren went out of control.
♪
(snickering)
(gasping)
♪
(roaring)
(groaning)
♪
(shuddering)
(moaning)
He fought all the time.
Relying on that power
to keep him going.
He was trying to forget
the pain of Kai leaving.
Drowning in the
anger he felt.
I think he wanted
to prove to everyone
that he'd made
the right choice.
♪
Me, Kai, Ren.
Each of us were forced
to choose a path that day.
And we followed them,
for better or worse
to where we are
at this moment.
Huh, those two were
like best friends
from the day
they met each other.
They got along so well
that sometimes I would
feel jealous of Kai
for being so
close to someone
I've known
my whole life.
At first glance, you'd think
they were polar opposites,
but they're actually
quite similar.
Honor means a lot
to these guys.
They stand by what
they believe in,
and friendship means more
to them than anything.
Ren devoted himself
to getting stronger,
because it's what
Kai wanted for the team.
Without a doubt,
if it weren't for his
desire to help his friends,
Ren would have never
stumbled upon Psyqualia.
When Kai turned
his back on us,
he did it for
Ren's own good.
He wasn't able to stop Ren
with his current strength,
so he left with the intention
of finding the skills he needed
to bring him back.
I didn't want to
lose either of them,
but when the time came,
my choice was clear.
Powerless to
change the situation,
I decided to follow
Ren down his path.
Even if that meant
I'd be walking away
from Kai in the process.
No matter how
this fight ends,
it's my duty to
see it through.
As their friend
and as a card fighter.
♪
This new version
of Dragonic Overlord?
It's what I've
been looking for.
At 13,000 power, I finally
have a unit strong enough
to beat your Psyqualia.
Your abuse of that power
is going to come to an end.
♪
I call Bahr.
Supported by Conroe.
Burning Horn's
coming for Fatalita.
Supported by Flame of Hope,
Aermo, The End attacks.
♪
(growls)
Now to check
the drive trigger.
♪
(growls)
Not done.
Whenever Aermo supports
a successful attack,
I discard one card from my
hand and activate its skill.
Draw.
Hmm.
♪
The End isn't
finished either.
Activating his
ultimate skill.
Persona Blast.
♪
Dragonic Overlord
just stood back up?
♪
After landing an attack, this
Overlord can stand back up
if I discard another copy of
Dragonic Overlord, The End.
Time for you to
face the facts.
You're not the strongest
fighter in the world.
♪
Who am I supposed
to cheer for?
♪
Let's finish what we
started all those years ago!
♪
Ren!
(growling)
♪
(electricity crackling)
Let's finish what we
started all those years ago!
♪
Ren!
(growling)
♪
I guard with
Death Feather Eagle.
♪
Checking the
drive trigger.
♪
There, a critical trigger,
and I'm giving all the
effects to Berserk Dragon.
♪
The End wasn't enough
to finish the job.
Well, with any luck,
Berserk Dragon will get through
with critical damage.
That's Ren for ya!
♪
Now Bahr supports an attack
from my Berserk Dragon.
I use Abyss Freezer and
Blaster Javelin to guard.
DonnerSchlag intercepts.
♪
He stopped that too.
Hmm.
♪
I end my turn.
Oh, man.
After cross riding The End,
I thought he'd
finish him off for sure.
Ren Suzugamori's skills are
not to be underestimated.
Right.
Wow, what a fight!
I've got some
bad news for you.
You see, I knew it would
happen like this all along.
Why?
Cause I have Psyqualia.
I think it's about time we
brought this charade to a close.
It's my final turn.
♪
Huh?
Tell me.
Did you think you
were the only person
that knew how
to cross ride?
You can't!
♪
Witness the embodiment
of pain and destruction.
The triumph of shadows bound
in servitude to my eyes!
Cross ride...
Phantom Blaster Overlord!
(roaring)
♪
(gasping)
So that's
Phantom Blaster Overlord.
♪
Now get a load of this, Kai.
By cross riding
Phantom Blaster Overlord
on top of
Phantom Blaster Dragon,
its power
becomes 13,000.
♪
I call Phantom
Blaster Dragon
and Blaster Dark.
♪
Oh.
That makes three
Blaster units.
My, what a
beautiful front line.
(growls)
(snickers)
Go, Blaster Dark!
Crush Burning Horn Dragon!
♪
No guard.
(grunts)
♪
You know, this has
been a lot of fun.
♪
Boosted by Apocalypse.
It's time for my
Phantom Blaster Overlord
to steal the show.
♪
Apocalypse's soul blast.
Adding 6,000 power.
♪
And...
Huh?
Kai was able to
discard another copy
of The End to
activate an ability.
So, that means
Ren's gonna‐‐
(snickering)
(gasping)
Sending a second copy
to the drop zone.
Persona Blast!
♪
(growling)
Activating this ability
during Phantom Blaster
Overlord's attack.
Since the cost has been paid,
he receives an
additional 10,000 power,
and plus one critical.
(roars)
♪
This is real bad.
If that attack
goes through...
Ren will win.
♪
I'm not finished yet.
I guard that attack with
two Blue Ray Dracokids
and a Burning Horn Dragon.
♪
Defending at 38,000.
That's just enough.
♪
What a waste.
Check the drive trigger.
♪
Oh, look, I pulled
a critical trigger.
Huh?
♪
It can't be!
I guess I'll give
the 5,000 power
to Phantom Blaster Overlord,
and the critical
effect as well.
♪
Thirty eight
thousand power?
Triple critical?
(shuddering)
This is it.
♪
The end for The End.
Let's do this
Phantom Blaster Overlord.
It's time to put this
fool out of his misery!
♪
This will leave
you at seven damage,
which means the
only possible way
for you to survive
this amazing attack
is by drawing
two heal triggers.
♪
I'll show you!
Check.
♪
You'll see.
Now the second check.
There, a heal trigger.
♪
Adding 5,000 power
to The End.
♪
And I recover
one point of damage.
You should hold off
on the celebration.
♪
I've been
searching for years,
but I knew that one day
I'd have the strength
to defeat you.
♪
Now this time,
this draw,
everything changes here!
♪
You can't change destiny.
(roars)
There's always next time.
How could he lose?
It looks like you
got what you wished for.
Listen, you know
that's not how it is.
This is bigger than us.
The will of the cards
gets stronger every day.
You lost just
like I knew you would.
See, Kai, unlike you,
Psyqualia has never
once let me down.
Our friendship is
a thing of the past,
and if you really
want it back,
better build
a time machine.
So much for The End.
Look, I‐‐
Thanks for the trip
down memory lane.
I'd forgotten how good
it felt to beat you,
but my Psyqualia stands
like a wall between us.
Uh‐‐
♪
Though I suppose the real
thanks should go to you, Suiko,
for giving me this
Phantom Blaster Overlord.
♪
Huh?
You gave him a
card that strong?
Regardless of what
she did for me,
we all know it
was my abilities
that led me to
victory in that battle.
But why?
You seek to
diminish his strength,
and we can't allow that.
Then you don't care if a person
is destroyed in the process?
It's not our place
to pass judgment
on the after
effects of Psyqualia.
With only two known users,
we don't have a choice.
♪
This power will give me
everything I could ever want,
and there's not a person
on Earth who can stop me.
Not one.
(snickering)
Kai.
Ren, wait!
♪
You're gonna
have to accept
that this is the
path that he's chosen.
♪
Again.
Kai?
Stay away.
Leave me alone.
What's going on?
Ren Suzugamori has obtained
an unthinkable level of power
by abusing the
gift he's received.
He believes he can
take over the world,
and I think
he might be right.
♪
Huh?
When given the option,
Ren took the card of darkness.
Light that consumes
the darkness,
darkness that
blankets the light.
Aichi Sendou, it's time
for you to make a choice.
♪
I choose...
I can't believe Kai lost!
You're really surprised?
You don't honestly think
that someone without Psyqualia
could beat me, do you?
But he's such
a strong fighter!
Give in to your destiny,
and start using
your powers again.
You won't regret it.
The National
tournament final.
Can I really face
Ren without Psyqualia?
Next time,
"Fighting for the Top Spot".
My winning image, give me
the strength to do this!