♪
You're coming out for sure.
I need to make
room for this guy.
Hmm.
That should take care of
some of the balance issues.
Actually, wait,
on second thought.
(Kamui groans)
♪
(meows)
That's enough.
If you worry too
much about your deck,
you won't have any
energy left for tomorrow.
Hmm, just a sec.
This card has a
higher attack power,
but this one
has a better skill.
If you don't get out of here
and rest, I'll kick your butt.
Yes, ma'am!
Be back tomorrow
morning at 7:00 AM.
Gotcha!
He seems nervous.
Well, not everyone can keep
their cool like you can.
(meows)
♪
Tonight the entire
Vanguard world
is buzzing with
anticipation.
Eager to see who
takes the prize.
Team Asteroid is going for
their third straight title
against a group
of card fighters,
who, until recently,
were unknown.
I can't make sense of it.
What do you think, Dr. O?
I think in this case,
I'd put the odds in
favor of Team Asteroid.
Obviously, the
favorite to win,
they've proved their
dominance time and time again.
What is it exactly
that makes them
such a force
to be reckoned with?
That's easy!
All you have to do is take
a look at their leader.
I feel bad for Q4 cause
no matter who plays Ren,
the loss will
be overwhelming.
Interesting.
Thanks for the
analysis, Doctor.
Hmm!
♪
Aichi's really pushing it!
I mean, who does he think
he is staying out this late?
Well, I think he deserves
to hang out with his friends
and relax a bit.
(sighs)
Hey, I'm back!
Welcome home.
Hey, what's the
big idea, mister?
Sorry, Emi, long day.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
I'm not hungry,
maybe later.
I've got work to do.
Sure, you can microwave it in
a bit and eat it in your room,
but don't leave
any dishes up there.
I won't, Mom!
I worry.
He just needs a
little time to himself.
Alright.
(door opens, closes)
You can't change destiny.
♪
There's always next time.
If Kai wasn't
able to beat him...
What am I supposed to do
against Ren Suzugamori?
I always figured that
if Q4 made the finals,
it'd be Kai that
took him on, but me?
♪
Even if I have no chance,
I'm gonna give it my best shot.
♪
Ren.
You're different from me,
and yet, we're kinda
the same, aren't we?
♪
(squeaking)
(snickering)
I can't wait
to see it, Aichi.
That terrified
look in your eyes
as you realize defeat
and hopelessness.
(laughing evilly)
Misaki!
Remember those registration
forms you told me not to lose?
They're in the trunk.
Good, you passed the test.
Ah, and for
your next test,
I want you to locate
the keys to the van.
They're in your
right pocket.
Huh?
Oh, what a surprise.
You're on the ball.
♪
Take a relaxative.
Hi, Misaki!
What a great morning.
Oh, hey.
Good luck today.
I know you're gonna win.
Thanks, it's really nice
of you to come see us off.
Yeah, well, Aichi'd probably
get lost on the way over.
(chuckling)
Speaking of lost,
where's Kamui?
We need to hit the road!
But‐‐
Hold on everybody!
(panting)
How did I sleep in?
Here, yo!
We made it!
(breathing heavily)
Starting the
day with a run.
How healthy of you.
Yeah, not by choice.
Didn't I say
I'd kick your butt
if you didn't
get some sleep?
Wow, you're in rough
shape this morning.
Huh? I just got up.
But I'm feeling super good.
‐What a mess!
‐Alarm clock fail.
See, the funniest thing
happened before bed.
My deck it was on the desk
and I went to
check it one last time
and wound up completely
rebuilding it.
Well, you shoulda
been getting some sleep.
I'm unimpressed.
(sighs)
Okay, team, looks
like we're ready to go.
Huh?
Anyone seen Kai?
Actually, guys,
I don't think he's coming.
You sure about that?
Pretty sure.
Oh, well, then,
we'd better get a move on.
The three of
you have proven
you're ready for
today's challenges.
Let's do this!
‐Okay.
‐Yeah.
Wow, today of all days.
Kai's timing
really stinks.
Hey, Kamui?
Yes, ma'am?
How can I be
of service?
Can you keep
an eye on Aichi?
He seems pretty down.
Huh?
Something's really
bothering him.
Don't worry
about it, my lady!
I'll stick by his side
and keep his spirits up.
You can rest absurd
that I'll blemish the job.
I think you mean
"rest assured".
You said you're gonna
"blemish" the job.
(giggles)
Thanks, Kamui.
I'll be cheering you on,
so do your best.
Gee, that's all the
encouragement I need.
Now I'll win my
match, no prob!
And don't worry about your bro,
I'll be his personal f‐court.
That stands for
fantastic escort.
Nice save, yo.
See you after we win.
(meowing)
♪
This is it, Aichi!
We're gonna win
this thing no problem.
Huh?
Kamui.
Yeah, they aren't
gonna know what hit 'em!
Hmm.
♪
Look, I wasn't
there for you
the last time you faced
off against Asteroid.
This is my chance to make up
for letting the team down.
Huh?
It's fine to feel bad about
what happened back then,
but you've really got to‐‐
I'll forgive myself
when we beat those jerks.
It's now or never.
He's even more
high strung than usual.
Can you blame the guy?
I'm sure Kamui
isn't the only one
who's trying to
prove something.
I mean, we've got a
big score to settle too.
Hmm.
♪
Right.
‐Hmm.
♪
Man, we're gonna be
so close to the action,
my heart is beating
like a jackhammer.
Try imagining how
the members of Q4 feel.
Let's cheer our
guts out today.
Yeah, cool.
I just hope we can recruit
Morikawa to cheer with us.
So, where is that
blockhead anyway?
He must be on his way.
Right, I forgot who
I was talking about.
I'm sure he's‐‐
You'll never believe it!
Hey, take a look at
all this sweet stuff!
This limited edition Kourin
merchandise was on sale,
so I bought as much of it as
I could carry out of there!
They sold out as soon
as I left the store!
I've got a handful
of collector's items.
And we're not the
least bit surprised.
No, we're not.
Well, the best part of the
national tournament is over.
What do you mean?
Come on, you've gone crazy
if you don't think that card
fights are the best part.
Oh, man, I'm running late!
(breathing heavily)
My head.
Watch where
you're going, man.
Huh?
♪
That's Tetsu
from Team Asteroid.
♪
That's Tetsu
from Team Asteroid.
Sorry about that,
little guy.
Game's about to start.
‐Better hurry.
‐Huh?
Hey, what's the hold up?
We're late for the match.
I'm just helping a lost kid.
"A lost kid?"
Hang on a sec!
Then he didn't
even recognize me.
That jerk!
♪
‐Huh?
‐About time.
Hey, what's with
the funny costume?
(growling)
(giggling)
Come on, would it be all
right with you gentlemen
if we sat with you today?
Huh?
Well, uh, yeah, of course.
(snickering)
Hey, welcome to our broadcast
of the final match
of the Vanguard national
championship.
The stadium is sold out
and we're eagerly
awaiting the arrival
of our top two teams.
No matter what happens,
this will be a day
for the history books.
‐Now, let's get going!
‐It's so exciting!
♪
I'm trickling
with enticement.
Wait, was that a joke?
(chuckling)
We can always count on you
to ease the tension in a
moment like this, can't we?
Guys, let's
make this a day
that Team Q4 can
be really proud of.
♪
Yeah!
Right!
(crowd cheering)
There they are, folks!
Our teams have
taken the field!
Who's ready for
some card fights?
♪
Our returning champions, the
unparalleled Team Asteroid,
is about to face off against
a group of relative newcomers,
Team Q4.
(meows)
Let's take a look at the
pairings for this match.
♪
This first card fight will
feature Asteroid's Tetsu Shinjou
and Q4's Kamui Katsuragi.
♪
Hey, aren't you‐‐
Then let's get going,
cause I don't think
I can wait any longer!
I'm sure this crowd
would agree with you there,
but first things first,
we've got to take a look
at our other two matchups.
Our second
card fight of the day
will feature Asaka Narumi
versus Misaki Tokura.
Oh‐ho, those two squared
off against each other
in the last tournament,
and now Misaki Tokura's
got herself
a shot at redemption.
It's all so exciting!
Yes, but let's not forget
about our third pair.
Ren Suzugamori
versus Aichi Sendou.
♪
This'll be a blast.
(growling)
♪
Next, without
further ado,
you've seen the
card fighters.
You've made
your predictions.
It's time to get started
with the main event!
Hold on to your
hats, everybody!
Aw, you nervous?
Huh? Well,
of course, I am.
We're about to see who the best
card fighter in the world is.
And I bet you want
Aichi to win, huh?
Do you want me to
help you cheer him on?
Do whatever you want.
See? I knew Kourin
was an Aichi Sendou fan.
Have you picked
a favorite yet?
I'm not cheering for either.
It's like I said,
the cards will decide the
outcome of their battle.
The first card fight.
It looks like The General was
eager to get out onto the field!
He's one tough customer!
And his opponent,
Q4's Kamui Katsuragi
is participating in his
first national tournament.
How will he
handle the pressure?
He's shown some
great skills so far,
but there's no telling
what he'll do at this level.
Wait!
I thought he was
on the team last time.
Nope, you really
don't remember?
He had a fight with Kai,
and took off when the
team needed him most.
I forgot that.
Are you kidding?
That kid's half
Tetsu's size.
Yeah, what's a
brat doing down there?
He got matched up against
The General in the first game.
Thanks for
coming out, Junior!
You got that right.
(growling)
Take that back.
(chuckling nervously)
It's my kind of crowd.
Those guys would be happier
if I was down there
representing Team Q4.
Unbelievable.
I've heard enough from you.
Morikawa, you're
nothing but a joke!
You're a freak, yo!
I'm not a freak, pipsqueak!
Cool it, this is
important to them.
You could be a
little more sensitive
to people's feelings,
you know?
You doubt his greatness.
His dedication.
The Great Kamui has come to make
amends for his past mistakes!
He's gonna
prove to everyone
that he has the
heart of a champion.
Redemption.
It's staring him in
the face right now,
and he needs
you to cheer.
Okay, I'll cheer him on just
turn off the water works.
♪
Kamui.
I didn't recognize you
when we ran into each
other earlier, little guy.
I'm Kamui Katsuragi,
and don't you forget that!
To me, you
don't have a name
until you've proven
yourself as a card fighter.
Say what?
Come on, you two,
the whole world is
waiting for you to start!
Let's play Vanguard!
The first match begins!
(machinery whirring)
‐Stand up, my vanguard.
♪
Allow me to
kick things off.
Draw!
The Great Kamui
will ride Blau Panzer!
♪
Using Blau Junger's skill,
when I ride Blau Panzer,
I can add a copy of
Blau Kluger to my hand!
Then Blau Panzer
gains 2,000 power.
♪
And that's it for me.
Here goes.
♪
I ride Prisoner Beast!
(roars)
And by activating
Vermillion Gatekeeper's skill,
I soul charge.
Prisoner Beast
is on the attack.
Fine by me!
Drive trigger check.
♪
Damage check.
My turn is over.
♪
I figured Kai
wouldn't come.
Alright,
I stand and draw.
I'll start by
riding‐‐ huh?
♪
This guy isn't
even looking at me.
He's daydreaming
at a time like this.
What's the big deal?
Huh?
You'd better pay attention
to me, Ham Fist!
Blau Kluger!
♪
With Panzer
in the soul,
Blau Kluger gets
an extra 1,000 power.
Screaming and
dancing announcer, Shout
and Street Bouncer
to rear guard!
Buy now for four
easy payments of $49.95!
♪
I'm activating
Street Bouncer's skill.
Resting the units
in this row, I draw.
Next up, I call
Army Guy and Army Lady.
♪
Supported by Army Guy,
Army Lady is ready for action!
♪
Now, let's go Blau Kluger!
I don't guard.
Drive trigger.
♪
Damage check.
Check it, the
Shorty's on a roll!
Something's up with him.
Yeah.
Normally, he'd have a full
battle formation at this point
using Grade Zero's
to fill the empty spots.
I have to play smart
against this guy.
After watching
him beat Aichi,
I know what his deck
is capable of.
♪
(roars)
This just cant be.
What about
Soul Saver Dragon?
Witness the power
of the Stil Vampir.
For this turn,
I replace your vanguard
with the rear guard
of my choosing,
and I chose
the weakest one.
Aichi lost to that ability,
and I won't
let it happen to me.
I've got to gather the
strongest units I can find
and save the
Zero's for defense.
Interesting.
You look like the type to play
a little more recklessly.
Oh, so you can
see me after all.
Here I thought you were gonna
ignore me the whole game.
After this fight, you're
gonna remember the name
"Kamui Katsuragi" for
the rest of your life!
♪
You can do it.
Tetsu Shinjou, you may
have your sights set on Kai,
but your opponent is
right in front of you!
Underestimating me will be
the last mistake you ever make.
Here comes the
Grade School Whirlwind!
Give him what for,
your greatness!
Yeah, kick his butt!
You've got this, Kamui.
He may be strong,
but I know
you have what it takes
to win this thing.
He's exactly
where you want him.
Next time,
"Wall of The General".
Break through, Kamui,
with your winning image!