(school bell ringing)
Hey, guess what
I got here, guys!
Look, Aichi, they finally
released the flyer
for the Card Capital
Vanguard tournament!
Ha, I went by the shop
on my way to school!
Oh, yeah, you were
telling me about this
on the train
the other day.
Yep!
It's an all out
Vanguard showdown,
and between the card shop's
most skilled players.
I wonder if Kai
will be there.
Hard to tell with him.
He's not exactly
a shop regular,
so I wouldn't
count on him entering.
Well, regardless of
who decides to enter,
I think it's safe to say
we all know who's
gonna win, eh, fella?
Hopefully I still
remember who you guys are
after I rise to stardom
as a Vanguard prodigy.
(chuckling)
It says the
application deadline
for the shop tournament
is tomorrow afternoon.
Good thing
you're not entering.
Huh?
Well, that's what
you said to us
the other day, right?
Oh, yeah, he's gonna
be too busy cheering for me
to play in any games!
Well, better go practice
my victory speech.
♪
(sighs)
Huh?
Hey, what are
you looking at?
Wow, it's a
Vanguard tournament.
I didn't know
they had those.
So, are you gonna enter?
I've heard there are a lot
of really skilled players
that enter these
sorts of things.
Oh, really?
Well, then, I guess you
shouldn't even bother trying.
Cause you just started
playing not too long ago,
so there's no way
you're at that level.
If you enter
something like that,
it'll probably
just make you feel bad.
(sighs)
Yeah, you got
a point there.
Emi, can you
help me for a minute?
Coming!
♪
What was I thinking?
Me playing in
the shop tournament?
♪
But I'd sure love
to show everyone
how good my
deck is getting
now that I've
added some cards.
♪
The King of Knights, Alfred.
I'm not sure why
she gave it to me,
but this is gonna
help my Royal Paladins
shine brighter than ever.
♪
Hmm.
(grunting)
(breathing heavily)
Folks, the
Card Capital tournament
is a special event that
only happens twice per year,
and there are only two,
count 'em, two
spots available.
Is there a fighter among us
that thinks they're
up to the challenge?
Man, I'm too nervous.
I really don't think
I'm good enough yet.
I'm not surprised that
they're having trouble
getting people to
sign up for this thing.
I mean, have you
seen how many
super good players
they have already?
Players like us
don't stand a chance.
♪
Maybe I'll try out my
new deck some other time.
Hmm?
♪
Hey, Aichi!
You're here to enter the
shop tournament, right?
No, I‐‐
Sure, with the way
you've been playing lately,
I'd say that you stand just as
good a chance in this thing
as anyone else.
All you have to do
is fill this out.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
♪
No, it's scaring me
just thinking about it.
♪
Huh?
Hey, Kai.
You can count me in.
Wow, great!
I'm so glad you
could join us.
I hear you've got some
pretty good players
I haven't fought yet.
Let's just hope they
bring their A‐game.
(snickers)
♪
Well, folks, there's
only one spot left!
So, who wants it?
First come, first serve.
That'll be me!
Um, name.
Grade.
Just put it on the counter
when you're done, okay?
All finished!
Huh?
Well, looks like
I got my application in
right before you did.
Miss, please verify that my
application is acceptable.
Let's see.
Kishida Osamu, grade 10.
Oh, dear.
Excuse me, sir, but the
final spot in the tournament
was supposed to be mine
and I really want it!
That's a sad story, kid, but
you heard the shop manager.
It's first come,
first serve.
If you want to play,
you have to prove
you submitted the
application first.
♪
So, can you show me
what second, what minute,
what hour and
what day it was
when you handed in
your application, huh?
Make me a believer!
Maybe we could
just discuss it?
Either show me the proof
or get out of my face, kid,
and take that late
application with you.
But please,
listen to me!
Okay, that's enough.
It's very refreshing to see
two people get so passionate
and fired up about
our little tournament,
but all this arguing
isn't getting us anywhere.
I trust you'll
sort this mess out.
Yeah, but how?
Ah‐ha!
A commemorative event?
A fight for the
last entry spot?
Man, I wouldn't
be surprised at all
if Shin was planning to set
this up right from the start.
Hmm.
Well, you did manage to
make that sign pretty fast.
On that note, the
winner of this battle
will be able to
enter the shop tournament.
How's that sound?
Sounds great.
This seems like
a good chance
to practice my deck
before the big day.
♪
You're joking, right?
I have nothing to gain
fighting someone
as weak as you.
Kai said I was weak.
That I didn't
deserve to fight him,
but if I can enter
myself in the tournament,
I might prove him wrong.
That's the kind of chance
I'm willing to fight for.
♪
Now, for a guy who doesn't
care about Aichi Sendou,
you sure are watching
him pretty closely.
I'm actually wondering
about that other guy.
I've never seen
him play before.
Let's just see if
he's up to the challenge.
(chuckles softly)
Are the competitors
ready for the main event?
‐You bet.
‐Of course.
In that case,
let's card fight!
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
♪
That unit doesn't look like any
of the ones I'm familiar with.
Given that stare of
uncertainty on your face,
I'd say that
you've never played
against a Megacolony deck
before, have you?
Huh?
I'm gonna enjoy this fight.
Almost as much as I'll
enjoy watching you lose it.
♪
First turn.
I ride Wingal!
Using Barcgal's skill,
I move him to the rear guard.
♪
Hey, how is that guy able
to move his unit around?
That ability
can only be used
when another Royal Paladin
unit enters the battlefield.
Which is why Barcgal
is a good choice
for his starting vanguard.
‐Oh.
This match is a great chance
for Aichi to show everyone
just how much he's grown.
Barcgal, call your friends.
(snickers)
Using Barcgal's skill,
I search my deck for Flogal
and call her to
the rear guard circle.
♪
That's it for my turn.
Forgive me for
not understanding,
but why would you
even bother assembling
such a weak
group of units?
Well, not to worry.
I ride Phantom Black.
♪
And I call the Embodiment
of Armor, Bahr!
(roars)
No way!
But Bahr's not a
Megacolony unit.
(giggling)
I like to mix
and match my units.
Megacolony is my
favorite clan for sure,
but by mixing together
units of different clans,
I can take the strongest
units from each.
Thus giving my deck the
overall power advantage.
Now, Bahr against Wingal.
Attacking.
(roaring)
(grunting)
I check for a
damage trigger.
(snickers)
Next, Phantom Black
against Wingal.
Attacking.
Cannot forget
the trigger.
Check.
(yelps)
Checking damage trigger.
That's two damage.
Looks like this game
will be over pretty quick.
I won't let this guy
back me into a corner.
♪
Otherwise, I'll
never fight Kai.
♪
Hmm.
Here I go.
♪
I can beat this guy!
Stand up, my avatar!
Ride, Blaster Blade!
♪
(grunts)
I call Gallatin
to join the battle
and the little sage,
Marron, as well.
♪
I'll lend Barcgal's
support to Gallatin.
♪
And I'm attacking
Phantom Black!
♪
(yelps)
I'm checking for
a damage trigger.
I add Flogal's support
to power up Blaster Blade.
♪
Here comes another attack
against your vanguard.
♪
(grunts)
Checking for
a drive trigger.
(grunting)
Damage trigger, check.
♪
Finally, I attack
Phantom Black with Marron.
But Lizard Solider
Ganlu guards!
♪
‐Hmm.
Look, that blue haired guy
managed to even up the score.
♪
I'm so glad you're not as weak
as I first thought you were.
Now, beating you is
gonna feel so much better.
♪
Bloody Hercules, ride!
(growls)
And here's another Bloody
Hercules to deal with.
I move Bahr to the back
and into that empty
spot, Karma Queen.
Call.
♪
Karma Queen
activate counter blast.
This is my
favorite ability.
Cause I prevent Gallatin
from standing up
during your next turn.
You what?
(gasps)
Feel yourself bend under
the power of the queen!
(grunts)
♪
No way!
That lady is too strong.
Now you see the true
nature of the Megacolony.
In order to control
the battlefield,
we bind our
opponent's best units.
By preventing
you from attacking,
I practically
guarantee my own victory.
♪
Blaster Blade is
staring down the barrel
of a rear guard
Bloody Hercules attack!
♪
Guarding with Marron!
(screams)
♪
You've stopped one, but let's
see how your Blaster Blade deals
with my vanguard
Hercules attack.
♪
Don't forget
to drive check.
♪
Checking for a
damage trigger.
♪
With Bahr's support, my
Karma Queen is powered up.
Her sting is aimed
at Blaster Blade.
♪
I check for a
damage trigger.
Hmm.
Enjoy your turn,
it may be your last.
♪
With Gallatin sealed
in the front row,
he won't be launching
much of an attack.
Everything's going
according to plan.
Hmm.
What's up?
The guy with the
glasses isn't that good.
Huh?
He acts all smart,
but he hasn't figured out
why Aichi's gathering
all those weaker units.
The Royal Paladins
are about to shine.
Draw.
♪
It's finally time.
Lend me the
strength I need.
Please!
♪
Enter the fray,
kneel before your King.
I ride the King
of Knights, Alfred!
♪
You've got that card?
That's the best card in the
entire Royal Paladin clan.
I move Marron back
and then call Gancelot.
♪
With the addition of
Alfred and Gancelot‐‐
Oh, no.
Alfred rides into battle against
your vanguard, Bloody Hercules.
♪
First off, I need
to check my twin drive.
♪
And then the second check.
That's a critical trigger.
Great timing for it.
Now for the effects.
Alfred's damage just went
critical at plus one,
then Gancelot can have
the attack power boost.
As well, Alfred
has his own ability.
For each Royal Paladin
rear guard in play,
Alfred gains an extra
2,000 attack power.
Then he's getting a
10,000 attack power bonus?
♪
Now witness the
strength of King Alfred!
My Royal Paladin units are
finally working together.
♪
(shouts)
I check for a
damage trigger.
And the other one.
Oh, joy, I drew
a trigger effect!
That critical trigger
I just scored off Rakshasa
is gonna pump up my
vanguard by an extra 5,000.
Fifteen thousand power?
In that case, I'll have
Marron support Gancelot
in an attack on
Bloody Hercules.
I guard the attack.
Sorry, kid, but
you're just not good enough.
There's no way
you can win now.
I've got my own power.
Rise from the depths,
the eight legs of evil,
ride, Hell Spider!
Hell Spider
counter blast active,
which means on
your next turn,
Gallatin won't be
able to stand up.
(grunts)
Hell Spider has
that ability too?
(groaning)
It's really unfortunate
that I can't use
it on your vanguard,
cause it would
be so much fun
to get Alfred in
a web right now.
I call a pair
of Phantom Blacks.
♪
I support Hercules
with Phantom Black.
In an attack on Alfred.
Future Knight Liew
will guard that.
♪
Let's see how
you like this one.
Hell Spider
with support.
And once again,
I attack your vanguard.
(yells)
I guard with Isolde!
I activate
Isolde's defense skill
by dropping Wingal
from my hand,
completely protecting
Alfred from harm.
♪
(grunting)
Fine then, I'm checking
the first twin drive card.
Second twin drive card.
Whatever!
With my last move,
I'm gonna send
Karma Queen
at King Alfred
with the
support of four!
I'll use Elaine
to block your attempt.
♪
Even that couldn't
break through.
All those great
attacks were for nothing.
This isn't going
like I planned it.
‐Oh ho.
‐Hmm.
I retire Gallatin
and call Wingal instead.
Why'd he replace a Grade Two
with a lower Grade unit?
That Gallatin wouldn't be able
to attack this turn anyway,
but now Wingal can.
(grunts in frustration)
He's got three
attacks again.
Gancelot, with the support of
Marron, will attack Hell Spider.
♪
Aermo will guard him, as well,
I intercept with Hercules.
Huh?
♪
Ha ha, your attack
fails under the weight
of my amazing
defensive double play.
Well, since Gallatin was tied
up, Wingal attacks for him.
(growls)
Supported by Barcgal,
he attacks your vanguard.
♪
(yells)
Checking for
a damage trigger.
♪
That makes five damage.
This is my final attack.
Your puny Hell Spider is
no match for King Alfred!
My Royal Paladins
lend their strength
giving 10,000 attack power.
♪
(moans)
(whimpers)
That was a great fight.
There you go, folks!
Aichi Sendou has just
claimed the final spot
in the Card
Capital tournament.
(crowd cheering)
(meows)
Twas an excellent
battle we just had.
Huh?
With your skills
and that deck,
I'd say the rest of
the tournament players
better watch their backs.
Based on my calculations,
I believe you have an 85% chance
of winning the entire thing.
That's great, but how exactly
did you come to that conclusion?
Let's not
worry about it!
I wish you the
best of luck.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Aichi.
I'm expecting big things
from you at the tournament.
Right.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Now that we're both
in the shop tournament,
we may get a chance
to play each other again.
Using Alfred like that
was a lowly beginner's
strategy for winning.
Simple tactics aren't
gonna get you very far
in a tournament setting.
Remember that.
♪
Don't listen to him, buddy.
You did great today.
♪
I don't care
what you say, Kai.
Cause I'm gonna win my way
right to the top of this thing.
Until I fight you together
with the strength of my cards.
♪
What's going on?
You need courage to take
that first step, right?
I'm so nervous, I don't
know what I'm doing anymore.
You're so calm, Misaki.
I bet this never
happens to you.
That's not true.
I feel anxious too.
Next time, "The Shop
Tournament begins!"
I'm actually entering
the shop tournament.
Picture it, picture it.
But everything I picture
is negative!
Like I said,
it's not just you.
Everyone feels
the same way.