♪
(heavy breathing)
I'm burning up.
It's not even 8:00
in the morning.
Why does it have
to be so hot?
It's summer, yo.
Oh.
Would you stop
wasting your breath
saying, "Yo," all the time?
You're just making it hotter.
I'm not wasting
my breath, yo.
I told you to
stop saying that!
I can say whatever I want,
and there's not a thing
you can do about it, yo.
You think so?
Yeah, yo.
Hey, how about
you two stop acting
like a couple of babies?
‐Take a hike!
What did you say?
‐Oh, uh, hi, Kamui.
Why aren't you
at Card Capital?
We're not leaving
for a while,
so I thought I'd
come see you off.
But, listen, you guys
are gonna have
a long train ride today,
so you better stop arguing.
Besides, who could be upset
with all this beautiful
weather we're having?
Beautiful, huh?
Kamui, aren't you
feeling the heat at all?
Now that you mention it,
I am pretty toasty.
But this scorching weather
is just what we needed.
What do you mean?
It's the blazing hot start
to the national tournament!
Oh, right.
I still don't get it, yo.
If the other teams think
they're sweating now,
just wait till they
get a load of us.
♪
Oh, man, it's gonna
take hours to get there.
It's got to be nice that you
don't have to come with us
on the smelly, old train, yo.
Trust me, it's not
as good as it sounds.
You haven't seen
Shin's driving.
(sneezing)
(sniffing)
I can't believe all of
you guys are gonna try
to pile into that
tiny van for the trip.
Don't forget about
their bags and Kai's ego.
It's gonna be a
tight squeeze, yo.
Ha, do me a favor,
and don't even mention
that jerk in front of me.
Not a fan of Mr. Mean?
As if.
I finally made
it to nationals,
but the fact that I
have to play with him
makes me wish we'd
never gotten this far.
(sighing)
Hmm!
♪
Hey, bro, how's it going?
Oh, hey, I didn't
see you there.
(chuckling)
(grunting)
‐Huh?
‐Hmm.
Well, it looks like
everyone's here.
What do you say, guys,
should we hit the road?
I call shotgun.
Uh, sorry, Kamui,
you can't sit up front.
Misaki needs that spot.
What?
He won't be able to find the
way there without my help.
If you don't know the roads,
just buy a GPS or a map,
you great for something.
I'm sorry, were you trying
to call me a
"good‐for‐nothing"?
Yeah, that's the one.
Why should I buy a GPS
when Misaki can
memorize the directions?
I guess you got
a point there.
Hmm, I win.
Eh, like I care.
I'll just grab one of
the back window seats.
Ugh, you're kidding me!
What now?
You're sitting in my seat!
‐Really?
‐Oh, so now you're gonna act
like you don't know
what I'm talking about.
Listen, Kai, I always
sit by the window.
Like I care.
Ah!
It's okay.
There's another window
seat on this side.
You can both have one.
(yawning)
(chuckling)
All right, team, here we go.
♪
Take that right turn.
Sure thing.
I said, "Right!"
Huh?
Ah!
(meowing)
Some driver.
(gulping)
Oh, boy, that hits the spot.
(train horn blaring)
♪
‐Wow!
‐No way!
I'm pretty sure this
is the back entrance.
Seriously?
The tournament hall for
the regional championships
was impressive,
but it's nothing
compared to this stadium.
What do you expect?
This is the
nationals, after all,
and I'd say it's probably
gonna be a sold‐out crowd.
Whoa.
I'm gonna go drive
around for a bit
and try to find a place
to park this thing.
You guys hang tight
here till I get back.
Sounds good.
Ten bucks says he gets
lost and doesn't make it.
Guess we'll be
taking the train home.
No thanks.
Huh?
What's that all about?
Oh, that's just one
of the network crews
that'll be around
filming stuff
for the live television
broadcast later today.
What, you're kidding?
They always show the
Vanguard Nationals on TV.
Haven't you seen it before?
No.
Hey, take a look, you guys!
I think that might be
Dr. O over there.
(indistinct chattering)
Which means Vanguard
TV must be here!
Come on, bro, let's
go see if we can get
his autograph or something.
I've always wanted to
meet a famous person,
and here's my chance!
All right, follow me!
Kamui!
I'm sorry, I didn't
see you there.
That looked bad.
Hmm?
♪
"Ancient Roman History"?
Hey, are you
gonna be all right?
Don't worry, bro,
I'll be just fine.
Oh, thank goodness.
"Oh, thank goodness."
You're not getting off
that easy, you big oaf!
It feels like I
just got run over
by a dump truck
full of rocks.
You're right, it was
super careless of me
to get run into like
that all of a sudden.
Please, accept my
most humble apology.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
lost my temper.
Sorry for running into you
and blaming you for it.
He didn't mean to.
What's going on, Koutei?
Are you getting us
into trouble?
It's okay, we just had a
little accident, that's all.
Are you okay, little guy?
Did you get hurt anywhere?
Little guy?
Don't talk down to me
like I'm some kid.
That sure is a nasty
scrape on your elbow.
Hold on a second,
I'm pretty sure I have
a bandage with me.
It's no big deal, so just
give it a rest, all right?
Oh, no, you're injured?
I feel really bad about this.
Everything's fine.
Here.
Oh, great, thank you.
Okay.
Who's a big, brave boy?
Yeah, well,
don't expect me to thank you.
You're welcome anyway.
(chuckling)
Just sad.
Huh?
(grunting)
Just great, you
knocked me over,
and now I don't
get to meet Dr. O!
Oh, as if it wasn't
bad enough already.
I'm really sorry.
Could he be any nicer?
Hmm, those kids.
What do you think
they're up to?
Looks like they're
arguing with another team.
I don't know how
long they'll last
if they go around
picking fights.
I wonder.
Wait, I just realized
who they're talking to.
What are the chances?
You're Team Caesar?
So, you've heard
of them before?
Are you kidding me, bro?
They were last
year's runner‐up,
and the year before, they
were national champions!
I had no idea.
Hey, look, everyone.
It's Team Caesar.
Oh, so the former
champions have returned then.
I bet they're looking
to get some revenge.
I think we should
go find a place
that's a little less crowded.
I'd rather not have all
these eyes staring at me.
Huh.
They must be really strong.
Oh, no, our bags!
Sorry, we just need a minute!
Amazing, it's like they were
meant to meet or something.
It's only a coincidence.
Was it fate or
just dumb luck?
We'll know the answer
to that question
once this tournament is over.
Right.
What do you mean?
This spot's better.
Isn't it about time you
got over your stage fright?
I just don't like it
when people look at me.
And, yet, when thousands of
fans are watching you play,
you're totally fine.
What a strange guy.
I don't think
we had the chance
to properly
introduce ourselves.
The name's Kenji Mitsusada,
and I'm the leader
of Team Caesar.
Just call me Yuri.
She's my big sister.
They call me Gai.
Wait, so your name's
Kenji Mitsusada?
I thought you called him
by a different name earlier.
Oh, yeah, Koutei.
‐Koutei?
‐Yeah.
It's a nickname he
got when we were kids.
So I guess you've been
friends for a long time.
So what's the reason for you
calling yourselves
"Team Caesar"?
Yeah, good question.
I guess I should explain,
otherwise you'll
wind up thinking
we're named after a
salad or something.
See, nearly 2,000 years ago,
this guy named Julius Caesar
lived in Ancient Rome
and he was a
powerful general who‐‐
Spare us the lecture.
But I was about to
get to the good part.
Yeah, well, I don't
want to hear any parts,
good, bad, or otherwise.
Fine, how about we settle for
the story of Octavius then?
Kidding.
Basically, Koutei is a huge
fan of Ancient Roman history,
so we named ourselves after
one of their
greatest emperors.
That makes sense, right?
Sure does.
(screaming)
It's my Kourin!
Morikawa's here?
(chuckling)
Finally, my collection
of Ultra Rare
limited‐edition
merchandise is complete!
I've just accomplished
all I set out to do today.
So that was your whole reason
for coming to the
national tournament?
I guess cheering for Team Q4
will have to take a back seat.
Don't look too
jealous there, guys.
This little baby just
gave me a huge boost
to my Ultra Rare
fan club points,
which pretty much means
I'm the best boyfriend ever,
if I'm not mistaken.
Hey, Aichi, look at all
the cool stuff I got!
Give it a rest, man.
Try and stop me!
Annoying as he is,
there's something reflexing
about seeing him here,
‐you know?
‐Relaxing?
Having some friendly faces
around really
puts you at ease.
Hardly.
That reminds me, weren't Reiji
and Eiji gonna come today?
Oh, no, I hope those two
didn't take the wrong train.
Actually, if Morikawa
managed to make it,
I'm sure they won't have any
problems finding their way.
Good call.
Watch what you say
about me, Kamui,
or I'll have to
come over there!
Could he actually hear me?
Nah, he probably just
assumed you said it.
Impressive.
Totally.
Hmm, weird, I feel like
we're forgetting something.
Where is everyone?
I told you to wait
here and you didn't.
♪
(cheering)
♪ Nothing could
be stopping me ♪
♪ I don't care,
whatever, you see ♪
♪ (indistinct lyrics) ♪
♪ Don't tell me what to do ♪
♪ If you live in
this magic moment ♪
♪ Open your arms
and sing, the moment
will just be worthwhile ♪
♪ Look in the eyes
on their lives ♪
♪ Having no sparkle, why ♪
♪ And I swear ♪
♪ I'm just me, ain't
gonna be anyone else ♪
♪ But if inside my heart ♪
♪ How this fire
makes you smile ♪
I love you!
Cheer louder, guys,
and put on that robe!
‐Me too?
‐Obviously.
This is the whole
reason we came, right?
‐As if!
Wow, they're putting
a lot more effort
into the opening
ceremonies this year.
You mean it's not
always like this?
Well, they do their best
to make it exciting,
but this is taking it
to a whole new level.
‐I mean...
‐Kourin!
...a concert by Ultra
Rare is pretty big.
If they plan on doing
the same thing next year,
I'll be sure to bring
some ear plugs.
This might not be
our type of music,
but it looks like
those guys are having
the time of their lives.
Uh, did she just call me
one of these guys?
The men of Earth can't
get enough of Ultra Rare!
Nonsense.
Which one of you called
my Ultra Rare "nonsense"?
Calm down, Morikawa.
I didn't hear anyone over
there say that sort of thing.
Really, 'cause I
could have sworn
I heard someone
say that, or did I?
He acts without thinking,
and then immediately
doubts himself.
This guy's ridiculous.
Hey, what's it like being
on a team with four players?
Do your top three players
hog all the action,
or does everyone
get a chance?
Huh?
Do you change up your order
based on who your
opponent is or...
Or maybe you guys don't
waste time thinking about it.
Well, we, uh...
I forgot.
We'll be fighting as
a three‐person team
just like at the
regional tournament.
Misaki wasn't there
last time, so she's in.
Between Kai and Kamui, I don't
think I can steal a spot.
Guess I'm sitting out.
Give it a rest, Gai.
It's rude to poke your nose
into another team's strategy.
Oh.
It doesn't matter.
‐Huh?
‐Hmm?
Deciding who plays doesn't
involve any strategy.
It's easy, the weakest
player on our team
will always sit out.
And that's final.
‐Oh, yeah?
‐Problem?
How about you show some
respect to your teammates?
Hmm.
Calm down, guys, there's
no need to get angry.
Look, this is
Team Q4 business,
and I'd appreciate it if
you kept out, all right?
Uh, sure.
I don't care about
you or this team.
‐That's it.
‐It's okay, Kamui.
‐Come on, bro.
‐I know I'm not gonna get
the chance to play.
Kai's right, we should
have our top three players
representing the team
whenever possible.
And with the way
you guys play,
we all know who
the weakest link is.
I don't mind.
Are you sure?
That settles it then.
(grunting)
There's something
I need to know, Kai.
Why does a guy like you
even play Vanguard anyway?
The thrill of taking a strong
player and destroying them.
That's the whole reason
I play this game.
Is that all?
Yeah.
Well then.
♪
You know, the whole reason I
started going to Card Capital
is that there wasn't
anywhere else for me to play.
I needed to get
myself as far away
from Team Handsome as possible,
so I decided to try card
fighting at a different store.
I was only in it for myself.
I didn't care about the
team or the rest of you,
as long as we won our games.
But all that's changed now
'cause I know we have
something special.
I want us to win this
tournament together.
I don't get you.
You don't care about anybody.
If she wants to quit,
I say we let her do it.
But, Kai...
You act like she's the
only one with a past.
If she's gonna use a car
accident as an excuse
for her own weakness,
then we don't need her.
How can you act so heartless
to the people
around you, Kai?
(sighing)
I guess being on this team
doesn't mean anything
to you, does it?
Forget the team.
When I'm card fighting,
none of you matter to me.
That's it.
Kamui.
That's the last draw.
Straw?
Bro, I hate to do this to ya,
but there's just no way
I can bring myself
to fight alongside a
jerk like him anymore.
Sorry.
‐I quit!
‐No, Kamui, wait!
Huh?
‐What's going on?
‐Beats me.
Oh!
Oh, good!
I've been looking
all over the place.
It took me
forever to find you.
I'm sorry, I can't
stay and talk.
I'm in a hurry right now.
Oh, you gotta use the
bathroom or something?
Hold on, you can't leave.
Now that the concert's over,
it's time for all
the teams to head out
onto the tournament floor
and draw the pairings
for the first round.
Wow, we're starting already?
(grunting)
Let's not waste any time.
♪
Come on, Aichi.
Hmm, you mean...
Now that Kamui's
out of the picture,
we're down to three members,
so if you don't come with us,
then Team Q4 is
gonna have to forfeit.
Is that what you want?
Wait, Kamui quit the team?
What happened
while I was gone?
‐I don't know.
‐Not sure.
No clue.
Want my advice?
Koutei?
You know that is just the
first day of the tournament
and the big games don't
happen until next week, right?
‐Uh, yeah?
‐Well, the games
you're about to play
are elimination matches,
and if your team loses,
you won't be able to
compete in the finals.
You just need to see how
much is on the line here.
♪
I know you want to chase
after your friend right now,
but if you don't play today,
there won't be a team
for him to come back to.
Sometimes doing what's
right isn't easy.
I guess so.
Good choice,
'cause that's what
being on a team is all about.
Yeah, totally.
(sighing)
Oh, no, I think this
is the rear entrance.
Oh, man, I thought you said
this was gonna be
a shortcut, yo.
(panting)
We're so late, I bet the
tournament's already started.
Not to worry, I checked
the schedule online,
and it looks like we're
gonna be just in time.
Huh, hey, that's Kamui.
Wait for us!
Can you show us where
the entrance is, yo?
I'm exhausted.
Really, you don't get
excited singing for everyone?
I just don't have the energy
for this kind of thing.
Oh, it's 'cause
you're old, right?
That's enough.
Just for that, I'm gonna
sing all your lines
in our next
performance, Rekka.
No, but that's not fair!
What's this?
Suiko?
Oh.
He's from that team.
You think they...
...had a fight?
(knocking)
We need you back on stage in
a couple of minutes, ladies.
Please be ready.
‐Sounds good.
‐Let's go!
And, now, allow me
to introduce you
to the master of ceremonies
you all know and love.
It's me, of course, MC Mya!
Nobody likes you,
so get off the stage,
you lousy waste of space!
Listen up, four eyes!
We don't need to hear
you blathering on
with your phony excitement,
so why don't do your job
and just get Ultra Rare
back on the stage?
There's always a critic.
Hurry up, and get
Kourin back on the stage!
Really?
And stop holding
the mic like that!
Not you, too.
These guys.
Without further ado,
it's time we said hello
to my lovely
co‐host for the day.
It's Rekka, Suiko, and Kourin.
Here they are,
folks, Ultra Rare!
(cheering)
♪
I've waited so long
for this moment, Kourin.
Yeah, how long?
Dude, it's only been
about ten minutes.
But those ten
minutes apart from her
were like ten long years
on a desert island.
‐Yeah, yeah.
What a great day for a
Vanguard Tournament, right?
Right!
Okay, everyone on this side,
make some noise for me.
(cheering)
Come on, people, you can cheer
louder than that, can't you?
(cheering)
That's the spirit, everyone!
Now let's play some Vanguard!
(cheering)
♪
Well, I'm glad
they didn't forfeit
after working so
hard to get here.
Koutei, you've got
to learn to stay out
of other people's business.
I couldn't agree more.
Start paying attention to
our team and the games ahead,
or we'll lose our
matches and blame you.
Oh, you're too kind, Yuri.
Now, let's show
those guys who's boss.
(laughing)
♪
Hold on, Kamui.
I know how badly you wanted
to play in this tournament.
That's why I'll do
everything in my power
to get us to the finals.
Your team will be
waiting for you.
♪
What are we gonna
do about Kamui?
Did you forget what
Team Caesar told us?
Oh, yeah, the thing
we should focus on
is making it to the finals,
so let's do our best
to win some matches.
You can count on me.
Thanks, Misaki.
Next time, "Jurassic Army."
I'm imagining myself winning
the first match for my team.
I'm focused, calm, and ready.
Aichi Sendou to the rescue.