(sighing)
Hi, you guys.
(meowing)
Hey there.
Took you long enough.
Where's Misaki?
Oh, she wasn't
feeling very well,
so I told her to
just take the day off.
That's too bad.
Hey, bro, I guess
we might as well
take the day off, too.
Yeah.
(sighing)
♪
Mommy, Daddy?
They can't be.
(crying)
♪
(sighing)
The day of the
regional tournament
was the anniversary of
her parents' car crash.
No wonder she
couldn't make it.
Yeah.
Imagine living with
the constant reminder
that your parents are gone.
Looks like having
a good memory
isn't quite what we thought.
Yeah.
I can't believe I
kept talking about
how much easier her life
must be because of it.
I suggested turning her brain
into a weapon for Team Q4.
And here I thought
Misaki was just being lazy
when she didn't show up to the
regional tournament on time.
What are we supposed to do?
All right, we need to focus.
The nationals are
right around the corner.
We've got to convince
her to rejoin the team.
Ah, if only there was a way
we could get a hold of
her outside the shop.
You guys have officially
ruined my afternoon nap.
So what?
Sorry, but Misaki
quit the team,
and I thought maybe
you could help us
figure out what to do.
Help us, and you can
go back to your naptime.
She should quit.
Huh?
If she wants to quit,
I say we let her do it.
But, Kai...
You act like she's the
only one with a past.
If she's gonna use a car
accident as an excuse
for her own weakness,
then we don't need her.
You've got some nerve
saying that kind of
thing about her.
She's our teammate!
Whether you like it or not,
we're in this thing
together, you big jerk!
‐Hmm.
‐Ah.
♪
What's his problem?
I don't know.
♪
I'm home.
Oh, hi, Aichi.
‐Hey.
‐You're home early.
With the nationals coming up,
I thought that you'd be
playing over at Card Capital
with your friends
until way later.
Aichi?
(door closing)
‐What's the matter?
‐Don't know.
Emi, where are you off to?
♪
(meowing)
And there we go.
Misaki!
I know you're not
working today,
but would you
come down to help
set up the new cards, please?
Please?
Hmm, I don't think she heard.
(meowing)
Looks like it's just
you and me, Assisticat.
(whimpering)
I feel so helpless right now.
I wish there was
something I could do.
(meowing)
Don't be so rough with it or
you'll rip the cards inside!
Who's a good kitty?
♪
Oh.
Right on!
The new booster packs and
constructed decks are here.
‐Hello.
‐Hey, look who it is.
Sorry, I'm trying
to find Misaki.
(indistinct chattering)
There you are!
Emi, hi.
‐What's up?
‐Well, actually,
there's something I
really want to ask you,
but I don't know if I should.
It's okay.
What is it?
Aichi seems really sad.
He's been so excited about
the national tournament,
but now he's acting weird.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
The way he's been acting,
I thought maybe he could be
having problems with the team,
and I wanted to see if
you knew anything about it.
Sorry, Emi, I can't help.
Oh, that's okay.
Thanks anyway, I'll
go check with Kamui.
Hey, now, you came
all the way down here,
so you might as
well stick around.
Besides, we just got an
exciting shipment of new cards.
Ooh, can I take a look?
Sure, Meteor Break Wizard,
Goddess of Flower
Divination, Sakuya;
Sword Dancer Angel.
Then we've got Dark Cat,
Battle Sister, Maple;
and this one's Victory Maker.
I can't believe how cute
all these cards are!
Right, Misaki?
Sure thing.
I bet they'd be super strong
in a real card fight,
don't you think?
Would you like
to try them out?
‐Mmhmm.
‐You can play her.
Who, me?
Sorry, I'm not really in
the mood for that right now.
Come on, please, Misaki.
(groaning)
(meowing)
As always, we'll be using
the aptly named
standing fight table.
Hey, Misaki,
where's your deck?
♪
I can't.
I'm quitting the team.
You'll have to go to
nationals without me.
(meowing)
Uh, Shin, I don't...
There's no need to worry.
I've got it in a safe place.
But for today, look!
New decks to use.
Constructed decks?
That's right.
Here, Emi's gonna be playing
with an Oracle
Think Tank deck,
and now, for you,
Nova Grapplers.
What's a constructed deck?
It's a special deck
that's ready to play
right out of the box.
So why do people
build their own
when they can just
buy a premade one?
Most players enjoy the
amount of time and effort
that goes into
building their deck.
The manufacturers have put
the same love into these ones
to ensure that even new
card fighters can play.
They love the cards?
♪
(groaning)
Misaki?
Well, the cards
are all you need,
so I'll be taking back
those empty boxes,
if you don't mind.
Mm, I'm just fine, Emi.
Well, are you ready to start?
Yeah!
(sighing and meowing)
Hmm.
♪
(sighing)
Stand up, my Vanguard.
I'm going first.
I ride Oasis Girl.
(giggles)
Battleraizer moves
to the rear guard.
That's all for me.
Okay, it's my turn.
Here it goes.
Hmm.
I ride Battle Sister, Maple.
♪
Lozenge moves back.
And, then, I call
the Black Kitty!
Duh!
Uh, that's called "Dark Cat,"
Emi, not Black Kitty.
Well, it sure looks like
a black kitty, doesn't it?
(meowing)
Hmm.
It's Pink Doggy!
That one's called
"Flogal," sweetie.
Oh.
So that's your name.
Now I need to attack.
Uh, hold on.
Huh?
When Dark Cat
comes into play,
you check to see if there's
an Oracle Think Tank unit
in the Vanguard Circle.
Since Maple is
from that clan,
we both get to draw
an extra card.
Oh, that's right.
Hmm.
Now I'll have Dark Cat
attack your Oasis Girl.
(shouting)
Damage check.
Attacking with Maple.
Huh?
Aw, she doesn't
have enough power.
It's okay.
Whenever Maple attacks,
as long as you have four
or more cards in your hand,
she gets an extra
3,000 attack power.
Oh, great!
(gasping)
Drive trigger check.
(grunting)
Damage trigger check.
Has she already memorized
the abilities
of the new cards?
I don't even know
half of them.
You're really
something, Misaki.
That's all for me.
Now it's your turn.
But even with
that amazing memory,
you're forgetting what's
right in front of you.
I draw.
And I ride Super
Electromagnetic Lifeform, Storm.
I call Prototype, Minotaur,
and Oasis Girl, too.
Uh, sorry, but you're
sleeping on the box I need.
Pretty please?
(meowing)
♪
With support from Dark Cat,
I'll have Sword Dancer
Angel attack your Vanguard.
Cannon Ball will guard.
♪
What?
Then, I guess I'll, um...
I'm sorry.
I wasn't gonna use you,
but I need your help.
Lozenge Magus supports my
other Sword Dancer Angel.
♪
(grunting and shouting)
Drive trigger check.
(yelling)
Damage trigger check.
(sighing)
Lozenge had to leave.
Oh, that's right.
You didn't want to attack
with that card last time
because you'd have to shuffle
her back into your deck.
That's 'cause I like
having her around.
Is that so?
Well, I can see why you'd
get attached to the units
that fight for you.
Now, my turn.
First, I stand and draw.
I ride Death Metal Droid.
(shouting)
I move Battering Minotaur
back and call Storm.
With support
from Battleraizer,
I'll have NGM Prototype
attack your Vanguard,
Sword Dancer Angel.
Thanks to
Battleraizer's support skill,
an extra 3,000 power will
be added to this attack.
♪
Ah!
Next, I'll have
Death Metal attack,
supported by Oasis Girl.
Now, does Death Metal...
Counterblast.
Adding 3,000 power.
It's up to 20,000.
Hmm.
I don't have the right cards
to stop this from
getting through.
Next, I'll check
the Twin Drive.
Oh.
Second check, stand
trigger activated.
Huh?
With this, I get to give a
unit a 5,000 power bonus.
Storm is still standing
and ready to attack.
It goes to him.
That leaves the stand effect
which is going
to NGM Prototype.
I wonder how Emi
will respond.
Ah!
Damage trigger.
Here we go.
With Minotaur's support,
I'll have Storm
attack your Vanguard.
(grunting)
Next, I activate
Storm's skill.
When he lands an attack
on my opponent's Vanguard,
I can flip over one
card in the damage zone.
Are you done?
Not quite.
Don't forget this guy.
I attack your Sword Dancer
with NGM Prototype.
(giggling)
Um, wait, my Dream
Eater will guard that!
♪
Great defending, Emi.
Misaki isn't
holding back at all.
She's going full force.
To end the turn,
I'll put Battleraizer
back into my deck
and then shuffle it.
(sighing)
You're doing well.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're already on your way
to becoming a really
good card fighter,
so there's no reason
for me to go easy on you.
Huh, yeah.
There's so much I still need
to learn about the game,
but, you know, I'm
having a lot of fun.
Fun, huh?
Are you having fun, Misaki?
You sure like looking
at those, don't you?
Mmhmm, there's so many
neat things to learn.
Misaki told me last night
that she remembers
all the cards.
She has a great memory.
Yeah, she must get it
from her old man.
No, she gets it from me.
Not a chance.
Honey, you can't even remember
the shop's phone number.
‐Yeah, but...
‐And when you're driving,
if I'm not there to tell you
where to go, you get lost.
(grunting)
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Ah, well,
there they go again.
Let's go, manager!
Beat him, old lady!
Who are you calling "old"?
In the last month,
Mom's won 45 card fights,
but Dad's only
beaten her 14 times.
At least try and win half
your matches, old man!
That's "manager" to you!
(laughing)
♪
Wait.
Mom and Dad were
both so happy.
And I was too.
Let's see.
When this unit is called
to the Vanguard Circle,
all of your Oracle Think
Tank units in the rear guard
are returned to your hand.
I ride the Goddess of
Flower Divination, Sakuya,
sending these two
cards back to my hand.
Then I call two
Sword Dancer Angels,
as well as a Black
Kitty to rear guard.
When Black Kitty‐‐when
Dark Cat enters play,
if an Oracle Think Tank unit
is in my Vanguard Circle,
then we can both draw a card.
That activates Sword Dancer
Angel's battle skill.
When I draw a card, her
power goes up by 1,000.
Next, I call Gemini
and Weather Girl, Milk.
♪
For my first attack,
I'll have Dark Cat
support Sword Dancer Angel.
I guard that with
Ring Girl, Clara.
Hmm.
I attack with
my Vanguard next.
Milk's support gives her
a total of 16,000 power.
♪
Twin Drive check.
First.
Second.
Ahh!
I check for damage.
I attack one more time
with my other Sword Dancer.
I'll use
Battleraizer to guard.
(sighing)
All that, and I was only
able to deal one damage.
Don't worry, Emi,
you're doing a great job.
Remember, this is
only your second game,
and you're playing so well.
If you keep at it,
there's no telling
how good you could get.
(meowing)
Really?
You think if I
work really hard,
that one day, I could
be as good as Misaki?
Dad, do you think if
I practice really hard
that I might be as
good as you one day?
Oh, I know you will.
In fact, I wouldn't
be surprised at all
if you got way
better than I am.
If card fighting is
really what you want to do,
I know you'll be
amazing at it.
Every match will
make you stronger,
and with the right
friends to challenge you,
who knows your potential?
You could even make it to
the national championship.
Could you imagine?
Everyone at Card Capital
would be there
to cheer her on.
And I'd be standing out in
the crowd with a huge banner.
A banner?
Yeah, a gigantic one!
Bigger than a bus!
So you want to become
the same kind of card
fighter as Misaki, do ya?
Yeah, I've got to get
strong enough to beat Aichi.
The old Aichi had
a really tough time.
He was always
getting picked on
by the other kids at school.
But now he's got a lot
of great friends,
and he's off to compete
in the national tournament.
It all sounds so fun!
When you put it
like that, Emi,
I know that I made
the right choice
giving you that
constructed deck to play with.
Huh?
Just like I said.
A lot of love went
into selecting the cards
in that deck, so that
even a new player like you
could enjoy this great
game to its fullest.
Oh!
My own deck?
Yeah, I poured my heart and
soul into building that deck,
and each card in it was
chosen especially for you.
Thanks, Dad, I love it.
Oh!
(giggling)
Is it my turn?
First, I call King of Sword,
I retire NGM Prototype,
and then I call
Queen of Heart.
Why?
The king attacks with
the queen's support.
Her skill adds 4,000 power.
I intercept with
Sword Dancer Angel.
We'll protect
Sakuya at any cost.
Ah!
All this time,
those were the memories
I should have
been focusing on.
I attack with Death Metal.
♪
Ah, well,
there they go again.
Let's go, manager!
Beat him, old lady!
Who are you calling "old"?
(laughing)
♪
There were a lot
of happy times.
Twin Drive check.
Checking damage trigger.
I attack with Super
Electromagnetic Lifeform, Storm.
I get so sad sometimes
that I forget about
all the amazing years
I spent with them.
If card fighting is
really what you want to do,
I know you'll be
amazing at it.
Every match will
make you stronger,
and with the right
friends to challenge you,
who knows your potential?
You could even make it to
the national championship.
Oh!
My own deck?
Yeah, I poured my heart and
soul into building that deck,
and each card in it was
chosen especially for you.
♪
Hmm, too bad.
It was fun playing you.
We should do it again some‐‐
(crying)
Misaki?
♪
Misaki.
Uncle, that treasure box.
I can't, I...
I don't have the key.
The deck my dad built
for me is locked inside.
He put his whole
heart into making it.
Help me find the key.
Please, Shin.
Hmm.
I always knew you'd
remember it someday.
You want to know why I've
been holding on to this?
Because I knew it unlocked
something very special.
Oh.
Thanks, Uncle.
♪
I'll go first.
I was a real jerk.
You were a jerk?
I was two times the
jerk that you were.
We can't afford
to lose Misaki
as a friend and a teammate.
Okay, let's do this.
Misaki, you've
got to forgive us!
My actions were
completely unacceptable!
Same with mine!
Please don't quit the team or
stop being friends with us!
(meowing)
Huh?
You're late.
♪
The devastation.
Is she on a rampage?
Aichi, it was so amazing.
Misaki just defeated
everyone in the store.
Seriously, not a
single one of them
posed the slightest
challenge for me.
How am I supposed to
train for nationals
if this is the trash
I'm up against?
You said nationals!
You mean we're a team again?
Yeah, but spare me
the tearful reunion.
You, me, card fight, now.
Ah!
Sure thing!
Oh, yeah!
I'm up first.
I'm not gonna go easy on ya.
(meowing)
Well, are you good?
Yeah.
All right, stand up,
my Vanguard.
♪
Hey, Misaki, you want to
have another card fight?
Why not, it's good practice
playing against you.
Great, so for the
national tournament,
we're gonna drive
again, right?
Yeah, I've memorized
how to get there,
so we're all covered.
Just one glance at the map,
and you become an
instant navigator.
That's incredible!
Oh, I'm sorry, please don't
take that the wrong way.
Next time,
"A Stormy Beginning!
The National Championship!"
I'm imagining new encounters.
Kamui, please, you've
got to control yourself!