Using Pongal's skill,
I counterblast,
adding Soul Saver
Dragon to my hand.
♪
Now I'm ready.
Koutei, prepare
to feel the wrath
of the Royal Paladins
at full force!
♪
I can see right through you.
I'm charging at you with
Knight of Friendship Kay.
♪
Kay gets an extra 3,000 power
when Blaster Blade
is my Vanguard.
Enigman Ripple will guard that.
♪
(grunts)
Here comes my avatar
with a boost from Marron.
♪
I don't guard.
Drive trigger check.
♪
(shouts)
Damage trigger check.
Gaining support
from Wingal Brave.
The Knight of Loyalty
Bedivere attacks.
He also gains 3,000 power when
my Vanguard is Blaster Blade.
(grunts)
Guide Dolphin
will guard that.
♪
I end my turn.
I only managed to get
one damage through.
But my next attack
is gonna be massive.
♪
With Soul Saver
Dragon in hand,
and the positioning
of his units,
he's getting ready
to end this game.
♪
Aichi, you never
cease to amaze me.
Hm.
It's a winning strategy.
Your only mistake was thinking
I'd let you get away with it.
♪
I stand and draw.
Being of pure power,
descend on my foes.
I ride Enigman Storm.
(roars)
And then I call...
♪
Supported by Cosmo Roar,
Masked Police Grander
attacks the Knight
of Loyalty Bedivere.
Hitting my rear‐guard?
With Grander's skill,
my Vanguard receives
an extra 2,000 power.
(grunting)
♪
Guide Dolphin's
giving his support
as Enigman Shine swings in
at Knight of Friendship Kay.
♪
(grunts)
So that's it.
You know I have Soul
Saver Dragon in my hand
and you're trying
to mess with my plans.
It's the Holy Charging
Roar I'm worried about.
With a five point Soul Blast,
you can give three of
your rear‐guard units
and extra 5,000 power,
which could lead
to a battle phase
that I might not survive.
By taking a couple of
your rear‐guard units
out of the picture,
I've put myself in a
position to win this game.
He ain't jokin'.
Oh, man.
(giggles)
It takes a great player
to set up and execute
a strategy like the
one you were planning,
but this match won't
be won so easily.
(cheering)
It looks as though Kenji is
taking control of this game.
That kid was starting
to gain some momentum.
Too bad for him, he's been
brought to a screeching halt.
I doubt he'll be
able to recover.
Sendou has no business playing
against a former champion.
The outcome of
this match is obvious.
You're right, Tetsu.
He doesn't have a
chance at winning this.
Unless he's willing to
activate his PSY Qualia.
♪
Aichi, you know you want to.
Surely you must have realized
what you walked away from.
Use your power and Kenji
will be no match for you.
Show me a victory
worthy of a fighter
chosen by PSY Qualia.
Come on!
(chuckles)
♪
Enigman Storm taking
aim at Blaster Blade.
♪
(grunts)
Checking twin drive.
♪
It's a stand trigger.
Enigman Shine, stand up
with another 5,000 power.
♪
(screams)
Damage trigger.
Time to rise and shine.
Huh?
♪
(shouts)
Over to you, Aichi.
Hm.
♪
Koutei just
keeps getting better.
He weakened my
offensive formation
to prevent me from
taking full advantage
of Soul Saver Dragon.
And he dealt me two
damage in the process.
I've got to face it.
He's a top level fighter.
♪
I don't know if someone like me
even has a chance against him.
What am I supposed to do?
♪
(gasps)
Hold on.
♪
Using PSY Qualia would
allow me to win this fight.
It would show me
the cards to use
and take the
decisions out of my hands,
but...
I have to do
this on my own.
I can't afford to let
that power consume me again.
♪
I know you're
all eager to help,
but this is my battle.
♪
It's the right thing to do,
facing him alone
with my own strength.
I'm not gonna
pull any punches.
That's the only way
I'll ever become
the fighter I want to be.
♪
What's this?
Hm.
For a moment there,
I could have sworn
I felt a PSY Qualia activating.
Now...
Hold on, is he using it or not?
Draw.
Sacred Dragon, appear
and fill this battlefield
with holy light.
I ride Soul Saver Dragon.
(roars)
♪
Using my soul blast,
Holy Charging Roar.
♪
This ability should have
been powering up three units,
but he saw to that.
No matter.
Even if I don't get full value,
I'll still make
these attacks count.
I call...
Palamedes will get it started.
Attacking Enigman Storm!
♪
Not so fast.
Grander guards.
Hm?
Boosted by Marron,
Soul Saver Dragon attacks!
♪
I don't guard.
Then I'll check
the twin drive.
♪
(explosion)
Damage trigger check.
With support
from Wingal Brave,
Gordon's comin' atcha.
Cosmo Fang will guard.
♪
(snarls)
With that, my turn ends.
No fair.
Aichi had this game
in the palm of his hand,
but thanks to
Koutei's meddling,
he just wasted what was
supposed to be his final turn.
Listen up, Aichi,
I want you to know
how much I respect
you as a card fighter,
so I'm not gonna let
myself hold back against you.
Moving Guide
Dolphin to the soul
and adding 3,000 power
to Enigman Storm.
Cosmo Beak to rear‐guard,
counterblast.
Enigman Storm gains
another 4,000 power.
And next I call...
♪
Activating
Enigman Storm's skill.
If his power exceeds 15,000,
he gains one critical.
Going critical that easily?
Aichi's done.
Koutei's got him
right where he wants him.
He sure does.
And once The Emperor
begins his march,
nobody will be
able to stop him.
He's a young Caesar,
reborn in the modern day.
♪
Supported by Glory Maker,
Enigman Storm attacks Gordon.
♪
Why him?
We can't have your intercept
spoiling all the fun.
This way I can be certain
that the rest of my attacks
will make it through
to your Vanguard.
With Glory Maker's skill,
if my damage zone has
four or more damage,
then her boosted unit
gets another 4,000 power.
28,000!
Before triggers.
Doesn't that seem
like a waste to you guys?
I mean, if you've
got that much power,
why use it to attack
a rear‐guard unit?
Good call.
He could have used
his own rear‐guard
to clear out that intercept.
You two don't get it.
Koutei's got a plan.
Watch.
Now to check twin drive.
The first.
♪
Second.
Wow, this really couldn't have
shown up at a better time.
Stand trigger activated.
That's 5,000 power
to Enigman Storm
and Glory Maker stands up.
♪
(shouts)
Fasten your seatbelt, Aichi.
Huh?
Using Commander Laurel's skill,
I put four of my
rear‐guard units to rest.
♪
Which'll let me
stand up my Vanguard.
He gets another attack?
And now for my ultimate move.
The Emperor's March.
♪
(whimpers)
That's crazy.
Doesn't it seem weird
that Commander Laurel
lets you stand your
Vanguard back up?
This means he can attack
with Enigman Storm again.
Aichi can totally afford
to take one more hit.
Are you sure about that?
Huh?
Having to rest four of
your rear‐guard units
is a hefty cost.
The upside is that by attacking
twice with your Vanguard,
you can double twin drive
which draws more triggers
and a big card advantage.
Destroying Aichi's
intercept was the only option.
He's doing everything he
can to give the final attack
the best possible chance
of getting through.
Enigman Storm can
finish the game right here
with that skill of his...
(gasping)
This attack was critical.
(exclaiming)
But Aichi's already
got four damage!
Two more and he'll...
Glory Maker's standing
ready in the back row.
Exactly.
This attack's coming
in at full power.
It's too strong.
There's no way his
Vanguard can withstand it.
Come on, bro,
gotta think fast.
His back's flat up
against the wall.
What will he do about
this gathering tempest?
The next few moments
could decide the match.
Oh, the intensity!
♪
You're far more powerful
than I expected you to be.
For my team's sake,
I've got to finish you off.
So let's wrap this up
with one last attack.
♪
Really?
Hm.
♪
What's wrong with him?
The odds are stacked
in his opponent's favor.
Why is he so calm?
♪
This is what real
strength is, Aichi.
Ooh.
Check out his game face.
He's strong.
In fact, he's stronger than
we ever gave him credit for.
Now that he's back to
normal, we can finally see
the power he had
all this time.
He looks like...
Yeah, his eyes are
intense like Kai's were
before he won that fight.
♪
With Glory Maker's support,
go, Enigman Storm!
Glory Maker's skill
pumps him up to 33,000.
♪
We'll see about that.
Paladins, stop him!
♪
Hm.
Checking twin drive again.
♪
Hm.
Incredible.
I can't believe you still
had enough in your hand
to defend an attack
of that size.
I knew you were gonna
come at me with everything,
so I held onto as many
defensive cards as I could.
No way.
This is amazing.
It's impressive how Aichi
is keeping up with him.
Yeah.
Meeting your
opponent as an equal
and laying it
all on the line.
That's what Vanguard
is supposed to be about.
♪
Hm.
What is it?
♪
My turn's over.
I'm surprised you managed
to stop that attack, but‐‐
There was no other way.
I used up my whole
hand to stay in this.
I'll fight until
the bitter end.
Hm.
Even though he made
it through the storm,
things sure aren't
looking any brighter.
He starts his turn with
zero cards in his hand
and there's a rear‐guard unit
missing from his front row.
He should be
ending the game here,
but he can't do that
without more reinforcements.
Hey, I've got some bad news.
♪
Koutei has two
Diamond Aces in his hand,
so by dropping a card he
can nullify two attacks.
Well, then he just needs
to get a third attacker out.
But Koutei also has
Cosmo Beak in the front row
set to block.
It's supposed
to be my turn now.
Why do I still feel
like I'm on the defensive?
Hm.
I fought my hardest
alongside my rightful clan.
All these cards
mean the world to me.
Thanks to them,
I'll never give up.
Hm.
You‐‐you've
come to save me?
Hm?
See the king as he once was.
Knights unified by the light.
It can't be.
♪
I ride Alfred Early.
(grunts)
♪
Alfred Early was sitting
on top of his deck?
Yeah, this is the
big chance he needed!
Activating Alfred's skill.
Stand up once more, my avatar.
Superior call Blaster Blade.
Blaster Blade's about
to pass final judgment
on that troublesome Cosmo Beak.
Counterblast.
♪
(growls)
Had to get rid of
your intercept first.
My Royal Paladins
are assembled
and we're ready
to finish you off.
Well, folks, Aichi Sendou
really has a chance here
to turn things around.
Drawing Alfred Early
was the best thing
that could have
happened to him.
Indeed, the king riding
in to save the day.
It's like his deck
refuses to give up.
His deck refuses?
And he did say, "We're
ready to finish you off."
He's connected to his
cards without PSY Qualia.
Hm, seems so.
I wasn't expecting him
to play at this level.
Huh?
Pay attention, buddy,
this isn't a holiday.
You saw it with your own eyes.
Aichi was about to lose
and he drew the one card
that could save him.
♪
It's as if the cards
have a mind of their own.
You can just feel
it in the air.
♪
Swordsman of the
Explosive Flames, Palamedes.
(grunting)
♪
Five damage.
You're close, but I'm not gonna
let anything else get through.
With Marron's support,
Alfred Early attacks.
(grunts)
♪
All right, Diamond
Ace nullifies that.
(grunts)
♪
Checking twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
(snarls)
Sharon.
It's so good to see you.
So, thanks to this trigger,
I'll be giving Blaster
Blade another 5,000 power,
and Palamedes stands up.
♪
This is is just great.
Now he's got two more
attacks for me to stop.
♪
My Diamond Ace can take care
of one of them, no problem.
But that leaves me defenseless
to deal with the next one.
♪
Here I go.
Supported by my Wingal Brave,
Blaster Blade attacks.
Hm, I don't guard.
There's nothing
left for me to do
but leave it in the hands
of the damage triggers.
♪
(battle cry)
(grunts)
♪
This is it.
Too bad.
Caesar's fallen.
♪
The winner: Aichi Sendou.
(cheering)
♪
And there you have it.
Team Q4 is moving on
to the main event!
They'll be coming back
once again to face off
against Team Asteroid in the
national tournament final.
This is for all the marbles.
That's wild!
He did it without relying on
the power of his PSY Qualia.
Yes, but that
won't work tomorrow.
He'll need to use it
if he wants to beat Ren.
A matchup between the
only people on Earth
known to possess it.
There's a lot more at
stake here than the title.
PSY Qualia makes it possible
for the user to be victorious.
I wonder what will happen if
both players have that skill.
Now we'll find out
once and for all
the true nature
of that power.
Is that what he
wants us to do?
(cheering)
Hey, bro, you did it!
You got Team Q4
into the final round!
We're counting on
you three to win this.
Be sure to let
Asteroid know who's boss.
You're the best team for
the job, so act like it.
(laughter)
If anyone can beat
them, it's you guys.
Yeah!
You four!
We have a big day tomorrow.
The sooner we hit the road,
the sooner we can relax.
Sounds good!
Smell you later!
(cheering)
Hm?
♪
They expect us
to play Team Q4?
It's been fun, Aichi,
but without your PSY Qualia,
you don't stand
a chance against us.
(chuckles)
I'm gonna enjoy wiping that
ridiculous smile off your face.
Once I've destroyed you,
I'll be the only
one with this power.
(chuckles)
♪
Aichi, our battle was
epic to say the least.
Now it's time for you to
focus on the task at hand,
winning the title.
Don't forget my friends,
I wouldn't have
made it without them.
Kamui, Misaki, Kai.
Next time, Fateful Showdown.
Asteroid may think they're
the best team on Earth,
but I know that
we can beat them.
Ren, I understand your
power better than I used to,
and I'm gonna return you
to the way you once were.
Kai...