(zapping)
♪
Ah!
(gasping)
You were able to
picture it, I see.
Witness true Vanguard.
This battle is a lot of fun.
So then you're
Aichi Sendou, right?
That's right, Kai,
and you gave me the power to
stand here before you today.
I see.
Arise my avatar, ride!
(grunting)
Blaster Blade!
♪
(purring)
(grunting)
♪
Blaster Blade, huh?
Man, what luck.
With cards like that,
he actually stands a chance.
♪
I activate Blaster
Blade's ability.
Paying two from
my damage zone,
I retire one of
your rear guards.
Hmm.
♪
I remember you now.
Aichi Sendou.
You were the kid with scuff
marks all over your face.
Yeah, in those days, I was
getting beaten up so much
that I almost didn't want
to go to school anymore.
I felt like the world
around me was collapsing.
♪
Huh?
Man, you're a mess.
Did you lose a
fight or something?
(groaning)
Hey, kid, hang on.
Hmm?
Here, check it out.
I want you to have this.
Oh?
♪
You've got a really tough
warrior in your hands there.
So, come on, cheer up already.
Try to imagine yourself
becoming powerful
like the warrior on that
card I just gave you.
But‐‐but I can't.
(laughs)
Well, no, not at
first, I guess.
But if you
believe in yourself,
then nothing can
stand in the way
of you getting big and
strong like Blaster Blade.
I'll get strong?
From now on, that image
can be your power.
♪
Ever since I got that card,
life has been a
little better each day.
From the moment
you gave this to me,
I wanted nothing more
than to battle you.
I even obsessed over
picking the cards I would use
to build my deck.
But before I could finish
building it, you moved away.
Yeah.
You know, while I was
making this deck,
I managed to forget
all the awful things
in the world around me.
Hmm.
I still can't really picture
myself as being any stronger,
but the person that showed me
how to be happy
again was you, Kai.
I call the Knight of Silence,
Gallatin to rear guard.
This battle is my way
of saying thank you
for helping me
believe in myself.
That's all I needed.
I support Blaster
Blade with Wingal,
and attack Nehalem.
Hmm?
♪
‐Whoa.
‐He took another damage.
And, next, I'll support
Marron with Flogal,
attacking Nehalem again.
Hmm.
♪
I'll attack Nehalem one
more time with Gallatin.
Wow, a triple attack?
This can't be the same
Aichi Sendou from school.
(shouting)
♪
Five damage?
One more and it's
all over for him.
Kai is finally gonna lose.
Not likely.
He hasn't even broken
a sweat yet, look.
He's got some plan.
All right, it's
your turn now.
Hmm, I showed you
how to be happy?
I think you
misunderstood, little boy.
I didn't care about
your feelings one bit.
I just wanted you to
start playing Vanguard
so I could beat you in a way
those bullies never could.
Oh, that's so mean!
No wonder I couldn't beat him.
This guy is pure evil.
Kai, you wouldn't do
that sort of thing.
Th‐‐that's a lie!
The Kai I know would never
do something like that.
Ha, be quiet!
I'm not the
person you admire.
You've made up some
fairy tale in your head.
I‐‐I...
(fire roaring)
Hmm.
What?
I guess it's about time I
show you who I really am.
Ride the Vanguard!
Burn everything in
this world to ash
with your apocalyptic fire!
Dragonic Overlord!
♪
Huh?
It's amazing.
Whoa.
That's what he used on me.
Hmm, this battle is over.
I call two Monicas.
And, then, I pay three
from my damage zone
to activate Dragonic
Overlord's counterblast.
Dragonic Overlord's power
just went up by 5,000.
♪
Shall we?
I support Bahr with Monica...
♪
...and I attack
your Blaster Blade!
Stardust Trumpeter, guard me!
♪
(grunting)
Hmm.
I'm not through yet!
I support Monica with Jarran
and attack Blaster Blade.
♪
I guard with Gallatin!
(grunting)
♪
Whoa, he survived it.
(heavy breathing)
Hmm.
Used up your entire
hand to hold me back?
It's too bad for you
that my attacks aren't
even close to over yet.
Dragonic Overlord,
it's your turn now.
With Aermo's support,
attack Gallatin!
Gallatin, why?
♪
And, now, let's check
the drive trigger.
(shouting)
Gallatin is retired.
All right then,
Dragonic Overlord, stand up.
Oh, my, looks like
you weren't aware of
the Dragonic Overlord's
special ability.
When his counterblast
is activated
and if he defeats an
opponent's rear guard,
then he stands back up.
I won't stop attacking
until all your units
are burnt to a crisp.
That's Dragonic Overlord's
ability, eternal flame!
Then you're...
Attacking Marron.
And I think I'll check
the drive trigger here too.
♪
Ahh!
Marron is also retired.
Just like the last time,
Dragonic Overlord stands up.
Oh, no.
Now we're talking.
Can't you imagine if I had
one of those cards in my deck?
I just need to score one,
and it'll be all
winning, all the time!
(sighing)
Now for the final swing,
I use Dragonic Overlord
to attack Blaster Blade.
Ahh!
Let's check for a trigger.
Now that's a
pretty sweet bonus.
Tahr's trigger adds
5,000 power to my attack.
♪
(screaming)
The yellow triggers
give a critical effect
adding plus‐one
to attack damage.
But that means...
That's right,
another two damage
to add to the four damage
you've already taken.
It's over.
(chuckles)
It's about time.
One damage.
And two...
Ah.
Huh?
Wait, this is...
The Yggdrasil Maiden, Elaine.
♪
What is that?
Yggdrasil Maiden, Elaine.
A heal trigger.
When you trigger it,
you can take a card back
from your damage zone,
as long as you have more
damage than your opponent.
That means...
...that the battle
isn't over yet.
My damage zone
is at its limit.
It's your time to
shine, Aichi Sendou.
Thank you.
Aichi is back on the attack,
and Kai's got five damage.
All it's gonna take
is one more hit
and this fight's over.
Looks like Aichi
is gonna win.
Too close to call.
Kai is such a good player,
there's no telling
what he might do.
I don't believe any of that
stuff you said to me earlier.
Oh, yeah?
You expect me to believe
that you only gave me
this Blaster Blade card so
that you could bully me later,
but if that's the case,
then I don't think this
card would have inspired me
to get stronger or given me
the courage that it did.
Ha, what a joke.
Mm, no.
No matter what you say,
this Blaster Blade has been
really important to me,
and that will never change.
I'll always remember how
pathetic I must have seemed
the day you were nice
enough to give me this card.
I really looked up to you.
My memory tells me the truth.
I can picture the way this
battle is going to end.
I can picture
my Blaster Blade
as he leads the
way to victory!
I call Elaine.
♪
I support Elaine with Flogal.
And I attack your
Dragonic Overlord.
♪
I guard with Tahr.
Ah!
Hmm, you don't
stand a chance.
Whoa, he blocked the attack!
Come on, Aichi.
If Kai can manage to defend
against this next assault,
there's no way Aichi would
ever be able to survive
another turn against him.
In other words,
Kai is gonna win.
The kid only has
one more attempt,
but Kai is holding on
to one defensive card.
That means...
...he has a defensive
power of 21,000.
The attack power of
Blaster Blade is 9,000,
plus Wingal is 6,000.
The ability adds 4,000.
It won't be enough.
This is it.
I attack you with
Blaster Blade!
♪
Hmm.
This is it.
I attack you with
Blaster Blade!
Ah!
Huh.
I've been dreaming of this
battle since we were kids.
♪
Go ahead, attack,
Blaster Blade!
♪
Ha.
Hmm.
I guard with Tahr.
♪
Sorry, your attack isn't
gonna get through this time.
I've come this far.
Please.
I check for a drive trigger.
♪
This is...
Hmm.
Drive trigger activated,
raising attack power by
5,000 and damage by one.
Then that means...
♪
(grunting)
(yelling)
♪
That hit proved
to be too much,
even for my Dragonic Overlord.
And, now, I'm a spirit again.
My units have been removed
from the planet Cray.
So you've...
I have lost.
Oh.
Dude, you beat him!
Huh?
(gasping)
But, Kai!
Looks like that was
your card after all.
No way.
Uh, hey, wait up!
Come on!
Hey, Kai!
Thanks a lot.
(chuckles)
Oh, oh‐‐
I did it.
♪
Well, let's go.
Don't forget your bag.
Oh, right.
♪
"Alone in the orchard
with the wind
blowing in your hair,"
which poet wrote these words?
Aichi Sendou.
Yes, ma'am?
Um, let's see, well...
Sounds French to me.
Is it Pannett?
Oh, come on, that's
not right at all.
Gotta keep guessing, Shychi.
He's going red.
You guys are hilarious.
Um, Fontaine?
(clock chiming)
(indistinct chattering)
♪
I still can't believe it.
Let's go.
Hey, you want to head
down to Card Capital today?
Of course, man,
gotta fine‐tune my deck.
You sure like this game.
Quite the opposite.
You see, Vanguard likes me.
Morikawa!
What do you want?
I‐‐I was wondering if
maybe you and I could have
a Vanguard battle sometime.
Huh?
You wanna beat me too, huh?
Mm‐mm, no, I'm still
really new to Vanguard,
and I was hoping
that you could play me
and maybe teach me
a couple things.
Hmm.
Teach you?
Look, I don't want
to waste my time
teaching a shrimp
like you how to swim.
Yeah.
Okay, thanks.
Man, Kai is so lame.
He moves back here and
starts acting like a big shot,
but then he goes and loses
to rookie like Aichi.
Yeah, no kidding.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he never shows his face
in that store again.
(laughing)
Hmm.
(birds chirping)
Hey, want to have
a card fight?
You're on!
Huh?
My new deck is way stronger.
Whoa.
Yeah, well, I kind of doubt
it can beat my ultimate deck.
Oh, yeah, well, mine is the
super ultimate times two.
Well, then mine's the
super‐duper ultimate.
Then mine's the
ultimate times infinity!
Picture yourself
big and strong.
♪
That's right.
I'm a Royal Paladin,
the Knights of Strength,
and I'm gonna get
stronger with each battle.
♪
Kai.
Heh.
♪
(sighing)
(meowing)
Hello again.
Hi.
Nobody's here.
Well, it is still early.
Yeah, I guess
that must be it.
♪
(sighing)
(groaning)
Are you waiting for someone?
Yes, but I don't
know if he's coming.
The guy I battled,
he probably hates me.
♪
And after all those
years of waiting.
♪
(meowing)
You know, I wouldn't
be so sure about that.
Huh?
♪
Kai, you're here!
Hey there, Aichi.
Glad to see you back.
Hey, new guy.
Uh, I was hoping that...
(chuckles)
Say no more, buddy.
How about you play me today?
Hmm?
No way, I got dibs
on that small fry.
Then me!
Ah!
What's the matter?
Thanks a lot for
coming down, you guys.
So good.
What are you doing back here?
What a shock.
You guys are too funny.
(laughing)
Did you seriously think...
With countless people
around the world
playing trading card games...
Don't run.
...they quickly become
a part of our daily lives.
These days,
the biggest of them all
is Cardfight Vanguard.
♪
I never would have thought
that a game could
change my life forever.
♪
Come on, Aichi,
that whole thing about you
being a beginner at Vanguard
was a bluff, right?
It's true!
But I finally got to have my
long‐awaited match with Kai.
Feeling good about yourself
after playing that guy?
That's the Aichi I know.
Then will you play
me next, Morikawa?
Ha‐ha, I'll show you
all my awesome skills.
Next time, "Welcome
to Card Capital."
I'm picturing myself
standing on the planet Cray.
Wait, Emi, why are you here?