(cheering)
♪
So it's come to this.
Listen, you guys can't
hold back against us.
No problem.
Team Caesar is going down!
Guess this means we're rivals.
You ready to show
these boys how it's done?
You know I am!
♪
"This means we're rivals!"
Hear that?
Team Caesar is taking
this match seriously
'cause they know
how much we've grown
since the last tournament!
Yeah, we're lucky to play them!
I mean, they're so
mature and friendly!
Everyone should
be more like that.
You know what I'm saying, Kai?
Oh, totally.
I think it would
benefit the whole team
if you were a little
bit more mature.
Mm, wow, you see?
Everything goes right
over the poor boy's head.
Our second match
of the semi‐finals
features two more
groups of card fighters!
Representing Team Q4,
it's Kamui Katsuragi!
Give it your best.
All right, let's do this!
♪
And his opponent from
Team Caesar, Gai Usui!
Guess I'm up.
This match is
really important, Gai.
Have you found
your winning image?
Yeah, well, I'm
starting to doubt
whether I actually
need one, you know?
At the end of the day,
I'm just a gladiator,
which means I'll
protect my teammates.
(cheering)
♪
What do you think?
He's strong, but I'm not sure he
has the will to beat that kid!
How about instead
of complaining,
you kick back and enjoy
this incredible moment, Yuri?
You're gonna be
the one complaining
after I knock a little
bit of sense into you!
Sorry, my mistake,
I take it back!
(cheering)
Go get 'em, Gladiator Gai!
Team Caesar rocks!
We're counting on ya!
This crowd is really fired up!
That's to be
expected in this match.
Team Caesar has been
runner‐up two years in a row,
and they're a fan favorite.
♪
Oh, man.
I think we're the only ones
in the stadium cheering for Q4.
I wonder if Kamui will be okay,
'cause from here it kinda
looks like he's gonna be sick!
Kamui, just think
happy thoughts!
Keep it together, yo!
I've waited so long for this.
I can't get nervous!
♪
What's wrong with me?
I know he's really strong,
but my whole team
is depending on me.
Time to show 'em
what I'm made of.
I'm ready for you, Gai!
Good, come and get me.
‐Stand up my Vanguard!
♪
(rumbling)
Finally‐‐I thought this
game was never gonna start!
The anticipation has
been hard to bear,
but now that we're underway,
I'm sure everyone is eager
to see how this one plays out.
♪
Late night?
I'm gonna nap until
it's Aichi's turn.
We won't disturb you.
Ah‐‐hmm.
♪
I know you can handle
the challenge, Kamui.
♪
Hmm.
This match is as
close as they get!
Gai versus the young Kamui!
Who will win it?
We're gonna find out soon‐‐wow!
Hmm.
♪
We've got a real
nail‐biter here, folks.
With our fighters
tied at four damage!
♪
I'm hitting him with
everything I've got,
but I can't seem
to finish the job!
Is this what it's like to
play top level Vanguard?
I stand and draw.
I call Cosmo Beak, counterblast!
♪
That's 4,000 power
to my Vanguard.
♪
And now, with Daiyusha's skill,
he gains plus one critical.
Next up, I call Cosmo Roar!
♪
With support from Cosmo Roar,
my rear‐guard Daiyusha
attacks Top Gun!
♪
I don't guard that!
Damage trigger.
Supported by Diamond Ace,
my Vanguard attacks!
♪
Dispense justice, feel the
power of the Dimension Police!
♪
Be careful!
Kamui!
Guys, Vanguard is charging in!
♪
Twin Blader will
stop that attack!
Dropping one guard from my hand,
I nullify your attempts!
♪
Checking the Twin Drive.
It's a critical trigger!
The power increase
and the critical effect
will both be going
to my Cosmo Beak.
♪
Second check.
Not another critical trigger!
Giving all the
effects to Cosmo Beak.
♪
Supported by Cosmo Roar,
Cosmo Beak is comin' at ya!
♪
Clara and Prometheus will guard!
Guess that's it for my turn.
(groaning)
‐Hmm.
‐I thought he was done for!
Oh, wow!
Kamui has weathered the storm
and stood up to the challenge
of Gai's ferocious assault!
Yeah, that was O‐mazing!
I can't believe
he blocked Daiyusha
and still had enough to hold off
a double critical Cosmo Beak!
See, he's the greatest!
Gai didn't hold back and
Kamui still shot him down!
Wow, nicely done!
Oh, man, staring down
a double critical attack,
and he blocked
without flinching!
That's it, I will make
him my next student.
That's a joke, right?
I'll say O. K.
You agreed to that?
I said Only Kidding!
Yo!
Now I get it.
Speaking in code, huh?
I've got him now!
Hmm, he's playing well.
I stand and draw!
I call Tough Boy!
♪
Boosted by Tough Boy,
Death Metal Droid
attacks your Vanguard!
I'll use Death
Metal's counterblast,
paying the cost to give
him an extra 3,000 power!
Top Gun's ability is online!
He gains 1,000 power for
each of my rear‐guard units
in the resting position,
so that's an extra 2,000 power!
♪
(gun firing)
(groaning)
♪
With a boost from Army Guy,
Army Lady attacks!
♪
No chance, Justice
Cobalt guards!
♪
This attack won't hit.
What a match, hey, Gai?
♪
Here it comes, full throttle!
Yeah.
Get it done, Top Gun.
♪
That's Kamui's Vanguard!
But he's only got 14,000 power!
(yelling)
And with Justice
Cobalt, I guard!
It all rides on this.
Ready or not.
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
That's it.
I'm gonna find a
way to beat you!
Checking Twin Drive.
First check.
♪
Death Metal Droid, stand up
with an extra 5,000 power!
Second check.
There, it's a grade three!
Revealing this makes all my
Army units stand at attention!
Huh.
I'm gonna finish you off!
♪
It's over.
(groaning)
(gun firing)
♪
The winner‐‐Kamui
Katsuragi of Team Q4!
(cheering)
Can you believe it?
He's just done the unthinkable‐‐
stealing the first win away from
Team Caesar's noble gladiator.
Truly a match to remember!
I did it!
This brave young card fighter
has stood up to the test
and triumphed over
a very tough opponent.
Witness history in the making!
Indeed.
Nicely done.
You know, that was fun.
But Gai...
I could tell we
would make good rivals.
Thanks for the close match.
Later.
♪
Wow, thank you so much.
Not bad for a grade‐schooler!
The Great One wins!
What are the haters
gonna say now, Kamui?
♪
Sorry, I let you down.
Don't feel bad about it, okay?
You're too kind.
I won't be kind at all.
Sis, I...
♪
What did I tell you
about going to battle
without a clear image
of victory in your head?
I did the best I could!
If you're not
gonna listen to me,
then I might as well
pull your ears off!
(whining)
Please save me, Koutei.
Uh, Gai, you're supposed
to protect me, aren't you?
♪
Yeah!
You were amazing out there!
It felt so good to
get the first win,
but I still can't believe
I was able to defeat
someone I admire like Gai Usui.
Well, believe it!
Training with those guys
was a huge help for us.
You showed them
how much we've grown!
I really did it‐‐I
took him on as an equal!
Kamui looks so
excited down there!
Well, he just defeated
someone he respects,
and a former National
Champion at that!
Q4, let's go, yo!
Hey, check it out.
Team Caesar's got some problems.
‐Huh?
She's really giving it to him.
"You lost to a kid that
still has training wheels
on his bike!
You're grounded, Mister!
You can't watch any TV
and forget about
seeing your friends.
‐You've messed up‐‐"
‐Please stop talking now.
There's an awful lot
riding on this second match!
From Team Q4, we've
got Misaki Tokura
and Yuri Usui of Team Caesar!
(cheering)
Let's go, Misaki!
You can do it!
Yes, after waiting for so long,
I finally get to see them fight!
‐Say what?
‐Those two girls
are gonna show the
world how it's done!
I mean, normally we watch
fights between nerdy guys,
but now we get to see
girl power at its finest!
Girls have powers?
I'm not talking super powers,
I'm talking the
incredible confidence
that radiates from a smart,
strong lady on the battlefield.
Whatever.
Oh, you'll see.
If it's not Kourin,
he isn't interested.
I'm looking forward
to some girl power.
♪
Well, looky, looky.
They've taken the field
with determination
shining in their eyes.
I'm completely overwhelmed
by the excitement of it all.
So it seems!
And we're ready to go!
Ready‐‐fighters, let's begin!
♪
We're in the big time,
which makes you my
enemy till this is over.
♪
That's intense.
She can sure get
scary sometimes, huh?
Trust me, it's
not just sometimes.
♪
‐Stand up my Vanguard!
I hope you're ready for this.
Using Godhawk
Ichibyoshi's skill,
checking the top
five cards of my deck,
and if Goddess of the Crescent
Moon Tsukuyomi is there,
then I can superior ride.
♪
It wasn't there?
That's a bad sign, you guys.
Next I ride Dark Cat.
♪
Thanks to Dark Cat's skill
when it enters the battlefield,
both players get to draw a card.
I hate that this helps
you, but I need the draw.
♪
I end my turn.
Stand and draw!
Ride Enigman Ripple.
♪
As long as Enigman
Flow is in the soul,
my Vanguard gets an
additional 2,000 power.
And by using Flow's skill,
I search for Enigman Wave
and add it to my hand.
♪
I call Magical Police Quilt.
With her support, Enigman
Ripple attacks Dark Cat!
♪
Drive trigger check.
Damage trigger.
The nice thing about Quilt
is whenever she supports
a successful attack,
her skill activates.
I drop one from my hand
and draw a new card.
That's all, my turn's done.
So whatcha gonna do?
Hmm.
By drawing and discarding,
Yuri has a good chance
of getting the units
needed to defeat Misaki!
Then shouldn't she
have guarded that attack?
Wrong‐‐she can't afford
to waste her hand of defense
this early in the game.
I'm gonna take a nap, okay?
Please, wake me up when
the grade threes come out?
Why do we always end up
sitting near this guy?
His words hurt my brain.
I stand and draw.
Goddess of the Half
Moon, Tsukuyomi ride.
♪
Too bad you're missing the
Crescent Moon in your soul, huh?
It only stops me from
using one of her skills.
Now...
I call Battle
Maiden, Tagitsuhime.
♪
I'll start off with
an attack from Tsukuyomi.
♪
I don't guard that.
Drive trigger check.
♪
Damage trigger check.
Battle Maiden, go!
♪
Heeyah!
Checking for a trigger.
‐I'll pass it to you.
‐Hmm.
You're better than
my little brother.
‐Hmm?
‐Uh‐oh.
Cheer up, Gai.
Look at that!
Forget the respectful
first match!
This time the gloves are off!
As the turns pass, the
intensity is rising, Dr. O!
And how?
There's a garden
of anger growing
down on the stadium floor.
Watch out for the flowers,
'cause these roses have thorns.
(whimpering)
I've fought Yuri
a couple of times,
and she never acted
like this before.
Well, there is a
lot on the line here,
so maybe she's just fired up
because her team
needs her to be!
Hey, Misaki's not exactly
playing nice either, you know!
I never thought
this day would come.
That's girl power.
You can't say stuff like that.
Come on, man, what
if he heard you?
Girl power?
I knew there was a reason
I couldn't beat her.
Great, here we go.
Is girl power contagious?
Breathe through your nose!
(laughing)
♪
I feel for Misaki.
Yeah, I haven't
seen your big sister
get this serious in a while.
This goes to show how
strong Team Q4 has become.
They really are our new rivals.
First I stand and draw!
Enigman Wave, ride!
♪
And with his skill, if
Enigman Ripple is in the soul,
1,000 power is added.
♪
Calling two Super
Dimensional Robo, Dailadys
and a Cosmo Roar to rear‐guard!
♪
Now it's time for you
to see what I can do.
Hmm.
♪
Will she be okay?
Team Caesar's most
fearsome fighter!
With overwhelming force, Yuri
leads her units into battle
like an empress general
of times long forgotten!
♪
It's on!
Oh, yeah, I beat Gai, and he
acknowledged me as his rival!
We've made the
big time, you guys!
This is awesome!
Misaki's in a bad spot.
She's up against Team
Caesar's fierce empress!
She'd better watch out!
Wow, they're both so
determined to come out on top!
Next time, Caesar's Empress!
Misaki, you can win this 'cause
your friends believe in you,
so don't let Yuri
push you around!
We're standing beside you!
No matter what!