All right,
it's finally time
for that last match
in our regional
qualifying tournament.
Now, let's play Vanguard!
♪
You know, I almost
didn't stick around.
♪
I got it, I'll just
get up and walk out.
That way Misaki will
have to take my place.
People who run
from cardfights
aren't worthy of
facing off with me.
(gasp)
♪
This is the final turn.
F‐final turn, you say?
♪
Ride the Blazing Flare Dragon.
Blazing Flare Dragon
skill activates.
When one of your units
goes to the drop zone,
the dragon's power
goes up by 3,000.
No way!
Conroe supports Blazing
Flare Dragon's attack.
It's too big
for me to stop!
Now to check the twin drive.
First.
Second.
That's a critical
trigger, times two.
(gunfire)
♪
But while
watching Kai's fight,
it all became clear.
♪
I want to be as
strong as Kai someday
so that I can face
him as an equal.
And yet, here I was
thinking about running
away from a battle
like a coward.
What good would that do?
♪
Third match of the
tournament final, begin!
‐Stand up my Vanguard!
♪
And here we are
at the final match.
It's Team Handsome
against Team Q4.
The last battle has begun
with the winning
team going on
to complete in the
national tournament.
Both teams have put on
an amazing display
up to this point
and everything
comes down to this.
(sighing)
All we can do now
is hope for the best.
Come on, bro,
please save me
from having to marry Nagisa.
Really?
Let's recap what
we've seen so far
from these excellent teams.
Their first match was
a Nova Grappler love story.
Huh?
No, you're wrong!
Kamui, my love.
You're so cute
when you blush.
‐Argh!
‐Ha ha.
We followed that up
with an exciting match
featuring Granblue
and Kagero decks.
Despite his explosive name,
Kaboom failed to blast out
the victory his team needed.
Sea urchins.
Huh?
Kaboom.
So, looking back over
all that's happened here,
I'm sure this last match
will not be
a disappointment, folks.
♪
For my first turn, I draw.
I ride the
Little Sage, Marron.
♪
Hmm.
Barcgal moves to
the rear guard circle.
And then, I activate
Barcgal's skill to call
Flogal from my deck.
♪
That's my turn.
I've got to make
sure that this game
doesn't end up
like the last one.
(growling)
If I don't draw
a heal trigger here,
I lose the game.
♪
You beat me.
(growl)
Hoping for a
different result?
Well, history
repeats itself, kid.
(moan)
It's my turn, I draw.
Here goes, I ride
the Dandy Guy, Romario.
♪
I activate
Guiding Zombie's skill
to move him to
a rear guard circle.
I call Samurai Spirit.
♪
That's not all,
I call Rough Seas Banshee.
Now get a load of this.
Since there's a Granblue unit
in the Vanguard circle,
I can activate
the Banshee's skill,
moving her to the soul,
and I draw a card.
Ugh.
Hmm, why would he make
such a useless move, huh?
We'll have to wait and see.
Seriously, why would you
bother calling out a unit
if all you're
gonna do is send it
directly to the soul?
Are you really
that clueless?
Huh?
Using that skill
didn't cost him anything
because he drew a card
to replace the one
he just played.
Oh.
Increasing his
soul this early
means he's planning
to do something big later.
Here I come,
with a little support
from Samurai Spirit,
I power up my Guiding Zombie
and attack Marron.
♪
Aahh, damage trigger check.
Next, I'll have
Romario attack Marron.
♪
Drive check.
Aargh!
I check for a damage trigger.
Two damage already.
That's all for now.
Big brother,
you can do it!
Hurry up and
beat this guy
so Kamui and I
can get married.
Aichi, I'm begging you.
My future is at
stake here, bro.
Heh‐heh.
Gouki plays like a champion.
But, I have to be strong
and stand my ground.
Even if I get scared,
I won't run away.
Now, I'll show you
my true strength.
Hmm.
♪
Using Barcgal's skill,
I'll search my deck
for Future Knight, Llew.
And now I activate
Llew's counter blast.
♪
Llew goes to the soul.
Barcgal and Flogal, too.
Here we go.
I search for
Blaster Blade in my deck.
Argh!
Huh?
Now, stand up my avatar!
Superior ride,
Blaster Blade!
So with Llew and
Barcgal together,
he was able to get
Blaster Blade.
Wow, I've never seen
Aichi play like this.
That's a really
great combo.
Aah.
There's something
different about him.
This guy,
he's gotten better.
Knight of Silence, Gallatin.
Wingal, Little Sage,
Marron, join me.
♪
Yeah, see that?
Sometimes useless moves
turn into a wicked combo.
Whatever, he doesn't
even have a grade 3.
Your expectations
are too high.
‐(giggle)
‐(moan)
♪
I'll have Marron
attack your Vanguard.
♪
Ha!
(moaning)
Checking for
a damage trigger.
Now, Blaster Blade
attacks Romario.
Ugh!
Drive trigger.
Heal trigger activated.
That's 5,000 power
to Gallatin.
And I heal one
point of damage.
Aarrgh!
(screaming)
Damage trigger check.
Yes, it's a
critical trigger.
I give the power
to Romario.
In my final attack,
I've got Wingal
supporting Gallatin.
Huh?
I guard with
Rick The Ghostie!
♪
(chuckle)
Aaaaaa ya!
♪
I end my turn there.
Looks like you've
gotten a lot better.
But is it gonna be enough?
Hmm.
Deep in the Granblue where
the sunlight doesn't reach
is where the pirates are.
Ugh.
I ride Captain Nightmist!
♪
(evil laughter)
Oh, no, that's the unit that
gave me so much trouble before.
(evil laughter)
Using Captain
Nightmist's counter blast
from the drop zone.
Pirates may die
but they're never gone.
You can activate
their abilities
out of the drop zone?
There's no way
Aichi's gonna win this
now that Gouki's set up
his big finisher,
the unstoppable pirates.
His legion of undead units
will keep coming back
to haunt you until they
finish the job for good.
First, I'll call Ruin Shade.
♪
Next, I call Evil Shade.
I'm attacking Blaster Blade
with my Ruin Shade!
Activating her ability.
Sending two cards
from my deck
to the drop zone
for a power boost.
Perfect.
I activate Nightmist's
skill as well.
Huh, when did you...
Ruin Shade's skill through a
Nightmist into the drop zone.
And thanks to that,
my Vanguard Nightmist
is getting an extra 3,000
attack power this turn.
You used this strategy
on me last time.
His other units get
Nightmist into the drop zone
and it powers up
his Vanguard Nightmist.
♪
Facing my Undead Pirates again
was a big mistake
on your part, kid.
♪
(laughter)
Uh.
♪
Aichi, this new opponent
seems like a really
skilled player.
Will you be all right?
There's nothing
to worry about, Emi.
Your brother is
down there fighting
on behalf of Kamui.
There's no way
he can lose.
It's in the bag, yo.
So he's fighting
for Kamui, huh?
You guys sure about that?
Yeah, right, as if he'd be
playing for that little wimp.
‐Exactly, the team is‐‐
‐Isn't it obvious
that he's down there
fighting to uphold my honor?
(laughter)
Well, anyway, this is
the most important cardfight
your brother's ever had.
And no matter
who wins or loses,
the best thing
we can do right now
is just cheer him on
with everything we've got.
That's how we can help.
‐Mm‐hmm.
You see?
Mm‐hmm.
Do your best, Aichi.
Aarggh!
It's still pretty
early in the fight.
That being said,
I can see why
Gouki made
nationals last year.
Wow, this match is
really getting interesting.
The Undead
Pirates of Granblue
are about to strike back
against the Royal Paladins.
Argh.
♪
Let's see how
you like this.
Ruin Shade attacks.
Aarrgh!
Argh, I check for
a damage trigger.
Evil Shade
supports Nightmist.
Ooh, yeah!
I activate
Evil Shade's skill.
By putting the top
two cards from my deck
into the drop zone,
I add 4,000 power
to this attack.
♪
Drive trigger check.
Aarggh!
Damage trigger check.
He's so strong.
♪
Hmmm.
Wow.
That Nightmist
is so sneaky
you'd think
he was a ninja.
We all now how much
you love ninjas.
I bet you want to get one
of those for your deck now.
No way, I only care
about getting grade 3s.
Of course.
Oh, the grade 3 fever
is still raging.
Grade 3 fever?
Dude loves power cards.
♪
This is the level of play
that gets you to nationals.
This guy's really good.
(moaning)
Huh?
Come on, Aichi,
you've got to
beat this guy.
I don't want to wind up
with a box and stick.
Hmm?
Oh, you were trying to say
ball and chain, weren't you?
Gouki's the strongest
opponent I've ever faced.
But, well, I can't let
something like that
stop me from winning.
♪
Hmm‐hmm.
Ugh.
♪
Hmm.
Uh.
Ha.
Hmm.
Well, guys.
That's right, the Royal
Paladins are my clan.
If we fight together
and believe in ourselves,
we can win this.
♪
All my friends in Team Q4
are counting on me.
I'm not‐‐I'm not
gonna let them down!
♪
Okay, Aichi's
ready to fight back.
Looks like he's finally found
the confidence he needed.
‐Oh, yeah?
‐Huh?
How can you be so sure?
Huh?
Oh, my bad.
I forgot you can
only see the obvious.
I see a lot of things
that aren't obvious.
Like what about the air?
It's invisible and yet I
see the way it pushes things.
You can stop talking now.
You look like you're
enjoying this beating.
So there's
no reason to stop.
With Samurai Spirit's support,
Guiding Zombie attacks.
I won't let him
damage me again.
I guard that attack with Llew!
(laser fire)
Aargh!
Huh, but I still hit
you for two damage.
I end my turn.
Hmm.
What?
There's something
different about that boy.
He's changed.
You're right.
Yeah, yeah?
Fine, you're
on to something.
Time for my turn.
I draw.
All right, enter the fray,
your Paladins await!
I ride the
King of Knights, Alfred!
♪
Yes, that's his best card!
Now he's got a chance
to win the game!
♪
With this string,
I thee wed.
Please save me, Alfred!
Nothing but your holy sword
can cut through this string!
Hey, look there.
Aichi's about to
start turning it up.
Marron, move
to the back row.
I activate Alfred's
counter blast.
♪
Hang three, I search my
deck for a grade 2 unit.
♪
‐Hmm.
Paladins, we ride.
The knights are about to
bring the pirates to justice.
Lucky for Aichi he's
got a grade 3 out.
That should do.
That should do?
♪
First I'll have
Wingal support Gallatin
and attack Nightmist.
♪
Uh, no guard.
Grrr, gotcha!
Ugh, damage trigger check.
Royal Paladins,
the king needs your help.
I call on you to
lend me your strength.
♪
Uh, I don't guard.
Twin drive,
first check!
(galloping)
Second check.
Now feel the mighty
power of the holy sword!
Face your punishment!
Aargh!
I check for a
damage trigger.
Huh?
It looks like the pirates
are the lucky ones today,
'cause I just got
a heal trigger.
Captain Nightmist
gains 5,000 power
and I also get to heal
one point of damage.
(whinnying)
With support from Marron,
Gordon attacks your Vanguard.
♪
Fine, I defend against
that with Nightmist.
♪
Hi‐ya!
My turn's done.
I can't believe I only
dealt one damage to him.
If it wasn't for
that heal trigger,
I'd be in pretty
bad shape right now.
I shouldn't
underestimate him.
He's not the same kid.
He‐he, look at Gouki.
He's getting super
frustrated right now.
Both of them
have three damage.
Impressive, Aichi's really
holding his own out there.
He is playing a lot
better these days,
wouldn't you say?
Hardly.
What do you think, Kai?
Aichi's sure playing a lot
better these days, isn't he?
‐Right?
‐Mmm‐hmm.
Wow, the battle is even
up to this point, folks.
This is the
championship match
we've been waiting
for all day long.
This has to be one of the
most exciting Vanguard fights
I've ever seen
in my entire life!
It's more than
I can handle!
It just keeps
on getting better!
How is this audience
containing their
excitement so well?
It really is a
fun match to watch.
Right?
Ah‐ah‐ah‐choo!
I'm sick of waiting
for the results.
You may have improved
since last time, Aichi,
but listen up, you're still
not playing at the level
of someone who's ready
for the national tournament.
You probably think you've
got my deck all figured out,
but I'm gonna show
you the true power
of my Undead Pirate crew.
Here I go.
Hmm.
I call Knight Spirit.
Rawr!
Now I activate Spirit Exceed's
skill from the drop zone.
I move Samurai Spirit
and Knight Spirit to the soul.
And since I have
a grade 2 Vanguard,
Spirit Exceed can move
into the Vanguard circle.
Ghost of the captain return
to the living world once more,
with a superior ride!
Spirit Exceed!
Rawr!
A grade 3 came back
from the drop zone?
Ha ha, I hope you didn't
think that Captain Nightmist
was the only unit
you had to worry about.
It's like I told
you last time,
my pirates will
keep coming back
until they defeat you.
This is bad.
I don't know
if Aichi can deal
with a resurrection
of this level.
Looks like Gouki is getting
ready to finish him off.
Of course he is.
No one can beat
our captain, kaboom!
If only the same
was true for you
we wouldn't be
here right now.
Oh, kaboom.
Guiding Zombie
moves to the back row
and I call
a second Spirit Exceed.
Rawr!
Raise the sails
and swab the decks,
the pirates are gonna
make you walk the plank.
♪
He's got two grade 3s
in the front row.
That's a lot more power
all of a sudden.
Come on, man, you just need
to survive this attack.
Aichi.
♪
Please, bro.
Gouki is really good,
how long can I hold on?
Aichi, the best defense
is a good offense.
If you spend too much
of your hand on defense‐‐
Then I'll lose.
Oh, that's right.
If I lose,
so does the team.
Kai, Misaki, Kamui.
Okay, I'm gonna do
my best for everyone.
Team Q4, watch me.
Next time, The Holy
Dragon Descends.
I'll picture it.
The winner of this
cardfight will be me.