♪
That hit proved to be too much,
even for my dragonic overlord.
And now, I'm a spirit again.
My units have been removed
from the Planet Cray.
I have lost.
♪
Aichi.
Aichi!
Huh?
♪
I have to...
Good morning.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you didn't even
have an alarm clock.
My bad.
I worry about you.
Here, have some breakfast.
Thanks.
Emi, you're the greatest.
Yeah, whatever, just
hurry up and eat already.
You can't be late
for school again.
Okay.
Huh?
♪
Oh.
Ah.
Mm‐hm.
♪
Aichi, you'd better
be ready to go!
Huh?
You hear me?
(frustrated sigh)
♪
Huh?
Bye, you guys,
I'll see you after school.
♪
How could...
How nice.
Aichi's been heading off
to school earlier these days.
But up until last week,
I was still having to drag him
out of his room in the morning.
Now that I think about it,
he's been late coming home
for the last couple of days too.
Wouldn't it be nice
if your brother's found
something fun to do at school?
At school?
Mm...
(kettle whistles)
Huh‐‐oopsie!
Emi, you need to get going.
You're gonna be
late for school.
(gasps)
See ya later!
♪
(panting)
What's up with him?
Hey, Emi, good morning!
Oh, nice to see you, Mai.
Everything okay?
Huh?
Yeah, I just thought
I might be late for school.
Anyways, did you
finish your homework?
Do you mean the report
on insects' habitats?
I think bugs are gross,
so I didn't do it.
Huh?
Can I put my name
on your report?
Hey, what gives?
Uh, no‐‐nothing, let's go.
Sure.
(laughter)
‐Hey!
‐What's up, Aichi?
Oh, hey guys.
We'll race you
to school, come on!
Eat my dust!
Can't this wait for gym class?
A great number of famous
literary figures appear
during this time period.
‐Of course, this had...
‐These are great!
(schoolyard chatter)
Goodbye, my ride's here.
Okay, see you tomorrow, Emi.
Yeah, see you.
Hm.
Now that I think about it,
he's been late coming home for
the last couple of days too.
Wouldn't it be nice
if your brother's found
something fun to do at school?
I've gotta figure this out.
(sighs)
It's one thing if
he wants to have fun,
but Mom might worry if
he's late for dinner again.
Seriously?
Yeah, I really said that.
Hey, what's that private
school girl doing here?
Oh, waiting for a boy, probably.
Ha, maybe I'm that boy.
As if, dude.
Huh?
Ah!
This school doesn't even
have a security guard.
(Emi gasps)
Aichi!
Hold it right there, Aichi.
You're not allowed
to go home yet.
Huh?
Oh, hey there.
You probably thought
you were gonna get away
from us today, huh,
but we've got
other plans for you.
Hm‐‐oh.
Oh, Aichi's gotten involved
with some bad people!
Yeah, I'm in
a gang or something.
(gasps)
Because today, I'm gonna
show you my full strength.
Hope you're ready for a beating.
You wanna battle me again?
Are you too good
to fight me or something?
Uh, no, I didn't mean it
like that, Morikawa.
Well then, let's get going.
On to battle!
You're gonna fight me after.
Sure, but not before
I let him have it!
Don't go too hard on me, guys.
I'll save you, Aichi!
You are gonna get it.
No!
I'll stop these
punks myself, hmph!
♪
Why doesn't he just run away?
They're not even
holding on to him anymore.
♪
(sinister chuckle)
Huh?
♪
(sinister chuckle)
(Emi gasps)
What should I do?
These are the scariest
guys I've ever seen.
How awful!
♪
‐We're here!
‐Huh?
♪
"Card Capital"?
Why'd they come here?
Oh no, this must
be where they‐‐
(indistinct conversation)
Whaddya think of our hideout?
This is where we'll battle.
Only it's gonna be twenty
of us against one of you.
Huh?
I only like fighting people that
are drastically outnumbered.
♪
I'll save you, brother.
(indistinct chatter)
Huh?
(stammering)
♪
This place, what is it?
Hi there, little lady.
Thanks for visiting
Card Capital.
I'm the manager of
this fine establishment.
Please, call me Shin.
So, how can I help you today?
Well, I...see, I...
Is, uh, this your first
time in a card shop?
I‐‐yes.
I see.
Okay, this shop sells TCG,
trading card game
products and such.
What's a trading card game?
Uh, well, they're games
where you collect
different cards and
battle your friends.
As you can see,
once school is over,
we get pretty busy in here.
So that's it!
Hey, I know that uniform.
You go to that
all‐girls private school.
Well...yeah?
Hm, if I could
get you interested
in trading card games,
it could spread throughout
your entire school.
Yeah, right.
Hey, would you like
a guided tour from
the shop manager?
Sure.
The staff generally
hangs around the counter.
If you need anything,
you can talk to them.
The sleepy one is my assisticat,
and that angry‐looking
girl there is Misaki.
If you call me that
one more time...
(Shin gasps)
Scary!
I'm kidding.
She's actually my niece,
and you know, she really
loves trading card games.
What?
Speaking of which...
This is our most
popular game right now.
It's called Vanguard.
(Emi gasps)
Oh.
Those are the game tables.
That's where people can sit
down and fight their friends.
Aichi.
Oh, check it out!
Those two players
are about to start
their very own Vanguard battle.
See, the best part
of the game is‐‐hm?
Hm...hm.
Are you ready for
an epic battle, Aichi?
Yeah.
(gasps)
(me‐yawning)
Okay, I'm gonna beat you
and show everyone who's boss.
All right, let's do this.
♪
‐Stand up my... Vanguard!
(screeching)
(chuckling)
A handful of powerful
cards, as expected.
Better watch out, Aichi,
this is gonna be a quick one.
I'll do my best to stop you.
♪
Ride, Little Sage, Marron.
I'll end my turn there.
Oh yeah!
Hm.
Just perfect.
I ride my Vanguard.
Embodiment of Armor, Bahr!
♪
(roaring)
Here comes my
super‐strong attack!
Oh no, I guard with Elaine.
(gasps)
Check for a drive trigger.
(bellowing)
♪
Looks like you escaped
that one, Aichi.
(Aichi weakly chuckles)
But your Grade 1 Vanguard
won't be safe for much longer,
'cause I've got some
super‐powerful units
in this deck.
The clock is ticking and
your time's almost up.
Right, then in that case...
Hm.
♪
Aw, geez.
Looks like that guy's deck
has some serious balance issues.
Oh?
Hm.
You're watching that
game pretty closely.
Do you understand
what's going on so far?
Uh‐uh, not really.
It all happened so fast.
It's okay.
It takes everyone a while
to learn the rules of the game.
So don't worry.
Hey, I know.
When this match is over,
I can give you some
Vanguard lessons.
Shouldn't you be working?
Well, if you wanna
know anything,
‐just ask me.
‐Thanks.
Huh.
You ready?
Huh?
(exclaims)
Not him!
Stand up, My Avatar!
Now ride, Blaster Blade!
♪
This is a side of
Aichi I've never seen.
I call Wingal to rear guard
and a pair of Gallatins.
♪
Oh man, what a pain.
But if you think I'm afraid
of Grade 1 and 2 units,
then guess again.
I just need to get some of
these Grad 3 units into play.
I'll start by attacking
Bahr with Gallatin.
♪
That's only one damage.
For my next attack, I support
Blaster Blade with Wingal
and attack Bahr.
♪
Blaster Blade gains an
additional 4,000 attack power
when supported by Wingal.
♪
I check for a drive trigger.
(roaring)
Hmph.
Are you done yet?
Finally, I attack with
my other Gallatin.
(yelping)
What's the matter, man?
Why aren't you
guarding these attacks?
'Cause I can't‐‐just look here.
Hm?
Uh...they're all Grade 3.
My deck is all power cards.
Why would I waste space
with stupid Guard 1, right?
♪
That's the end of
my turn, Morikawa.
Yeah!
Playtime's over, you lose!
And now, my comeback.
Come on, Grade 2.
(gulps)
Hey, so what'd you get?
Oh.
Without a Grade 2 unit,
that handful of Grade 3s
isn't gonna do you any good.
Why do I never draw the
cards I actually need?
It's like my deck is
haunted by an evil spirit.
Why must the spirit mock me so?
We don't allow evil
spirits in this store.
Huh?
Your Vanguard starts at Grade 0
and you have to work your
way up to Grades 2 or 3
using all grades of units
to get you there.
It doesn't matter how many
powerful cards you have
if you can't play them.
Oh.
Time for a Bahr tag team.
♪
(maniacal laugh)
You think you're so smart
with your good grades
and your good deck.
Well, I have a good
deck too, here it is.
I attack with Bahr,
supported by Bahr!
(roaring)
Now I check the drive trigger...
no luck, as always.
But I scored another
awesome Grade 3.
My attack doesn't need
a drive trigger to hit you.
Blaster Blade!
Then I guard with Flogal.
Huh?
(roaring)
♪
No way, not again!
Why do I always have
such terrible luck?
What a rookie.
Well, I guess it makes sense
that a guy who's
so easily excitable
would fill a deck
with all power cards
and then lose with them, huh?
So it's my turn now, right?
Okay, Gallatin will
attack Bahr first.
♪
(roar)
That's odd.
To look at my brother
and that spiky weirdo now,
it's like watching two
completely different people.
When I first laid
eyes on that guy,
all I could think was how
big and scary he looked.
But now, he seems so harmless.
And...
I'll check for a damage trigger.
Gimme something!
About time he got a good draw.
Okay, get out
the history books,
'cause I'm about
to make a big play.
Hm.
Oh.
Aichi has always been afraid.
I used to have to force him
to go to school in the mornings.
♪
But he looks so much
bigger than he used to.
♪
With my Blaster
Blade and Wingal,
I attack your Bahr for the win!
♪
And the thing
that changed Aichi,
I'm sure that it must
be this card game,
Vanguard.
(growling)
I'm not gonna let
you do that, Aichi.
I guard with the power of Tahr,
uber‐strong spear god.
10,000 plus 8,000
equals 18,000.
That means your attack
has failed to hit.
Uh, you sure?
What do you mean?
You see, my Blaster Blade
has got 9,000 attack power
to begin with,
and he gets a 4,000 point bonus
when Wingal is in rear guard.
Combined with Wingal's
own power of 6,000, and...
19,000 total.
And then...
What now?
I can't forget to turn over
a card for a drive trigger.
Huh?
Oh!
Epona.
That's a critical trigger!
5,000 attack power.
Also, one damage.
Hm.
(exclaiming)
♪
(yelling)
That's the end of the game.
I can't believe it.
Yet again...I lose.
Yeah, I mean, no kidding.
Aichi has zero cards
in his damage zone.
What?
You're right!
How could I fail so badly?
Geez, man, what did
I do in a former life
to deserve this?
(sighs)
‐Aichi?
‐Hm?
Huh‐‐Emi!
Oh.
Do you know that
guy or something?
A friend, maybe, or is he‐‐
Well, sir, this girl is my‐‐
So I guess you've
been getting home late
because you're coming
here to play games.
Um...yeah.
‐Huh?
‐Oh?
♪
Uh...
So this is Vanguard, huh?
I like the pictures.
Blaster Blade.
Stand up, My Avatar!
Now, ride, Blaster Blade!
♪
This is what you've been up to.
Emi, I‐‐I can...
You know what?
I think you've changed
a little, Aichi.
Hm?
Is it really fun to play?
♪
Mm.
Can this be happening?
Is my brother finally
coming out of his shell?
Is she your girlfriend
or something?
Yeah.
Guys, that's my sister.
Ah, makes sense.
Aichi, will you play
again so I can watch?
Huh?
It's fun, right?
So fight again.
Uh...well, I...hm?
Yeah, come on!
This could be the
epic comeback rematch
I've been waiting for!
Heh.
‐Pulverize 'im.
‐Huh?
Mm.
Let's do this!
I'll take you, and
your tiny cheerleader!
♪
‐Stand up!
Vanguard fighting?
So that's what
you've been up to?
Yeah.
‐It's fun?
‐Totally.
Mr. Sendou, tell the
class why it's fun.
Yes, teacher.
I made friends,
and when I play,
I'm not shy anymore.
I'm a fighter!
So who are you fighting next?
Misaki?
The image of this battle
is crystal‐clear in my mind.
♪