(evil laughter)
(shouting)
We always play
a game of numbers.
I can only imagine your despair,
being cornered like a rat.
♪
This turn will be
your last, Aichi.
Think long and hard about
the move you're going to make.
♪
♪ Vanguard, well
it's not a lie ♪
♪ This legend will
be starting now ♪
♪ To the future, just
lead us all the way ♪
♪
♪ Go! ♪
♪ We can't hold back this
feeling just any longer ♪
♪ Come on, tear off
everything you've got ♪
‐♪ Get crazy way ♪
♪ There's no stopping,
there's no running ♪
♪ I can hear his voice
calling for me somewhere ♪
♪ I'll cross the bridge,
a head‐on battle now ♪
‐♪ Here we go ♪
‐♪ Hurry up ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
ever interfere ♪
♪ 3, 2, 1, let's go! ♪
♪ Vanguard, an image
comes rising from deep
within our souls, yeah ♪
♪ Awaken it right now
with a miracle ♪
♪ Vanguard, now we all become ♪
♪ That burning red hot
blazing flame to the future,
we'll keep on racing through ♪
♪ Final turn ♪
♪
(indistinct conversations)
(whimpering)
♪
Here goes.
Elaine, it's a good card,
but it's not that
great for attacking.
I know what to do.
This is my chance.
Enter the fray, kneel
before your king!
I ride!
(screaming)
(explosions)
♪
Oh, you have Alfred, the
king of the Royal Paladins.
He gains attack power from each
of his loyal allies, correct?
I'm impressed that you have a
card that strong in your deck.
Will it help, I wonder?
So that's what he's
been holding on to.
Keeping a Grade Three in hand
is exactly what I would've done.
Looks like Aichi's
finally starting to learn.
Alfred's skill gives him
an extra 2,000 attack power
for each Royal Paladin
in the rear‐guard
with a max possible
boost of 10,000.
Add that to his own number
and he's attacking
for 20,000 a turn.
My Voidmaster only
has 9,000 attack power.
Even if I were to guard
with a 10,000‐point shield,
it still wouldn't be enough.
The attack would get
through to me quite easily.
However, you only have
three Royal Paladins
in your rear‐guard,
meaning Alfred only has
a 6,000‐point bonus.
What you really need to
do is call two more units,
but with merely
one card in hand,
I'm afraid that's not an option.
‐That's where you're wrong.
‐Huh?
Royal Paladin units
share a bond of trust,
and therefore, I can
call units into battle
‐straight from my deck.
‐What?
First, I move Marron
to rear‐guard.
Then, I activate Barcgal
and Alfred's abilities.
(howling)
♪
Join the battle, Flogal.
Silent Knight, Gallatin,
your king calls!
♪
Five Royal Paladins,
just like that?
I wasn't aware you could
do that sort of thing.
Yeah, Paladins know
how to work together
‐for the greater good.
‐Is that so?
Then perhaps you'd
be willing to show me
the true power of your clan.
I support Gallatin with Flogal
and attack your Voidmaster!
♪
Not again.
It's the Ninja Art
of Log Substitution.
So now you're talking
like a ninja too?
Nice try, but unfortunately,
an attack of that level
isn't going to get
through my defenses.
Yeah, how about this?
I attack you with Alfred!
♪
With 20,000 attack power?
I have no choice but
to take the damage.
♪
It's time for my twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
Hm?
Yes, stand trigger activated!
What?
I add 5,000 attack
power to Gallatin.
Plus, I stun the Gallatin
that just attacked.
♪
You're doing great, bro.
You've got him at
five damage already.
‐Just one to go!
‐You're gonna win, yo!
Using the support of Marron,
I attack with Gallatin.
♪
Ninja Art of Log Substitution!
That's not enough
to stop the attack.
Quickly, my ninjas, go forth.
Protect Voidmaster at all costs!
♪
Was that ever a close call?
‐Huh.
‐Hey, what's up?
That was a bad play.
He should've just let
the attack go through.
Huh, hm?
Hm, I see, since he had to use
intercepts on that last
attack I guess that one card
in his hand probably doesn't
have a damage shield.
Yeah, that's gotta be the case,
which means the only way
he's gonna survive
Aichi's next attack
is if he's able to
draw a heal trigger.
So if he needs to pull
a heal trigger to win,
he's better off trying to
get it earlier in the turn
‐rather than later, right?
‐Exactly.
It would've reduced the damage,
and his Vanguard
would've received
an extra 5,000 attack
power on top of that.
Now it makes sense, with
a boost to his attack power
he wouldn't have to use as many
cards to guard against attacks.
That last play put him
in a really bad spot.
His inability to think ahead
just cost him the game.
This fight is over.
With Gallatin
standing once again,
I attack your Vanguard
for the win.
(whimpering)
♪
Who is this kid?
Answer me this, Aichi Sendou!
I, I guess, I guess
I would make sure I always
had an escape plan.
In the classroom
he's a nervous wreck,
but on the battlefield it's
a completely different story.
He's overflowing
with confidence.
How did this happen?
Well, Ninja Master, will
you guard the attack or not?
♪
Looks like I'm checking
for a damage trigger.
No such luck.
(shouting)
You've beaten me.
Our winner is Aichi Sendou!
(cheering)
♪
I did it!
‐That was amazing, bro.
‐Wow, buddy.
‐Talk about an epic comeback.
‐Thanks, you guys.
I knew he'd win, he beat
me after all, right?
Like that's hard to do.
(laughing)
He looks happy.
Pretty impressive for
his first tournament.
Hey, when exactly
did you get so good?
I guess you've finally been
taking my teachings to heart.
The only thing
you teach people‐‐
Good work, Aichi,
it appears you've finally
made some new friends.
Always hang on to a strong card.
Man, can you believe you
beat a real Ninja Master?
Uh, he may look like a ninja,
but that's really just‐‐
hold on, where'd he go?
Oh, you let him get away!
What's the matter?
I was gonna ask the Ninja Master
to make me his disciple.
‐Huh?
‐I had it all planned.
He and I were gonna become
a crime‐fighting duo
called The Super Sonic
Ninja Fighters of Doom.
I can't do it alone!
It's okay, maybe you'll
see him again someday.
As if, ninjas only reveal
themselves to attack.
Oh hey, are those some of
my students over there?
Hey, hey, Mr. Mark.
What a coincidence
bumping into you guys.
Are you cats playing in
that tournament today?
Oh, totally, this
guy just battled
‐a real Ninja Master and won.
‐Wow, really?
That's amazing, I would've
loved to see that battle!
Hey, teach, I don't think
I've ever seen you here before.
Uh, yeah, the funniest
thing happened.
I was just in the
neighborhood and I heard
there was a card
tournament going on,
so I figured why not
check it out, right?
‐You don't say.
‐If you like Vanguard,
then why don't you try
playing it some time?
Yeah, not a bad idea.
Wow, seems like you've got
a pretty cool teacher, Aichi.
Uh, hey, Mr. Mark,
what're you gonna do with
that bag you're carrying?
This is just a bag of clothes
that I'm donating to charity.
It's certainly not a ninja
costume, 'cause that'd be crazy.
Okay, it's time for our
next two card fights.
Um, pardon me, but
can you hide this?
♪
Thanks for being
such a great teacher,
Ninja Master M.
We will now begin our last
matches of the second round.
Let's start!
‐Stand up, my Vanguard!
♪
This is it, Asura Kaiser, go!
Finishing hold!
‐Darn.
‐The winner, Kamui Katsuragi!
‐Oh yeah!
‐The finals, here we go!
‐Like a champ, yo!
‐You know it, my peeps.
You didn't really
think the great Kamui
would get knocked out
in the second round.
(laughing)
That's good, I'm
glad he made it.
Ha, he's got a big ego
for someone so small.
Looks like Misaki is
having a tough battle.
Huh?
They both have four damage.
And their units seem
pretty evenly matched too.
Yeah, it's a close fight.
Hm, a close fight?
Someone should teach those boys
that looks can be deceiving.
Activating Amaterasu
soul charge.
Now I get to take a sneak peek
at the top card of my deck.
Silent Tom, huh?
I'll send this card to
the bottom of my deck,
'cause next I'm gonna play
Oracle Guardian Hermes.
His eye predicts the future
and sees through all.
Until this turn is over,
you're gonna have to play
with your hand revealed.
What?
You can't hide
anything from Hermes.
Now show me your cards.
There.
So that's what you're
holding on to.
Now show me the top
card of your deck.
What, that too?
I told you, Hermes
sees everything.
♪
Put that card back
on top, please.
I'll have Hermes swing in
at your Stardrive Dragon.
Tristan will guard that attack.
♪
Next, with the support of CoCo,
I'll have Silent Tom
attack your Vanguard.
♪
She won't be able to
guard with that one,
'cause it's a Grade Three.
And Misaki knows
she can't defend it.
‐That is so cruel!
‐But that's not all.
‐I check for‐‐
‐You don't have a trigger.
(sighing)
Misaki stacked the
deck against that girl
by leaving that card on top.
What a scary way to play!
That's how it was when
I fought against her.
I attack with Amaterasu
supported by Gemini.
♪
I'm checking twin drive.
Milk, Wiseman, no triggers.
Still, this attack
is for 22,000.
Even if you activate a damage
trigger you're only gonna get
a bonus 5,000 attack
power at best.
To put it simply, there's
nothing you can do about it.
The only chance you have
of surviving right now
is if you have a heal
trigger on top of your deck.
Damage check.
So this is the way it all ends.
(explosions)
Our winner is Misaki Tokura!
(cheering)
There you have it, folks,
after two action‐packed rounds
we've got our four finalists.
A Block winner, Aichi Sendou.
Way to go, Aichi,
don't loose, okay?
I think that's the plan.
B Block winner, Misaki Tokura.
‐Is she blushing?
‐How cute.
Bite me!
Hey, you guys, don't
get me into this.
The winner of Block C,
Kamui Katsuragi.
‐Yay, Kamui!
‐Thank you.
‐Thank you!
‐No way, best in the world!
Best in diapers, hail King Baby!
Knock it off, which one of
you guys is making fun of me?
Uh‐uh, uh‐uh, uh‐uh, uh‐uh.
And our Block D
winner, Toshiki Kai!
(cheering)
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
but before we move on,
there's one more thing
we have to take care of.
‐We're drawing numbers, right?
‐Nope.
It's time for lunch.
‐Are you serious?
‐Check it out.
It's on today's schedule
and everything.
Huh?
Oh, look at that.
Like I was saying,
we'll break now for lunch
and meet back here
at one o'clock.
Do your best not to be late.
Being a referee is no easy job.
My back is killing me.
Hm, that's just over an hour.
Ahhh, why do we have
to wait an hour?
I wanna get this
going right now!
Well, unlike you, some of us
actually need to eat food.
‐Oh, I didn't bring anything.
‐I did!
What?
Here, Aichi, it's for you.
No way, you mean
you made us lunch?
Wow, looks like you've
got a whole picnic there!
You're amazing, no,
really, to prepare‐‐
I didn't do it all by myself.
Mom had to help me
out a little bit.
‐It's so beautiful!
‐Actually, Mom made all of it.
I just carried it here.
(meowing)
♪
Oh hello, what's the
matter, little guy?
Well, I understand
a little cat language
‐if you need me to translate.
‐Really?
No, just messin' with ya.
Hey, did she just‐‐
Make a joke?
(laughing nervously)
Assisticat just wants to tell
you that you're not allowed
to eat your lunch
inside the store.
Oh, I didn't know.
We have a no food
or drink policy here.
Well, yeah, the cards
wouldn't be worth anything
‐all covered in food.
‐Okay then.
I'm sorry, no one told
me all these rules.
(meowing)
What do we do about lunch?
There's a bench right next to
the shop that you guys can use.
Perfect!
I never knew Card Capital
had a spot like this.
Who would've thought eating in
an alley could be so much fun?
‐Thirsty?
‐Thanks, that looks great.
I feel bad for making
you leave the store.
Mm‐mm, it's okay,
we were just talking
about how much we
like it out here.
Good, you're not alone.
‐Huh?
‐Hm?
‐Is the kitty gonna join us?
‐Yeah, there's a cat door.
‐Oh, what a great idea!
‐Really?
I guess so.
‐Would you like‐‐
‐The girl of my dreams
‐with the lunch of my dreams.
‐Tasty, yo.
Why didn't we pack
a lunch like that?
If I could only
share it with her.
(laughing)
♪ Running through
a meadow with you ♪
♪ Oh, what a dream come true ♪
Look, dear, our favorite
spot is right over there.
Yes, the perfect picnic place.
♪
I made some yummy yummy
sandwiches for us.
Oh, you've really
outdone yourself today.
Thanks, now say, "Ahh."
Ahh.
‐What do you think?
‐Mmm!
So good!
♪
Just you wait, one day
I'm really gonna‐‐
Oh boy, Emi, are you
sure we can have some?
‐It all looks delicious, yo!
‐Hm?
Of course, eat up!
No way!
What do you two think
you're doing, huh?
Well, we were
staring at the food
and she asked if we wanted some.
You should have some, yo.
You fools!
How dare you take food
out of Emi's lunchbox?
You're not worthy
of her great cooking!
‐Hey!
‐Huh?
Listen up, it's my lunch, and I
can share it with anyone I want!
‐You got a problem with that?
‐Uh, no.
‐I was just hoping‐‐
‐Hey, it's okay, Emi.
He just got a little excited.
Kamui, you can have
some if you're hungry.
Are you sure about that, bro?
Sure, there's enough
to go around.
I guess I could share my
lunch with someone like you.
(bell ringing)
I guess I can share my lunch
with someone like you.
Here.
Ahhh!
Wait a sec, are you really
sharing food with me?
Huh, uh, yeah.
It's finally happening,
my feelings for Emi
have broken through
to her heart.
♪
Well, I'm ready to
taste your cookin'.
‐Ahhh!
‐What?
Huh, guess he doesn't
wanna get his hands dirty.
‐Ahhh!
‐Ahhh.
Ahhh!
It's so good!
Oh, Emi, it's just the best.
‐'Mui, you're so lame.
‐Super lame.
So what do you think
of the tournament?
‐I expected better.
‐Really?
Don't you find it
interesting that Misaki
made it into the semifinals
and she only started playing
Vanguard a couple weeks ago?
You gotta admit, that's
pretty cool, right?
That just shows how
weak these players are.
Yeah, but what about Aichi?
He's worked really hard
to get to this point,
and it's all because he's
hoping for the chance
to play against you, that
would be a good match.
Aichi's not good enough
to battle with me.
Just like everyone else
here, most of these people
don't even know how to play.
None of them should be
called Vanguard fighters.
You try and act cool, Kai,
but I think you're actually
having a good time.
‐Yeah, right.
‐Oh, come on.
(yawning)
Welcome back, everyone.
The time has come for us
to determine pairings
for the final rounds.
There are four slips of
paper inside this box,
and each one of them has
a number written on it.
All of the fighters will draw
one to decide their positions.
Now we'll start with Aichi.
Go ahead.
Right.
Hold it, don't open it yet!
We'll let everyone
else draw first.
Uh, okay.
Next, pick a number, Kai.
♪
And the last one.
Saving the best for blast, huh?
‐Seriously?
‐The best for blast?
I think he meant best
for last, same old Kamui.
Now, let's find out the results.
Here it is, my chance to
get matched up against Kai.
Come on, let's see!
♪
‐I'm number one.
‐Four.
One and four?
Guess I won't be
playing Kai after all.
‐I've got three.
‐Then that means‐‐
Looks like we get to play
each other again, bro.
I'll have to beat
Kamui to move on.
♪
I'm not gonna hold back
against you, Aichi,
even if you are
my future brother.
Huh?
I won't hold back either.
♪
The winner of these matches
will move on to the finals.
Let the semifinals begin!
♪
♪ I feel the sunshine
lighting up the sky ♪
♪ The sea, the horizon,
feeling so alive ♪
♪ Yes, I have never
felt this way before ♪
♪ The stars in the sky
are glowing just for me ♪
♪ The wind, I've been waiting,
it's here and I believe ♪
♪ Now's the time
and I will fly ♪
♪ I see the "go" sign ♪
♪ Take a chance, yes, no ♪
♪ I can see my
hopes and dreams ♪
♪ I'll fight until the end ♪
♪ Just believe, you will see ♪
♪ It's time to show
the fire burning in me ♪
♪ Fly away, fly far away ♪
♪ Blasting rockets to the sky ♪
♪ We will soar away up high ♪
♪ Let's go together ♪
♪ Catch my star, yes I can ♪
♪ It's the moment of our lives ♪
♪ Our passion burning,
blazing bright ♪
♪ Never giving up, I trust
my heart, now I believe ♪
♪ Yes, we believe our dreams ♪
♪ Together we'll
create new miracles ♪
♪ A beautiful world ♪
♪ Now is the time ♪
♪ We are ready to fight ♪
♪ What are you waiting for,
we are Dream Shooters ♪
All right, I managed to win my
fight against Ninja Master M.
Good going, bro, you've gotten
way stronger since we first met.
Make sure you fight
with confidence
no matter who you're up against.
Thanks, but wait, I'm
fighting you next, Kamui.
All right!
I can't imagine anyone I'd
rather be up against, bro!
Let's fight it out,
bears and bears!
Fair and square?
Next time, Aichi versus Kamui.
I can see it, the path
to victory is before me.