(bell chiming)
Bye Emi, guess I'll
see you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you then, Mai.
Toodles.
Are you guys as excited as I am
for the Vanguard regionals?
Let's get there super early
and grab some good seats.
Hey, do you think we
should ask the winning team
to take a look at
our decks for us?
♪
I wish we were
competing at regionals.
All we have to do is win
the next shop tournament.
‐Easy!
(humming)
Meow.
Good afternoon.
Oh!
Good to see you, Emi.
Your brother and his
friends aren't here yet,
but you're welcome
to wait for them.
Thanks.
Hello, kitty.
Meow.
Huh?
Hm.
So.
You're interested
in Vanguard, huh?
Oh!
Well, yeah, but I don't
think I'd be very good.
It's a hard game, right?
Actually it's not
as hard as you think.
Hm.
Why don't you play a game?
♪
Ow, the power of
life surges through me!
You're sure happy
today, Morikawa.
Yeah.
I've been reading
some amazing things
in this self help book.
Really?
Let me see.
Hey!
I didn't know you could read.
"Mr. Wizard's Self
Improvement Spell Book"?
"How to brainwash people
into liking you more"?
Hey, you used that
spell on me, didn't you?
That wouldn't work on you,
you have to have a brain.
This is the part I'm reading.
Check it out, Aichi.
Let's see.
"A great smile is a
wizard's best friend,
so brush every day".
(laughing)
Every day, as if.
"It's well known that young
people respect the power
of amazing smiles".
Did you hear that, guys?
I'm gonna get the
grade school kids
to worship the ground I walk on.
Yeah.
We'll see about that.
♪
Huh?
Hey, Misaki.
Hi, after you.
Right.
I'll lead the way.
Thanks.
♪
Hey, guys.
Emi, what are you doing here?
Get this.
Your sister's decided to
start playing Vanguard with us.
♪
You mean it?
Not exactly, but I wouldn't
mind trying it out once.
There's no better
place for your first game
than on a Card Capital
standing fight table.
Huh?
Look, I went ahead and adjusted
the step for you and everything.
But I don't even have a deck.
Misaki!
We've got a cardless
young lady over here
in need of your help.
Don't snap your fingers at me.
Here's my deck, use it.
It's strong against boys.
What?
Really?
Wow.
Now let's see.
Who should your
first opponent be?
How about your big brother?
No way.
It's just like the book said.
A grade school kid.
What?
You're playing me.
I taught your brother
everything he knows.
Hope you're ready
for a crash course
in the Morikawa
school of card fights.
Aichi?
Give it your best, Emi.
But I still haven't learned
all the rules of the game yet.
Not a problem.
Kai had to teach me the rules
the first time we played.
We'll help you.
You little...
What do you think you're doing
mentioning that big
showoff in front of me?
Just kidding.
You're the best
Vanguard teacher.
Did you hear that?
What I lack in experience
I make up for in enthusiasm.
Uh...
♪
First give your
deck a good shuffle.
Uh, like this?
Watch this.
It's the Morikawa ultimate
shuffling technique.
No offense, but you look
pretty silly doing it like that.
(panting)
That's enough.
Let's cut each other's decks.
Uh, okay.
With your starting
Vanguard in place,
the rest of your
deck can go over here.
Okay.
All right.
Take the top five
cards of your deck.
Watch a pro.
♪
One, two,
three, four,
five.
Ready, grade school girl?
Yeah.
It's time for one of my
amazing Vanguard tips.
Before the game starts
you can take any number
of cards from your hand
and shuffle them back into
your deck to draw new cards.
You've gotta go for sure.
What are you doing here?
I'll draw three new cards.
There we go.
Powerful grade three units
are the reason I
win so many games.
Last time I checked
you don't win any games.
♪
Oh, how cute!
Actually I'll get rid
of these weird ones.
(laughing)
♪
This one's cute, too!
You like the cards?
That's a good start.
Now, the time
for battle is here.
Imagine yourself!
Our spirits have
just been transported
to the surface of
the planet Cray,
a place much like Earth.
That's the exact
thing Kai said to me
when we first played.
Darn it, Aichi!
Stop trying to embarrass
me in front of my student.
What does Cray look like?
Wow, it's so pretty.
This is pretty?
Hey, where are you?
Uh, I'm right here.
There you are.
Let's do this.
‐Stand up, my Vanguard!
Lozenge Magus!
Go, Lizard Runner, Undeux!
♪
Your guy's scary.
You think this is bad,
just wait until you see what
I have in store for you later.
I hope Emi is there today.
And if I'm lucky
maybe Kai will be, too.
Emi I can understand,
but why on Earth would
you wanna see Kai again?
Makes no sense, yo.
‐Huh?
I attack with Asura Kaiser.
Finishing hold!
I can't believe you
were able to beat Kai.
And now you're the
best player in town.
Is there something
you wanna ask me?
Please, teach me
how to play Vanguard.
Are you sure I'm the right guy?
Of course you are, Kamui.
I wouldn't trust anyone else
to teach my sister
about the game we all love.
Help me, Kamui,
you're my only hope.
♪
Huh?
Ah!
‐What is it?
Why is this happening?
What's the matter?
Tell me it's not real.
It's all a big joke, right?
There's nothing
to be upset about,
she's just playing her
first game of Vanguard.
Yeah, but she's playing
against that big loser.
It should have been me.
I was supposed to
teach her how to play!
Stop your crying.
We're very, very sorry.
I'm with Misaki here.
Please don't get too angry.
Very sorry, yo.
Listen, once a card fight begins
it can't be stopped.
You know that.
It's okay, yo.
But she's with someone else.
Now it's my turn.
I draw.
Oh, yeah, another grade three.
It's sad that your
first game of Vanguard
is about to end
before you know it.
I ride uh, wait, wait a sec.
No way!
My hand is so strong I
don't have any cards to ride.
Oh.
Why?
Why does she have to
play a game with that guy?
It should have
been me up there, me.
I feel so bad for Kamui.
His dreams, yo.
So then, the first thing
I have to do is draw?
Oh, Emi.
It hurts to watch.
I wanted to play you first,
but if I have to sit back here
I promise to do my best to help.
Uh, this one's the cutest.
So I'll ride it.
Hm.
You decide based
on its cuteness?
Is that bad?
You're better off
choosing the unit
with the highest attack power.
Or maybe a unit with an ability
you can use in
the Vanguard circle.
Hey, Kamui.
There's no problem with
people teaching her the rules,
but I'll have to ask you to
keep your personal play style
to yourself for right now.
But it's her first time, yo.
And Kamui's got
lots of experience.
The more decisions
she makes for herself
the more she's gonna learn about
the world of card fighting.
She has to trust her instincts.
It was the same for the rest
of you in your first game.
Yeah.
Yup.
Hm?
Sorry about that, Emi.
He's right, just play
the way you want to.
In that case, how about this?
All I can do is
sit back and watch
while Emi discovers
Vanguard for herself.
I'll never forgive
that loser, Morikawa,
for stealing the first
game against my dream girl!
Aichi, can I put
this one in the back?
All righty.
Next I call um,
these two, Dream Eaters.
♪
Um, first I'll use
Lozenge Magus for support
and attack Undeux with Milk.
If you boost with Lozenge Magus
you have to return
her to the deck.
Nevermind then.
What?
You're not gonna do...
(thud)
‐Are you okay?
Seems like Emi already has
her own style of playing.
♪
Don't forget to
check the trigger.
Oh, yeah.
It's a cute one!
♪
Damage trigger.
Great.
♪
So how exactly do triggers work?
Well, uh...
You go for it.
Step aside, my boy,
I can explain how they work.
Here, how about we take
a look at Lozenge Magus.
It's got, I mean she's
got a drive trigger mark
sitting right above
her shoulder there.
Yeah, I see it.
When your Vanguard
attacks or you take damage
you draw a card.
If you see a mark like that
you'll get a power boost
for one of your units
and an extra effect
based on the mark's color.
Now that green one there
has a healing effect.
Hm.
He's such a great explainer!
Good work, yo.
I think you understand
enough about the game, Emi.
My turn.
Draw!
Huh.
♪
By the great wizard's
beard, a grade one unit.
I say, it's about
time I drew this.
That coming from the guy
that shuffled one away
before we started.
♪
I ride the Embodiment
of Armor, Bahr!
And I call the
Embodiment of Spear, Tahr!
Here comes a super strong
attack at your Vanguard!
Emi, you should
guard the attack.
You can't!
What?
That's the cutest way
to guard I've ever seen.
This unit is my favorite
and I'm not gonna
let you destroy it.
Your Vanguard can't
actually be destroyed.
Are you serious?
But he's gonna hurt her.
Then why don't you use one
of the cards from your hand
to guard the attack?
That's not any better,
the defender will get hurt.
I'll handle this.
You see, in the game of Vanguard
only your spirit makes it down
to the surface of planet Cray.
And it's the creatures
you call into battle
that are gonna
compete on your behalf.
Your units are playing
the same game you are.
So no one gets hurt.
In that case,
I guess
I'll let the attack go through.
Wow, you guys,
she's learned so much.
I knew I loved this
girl for a reason.
‐Uhhuh.
Enough of this sentimental
motivational speaking.
It's time for Bahr's
super strong attack.
♪
All right, my turn.
I stand and draw.
I ride the Maiden of Libra.
She attacks your Vanguard.
I won't let you do that.
I guard with Bahr.
♪
Oh, no.
Aren't you forgetting
to check something?
Thank you.
Drive trigger check.
No way!
There it is!
And it's critical, yo!
Great, you get
5,000 attack power
and an extra damage
for one of your units.
Ha!
♪
Oh, man.
Why am I losing
to a little girl?
You're doing so well
for your first time.
We're cheering for ya.
Yay, Emi!
Unreal, what a great draw.
That drive trigger couldn't
have shown up at a better time.
‐Mhmm.
So luck does play a part.
♪
You seem to have
lady luck on your side.
But I've got the
self improvement wizard.
I haven't had a
chance to read all of it.
But what I have
read has inspired me
to use my winning
smile and charm
to cast a magic spell on you.
The spell of having
respect for your elders.
Oh.
♪
I draw.
Yes, it's a grade two.
I ride the Dragon
Knight Nehalem.
♪
I combine my units for an
attack on the Maiden of Libra.
♪
Drive trigger check.
No trigger.
(screaming)
♪
It's bad news for you, Emi.
Next turn I'm gonna
unleash my ultimate technique,
the triple Morikawa Masher
You see, there's nothing
you can do to stop me.
Once I've done my att‐‐
Now it's my turn, right?
Way to steal my thunder.
In all fairness, you were
being kind of creepy, man.
I'm gonna go draw.
Hm, Appollon is weird looking.
I'll save him for later.
Oh, these two are cute
so I'll have them attack for me.
I call Chocolat
and another one.
Look out, Nehalem.
So adorable how she won't
use her Lozenge Magus.
‐Whatever you say.
Don't tell me
that's all you can do.
Maybe you'll get
a drive trigger.
Oh, this one's the cutest!
It's time for you to
attack, Dream Eaters.
And Chocolat girls, support 'em!
(screaming)
Now that's impressive.
She's taken me to five damage
and it's only her first game.
I can see now that you
really are the sister
of my number one student.
Time for a new lesson.
Here goes.
I hope you're taking notes.
Draw.
Here comes the star of the show.
Just in time to
take the main stage,
I ride Juggernaut Maximum!
♪
Begone.
I have no use for anything
lower than a grade three.
Bow before me,
the great and
powerful Mr. Morikawa.
You're gonna make
a fool of yourself.
Monster Frank.
Tyrant Death Rex.
Demon Eater.
Stealth Dragon Voidmaster.
Hell Spider.
This is what my ultimate
ability looks like.
How do you like it?
The triple Morikawa Masher
leaves you with six
grade threes to beat.
Think of all that twin drive.
Only the Vanguard can make
use of the twin drive ability.
At this point I'm
not even surprised
by how little he
understands the game.
Looks like the bar
has been lowered again.
Wow, this is gonna be good.
(yawinig)
Juggernaut Maximum's
charging in.
♪
Twin drive.
There it is.
Thanks to this trigger
you're about to take even more‐‐
What's wrong?
Afraid of taking the damage?
Actually you can't use a trigger
without having a unit
from the same clan.
Wait, isn't Tahr in...
Begone.
I have no use for anything
lower than a grade three,
grade three, grade
three, grade, three...
What a goof.
Of course, I just
did that to teach you
about not giving up
when you make mistakes.
Let's see you deal with
Monster Frank and Death Rex.
Yeah!
I end my turn.
You need to
lighten up, Morikawa.
Then it's my turn now, right?
I ride CEO Amaterasu
♪
So you're not gonna give up yet?
Your determination to
fight on is impressive.
I call Maiden of Libra
and Oracle Guardian, Nike.
♪
I attack Juggernaut
Maximum with Amaterasu.
And Tahr will guard that attack.
♪
So much for
damaging my Vanguard.
I'm gonna check my twin drive.
Come on.
I really need this card.
Got it!
No way, she got it?
That means 5,000 power
and she gets to
draw another card.
Amaterasu's skill
gives her a power boost
when you have more
than four cards in hand.
So that's 4,000 for the ability.
And an extra 5,000
for the drive trigger.
‐19,000 power.
Which means that
she's about to beat me.
♪
Wow, she just won
her first game ever.
Way to go, Emi!
You're amazing!
A natural, yo.
I'm really proud of you.
That was great.
Aw, thanks, Aichi.
(whimpering)
She stopped the
Morikawa Masher.
But how?
Hey there, are you
gonna be all right?
I should have known my spells
wouldn't win me the game.
This was a battle of
raw talent, after all.
I was wrong to use magic!
Face the facts.
It doesn't work.
You can't just cast
a spell on someone
and make them respect you.
That's weird.
Why would Mr. Wizard lie to me?
Excuse me.
That was a lot of fun.
You were a great teacher,
Mr. Morikawa, thanks.
Uh...
Mister.
(laughing)
What can I say?
I certainly owe a lot to the
teachings of this great book.
I declare you to be
the second graduate
of the Morikawa School.
You call yourself a teacher?
But you're the worst.
Raise your hand, please.
No, we're not in class.
Au contraire.
You know, he is kind
of strong in his own way.
Agreed.
Aichi.
I think next time I
wanna build my own deck.
You should let me
build a deck with you.
I'm great at it.
You know, I've got free time.
How about it?
You wanna enroll in the
Morikawa School of Vanguard
as my third pupil?
Why would I wanna
be your student?
Oh, yes.
My student you will be.
Can you picture it or what?
Show that guy who's boss, Kamui!
Get revenge, yo!
Next time would you mind if I
bring one of my friends along?
Of course not.
The more, the merrier.
So I take it you had fun then?
Mhmm.
Meow.
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Stand up!
♪
Did you have a good time, Emi?
Yeah, it was fun.
But I wonder if
Mr. Morikawa went easy on me.
Um, well, you never know.
Hey, Kamui really wants to
teach you about Vanguard.
Why not play him?
I'd rather play against you
when you're not busy getting
ready for the next tournament.
Next time, Team Q4 heads
for the regional tournament.
The Championship Tournament
is finally about to begin.
Huh?
Where's the manager, Misaki?