♪
And now‐‐
No way, not that!
Not that card!
Yes, it is that card.
No, it's another
Young Pegasus Knight!
♪
Just like I said,
this is the card
I'm going to use to defeat you.
(nervous laughter)
♪
(chuckling)
Why...why do I keep seeing Ren?
♪
Now, picture what lies ahead.
You'll be defeated by
my hand and there's nothing
you can do about it.
♪
Aichi...it's as I feared.
Aichi.
♪
What do you mean there's
nothing I can do about it?
♪
Ugh, man.
Yeah.
Who does he remind you of?
♪
Activating
Alfred's Counterblast.
Superior call Margal!
♪
All right, Aichi built
the last rear‐guard circle!
Which means that Alfred's
finally reached his full power.
♪
First, with support from Marron,
I'll have Palamedes attack
your treasured Black Panther,
and with Palamedes' skill,
he gets
an additional 3,000 power.
21,000, really?
I don't guard.
(grunting)
♪
I check for a damage trigger.
Come on!
Here goes.
Alfred attacks next.
♪
Twin Drive!
(screams)
♪
Nice!
Aichi's got him at 4 Damage!
He's caught up!
It's time.
With a boost from
Pegasus Knight,
Gallatin attacks!
♪
Pegasus Knight!
(chuckles)
(grunts)
I won't let you!
I guard that attack
with Silence Joker!
♪
(grunting)
That's it for my turn.
He's just messing with my head.
I'm not sure what he's planning
with that Pegasus Knight of his,
but if I end the game
now, it won't matter.
We're tied at 4 Damage, and
I've got all the cards I need
to finish this guy off.
You're going down.
(chuckles)
The Great Kyou
rides General Seifried!
♪
That jerk!
I know, yo!
How many times
do we have to tell you?
I'm the great one!
Nobody cares.
I call Highspeed Brakki.
Mecha Trainer moves
to the drop zone.
Supported by the assault squad,
Brakki attacks!
♪
Using Brakki's Soul Blast...
he gets 5,000 power!
(growling)
I don't guard.
(grunting)
I check for a damage trigger.
♪
I don't know if I can watch!
Come on, bro.
(chuckles)
After using Brakki's
Soul Blast to boost his attack,
I shuffle him back
into the deck,
and assault squad stands up
after supporting that hit.
Okay, this is it,
one more damage
will finish you off
and you're gonna squirm
when I beat you.
♪
Who does he think he is?
With a boost from Dudley Dan,
Seifried attacks your Vanguard,
activating Seifried's skill
adding 3,000 power,
and I'm using
Dudley Dan's counterblast!
♪
I superior call
Wonder Boy to rear‐guard!
♪
Let's go, Seifried!
The General's Crusher!
♪
(gasping)
Epona and High Dog
Breeder, Akane will guard that.
That's 25,000.
And Seifried's power
is 17,000 right now.
But if he's able to draw two
triggers during the Twin Drive‐‐
Then the game's as good as over.
Things are looking bad
for Aichi Sendou,
and the thought
on all our minds is:
Will he be able to defend?
Indeed, the Spike Brothers'
deck has the ability to deal
some devastating blows.
Aichi can't afford
to deplete his hand too soon.
It's so tense!
It certainly is.
Aichi's got to survive
this attack and guard
the next one, too!
He just needs some luck.
Drive trigger check.
Nothing there.
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Huh?
With General Seifried
as my Vanguard,
during his Twin Drive check,
if I reveal a Grade 3
Spike Brothers unit,
I can call it to
a rear‐guard circle.
♪
(chuckling)
Now, I've got everything
I need to finish you off
once and for all.
(chuckles)
What's wrong?
Are you too afraid
to talk all of a sudden?
Hardly, I'm just fine,
now hurry up and finish
checking your Twin Drive.
Works for me.
Second check.
♪
Just when you thought
the situation couldn't
get worse!
Then this happens.
You've gotta find a way
to survive these attacks.
Come on!
Well, it's been
fun playing you,
but I've had about enough.
Let's go!
How about we start
with Sky Diver on the right?
He swings in with
a boost from Wonder Boy!
Elaine will guard.
(grunting)
♪
Agh, you may have managed
to stop my first attempt,
but there's more
where that came from!
This time, it's
the Skydiver on my left.
He attacks with a boost
from assault squad!
Pongal will guard.
That isn't gonna
be enough, Aichi Sendou,
and you don't have
any more cards in your hand.
(chuckles)
Do it, Gallatin!
♪
Ugh, he's intercepting?
All right!
I knew he'd find a way.
♪
Way to go, Aichi!
I attacked him four times
and was only able to deal
one lousy damage.
Huh?
♪
Now he's got an open space
in the front row, which means
on his next turn, he'll bring
that Pegasus Knight forward!
Are you done?
Uh, yeah.
Perfect.
Final turn!
(gasping)
No way!
He just said‐‐
Final turn.
♪
Ah, this match
is getting really good.
Is he...?
♪
You're calling final turn?
Are you trying to make
a laughingstock out of me?
I don't have to try,
you're doing just fine
without me.
Quit messing around!
This is bad.
Yeah, he might lose.
That guy acts just like Ren.
♪
Pegasus Knight moves up,
then I call Marron to
the rear‐guard circle.
Activating Margal's skill
by moving Margal to the soul,
I can add 3,000 power
to the unit of my choice.
I'll give it to Pegasus Knight
and have him gain
an additional 3,000
off his own skill.
This is getting ridiculous!
Is he actually gonna win
this fight with that silly card?
With Marron's support,
I'll have Pegasus Knight attack!
(cackling)
Hold on, what happened
to your young Pegasus Knight
finishing me off, huh?
I'm sitting
at 4 damage right now.
So, even if the attack
goes through, that only
puts me at 5 damage.
Stop wasting time.
You gonna guard?
No, I'm not.
(grunting)
♪
Damage trigger check.
I just got a draw trigger!
That's 5,000 power
going to Seifried
and I draw a card.
Perfect, I've got exactly what
I need to defend against him.
(chuckles)
You know, for a moment,
I actually thought
your Pegasus Knight
prediction would come true.
Now, I'm ready to make
my own prediction.
I'm gonna stop your attacks
and the game is mine!
(cackling)
Didn't you hear me?
I said this is the final turn!
(yelps)
Here goes.
♪
(grunts)
Cheer Girl Tiara
will guard that.
♪
Twin Drive check.
Looks like I just
got a stand trigger.
No way!
Pegasus Knight stands
and gains another 5,000 power.
No, you can't!
Hold on, what is this?
It feels like Ren
is in the room.
(whimpering)
(screaming)
♪
(gasps)
Next up, I attack
with Swordsman of
the Explosive Flame's Palamedes
supported by Marron.
During his attack,
Palamedes' ability gives him
an additional 3,000 power.
♪
Ugh, he's at 21,000?
I have to do it.
I'm gonna discard a card
and completely guard
that attack.
Time to fly, Pegasus Knight.
Now, see if you can picture it:
You're standing on
the surface of the Planet Cray,
unable to stop me.
Huh, wait, this is...?
What am I doing here?
Oh, wow.
So, it's true, then?
Yes, he's got it.
Psyqualia.
Hey, this is messed up.
Yeah, the match is ending
exactly the way Aichi
said it would.
It's true.
♪
Agh!
No, no, not
Young Pegasus Knight!
There's nothing I can do.
I won't be able to guard.
(cackling)
♪
Hold on, it's not over.
This can't be it, I haven't
had a chance to get my revenge.
I'm not gonna let
my dream end like this.
All I need to do
is draw a heal trigger!
(grunting)
Huh?
Impossible.
How could this happen?
Did I really just lose
to that little weakling?
I guess I did.
(gasping)
(hysterical caterwauling)
Kyou!
What happened?
Come on, man,
get a hold of yourself.
♪
(gasping)
Oh, no, what are
you turning into?
The winner:
Team Q4's Aichi Sendou!
♪
I won, didn't I?
(grunting)
♪
Huh?
Aichi.
What's wrong?
Are you gonna be okay?
I think so, it's just...
I feel so... strange.
Boy, how lucky are we?
This means it wasn't just
a coincidence that he wandered
into Psy Shop that day.
Right, fate brought him to us.
Hey, you sure look
happy about it, Kourin.
Huh, what do you mean?
Of course I'm happy about it.
We finally found what we've been
looking for this whole time.
Plus, he's a cute guy.
Yeah right, as if.
And what a shocking finish!
Looks like Aichi Sendou
should get a part‐time job
as a fortune‐teller.
That was a cardfight worthy
of the final matchup.
Oh, frankly I'm still shocked
that he was able to turn
his pregame
prediction into reality.
That was definitely
the highlight of the day so far.
Of course it was,
my fights are
always entertaining.
What happened to you
out there anyway?
‐Stand up, my Vanguard.
(cheering)
Do you hear that sound, Emi?
The second fight's started.
Yeah, but, Aichi,
are you gonna be all right?
I'm worried about you.
I'm gonna be just fine.
I think you're overreacting
making me stay here.
In that last match‐‐
Huh?
You scared me.
Why?
It wasn't any different than
the other cardfights I've had.
So, I'm gonna go see
if I can find us some drinks.
Uh, sure.
How come she said
she was scared?
♪
Hey, what about her?
She's doing well.
It's true, she's got
a really sharp mind.
Her powerful memory
makes it possible for her
to stay ahead of the game.
Go, go, go!
Is she...?
No, I...I can't see any traces
of Psyqualia in
the way she plays.
Unfortunately, it doesn't look
like we'll be able to use her.
I was wrong.
Don't feel bad, at least
we've found another one
that has it.
That's right.
♪
(gasping)
Winner, representing Team Q4,
Misaki Tokura!
(cheering)
Yeah, Misaki!
♪
What happened?
Misaki won.
Oh, really?
Then that means
we won the tournament?
Yeah.
All right, we did it.
Uh, Kai?
What is it?
Do you think I've gotten better?
♪
Ever since I started
playing Vanguard,
I've trained and practiced
every day in hopes that I
could be more like you,
and today I finally felt like
I was the player I wanna be.
I'm stronger now, right?
No, Aichi Sendou,
you've gotten weaker.
Huh?
And Team Q4 wins again!
Let 'em hear it, everyone!
(cheering)
Way to go, I knew
you guys could do it!
(cheering)
Here.
(chuckling)
♪
I'll get them.
Now, what's the plan?
Well, I guess this is
the end of the road for us.
Huh?
You guys can't
be ready to give up yet!
We just need to find
another regional qualifier!
Win one of those and we
can still get our revenge
in the national tournament.
We'll destroy everyone!
First, we'll get Ren,
and then we'll get Kai,
and then that Aichi Sendou!
You serious?
It's not gonna happen, dude.
What a poor sport.
It can't be.
The Brilliant Stars!
But why are you guys here?
We heard a rumor that
some pathetic deadbeats
were planning something
at the regionals over here.
We took it upon ourselves
to come by and put a stop to it.
If you guys were smart,
you would have disappeared
from the world of Vanguard.
Disappeared?
It's our job to make sure
filth like you don't ruin
this beautiful world.
♪
Kai, you don't really mean it?
You have gotten weaker.
But why?
I defeated Kyou
in front of everyone!
And now...now this.
If that's what you really think,
then why don't you fight me
and I'll prove to you
exactly how strong I've become!
Hmm?
♪
What's wrong?
You're afraid.
You know that if
we play, I'll win.
(gasps)
Hey, Emi.
Huh?
Are you here to look
after your brother?
Uh.
Aichi, I'm sorry, but I'm
not going to fight you.
Goodbye.
♪
Hey, Kai!
The time has come
for me to quit the team.
Huh, why would you
do something like that?
♪
It's happening again,
just like the last time.
♪
He's gone.
Take it, this card is for you.
♪
From now on, that image
can be your power.
(groans)
♪
Looks like that was
your card after all.
♪
Thank you.
Why, Kai?
(sniffling)
♪
We made it through
the regional tournament.
Now it's time for us
to get ready for
the nationals again!
I know I caused a lot
of trouble last time,
so I'm ready to make up for it.
But what's with Kai
quitting the team?
He's gone, why?
Don't worry, bro!
We're a strong enough
group without him!
You're right.
Next time...
We're better than ever now.
Just picture
the power of our team.
Huh, Ren?
What's this?