Enter the battle
and lead the way.
Ride, King of Knights, Alfred!
♪
And I call Blaster
Blade to the rear guard.
♪
Final turn.
We're not done yet.
♪
(screaming)
I used up my entire
hand to defend it
and it still wasn't enough.
♪
Our first player moving on
to the championship match
is Toshiki Kai!
(cheers and applause)
Kai won his match.
Kai.
♪
That was so fast.
Can you believe that match?
I've seen him finish
quickly before...
Looks like you made
it to the final round.
Hm.
Was there ever any doubt?
That settles it.
The winner of this battle
is moving on to fight
Kai for the championship.
I'm gonna take this.
♪
I know Aichi really
wants to battle Kai,
but I can't lose
in front of Emi.
♪
Sorry, Aichi.
You're going down.
It's my turn.
And he's already at four damage.
♪
I've gotta find a way to
get my attacks through.
♪
Here I come, Kamui.
First I'll switch the
positions of Marron and Epona
to make way for Gancelot.
♪
Now I'll have
Wingal replace Flogal.
He's shifting around
his battle formation
to increase attack power.
This is the most
important moment of the game.
I'll defend with
everything I got.
With support from Wingal
I increase the power
of Blaster Blade.
He's attacking your Vanguard,
Mr. Invincible.
Thanks to Wingal's support skill
he gets an
additional 4,000 power.
♪
I'll let that one through.
But that would be
really easy to guard.
Does this mean
he's giving up, yo?
♪
Damage trigger check.
Yes, I got one.
That's an extra 5,000
power going to my Vanguard.
And I return my
rear guard Invincible
to the standing position.
Power boost or not,
I'm attacking Mr.
Invincible with Alfred.
Royal Paladins,
it's time to lend
your power to the king.
♪
I guard with Shining Lady.
Well, that should do it.
A damage field on top
of the trigger effect
he just gave to his Vanguard.
Looks like this attack
isn't gonna be strong enough.
I guard with Rock the Wall, too.
Huh?
Hey, what was the
point of doing that?
He just wasted
another defense card.
Actually, you can't
be so sure of that.
My twin drive.
First check.
♪
Second check.
All right, a critical trigger.
Huh?
With a double shield
this attack isn't
going anywhere.
What's he gonna do?
So Aichi was able to
get a critical trigger,
but it's not gonna help him?
Looks like Kamui planned ahead.
He used two cards to guard
because he knew
this could happen.
Hm.
Hmm.
I won't let this
chance go to waste.
Activating critical trigger
giving all effects to
Solitary Knight, Gancelot.
♪
I just need to deal
one more damage to him.
It all comes down
to this attack.
I'm gonna move Shining
Lady over to the drop zone.
Rock the Wall's defense skill
sends him to the
soul after guarding.
That makes five
cards in the soul.
I attack your
Vanguard with Gancelot
supported by Marron.
♪
With only two cards in hand
he might not have
anything left to defend with.
I guard the attack
with Rock the Wall.
♪
I move this card to
the soul stack as well.
I gave it everything I could,
but it wasn't enough.
I was so close to ending it.
Hey, can I ask you
something about Rock the Wall?
Don't cards usually
go to the drop zone
after they guard an attack?
Not that card.
Its ability allows you
to place it into the soul
instead of sending it
up to the drop zone.
Ah.
Now that I think of it,
Kamui's soul must
be pretty big by now.
I stand and draw.
Listen up, Aichi.
It's been fun so far,
but we need to bring
this game to an end.
I can't let him do that.
Hit me with your best shot.
Here goes.
I ride Invincible
on top of Invincible.
Huh?
♪
Now that seems like
a waste of a card.
Hm.
What was the point of that?
And now I soul charge
using Invincible's skill.
That makes eight
cards in the soul.
However, I haven't flipped
any cards in the damage zone
so there are no
abilities activated.
He just wasted another card.
What's he up to?
Calling King of Sword.
♪
I'm coming at ya, bro.
I'll have the King of
Sword attack Alfred.
I have to let this one through.
♪
Checking for a damage trigger.
He has two more attacks
and I have two defense cards.
I can do this.
With the support of Shining Lady
I attack your Vanguard again.
Let's go, Invincible!
♪
I guard that with Llew!
Okay.
Here comes the last one.
Using Lucky Girl as support
I attack Alfred
with my Vanguard.
♪
I guard with Morgana.
Joining the defense
I intercept with Blaster Blade.
♪
Hm, here we go.
First check.
He has to pull a
drive trigger here
or the turn passes back to me.
Now the second check.
Stand trigger.
I stand King of Sword.
Plus, I add 5,000
power to my Vanguard.
I guess this is the end.
♪
Iron Fist strike!
Ah!
Damage trigger check.
No way, it's a heal trigger!
I use its effect to raise
Alfred's power by 5,000.
And I recover one damage.
I did it.
I was able to
survive all his attacks.
There's something
you should know, Aichi.
Huh?
My Vanguard soul has
eight cards in it.
A soul blast?
♪
My soul blast.
What does it do?
I move eight cards from
my soul into the drop zone.
Next I pay a cost of
five from the damage zone.
Activating
Invincible's final skill
I'll have all my units
stand up once more.
What?
♪
His secret technique?
Tornado stand galactica!
♪
(laughing)
In order for Kamui to activate
Mr. Invincible's soul blast
he had to have eight
cards in the soul
combined with five
unflipped damage as well.
And you can only use that move
after your Vanguard
lands a damaging attack
on your opponent.
Huh, I see.
That explains why he's
been sending so many cards
to the soul recently.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
He's been preparing for
this moment the entire game.
Exciting.
♪
All of his units
are ready to attack?
This is the end, bro.
Now you know
the power of my Nova Grapplers.
With the support of Lucky Girl
I'll have Invincible
attack your Vanguard.
♪
There's nothing I
can do to stop you.
♪
Twin drive, first check,
second check.
♪
Iron fist strike!
I do a damage trigger check.
♪
I lost the game.
Kai.
Looks like I just wasn't
strong enough after all.
And there you
have it, everybody.
The winner is Kamui Katsuragi.
Oh, yeah!
Aichi.
I still haven't learned
all the rules of the game.
But I had a lot of
fun watching you play.
So you did great.
Oh, that's sweet, Emi.
She's right, man.
Oh, hey you guys.
That was epic!
Yeah, not bad for a shrimp.
Hey, Aichi.
Huh?
You know, you've
gotten so much better
since the last time we battled.
At this rate I don't like
my chances for next time.
We know a crazy strong
player when we see one.
Say yes, yo.
Thanks, you guys.
Hey, you already won,
you don't need to
make fun of him, too.
It's not what
you think, Morikawa.
They're just trying to make
me feel better about losing,
that's all.
And I'm really happy I
got to play in that match.
It was fun,
but losing feels awful.
♪
Aichi.
Hm.
Hey, Kamui.
We'll start the final match
after a short break, okay?
Prepare yourself.
Sure thing.
Hey, you're gonna
watch me, right, Emi?
I'll be champion in no time.
Well, uh...
So, are you ready
for the finals or what?
Of course I a‐‐ oh!
Huh?
You okay?
What happened, yo?
Uh, forget about it.
My legs are feeling
wobbly all of a sudden.
What's going on?
It looks like he does
get nervous after all.
Hm.
♪
Did you have fun today?
Not really.
I wouldn't have
entered this tournament
if you hadn't forced me to.
♪
You know Kai is obviously
gonna win the championship.
No way, dude.
Kamui's the best ever.
You're not allowed to leave yet.
Wait around until
after the final match.
Huh?
Okay.
For the final we'll
be using the patented
Card Capital standing
fight table, patent pending.
♪
How do you expect
me to battle someone
I can't even look in the eye?
Raise my platform
higher, already!
Well, if I raise it any higher
you'll have trouble
handling your cards.
Kamui, I think you're just
gonna have to put up with it.
That's lame, yo.
Fine then.
I'll play at a
height disadvantage.
But I'm not happy about this!
Aichi.
Now then.
The time has finally come
for the Card Capital Shop
Tournament Championship Match!
Toshiki Kai
versus Kamui Katsuragi.
I've been waiting for
my chance at a rematch.
But this time I, uh,
I'm gonna have my reform.
He means "revenge".
That didn't make sense.
It's too bad
that I have to face you again.
What?
I was hoping I'd be able to play
someone worthwhile
in the finals,
but it seems I was dreaming.
I'll show you.
Hey, what are you
doing over here?
Huh?
Are you still
upset about losing?
Look.
I'm a bit of an expert.
When you lose you're not
allowed to give up, okay?
You're an expert?
On losing, yeah.
I needed that.
Thanks, guys.
Stand up, my Vanguard.
Stand up, the Vanguard.
The main event.
Come on, let's go watch.
Sure.
I ride Jarron and call Aermo.
I ride Tough Boy.
♪
Brutal Jack released
into high gear.
I attack you with Brutal Jack.
Your attack will fail.
I guard with Ganlu.
♪
This match.
It's great.
But see how you like
my superior ride.
The embodiment
of victory, Aleph.
♪
Nova Grapplers,
rise to the occasion.
Tornado stand galactica!
♪
That's it.
The move he beat me with.
Let's see if you can withstand
three more of my attacks.
Just you try me.
Oh, yeah?
Such big talk for
a guy about to lose.
With Tough Boy's support,
my Clay‐Doll attacks
your Dragonic Overlord.
♪
Checking the damage trigger.
Supported by Clara,
Mr. Invincible attacks you next.
I'll guard with Tahr,
the Embodiment of Spear.
Kai just stopped
him in his tracks.
There's still more.
I'm sending in
Tough Boy supported by Shout.
I intercept with Nehalem.
I've used too much of my hand,
not to mention my rear
guard holding him off.
My units don't have
the power to finish him.
They're both playing so well.
Kai hardly flinched
stopping all those attacks.
Even after tornado
stand galactica.
I've never seen
anything like it.
This match is at a
whole other level.
Let's put an end to this.
Ah.
Final turn.
Huh?
I can't believe it.
The last battle
of the tournament.
It all comes down to this turn.
♪
Supported by Bahr
I attack Invincible with
my Dragonic Overlord.
♪
Lucky Girl will guard that.
The twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
♪
I got a critical trigger.
Dragonic Overlord
gains 5,000 power.
♪
And I give it the
plus one damage as well.
♪
I need a heal trigger.
(shouting)
♪
Now you're finished.
There you have it, folks,
you've seen it yourselves.
The winner is Toshiki Kai.
(applause and cheering)
Amazing.
They're both such
great fighters.
Hopefully I can be
like them one day.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
The champion has been decided,
but that's not the
only exciting news.
I have a very important
announcement to make.
Huh?
Pardon me.
The Card Capital Shop
Champion, Toshiki Kai,
and our runner up,
Kamui Katsuragi,
will be joined by our
other semi finalists,
Aichi Sendou and Misaki Tokura
as they prepare for this!
Excuse the small poster,
there was a larger version.
But the assist‐i‐cat
had a nap on it.
Whoa.
No way.
Great work, man.
What is it?
Whoa, incredible.
Misaki, you get to compete in
an even bigger card tournament.
Isn't that great?
The National Championship
is our country's biggest
Vanguard tournament.
By making the top four
you've proved that you're
ready to represent Card Capital
on the national level.
First you'll have to compete
in a regional qualifier
on your way to the nationals.
But with players this strong
I have no doubt you'll
win the regionals.
Then you'll compete against
the best in the country
for the title of
National Vanguard Champion.
Now your team can
only have three players,
with one of you
serving as an alternate.
You're all so talented
I know Card Capital
will be well represented
in the weeks to come.
Everyone, please.
Give these four players a
great big round of applause!
(applause)
You did it!
That's awesome.
You guys rock!
It's great, isn't it?
Hey, Aichi!
Can you believe this?
We're going to the
Regional Championship, bro!
We're gonna get the chance
to play against so
many great players!
All right, I can't
wait to get out there
and show everyone in
the world what we've got.
‐Say what?
What we've got.
Emi, please watch me!
First we're gonna win
regional qualifier,
and then it's off to
the National Championship.
After that we can
g‐, g‐, g‐, go...
Let's go!
Oh, yeah, I'm all fired up.
♪
Wait.
So I'll be on the same team
as Kamui, Misaki, and Kai?
At the Vanguard Championships?
In front of all those strangers?
(crowd cheering)
Huh?
I wonder if I'm
imagining this right.
Huh, a baseball?
♪
I'm gonna be in a regional
Vanguard tournament?
Yes.
Our four semi finalists are
moving on to bigger things.
Make me proud!
Right.
There's a little
time before regionals.
Devote your time to training.
Yeah, only I'm not
sure how to get better.
Next time, the fearsome undead.
The granblue deck.
This person is really good.
Oh, another shop?
You're leaving Card Capital?
For another shop?