The winner, Aichi Sendou!
And there you have it.
Team Q4 is moving
on to the main event.
They'll be coming
back once again
to face off
against Team Asteroid
in the national
tournament final.
Well, look at that.
You won without
activating your Psyqualia.
Are you foolish enough
to do that against me?
♪
It's time for us to learn
the true nature of your power.
♪
Hm.
Are you guys ready for
the toughest cardfights
‐of your lives?
‐For sure!
Hm.
♪
He made it this far with
nothing but his own strength.
We're in the finals!
Thanks to Alfred Early!
Wasn't that crazy?
Let's hope you didn't use up
all your luck on that draw.
(chuckling)
♪
(wind howling)
This is where it ended.
You and I together with
our army of elite fighters
can conquer the
world of Vanguard!
‐No chance.
‐Huh?
Get your deck.
But‐‐
I'll show you who's
the strongest right now.
♪
So, Kai, like my winning image?
Ren,
get me outta here!
Rising from the shadows
to cut down my enemies.
Go!
I'll destroy anyone
that interferes with me.
(sinister chuckle)
♪
(exclaims)
(grunting)
Ren!
Kai...I...I've
gotten much stronger.
♪
Leaving?
You can come
with me if you want.
I'll never turn my back on him.
Yeah.
♪
(gate rumbles open)
I couldn't save him then.
His newfound power
was overwhelming.
Losing my friend like that was
too difficult for me to bear.
So I did the only thing
that made sense at the time:
I ran away.
Still, I'm not the same
person I used to be.
You know it, Aichi.
This isn't what you
pictured for our battle.
It's true, I wanted to be
your equal and friend.
♪
Aichi almost lost
himself to Psyqualia.
But knowing what I know now,
I was able to stop him.
Which means...
♪
This time, I won't fail.
Tetsu.
♪
Hm...
(exclaims)
(thud)
Well, it's about time.
I knew after your team
made the finals you'd come.
Do you know why I've come back?
Yeah.
You want to rob me
of my powers, right?
Just like you did to Aichi.
(whirring)
Poor kid.
Thanks to the way you've
messed with his head,
he has this idea that
the best thing for him to do
is deny himself the amazing
gift that he was given.
What's your problem?
Are you jealous that
he has it and you don't, hm?
I didn't realize your ego
was so easily damaged.
I watched as that power
changed you for the worse.
Relying on it has made you
forget the whole reason
we started playing Vanguard
in the first place.
All you play for now is your
obsession with your own image.
Do you even remember
what it was like?
cardfighting because
it was what you loved to do?
Easy, now.
I'll never forget the past
we shared as teammates.
We sure had some
good times together.
But then, you ruined everything,
Kai.
You were the one that
turned your back on us.
I thought I was your friend.
That all ended the day
I became stronger than you.
The three of us
built Team Asteroid.
We dreamed of playing
in the national tournament,
though none of us
were ready for it.
I didn't care
if we were the best,
I wanted to spend
time with you guys.
♪
Yet it wasn't to be.
You became fixated on getting
our team past the regionals.
I felt bad, it obviously
meant a lot to you.
♪
I decided I needed
to step it up,
for you and Tetsu, my teammates.
I had to improve because
that's what you wanted
for the team.
We were trying to get
to the national tournament.
And if we won there,
then we'd always be together
if we had the strength to do so.
Then...
♪
I need to get stronger!
(lightning crashes)
♪
My friends are counting on me.
I have to get better.
If I don't get stronger,
my team will...
(lightning crashes)
Huh?
♪
(gasps)
I hear it‐‐the cards
are talking to me.
I knew I'd found something
special right away.
More possibilities
than I'd ever imagined.
And it was so easy.
The only thing I had
to do was listen to them.
They told me
which unit was needed
for me to win my next match.
My deck itself was
a path to victory.
I attained real power
for the sake of your goals.
I was excited to show you guys.
My best friends needed
to share in my discovery.
Though Tetsu's fear
was plain to see,
he continued to stand by me.
But not you.
Our friendship wasn't
worth that much.
My new power was supposed
to help us realize our dreams.
Tell me, why did you run?
Why did you betray us?
♪
(gasps)
(growling)
How dare you!
(echoing)
Kai!
♪
I became consumed
with hating you.
In every fight I won,
every player I defeated,
in my mind, I was
always beating you.
Psyqualia was a gift,
and it was my job
to share it with the world.
Then, even fools like
you would see the truth.
(chuckling)
♪
And now,
the world's top players
have flocked here
just for the chance
to play beside me.
I have over 500 hopeful
cardfighters at my disposal.
I wish you knew
what it felt like.
The power surging
through my veins,
sharpening my skills.
You've got to admit it,
it's pretty funny
we used to dream about
going to nationals.
The players there aren't
even worth my time anymore.
And I couldn't have
done it without you.
(growls)
Hating you made it
possible for me
to focus my wild ability.
Take a look at me now.
I'm unparalleled by
anyone else on the planet.
Winning the nationals
without even trying.
With Team Asteroid,
there's no limit to the things
I'll be able to accomplish.
Well, where do we go from here?
I know.
Maybe I'll take over
the world next.
♪
I didn't come for
a lecture, Ren.
(chuckles)
I came 'cause I'm finally
strong enough to beat you.
I'm gonna bring back
the person you used to be.
I swear it to you.
The person I used to be?
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Sorry to be the one
to tell you this,
but the guy I
used to be is gone
and the world's top
cardfighter remains.
Then again, you wouldn't
have come without something
up your sleeve,
and that's perfectly fine by me.
You'll need all
the help you can get.
I'm gonna destroy you
with the power
that you hate so much.
♪
No.
‐Tetsu?
‐Huh?
Hang on to this for me.
Hm.
I'd rather just use the glove.
Those helmets are way too bulky.
So, are you ready?
I wish it didn't have
to go down like this.
We'll be watching
this fight too...
if it's okay with you boys.
Hm?
♪
What are they doing here?
They're my biggest fans.
What's the problem?
Don't tell me you're
afraid of losing a battle
in front of your
favorite pop group.
♪
Hm?
Took long enough.
Hey, Kai.
And Ren too?
Aichi!
Huh!
Uh...you see...
Kourin asked me to come down.
I think he's earned the right
to watch what happens today.
(chuckles)
Yeah, he sure has.
Isn't it wonderful how
people flock together
to witness me play?
Makes me feel all
warm and fuzzy inside.
Listen up.
If you're gonna stick around,
then study the way he plays.
You guys are gonna fight?
♪
What's this about?
It's time.
The training I've done
in the last few years
has been for this moment.
I guess you must be curious
about what my power
is really like.
Hardly, it doesn't matter.
You say that, Kai,
but you know what I think?
You should see it for yourself.
♪
Huh?
No way!
I've been here.
His Psyqualia.
Hm!
(laughing)
♪
Is it clear?
My winning image.
So it's...that unit.
♪
Who cares about your power?
You'll soon realize,
no matter how strong you get,
you're never gonna be able to
play at the level I've reached.
(sinister chuckle)
♪
Stand up, the Vanguard!
Draw.
I ride Bahr...
and move Conroe.
I draw.
I ride Blaster Javelin.
(roar)
♪
I call‐‐and attack!
Javelin, let's go.
(roaring)
♪
I ride Dragon Knight, Nehalem!
Burning Horn Dragon and
Aermo to the rear guard.
♪
With Conroe's support,
Burning Horn Dragon
attacks Gururubau.
♪
Gururubau!
Aermo supports an
attack from Nehalem.
♪
Checking the trigger...
(yells)
Perfect.
It seems the cards
favor me again.
Blaster Javelin
gains 5,000 power.
I draw.
♪
I never thought
I'd see the day
when the three of us
were back together again.
But things have changed
a lot since then, Kai.
You have no chance of winning.
Ren's power level
is terrifying.
I ride.
Blaster Dark!
Call!
♪
Nemain's counterblast.
DonnerSchlag attacks.
Bahr will guard.
Next, I attack
with Blaster Dark.
I don't guard.
♪
Looks like a critical trigger.
(sounds of struggle)
♪
Heal trigger activates.
The power to Nehalem,
and I heal one point of damage.
Face it, Kai.
You're afraid because
you don't understand it.
♪
This'll be just like last time.
Your fear will betray you.
In the end, you'll run away.
Not a chance.
I won't run!
But, Kai...
♪
I ride Dragonic Overlord!
I call Berserk Dragon.
♪
Counterblast.
I banish Karen.
I'll have Berserk
Dragon attack Nemain.
♪
(screaming)
With Aermo's support,
Overlord attacks.
(roaring)
♪
I don't guard.
Checking the twin drive.
♪
There‐‐a critical trigger.
Overlord gains
the critical effect,
and the 5,000 power
goes to Burning Horn.
♪
Aermo's skill.
With Conroe's support...
Burning Horn attacks.
Burning Horn's ability?
As long as my Vanguard
has the word
"Overlord" in its name,
this unit gets
an extra 3,000 power.
♪
(explosion)
Well, well, a heal trigger.
The power boost goes
to Blaster Dark,
and I heal one point of damage.
That's so sad.
Huh?
Fighting is the only way
they can talk to each other.
This is what true rivals are.
No kidding.
I stand and draw.
Surely you must have
guessed what's coming next.
Hm.
I ride Phantom Blaster Dragon.
(yells)
♪
I call.
DonnerSchlag's coming in.
Kimnara will guard.
And now, with support
from Apocalypse,
Phantom Blaster
Dragon takes aim.
Apocalypse's Soul Blast!
Since the boosted unit
has "Blaster" in its name,
this attack gets
another 6,000 power.
♪
No guard.
Check the drive trigger.
♪
The cards favor me.
The power boost
goes to Fatalita.
And then I draw.
♪
Got my own draw trigger.
The power goes to Overlord.
♪
Boosted by Karen,
Fatalita attacks!
Tahr will stop you.
I've never seen a battle
with this much animosity.
♪
As I expected,
you've lost sight of the reason
we started playing this game
in the first place,
and I'm going to remind you.
By defeating you here,
I'll be able to bring back
the Ren I once knew.
Seriously?
The Ren you used to know
is but a shadow of the past.
You keep going on and on
about how you've come
to save me from whatever
it is that I've become.
Why can't you see it's futile?
‐I've got this.
‐Hm?
This is the card that
I'll use to defeat you
once and for all.
(growls)
Harbinger of Destruction,
spread your ravaging flames
across this battlefield...
and rise from the ashes.
The Overlord has reached
his ultimate form!
Cross Ride!
Dragonic Overlord, the end!
♪
I've never seen that
used before in my life.
♪
(growls)
What do you think of
my Dragonic Overlord's
final evolution?
Its true form.
All right.
Let's see if we can't
find the old you, huh?
♪
Cross Ride?
Wow, as soon as
I thought I knew
everything about this game.
Aichi, watch closely.
This fight is important.
I'm gonna bring him back
just like I did you.
Give it up, Kai.
In the face of Psyqualia,
even your best efforts
will be wasted.
If Ren knows how this
is going to unfold,
how can Kai possibly win?
That's weird.
I can't picture how their
battle is going to end.