♪
(laughing)
It's good to see you here, Q4!
Did you miss me, Kai?
(laughing)
You know, I was worried
we'd never get the
chance to catch up,
so this is a big treat.
What is he even talking about?
Hey, man, why'd you have
to come to our tournament?
Doesn't Team Asteroid have their
own regionals to deal with?
Hmm.
This is revenge.
Yeah, I've come back
to take my revenge on you
for defeating me!
(laughing)
♪
(maniacal laughter)
Hmm‐‐do you guys notice
something different
about the way he's acting?
I wonder what happened to him!
You dare?
Yeah, thanks to you,
a lot of things
have happened to me.
♪
Losing to you guys at
Nationals cost me everything!
♪
Hmm‐‐I ride Nehalem!
With a boost from
Conroe, Nehalem attacks!
(groaning)
♪
Please don't do this!
You've gotta give
me another chance!
Please, Tetsu!
Ren doesn't allow any
failures on the team.
Now please hand over your I. D.
♪
It's what you deserve.
Why's that?
Did you forget what you said?
I've heard it.
Ren thinks that you're his equal
when it comes to cardfighting.
All I have to do is defeat you,
and I'll prove that
I'm stronger than Ren is,
then I'll be the
leader of Team Asteroid!
That big mouth of yours is
gonna get you into trouble.
Why‐‐it only makes sense
that the best player
should be the leader.
The best.
That's not you.
Now you understand
what happens to people
that lose faith in our leader.
♪
Having you around
is making me sick!
Get out!
Huh‐‐whatever, Team Asteroid.
Who needs 'em?
A player as good as me
can cardfight anywhere.
There are tons of
teams in this city
that would be glad to have me!
I'll show you guys.
But I was in for a big shock.
What did you say‐‐
you're kidding me!
I just offered to
join your stupid team,
and you don't want me?
Huh‐‐wait, wait, I see.
You guys just don't
know who I am, is that it?
I know you, Kyou Yahagi.
You were fired
from Team Asteroid.
I call Romario and Cutlass.
There's no chance of
you getting on this team.
We have no intention of
crossing the likes of Asteroid.
All right, I
attack with Basskirk!
Hey, good luck, bud.
You can't play here.
You've got to go.
♪
Fine!
(rain pouring)
♪
Ren.
(laughing)
♪
My revenge!
I'll get my revenge
on all of you!
Revenge!
I'd made up my mind,
but I needed a team,
so I went out in
search of the others
that had been fired by Asteroid.
Our plan was simple enough.
All we wanted was
to settle the score
with Ren and his lackeys.
♪
And that's who we are now.
We are Team Avengers.
(laughing)
♪
We Avengers have a
grand plan in the making.
We're gonna go to the Nationals
and beat Ren at his own game.
When we reign over all
the other Asteroid teens,
then the whole world will
see our ultimate revenge!
But before we go to
Nationals, Toshiki Kai,
I'll pay you back for all
the trouble you've caused me
since your lucky win
those long months ago.
A challenge‐‐fight me
in the first match,
unless you're afraid
to lose, of course!
(laughing)
♪
All right, after a big day of
watching incredible cardfights,
it all comes down to this.
It's the Championship match!
Let's meet our competitors!
This newly formed group
displayed some top notch talent
on their road to defeating Team
Handsome in the semi‐finals!
It's Team Avengers!
They're up against the winners
from the last regional
tournament, Team Q4!
Our returning
champions are eager
to make it back to
the national stage.
The stakes couldn't be
any higher here, folks!
Wow, what an exciting match!
Kyou Yahagi, ugh.
He's such a creep.
Yeah, but he defeated Gouki.
Looks like he's dangerous
whether he's with
Team Asteroid or not.
Well, are you
gonna cowboy up, Kai?
‐Let me fight.
‐Huh?
Are you sure you
wanna do that, bro?
You were pretty rough
after that first one.
♪
What's wrong?
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Guess that fight
took a lot out of me.
♪
Yeah, but I feel better now!
Besides, I have this
feeling that I'll win.
♪
I don't mind‐‐
knock yourself out!
I won't let ya down.
♪
Kai is finally starting
to believe in me!
♪
I'm gonna beat this
guy, no matter what.
♪
(laughing)
So Kai was too
afraid to face me.
And he sent the weakest
player on his team instead.
Well, at least this
won't take too long.
Look, I guess we know what
Team Q4's really made of now,
‐don't we, boys?
‐Pathetic.
They're shaking in their boots.
(laughing)
You have no chance, Kyou.
What did you say?
♪
And this is the card
that I'll beat you with.
‐Say what?
‐Huh?
What do you mean by that, bro?
♪
Declaring his victory
before the battle begins?
He must've been paying
attention to my lessons
on how to look cool!
My work here is done.
That doesn't seem like the
kind of thing Aichi would do.
What do you think, Emi?
‐Well, I‐‐
‐Actually,
that's not like him at all.
Aichi.
♪
Huh?
(laughing)
For a minute there, I
actually fell for your display!
But I'd double check the card
you're holding if I were you.
That's just Young
Pegasus Knight.
You're gonna beat
me with a Grade 1?
This little joke has
gone on long enough.
Yeah, good point.
I thought I told Aichi
to take the Grade
1s out of his deck.
Really‐‐bad idea.
Why does he keep
defying my teachings?
Smarten up down there, Aichi!
How can a Grade
1 win the game?
Good question‐‐I guess
we'll have to wait and see.
Mhm, mhm.
Grade 3s, Aichi!
The grade doesn't
matter in the slightest.
This is the card you'll lose to.
The outcome of this
match has been decided.
♪
Ren?
Calm down, he's just
some loser walking around
in Toshiki Kai's shadow.
He's nowhere near
as good as I am,
and he's bluffing
because he's scared.
Are you both ready to start?
‐Yes.
‐Of course I am.
I'm gonna teach you a lesson
for opening your big mouth.
Yeah, Aichi Sendou, you'll see.
‐So strange.
‐What is?
The boy‐‐I've never seen
him act so aggressive
or confident before.
‐Yeah, you're right.
‐What's wrong with that?
It's more fun this way!
All right, let's
get things started!
It's the first
game of the finals.
(machinery whirring)
♪
‐Stand up, my Vanguard!
Draw.
♪
I ride Marron.
Barcgal moves to the rear.
I activate Barcgal's skill,
and I superior call Flogal.
♪
I end my turn.
That's all you've got?
What about the amazing
Young Pegasus Knight?
Isn't he gonna win
the game for you?
Instead of wasting my time,
why don't you go ahead
and start your turn?
‐Say what?
‐I've never seen Aichi
‐like this before!
‐I don't get it!
What's with him today?
Well, he might just
be in a bad mood.
(sighing)
♪
Who does he think he is?
Time to show this kid
who he's dealing with.
I've worked long
and hard to get here,
and I won't lose to you!
Got that?
The Great Kyou rides Wonder Boy!
♪
Oh, yeah!
The Great Kyou rides again.
(groaning)
Hey, you can't just go
around referring to yourself
as The Great Kyou!
My friends call me The Great,
and I'm nothing like you!
‐The Great Kamui!
‐He's The Great!
You're the lame, yo!
I should change seats.
I move Mecha Trainer.
And now I call Spike Brothers
Assault Squad to rear‐guard!
♪
Here it goes‐‐
attacking your Vanguard!
I don't guard.
Checking my drive trigger.
♪
I check for a damage trigger.
With support from
the Assault Squad,
Mecha Trainer attacks Marron!
♪
No guard.
The Great Kyou's turn is over.
Two damage already.
I like how this is shaping up.
I stand and draw.
♪
Calling Young Pegasus
Knight to rear‐guard!
♪
That's it!
The card he said
he would win with!
I'll use Barcgal's ability
to get Future Knight, Llew!
Superior call!
Activating Llew's counterblast!
I superior ride Blaster Blade!
♪
Now I activate Young
Pegasus Knight's skill!
During my main phase,
Young Pegasus Knight
gained 3,000 power for each
card added to my soul this turn.
The number of cards
added to his soul this turn
was‐‐Izaki, you must remember.
Marron, Barcgal,
Flogal, and Llew.
There were four altogether.
Which means
Pegasus Knight's power
is all the way up to 18,000.
♪
So you used that superior ride
to boost his power
up even higher!
I call Gallatin!
♪
Attack!
The Assault Squad will guard!
♪
(growling)
So much for that attempt.
Gallatin, move aside!
♪
I'm not gonna guard!
Drive trigger check.
(yelling)
Damage trigger
check‐‐critical trigger!
Giving all the
effects to Wonder Boy!
♪
An extra 5,000 power
won't be enough.
You'll need a lot more
if you wanna stop this one.
Go, Pegasus Knight!
♪
Ahh!
Nice!
That's the card he said
he'd use to win the game!
But Aichi's only managed to
deal him two damage so far.
I don't know‐‐do you think
maybe he could've been bluffing?
Possibly.
You're trying to scare me.
Throwing all those cards into
your soul for a power boost
was just a one‐time trick.
When the turn ends,
Young Pegasus Knight
will be nothing but
a little weakling.
Still think you can
win with that Grade 1?
You're all talk, like I thought.
Well, we'll see about that.
♪
What's going on over there?
Don't tell me you're
actually afraid of this kid!
You, keep quiet!
Why?
Why do I keep picturing Ren?
♪
That'll be the end of my turn.
Get a hold of yourself.
If you can't beat this loser,
how are you ever
gonna get your revenge?
I'm Crusher Kyou!
He's just messing with me.
A Grade 1 unit like that
couldn't possibly change
the outcome of this game.
♪
First, The Great Kyou will
ride Treasured, Black Panther!
♪
And I call Dudley Dan.
I think I'll have to
retire your Pegasus Knight!
Mecha Trainer attacks with
support from the Assault Squad!
♪
(laughing)
Your little prediction isn't
gonna come true now, huh?
Ahhh, that's unfair.
‐Uh, why are you so upset?
‐You know!
"This card‐‐this is the one
I'm gonna beat you with."
You heard him say that,
but now that card is gone,
removed from the field!
It's embarrassing.
I can't listen to this.
‐Can I hit him?
‐Sorry, man,
Morikawa never learned to
deal with disappointment.
That's too bad.
That would've been
cool if it worked out
like he said it would.
As if‐‐we all know that
boy is nothing special.
‐I'm not sure.
‐You're kidding.
The fight is
still far from over,
and there's something
strange about how he's playing.
‐Hmm.
All right, let's go.
With Dudley Dan's support,
Treasured, Black Panther
attacks Blaster Blade!
And I'll be activating
Dudley Dan's counterblast!
By taking a Spike
Brothers card from my hand
and moving it to the soul,
I can superior call Sky Diver!
(laughing)
What?
His Vanguard is
only a Grade 2,
and yet he was able to
call a Grade 3 unit
to the rear‐guard circle?
No way‐‐I didn't even
know that was possible!
This guy is amazing!
It figures you'd cheer for him.
So what are you gonna do?
‐I don't guard.
‐Works for me!
I check for a drive
trigger‐‐good timing!
A draw trigger!
I add 5,000 power to Sky Diver!
♪
And then I draw‐‐
go, Black Panther!
Ahh!
Coming at you next with his
16,000 power is Sky Diver!
♪
(laughing)
You drew that stand
trigger for nothing.
How's losing feel?
Aichi's up to four damage now.
And his opponent has two.
The situation is
starting to look grim.
Don't worry, guys.
It's still early.
Aichi.
I stand and draw.
♪
Why do I feel so
anxious right now?
Wait, that's‐‐
Enter the fray,
King of all knights!
I ride King of Knights, Alfred!
♪
‐Nice!
‐It's about time!
Yeah, I thought he'd
never get a Grade 3
Give it a rest.
Next, I call
Little Sage, Marron,
and Swordsman of the
Explosive Flames, Palamedes!
♪
Ahhh!
And now...
No way‐‐not that‐‐not that card.
Yes.
It is that card.
No, it's another
Young Pegasus Knight!
♪
Ha‐‐he had a second one!
Then does that mean...?
♪
I call Young Pegasus Knight.
Just like I said,
this is the card
I'm going to use to defeat you.
(nervous laughter)
Aichi, it's as I feared.
♪
Why‐‐why do I keep seeing Ren?
Now, picture what lies ahead.
You'll be defeated by my hand,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
♪
Here we are in the final round.
Let's not worry about the
pressure and just have fun!
I'll win this match.
It's only a matter of time.
Aichi, you're such
a passionate cardfighter,
I don't want you
to get too wound up,
‐so just relax, okay?
‐Oh, I'm relaxed.
Just make sure Misaki and
Kamui don't get in my way.
‐Huh?
‐Next time, Psyqualia!
I can picture the
road to victory.
It's right before my eyes.
Aichi?