♪
Cursed Black Dragon.
Pain will flow through
this battlefield.
I ride...
Phantom Blaster Dragon!
♪
(roars)
This is incredible.
When I used his skill,
I could feel myself
getting stronger.
The strength
of my vanguard
surges through me.
(chuckles)
I'll end this right now.
Someone like you
could never stop me.
Humiliating you
isn't enough anymore.
I'll destroy you
and transform you
back into the thing
you hate the most.
(laughs)
♪
Then to rear guard
I call another dragon.
♪
(roars)
What a terrifying
level of power.
My vanguard Phantom
Blaster Dragon will
start us off.
Attack!
(roars)
♪
I guard.
Alabaster Owl
and Star Call Trumpeter.
Bedivere intercepts.
♪
That's a shield
of 20,000 on top
of Blaster Blade's
original 9,000.
Guess it'll have to do.
♪
Ah.
Let's see what
the twin drive says.
♪
Second check.
Critical trigger
at a time like this.
And of course I give
all of the effects
to my rear guard
Phantom Blaster Dragon.
♪
How is Aichi supposed
to stop two attacks
of that strength
in a single turn?
(whimpering)
Oh, no!
♪
(grunts, screams)
My dragons are unstoppable.
♪
No guard.
Can you picture it?
♪
Huh?
(shouts)
(Ren chuckles)
He's got a pretty firm
grip, wouldn't you say?
You don't need to struggle.
It's pointless.
Psyqualia will set you free.
(struggles)
Aichi, stop denying your
power and activate it already.
♪
No.
No!
(echoes)
(grunts)
♪
Look at you,
still so afraid.
Is strength
really that scary?
Aren't you even
gonna try and get
revenge for what
I did to Kai last night?
Don't tell me you already
forgot how it ended.
I crushed the sorry loser.
He was so pathetic
I couldn't even
feel bad for him.
What it's like to walk in
the footsteps of a weakling.
You can't talk
about him that way
after all he's done for you!
Letting your anger out
isn't a bad start,
but it still
won't be enough.
You have to use it!
Right now you have
absolutely no power.
And there's no way
you'll be able
to take revenge
unless you're willing
to battle me
on equal ground.
(laughs)
♪
(screams)
(chuckles)
Huh?
♪
Looks like he's hurt.
What happened to him?
♪
Damage check.
And the second check.
♪
Well, your turn.
I wanna wipe the
smile off his face.
But how?
I stand and draw.
Faced by crushing darkness,
a single light
shows us the way!
See the King
as he once was!
I ride...
...Alfred Early!
Royal Paladins
are too loyal
to let their king enter
the fray on his own.
Superior call...
Blaster Blade.
The verdict has
been passed on your
Phantom Blaster Dragon.
♪
What a pain.
Such a cute little trick,
but it'll take
a lot more than that
if you actually
wanna win this match.
♪
Ah!
(deep breath)
♪
(chuckles)
Just as I thought.
Anger is the key
to awakening your power.
Using it will transform you
back into the thing you hate.
Yes.
Give in, Aichi.
You're so close.
♪
But it's too late for
you to change the outcome.
My victory has
already been determined.
I control it all.
This fight, my future,
your life, everything.
I'm sure Kai's probably
feeling a lot better by now.
Though, I imagine it
must be pretty hard
for him to sit here
and watch as you struggle
to stay in the game.
Do you wanna be
just like him
when you grow up?
(growls)
It's like two little bugs
trying to take down a giant.
It's almost not even worth
my time to defeat you.
(blows)
How about you guys
do the world a favor
and disappear?
Ren!
You're a disgusting
human being, you know that?
(growls)
♪
Aichi Sendou has given in
and activated his Psyqualia.
Hmm.
(startled gasp)
♪
Rekka, what's the matter?
They've connected.
Huh?
It's him.
Yes, I've commandeered
Rekka's body for
the remainder
of this conflict.
I need to see what
comes of this myself.
♪
A warrior of light
standing to the King's left
casts a shadow which
reaches the King's right.
Darkness takes you!
Rise my avatar!
Call Blaster Dark!
(gasps)
There's no way!
You guys!
He can't!
A Shadow Paladin.
♪
What is this about?
It's making my skin crawl.
Hmm.
I don't like it one bit.
I mean, the last time he
used the Shadow Paladin
he practically turned
into a different person!
♪
I don't want him to change.
Boosted by Wingal Brave,
Blaster Blade attacks.
♪
Guard
with Death Feather Eagle.
♪
With Marron's support,
Alfred Early!
♪
Hm.
Twin drive check.
The first...
and second.
Draw trigger
giving the power
to Blaster Dark.
♪
(chuckles)
(grunts)
♪
It's been too long
since I saw you,
my old friend.
Get ready to strike!
With you at my side,
my victory in this match
is guaranteed.
Now, let's teach
this jerk a lesson.
♪
Can you picture it, Ren?
What's all this?
Huh?
♪
I can't believe I'd
forgotten how good it felt
to have this dark energy
surging through my veins.
(chuckles)
♪
Feel my hatred and let
me drag away your hope
along with it.
Weakness can
never be tolerated!
♪
(Ren grunts)
Is he hurt?
♪
(laughs)
You've become what
you hate the most.
Don't you see,
this game is going
exactly the way
I want it to.
(mischievous laugh)
♪
He's changing.
Knock it off, bro.
Aichi!
What's gotten into him?
Don't know.
This is bad.
♪
Aichi!
Turn back.
♪
As we reach the end
of the sixth turn,
we see a complete
shift in momentum
as Aichi Sendou
with four damage
has pushed
Ren Suzugamori
to five damage.
Frankly, I'm at
a loss for words here.
Well, I can hardly
believe this is happening.
You've got to assume
that Ren has a plan
to bring this to an end,
because his time
is running short.
This final bout
is certainly living
up to the hype.
Hmph.
Then we're in for
an o‐verwhelming climax,
wouldn't you say?
You took the words
out of my mouth!
♪
Hmm.
The power known
as Psyqualia
has some obvious risks
that are associated
with its use.
You're concerned
for the boy's safety,
aren't you?
I am.
There is nothing
we can do for them
once the wheels
are in motion.
The chaos of Planet Cray
flows through them.
There's no turning back.
I know.
If what we've
heard is true,
there really is
a mysterious force
spreading across your planet.
They say a darkness
moves over the landscape
destroying life
in its wake.
You're correct.
The people of Cray
are facing extinction
if something isn't done.
But our most trusted
heroes can't seem to agree
one what the best
course of action might be.
♪
(grunts)
Join us and assemble
under our banner.
Pledge your loyalty
to the Shadow Paladins
and I can promise
a swift victory
will belong to us all.
Royal Paladins will
never serve under
the banner of Shadow.
In these dark times,
a light must emerge
to lead the way.
We must inspire
our brethren
to unite for
the common good;
a covenant.
Without it, we've
already lost this war.
And so began the struggle
between our
strongest warriors.
The armies of Cray
will offer their
allegiance to the winner.
♪
As we speak,
skirmishes are still
waging on the
surface of my planet.
♪
I get that your
people are fighting,
but what does it
have to do with us?
The winner of this battle
will decide which clan
leads our combined forces
against the mysterious
evil that threatens
to wipe out
everything we hold dear.
But the outcome
of the clan war
isn't ours to decide.
Everything is riding on them,
the clash between these
impressive warriors
because the moment
those two activated
their Psyqualia,
they took on the mantle
of the heroes
of our legends.
They are the vanguards,
they will show us the way.
♪
We can hope.
With their help,
Cray's forces
will finally be able
to conquer the chaos
threatening our safety.
♪
You've probably wondered
about the true nature
of their gift.
Its users have
the ability to synchronize
with the Planet Cray.
Look, they're enacting
the war for leadership
between the Shadow
and Royal Paladin clans
with the fate of my people
hanging in the balance.
This isn't the first
time this has happened.
Gifted beings from
other worlds have
been called upon in the past
to help settle
smaller disputes.
And that's the reason
you gave them that power.
All that's left
for us to do
is watch as these two
determine my future.
Nice to see you've
finally accepted
what you really are.
Unfortunately, this game
already belongs to me.
My eyes have shown me
the path I must take.
Hmph!
You're speaking as though
you have some level
of experience facing off
with an opponent who can
see the cards like you.
Huh?
This match is the
first of its kind,
so I doubt
those predictions
will become a reality.
I can't wait to see
your look of despair
as you realize
the strength
you hold so dear
has betrayed you.
(maniacal laughs)
♪
Let's do this.
Knock it off!
♪
Aichi!
What is it?
♪
Don't you dare
lose yourself
to that power again
after I worked so hard
to bring you back to us!
You hear me?!
♪
Think about the
fight we had.
Remember!
♪
Never forget the
real Aichi Sendou.
♪
Hm.
Never forget...
the real...
(Ren chuckles)
I find it very hard
to believe that this
isn't the real Aichi Sendou
that stands before me now.
You desperately wanted this
gift to make yourself stronger.
You're afraid
to admit it,
but the truth has
been painfully obvious
this entire time.
Face it.
You're the same as I am.
I'm not.
I can't!
Who am I?
You're me, I think.
♪
Come on!
(groans)
Final turn.
What?
Huh?
‐Huh?
‐He can't!
This is real bad.
And there it is, final
turn has been called.
Ren Suzugamori
of Team Asteroid
has just made
a gutsy pledge
to this audience.
In front of
the entire world
he's making the claim
that he can bring
this match to an end!
The pressure's on.
Oh, no!
He can do it.
♪
Psyqualia has never
let me down before.
This is the card
I was shown.
Gathering shadows
assume the ultimate
form of darkness.
The bringer of the end,
the destroyer of dreams,
he's here!
I crossride!
♪
You remember Phantom
Blaster Overlord?
(roars)
(shuddering)
♪
(groans)
(mischievous laugh)
I know you haven't
forgotten about him
and his power.
Let's do this,
Phantom Blaster Overlord!
It's time to put this
fool out of his misery!
♪
Psyqualia chose me first,
and I think it's
only fitting that I
be the one who gets
to finish you off.
I'm gonna enjoy watching
the look on your face
as you plunge into the
depths of utter helplessness.
Ready?
(maniacal laugh)
♪
This is Phantom
Blaster Overlord!
(Ren chuckles)
You and I are exactly
the same, Aichi.
There's no reason
to hide from the truth.
We are the only two
card fighters chosen
by Psyqualia.
That makes us special.
We sought out power
and were fortunate
enough to find it.
I was looking
for power,
but not like this!
Next time, Awakening
of the Twin Blades!
Light and shadow,
show me the way!