I can hear you calling me.
Grim Reaper!
♪
Now you get a critical trigger?
Giving all the effects
to Blaster Dark.
♪
Oh, no!
Shadow Paladins.
This is the deck I
was meant to play.
With this, I
won't lose to anyone!
Finally.
I've gotten stronger.
♪
(wind blowing)
(chuckling)
The weather's awful today!
‐Huh?
‐I sure hope it clears up
before the tournament tomorrow.
I checked online‐‐
it'll be sunny all week.
Good.
‐Hmm.
What is with your
brother these days?
He should be down here, too.
‐Uhh.
‐Hmm?
I think he's got
a lot of work to do
getting his deck
ready for Nationals.
Let's leave him be.
I'll take his cake up later.
If you think it's best.
Aichi.
♪
I'm a lot stronger thanks
to the Shadow Paladins.
This is my chance.
I'm gonna get better.
And then you'll finally
look at me as your equal!
Isn't that right, Kai?
♪
‐See ya, Mr. Manager!
‐You two be careful
on your way home!
I hope Q4 wins
Nationals this time around!
Yeah, well, that
makes two of us!
(meowing)
You know, Aichi
hasn't been in the store
since the regional tournament.
Do you guys think his nerves
finally got the best of him?
No, Aichi's not
the same guy anymore.
I bet you anything he's
just holed up in his room
all shivering and shaking.
Help me, Morikawa, I'm scared!
I need more of
your wise teachings!
Am I right, am I right?
Could you stop talking now?
(meowing)
Hm.
(motor rumbling)
Uh, I'm sorry, but we're
closing up shop for the day.
Huh?
Hey, it's...
‐Ultra Rare's‐‐
‐Kourin, did you get my letter?
What brings you to Card Capital?
Isn't it obvious, Izaki?
She came to be reunited
with her true love!
You know what this is, guys?
It's the best day of my life!
Of course it is.
I'm looking for Toshiki Kai.
Hmm?
Haven't seen him.
Well, can you get
him down here for me?
Easier said than done.
That guy has a habit of
vanishing into thin air.
One of you must know.
‐All right.
‐You know where he is?
Of course!
Kai would get mad
if I told you this,
but this sounds important.
I'll take you to where
he hangs out these days.
Good, there's no time to waste.
♪
Hold on, I wouldn't
wanna lose ya.
‐Uh, sure.
‐Hey!
You get your hands off of her
if you know what's good for you!
‐Easy, tiger!
‐It's not like I've got
a lot of options here‐‐I've
gotta hang on to something!
(screaming)
Wait, Kourin, my darling,
take me for a ride instead!
♪
This is our turn!
It's down that alley!
Ahh, slow down!
♪
Is your life supposed
to flash before your eyes?
‐You sure he's here?
‐Uh‐huh.
Look, he's playing right now.
‐I lost?
‐Who's next?
‐You should go.
‐No, thanks, man,
‐it's your turn!
‐Really, me?
Take it easy on them.
I know you're frustrated,
but my guys can't handle
this kind of punishment.
Hey, Kai!
Hi, glad to be back!
How long has it been?
I realize you're busy
kicking butt right now,
but how about you take a minute
to talk to your old buddy?
I've got nothing
to say to you‐‐hmm?
‐Whoa.
‐Oh, man.
Oh, she's a member
of Ultra Rare!
Should we ask her
for an autograph?
She doesn't look
too friendly‐like.
Something tells me
she didn't come to sing.
I'm just here for a card fight.
Huh?
I wanna see if all
the hype holds true.
Are you up to the challenge?
Sure, why not?
Seriously?
‐Why am I wearing one?
‐Trust me.
This is the best place
to watch the action.
‐I'd rather not.
‐He'll love it!
Right, guys?
Oh, sure, give the
best spot to him!
‐Lucky!
‐It's unfair!
Yeah, right.
You know what you're doing?
Yeah, I'm quite
familiar with the system.
I'm ready when you are.
‐Stand up, the Vanguard!
(grumbling)
♪
Amber Dragon, Dawn!
Brugal!
I'll go first, if
that's all right.
I ride Lake Maiden, Lien.
♪
Brugal moves back, and
I activate Lien's skill.
I drop one card from
my hand and redraw one.
She got rid of a card
with a 10,000 point shield?
I draw.
First up, I'll ride
Amber Dragon, Daylight!
♪
And I activate Dawn's skill!
When I ride
Daylight on this unit,
I can search through my deck
and add a copy of Amber
Dragon, Dusk to my hand.
Thanks to Daylight's skill,
if Dawn is in the soul,
he receives an
additional 2,000 power!
Now I attack Lake Maiden, Lien!
Aw, geez!
(whimpering)
Drive trigger check.
♪
You had a good start,
but it won't last.
Being this close to the
action is bad for my nerves.
Eh, you'll get used to it.
What if I don't want to?
I ride Beast Knight, Garmore!
♪
With Garmore's skill, I
drop a card from my hand,
and superior call Snogal.
♪
Moving Brugal up, bam!
I call another Snogal.
He gains 1,000 power for
each other one of his kind
on the battlefield.
Now boosted by Snogal,
Garmore attacks your Vanguard!
♪
Drive trigger check.
Critical trigger.
That's 5,000 power to Brugal,
and Garmore takes
the critical effect!
♪
Brugal attacks with
support from my other Snogal.
♪
Gattling Claw Dragon will guard.
No, not him!
He's huge!
(growling)
(coughing)
That's it!
The reason she
threw out the unit
with the 10,000 point shield
is that she's got
11 more just like it.
On top of the 12
critical triggers,
she has multiple
copies of Snogal!
She's focused on
an all‐out attack!
I hope you're ready for this.
First, I ride
Amber Dragon, Dusk!
♪
With Daylight in the soul,
Dusk gains an extra 1,000 power.
I call Lava Arm
Dragon and Daylight.
♪
Daylight's skill activates.
When I call him to one
of the rear‐guard circles,
I can choose and discard
a Grade 3 Kagero unit,
then search my deck
for Amber Dragon Eclipse
and add it to my hand.
What was the point of that?
All he did was replace one
Grade 3 with another!
'Cause you don't want too
many of them in your hand.
A Grade 3 can't intercept
and has no shield.
A handful of those,
and you're defenseless.
Of course!
This way, he was able
to trade the unit he had
for the unit he wanted to have!
I'll have Dusk attack your
Vanguard with Daylight's help.
Hmm?
♪
Drive trigger check.
When Amber Dragon Dusk
attacks an opponent's Vanguard,
it gains an
additional 2,000 power!
Hmm?
Hot, hot, hot!
Oh, there's sparks everywhere!
Damage check.
Knock it off‐‐you flew
that close on purpose!
♪
Lava Arm Dragon attacks next.
His skill grants 2,000
power when he attacks!
♪
Hmm.
My turn's over.
So what exactly did Kai do
to make the celebrity angry?
Nothing!
As far as I know,
they'd never even spoken
before she showed up
saying she needed to see him!
But then again,
maybe she's just drawn
to his winning personality.
Huh, that's right!
Aichi's been over to
her shop a couple times.
♪
You know, I gotta say,
I expected you to play a
little more aggressively,
given your reputation and all.
Look, if you've got something
to say to me, just say it.
Don't play dumb!
We both know Aichi Sendou
would not have sought
out that power on his own.
Huh?
♪
Don't play dumb!
We both know Aichi Sendou
would not have sought
out that power on his own.
So that's it.
‐You know...
‐What now?
...he chose that
path for himself.
Uh, hey.
And who showed him the way?
I stand and draw!
I ride Fang of Light, Garmore!
I drop Marron from my hand,
and superior call Snogal!
♪
My Vanguard skill
grants him 1,000 power
for each Snogal and
Brugal on the battlefield.
With that many of them,
he gets a huge bonus.
I call High Dog Breeder, Akane!
And I'm activating
her counterblast!
Calling another
Snogal to battle.
♪
Brugal is retired.
She's got four Snogals
at 9,000 power each!
How do you like it, Kai?
This is the Royal
Paladin's Blizzard Formation!
♪
With Snogal's support, Fang
of Light, Garmore attacks!
♪
Checking the Twin Drive.
I pulled a critical trigger,
giving the critical
effect to Garmore
and the power to Snogal.
Second check.
♪
It's a draw trigger.
That's 5,000 power
to my Vanguard.
And I draw.
With a little
support from Snogal,
High Dog Breeder, Akane attacks.
♪
Embodiment of Armor,
Bahr will guard!
(roaring)
‐Ya!
‐Oh!
(groaning)
Snogals, finish him off!
Dragon Monk, Genjo
will guard that attack!
Not Genjo!
♪
His strength is far
beyond yours or mine.
Don't you see?
You were the only one
that could've stopped Aichi
from obtaining that much power.
It's strange, but I
don't know why I'm here.
Playing with this deck
will expand your power
far beyond what you
ever thought possible.
Trust me, you were
meant to have this.
Take it if you
desire real power.
Why did you let him
walk down that path
if you knew you wouldn't
be able to stop him?
Hmm.
Hmm?
♪
I stand and draw.
Amber Dragon Eclipse, ride!
(roaring)
Eclipse gains 1,000 power
when Dusk is in the soul.
♪
Then I call Demonic
Dragon Mage, Kimnara,
and Dragonic Overlord!
♪
Do you know him or something?
I always hoped that one day
I would get the chance
to battle with you.
I'm gonna get stronger‐‐
I know I can do it, Kai!
♪
It's like they want me to win,
and they're telling me
how to make it happen.
It never made much sense,
but I finally understand
what you meant about
picturing the battle.
Aichi, I'm sorry, but
I'm not going to fight you.
♪
Answer me!
Yeah.
It's my fault.
♪
All mine, because I've
seen that power before.
♪
I wasn't able to stop him‐‐
no, I couldn't have stopped him.
I didn't even know how.
Uh...
But unlike the last time,
I'm gonna set things right.
Using Kimnara's counterblast,
I can force one of my opponent's
Grade 1 rear‐guard units
to retire from the battle.
I choose Snogal!
(groaning)
Eclipse's counterblast!
When he hits you this turn,
I'll be sending two more
of your rear‐guards
to the drop zone!
Here he comes with a
boost from Daylight!
(crying)
I don't think so.
Alabaster Owl will guard.
Also, High Dog Breeder,
Akane intercepts.
♪
First check, draw trigger.
That's 5,000 power to Eclipse.
But for this to get through,
he'll have to pull a trigger
on the next draw, too!
♪
Second check‐‐critical trigger!
Another 5,000 power to Eclipse,
and extra damage for you!
♪
(screaming)
(sighing)
Look out for sparks!
With that successful attack,
I force two more of your
Snogals off the field!
(groaning)
♪
He wrecked the
Blizzard Formation!
Her power just took a huge hit!
All in one turn, he
dismantled her strategy!
Amazing!
Dragonic Overlord attacks!
Epona will guard!
Now Lava Arm Dragon!
‐Another Epona!
‐My turn's over.
So how are you going
to fix this problem?
I'll just become stronger
than he could ever be,
and bring him back myself.
Well, then let's not
waste any more time.
Do you honestly believe
that you can surpass
that level of power?
‐Yeah.
‐And can you save Aichi
from himself?
Of course I can.
♪
I call Knight of
Conviction, Bors,
and Knight of Silence,
Gallatin as well.
Snogal moves back.
‐And Garmore attacks!
‐Ahhh!
Wyvern Guard, Barri
will put a stop to that.
I still need to do
my Twin Drive check.
Second check!
Well, looky here,
a critical trigger.
I give all effects to Gallatin.
With a boost from
Snogal, he attacks.
(growling)
Tahr and Nehalem will guard!
♪
He is such a stubborn guy.
If he's worried about Aichi,
he should've just come
right out and said so.
♪
Dragonic Overlord attacks!
I don't guard.
♪
(yelling)
(roaring)
♪
(crickets chirping)
(grunting)
(birds chirping)
(cheering)
♪
Hmm?
Aichi.
Hey, you feeling
nervous about today?
What would make you think that?
He doesn't seem like
his usual self at all.
Don't worry, we're
gonna win this thing
because now I've got this deck.
Hold on.
Where did you get
those cards from?
What have you done
with your Blaster Blade?
‐Who cares?
‐You serious?
Hmm.
This deck was meant for me.
I'll use it to get better.
Then Kai will have no choice.
♪
(snoring)
I wish I'd been strong
enough to stop him.
♪
Aichi.
Does it have a name,
that awful power?
Psyqualia.
So that's what it is.
♪
Stand up, Vanguard!
‐Aichi's new deck‐‐
‐The Shadow Paladins?
Right, it's the same
one Ren Suzugamori used
at the last national tournament.
Thought so‐‐what is up
with Aichi these days?
And how did he get that deck?
No one can stop us.
It's a shame that
Kai couldn't be here
to see how powerful I've become.
Next time, Shadow Paladin!
Now that I've got these cards,
my winning image is
solidified in my mind.