(grunting)
♪
Hmm.
(grunting)
Pitiful, Nehalem.
You can't stop the attacks
of my Juggernaut Maximum
forever, you know.
Huh, you really think so?
♪
I got you!
You've got nothing.
You never stood a
chance against me.
Say what?
I'm gonna ride up to the
next grade right now.
(gasping)
Now ride the Vanguard!
Descend, Dragonic Overlord!
♪
Impossible.
(whimpering)
(shouting)
♪
(indistinct chattering)
(grunting)
Hmm, we're finished here.
I can't believe you beat
my Juggernaut Maximum.
What's with your luck, huh?
My luck?
How dare he.
Are you okay?
Winning matches
as usual, eh, Kai?
Hmm?
Miwa.
Have you even lost a game
since you moved back here?
No, not yet.
Nice!
Hey there!
Are any of your
regulars better
at Vanguard than this guy?
Don't know or care.
That settles it.
If she can't decide,
then I'll be the one.
Kai is the best!
Hey, man, he's not that great!
I almost had him.
Nice try, loser.
‐Hey!
‐Calm down!
Is the sore loser sore
about being called "loser"?
If he wasn't holding me
back, you'd be sorry!
Yeah, right.
Is that all it
takes to be on top?
These easy games are
a waste of my time.
Isn't there anyone
better around here?
♪
With countless people
around the world
playing trading card games,
they've quickly become
a part of our daily lives.
These days,
the biggest of them all
is Cardfight Vanguard.
♪
I never would have thought
that a game could
change my life forever.
♪
And the battles
of Kawanakajima
reach their bloody climax!
The fifth and final battle.
The forces of Uesugi
numbering 12,000.
Using a battle formation
known as "wheel winding"
they managed to ambush
Shingen's main force.
His opponent only
has 8,000 men.
Smelling the ambush, Takeda
prepares a counterattack.
The odds are bad!
Takeda's going down, oh!
Man, he's trying hard
to make this interesting.
Yeah, no kidding,
and he's not doing a very
good job of it, right, guys?
Ahem, so, it's clear
this was a time period
of life‐and‐death decisions.
Let's see.
Answer me this, Aichi Sendou.
Uh, yes?
How would you
have stayed alive
if you were transported to
the Warring States period?
Well, I guess, I...
Don't ask Shychi Aichi.
He chose the
quietest kid in class.
We're gonna be here
all afternoon.
Come on, Mr. Sendou.
Imagine you're really there.
I‐‐I guess...
I guess I would make sure
I always had an escape plan.
(laughing)
He's such a coward.
No wonder everybody
picks on him.
There he
being weird again.
What a great answer.
Man, oh, man,
you're hilarious.
Well, you know,
it's not a bad plan
if all you want
to do is stay alive.
How about next time you
try imagining yourself
with a bit bigger
role to play?
I‐‐I'm sorry.
Man, I sure messed that up.
Now then, this battle
at Kawanakajima
caused him to
lose his chance...
There's no way
that I would fit in
with such amazing soldiers.
Hmm.
But I just know
he would be a hero
in the Warring States period,
the Vanguard warrior
Blaster Blade.
♪
Move it, scum!
I am Blaster Blade.
I have come from
the United Sanctuary.
Five, bring me his head.
Let's go!
Taste my pain.
Heh.
Of course, he would never
have that chance again!
This would haunt him
till the end of his days.
Oh, man.
I was hoping this pack
would have something
strong enough
to beat that guy.
I suck.
No, it's all because of Kai.
I used to be the best
player at that store.
He thinks he can just waltz
in here with his cool hair
and beat me at my own game?
I've got to get my hands
on some better cards.
Hey, what's that small
fry so happy about?
Wait, that's a Vanguard card.
And it's Blaster Blade!
That's the kind of rare
power card I'm looking for.
♪
(clock chiming)
Wh‐‐what do you want from me?
Hey there, Aichi.
Why didn't you tell me you
were a Vanguard fighter?
A Vanguard what?
Don't play dumb.
If you've got the cards,
then you must be
familiar with the game.
You've got some, right?
Well, yeah, but I‐‐I‐‐
I never actually
use them or anything.
I'm not what you think I am.
‐Hmm.
Yeah, whatever,
just show me the card
you have hidden
in your pocket.
(whimpering)
♪
Ha‐ha, no way,
it is Blaster Blade!
With this, I could
finally beat that show‐off.
Oh, let me see!
Whoa, cool!
How about we go
to Card Capital?
‐Yeah!
‐Wait.
Morikawa.
That's mine!
It was a special gift!
You can't take it
away from me!
‐Wait!
‐Oops.
Don't push it.
You're not a Vanguard
fighter anyway.
A card this awesome
deserves to battle every day,
so I'll take it off
your hands, buddy.
Okay, let's get
to Card Capital!
Yeah!
Gi‐‐give it back.
That's not yours, you can't‐‐
♪
(indistinct chattering)
(panting)
Huh?
I challenge.
Huh, you're no challenge.
You talk like a big shot,
but I want a rematch
to decide who's best in
the shop once and for all.
No thanks.
What?
You're not very
good at this game.
You lack foresight and your
strategy is pretty weak.
All you care about
is brute force.
Playing you again would
just be a waste of my time,
so why bother?
Dude, that's harsh.
You won't get anything
out of it, huh?
Well, then, if you beat me,
you can have this card.
Oh, wow, that's Blaster Blade!
Those things are super
rare, man, that's great!
Blaster Blade?
Could it be that card?
Shall we?
Fine.
Oh, it's on then.
♪
My‐‐my card.
Oh, man, come on!
Why is my luck so bad today?
Your luck doesn't matter.
Now ride the Vanguard!
♪
I'm pretty sure that this
is the place he mentioned.
♪
That's six damaged, so I win.
Oh!
No way!
Let's play again.
We're finished here.
Hey, heads‐up, buddy.
Blaster Blade.
Hey, man, cheer up, you won.
Gi‐‐give me my card back.
‐Who's this?
‐Aichi.
Morikawa, hand it over.
Come on, it means
a lot to me!
Hey, I don't have it.
A missing card.
Do you mean that one?
Yeah, that's it.
That's my card.
Please, give it back.
No way.
This card belongs to me.
♪
Hey.
Huh?
Uh...
It's important that we respect
the terms and conditions
of a Vanguard battle,
don't you think?
This guy bet me
the card and lost.
(grunting)
‐Well, can I have it?
‐Sorry, kid.
When you lose a
card in battle,
you've got to fight
to get it back.
Well then, why don't
you fight me for it?
Huh?
(gasping)
Hmm, okay, kid, it's a deal.
Hold on, you can't fight him!
You've never even
played Vanguard before.
You don't have
a deck, do you?
It's true, I've never played.
But I built this deck
just in case I ever
got the chance to play.
Say what?
Take a seat and get comfy.
Move it along, loser boy.
(meowing)
What are you so
happy about, huh?
This battle.
We're about to
witness a match
between the best
player in the store
and a guy who's
never played the game.
This is gonna be hilarious!
Stop saying Kai's the best.
With the right cards,
I'm sure I could have...
♪
Since this is
your first time,
I'll explain the
rules as we go, okay?
‐Sure.
‐Oh, yeah.
You're not gonna stand
much of a chance against me
unless you have this Blaster
Blade back in your deck.
Yes, that's right.
So, you can borrow it until
I beat you and take it back.
Blaster Blade.
Th‐‐thank you.
You're lending him a card
and you're gonna
explain the rules?
How unusually
sweet of you, Kai.
Are you finished?
I'm only gonna explain
the rules once,
so you better listen.
‐Let's start.
‐Right.
Now, imagine it.
Our spirits have just been
transported to the surface
of a planet similar
to Earth called "Cray".
In this form, there are only
two powers available to us,
the first of which
allows us to summon the
monsters of this planet.
The cards in your
deck are your units.
Call to them.
But, first, we both need
to draw our starting hands.
Got all that?
The cards you draw can both
attack and defend for you.
These are your units.
Hmm.
Each card has its
own grade and powers.
Any other abilities
will be on the card.
♪
And, then, there is
the second power
of our spirit form.
The power to ride is to
possess one of our units.
‐Oh, really?
‐Oh, dude.
The units that we merge with
are called our "Vanguards."
You follow?
The word "vanguard" means
"the one that leads the way."
The Vanguard leads the way.
Now, the object of the game
is to defeat your opponent
by landing attacks
on their Vanguard.
The card in front of you is
a grade zero unit, right?
‐Yes.
‐Okay, flip it over.
Ready, stand up the Vanguard.
Lizard Runner, Undeux.
For me?
Stardust Trumpeter, stand up.
♪
Our Vanguards are ready for
battle on the planet Cray.
It'll be easier
for me to explain
if I take the
first turn, okay?
Sure.
You start each turn
by drawing a card.
Each turn, you can
promote your Vanguard
using a unit of no more
than one grade above.
Stack that unit on
top of the Vanguard.
Ride the Embodiment
of Armor, Bahr.
Now, once your
Vanguard is promoted,
you can summon lower
grade support units
to the battlefield.
These are called
the "rear guard".
I call the Flame
of Hope, Aermo.
♪
I now have two
units on the field,
and with them, I attack.
Huh?
Except that you can't
attack on your first turn.
(sighing)
The downside of going first.
It's your turn.
Right, I'll draw a card.
Then, I'll promote.
Ride Little Sage, Marron!
And call Wingal, too!
♪
Well, it looks like we both
have two units in play.
So are you attacking?
I‐‐I'll attack you.
Okay, then do it.
Turn your Vanguard
to signal the attack.
Then I attack your Bahr
with Little Sage, Marron.
When your Vanguard attacks,
you can increase its power
by supporting it with
one of your rear‐guard.
In that case, I'll
add Wingal's power
to Marron's attack.
When your Vanguard attacks,
you need to reveal the
top card of your deck
and check for
a drive trigger.
Look for a mark in
the upper‐right corner.
If there isn't one,
add it to your hand.
Then, my attack went through?
Uh‐huh.
Okay.
Your attack
overwhelmed my Vanguard.
This is the damage
from that hit.
Now, if you can deal me
five more damage,
then my forces will banish
from the surface
of the planet.
That means I lose.
Does it all make sense?
Uh, yeah.
Well, it's good to see
that you're catching on.
It's my turn.
Rid the Dragon
Knight, Nehalem.
I call Bahr.
♪
Ride the Vanguard.
No more Mr. Nice Kai, eh?
Aichi doesn't stand a chance.
(laughing)
I attack Marron with Bahr.
Um, Bahr and Marron both have
the exact same attack
power, so then...
If the power is equal,
the attack goes through.
But if this attack
goes through now,
you'll be able
to hit me again
with the Dragon Knight,
Nehalem afterwards,
and I'll take
two damage, right?
Yes, but you can weaken
your opponent's attack
by defending with the
cards in your hand.
Then, I guard with the
Bringer of Good Luck, Epona.
The number on the
side of the card
becomes your damage shield.
Bahr's power isn't high
enough to break through.
My attack has no effect.
But now that card
you defended with
has to go into the drop zone.
Next, I attack Marron with
the Dragon Knight, Nehalem,
combined with the
rear guard's power.
I don't guard.
Not that I need it, but I'll
check for a drive trigger.
(shouting)
♪
'Kay, now it's your move.
Right.
We both have one damage each.
All right.
Ride the Knight of
Silence, Gallatin!
♪
And, also, I call
Marron and Flogal.
I use Gallatin with
the support of Wingal
to attack Nehalem!
♪
Then Marron with
the power of Flogal
will attack Nehalem again!
I can't let you do that.
Your attempt fails.
Then, in that case,
I guess my turn's over.
But I did cause one damage.
If we continue trading
damage like this,
I'll just barely win.
Hmm, why do you
look so relieved?
Did you seriously think I was
gonna let it end this way?
Time for your final lesson.
I call Wyvern Strike,
Tejas and Jarran.
(grunting)
Picture it.
The assault that
I'm about to begin.
(gulping)
First, I attack
Marron with Bahr.
I guard with Flogal.
Ha, then I come for Gallatin
with the combined might
of Jarron and Tejas.
I can't stop that.
That's right, and these
two get a special bonus
for supporting each other.
An extra 4,000 power.
♪
(firing)
Now I have two
damage, as well.
Guess we're tied.
Oh, who said I was
finished attacking you?
I attack Gallatin with
Nehalem, supported by Aermo.
Over 16,000?
Are you sure that's all?
Hmm.
Embodiment of Spear, Tahr,
but just look
what's in the corner.
When this mark appears
on a card, you draw.
It gives you a 5,000
attack power bonus,
and it also increases
the damage of the attack
by one point.
Then‐‐then that means...
This one is gonna hit
you for two damage,
and once I get the lead,
I don't give it up.
(gasping)
(zapping)
♪
(grunting)
(shouting)
(gasping)
Are you okay, man?
Uh‐huh.
Two damage.
Putting me at
a total of four.
This is bad.
You were able to
picture it, I see.
Witness true Vanguard.
Guess it's all over.
If it was me, I could
still make a comeback.
For sure.
It's your turn.
Uh, mm.
What's up?
Have you lost the will
to continue fighting?
(laughing)
Aichi?
You're really good,
but, still, this battle
is a lot of fun.
♪
Do you know him or something?
I always hoped that one day
I would get the chance
to battle with you.
So then you're
Aichi Sendou, right?
That's right, Kai.
And you gave me the power to
stand here before you today.
I see.
Let's go.
Arise my avatar, ride!
(grunting)
Blaster Blade!
♪
You're really good,
but, still,
this battle is
a lot of fun, Kai.
Sendou, right?
You guys know each other?
Yes, the one who gave
me this Blaster Blade,
and the one who made me think
of becoming a
Vanguard fighter.
The person who
started it all?
Are we finished talking now?
On the next
Cardfight!! Vanguard,
"Ride to Victory!"
Now, whenever
you're ready, Aichi,
picture our Vanguard
fight in your mind.