♪
I've had countless card fights
with Izaki and Morikawa,
and Misaki's taught me the
importance of Grade Three's.
♪
I call on the power of the
proud white wings of fate!
Ride!
Solitary Knight Gancelot!
Kamui turned out to
be one tough opponent,
but you know,
I feel like that battle
made me a bit stronger.
♪
So, Card Capital is the only
card shop you've been to?
Uh, yeah.
This is gonna be awesome.
At a new store,
there'll be fresh people
for us to card fight with.
Come to think of it,
Kai said that he fights
at a lot of
different shops.
Plus, you never know.
We might have a
fateful encounter
with a rare card today.
It calls me, I can
hear its voice calling out
ever so gently
to my warrior soul!
You sure are excited today!
Course, buddy, it's almost
time for the shop tournament!
"Shop tournament?"
You're entering, aren't ya?
Me, enter?
I don't think so!
I've still got
a lot to learn,
but I'll be sure to cheer you
guys on from the sidelines.
Come on, Aichi, have some
confidence in yourself.
I knew I could count
on you to cheer me on!
♪
Now, where could it be?
I swear there was a
card shop around here.
Please don't
tell me we're lost.
What‐‐I never get lost.
I always know the way.
Rare cards call
to me once again!
I beg you!
Let me hear
your sweet song!
♪
Hey, you guys,
take a look.
Is that it right there?
♪
This place
looks pretty weird,
but I guess every card
shop is gonna be different.
Okay, Aichi,
you lead the way.
Hey!
♪
What's this?
Customers?
Excuse me, is
there anyone here?
What's with this shop?
The ceiling looks
like outerspace.
‐It's a projection.
‐"Projection?"
It isn't Card Capital,
that's for sure.
No doubt.
Hey, guys!
Look.
♪
I think that's a Crested Dragon,
and that's a Star Drive Dragon.
Those cards
are legendary.
I mean, they're not
even sold anymore!
The rare cards'
voice has led us here.
Holograms?
Welcome, gentlemen.
♪
Thank you for coming
out to Card Shop Psy.
Psy?
♪
Hi there, what's up?
That's better.
Please come with me.
♪
(groans)
No way.
What is it?
It's the Vanguard
fight stage.
That's so awesome!
♪
Check out those play mats.
Do you mind if
we use this thing?
Of course not, try it.
If you can, that is.
I challenge you
to a card fight.
For sure!
It's not working.
Well, turn it on.
Hey, is there a
switch on your side?
Huh?
Doesn't look like it.
There aren't any buttons.
(whooshing)
(gasps)
Place your deck
on the terminal.
Okay.
(machinery whirring)
The system turned on for him?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, let's do this.
Out of the way.
‐Huh?
‐What?
No, this game is mine!
You can't just come
over here and butt in.
Huh?
♪
I mean, be‐‐be my guest.
Huh?
Um, I‐‐
Hey, my name's Kourin.
You are?
Aichi Sendou.
So, you think you can
show me how good you are?
You want to
fight against me?
♪
Man, what is it with this woman
just showing up out of nowhere.
Right, Morikawa?
Kourin, what
a nice name.
I think I figured it out.
The force that led us here
today wasn't a rare card.
It was her beauty!
Are you okay?
Aichi Sendou.
I've never heard
that name before.
What tournaments have
you competed in?
Oh, no tournaments
for me, ma'am.
I'm still kinda new to this.
Hmm.
♪
Mm‐hmm.
He's really never
been in a competition?
He just started a
couple of weeks ago.
(growling)
That a beginner like him
can battle my darling Kourin
ahead of me is
unforgivably insane!
She seems like
she's really good.
At least I get to try out
a Vanguard fight stand.
This should be fun.
♪
I'm ready when you are.
Alright!
(machinery whirring)
It's gonna start!
‐Stand up, vanguard!
Stardust Trumpeter!
(whooshing)
No way!
I can see all the units
on the battlefield
like I'm actually there.
Why do I have to
fight a rookie?
This isn't even going
to be entertaining.
I'll end it quickly.
I'll go first.
I draw and ride the
flash shield, Isolde!
It's my turn, draw.
And I also ride Isolde!
That is so weird.
I guess this means
you're running
a Royal Paladin deck too.
I am.
Small world, huh?
I call Starlight Unicorn!
♪
Raising Isolde's attack power
by 2,000 for this turn.
♪
With Gancelot's
in‐hand skill,
I shuffle him back
into the deck
and search for a lower
Grade Royal Paladin.
That card is...
Hmm, you've
got a rare one.
I'm impressed, kid.
♪
A Blaster Blade?
Yeah, it's pretty much
his favorite card.
And it's only a Grade Two.
I attack Isolde
with Unicorn.
♪
Now checking for a trigger.
Trigger activated.
Isolde's power just
went up by 5,000.
♪
With that power
boost to her Isolde,
there's no way I'm gonna
land an attack this turn.
But if I get a trigger,
I can deal her damage,
and if not, at least
I get another card.
♪
I'm attacking my Isolde
against your vanguard.
♪
I check for
a drive trigger.
No trigger.
I'm done now,
it's your turn.
Then, I stand and draw.
I ride Tristan.
♪
And I call Starlight Unicorn
and Flogal to the rear guard.
♪
My Unicorn attacks!
Damage trigger check.
Trigger activated!
Isolde's power is
raised by 5,000 points.
Tristan attacks with
the support of Flogal.
♪
Checking for
a drive trigger.
(yelps)
She's pushing back.
Go, Kourin!
Win this for me, sweetie!
So you've taken more
damage than I have,
yet our decks are
really similar.
Can you spot the
difference between us?
Can you, rookie?
(shuddering)
♪
Your friend is
pretty bad at this.
Yeah, but he's still just
a beginner, and besides,
this Kourin seems
really good if you ask me.
Maybe we should go save him?
No, this is his
problem to deal with.
What are you‐‐ I get it.
You think this battle will help
him build character, right?
No, this is what he gets for
battling Kourin before me.
Aichi, you're no
match for her beauty!
Huh?
After careful
consideration,
he's the bad one.
Poor thing.
Don't bully him
too much now.
Hmm.
Hmm!
How long are you
gonna make me wait?
If you're gonna give up,
then hurry and‐‐
Hold on a minute.
I'm not giving up just yet!
Sorry for stalling the fight.
I made some
mistakes earlier,
but now I'm ready to
show you what I can do.
Oh, this is gonna
be just great.
My turn!
Stand and draw!
I don't want to give up.
Not before I get a chance
to bring Him into battle.
Stand up now, my avatar!
Ride Blaster Blade!
♪
Oh.
Oh!
♪
Whoa, that is so awesome.
So, that's Blaster Blade, is it?
♪
Wingal, then I move Starlight
Unicorn back and call Gallatin!
♪
(roars)
Give me strength.
♪
Blaster Blade.
Rear guard, you ready?
♪
Hmm.
Gallatin attacking
your vanguard,
with Starlight Unicorn's
support,
his attack power is 16,000.
I guard the attack
with Epona.
♪
(growls)
(grunts)
Go, Wingal!
With Wingal in support, this
attack will hit for sure.
Yeah, those two units work
really well together.
♪
(shouts)
(grunts)
Attack!
♪
(yells)
Check for a drive trigger.
Nothing there.
Well, that makes two of us.
My poor Kourin is tied
for damage with that rat!
You know, kid, you're
pretty good for a rookie.
My turn.
Stand and draw.
I ride Crimson Butterfly,
Brigitte!
I call a second one
to my rear guard.
Next, I move Starlight Unicorn
back and call Tristan.
Oh, man, she's got
so many powerful units!
Aichi, get ready
for a gorgeous end!
Two Grade Three's?
Rear‐guard Brigitte is
attacking Blaster Blade!
♪
Epona, I'm gonna
leave this up to you!
♪
(roars)
I wonder if you can
guard this next one.
♪
Go!
(shouts)
Come on, Blaster Blade!
Let's not forget
the twin drive!
Looks like it doesn't
have a trigger.
Lucky for me, Gancelot
is Grade Three.
Revealing a Grade Three
in a drive check
raises Brigitte's
power by 5,000.
♪
Second.
Now it's really on!
Brigitte is gonna keep the
critical effect of this trigger,
but I'm going to
have Tristan gain
the extra 5,000
attack power bonus.
♪
Burn in the fire,
little Blaster Blade!
♪
(grunting)
You're the best, Kourin!
Could you heat me up
with your flames too?
(chuckling)
♪
Attack now!
(grunts)
That makes five.
Huh?
Damage trigger active.
I recover one card
from my damage zone.
You had some pretty lucky timing
there on the heal trigger.
My turn's over.
And he does it again, folks.
Why doesn't Aichi just quit?
It's my turn.
I stand and draw.
If I leave Isolde in my hand,
I might make it
through the next turn,
but if I attack with full force
and get a drive trigger...
Defending again
is too risky.
I've got to push
for the win.
I call on the power of the
proud white wings of fate!
Ride Solitary
Knight Gancelot!
Aichi did it!
He got a Grade Three
out on the battlefield.
Don't talk to me.
I counterblast.
Raising his attack
power by 5,000.
One more time.
♪
That is gonna be a
really strong attack.
Now I call
Isolde and Marron.
♪
He's finally showing
up for the battle.
♪
Gallatin, attack her!
Hmm?
♪
(roaring)
Epona.
♪
I attack with Marron.
Guard!
♪
(grunts)
Let's go!
♪
Checking for drive triggers.
First check.
No help.
♪
Come on, cards, I need you.
Looks like you didn't
get what you hoped.
Seems so, no drive trigger.
(groans)
Checking damage triggers.
One, and that's two.
Third card.
Huh?
Heal trigger activated.
One damage recovered.
My turn.
Stand and draw.
I call Isolde!
♪
You better hope for
another heal trigger.
It's not over yet.
There must be a way to win.
Brigitte is attack Gancelot.
♪
I guard with Flogal.
(growling)
Again!
No guard this time.
Aichi, you're finished!
Just run.
What's wrong?
He's not even defending it.
One more to go, so long as
she doesn't draw that card.
♪
You know the timing
for your all out attack
was pretty
impressive, rookie.
Unfortunately, this
is the end of the line.
(gasps)
No way!
(groans)
Critical trigger activated!
(screaming)
So, how do you turn
this thing on?
Sorry, the batteries ran out.
Those must be
huge batteries.
I guess I still have
a lot to learn, huh?
Huh?
That was your hand?
You had no options,
but you never gave up.
Thanks, Kourin.
I know I lost, but it
was still fun to fight you.
(clapping)
What a great fight.
It was impressive.
Suiko.
For you.
It's the King of
Knights, Alfred!
You're giving this to me?
As a memento of your visit.
Thank you so much.
Tournaments.
Enter tournaments,
and once you're better,
I'll fight you again.
What do you say, rookie?
Really?
Me next, sweetheart!
Defeat me so bad.
Make me learn so good!
Gee, looks like
we're closing now.
Alfred, huh?
That's pretty cool.
♪
That boy.
I think he'll
be back again.
♪
It's missing!
What's the problem now?
That shop where my
beautiful Kourin works!
I've looked all over
and I can't find it!
Maybe it went under.
No customers.
Oh, that's not fair!
I haven't even had the chance
to fight my baby
Kourin yet, oh!
Be quiet.
Which shop was it now?
It was in the city, and
they had this special table
that visualized
the battle for you.
That part was so cool!
Yeah!
Without her,
I'll be nothing!
Nothing!
(crying)
You're nothing anyway.
That card shop.
I've never heard of it.
(Morikawa continues crying)
♪
Aichi, was that
card shop big?
Was it clean and neat?
Did it have lots
of customers?
Shin, you're being
too competitive.
But it must
make you wonder.
Right, Aichi?
Well, the most amazing part
was how the units came
to life before your eyes!
Yeah, that might be tricky
to set up in Card Capital,
but maybe we could
do a standing fight.
"Standing fight?"
Next time,
"The Fearsome Soulblast!"
The battle between
Kai and Kamui
will trigger pictures
in my mind.