♪
Hmm, even with
the cards I cut,
I'm still over 50.
Well, I guess‐‐
There.
At least this way
the deck's balanced.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hang on a sec!
(stammering)
(grunts, groans)
Hey, what's the big idea?
Huh?
You've got some nerve trying to
kick me out of your deck, Aichi!
If you're looking for
someone to get rid of,
you should start with that
little weakling, Flogal.
What was that?
Of course he'd rather
keep me in his deck,
what with my lovely
stand trigger and all.
You think that just cause
you've got a 1,000 more power
you're better
than me or something?
You want to fight?
Bring it!
(growling)
No, hold on, there's
no need for that.
I'll cut something else!
Calm down!
Well, you better
not cut me.
That's right!
I refuse to be cut!
I'm the most powerful
card you've got!
Don't forget how important
a critical trigger is!
(cards talking indistinctly)
Aichi?
Emi, I'm a little
busy right now.
Aichi!
(cards continue talking)
Stop!
I told you, I'll
talk to you later!
Enough already!
You're talking in
your sleep again!
Huh?
‐Emi?
‐Look at you!
If I wasn't here, you'd
miss the whole training camp.
"Emi?"
"All my cards have
turned against me!"
"Who will save me?"
Morikawa, Izaki!
(laughing)
‐"Emi!"
You better not tell
anyone about this!
Try and stop me!
Well, I guess
this just proves
that you can't get out
of bed without my help.
♪
Come on, I need
help waking up too!
♪
Morning, everyone.
‐Good morning!
Well, better late
than never, right?
Good sleep?
Looks like he's
still asleep.
Yeah, I was up late
working on something.
You sure were.
♪
(yawning)
So, did you manage to make any
improvements on your deck?
Uh, you see, I took all
the cards I have right now
and I tried to rebuild
the deck from scratch,
but it wound up being
pretty much the same.
I'm not surprised.
You're a new player
with a limited amount
of units to work with.
Just don't get discouraged.
Sure.
Hold on, are Kai
and Kenji still asleep?
Nope, I'll show you!
♪
They were up at
the crack of dawn,
and they've been battling
each other all morning!
(gasps)
So, that's it.
Nice plan.
Oh, I know you're hiding
something from me.
♪
Come on, give
the cards a rest.
Breakfast is getting cold.
Okay.
Without your help
we'll never be able
to finish everything
so hurry up!
♪
Yeah, we'll be in
after this.
No, no, no,
not after this.
Now!
(shuddering)
It'll just take a second.
We should be done here
in the next couple turns,
don't ya think?
Kai?
Hmm, works for me.
Good.
Well, then, I believe
it's your turn.
Yep.
What gives.
You can't tear
these two apart.
♪
Seriously?
Last night's leftovers?
Sorry, guys, but we have
to use the rest of the stew
or it'll go to waste.
I guess we did peel
a lot of potatoes.
I'm not gonna name names,
but someone here
chopped a ton of onions.
I like onions.
Well, we'd better
finish this off
or we'll be having stew
for our lunch as well.
‐No, thanks.
‐Aichi, start eating!
♪
Wow, it's even
better today!
I could have it again!
Kids these days.
(groaning)
♪
(giggles)
Huh?
Hey!
Why isn't she
eating any, huh?
I'm not a big fan
of food in the morning.
Is that okay with you?
I thought so.
♪
Nice!
Looks like we've
taken care of that.
Good work, guys.
Oh, I'm never eating again.
Are you okay, Aichi?
How about you all
head down to the ocean
and settle your
stomachs a bit?
♪
That's right!
Our journey to the sea
was not without purpose!
The time has come!
I shall conquer the beach.
You remembered your
bathing suit, right?
Yeah, but I sunburn
really easily,
so I'm not sure how
long I'll stick around.
What a baby!
Yeah!
(Morikawa laughing)
(stammering)
(grunts)
(groaning)
Why did you trip me,
you little brat?
Answer me this.
What is the purpose
of this camp?
Well, uh, to go swimming?
Wrong answer!
We're training
our card skills!
Oh, yeah,
there's that too.
Really?
How could you possibly
forget the main reason
for us coming here?
Listen, we're
not gonna waste
our day on the beach
goofing around.
What else is there?
I knew I could count on
you to ask that question!
The time has finally come,
and now we begin...
Our special training.
"Special training?"
Yeah.
We need to find the strength
to defeat Team Asteroid
and the only way to do that
is if we undergo special
Vanguard training.
Training.
Maybe I could beat Kai!
Sure, training makes
anything possible.
Alright, let's do this.
But first, before we start,
I need to know that
you'll be able to follow
the Kamui training
regimen without question!
Can you do that?
Yes, sir!
What are you?
(groaning)
There are leaders and
then there are followers.
No kidding.
Those two are so similar,
I'm surprised they
aren't best friends.
Here we are, guys.
The perfect place to start.
So what exactly do you
have planned for us?
We have to begin
with the basics,
so let's do some
practice draws.
‐Really?
‐Really.
First, you need
to make sure
your feet are
shoulder width apart.
Drop your hips down,
then calmly pull your hand
back into striking position.
Your eyes fixed
on the target
like an eagle
circling its prey.
Intensity in your gaze.
And draw!
Draw!
‐Draw!
‐Yes!
‐Great start, Morikawa!
‐Draw!
‐Draw.
I can't hear you!
Draw, draw,
draw, draw, draw.
Draw, draw, draw.
I‐‐I draw.
No, no!
Your grab is too weak.
You've got to lunge forward
like it's the last card
you're ever gonna get.
Draw, draw, draw, draw!
I draw!
Right.
A thousand more!
Get to it!
Yes, sir!
All together now!
‐One!
‐Two!
‐Three!
That's how they're planning to
spend their day at the beach?
Silly boys.
Believe it or not, ladies,
it's worse over here.
‐Nine hundred and ninety nine.
‐One thousand.
(panting)
Now, that's a
Vanguard workout.
Giving up already?
I thought you
weren't a loser.
"Giving up?"
I'd sooner wear a dress!
Alright, sir, what
are your orders now?
Nice.
Let's continue.
Next up, we're
gonna learn about...
the Vanguard slam!
What's a Vanguard slam?
Sounds exactly the same
as what we just did.
The draw is like an
eagle seizing its prey,
but the Vanguard slam is
like an eagle taking its prey
and ripping it in half.
An eagle?
Ah, check it out!
You embarrass
us all, Morikawa!
Huh?
‐One!
‐Two!
‐Stand up, the vanguard.
(giggles)
My friends, we're
not just a bunch
of weaklings
playing a card game.
Push‐ups, sit‐ups,
lunges and squats!
I want to see five sets
of each from every one!
Move it!
Go, go, go, go!
Take no prisoners!
(whimpering)
The total power on
this attack is 22,000.
I don't guard.
(shouts)
I win!
(all groaning)
Right!
On your feet!
‐Hey, wait.
‐What now?
Have you finally
decided to give up?
Never, you've
just forgotten
one of the most important
things in Vanguard.
Like what?
What could I possibly
be missing?
The game of Vanguard is
nothing without imagination.
Imagination?
Yeah.
In a Vanguard fight,
there's nothing more important
than your imagination.
It allows you to
feel the connection.
♪
In a world where
the melding of science
and magic is developed
into a unique civilization,
one being has descended
onto its surface
to stop the
long‐lasting chaos.
I am the vanguard!
The strongest fighter known
to man, Katsumi Morikawa!
(gasps)
That's amazing!
I totally get what
you're trying to do!
Come on, Izaki,
picture it!
You too, Kamui!
Oh, I guess if you say so.
♪
Picture it.
Imagine it.
♪
Hey, you guys!
Lunch is ready!
Lunch! It's about time.
Imagine, imagine,
imagine, imagine.
(groans)
Imagine, imagine,
imagine, imagine.
Breakfast was heavy,
so I figured we'd just
have some noodles for lunch.
What a good call!
This is about all
I can handle right now.
That sure hits the spot!
After this, we'll
do some more exercises,
unless you maggots
are ready to quit.
Well, I, for one,
will never give in,
no matter how bad it gets!
I have something
much better planned.
Wait until
you see this.
(all gasping)
♪
Manager, where
are these from?
(chuckling)
I'm a bit of a collector,
and you're looking at my
personal stash of cards.
So, every single one of
these is a Vanguard card?
You bet your booties!
To help you train,
you can borrow the set
for the rest of the day.
Yes!
Hands off!
You're so greedy!
You're only
borrowing them.
Please be careful.
(all arguing)
Hey, Aichi.
Put out your
right hand for me.
Here.
Those are the best
Royal Paladins I have.
(gasps)
Thanks, these
cards are amazing!
♪
Wow!
There's a ton of cards
in here I've never seen!
I bet.
Now as part
of your training,
I want you to
rebuild your deck
using those cards to
fit your winning image.
Huh, you mean‐‐
You got it.
Now's your chance to try and
realize your full potential.
♪
Okay!
Hmm.
‐Hmm.
You don't have enough
Grade Three's, man.
With this many options
added to the mix,
it's nearly
impossible to decide
which ones to
put in my deck.
Aichi.
Aichi Sendou.
Huh?
Hmm.
Read my lips,
more Grade Three's.
Did a card just talk?
No, no.
I'm just really tired today.
Aichi Sendou.
(whooshing)
Our leader.
Aichi Sendou.
♪
What‐‐what's going on?
What‐‐what's
happening to me?
(screaming)
♪
Is this Cray?
(whistles)
♪
(howls)
(gasps)
♪
Well, well.
Have you finished
working on your deck?
Oh!
Nice.
How about you and I play a
game to test your new units?
Okay.
♪
What have we here?
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
♪
I don't actually remember
building this deck.
But I can't
shake the feeling
that these cards
will help me win.
♪
Come on now.
You've got
the first turn.
Oh, yeah, sorry!
Here goes; no time
for distractions.
I draw.
I ride Little Sage, Marron.
Barcgal moves
to the rear guard,
and with his skill,
I call Flogal.
♪
I think I'll
end my turn here.
Well, that's a pretty
standard start for him.
I guess I'll have
to wait until next turn
to see what kind
of changes he's made.
I start by riding
Karenroid Daisy.
♪
And then I call one more
Karenroid Daisy.
♪
First up, I'm gonna attack
Marron with my vanguard.
♪
Drive check.
I got a trigger.
I'm giving the attacking
Daisy the plus one critical,
and the power bonus will
obviously go to my other one.
(grunts)
Now, the powered up
Daisy attacks Marron.
I'm not gonna guard.
♪
(grunts)
Damage trigger check.
I got a critical trigger giving
all the effects to Marron.
Okay, but I don't have
anyone left to attack with.
It's unfortunate
that you were unable
to pull that at
a more useful time.
My units stand and I draw.
♪
Nice!
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride...
Blaster Blade!
♪
I'm not sure
what to do next.
Aichi, use me.
♪
Of course!
First, I call
High Dog Breeder Akane!
♪
"High Dog Breeder Akane?"
That wasn't in
his deck yesterday!
I pay the cost to
activate Akane's skill.
Now, I'm grabbing Pongal.
Superior call!
♪
(whistles)
Another one.
I've got just enough for
Pongal's counter blast.
(howls)
♪
(electricity crackling)
This is...
♪
(gasps)
Good work, looks like
you've finally found
the winning image
we talked about.
♪
Hmm.
Yeah.
♪
I've got a winning
image for sure.
As expected
from my best pupil,
you've grown a lot and now
you're almost as good as I am.
But Morikawa‐‐
The time has come.
You must defeat me
in a game of Vanguard
in order to
complete your training.
But I‐‐
To be fair,
I got to warn ya,
the deck that I created
with the manager's cards
has more
Grade Three's in it
than a playground
at lunchtime
in a school for
only Grade Three's!
You've got to hold on.
I'm still fighting here.
That's okay,
I'll switch with him...
now that I've
seen your new deck.
And it's a good one.
See you!
Thanks very much, Yuri.
So, you ready, buddy?
Those kids sure
do have a lot of energy.
No doubt, but you know,
they are getting better.
In what way?
Being able to modify
his deck so quickly,
that boy has real talent.
Sounds like Toshiki Kai isn't
the only member of their group
we need to our eye on.
♪
Team Quadrifoglio.
They might just be the rivals
we've been looking for.
♪
This training camp?
It was a good idea.
♪
Has everyone been
to the bathroom?
Cause here we go!
(cheering)
Before we leave, I just
want to tell you guys
how much fun we had.
Thank you for inviting us.
I'm so glad you
were all able to come.
Catch you on the flip side.
Next time we
play each other,
it'll be at the
national championship.
Right!
♪
Hey, you guys!
I've got a fun card game
we can play on the way home.
♪
Hmm, they're still just kids.
But they're all working so hard
to realize their potential.
(snoring)
I have this
really weird feeling
I forgot to do
something this weekend.
I just realized I never got
the chance to go swimming!
Oh, Manager, go back!
We need to go
to the beach now.
I‐‐I can't do that.
(stammering)
Oh, cruel fate!
Why do you mock me so?
♪
A deck made to win.
Shouldn't every
deck be made to win?
I guess it's about finding
your way to victory,
or having your
opponent play it your way.
Ha, actually that
sounds about right.
Develop your units
and force your play style on
your opponent just like Kai.
Right!
Next time, "The King of
Underground Fights".
Kai's so good, I bet he
has tons of winning images.
I wonder about
that guy sometimes.
It feels like if I
don't watch his back,
he's gonna get
himself into big trouble.