(car whizzing)
♪
Hmm?
This one is named
Oracle Guardian, Apollon.
And this is Lozenge Magus.
(meowing)
Stop it, these aren't
for you, kitty.
(meowing)
Oh, oh, that's great.
You made me drop the deck
that Dad built for me.
Well?
(meowing)
Why are Mom and Dad so late?
I hope they didn't forget
they promised to teach me
how to card fight today.
(sighing)
Misaki, come quickly!
There's been an accident,
and your parents are‐‐
Huh?
♪
(gasping)
(grunting)
(meowing)
It's been years and I still
dream about that night.
(birds chirping)
♪
(meowing)
Oh, my head.
Oh, don't worry.
It's not really that bad.
(groaning)
♪
Misaki, are you up yet?
I made breakfast.
You should come down
and eat something
before it gets cold.
Why does my uncle insist
on taking care of me
like I'm some little kid?
I'll be right down.
But I'm only gonna
have toast today.
Toast?
Then who's gonna eat
all these pancakes?
♪
(humming)
Wow, what a great job.
I really outdid
myself this time.
Hey, check these out.
And what are those for?
I'm putting up a sign
in honor of Team Q4,
only I can't decide
if it should say,
"Congrats, Q4,
on making the nationals,"
or, "Congrats on making
the nationals, Q4."
What should I do?
Either one sounds fine.
He gets excited about
the little things
just like Dad used to.
What a beautiful sign.
This is the most beautiful
drawing I've ever seen.
I'm gonna hang it up in the
store first thing tomorrow.
Ah, Assisticat,
what are you doing?
(meowing and grunting)
‐That's new.
‐Spiffy.
‐Nice sign.
‐Are you guys serious?
This one has a
ketchup stain on it.
Look!
You're right!
Wait, that's not ketchup.
Ugh.
(meowing and groaning)
This is bad, bro, really bad.
What's bad?
Ren Suzugamori, of course.
Hmm?
♪
Why are you so
worried about that guy?
Don't you get it?
He's just one of the people
we're gonna have to
deal with at nationals,
and who knows how good
the other players will be?
I hope for your sake those
others aren't at my level.
I hope for the world's
sake they aren't that bad.
Actually, after
seeing Ren play,
I'm feeling kind of
nervous about the nationals.
Fear not, bro!
We've got this.
What is it?
I put together a copy
of the deck he was using
the other day so we can learn
more about his play style.
Not a bad plan for
a little shrimp.
Who are you calling
a "shrimp," loser!
Come again?
‐Kamui.
‐Morikawa.
At least I know how
to play Vanguard!
‐This is wrong.
‐Huh?
You're missing
a copy of CoCo,
and there were two copies
of Chocolat, not three.
Hmm, you're right.
But as far as the deck goes,
he only used it that
one time at PSY shop.
I doubt we'll be able to
learn anything from it.
But‐‐but I thought...
Fine then.
I've got another idea.
Card fighting isn't
all about experience.
It also has to do with
your own personal style.
Basically, if we
improve the way we play,
then we can still win big
regardless of how
new you guys are.
That's a pretty
good idea, Kamui.
Yeah, well, I have a lot of
experience at Vanguard...
What a pain.
Now, now.
I guess you could
say that, for Q4,
I'm the brains
behind the surgery.
Mm, operation?
Uh, yeah, that's what I said,
the brains behind
the operation.
Cut it out!
Make me!
Well, enough messing around.
Let's start the battle.
Don't forget this match
is all about improving
your play style, okay?
Improving my play style?
That's easier said than done.
♪
(sighing)
‐Hmm.
‐Huh?
No Grade Twos.
I'm gonna redraw.
Yeah, me too.
That's a good move.
He's only got one
grade three in his hand.
Seriously?
Hmm.
No luck.
Libra, Amaterasu, Milk.
Daddy, this one is
Weather Girl, Milk, right?
And let's see, what
could this one be?
(chuckling)
♪
Misaki?
Is it okay with you
if we start the match?
Huh?
Sure.
Come on, hold it together.
‐Stand up.
‐Vanguard.
Barcgal.
Lozenge Magus.
♪
Since I'm going first,
I draw and ride
Weather Girl, Milk.
♪
Lozenge moves to
the rear guard.
I end my turn.
All right, here it goes.
Ah.
This isn't what I needed.
Without a Grade Two,
my Grade Threes are useless.
What do I do?
Oh, yeah, I know
how to get one!
I ride Wingal.
Now I move Barcgal
to the rear guard.
I activate Barcgal's skill
to call Flogal from my deck.
♪
And, finally, I call Elaine.
My Wingal attacks
your Vanguard.
(grunting)
Checking for a drive trigger.
Ah!
I check for a damage trigger.
With Flogal's support, I'll
have Elaine attack Milk next.
♪
(gasping)
Ah!
Damage check.
I end my turn.
Stand and draw.
I ride the Maiden of Libra.
And then I call the
Oracle Guardian, Gemini.
♪
Maiden of Libra
attacks Elaine.
Gemini support
adds 8,000 power.
♪
Ahh!
Elaine retires
from the battlefield.
I end my turn.
Over already?
What's the big idea?
She's probably got some
great cards in her hand,
so why doesn't she
just play 'em, right?
Keep quiet.
(chuckling)
Weird, she didn't
yell at you.
She barely called
anything onto the field,
and she attacked my rear guard
instead of my Vanguard,
so I didn't receive
any damage, but...
Misaki, what exactly
are you planning?
Hmm.
Just don't think about it.
Keep your mind on the game.
♪
Mm?
Hmm.
Now for my turn.
Where are all my Grade Twos?
It's okay.
I can use Barcgal to
call Llew from the deck,
then I'll use Llew's skill
to bring out Blaster Blade.
Oh, no, I don't
have any damage
to pay for
Llew's counterblast.
Did she just...
Maiden of Libra
attacks Elaine.
(gasping)
Ahh!
Elaine retires
from the battlefield.
She knew what I
was going to do?
The stunned look on your face
says you were planning to use
Barcgal and Llew's
skills together.
Even without
drawing a Grade Two,
you can use that combo to call
Blaster Blade from the deck,
just like you did in
your match against Gouki.
Oh, that's right.
Using Barcgal's skill,
I'll search my deck
for Future Knight, Llew.
And now I activate
Llew's counterblast.
Stand up, my avatar!
Superior ride, Blaster Blade!
Nothing that just happened
makes any sense to me.
See, even though it's
early in the game,
Misaki was able to
predict Aichi's next move.
How'd she do that?
Obviously, she's
reading his mind.
No way, if she
could read minds,
then she must know that I'm
secretly terrible at Vanguard.
Everybody knows that.
She's not a mind reader, guys.
She's, well, uh...
Ah, I get it.
You've got a
really good memory.
Huh?
That must be it, I mean, you
remembered the combo I used
at regionals, and you only
saw it in that final match.
Yeah, she's clever,
that's for sure.
Memory.
I've got one of those things.
Wow, congratulations.
Oh, yeah, you were able
to memorize the cards
from Ren's deck, too.
That's amazing, Misaki!
Hardly.
It's not what you think.
I'm not trying to
remember all these things.
So, it just happens?
That's even more impressive.
Awesome!
Stop interrupting
the card fight.
Sorry.
Let's see, I call the
Little Sage, Marron.
(whooshing)
With support from
Barcgal, Wingal attacks.
♪
(grunting)
Drive trigger check.
Nice one, another Grade Three.
Actually, right now,
he really needs a Grade Two.
Huh?
(grunting and screaming)
Damage trigger check.
With support from Flogal,
I'll have Marron attack you.
Dream Eater will guard.
♪
It's your turn.
I stand and draw.
♪
I ride CEO Amaterasu.
That's amazing, Misaki!
What's so amazing about it?
I activate Amaterasu's skill.
Soul Charge.
I'm gonna send this card
to the bottom of my deck.
Hmm.
Calling Silent Tom
and Oracle Guardian
Wiseman to battle.
♪
Wiseman attacks.
Ah!
♪
Next, Amaterasu will attack
with support from Gemini.
♪
(growling)
Checking for two
drive triggers.
First check.
Second.
Critical trigger.
That's 5,000 power
to my Silent Tom,
and two damage to you.
♪
(grunting and screaming)
(gasping)
And, finally, I attack
with Silent Tom.
(giggling)
(grunting)
That's four damage.
The mind reader
is kicking his butt.
Well, at least he can afford
to pay for a counterblast.
Huh?
Misaki.
Now, let's see what I can do.
With Barcgal's skill...
I search my deck for
Future Knight Llew.
You know what,
it wasn't too long ago
that you and I played each
other for the first time.
That was your
first card fight,
and, yet, you knew
all your cards so well.
You played like a seasoned
veteran even back then.
And if I recall, you
beat me really badly.
(chuckling)
Hurry up and go.
Sure.
Misaki can see
right through me.
But there must be a way for
me to turn this game around.
I'm activating
Llew's counterblast.
I pay the cost of one
and move Llew, Barcgal,
and Flogal to the soul.
♪
I superior ride
Blaster Blade!
(howling)
♪
Using Blaster Blade's
counterblast...
(clanging)
...I force Silent
Tom to retire.
♪
Ah!
Moving Marron to the back.
And, now, I call
Knight of Rose, Morgana,
and the Bringer of
Good Luck, Epona.
Blaster Blade
attacks your Vanguard
with support from Epona.
(grunting)
♪
I check for a drive trigger.
(shouting)
Damage trigger check.
I attack with Morgana,
supported by Marron.
♪
I guard with Nike.
Hmm, that's the
end of my turn.
Looks like they're finally
tied for damage, only‐‐
He doesn't have
a Grade Three.
Hey!
Actually, this time,
you've got a point.
He was late playing a Grade
Two, and it's hurting him.
I stand and draw.
♪
That's Dream Eater.
Its power and shield
are both 5,000.
I got it right.
(chuckles)
♪
Amaterasu's skill,
Soul Charge.
Checking the top card,
putting it on the bottom.
I call Luck Bird.
And pay two for
its Soul Blast.
I draw one card.
♪
I call Wiseman.
Luck Bird supports
Wiseman's attack.
♪
Guarding that with Llew.
‐You know...
‐Huh?
Just think of it.
If she had more
experience playing Vanguard
with that memory of hers,
why, she'd probably be better
than all of us combined.
Yeah.
That's for sure.
Why didn't she start sooner?
When we get back, I'll
teach you how to play.
Would you like that, sweetie?
Yeah!
Take care of the store, okay?
Don't worry, Mom, I'll
keep it safe for you.
Take care of Uncle Shin too.
Bye, sweetheart, love you!
♪
I'm gonna miss you guys!
How cool.
I can only imagine how
much easier life must be
with a memory like yours.
Yeah, Misaki, seriously.
Why didn't you tell us
you had this hidden power?
I think I know how we
can win at nationals.
See, all we have to do
is turn Misaki's memory
into a weapon for Team Q4.
(groaning)
Huh?
Are you okay?
Sometimes I wish I didn't
have any memories at all.
Amaterasu attacks Blaster
Blade with Gemini's support.
Oh, oh, that's great.
You made me drop the deck
that Dad built for me.
‐Well?
‐Meow.
Why are Mom and Dad so late?
I hope they didn't forget
they promised to teach me
how to card fight today.
(sighing)
Misaki, come quickly!
There's been an accident,
and your parents are‐‐
Huh?
♪
Checking for drive triggers.
First check.
Do you know what happened?
(indistinct chattering)
♪
Mommy, Daddy?
They can't be.
(crying)
♪
Second check.
A critical trigger increases
Amaterasu's power by 5,000
and plus‐one damage.
(grunting)
♪
(groaning)
(panting)
Whoa, she beat you good.
Are you all right?
Uncle Shin, are you
sure about this?
Your mom and dad
loved this store,
and I'm gonna make sure
nothing bad ever
happens to it.
You'll help me out,
won't you, Misaki?
No thanks.
Wh‐‐oh.
I don't even
understand the game.
The two of them loved
card fighting so much,
they always said they
would teach me someday,
but they never
got the chance to.
I miss them both
so much it hurts.
Why did this have
to happen to me?
Why did my parents
leave me alone?
Misaki.
I don't want anything
to do with that game.
(crying)
♪
She took you out.
I bet that great memory
had something to do with it.
Amazing.
This is perfect!
We're so lucky to have Misaki
on our team for nationals.
She can analyze our opponents
and help us form strategies.
She's the trump card we've
always needed, right, guys?
Misaki?
I can't.
Huh?
What are you saying?
I'm quitting the team.
You'll have to go to
nationals without me.
(meowing)
What's up with her?
Now hold on!
That was strange.
For sure.
Why did Misaki get so
upset all of a sudden?
I‐‐I don't know.
Hmm.
♪
Misaki.
Hey, Shin,
what happened to Misaki?
Did I do something wrong?
No, you and Kamui
didn't do anything wrong.
Don't worry.
But she seemed so sad.
And she's quitting the team!
It'll be all right.
She just has some
pent‐up emotions
that she needs to deal with
before we head to nationals.
What, I don't know anything
about girls' feelings.
Next time,
"Beyond the Memories."
I'm trying to figure out
a way to help Misaki,
but I just can't do it!