♪
The action here at the
Vanguard Championships
has been fierce
up to this point,
and I'm sure you're
ready to see more,
but you'll have to wait.
When we come back,
it's the thrilling conclusion
to our elimination matches.
Isn't that right, Dr. O?
Dr. O?
Oh, I thought we were
gonna have lunch together.
Looks like the only team
in our block with two wins
is Asteroid.
We're tied with Jurassic
Army for second place
with one win each,
so we have no choice
but to win our next match‐up.
Hm.
♪
We gotta do it so
Kamui can rejoin the team
when we compete in
the finals next week.
What a bro.
Wait a second, do
you guys already know
which team you're
gonna be up against
in the final round?
Mm, we're playing Team Asteroid.
They were last year's
Vanguard champions.
You‐‐uh...
Does Q4 even stand a chance?
Pretty hard to say
at this point.
(all sigh)
You know, maybe we do.
The power of positive thinking!
Only natural from
my number one student.
(chuckling)
How you feelin' about this?
I'll get the first win,
but after that...
(chuckling)
‐(all gasp)
‐You're hilarious.
Seriously.
If you think you can beat us,
you must be dreaming.
Team Asteroid!
♪
So let me get this straight.
It's your first time
at nationals,
and you honestly think
you can beat the likes of us?
This is some sort
of joke, right?
Now, hold on.
We won't know until we play.
We're gonna crush you.
(exclaims)
Cool it, Morikawa.
Looks like you guys are having
a loser convention over here.
This kid's worse than Kamui!
(growls)
Hey, where's your leader?
It's just like
I told you before.
He has no interest in playing
these elimination rounds.
For a player as skilled as Ren,
anything before the finals
is simply a waste of his talent.
The three of us
can win without him.
You know, this is the second
time you've asked us about Ren.
What's wrong, do you miss
your old teammate that badly?
(gasping)
(slurps)
Kai, is that really true?
Ren, Ren, Ren, Ren.
What's so great
about him, anyway?
Kyou, watch what
you say, all right?
Ren is our leader, after all.
Butt out, Asaka, I'll
say whatever I want.
You think Ren's the
only one on our team
that can take you down?
Then I'll fight you
in the next round
and prove you wrong.
♪
I've heard it.
Ren thinks that
you're his equal
when it comes to card fighting.
All I have to do
is defeat you
and I'll prove that
I'm stronger than Ren is.
Then I'll be the leader
of Team Asteroid.
Quiet‐‐that big mouth of yours
is gonna get you into trouble.
Why, it only makes sense
that the best player
should be the leader.
‐Best player?
‐That's enough.
Hmph!
Huh!
Team Q4 doesn't stand much
of a chance against us.
We'll prove it
on the battlefield.
Let's go.
(taunting)
Morikawa!
So Kai used to play
on Ren's team?
Uh‐huh.
Hey!
Well, guys, it's
obviously something
he doesn't really
wanna talk about.
Let's just leave him be for now.
‐Aichi!
‐Huh?
Emi!
She's here!
Mom and I made a special
lunch for you today,
but I guess you ate already.
Yeah, sorry 'bout that.
It's okay.
Save it for a victory feast
after Q4 wins their last match.
Great idea.
Looks like Kamui misses out.
That fine sandwich I had
last time was awesome.
Ahh, the lunch that love made!
Hello, my darling!
Oh‐‐Nagisa, Gouki.
Hey!
We came all this way
to cheer you on.
Seems you're still
hangin' in there.
Yeah, we are.
Thanks so much, you guys.
Huh, where's Kamui?
I made him something
special for his lunch.
Uh, actually, nobody's
seen him since this morning.
He ran off, yo.
(Nagisa wails)
Kamui, where are you?
Well, this is just the worst.
I have to miss out
on another one
of Emi's lunches!
Come here, my love!
(sighs)
Kai.
♪
Ren.
Ren, we weren't
expecting to see you
until after the
elimination rounds were over.
Hmph.
How are things going?
We won our first two matches.
There's only one left.
Anything else?
Well...the team
we're up against next‐‐
Will be easily beaten.
We appreciate your concern.
Hm.
♪
Very well.
Tetsu, why didn't you
mention anything about Kai?
Hm.
The silent treatment?
Fine, be that way.
Welcome back from the break.
At the commentator's desk,
as always, I'm MC Mya.
I'm Dr. O, prescribing
Vanguard knowledge.
Elimination round, Block A,
Team Asteroid versus Team Q4.
So what can we expect
from these guys?
Asteroid are the
returning champions,
and so far in this tournament,
they've won all their match‐ups
without losing a single game.
The rookie team Q4 really has
their work cut out for them
in this pairing.
♪
We have to win.
Hm.
Fear not, you guys!
My cheering will
lead Q4 to victory.
If only that were true.
I think his cheering
leads to hearing loss.
Hm.
We're my Kamui hiding?
For the last time,
we don't know.
Stop asking, yo!
The first match,
Kyou Yahagi of Asteroid
versus Q4's Toshiki Kai!
Kai!
Well, well.
He decided to come back.
Huh, Tetsu.
You hid him from me.
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep them from
seeing each other again.
Ren's hatred for Kai has
turned into an obsession
since they parted.
Hmph.
After I've beaten
the pants off of you,
it'll prove once and for all
that Crusher Kyou is
the strongest member
of Team Asteroid.
So he is here.
♪
Hey, eyes this way.
I'm the one you're fighting.
Judge, let's start this already.
Begin the match!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
♪
I ride Embodiment
of Armor, Bahr!
(roar)
I move Conroe back.
Punk's using
a Spike Brothers deck.
Isn't the the clan your
Juggernaut Maximum comes from?
Yeah, dog, I think it is!
Shouldn't you know that already?
The great Kyou is
riding Wonder Boy!
(exclaims)
Hey now, Kamui's the
only great one here.
♪
Take this!
(explosion)
♪
The Dragon Knight Nehalem, ride!
I move Conroe to the front,
then I call Demonic
Dragon Mage Kimnara
and Blazing Core Dragon.
I attack with
Blazing Core Dragon!
♪
Next, I swing in with Nehalem.
(yelling)
Lastly, with Kimnara's support,
Conroe's comin' at ya.
The Spike Brothers
Assault Squad
will guard that attack.
♪
I end my turn.
The great Kyou rides
Treasured, Black Panther.
(whimpers)
I call Highspeed Brakki
and Devil Summoner.
Activating the Summoner's skill,
I flip over the top
card of my deck
to check and see if
it's a Grade 1 or 2
Spike Brothers Unit.
And if it is, I send it
straight into battle.
Assault Squad, superior call!
That's gonna be trouble, huh?
Superior call is
a superior pain, yo.
I attack with Brakki,
supported by the Spike
Brothers Assault Squad.
(yelling)
Next up, Panther attacks!
Supported by the Mecha Trainer,
Devil Summoner attacks!
(growl)
Tahr will guard that.
♪
Hm, then I end my turn.
It's a close game so far.
‐Wouldn't you say?
‐For sure.
But why do I feel so nervous?
(crowd noise)
Imagine it.
This battle's about to get
a whole lot scarier.
Now ride, the Vanguard!
♪
Flames of destruction
reducing this world to ashes!
Dragonic Overlord!
(roaring)
(gasping)
(growl)
I call Dual Axe Archdragon.
Activating Overlord's
counterblast.
♪
Once he pulls that off,
the game's pretty much over.
Is it just a power increase?
Not quite.
He has to give up
the twin drive ability.
But when an attack
destroys a rear guard unit,
Overlord stands.
This match is in the bag.
Ah!
With support from Bahr,
Dragonic Overlord attacks.
♪
Now, burn in eternal flame!
(flames roar)
I guard with Silence Joker,
Cheer Girl Tiara,
and Dudley Dan.
He's guarding the attack
with three units!
Oh man, even if Kai
gets a critical trigger,
it won't be enough.
Checking the drive trigger...
critical trigger.
Using it on my Overlord
would be a waste.
(chuckling)
Giving all effects
to the Archdragon!
♪
That's awful.
Dragonic Overlord
just got shut down.
(roaring)
♪
Ha‐ha, looks like I just
spoiled all your fun.
Your little tricks
aren't gonna work
on the great Kyou.
You wasted three damage
on that counterblast
and it failed miserably.
♪
Is he actually gonna lose?
If Kyou hadn't stopped that,
Kai would have wiped out
his rear guard units
before attacking the Vanguard,
not to mention the
three drive triggers
he would have drawn.
He had to sacrifice
a lot of his hand,
but he made the right move.
Now, come and get me.
Blazing Core
attacks your Brakki.
Summoner intercepts.
(roars)
♪
He's protecting the rear guard?
He was making sure
the stronger units
stayed on the field.
Supported by Kimnara,
Archdragon attacks.
(roaring)
(scream)
Damage trigger check.
It's a draw trigger.
It's time for you
to feel the power
of the Kyou Crush Rush!
‐Crush Rush?
‐Cool name.
Kai, be careful,
this looks bad!
(laughing)
Good luck stopping
these attacks.
Flying my way to victory,
the great Kyou rides the
winged terror, Skydiver!
♪
Mecha Trainer's counterblast.
I'm searching my deck
for a Grade 1
Spike Brothers Unit
and adding it to my hand.
Now I call Dudley Dan.
This strategy
doesn't seem so bad.
Skydiver attacks with
support from Dudley Dan.
♪
Next, I activate
Dan's counterblast.
By placing a Spike
Brothers card in the soul,
I can superior call
a different one
from my deck.
♪
Another unit?
How many superior
calls can he make?
This is the Spike Brothers
plan at its best.
Impressive!
It's just like watching
an American football game.
Players, or in this
case, the units,
are being called out
onto the field as needed,
allowing Kyou to make
devastating plays
attacking wave after wave.
Checking for a drive trigger.
First card.
Second card.
Another draw trigger.
I give the power boost
to the Skydiver,
who hasn't attacked yet,
and then I draw.
(groan)
Supported by the Assault
Squad, Brakki attacks.
I guard with Blue Ray Dracokid.
I attack with Skydiver.
This powered‐up assault
is sure to break
through your defenses.
(shout)
♪
He survived.
I hope you don't
think my turn's over.
Activating Skydiver's
battle skill.
After dealing damage
to an opponent,
I can send the attacking
unit into the soul.
Then I can take
a Spike Brothers unit
from my hand and
superior call it.
This guy!
♪
And just like that,
I get to attack you again.
(laughing)
Witness the power
of the great Kyou
and his unstoppable
Spike Brothers.
All right, Skydiver.
Finish this guy!
Tahr will guard that.
I end my turn.
This is crazy!
Kai somehow managed
to avoid the Crush Rush.
He needs to finish
this kid off now.
Take a look at
Kai's hand‐‐no cards.
I stand and draw.
Blazing Core Dragon
attacks Brakki.
(yells)
This is intense.
It's the late stages
of the match,
but he can't attack
the Vanguard
because he lacks the power.
Bahr supports
my Dragonic Overlord.
Attack!
(flames sizzle)
Cheer Girl Marilyn will guard.
By sending one
Spike Brothers card
from my hand to the drop zone,
I can defend completely.
I'm checking the drive trigger.
Heal trigger,
giving 5,000 power
to Archdragon.
I recover one damage.
Supported by Kimnara,
Archdragon attacks!
(shimmering chimes)
(shout)
Checking for a damage trigger.
That's all you got?
It's the final turn!
♪
(Kyou chuckles)
That's what you
and Ren like to say,
if I'm not mistaken.
Here goes.
With a boost from Dudley Dan,
I have Skydiver attack.
Counterblast activated.
Out of my deck,
I superior call
Juggernaut Maximum!
(roars)
Aww, this game is
as good as over.
Can he finish him here?
Thinking you've won
against Kai is foolish.
♪
Dragon Monk Gengo will guard!
Drive trigger check.
Critical trigger.
I give all the effects
to Juggernaut.
Here he comes.
With support from
the Assault Squad,
Juggernaut Maximum attacks.
♪
Activating
Juggernaut Soul Blast.
By dropping one card
from the soul,
I can increase his
power by another 5,000.
I guard with Tahr.
In addition, I intercept
with Blazing Core Dragon.
♪
He just doesn't know
when to give up.
Juggernaut goes
back into the deck
and I attack you with Skydiver.
If he can survive to
the end of this turn‐‐
Then the game is his.
♪
I don't guard.
Huh?
Why?
If Skydiver's attack
goes through, he's gonna‐‐
I think Kai's figured
out how to beat him.
(grunt)
Activating Skydiver's
battle skill.
Moving Skydiver to the soul.
And then I‐‐
Black Panther isn't strong
enough to damage him.
I superior call.
Devil Summoner.
It all comes down
to the top card.
I needed that!
Superior call Brakki,
and he attacks!
(grunts)
Brakki Soul Blast.
When he attacks, if I send
one of the cards in my soul
to the drop zone, he gets
an extra 5,000 points.
Iron Tail Dragon will
guard against that.
(grimaces)
Sending Brakki back to my deck.
I end my turn.
‐Asaka, watch closely.
‐Huh?
Final turn.
♪
Why do you think
I allowed myself
to be hit by your Skydiver?
What do you‐‐
wait...are there three cards
face‐up in your damage zone?
(exclaims)
♪
Heal trigger.
I recover one damage.
I don't guard.
(grunt)
♪
After getting that heal trigger,
he let my attack
through on purpose
so that he'd have
three damage to spend.
I'm activating Dragonic
Overlord's counterblast
for a second time.
With support from Bahr,
Overlord attacks
your Devil Summoner.
Drive check: Eternal Flame!
(flames roar)
(yelling)
After destroying
a rear guard unit,
my Overlord stands in
preparation for the next attack.
♪
This...this can't be.
I'm going to lose?
Dragonic Overlord's
comin' at your Vanguard.
(exclaims)
Sonic Breaker and Black Panther
will guard against that attack.
Drive trigger check.
Supported by Kimnara,
Archdragon attacks.
If my opponent has less
than three rear guard units
when Archdragon attacks,
it receives an
additional 3,000 power.
I‐‐I can't stop this one!
♪
Hm.
(roaring)
♪
(grimaces)
I lost!
The winner of the first match,
Toshiki Kai of Team Q4!
(whimpering)
How could this happen?
Team Q4 with an
impressive upset.
Team Asteroid has finally
suffered their first loss
of this year's
national tournament.
♪
It's no surprise.
Kyou.
Huh?
(exclaims)
No, I can't‐‐I...
I won't‐‐no!
(Kyou wailing)
And now, let's move on
to the second match‐up.
Representing Team Asteroid,
it's Asaka Narumi.
And from Team Q4,
Misaki Tokura.
(crowd cheers)
‐Nice fight.
‐Yeah.
Hm.
An impressive win.
That was the best, Kai.
You should concentrate
on the next battle.
Okay, you can do this.
Hm.
Mm.
That win doesn't mean much.
I'm pretty sure the
other two are better
than the guy I just defeated.
(sobbing)
The second match,
Asaka Narumi versus
Misaki Tokura!
Listen up.
There's no way you'll
be able to beat me,
not with that deck you're using.
(gasps)
(sighs)
♪
Hm.
All right, Kai did it!
Looks like your
strategy is working out.
Yeah‐‐now we have to get
the second win, Misaki.
Hm.
Misaki Tokura,
you'll never beat me.
My teammates call me
The Assassin.
Team Asteroid.
I wonder how Asaka fights.
I'll be two steps
ahead of you,
and I'll win no matter what.