I want you to train me to
be a better card fighter,
'cause I know I can
get to the next level.
I want you to train me too.
I won't cause you
guys any trouble.
I'm gonna help Q4 win
the nationals next time.
‐Count me in too.
‐Huh?
I still don't know
enough about the game.
Putting a deck together,
making the most of the units,
staying ahead of my opponent.
Well, it looks like my
little four‐leaf clover
is growing stronger.
I've got just the
thing for you, boom!
Team Q4's Card Fighting
Summer Bootcamp!
♪
‐Hey guys!
‐Oh, hi.
Hey, you're sure here
bright and early.
I hope you don't
mind hanging out,
'cause we're not scheduled
to leave for a while.
I know, but I was tired
of waiting at home.
I mean, I hardly got
any sleep last night.
This is gonna help us
beat that jerk, Ren!
Uh, I'm glad you're excited
for the weekend, Kamui,
but I think you've
misunderstood the purpose
of this camp just a little bit.
We're trying to improve our
skills, not training to beat a‐‐
I'll get you, Ren!
You'll pay for trash talking all
the other teams at nationals!
(chuckling and screaming)
Two days of this?
(meowing)
♪
‐Good morning, everybody.
‐Oh hi, Aichi.
Looks like you're
the second one here.
♪
Good morning, everyone.
Wow, Emi's here.
‐Are you coming with us?
‐Yeah!
Aichi's gonna be a total mess
if I don't go along with him.
I told you I'll
be fine on my own.
Who do you think you're kidding?
If I'm not there to wake
you up, you'll sleep through
the whole camp
and learn nothing.
Emi, come on!
Well, I'm not
gonna take the risk.
(laughing)
Maybe if I sleep in
she'll wake me up too!
Kamui, it's morning, darling.
‐Wakey‐wakey.
‐Let me sleep.
Aw, get up, sleepyhead, you
don't wanna miss your breakfast.
(giggling)
♪
I envy your life
now more than ever!
Sorry, what are you saying?
Uh, nothing.
I assume you checked with
your mom to make sure
‐this was all okay?
‐Yup.
Well, it sounds like
you're coming then.
Hope you're ready
for a fun weekend.
You betcha!
A whole weekend with Emi?
Picture it.
(laughing)
‐I'm gonna get you!
‐Not if I run faster!
Oh, Emi!
I could chase you forever.
(giggling)
Man of the hour has arrived.
‐Huh?
(chuckling)
Why are you guys here,
the store's closed.
We're going to
the training camp.
You think you're
coming along with us?
Obviously, after all, you're
looking at Card Capital's
strongest fighter,
the amazing Morikawa.
The trip wouldn't be
the same without me.
Yeah, no lie there, it
would actually be restful.
Oh yeah, very funny, Misaki,
look, we play at the shop
and we wanna get better
at Vanguard too.
You know what,
that's exactly right.
This camp will be fun, we're
all gonna work together
to improve our card
fighting skills.
So the more the merrier.
‐Yes!
‐Glad to be of help.
‐I'll train everyone.
‐Something wrong?
‐Tell me.
‐No, it's okay.
You're wondering about
Kai, aren't you?
Uh, yeah.
You shouldn't waste your time
thinking about that guy, bro.
Yeah, he doesn't even like
hanging out with the rest of us.
It's like they say, the
lone wolf rides alone.
‐I know.
‐Well actually, you guys,
Miwa should be bringing
Kai over any minute now.
‐You're joking.
‐No.
If you wanna catch a fish,
just use the right bait.
Bait?
Hey, what's up?
‐Look!
‐Hey, hands off.
You're coming?
Oh look, the lone wolf.
You better not have
been lying to me, Miwa.
Well, just wait and see.
All righty‐roo, everyone's here.
Uh, one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
There's eight of us going?
Don't forget to count yourself.
Well, I meant to
do it like that.
There's no way that nine of us
are gonna fit into the manager's
beat up old van, so
what're we supposed to do?
I've got bad news.
Are you saying I
have to stay behind?
I won't stand for this!
Wait for me, ocean!
You don't need to worry.
See, I thought ahead
and booked a bigger van.
‐That was close.
‐Hm.
Wait, you knew there
was enough room?
Yeah‐huh.
She was totally
messing with his head.
‐Yeah.
‐Summer camp sure is fun.
Everyone's so excited right now.
I mean, even Misaki's
in a better mood.
♪
I don't know.
Listen up, you guys!
‐Get your seatbelts fastened!
‐We're waiting for you.
Then say it with me!
‐To the beach!
‐Be quiet.
♪
The sea!
The mountains!
Vacation!
We're here to train.
♪
Smell that fresh air.
There's nowhere else
I'd rather be right now.
♪
Her hair's dancing.
Well, Kai, this kinda thing
is nice once in a while.
Hmm.
Misaki, Aichi, last one
in is a Grade 0!
‐Hold it, Morikawa!
‐Thanks for reminding me.
Gotta do stretches
before I can swim.
‐And a one, and a two‐‐
‐Oh, brother.
We're staying at that
cottage on the hill.
I need some volunteers to
carry the luggage up there.
Oh, man, can't it
wait until later?
No chance, it's not fun
but we have to get it done.
It's just like school projects,
or maybe I could unload
the van and you guys could
do your math homework.
This is turning into
a bummer vacation.
I wouldn't mind
getting ahead on some.
No thanks.
Well, he sure knows
how to motivate people.
Chop, chop, let's get to it.
Ugh, no way!
Where did all this
stuff come from?
Must be a big job, you
guys want some help?
Yeah, that'd be great.
I get the feeling that
I've seen you three before.
Ah!
It's Team Caesar!
What're these guys
doing here, Manager?
Actually, they were
the ones that invited us
up to this training camp.
We made a point of watching
you play at the tournament.
We were pretty impressed
with what we saw.
Even though you weren't
able to make it past
the elimination round you were
the only team other than us
that managed to steal a win
away from Team Asteroid.
We thought you showed
a lot of raw talent.
To be honest, we wanted
this training camp to be
a celebration of us becoming
the national champions again.
Unfortunately though, it
didn't turn out that way.
Let's train together,
and next time
we go to the
national tournament,
Team Asteroid won't
know what hit 'em.
It's a dream come true.
Count me in, let's
kick some butt!
What do you think?
Instead of learning boring
old Vanguard tips from me,
you'll have a chance
to play against some
of the best players in the
country, and I can't think
of a better way to improve
your card fighting skills.
‐Sounds good!
‐You act like such a goof.
I never thought you'd be capable
of something like this, Shin.
‐Who knew?
‐Well, thanks for the support,
and call me Manager, all right?
♪
I'm glad I finally get
the chance to play you.
‐Likewise, Kai.
‐Hold on.
It sounds like you already
knew that these guys
were gonna be here today.
Yeah, they're the whole
reason I came along.
I see, so they're the bait
the manager was talking about.
Right, since Kai's always
looking for stronger opponents
to fight, I told him if
he came along with us
that he'd be able to battle
against Team Caesar.
That is good bait.
‐Are you ready?
‐Yeah, you bet.
Toshiki Kai versus
Kenji Mitsusada.
This fight is gonna be crazy!
It's a matchup between
players that are both worthy
of being the national champion.
And we all get to watch.
We've already found the
perfect spot for a card fight.
Come on, I'll show
you where it is.
♪
‐Hm.
Hm.
‐We should go watch it too, Emi.
‐Sure.
Hey, you guys,
what about swimming?
Seriously.
Argh, this is totally bogus!
Please wait for me, ocean!
(panting)
Looks like everyone
forgot about the luggage.
Uh, guys, anyone, help?
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Stand up, the Vanguard!
You know, we could
stay here and watch.
‐Then again‐‐
‐Huh?
♪
Let's have our own battle.
Yeah, sure thing.
‐Stand up, my Vanguard!
♪
‐You beat me.
‐Oh, man.
I had high hopes, but I
didn't think Kai would beat
‐the leader of Team Caesar.
‐You can't underestimate him.
Ha, seems like Team Caesar
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
‐Awkward.
‐Leave it to him to say that.
Thinking back on it, I
probably should've intercepted
on turn six rather than
using a card from my hand.
You knew what I had
because of those triggers.
Yeah, but there weren't a
lot of options left for you.
You needed to keep power
in your frontline.
You know, I'm just thinking
about all the cards
I still had in my deck.
There was a really good chance
I would've drawn a unit
of equal or greater strength
to replace the intercept.
Hm, you were up
against a Kagero deck.
Of course, I hadn't
considered your ability
to remove my rear‐guard
units from play.
Phew.
It's like they're speaking
a whole different language.
Ha, what good is talking?
A real man just
plays Grade 3s.
‐That's how you win.
‐Yeah, sure.
‐Whatever you say.
‐Don't encourage him.
Let's see if Aichi's
got a Grade 3.
Hm, oh.
It's my turn.
I attack Gordon with
Masked Police, Grander.
Activating Grander's skill,
2,000 power is added
to Super Dimensional
Robo, Daiyusha.
Gallatin will guard.
♪
Now my other Grander
attacks Gordon
with a boost from
Karenroid, Daisy.
With Grander's skill,
Daiyusha's power
increases by another 2,000.
♪
I don't guard.
With a boost from Daisy,
Daiyusha takes aim at Gancelot.
Whenever his attack
power is over 14,000,
I can activate his battle skill.
♪
It means on this next
attack he's coming in
with plus one critical.
If I take two more
damage I lose.
With Daisy's boost, the
total attack becomes 22,000.
Gancelot's power is 9,000.
Even if I guard with Epona, that
only brings it up to 19,000.
I needed Gordon
to stop this attack.
I don't guard.
Twin drive, first check.
♪
And second check.
Army Penguin, draw trigger.
The power boost to Daiyusha.
I draw, Gancelot's
in big trouble.
I check for a damage trigger.
One more card.
I was hoping for a heal trigger.
‐Aw, he lost the fight.
‐Hm.
Fun game, feel like
having a rematch?
Okay.
(panting)
Oh brother, how many more times
do I have to climb up that hill?
What, again?
Five losses in a row,
trying to set a record?
‐Sorry.
‐I was watching you play,
and it looks like you're
making all the right moves.
Would it be okay if
I took a quick look
through your deck, Aichi?
Uh, yeah, sure.
How is it?
Actually, it's not bad.
‐But there's‐‐
‐There's what?
Aichi, it's a good deck
and the units are strong,
but I don't see a
winning image anywhere.
What is that?
Think about it, when you're
playing someone with that deck,
do you have a clear image of
how you're going to defeat them?
Um, well, uh,
I never thought about that.
You need to clearly picture
how you're gonna win.
That way you'll know
which cards to play
‐and which ones to guard with.
‐Really?
All right, I'm Katsumi Morikawa,
the strongest card
fighter you've ever met!
So, which one of you
wants to be embarrassed?
I haven't had a chance
to play yet today.
Okay, but don't feel
bad when you lose
to my maximum
strength super deck.
I'll do my best.
A winning image, huh.
♪
Ha, ha, ha!
I guess that's enough
of a beating for one day!
‐You know you lost.
‐Yeah, he beat you
‐13 times in a row.
‐Oh yeah?
We'll see what Mr. Wizard
says about this.
Let's see, "A wizard
doesn't fear losing,
'cause it makes him stronger."
If that's true, then you must
be the strongest person I know.
I know it's here somewhere.
Spells to silence
sassy card shop girls.
Hey everybody, how 'bout
we put the cards away
‐for a little while?
‐Time for the beach?
Nope.
Everyone here is
gonna help to prepare
a special dinner tonight.
We gotta make dinner?
If you work as a team I'm
sure it will be delicious.
I've never cooked
anything before,
but I won't let that stop me!
Can't be worse than
your card fighting.
Come on, everyone,
it's getting late,
and we need to get started if
we're feeding this many people.
♪
‐Ah.
‐Huh, what?
You've gotta be careful when
you're using a knife, Aichi.
Right, I won't let
it happen again.
It just slipped out of my hand.
Peeling potatoes is tricky.
No, it's simple,
you're just clueless
'cause you never help out
in the kitchen, Aichi.
♪
Why does cooking
make me cry so much?
I don't know, but this river
of tears just won't stop!
It's because you're
chopping onions.
Hey, where's Kai hiding?
What do you want?
‐Nothing.
‐Fine, then.
Suit yourself.
I didn't expect him to be
that good with a knife.
I don't think we need
diced onions for the stew.
I'm planning to fry
all of these up
with a special seasoning.
Well, don't mind me then.
♪
So, how long are you gonna
be cooking those onions for?
Till they're ready.
Okay, let's take a look.
(sighing)
(together)
Over the lips and past the gums.
♪
‐Wow, guys, it's delicious!
‐I know.
It's different than the way Mom
would make it, but it's so good.
‐Don't you think, Aichi?
‐Yeah.
It's super tasty,
Emi, I can't believe
how well it all turned out.
Yeah, could use more onions.
‐More!
‐Get it yourself.
‐Mmm.
‐Mmmm.
It's nice that we can all
be together like this,
enjoying a meal
we worked hard on.
We're finished with the dishes.
Good, our card fight
just wrapped up.
He won, of course.
That watermelon for
dessert was great.
All right, let's go
to the beach, guys!
‐You're joking, right?
‐It's a little dark,
‐don't you think?
‐No!
No, no, no, no.
Get a grip, buddy, we
can still swim tomorrow.
Besides, now that
it's nighttime,
there's something
fun we can all do.
(crackling)
(shouting and laughing)
Look, I made Aichi dance!
It's only funny until
somebody loses an eye.
Ah, hey, stop it!
I don't wanna taste
my own medicine!
Huh, no fair,
I wanted to light up
the 100‐shot buster ball!
‐That's it?
It sounded cooler than it was.
(indistinct conversations)
♪
Time for bed.
Yeah.
Aichi, did you remember
to wash your hair?
Yeah, I washed it.
I mean properly.
You don't need to
worry about him, Emi.
He was in there for
like 15 minutes.
With that much time,
he must have washed it.
Okay, good.
Goodnight, Emi.
Aichi, wanna have a
pillow fight before bed?
No way, we're getting
up early tomorrow,
and if you sleep in you
won't have enough time
‐to go swimming, Morikawa.
‐Gotcha!
Hurry up and turn off the light.
But don't make it pitch black,
leave a small light on
so Izaki doesn't get scared.
Bet that loud mouth
talks in his sleep.
(chuckling)
(crickets chirping)
♪
(snoring)
Really, Kai, you
envy my card skills?
♪
I gotta find a winning image.
Don't strain your eyes.
Manager.
I hope you're able
to learn something
from our training trip.
Yeah.
♪
He just needs a push
in the right direction.
♪
But it can wait till tomorrow.
(yawning)
♪
It's great to be
training with everyone.
Yeah, making stew,
lighting fireworks,
having a pillow
fight before bed.
None of that counts as training.
Yeah, I forgot, the
beach, swimming, right?
Next time, Results
of the Training Camp.
Hey, I tried reassembling my
deck around my winning image,
but‐‐huh, Morikawa?
It looks like he
exhausted himself
with overexcitement
and dozed off.
I'm swimming in an
ocean of Grade 3s.