♪
This is the place.
Asteroid.
The next step in becoming
the card fighter I want to be.
♪
Huh?
Excuse me.
You wouldn't happen
to be waiting for anyone.
No, I'm not.
"Waiting For Anyone"
is an awful name.
That's not
quite what I meant.
"Not Quite What I Meant" is an
even worse name for someone.
(sighs)
This one's
a bit strange.
Huh?
Oh, I get it!
You must be a card fighter,
just like me.
Yeah, but I'm
not just like you.
I'm a guy.
I know.
I meant that‐‐
Wow, he must be even
more nervous than I am.
♪
Well, I'm guessing you've been
out here for quite a while now,
so why don't
we head inside?
We can't,
the door's broken.
What?
Normally
I walk up and bwa!
It opens right up for me.
You mean like this?
There it is!
You found the door's
secret hiding spot.
♪
I doubt he'll last
long in this kind of place
with that absent mind of his.
Poor guy.
♪
It's good to see you
this morning, Ren.
Though you
are a bit late.
Sorry, the front door
was playing tricks again,
but this girl
was nice enough
to show me
the way in.
You're Asaka Narumi,
is that correct?
Huh?
Yeah, but
then who's this guy?
♪
But then who's this guy?
This guy is
Ren Suzugamori.
He is the founding
member of Asteroid.
Our leader.
(gasps)
He's in charge?
♪
Boy, do we have
some fun ahead of us!
Welcome back to
the final round here
at the Vanguard
national championship!
By the sounds of it,
I'd say this crowd
is still recovering
from that last match
where Tetsu Shinjou
of Team Asteroid
managed to steal
the first game
out from under Team Q4.
I, for one, was overwhelmed
by the intensity!
Let's get to
the second match
featuring Asaka Narumi
and Misaki Tokura.
Dr. O, you were saying
that this is a rematch
from the last time
these teams played.
Yes, Asaka will be looking for
her second straight victory,
but perhaps Misaki
will have what it takes
to put a stop
to those plans.
♪
So, we meet again.
Uh‐huh.
♪
In our first fight,
she was able to read my moves
and get in the
way of my strategy.
Sure, I made
some bad plays,
and my deck was far
from perfect, but really,
what it came down to was a
lack of experience on my part.
♪
This time
it's different.
I've trained
alongside Team Caesar
and rebuilt my deck
from the ground up.
I've fought my
way into the finals.
You okay?
You're giving me
a creepy look.
It's gonna feel
great when I beat you.
That so?
You're borderline delusional.
The second match of
the tournament finals!
Let's begin!
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
♪
Godhawk Ichibiyoshi.
Hades Ringmaster.
♪
Hmm!
One more loss and her team
goes home empty‐handed.
I can see the
desperation in her eyes.
I won't lose.
Not to her.
Not to anyone.
♪
(machinery whirring)
Hope you don't mind
showing us what you can do,
cause it's mandatory.
Sure, that's fine.
Who am I playing?
It's not you?
Hardly.
You're not the only fighter
we've accepted today.
Two new recruits
seems like a fair match.
As if!
He's just a kid.
Hold on, I've seen
that look before.
You think
I'm a joke, right?
Huh? I didn't say that!
Don't give me any attitude if
you know what's good for ya!
Memorize the
name Kyou Yahagi,
because I'm gonna be
the best in the world.
Do they honestly expect me
to card fight against a girl?
I'm gonna make
you regret those words!
Obviously, they saw
something in each of us,
but I'll let the
cards settle this.
Is that so?
You'll be singing
a different tune
when I'm done.
We'll see about that.
♪
‐Now stand up, my vanguard!
I don't get it.
Why bother recruiting a
fighter at such a low level?
Sorry, what was that?
I'm talking
about Asaka Narumi.
She's nowhere near ready.
Yeah, but there's something
interesting about her.
I can see it in her eyes.
♪
And she's
just as ferocious
as the day
we met each other.
♪
(giggling)
Let's go.
I draw.
I'm activating Godhawk
Ichibiyoshi's ability.
Checking the
top five cards.
♪
Revealing Goddess
of the Crescent Moon
for a superior ride!
♪
Look at that!
She managed to pull Tsukuyomi
off the top this time!
Great way to
start this match.
I end my turn.
Crescent to half and then
the full moon comes out.
You'd think she'd have learned
some better tricks by now.
This game is gonna
end like last time.
I won't lose
in front of Ren.
It happened once,
but never again!
♪
Juggernaut Maximum attacks,
but first,
I'll use his soul blast.
That's 5,000 power,
not to mention the
boost from Wonder Boy,
making it a
total of 24,000.
(gasps)
♪
(screams)
They made a mistake
bringing you here.
What kind of card fighter
can't even beat
a little kid, huh?
Oh, man.
They must have thought
you were someone else
when they asked
you to come try out.
How else can you explain
why someone as weak
as you made it this far?
(growls)
(mocking laugh)
A Pale Moon deck!
Quite the performance.
(clapping)
It's got so many tricks.
Watching you play, it reminds
me of going to the circus.
I swear, they should call
it the Pale Moon Circus.
If it's okay, I'd
like to take a look
through those
cards of yours.
Are you sure?
Yeah, of course,
I'm sure.
Stop being so
serious all the time.
Wow!
Would you get
a load of these?
Um, excuse me, but
was I not the winner?
Indeed.
I noticed you
won the game,
but that match
wasn't about winning.
Your deck is like
a well‐oiled machine.
All of the pieces
are in the right places,
and as such,
I find it very boring.
You think so?
What's the deal, Ren?
You'll show
Ren some respect.
That is if you're smart.
Fine.
Here, you can
have it back.
Thank you.
Ren, I‐‐
(gasps)
I think the Pale Moon
is really interesting,
but as it stands,
this circus is still
in need of a main event.
What?
Your deck needs
some adjustments
and you'll have to fix it
if you want to
continue playing here.
I'll fix it!
Tell me how.
Unfortunately, only you
can answer that question.
♪
Listen to me.
You could become an
amazing card fighter.
If you do, you'll earn
a spot on Team Asteroid.
Team Asteroid?
We're building
an armada of teams,
but Asteroid
is our flagship.
The top four players in the
organization will make the team.
You'll give me
a shot at the top?
If you can prove to us
that you're ready
to play at that level.
Hey!
Did you guys forget
I just beat this girl?
Quiet! Far as
I'm concerned,
winning a single battle
isn't worth anything,
and Ren would agree.
Hmm.
Every person we scout has the
opportunity to play for us.
I won't lose,
so the second
spot on the team
is mine for the taking.
That means two
spots up for grabs.
♪
In order for you
to join Team Asteroid,
you'll have to win all of your
card fights from this point on.
♪
Hmm!
Hmm.
Don't let me down, Kyou.
Oh, I'll make it
onto your team!
No problem!
You as well.
That deck of yours, I can't
wait to see you use it again.
Thanks.
♪
Since that day, I've known
that I'd always have to
fight for his attention,
and that's why...
I can never lose.
♪
It's my pleasure
to welcome you
to tonight's performance
of the Pale Moon Circus.
Draw!
♪
I think you'll find my tricks
to be graceful and ruthless,
but enough talk.
Let's get on
with the show!
I ride Midnight Bunny!
♪
This whole act
is getting tiresome.
♪
I soul charge thanks to the
skill of Hades Ringmaster.
Now, my Bunny wants
to join in the fun.
♪
I don't guard.
Drive check.
(grunts)
♪
Ladies and gentlemen, this
concludes the first act
of today's
thrilling spectacle!
♪
Stand and draw.
Now, with Tsukuyomi's skill,
I check the top five.
♪
Come on!
She had five chances to
find the card she needed
and she mega‐failed.
It's not her fault
the card's not there.
Precisely, which means, some
other evil power is at work.
I remember reading
something about this!
I'm gonna need some garlic
and a three‐legged dog.
(chuckling nervously)
The half moon rises
with Tsukuyomi, ride!
♪
Soul charge.
Battle Maiden Tagitsuhime
to rear guard.
♪
Goddess of the
Half Moon attacks.
I'm not gonna guard.
Checking the
drive trigger.
(grunts)
(yells)
Then I check for
a damage trigger.
Tagitsuhime
attacks next.
(screams)
♪
Looking good!
No way, she's doing it!
Protect the lead, girl!
♪
She probably thinks she
has the upper hand on me.
Enjoy the feeling
while it lasts.
Her fighting style,
that pathetic deck.
This match doesn't befit
someone with my experience.
♪
Since the day I met him,
winning has been the only
thing I've cared about.
I poured myself
into Vanguard
hoping to obtain the
level of power I needed.
With every game I won,
I knew I was a
step closer to him.
♪
Then, at long last...
So, let me get
this straight.
I finally get a
spot on Team Asteroid,
and now I have to
be teammates with you?
Funny, I was just
thinking the same thing.
Let's not forget, Kyou.
I claimed the
third spot on this team
while you are nothing more
than the lowly alternate.
(scoffs)
Enjoy it while it lasts.
Oh, yeah?
You think you're gonna
surpass me, huh?
Of course, I will!
Talented as I am,
one of these days,
I'll be Team Asteroid's
top fighter.
You're crazy!
If you think
you can defeat Ren
then you've
seriously lost it.
You would say that.
I'm gonna dethrone
that space case myself,
and when I do, this
organization will be mine.
Kyou!
Sorry, Asaka.
I forgot how
much you hate it
when people insult your
boyfriend like that.
Personally, I see no
reason to respect a guy
who's stuck chasing after
Toshiki Kai's shadow.
Who is Toshiki Kai?
Sounds to me like you
should do your homework.
Come on, tell me
what you know.
My lips are sealed,
but you're a smart girl.
I'm sure you'll find
a way to figure it out.
(laughing)
♪
(keyboard clacking)
This is him.
The Toshiki Kai.
(gasps)
Huh?
♪
I was just‐‐
Snooping around
where you shouldn't be.
♪
What's going on?
Tetsu, you've got to know
something about him.
If I'm gonna be
on this team,
then I deserve to
understand our enemies, right?
♪
As it stands, Toshiki Kai might
be the only person on Earth
who can defeat
Ren in a card fight.
Impossible.
That's precisely what we
think about those rumors.
We're on the same page.
♪
There's more to this story.
Huh?
It's been a long time, Kai.
♪
So, Kai, I thought
you were avoiding us.
Why hasn't Ren
shown his face yet?
He's not playing in
the preliminary round.
Ren doesn't enjoy
wasting his time.
You should remember
that, at least.
Should I?
The past isn't something
I tend to dwell on.
It's really him!
♪
So he'll be playing
in the final rounds?
Couldn't tell you.
Guess you'll have
to make it that far
if you want
to find out.
I have to be strong.
♪
Ren hates this guy
more than anyone,
and I'll see to it
that he's defeated.
♪
Then I'll finally know that
I'm worthy in Ren's eyes.
This is my chance.
I can't afford to slip.
Even for a second.
Finally!
The curtain can go up
on the second act
of the smashing
Pale Moon Circus!
Draw!
I'll start by riding
Crimson Beast Tamer!
♪
Call Mirror Demon,
Turquoise Beast Tamer,
and Skull Juggler
to rear guard.
Juggler's skill
lets me soul charge.
Then, with his support,
Mirror Demon attacks.
♪
(yells)
Damage trigger check.
It's a critical trigger.
Giving all of the
effects to my vanguard.
♪
Oh!
Turquoise, we should
turn up the heat.
(grunts)
I don't guard.
Now, to check
for a drive trigger.
(grunts)
♪
I'm checking
for a damage trigger.
As the curtain
falls on this act,
the score stands
at three to two.
Our wonderful audience
has a lot to look forward to
as the beginning of Act Three
is just over the horizon.
♪
Watch me.
Your act gets
old pretty fast.
Starting my turn with
Tsukuyomi's skill.
♪
(groans)
Not again.
Ha!
You don't have much
luck with your deck.
You haven't
figured that out yet?
Oh, yeah?
Well, unlike some people,
I don't need luck
to help me win my games.
You're so defensive.
I hate it when people act tough
when they're obviously losing.
Wrong, I am tough.
This is no act.
I believe in my deck
and my skills
to wield it.
Light bursting forth!
Show me the way!
I ride CEO Amaterasu.
♪
Activating her skill.
I get to preview
my top card.
Sending this one
to the bottom.
Calling Oracle Guardian
Red Eye to rear guard.
♪
Attacking Mirror Demon.
What?
That seems like a
waste of an attack.
♪
You want to play
it that way, huh?
My Big League Bear
will guard your attempt.
(roaring)
♪
Using Bear's skill,
I can soul charge two cards,
so thanks a lot.
♪
Tagitsuhime will finish
the job on Mirror Demon.
With six Oracle Think
Tank cards in the soul,
she receives an
additional 3,000 power.
The rear guard again?
What's she doing?
(scoffs)
I'm flattered you'd
waste two attacks
trying to stop my
Deadly Shadow Beasts.
Misaki lost to
that last time.
Oh, that's right!
Now I remember.
♪
Savage creatures lurk within
the darkness that is the soul,
and there's no way
for you to escape them.
Cower before the Pale Moon's
ultimate technique!
The Deadly Shadow Beasts!
Asaka was able to cycle
units out of the soul,
gaining extra attacks.
Misaki needs to prevent
that from happening.
♪
I wonder if you've actually
learned anything about my deck,
or if you're
just so frightened,
you've lost the ability
to think straight.
Option one.
Suit yourself.
The attack goes through.
♪
(screams)
Amaterasu is coming
for your vanguard.
I'm not gonna guard.
♪
Checking the twin drive.
First and second.
How do you like that?
Five thousand power to
my vanguard, and I draw.
(screams)
Damage trigger check.
Huh!
Looks like I'll match
you draw for draw.
Lucky.
♪
I end my turn.
The damage is
tied at three.
She's in a
real nail biter.
You can say that again.
Nice.
This fight is really
starting to get good,
wouldn't you say, Tetsu?
Not quite.
Oh?
The game is looking
fine in terms of damage,
but Asaka won't be able to use
the Deadly Shadow Beasts.
Without access to
her signature move,
her chances
are much lower.
Looks like you may
have to play the third game.
Well, I guess I'd
better go find my deck.
(snickering)
Ren, I can feel
you watching over me.
♪
Sadly, this little show is
approaching its conclusion.
Misaki Tokura,
the Pale Moon Circus
has a grand finale.
It's to die for!
(giggling)
♪
Misaki's match is really
intense, don't you think?
I can't believe my eyes!
It's like she gets
better every turn.
Let's just hope
she can keep it up.
Come on, Misaki!
Oh, amazing!
Did you see her
attack there?
And that card!
It flew my blinds!
She waited so long
for this rematch.
Now all we can do
is watch and hope.
Next time,
"Lord of the Fight".
Time for Q4 to take
charge of this situation.