(shouting)
♪
It's finally time!
The shop tournament is back!
This is gonna be our big chance
to prove that we're the best.
We better practice,
it's in a couple of days.
This time
I promise that I'll‐‐
Get past the
first round?
No, silly, get
Ninja Master M's autograph!
(groans)
My idol, my hero.
♪
Yeah, well,
I shoulda guessed.
Oh, that's different.
It's gonna be
a team battle.
We had to switch formats
because our very own
Quadrifoglio made it
all the way to the Vanguard
Nationals last time around.
Thanks to that, the popularity
of this little tournament
has grown a lot.
Looks like everyone
wants a chance
to fight the reigning
regional champions.
I can't wait.
Team battles?
Then that means the
formation of Team Ninja!
♪
(chuckles)
Actually, the
Ninja Master quit.
But that's impossible!
"The era of the ninja
has come to an end."
Those were
his exact words.
He probably doesn't have any
friends to form a team with.
That's so sad!
I would have been his
friend if he just asked.
Morikawa.
Stop crying, I've
got a surprise for you.
‐Huh?
Misaki, hand me that
bundle under the counter.
It's for Morikawa.
Hmm?
This?
What is it, what is it,
what is it, what is it?
♪
The shop tournament
starts tomorrow.
With your skills, you're not
gonna beat anyone on that team.
Not yet.
I just‐‐
I'm gonna get stronger.
I know I can do it, Kai!
This time I'm gonna win.
To repay my
friends on Team Q4,
and show Kai I was
serious about what I said.
Paladins, lend me
your strength.
♪
Huh?
(roaring)
♪
(shudders)
(sighs)
That was so weird.
♪
I could have sworn
I heard a voice.
(knocking)
What are you
doing up here?
How many times do I have
to call you down for dinner?
I'm sorry, Emi.
I was working on my deck.
There's another
shop tournament tomorrow.
At Card Capital?
Hey, want to come watch?
I think I've got
something else going on.
Do you best though, okay?
Sure!
♪
(crowd chattering)
Alright ladies and gents,
we're full and it's time
to start the tournament!
But first, the group
that took our little shop
to the National tournament.
Team Q4!
Defeating this group will take
every trick that you can muster.
So tell me, my good people,
are you up to the challenge?
(crowd cheers)
Just give up now,
cause Team Q4 is
gonna take you all down!
You tell 'em, Kamui!
Can't wait, yo!
Yippee‐ki‐yay.
We've got the teams
divided into Blocks A and B
with every battle
taking place on one
of our patented Card Capital
standing fight tables.
The winning team
from each Block
will face each other
in the final round.
The winner of that
match is our champion!
Looks like our group
is in Block B.
Just wait and see, Emi!
I'll dedicate all my wins
to your unmatched beauty!
She won't be here today.
(yells)
Are you okay?
How could this be?
Without your sister
here to watch,
how's Kamui supposed
to win all his fights?
Seriously, dude!
Go get her, yo!
We're doomed if
you don't, Aichi.
(chuckles)
No, we're not.
It's not a big deal.
She's still
in my heart!
Stay strong,
my darling!
A talented card
fighter like you
will rise to the challenge
even if I'm not
there to support you
with one of my
delicious lunches!
(giggles)
She totally
believes in me.
Just stand aside,
you guys!
I'll set us on
the path to victory.
That's weird.
Morikawa and the
guys aren't here.
I wonder what
happened to them.
Test, test.
We're just about
ready to start.
Now would be a good time to go
over fight order with your team.
Oh, that's right.
We have to decide
when we're all gonna go.
I'm not playing.
What do you mean?
Win this thing
on your own.
If you can't handle
the competition
at a little shop tournament,
then what hope do you
have at a national level?
Without you?
I'll sit back
and watch you guys.
Kinda rude, but
he's got a point.
(growls)
Oh, yeah, you big jerk?
We're gonna win
without you!
From now on, it's
the three of us.
Let's do our best.
Well, obviously.
Hmm.
Hmm!
(meows)
Oh, that's no fair.
But I've been looking
forward to this!
A moment of silence
for all the card fighters
that couldn't participate.
Now let's get the Card Capital
shop tournament underway!
‐Stand up, my vanguard.
(indistinct whispering)
Stand up, my avatar.
I ride Blaster Blade!
♪
Whoa, he's got
a Blaster Blade.
Oh, man!
♪
Let's go.
Asura Kaiser attacks.
Finishing hold!
♪
(groans)
I lose.
(sighs)
Alright, it looks like
Team Q4 is moving on.
♪
That's another 7,000 power
to CEO Amaterasu.
I attack.
♪
(groans)
Paying the cost to
activate her counter blast.
I search through my deck
for Pongal and Superior Call!
(howling)
I attack you with
Mr. Invincible!
(laughs)
(grunting, laughing)
The winner of
Block B: Team Q4.
We did it!
Don't celebrate
too soon, bro.
We still got
a match to go.
You're right.
We're up against
Team Overthrow?
Hmm?
(snickering)
‐Huh?
Team Q4 will have their work cut
out for them in this last match.
Oh, wow, it's really
him, you guys.
No way!
It's Ninja Master M?
(grunting)
(laughs)
♪
Hold on.
He seems different.
Your eyes are keen.
You're looking at the new
and improved Ninja Master M.
I'm back and I've
brought my friends with me.
I'm a feudal lord.
I'm not sure what I'm
supposed to be dressed as.
That's Morikawa,
Izaki and Miwa, right?
Well, this explains what
was inside that package.
What package?
Yeah, come on, tell us.
This must have
been Shin's idea.
Hmm?
In ancient times,
power and intelligence
were precious commodities.
Only the strong and wise
could rise up
against their oppressors,
ready to overthrow them.
Now, in today's world,
there is a need
for those few
that would fight back
against the status quo.
Standing in defiance of the
reigning champions, Team Q4,
ready to
make history.
The winners of Block A,
say hello to Team Overthrow.
Ha!
This can't be for real.
I should've known you'd
pull a stunt like this.
Come on, this
is gonna be fun.
She's fighting the Loser.
Who's a loser now?
Huh?
An ancient proverb, "Who's a
loser now," said the monkey,
while taunting
the great tiger.
That made no sense.
He has some
serious issues.
As well as
this battle gear,
my predecessor left me his
secret ninja techniques.
You don't stand a
chance against me.
(snickering)
Alright, folks, the first match
of the shop tournament finals.
Team Q4's Misaki Tokura
versus the new Ninja Master M.
Ninja technique: super shuffle
of a thousand blazing cuts.
(shouting)
And we're
ready to play.
Let's imagine
and let's begin.
‐Stand up, my vanguard.
Here I go!
Stealth beast Hagakure!
♪
Godhawk Ichibiyoshi.
Looks like
I'm up first.
Ninja card draw technique.
Oh, yeah, it's
a Grade Three!
Uh, you're not
allowed to say that.
♪
My enthusiasm betrays me.
Q4's time has
come to an end.
Behold, you peasants, the age
of Team Overthrow is upon us!
(groans)
♪
Those stony looks
aren't fooling anyone.
I see you quivering
in your boots,
but if you think I'm
going to show you mercy,
then you've made a mistake
that'll be your undoing.
(snickering)
You're in for
a world of hurt.
This deck is packed with
the strongest Grade Three's
known to man.
In addition, I've tossed
in some special cards
that you've lost to
in previous battles
just to mess
with your heads.
(groans)
You guys are no match
for Team Overthrow
and its amazing captain,
the new Ninja Morikawa M!
Run, you fools!
(laughing)
When will he learn that
too many Grade Three's
are bad for a deck?
Yeah, well, he just
said his real name too.
Nice secret identity, yo.
Now, secret ninja technique.
♪
I can hardly believe that
this is happening to me.
I'm betrayed
by the very deck
I worked so hard to
sculpt with my own hands.
♪
(groans)
It's my turn.
I stand my units and draw.
Hmm.
♪
I'm activating Goddess of the
Half Moon, Tsukiyomi's skill.
I get to look at the
top five cards in my deck
to check and see if the Goddess
of the Full Moon, Tsukuyomi,
is among them
for Superior Ride.
♪
Your techniques
are equal in strength.
Tell me, are
you also a ninja?
♪
(laughing)
You didn't get it!
Man, you must
have rotten luck
if you can't even find the
silly card you're looking for!
Hey, if you're
not careful,
you'll get us kicked
out of the tournament.
♪
I ride.
Gentle light
breaking the darkness.
Your smile brings hope
to the entire world.
Goddess of the
Full Moon, Tsukuyomi.
You sneaky girl!
How dare you hide
that card in your hand!
I call Red Eye.
♪
With a boost from Gemini,
Tsukuyomi‐‐
Hey now, hold on
just a second.
You sure you
want to do that?
I attack.
♪
(screaming)
Twin drive, first check.
Second check.
♪
No fair!
Alright, folks, the
winner of the first match
is Misaki Tokura!
(crowd cheering, applause)
(crying)
I lost because
I turned my back
on the teachings
of Mr. Wizard
by donning this
ninja outfit.
We're supposed to be on the
final round of this tournament.
How'd someone that
bad make it this far?
♪
The other two must be
getting all the wins.
Listen up, guys, we're in
serious trouble right now.
Frankly, it
couldn't be worse.
All they need is one win
to clench the championship.
And who put us
in this situation?
Oh, whatever.
(giggling)
No need to worry.
I thought something
like this might happen,
so I went ahead and
prepared a secret weapon
to give our team
the edge we need.
‐A secret weapon?
Alright, if I could have
everyone's attention?
The second match.
From Team Q4,
it's Kamui Katsuragi.
Yeah!
You're gonna
win no problem.
Right?
Seems you're not
gonna get a chance
to play in
the final, bro.
Cause now it's my
turn to finish them off
and claim the
championship for our team!
This'll be a piece
of cake for you.
No doubt, yo.
(laughing)
I can't wait to tell Emi that
I won the final match for her.
(sighs)
And from Team Overthrow.
Say "Princess Maiden".
Come on, call her
"Princess Maiden".
Okay.
The Princess Maiden!
(snickering)
Huh?
♪
(screaming)
Emi?
I'm not Emi!
I'm the Princess Maiden.
You‐‐you're a princess now?
Well, yeah.
What's wrong with me
having a little fun?
(shuddering)
Are you okay?
Have I lost it or am I
really about to face off
against the girl
of my dreams?
It's working.
I got to say, Miwa,
this is brilliant.
Oh, 'tis true.
All set?
Let's start!
Stand up, vanguard!
Stand‐‐ no wait, vanguard.
Wait‐‐our‐‐what?
♪
(giggles)
Oh, man, this is
actually happening.
Oh, no!
Kamui looks like his brain
is about to break.
Yeah, I guess we're gonna have
to spoon feed him his lunch, yo.
This is not good.
(groans)
Ha!
(shudders)
I attack!
Nice one, Emi.
♪
I've been in love with her
since the day we met.
If I can win this match,
she'll totally want
to be my girlfriend.
(sighs)
‐Um?
‐Yes, dear?
It's your turn now, Kamui.
Right!
Of course it is.
I think Kamui's gone
right off the deep end.
If you don't
smarten up quick,
you're gonna lose, yo!
They're right.
Get it together.
It's the final round,
and we're one win away
from the championship.
(sighs)
Watch me now.
♪
I ride Asura Kaiser, and
then I'll call my Army Guy.
Let's go!
♪
For starters,
I'll counter blast,
and release Jack.
♪
With a boost
from Army Guy,
Jack will attack
your Top Idol Flores.
♪
Hmm!
My Lozenge Magus
will guard that!
♪
Shining Lady gives her support
to an attack from my Army Lady.
♪
I can't guard.
(screams)
♪
Huh? He's back
on the offensive!
Who does he think
he is attacking a girl?
I'm so sorry, Emi.
I really don't
want to do it,
but if I lose this match,
my team might not
win the championship.
Please forgive me, my love!
He's got such a big heart.
What a sweet guy!
Checking the
damage trigger.
Look at that!
It's a heal trigger.
I recover one damage.
Well, that's a relief.
(groaning)
I stand and draw.
♪
First, I call Sakuya!
My Caravel leaves the field.
♪
With a boost from Gemini,
Flores attacks.
Ha!
(giggles)
♪
I don't need to guard.
Twin drive!
Now, let's see.
Hey, look, I got one!
Good work, Emi.
Now you get to
check one more.
Second check.
(gasps)
Hey, look, you guys!
I got another one!
That's so great.
(grunts)
♪
(chuckling nervously)
(giggles)
♪
I had a lot of fun
playing you today.
Don't mention it, Emi.
Winner of the second match:
the Princess Maiden!
(crowd cheering)
Yeah!
(sighs)
Are you okay?
Those Bermuda Triangle units.
I think that's the deck
I want to play from now on.
Kamui, what about
your Nova Grapplers?
You're a traitor.
(sighs)
The match is tied.
It comes down
to me versus Izaki.
That was great!
Seems I taught
you well, huh?
You sure did.
Huh?
♪
Wait, I'm playing
against Miwa?
♪
So‐‐
This is the
first chance I've had
to card fight
against you, Aichi.
I just always thought you
didn't know how to card fight
cause you never play.
(chuckles)
It's true that
I do like watching
you guys battle
each other,
but Kai didn't get that good
at card fighting by himself.
You catch my drift?
This'll be fun.
♪
Kamui lost to Emi.
I'm not Emi, I'm
the Princess Maiden!
Right,
my apologies, Princess.
And it looks like
I have to play against‐‐
Kai's training partner, the
handsome and impressive, Miwa!
Prepare yourself.
Yeah, prepare
if you dare!
(groans)
Next time "Miwa's Ability".
So, uh, I don't know
what you're dressed as,
but I can tell
you're really strong.
Oh, I'm strong all right.
Just you wait and see.
(snickers)