That's why I want to
fight you in the tournament
so badly, it's my way
of making you pay
for everything you did for me!
Hah, I think you mean
pay me back, but thanks.
First battle, you and me?
Hmm.
If you're my enemy,
I won't go easy on ya!
Only two teams were cut out
to reach the tournament finals!
Making their debut,
Team Quadrifoglio
Q4, for short, now,
a team which requires
no introduction but
gets one anyway,
Team Handsome!
Let's play some Vanguard!
There's nothing I want
more than to beat Gouki.
‐Huh?
‐This is all so perfect.
What is?
Ah, you're kidding!
No, and if I win,
we're getting married!
Huh, ahh!
♪
The regional tournament finals!
In the first match,
Kamui Katsuragi,
versus Nagisa Daimonji!
We're about to witness
an amazing card fight, folks.
You can't expect
anything but incredible
out of these two teams
after what we've seen today,
and now that they've
reached the final match,
these two young fighters
aren't gonna leave
anything on the table!
You've got your seats,
ladies and gentlemen,
but you're only gonna
need the edge,
as this battle is sure
to be one for the
card fighting history books!
If such a thing existed!
Now, let's play some Vanguard!
Is she allowed to
play for those guys?
‐I thought‐‐
‐You shouldn't be so surprised.
‐Huh?
‐Even if she sat out
the entire day, as long
as she's registered,
she can join in at any time.
‐It's the same with Misaki.
‐I see.
Ugh!
Gouki, what's the deal?
Weren't you and I supposed
to play each other?
You promised me!
That's true, but I'd
gladly break that promise
if it meant putting a
smile on my sister's face.
And if she wants to fight you,
I'll do anything in my power
to make that happen.
Huh?
It's about time you learned,
that in matters of
the heart, love wins!
That's right, sweetie!
Hey, would you stop
embarrassing me!
Pardon me, would you mind
if we start the match now?
♪
Wait a minute, this
is a joke, right?
You don't even like Vanguard!
♪
Why would I watch
that silly old game
when I can sit here and
watch you, instead?
Hmm?
Oh, hey, how are you
going to battle against me
when you don't even
know how to play?
Don't be silly, I know
how to card fight!
The power of love, listen,
I'm gonna tell you a story
that'll make you cry for sure.
The day you swore
you'd beat Team Handsome
and stop coming
to the card shop,
was the day you broke my darling
Nagisa's heart to pieces!
Gouki hates to see
his sister upset!
Mess with her, and he'll
make you go kaboom!
Stop interrupting me, you guys.
As I was saying,
after weeks of crying,
Nagisa asked me if I'd train her
to be the best
card fighter in town.
If playing Vanguard
is the only way back
into Kamui's life, then
that's what I'll do,
'cause I love him!
She was a natural.
No matter how hard
the training was,
she fought on!
If I get stronger,
maybe Kamui will
come back to me!
(clears throat)
Don't you get it,
the power of love
drove her to become stronger
than any of us imagined!
I know you're thinking
she's just the alternate,
but she's actually a
full‐fledged member
of our team, now.
‐No!
‐Yeah, I just wanted
to cheer you on,
so I had Hiroshi
fill in for me!
Isn't that right?
Wait, Hiroshi went to
Nationals last year,
so if Nagisa bumped him
to the alternate spot,
she must be good!
Whoa, did you hear
that, Morikawa?
Hmm, I totally see where
you're going with this.
That girl would be
the perfect candidate
for Mr. Morikawa's school
of Vanguard playing.
Yeah, right, she could probably
teach you a few things
about the game.
Hah, that's for sure.
But don't ever
let a little thing
like common sense get
in the way of your dreams!
Oh!
Ha ha ha!
If Gouki put her on
Team Handsome,
she must have some serious
card‐fighting skills.
Kamui, are you ready?
If I win, you and me
are getting married.
I can't agree to
something like that!
Think you'll lose?
Eh‐‐
Oh, Emi.
Hmm?
Oh.
(both laughing)
‐My dear?
‐Yes, darling?
(laughing)
That's right, Emi is
the one I want to be with!
Fine, I accept your
challenge, but if I win,
you'll give up on me
once and for all!
‐Hmm?
‐Come on,
when are they gonna start
the card fight already?
I'm with you, buddy.
Yeah, we paid admission
to see the Vanguard battles,
not this grade school
love story, right?
Huh?
I accept.
This is it, Kamui's finally
got the chance to get
this crazy girl out of his life!
Don't lose, yo!
If you value your freedom!
Hmm.
(whirring)
Let the card fight begin!
Stand up my Vanguard!
(whoosh)
♪
Battleraizer?
Why aren't you using a
grand blue deck like Gouki?
I'd rather use
your deck, my love.
Eh, that's kinda creepy.
I ride Tough Boy!
I use Battleraizer skill
to move into the rear guard.
It's your turn.
Yeah, it's my turn.
(whooshing)
I ride the Queen of Hearts!
Kamui's girlfriend
uses the same deck
as he does, it's so cute
that they're both into Vanguard!
They must be super close
if they play with the same
cards as one another.
(giggles)
Bad news.
Ahh, for the last time,
Nagisa's not my
girlfriend, capiche?
Quiet down!
The only girl for me is...
...Emu.
Emu?
Huh?
Come on, supported
by Battleraizer,
I'll have the Queen
of Heart attack you.
With Battleraizer's skill,
I add another 3,000 power
to the Queen.
Hmm.
Drive trigger check.
Oh, look, a critical trigger!
That's plus one damage!
(whoosh)
Damage trigger check, first.
Second.
(whoosh)
And now I return
Battleraizer to the deck.
You use the Nova
Grapplers pretty well.
Of course, it's our clan, right?
Yeah, well, we'll
see about that.
For my turn, I'm gonna
ride Brutal Jack!
♪
Moving Battleraizer forward,
I call Cray Soldier!
Next up, King of Sword,
and Shining Lady, join us!
(whoosh)
‐Here I go, counter blast!
‐Blast!
Keep going!
Hey, I need to stay focused.
Anyway, Brutal Jack's
power is released!
(whoosh)
King of Sword attacks!
(roar)
I check for a damage trigger.
With the support of
Shining Lady,
I'll have Brutal
Jack attack you!
(whoosh)
‐And also‐‐
‐Since he's being
supported by another
Nova Grappler,
Brutal Jack gets an
extra 5,000 attack power!
Huh, is the whole game
gonna be like this?
Drive trigger check.
(whoosh)
♪
Damage trigger check.
I attack with Battleraizer,
supported by Cray Soldier.
Damage trigger check,
yes, heal trigger.
That means I recover one damage!
Hmm, she's pretty good.
That was a great attack.
If not for the heel trigger,
you would have dealt
three damage to me!
My key to winning is power!
You're adorable when
you act all tough!
My key to winning is the
powerful bond between us!
Whatever, just start
your turn already.
Sure!
Let's end this game,
we've got a wedding to plan!
Well, I don't know if
us guys can handle
much more of this
cutesy nonsense.
So hurry it up, you lovebirds!
(groaning)
Here I go!
I ride Magician Girl Kirara!
♪
It's a Nova Grappler,
but I'm not really
familiar with that unit.
I call Kirara, Shining
Lady and Tough Boy!
♪
And now, with support
from Shining Lady,
I'll have Kirara attack
your Brutal Jack!
Drive trigger check.
(yelping)
Checking damage trigger.
Oh boy, I actually
got through to you!
Isn't it a little
early to celebrate?
Not really, 'cause when
Kirara's attack hits,
I get to do a counter blast!
Counter blast, I draw
one card from the deck.
Hmm.
You know how to play this game,
that's for sure.
You're cute when you're angry!
Haven't I ever told
you that, wuggums?
Cut it out, this
is embarrassing!
(grunting)
Hmm, face it, you and I
are perfect for
each other, Kamui!
Ahh, what is it about me
that you just can't get over?
I've never even done
anything nice for you!
Huh, you don't remember?
That long time ago
when you saved me?
Huh?
Well, I was eating an apple,
a big, red, beautiful apple.
But then, a chunk got
caught in my throat,
and everything got dark
as I drifted away.
My brother and his friends
couldn't do anything but cry!
Just when I thought
all hope was lost,
you came by!
It's not ringing any bells.
Remember, you found me
in that meadow.
You gently put
your arms around me,
helped me up and kissed me!
And then with the
poison apple removed,
I came back to life!
Hey, cut it out!
Seriously, you just
made that up!
A poison apple and
pirate fairies?
You mean, you forgot
our first kiss?
We never had a first
kiss, you nutjob!
Kamui and my little sis
sitting in a tree,
K‐I‐S‐S‐I‐N‐G.
Be quiet you big
wollyscags!
‐Wollyscags?
‐Seems like Nagisa
loves Kamui more than
anything in the whole world.
Must be nice to have
someone love you that much.
Did you hear that?
Emi is the only one
I'll ever love.
Nagisa, it's time for
me to take you down!
I've gotta win
this match, for Emi.
Hmm.
♪
Welcome back to the Vanguard
regional qualifying tournament!
So far, we've seen a bunch
of amazing card fights,
and it's down to
the final match up,
Team Handsome versus Team Q4!
We're already halfway
through the first battle
in this epic showdown,
and both our competitors
are playing with the intensity
you'd expect at this level.
It's my turn!
Hmm.
♪
Mr. Invincible, ride!
Ahh!
Soul Charge!
By sending the top card
of my deck into the soul stack,
I can then put one card
from my damage zone face up,
sending Battleraizer
to the drop zone!
I call King of
Sword in his place!
Next, I call Tough Boy!
I attack your Vanguard
with my king,
supported by Cray Soldier!
Shining Lady will guard that!
(whoosh)
Oh yeah, well my
own Shining Lady
will support Mr. Invincible
in his next attack!
Oh, ho ho!
Twin drive.
First, second.
Ugh!
Damage trigger check.
That's not all, Tough Boy
supports my other
King of Swords.
Damage Trigger check.
Ahh!
Check it out, the
game is tied at four!
Their play has been really
impressive so far.
Still not quite
at my level, though.
I know, right, how can they
call it a tournament
without the king of
the losers playing?
Yeah, that's what I've
been saying all along.
Wait a minute, you
just called me a loser!
(whoosh)
Hmm.
When I win, I'm changing my
last name to Katsuragi!
Hmm.
I ride Mr. Invincible!
Oh ho ho!
The same as mine.
Soul charge!
♪
Hungry Dumpty to rear guard,
when he comes into play,
I can flip another card
from the damage zone, face up!
She's got her whole
damage zone face up,
‐just like that?
‐I call Lucky Girl!
Tough Boy supports Kirara
in an attack on your Vanguard!
(yelping)
Doing this trigger check.
It's a stand trigger, I'm
powering up Invincible!
And my King stands!
Kirara's counter blast!
Ah, if Kamui takes one
more damage, he's gonna‐‐
Don't say it, yo!
Nagisa is incredible,
she's just as good as he is!
This is a big fight, Kamui.
Just stay calm.
All right, with
Shining Lady's support,
Mr. Invincible attacks!
Mean Girl Clara will
guard that attack!
Oh ho ho!
Hmph.
You've almost got him, sis!
Twin drive, first check,
second‐‐
A critical trigger,
I give the power
and the plus one critical
to Hungry Dumpty.
That little girl has so much
riding on this game,
that she's doing a really
good job of keeping her cool.
Yeah, Kamui better be
careful out there.
Finally, I support Hungry Dumpty
with Lucky Girl and attack!
♪
I guard with Hungry Dumpty!
(laughs)
Yah!
Yes, I managed to stop her!
All right!
So close!
Take 'em down, Nagisa,
love is power!
Seriously?
(background chatter)
Come on, Kamui, please.
I stand and draw!
‐Sweet!
‐Hmm?
With the mane of courage
and the roar of justice,
I ride the king of
all cats, Lion Heat!
♪
Yeah!
I'm gonna win it right now,
watch out, Nagisa!
I attack with King of Sword
boosted by Cray Soldier!
I think you're the one
who should watch out, Kamui.
I guard with Shining Lady!
Not done yet!
My Shining Lady supports
Lion Heat's attack!
Oh no, you don't!
Twin Blader guards against that.
♪
But that unit's shield is‐‐
Zero!
I activate Twin Blader's
defense skill,
by sending a Nova Grappler unit
from my hand to the drop zone,
I won't take any
damage for this attack.
Ugh!
Oh, she totally shut me down.
Twin drive first
check, second check.
Critical trigger!
I give all the bonuses to
my standing King of Sword!
I just need to make sure
I land this attack.
With Tough Boy's support,
the King of Sword
ends your wedding plans!
Nothing can get in the way
of our marriage, my love.
I guard with another Twin Blader
and activate his skill.
She's stopped everything!
I'm done for!
You're gonna look
cute in a tuxedo!
This fight isn't over yet!
(background chatter)
Hmm.
Time for my last turn
as a single lady!
With the fuzzy mane of courage
and the cuddly roar of justice,
I ride the king of
the kitties, Lion Heat!
Ugh!
Can we have our wedding
in a beautiful castle?
Kirara attacks you with
the support of Tough Boy!
Forget the castle,
Shining Lady guards!
I've already bought a super
frilly white wedding dress!
Lucky Girl supporting
Hungry Dumpty
in my next attack on
your Vanguard!
I hope you kept the receipt,
because Queen of Heart
guards that attack!
It'll be so romantic
if we write our own vows,
with support from Shining
Lady I'll have Lion Heat
attack your Vanguard!
Well, here's my vow.
King of Sword will
stop your attack
with an intercept!
This will work as long as
she doesn't draw a trigger.
Love power, just need to
check my twin drive first.
Happy couple, check
the second card.
Wedding cake, stand trigger!
Ahh!
I give the power to Lion
Heat, and Kirara stands.
(giggles)
Hi‐ya!
No way am I gonna get married!
It all comes down to this.
First trigger check.
All right, heal trigger!
That's 5,000 power to Lion Heat.
Also, I get to
recover one damage.
Oh, thank goodness.
Kirara's attack will be too weak
to damage my Vanguard.
You're not getting away
that easily, my darling.
Huh?
You're forgetting that
when Lion Geek damages
my opponent, I get to
activate his counter blast
and stand a unit.
Ahh, how could I forget?
Tough Boy stands again.
I'll seal your fate
with a wedding ring.
Tough Boy supports Kirara
for his final attack!
♪
Wedding hold!
Ahh!
♪
Ugh!
(laughter)
I guess life isn't gonna
work out the way I planned.
Maybe this isn't so bad.
Miss Emi?
Huh?
(bell ringing)
Nagisa Daimanji is the
winner of the first battle!
You're mine!
Yeah, you're as strong
as you are cute, Nagisa!
‐All right!
‐Kaboom!
Are you okay?
He did an excellent
job of defending.
But in the end, he couldn't
keep up with Nagisa
and her relentless attacks.
Even with Emi's support,
Kamui still lost to her!
Huh?
This is the worst day ever, yo!
I learned an incredible
lesson today.
Love is something you can
win in a card fight,
Kourin, I challenge
you immediately
to a Vanguard battle,
and the winner
marries the loser!
We know which one you are.
Hey, there's some weird guy
out there calling your name.
Hmm, not him again.
Oren, my love!
Stop it, man, you're
embarrassing me!
Looks like this match
is about to get interesting.
I lost, so much for
asking Emi on a date.
Huh?
My darling, it's time for
you to fulfill your promise.
Now, let's get married!
Ugh!
Oh?
Welcome to the
family, little bro!
No way!
But you promised!
No!
Be a man.
(laughs)
Stay away, I'll never marry you!
Isn't young love
just the cutest?
Aren't they just
the perfect couple?
‐My love!
‐That was the best card fight
I've seen in ages.
Hey, let's make the
next match just as fun!
Uh, okay.
You'll never be
alone again, my love!
♪
Now the pressure's on
me to win my fight.
You've got it, bro,
our future is riding
on the outcome of this match!
But if you lost
to Team Handsome,
then what chance do I
stand against them?
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know why
I thought we'd wind up
with a happy ending.
Looks like Kai's
going before me.
Next time, Hidden Message.
Kai is trying to
tell me something.
Just watch my fight,
and you'll see.