♪
(screams)
(sighs)
I've got to try and get my
hands on some better cards.
My deck needs
a Grade Three.
(sighs)
♪
Huh?
Hmm.
Your deck is really bad.
Hey, kid!
I'm gonna stand and draw.
Hmm, this fight
belongs to me.
No way!
See for yourself!
I ride Asura Kaiser!
Is that a Grade Three?
♪
Destroy him, Asura Kaiser!
Finishing hold!
‐Oh.
‐Ha!
Now, who said
they'd never lose
to a little grade
schooler punk like me?
Tell all the
people who lost!
(growls, grunts)
I lost.
‐Say it louder!
Hey, take it easy,
you already beat him.
(taunting)
‐You.
‐What's up?
(sighs)
Only two damage?
Unreal!
Oh, I'm for real.
In fact, you could say
that this guy right here
is the true
genuine automobile.
I'm young, I'm cool,
and I'm number one.
I'm pretty sure you mean
"the genuine article".
The kid may
be a good player,
but I can't stand that horrible
personality of his at all.
You should look
who's talking.
Honestly, who does
he think he is
disrespecting
people like that?
I figure I should
probably teach him
a thing or two
about manners.
Kamui, you're the best.
CS, yo!
CS?
Crazy strong, dude!
This guy seems like a real
BH to me, right, guys?
Totally!
(snickering)
BH?
Butt head?
Why, you brats!
You think he's
as strong as Kai?
♪
Hey.
Would you have a
fight with me next?
Who are you?
Aichi Sendou.
Aichi Sendou?
You're weak, I'm strong.
No thanks, bud.
I can always
tell who's strong
and you are just
not it, my friend!
I draw the line at
beating up on babies.
But that's because I only
just started playing Vanguard,
and I don't have
any Grade Three's.
Even with a mitt
full of Grade Three's,
I would destroy you.
'Fraidy cat, guy.
Hmm.
Don't worry, I can take
care of him for you.
Katsumi Morikawa, the
number one Vanguard player
at Card Capital,
challenging you
to a card fight,
and when I win,
you'll respect me.
‐Huh?
That works for me,
and if I win,
you have to do the same.
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
Destroy him, Asura Kaiser!
(whimpering)
I lost.
Morikawa.
You like that?
Getting beat by
a grade schooler?
(chuckling)
Kamui is seriously good.
He wasn't kidding.
That's 29 victories in a row.
Kamui, you're the best.
Well, we don't call
him CS for nothing.
So were you bluffing
or something?
Cause you're by far the worst
player I've ever beaten.
Oh!
Hey, man, I was just
trying to go easy on you.
I thought it was a friendly
match or something.
You lost, now
show me some respect.
Loser!
I did say that,
Mr. Pipsqueak.
‐Oh, yeah?
‐Yeah.
(chuckling nervously)
So, you buying cards?
Huh? Oh yeah.
Maybe you'll score a
Grade Three this time.
I hope.
I've opened a couple
of packs before
and still haven't gotten one,
but you know what?
Today must be the day.
(door opens)
I knew I would
find you here.
♪
(shouts)
Who is that?
Hey, you all right?
♪
She's so...
I'm in love!
Hey, are you here
to learn about Vanguard
'cause I'm pretty much
the best player in town,
so if you want
to know anything...
Actually, right now, there's
something I wanna know.
How would you like
to be my girlfriend?
(giggles)
Is that a yes?
‐Huh?
(sputters)
Wow, Aichi!
Emi.
How do you think
they know each other?
Let's find out.
Just chill, yo.
What gives, Aichi?
You said you'd help me with
my homework today, right?
I swear I didn't forget!
I just thought I'd swing by
and grab myself a booster pack.
You thought wrong.
We're leaving!
But I haven't bought it yet.
What part of "we're leaving"
wasn't clear?
They act like they know
each other super well.
The way she just pulled
him out of here was crazy.
Don't you think
that maybe she's his...
‐Girlfriend?
(shouts)
♪
(scoffs)
I'm not even gonna bother
correcting them.
♪
And here's one
booster pack.
Thanks.
Please let there be
a Grade Three in here.
Grade One.
And next?
Grade Two.
Man, you've got
terrible luck
when it comes to
opening booster packs.
I mean, you've never
even seen a Grade Three.
How unlucky could
one person be!
The last card.
Alright!
Solitary Knight Gancelot!
Now, that‐‐that's a
good‐looking Grade Three.
Hey, that card you got
is a Royal Paladin unit.
Just like your deck, right?
Yeah!
I finally got one.
A Grade Three.
Huh? What is this?
A paper bag?
(grunts)
Kamui?
I challenge you to a duel!
A duel?
In accordance
with tradition,
I have challenged
you to a duel
by slapping you
with a white bag.
As usual, you've got
it completely wrong.
It's a white glove.
(groans)
A card fight!
Let's do this!
I thought you didn't
want to play me.
Yeah, well,
that was before
I saw you with
my dream girl!
What?
Do it, man.
You can avenge my loss!
Come on, Aichi!
♪
‐Hmm!
I don't really get it, but
I'd be happy to fight you.
♪
Hmm.
This is a terrible
starting hand.
What a pain.
So, you do know you can
take a redraw, right?
A redraw?
For crying out loud,
what a noob.
Once each game
you get the chance
to take unwanted
cards from your hand
and trade them for
a fresh draw, capisce?
Are you serious?
Of course, and you probably
don't know this either,
but you should try and
have a unit of each grade
in your opening
hand if possible,
because that's the
easiest strategy.
Of course!
That way you can ride your
vanguard to the next level
on each of your
first three turns.
Hey, thanks for
letting me know.
Oh, man, now you look
like the nicest guy ever!
That girl is gonna
fall for you for sure.
Well, then, I'm
gonna redraw three.
♪
I'll redraw two cards.
Okay, our starting
hands are set.
Let's go.
♪
‐Stand up now, my vanguard!
I guess I'll be
taking first turn then?
Yeah.
Going second
is what I prefer.
Hmm?
I ride the little
sage, Marron.
♪
I'm not able to
attack on the first turn,
so I'll pass
it over to you.
Sounds good.
I ride the screaming
and dancing announcer.
Stand up, Shout!
When you a ride a nova grappling
unit on top of Battleraizer,
his ability triggers, and
you can move Battleraizer
to any of your
guard's circle.
♪
What?
That is a good ability!
I call the Queen of Heart
and a Shining Lady!
You see, there's a reason
I like to go second.
Cause it lets
me attack first!
I support the Queen of Heart
with Battleraizer
and attack Marron.
When he's used
as a support card,
Battleraizer adds
3,000 attack power.
I guard with
Weapons Dealer Govannon.
♪
I'll have Shining Lady support
Shout in an attack on Marron.
(roars)
In that case, I'll
use my Elaine to guard.
Oh, yeah, check it
for drive trigger.
♪
There isn't a trigger,
that's good.
♪
(grunts)
Did you really have
to defend on those?
Huh?
Guess my turn's over.
I shuffle Battleraizer
back into my deck
as part of his
ability cost.
Come on,
give me your best!
♪
Stand up, my avatar!
Ride Blaster Blade!
♪
I call Wingal and the
Knight of Silence, Gallatin.
♪
Nice, you should have
come at me with everything.
You can't take damage
while attacking
and missing an attack
just hurts your chances.
♪
I attack Shout with Gallatin.
I don't defend,
and now I'm gonna check
for a damage trigger.
I support Blaster Blade with
Wingal and attack Shout!
Wingal's ability
gives Blaster Blade
an extra
4,000 attack power,
and then I check
for a drive trigger.
No trigger.
I do a damage
trigger check.
It's a stand trigger.
The trigger on this
lucky girl allows me
to add 5,000 power to a unit.
I apply this boost to Shout
plus I can stand one
of my rear‐guard units.
No, not that!
Wait a‐‐ that doesn't
really do anything to me.
Yeah.
That trigger works
best on my turn.
Oh, good!
I was a bit worried there.
Learn the basics, man!
♪
Perfect timing.
I ride Hungry Dumpty.
♪
I move the
Queen of Heart back,
and in her place,
I call King of Sword.
What's he up to?
I call Tough Boy
and Brutal Jack!
Wow.
Brutal Jack is only
a Grade Two and yet,
he has 11,000 attack power.
Yeah, I know, but in order
for me to attack with him,
I have to pay an activation
fee during my turn.
Man, what a useless unit.
You miss the point as usual.
(shouts)
I pay the activation cost
and release Brutal Jack
into high gear,
then I support
him with Tough Boy
and hit
Blaster Blade.
(roars)
What a powerful attack!
I can't afford to
use up anymore cards.
If only I still had
that Elaine from before.
(electricity crackling)
I check for a damage trigger.
Shining Lady
supports Hungry Dumpty
and attacks
Blaster Blade.
Time for a
drive trigger check.
Boo‐yah!
You probably recognize
this bad boy.
So now I get to stand up
one of my rear‐guard units
for another attack!
‐You don't mean‐‐
‐Exactly.
Brutal Jack.
Plus I get to distribute
a 5,000 attack power bonus,
which I'm gonna
give to Brutal Jack.
Sixteen thousand?
♪
I check for a
damage trigger.
♪
And now I attack
your Blaster Blade
with Brutal Jack once more.
♪
I check for another
damage trigger.
Not gonna happen.
I'll have the Queen
support the King of Sword
and attack Blaster Blade.
The Queen supporting
the King gives a bonus
of 4,000 attack power.
♪
I see!
So that's why you
moved that unit back.
Damage trigger check.
Four damage in one turn.
Kamui is seriously
good at Vanguard.
My only chance is to
hit him with everything.
♪
(inquisitive meow)
(grunts)
This is it.
Good draw.
Huh?
I call on the power of the
proud white wings of fate!
Ride!
♪
Solitary Knight Gancelot.
I activate Gancelot's
counter blast!
At a cost of two, I add 5,000
points to his attack power.
♪
Not to mention,
plus one critical.
♪
I'll activate it again.
Supporting with Marron,
I attack Hungry Dumpty
with Gallatin.
I have two cards in my hand
and only one of them
has a defense shield.
♪
If I can defend
against this attack,
I can still take
the three damage
that Gancelot is
going to hit me for.
♪
I'm safe as long as he doesn't
draw a critical trigger
during the
twin drive check.
I don't think this
guy's lucky enough
to do something like that.
Okay!
I defend with
Battleraizer!
♪
I'll have Wingal support
Gancelot and attack.
Twin drive, checking
for the first trigger.
‐Nope.
‐Yes!
Draw an Epona, and
beat that little brat!
The second drive
trigger check.
No again.
Oh, why couldn't you have
super good luck like me?
I always get
the draws I need.
♪
I check for three
damage triggers.
First check is...
Clay‐doll Mechanic,
no trigger.
No trigger on the second check,
another Clay‐doll.
And third check, invincible.
No trigger.
I got so close,
but that's my turn.
I stand and draw.
Here goes!
I ride Asura Kaiser!
♪
Counter class activated.
I release Brutal Jack
into high gear.
Using support
from Tough Boy,
I attack Gancelot
with Brutal Jack.
♪
I check for a
damage trigger.
Uh‐oh, no trigger.
I support the King of Sword
with the Queen of Heart
and attack Gancelot again.
♪
(roars)
No! I guard against him!
And I'll intercept
with Gallatin
to cover the
excess damage.
"Intercept?"
It allows your front row units
to join in and guard an attack.
Oh, of course, I was just
checking to see if you knew.
(chuckles)
Your attack won't
go through now.
Next, Shining Lady
supports Asura Kaiser
and attacks Gancelot!
♪
I guard with Gallatin
and Starlight Unicorn!
♪
Oh, yeah, you got him!
Just get me to my turn.
Hold it.
I think you're forgetting
that I have twin drive.
First check.
Yeah, just one more!
(growls)
♪
Oh, yeah.
I have the best!
A Grade Three, but
that means, we've won!
We've won!
Nuh‐uh, that's not how it
works on Asura Kaiser.
Huh?
Having Asura Kaiser
in my vanguard circle
means this card will let me
stand up one of my rear‐guards.
But‐‐ no way!
I call this my
stand of pain.
Brutal Jack is back up
and attacking your vanguard.
♪
Checking damage trigger.
No trigger.
(groans)
That's game.
Oh, wow, Kamui's
so strong, huh?
More like the
Junior High kids are weak.
Well done,
your greatness.
Dude, that's 30 straight wins
against Junior High kids, yo!
He's strong, but not in the
same way as Kai and Misaki.
I love being able to
fight all sorts of people.
Man, Aichi,
you're the worst.
I'm revoking our friendship
until you improve.
Yeah?
What were you thinking
fighting a guy that strong
with only one Grade Three
unit in your entire deck?
What?
He only had a
single Grade Three?
With a proper deck,
this guy could be trouble.
Oh, well!
‐Aichi Sendou.
‐Hmm?
You lost, now give me
what I want.
Sir, yes, sir!
No, I don't
care about that.
Then?
I'm gonna take
your lady, okay?
Uh?
What do you mean?
You know, your
girlfriend there.
Huh?
Huh? Aichi!
♪
(growls)
‐Keep it cool.
‐CS, yo!
So, you're here
again, Aichi?
Is your homework done?
Not yet.
Well, that's not
gonna work for me,
cause you know that
Mom told me to make sure
you finish all
your homework.
(growling)
That guy needs to step
away from dream girl.
Those two; it can
be hard to tell
which one of them is the
older sibling sometimes.
Huh?
What did she say?
They're brother and sister.
Commonly known as siblings.
Commonly known as?
‐Siblings?
Brother!
Come again?
I look up to you
like a brother.
Cause you're one of
the coolest guys I know.
What‐‐what are you‐‐
Please, Brother, you've got
to hang out with me again soon.
I'm not your brother.
Come on, bro,
I'm reaching out here.
Come on!
(screaming)
No way, seriously!
You're creeping me out!
Don't touch me!
You want a backrub, Brother,
do you, huh, do you?
♪
Brother Aichi, your little
sister is wonderful.
Yeah, but she's
really on top of things
and she gets angry
at me every day.
She yells at you, right?
That would be awesome.
Anyway, you're a
great player, Kamui.
I hope I get more
Grade Three's soon,
so I can fight
on your level.
Next time, "The
Mysterious Card Shop!"
Wow, the units are
fighting before our eyes.
Brother,
I‐‐I pictured it.
My future together
with Miss Emi.