Team Quadrifoglio,
good work on getting past
the first round.
You didn't have to do that.
Who's gonna clean up
all that confetti
you just spilled?
I'll do it.
Sure hope this gets better.
The first round was weak.
At least you weren't watching
from the sidelines while
your friends got to battle!
That's it; next match we play,
I'm going first and you guys
can watch me kick some butt.
Huh.
Huh?
Kamui!
Not again!
You did it, you guys won!
(grunting)
(giggling)
Get off!
Nagisa, you're annoying me!
Yeah, but I'm so happy!
Well, I'm not, okay?
I didn't get to cardfight
and you're all in my face!
But your face is so cute;
I can't stay away,
and I'll be here
to comfort you later
when your team gets knocked out.
What do you mean by that?
Even if you do make it
all the way to the finals,
well, you won't
make it past them.
Huh?
♪
Gouki.
Hmm.
♪
Next up, the final match
of the first round!
The team on my left
just spent all morning
setting up
their victory display.
It's Team Nadeshiko!
And representing
Card Shop Handsome,
Team Handsome!
There you have it, folks!
Now, join me as we welcome
the representatives
from each of these teams!
From Team Nadeshiko,
it's Hiromi Sakeuin!
She faces the captain
of Team Handsome,
Gouki Daimonji!
Why is Gouki going first?
I mean, shouldn't they save
their best fighter for last?
By the looks of it,
I'd say he's probably
just trying to win
the first match quickly
and get his team pumped up.
Generally speaking,
though, you've got
the right idea, Aichi.
By saving your strongest fighter
for last, it takes a lot
of pressure off
the other people on your team.
Determining the order
of when your teammates fight
can actually have a big effect
on the outcome of the matchup.
Team battles
are part of the reason
why tournaments are so exciting.
Huh, doesn't really matter
when I battle 'cause I'm
not gonna lose to anyone.
I love you, sweetie!
Knock it off!
♪
The winner, Gouki Daimonji.
So quick!
See that,
my big brother's unstoppable.
Tell me something I don't know.
Seems like he's gotten even
better than when I played him.
That's the great thing
about a game like Vanguard;
there is always something
you can improve.
And here I was hoping
that I'd be strong enough
to beat Gouki by now.
Still got a long way to go.
Peek‐a‐boom!
♪
We're finished!
There it is; Team Handsome isn't
wasting any time this early on.
Looks like our
defending champions
are moving on to
the second round in style.
The only way we're
gonna play those guys
is if we make it
to the final round.
That's just fine,
as long as we get
the chance to beat them
at their own game!
Oh, Kamui, you're so cute!
Cut it out!
It's non‐stop action as we move
straight into the second round!
Now, let's take a look
at our next matchup;
Team Martial Arts
versus Team Q4!
You think they can do it?
Yeah.
They just might go kaboom.
Kamui.
These teams both
had strong showings in
their preliminary matches today.
I'm playing first
and Kai's second.
You'll play the third game
if it goes that far, okay?
Sure, best of luck.
♪
I love you, win or lose!
Why couldn't that be
Emi cheering for me?
No, the only thing that matters
right now is this cardfight;
if I win this match
and all the others,
maybe Emi will
come down and be like,
"Oh, Kamui, you're
the best ever."
Let's go!
‐You ready for this?
(shouting)
♪
I'm gonna enjoy taking you out!
Here's my prediction: You lose!
♪
I ride Bloody Hercules
and call Lady Bomb
to rear guard!
Lady Bomb's counterblast!
That move makes it
so that your Queen of Heart
won't be able
to stand next turn.
I'll have Bahr support
Bloody Hercules
and attack Tough Boy!
Drive trigger check.
(gunfire)
I'm checking for
a damage trigger.
And I got it!
I'll have the Queen
of Heart stand up!
♪
Bad news for you.
Tried to hold us down,
but Nova Grapplers
will always rise
to the occasion!
That skill
is useless against me!
You tell 'em, sweetie!
If he thinks he can push
around my boyfriend,
he's crazy.
(grunts)
We're tied at 5 Damage.
He's only got two cards.
I'll win it here and now.
Three times the dragon
means three times the force!
Get ready for this ride;
it's Brutal Jack!
♪
He's using three copies
of Brutal Jack?
How primitive.
A triple release
by Brutal Jacks
into high gear.
Now all three of them
are headed your way.
First up, Brutal Jack
is supported by
the Queen of Heart
and attacks your Hell Spider!
Lizard Soldier, Ganlu,
will guard that attack!
No problem, Brutal Jack
attacks with support
from the Queen of Heart.
Since Brutal Jack is
in the Vanguard Circle,
this boost from
a Nova Grappler unit
gives him an extra
5,000 attack power.
I guard with Phantom Black,
as well, I intercept
with Lady Bomb
and Bloody Hercules.
I check for
a drive trigger, and‐‐
♪
Finally, I attack
with Brutal Jack,
boosted by Lucky Girl!
Finishing hold!
Checking for damage trigger.
Third time's the charm.
♪
The winner, Kamui Katsuragi.
That's my man!
That was great!
Yeah, bro, we're almost there!
Right.
Next, the second fight
from this matchup.
♪
Wow.
(grunting)
Q4 wins again.
Toshiki Kai!
(cheering)
♪
Heh, playing such a weakling,
of course he's gonna win!
Looks like we move on
to the next round.
Kai and Kamui
really are the best.
Huh?
I didn't say anything.
Even if I don't get
the chance to play again,
it's so exciting
to see our team win.
♪
We present you with
the signs of our dojos.
Uh, no thanks.
Team Q4 beat Team Martial Arts
two fights in a row.
This team has come
out of nowhere
and is charging toward
the finals, but now,
standing in their way
is none other than
the super strong
Team Chemistry Club.
(incoherent sobbing)
♪
(chucking)
(nervous tittering)
And just like that,
the match is over.
The winners, Team Q4.
♪
There's a chemical leaking
out of my face right now.
It's mostly water.
And some salt, too.
‐All right!
‐Way to go!
Finals, here we come!
Kamui, you're the best!
The best, yo!
Mmm.
That was out of this world!
We did it; we're competing in
the finals of
the regional tournament!
Of course and it's all thanks
to me, isn't that right, Kai?
(chuckles nervously)
It looks like Team Q4 is really
starting to come together.
Our second matchup of
the semi‐finals is coming
to a close!
Team Hot Noodles is corner.
Team Handsome is heading
toward victory thanks
to their captain,
Gouki Daimonji.
(grunts)
(squeals)
Team Handsome is the winner!
♪
There ya have it, folks,
another big victory,
just what we expect
from last year's winner!
This is a pain
not even noodles can fix!
Take a good,
long look at our finalists:
Team Q4 and Team Handsome!
Only one of them will be able
to claim the top prize
in the last round.
You've come a long way, kid.
This is what I've
been waiting for.
Hey there, sweetie,
good luck, okay?
YOU'RE RUINING MY MOMENT!
I love how passionate you are!
♪
The final matches
will begin this afternoon.
Enjoy the break.
I repeat, the finals
of the regional tournament
will be held in
the afternoon after a break.
Finalist Team Members...
Kamui!
Where are you?
Hey!
Why are you hiding?
Please come out here!
Kamui!
Looks like I'm
gonna get the chance
to crush
Team Handsome after all.
What do you think about that?
Ha, yeah, now if only
we were on the same team,
we'd be crushing
people together.
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you, Gouki,
but I'm gonna have to learn
to fight my own battles.
Some guy was picking on me
just because I was smaller
than he was.
I stood up for myself.
(chuckles)
(whimpers)
♪
I didn't stand a chance;
he was too big and too strong.
(sobbing)
♪
I walked into the nearest store
to use the phone and saw you
fighting a grown
man at Vanguard!
Drive trigger!
(chuckles)
(grunts)
Aw, man.
Wow, you've gotten good.
Here, you wanted
my bandana, didn't you?
Can I really have it?
♪
Care for a game?
(chuckles)
You told me that
in a Vanguard fight,
all that mattered was
the size of a person's heart.
Yeah, I remember saying that.
That's why I wanna fight you
in the tournament so badly;
it's my way of making you pay
for everything you did for me.
I think you mean
pay me back, but thanks.
First battle, you and me?
If you're my enemy,
I won't go easy on ya.
Good, I wanna beat
you at your best.
No, what do you mean
you forgot our lunch
at Card Capital?
This can't be happening!
I'm sorry, guys.
The Assistacat and I
must've switched bags
'cause all I have
is this cat food.
How is that even possible?
I know, and after I spent
so much time cooking
that lobster.
Boy, those things
can sure pinch.
I don't wanna think about it.
All right,
who wants some cat food?
Uh, I'm good.
Hungry.
Hey, you guys can
have this if you like.
That voice, it's... my love!
Emi, you brought lunch?
Mom just dropped me off here,
she said you might be hungry.
Shin was about
to make us eat cat food.
What a beautiful sight!
It all looks great.
Thanks so much, Emi,
you really saved the day.
So, how have the fights been?
We're the best!
Yeah, we're in
the finals coming up.
Good job, guys!
I guess Kai and Kamui
must be really strong, then.
Yeah, I guess they are;
they've won us a bunch of games.
Your brother's been
doing really well, too.
He won the first game
of the day for us,
and if it's not
too much trouble,
could I ask you a favor?
Could you call me
by my name again?
Here you go.
She wasn't listening.
Thank you.
It looks so good!
Eating your food,
I'll win for sure.
♪
There you are!
I knew you'd be hungry
so I made a special
love lunch for you and me!
♪
I figure Aichi might
need some advice from
his old teacher‐‐huh?
♪
Don't you dare
swallow that sandwich!
Give it back to me!
Spit it out right now!
Emi made that sandwich
for me and now it's gone!
There's no need
to be so angry.
Your girlfriend made
a delicious lunchbox for you!
"Girlfriend"?
(grunts)
♪
What was that about?
Ta‐da; it's you, Kamui!
Now we can both eat your face!
Try some.
Check it out,
looks like he's bitten off
more than he can chew.
Freedom!
Kamui!
Run, run, run!
I see, you're
working up an appetite.
(yelps)
I got it.
(munching)
(screaming)
What did you make?
It's just some rice mixed
with all the spiciest things
I could find in my kitchen.
Nagisa's Fireball Surprise!
I figured you were
a "hot" kinda guy.
You know I can't eat
anything spicy, right?
Oopsie, my mistake.
Let me go!
Never!
Emi, it's not what it
looks like; let me explain!
That must be
your girlfriend, huh?
Yuppers, and pretty soon,
we're gonna get married!
Seriously,
you need to stop that.
The girl I love is‐‐
Is Nagisa!
No way!
Yes way!
Quit it!
It's Nagisa!
No, it's not!
I'm in love with‐‐
♪
E...E...Emi.
Hmm?
(gulping)
Huh?
Hmm.
You stay away from my man!
♪
Ah, the fickle nature of love.
Wow, please stop it.
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry, Emi,
you didn't deserve that,
and what's worse
is that beautiful sandwich
you made me was eaten
by that loser, Morikawa,
and I just‐‐
Oh, don't.
You little...man‐stealer!
Huh?
The final round of
the regional tournament
will begin shortly.
Would all of our finalists
please make their way
to the designated area?
This is it.
Huh?
Misaki!
Hm?
We're glad you made it.
Hey, weren't you supposed
to be here for the whole event?
I had to play
an untested deck, you know,
'cause I thought I'd
be sitting this out.
I'm sorry, how did it go?
I won somehow, but Kai
and Kamui have carried us
the rest of the way
and now there's one round to go.
Wow.
So, are you gonna
take over for me?
I think you'd better
stay in there, Aichi.
You've come this far.
Mm‐hm.
If you say so, then I'll fight.
I hate to disappoint you,
bro, but I don't think
it's gonna come to that.
Kai and I are gonna end
this thing with two
quick victories in a row.
Fine, as long as we win,
I don't mind sitting this out.
Well, team, let's git 'r dun!
Yeah!
Wooo!
(me‐yawning)
♪
It's finally time for
the main event, folks,
the championship match,
but first, let's all sit back
and enjoy this exciting
warm‐up performance.
It's the debut single from
Vanguard's own pop idol group;
here's "Miracle Trigger,"
by Ultra Rare!
♪
(indistinct lyrics)
They are so good.
What songs have
you been singing?
♪
‐Stand up, Vanguard!
Stardust Trumpeter!
♪
For you.
You're giving this to me?
As a memento of your visit.
I can't believe
they're the same people.
♪
Thanks, everyone!
Ultra Rare!
Rekka, you were pretty off‐key.
Hey, I was not!
Looks like that blue‐haired boy
made it to the finals.
Yeah, I remember him.
I guess that means
he's making good use
of that card I gave him.
No doubt.
Only two teams were good enough
to reach the regional
tournament finals!
Making their debut,
Team Quadrifoglio,
Q4 for short.
The four‐leaf clover
is the ultimate symbol of luck
and boy are they gonna need it
against their final opponent.
Now, a team which
requires no introduction,
but gets one anyway,
the group that won
last year's regionals
and made an impressive run
at the nationals,
it's Gouki Daimonji
and Team Handsome!
I guess I should be
thankful she's over there.
All right,
the undefeated streaks
of our championship teams
are about to end!
Which one will emerge
as the day's big winner?
Let's play some Vanguard!
He's so cool!
Yeah, whatever.
♪
First round players
step forward, please.
Well, it all comes down to this.
Go get 'em!
If only I'd known that playing
at regionals would bring
me and Kourin closer together,
I wouldn't have let myself
get beaten at
the Card Capital tournament!
Never a dull moment with you.
Hey, Emi,
try to control yourself
when you see my cool moves.
You've gotta help
us cheer, goddess.
Oh, uh, sure.
Do your best!
You heard the lady!
Wow, I'll try!
I'm not gonna let you down!
Thanks!
(growling)
I can't believe it's finally
here, my chance to beat him!
First battle, you and me?
There's nothing I want
more than to beat Gouki!
Huh?
This is all so perfect.
What is?
Agh, you're kidding!
No, and if I win,
we're getting married!
Huh?
(screams)
♪
Can you believe
we made the finals?
my mouth is still burning?
Kai and Kamui
could win it without me.
No way, you never know
what could happen!
But those guys
are really strong.
You're so naive;
we live in an era
where sandwiches fall
from the sky and land
in your mouth.
Uh, that was‐‐
Next time...
The setting for this
battle might as well
be a wedding reception.
Poor guy, it's his
toughest battle yet.