Here we are at
the midway point
in the second fight of
our semifinal matchup,
and, boy, are the
emotions ever running high!
Neither competitor
willing to move an inch
as Yuri Usui looks to stop Q4
from running away with this.
Ooh, look at Yuri's units.
Now that's what I call
a battle formation.
The Dailadies
really complement
her Vanguard's abilities.
♪
It's on.
Cosmo Roar's ability.
I give an extra 2,000
power to Enigman Wave.
♪
That boost is
only the beginning.
♪
When Dailady lands
a successful attack,
she can give 3,000
power to another unit.
I can't afford to let
those ones through.
Because if Enigman Wave's
power is over 14,000,
he would give her
the edge she needs.
She'll get to draw a
card each time he hits me.
♪
I have no choice.
Dailady attacks your Goddess
of the Half Moon Tsukuyomi.
♪
Dream Eater will guard.
Huh?
Hm.
Next I attack with
my other Dailady.
Gemini will guard.
♪
She had no problem seeing
through Yuri's attack strategy.
What a play,
keep it up!
Nicely done.
She was able to prevent
Wave's power increase.
But I'm not finished.
♪
Supported by
Magical Police Quilt,
Enigman Wave attacks.
♪
Drive check.
(gasps)
♪
Misaki just worked so
hard to protect herself.
And the attack goes critical?
Bad luck, yo.
Giving all effects
to Enigman Wave.
(explosion)
♪
Hm.
Looks like I got you.
Activating Quilt's skill.
I drop a card
and draw a new one.
I think I'll end my turn.
Pulling that trigger
was pretty lucky.
Still, I didn't
come here to lose.
I draw.
Checking the top
five cards of my deck
for Goddess of the Full Moon.
She's not there.
♪
Maiden of Light,
it's your turn to shine.
I ride.
♪
I love it when Misaki
rides Amaterasu.
Yeah, now we're getting
our money's worth!
With Amaterasu's skill,
I soul charge and check
the top card of my deck.
I'm sending this
one to the bottom.
I haven't seen a unit
with a trigger in ages.
♪
37 cards
remaining in my deck
with 15 potential
drive triggers.
There's a chance
I'll hit one this turn.
I'll have Tagitsuhime
attack one of your Dailadies.
Ha!
♪
So that's the plan.
She wants to limit
my ability to intercept.
Amaterasu attacks Enigman Wave.
No guard.
Twin drive check.
♪
Got it.
Perfect time for a critical.
♪
Over to you.
All right!
That was lucky
getting a trigger there.
It wasn't a matter
of luck, you guys.
Misaki memorizes
the cards she sees.
Before attacking, she would
have calculated the chances
of pulling a trigger.
Really?
She's using math out there?
Amazing.
Taking in all that information
to work out the probabilities
brings her closer
to claiming victory.
That's Misaki's
winning image.
♪
I draw.
Can you hear the raindrops?
'Cause it's about to pour.
I ride Enigman Rain.
♪
Not done.
I call...
♪
And I activate Cosmo
Roar's skill again,
giving power to my Vanguard.
♪
This new Vanguard has
a different ability.
♪
Her strategy couldn't
be more obvious.
First I'll have Dailady
attack Tagitsuhime.
(grunts)
♪
Coming off my intercept.
I guess she's determined
to get her Enigman
Rain's attack through.
It won't.
With Daisy's support,
Miracle Beauty
attacks Amaterasu.
♪
(grunts)
Next, with a boost
from Magical Police Quilt,
Enigman Rain attacks!
♪
Not so fast.
Psychic Bird and White Hare
of Inaba will guard that.
♪
Checking the twin drive.
My turn's done.
Impressive.
Hm.
Check out Misaki.
She's holding strong
against some huge attacks.
She made a great choice
when she guarded against Rain.
Considering her
limited hand size,
it really was the best option.
Boosting Enigman
Rain's power to 12,000
unlocks an ability
where if Rain's
successfully
dealt damage,
then Yuri could stand
a rear‐guard unit.
And that's exactly
what she wanted.
Miracle Beauty's
skill would activate.
Because when Beauty returns
to the standing position,
she can also stand
the unit behind her.
Taking the hit from Rain
would have opened her up
to another full
strength attack.
Seems like she's got
my sister all figured out.
They sent the right
fighter for the job.
Yeah, but still...
There's no way Yuri
would let us down.
That's just not her style.
Guess you caught on to my
strategy on that last attack.
Watch out.
Now you know how
I'm gonna beat you.
I've heard enough of your talk.
I've got plans of my own.
Activating Amaterasu's skill.
♪
There, I'll get this
trigger when I attack.
I call.
♪
White Hare of Inaba's ability,
sending one card from
my hand to the soul.
♪
She finally managed to get
the Goddess of the
Crescent Moon in there!
With that, her Full Moon
Tsukuyomi will be able
to attack with 11,000
power, as she should be.
Yes, this is Grade 3
girl power in action!
You can do it, Misaki!
Dailady won't be
intercepting this turn.
Tsukuyomi, show her
the strength of the moon!
♪
Supported by White Hare,
Amaterasu attacks Enigman Rain.
♪
I'll stop that!
With Cosmo Fang
and Justice Cobalt!
♪
Her Vanguard's at 30,000!
No way.
I didn't think she'd still
have that much defensive power.
Twin drive check.
Here goes.
♪
Yuri's at 4 damage
and it's my 16,000
against her 30,000.
I know I should give
this trigger to Full Moon,
but there is one
other possibility.
If the second check
is the draw trigger,
then Amaterasu's
skill would activate
and her power
would reach 30,000.
And I'd win.
♪
But the attack would fail
with anything other
than a draw trigger.
Can I afford to risk the
game on a low probability?
No, my team is counting on me
to make the right choice,
and Tsukuyomi
is the safest bet.
Giving all effects to
Goddess of the Full Moon!
I'm gonna make sure
this next attack counts.
♪
‐Hm.
‐Hm?
That is the safer option.
Hm.
♪
Mm.
(gasping)
Choices, choices.
With both those drive triggers
plus Amaterasu's skill,
that would have been enough
to get her past my guards.
You could have
ended this already.
It was a tough decision to make
at this stage of the fight.
Card fights can be won or
lost on the luck of the draw.
You went for the option that had
a better chance for a payoff.
♪
You were just
trying to play it safe,
but now you've gone and
cost yourself the game.
♪
5,000 more power
to Tsukuyomi.
She's charged up
and ready to go.
Attacking Enigman Rain.
I guard.
♪
Another.
Hm, she might just
be able to do this.
♪
And this.
I'm done.
Yep, you sure are.
Though in stopping that,
I've used up my entire hand.
♪
You know what, it's
actually been a lot of fun
playing against you.
But it's about time
you saw my winning image.
♪
I don't worry about
calculating the best option.
I fight my hardest.
And when I do that...
♪
I rely on my cards
to bring me victory.
♪
Draw.
First I'm calling
Miracle Beauty.
♪
With Cosmo Roar's skill,
I give 2,000 power
to Enigman Rain.
♪
Supported by Daisy,
Miracle Beauty
attacks your Vanguard.
(screams)
♪
Boosted by
Magical Police Quilt,
Enigman Rain attacks.
♪
Same deal as before.
If this attack
makes it through,
Miracle Beauty and
Daisy will stand.
Not so fast.
Dream Eater and
Ginger will guard that.
♪
Working so hard to
stop Rain's attack.
‐Too bad.
‐Huh?
There's more than one
way to make a unit stand,
and if my Vanguard
won't do it my deck will.
I just need a stand trigger.
I'll stand Miracle
Beauty and Daisy,
then attack for the win.
♪
I don't calculate
the probabilities,
but I know the right card
will come when I need it.
Twin drive check!
The first...
♪
And the second check.
It can't be.
♪
(gasping)
She really got it?
♪
Why now?
She's amazing.
I wouldn't expect
anything less from her.
That trigger, it's like
she willed it into being.
Not looking good for you.
Miracle Beauty stands
with another 5,000 power.
Then I use her skill
to stand Daisy too.
♪
This is the end.
Miracle Beauty, supported
by Daisy, attacks Amaterasu!
♪
(whimpering)
(explosion)
♪
The winner from Team Caesar,
Yuri Usui!
(cheering)
(sighs)
What a bummer.
I thought Misaki would
take that game for sure.
(whimpering)
Came down to one draw.
Close one, huh?
I mean, you had the
chance to finish me off.
You were able to see
through every move I made,
but I knew that if
I played my hardest
that eventually I'd
get an opportunity.
So if that's what it's
like to be your enemy,
then I guess you and I
will just have to be friends.
Yuri...
Hey, let's put this fight
behind us, what do you say?
(giggles)
♪
Huh?
(crowd "Awws")
♪
Sorry about that.
She was a much bigger handful
than I thought she'd be.
It's okay.
Misaki, you see
the game of Vanguard
better than anyone
I've ever met,
and it's your ability
to make informed decisions
that sets you apart.
Yuri just has her
own way of playing.
You know, the fact that she won
doesn't mean her style's better.
In a card fight, it's important
to stay true to who you are
and how you play.
At least that's how I see it.
♪
Well, folks, this team
battle is going to take
a third and final game
with winner takes all.
Ooh, how lucky for this crowd!
It's gonna be Aichi
Sendou and Kenji Mitsusada.
With the way they've
performed thus far...
Wish me luck, you guys.
Going up against the leader
of Team Caesar is something
I wouldn't wish
on my worst enemy,
but I know you
can do it, bro.
You think so?
Hm.
♪
(gasps)
I wonder if we'll be facing
Team Caesar once again.
Doesn't matter who wins,
we're not leaving here
without our third
straight championship.
♪
I'm sure there are some of
you that think you can win,
but I'm here to bring
you back to reality.
Manipulating and humiliating
people might be fun for you,
but card fighting is
more than that to me.
♪
I've decided to
walk my own path
instead of blindly
following you down yours.
♪
Show me where your path leads.
Can you believe it, Aichi?
First Kamui and Kai,
then Misaki versus Yuri.
Watching card
fights like those,
I'm all fired up.
Let's finish this off in style.
Huh?
Now you are talking
like a champion.
Huh?
(laughing)
Let's make this fight count.
♪
Yeah.
(cheering)
The stage has been set and this
match is about to get underway.
Two great opponents,
winner takes all.
Stand up my Vanguard!
♪
Wingal Brave.
Enigman Flow.
I draw.
Enigman Ripple.
Ride!
♪
I'm activating Flow's skill.
Enigman Ripple's
power boost is in effect.
♪
Over to you.
Draw.
♪
I ride Little Sage Marron.
Moving Wingal Brave.
Next, I call Barcgal.
This allows me to
superior call Flogal.
♪
Supported by Wingal Brave,
Flogal attacks
your Vanguard.
♪
(barks)
Let's go, Marron!
Ha!
♪
My turn's over.
Right.
♪
It's time for Enigman Wave.
Since Ripple is in the soul,
Wave's power goes up.
Calling Masked Police Grander.
Ready?
♪
Grander, in on Marron.
(grunts)
Enigman Wave is coming atcha.
♪
It's your turn.
Oh, man.
They're tied at two damage each.
Tight game, yo.
Better keep your eyes peeled
'cause they're just warming up.
I superior call Llew.
♪
His counterblast.
Barcgal, Flogal, and Llew,
move to the soul.
Arise, my righteous avatar.
Superior ride,
Blaster Blade!
♪
He hasn't called Blaster Blade
like that in a long time.
He's enjoying this.
Yeah, we didn't get to see
this kind of enthusiasm
when he was using
the Shadow Paladins.
Watch out, Aichi's back
and he's stronger than ever.
♪
Hm.
Assemble!
♪
Hm.
So, that's it.
Using Pongal's skill,
I counterblast,
adding Soul Saver
Dragon to my hand.
♪
Now I'm ready.
Koutei, prepare to feel the
wrath of the Royal Paladins
at full force.
♪
I can see right through you.
Kenji has figured him out.
Aichi's battle strategy
is obvious at this point.
To be expected.
Kenji's among the
top in the world.
I don't think he'll
have much trouble
with Aichi Sendou.
Hm.
It doesn't matter who wins
because no one on Earth
can defeat Ren,
and that's a fact.
(chuckles)
Try as I might,
I'm getting no sense
of Aichi using his PSY Qualia.
You'd never be able to
beat someone of this level
without accessing your powers.
Or does the path
you're taking
involve losing
in the semifinals?
What's it gonna be, Aichi?
(chuckles)
♪
You almost had her, Misaki.
Yeah.
But you know,
I think I learned a lot
from fighting Yuri.
Totally, pushing yourself
is the only way to get better.
Koutei knows what
I'm trying to do,
so instead of planning
ahead I'll just hit him
with everything I got.
Next time, The Man
They Call "The Emperor."
Huh?
PSY Qualia's glow.
This can't be.
I...
Aichi, we earned this chance.
Let's not waste it.
Koutei.