(birds chirping)
♪
Meow?
Welcome back to the Vanguard
National Championship.
We've seen a number
of exciting fights today
as all the teams
are struggling
to get to the top of
their respective blocks.
We lost to
Jurassic Army.
I mean, we didn't even
win a single battle.
(cheers)
I'm sorry, guys.
♪
If I'd stayed
with the team,
maybe the results
would've been different.
That's right.
As long as
he's with them,
it's not my team anymore.
It belongs to him.
♪
We have to battle
each of the three teams
in our block,
and only the top two
can move on to
the finals next week.
We can't afford
to lose anymore.
♪
So he'll be playing
in the final rounds?
Couldn't tell you.
Guess you'll have
to make it that far
if you wanna find out.
♪
Ren...
Hey, Kai?
Sorry.
I was wondering if
maybe you could
help me decide the order
for the next fight.
Do whatever you want.
I don't care
where you put me.
Sure thing.
♪
Playing in this tournament
is the first challenge
I've had since realizing what
Vanguard really means to me.
♪
I wanna win,
and then when I do...
♪
They've both got so
much more left to learn
about the game.
Manager?
I, uh, could you take
a look at the order
I made for the next fights?
Your order is fine.
Huh?
But you haven't
seen it yet.
Kai is gonna play
the first game.
Is that right?
Er, right.
Kai will win
the first one,
making it a lot
easier for Misaki and I
to focus on getting the
second win for the team.
That plan probably
seems a bit cowardly.
Yeah, I'd say so.
But I think
it's a great plan.
Huh?
You've taken your
best player and built
your strategy around him
to better your chances.
Now you're starting
to plan your battles
like a real team would.
Hmm.
Thanks.
Okay, so Kai's up first,
Misaki's second,
and Aichi can go
third if need be.
That work for you?
Hmm.
The action hardly
ever stops here
at the Vanguard Nationals.
We're only in the
qualifying rounds,
but we're seeing
tons of great games,
and there's more
yet to come.
It's so exciting!
Next up, we've got
the second round
of matches from block A,
featuring Team Q4
versus Team Muscle Brain.
Yeah!
♪
Both of them lost in
their first pairings.
Whichever team wins here
will still have a chance
of moving on
to the finals.
Taking a quick look at
the roster selection
for Team Q4,
it's cardfighters
Toshiki Kai,
Misaki Tokura,
and Aichi Sendou.
Team Muscle Brain
is going with...
Are these their
real names?
I guess I'll read it.
Cardfighters
Kicking Shoe,
Punch Can,
and Wrestling Snake.
(nervously laughs)
I get it,
it says here
their motto is,
"The strongest brains
are in the strongest bodies."
That explains it.
To each their own.
Time will tell if
having a strong brain
and strong body
are the keys
to winning
the National Tournament.
This match could
be the best yet.
♪
Battling first,
Toshiki Kai
versus Kicking Shoe.
(crowd cheers)
Wanna know what
I do for fun?
No.
I'll tell you anyway.
I like to kick
baseball bats in half,
that's three a day,
over a thousand a year,
and I'm gonna do
the same to you.
‐Ooh, I'm shaking.
‐What?!
(growls)
♪
Please, Kai,
you can do this.
They've got Kai
going first now?
He better win this game.
If Team Q4
goes home winless,
I'm not going back
to Card Capital.
Like you've got
another card shop
to play at.
(chuckles)
In order for him to lose,
something pretty
extraordinary
would have to happen.
Let the battle begin.
(whirring)
‐Now, stand up the vanguard!
♪
A Nova Grappler deck.
I know those cards
inside and out.
If that were me
down there, I...
Hmm.
♪
I ride Blazing Core Dragon
and call Gatling
Claw Dragon.
♪
I'm gonna use
Blazing Core's counterblast.
Iron Tail and Gatling Claw
move from the
rear guard circles
into the soul.
And then...
♪
Lord of destruction
rising through sacrifice,
fly and set yourself
upon my enemy!
Blazing Flare Dragon,
superior ride.
♪
What?!
You went second and you've
got a grade 3 already?
♪
In addition,
I call Nehalem.
Time for my Blazing
Flare Dragon to attack
your King of Sword.
How does he get
so lucky all the time?
Oh.
You can't help
but feel a bit bad
for the other guy.
♪
Next comes Dragonic Overlord
and a powered up Nehalem.
Light him up!
♪
I guard with
Red Lightning!
(shouts)
Five damage already?
Oh, man, why does
he have to do so well?
Final turn.
(growls)
I call Demonic
Dragon Mage, Kimnara.
Counterblast.
Kimnara moves to the soul.
By doing that, I now
get to have one
of your rear guard units
retire from battle.
Tough Boy.
(growls)
By forcing your
unit to retire,
I activated another ability.
Blazing Flare Dragon's
power increases by 3,000.
And next...
I soul blast.
(gasps)
(cracking)
I retire another of
your rear guard units.
Hungry Dumpty.
As you've probably guessed,
Blazing Flare Dragon's
power just went up
by another 3,000.
♪
With support from Conroe,
Blazing Flare attacks.
♪
(screams)
The winner from
Team Q4, Toshiki Kai.
(crowd cheers)
What a win!
Kai just obliterated
his opponent.
Thanks to him,
Q4 has one in the bag.
I hope we see more
battles like that.
That was amazing.
Great work.
The way you won, Kai.
He didn't have a chance.
A win is a win, guys.
Doesn't matter
how you get it.
Kai always
plays it cool
no matter what.
All right, time for us
to start the second match.
Hmm, let's make this
two wins in a row, Misaki.
Hmm.
Hey, you okay, man?
Uh‐oh, bats aren't
breaking today,
it's his heart instead.
Get over it already.
I'll win this match
and even everything up.
(sighs)
That poor little guy.
‐Tough luck.
‐Huh?
They're starting
the next fight.
‐Stand up, my vanguard!
♪
Watch yourself,
you're playing
against a guy who
trains by punching
a bag of sand
a thousand times a day
just for fun.
I ride Tough Boy,
Turboraizer moves.
♪
He's playing
Nova Grapplers too.
Be careful, Misaki.
Hmm.
Where are all
my grade 3s?
I'm activating my
Ichibyoshi's skill.
I get to check the top
five cards of my deck,
and if Goddess of
the Crescent Moon,
Tsukuyomi, is among them,
I can do a superior ride.
♪
So that's the plan?
The other four cards
are going to the bottom
of my deck.
I call Oracle
Guardian, Gemini
and Psychic Bird to battle.
♪
With the support
of Psychic Bird,
Tsukuyomi attacks.
♪
Drive trigger check.
I'm checking for
a damage trigger.
Gemini attacks next.
♪
Another trigger check.
Two damage.
That's a good start.
Hmph.
So that's what
your punch feels like.
Thanks for the lovely gift,
without it,
this next turn
wouldn't be nearly as fun.
I ride King of Sword
and call Karma Queen.
Megacolony?
He's got a mixed deck.
What happens now?
I've never seen these
two clans together.
Ugh.
The Queen counterblasts,
preventing one of
your rear guard units
from standing on
your next turn.
Gemini, you're webbed.
I call Clay‐doll Mechanic.
♪
When Clay‐doll
comes into play,
I can flip over one
card in the damage zone.
I'm calling one more
Clay‐doll Mechanic,
flipping the other card,
and now I've got enough
to pay for Karma's
counterblast next turn as well.
Wow, I didn't expect
him to be this good
with Nova Grapplers.
Still not as good
as me, of course.
Time for you to feel
the power of my punches.
A left hook from Karma Queen!
(screams)
Damage check.
A right cross
from the King.
(grunts)
Drive trigger check.
Damage trigger.
And my Clay‐doll Mechanics
combine for
a powerful uppercut.
(screams)
Checking for
a damage trigger.
Draw trigger.
I draw.
What's the matter,
things not looking good?
♪
(Kai groans)
This'll be the one.
♪
No such luck.
Activating Goddess
of the Crescent Moon,
Tsukuyomi's skill.
I get to look at
the top five cards,
and if one of them is Goddess
of the Half Moon, Tsukuyomi,
then I can do
a superior ride.
It's not there.
Hah.
Too bad, so sad.
Hey, if you want, I'll
let you quit right now.
As if.
‐Huh?
‐You see, the changing
of the moon can't be stopped.
It's completely
outside of your control.
I ride Goddess of
the Half Moon, Tsukuyomi.
You had it all along?
♪
When she comes into play,
if Crescent Moon and
Godhawk are in the soul,
then I can soul charge
another two cards.
Psychic Bird's skill.
I move it to the soul
and draw one card.
Where could it be?
What's the matter?
Can't find what you want?
Gemini moves.
Hey, I'm talking here!
I call two Silent Toms
and Weather Girl, Milk.
With support from Milk,
Tsukuyomi attacks.
Milk's skill adds
an additional 4,000 power.
(wings flap)
Drive trigger check.
♪
I check for
a damage trigger.
Since Gemini can't stand,
all I can do is
target his rear guard.
I attack Karma Queen
with Silent Tom.
(screams)
And my other Silent Tom takes
aim at Clay‐doll Mechanic.
♪
This next move
could change everything.
I ride Gold Rutile.
I call Death Metal Droid
and another Queen.
I think it's time
I taught Silent Tom
a lesson courtesy
of Karma Queen.
Counterblast.
I'm gonna put one
of those bad boys
to sleep.
(gasps)
So, he's using that
annoying ability again.
Here's a quick jab
from Death Metal Droid.
♪
Thanks to my
Gold Rutile's skill,
whenever a rear guard unit
successfully damages you,
I can turn over one
card in the damage zone.
Why isn't she
guarding his attacks?
Maybe she's got
a bunch of powerful
grade 3 units.
Huh?
Turboraizer boosts.
Look, guys.
Here it comes.
My vanguard's gonna hit
you with a corkscrew punch.
Turboraizer's skill
adds an extra 3,000 power.
I'll guard with
Battle Sister, Chocolat.
She was waiting
for the right time.
Seems your attack
was a failure.
(screams)
(grunts)
Gold Rutile is a very
dangerous vanguard,
because if its
attack goes through,
you can then activate
a counterblast
and stand a rear guard.
That means another attack.
Wow!
She realized
the danger she was in
if that thing powered
up with a trigger,
so she nullified the attack.
Checking twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
Hah, critical trigger.
I'm gonna give all the
effects to my Karma Queen.
♪
Get a load
of this punch.
Karma Queen supported
by Clay‐doll Mechanic
deals a body blow.
I'll guard with
Oracle Guardian, Nike,
and intercept
with Silent Tom.
♪
Turboraizer goes
back to the deck.
Yes!
What defending!
Now she gets the
chance to strike back.
Come on, where could it be?
There's no other choice.
Tsukuyomi's skill.
I'm looking at
the top five cards
of my deck.
(gasps)
The first,
the second.
I think you used up
your luck guarding
against those attacks.
♪
It's the Moon Goddess.
Oh, wow.
The third.
The fourth.
It's great,
I adore it!
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks, Mom.
The fifth.
Hmm.
Huh?
♪
No!
How could...
Gentle light
breaking the darkness.
Your smile brings hope
to the entire world.
Goddess of the
Full Moon, Tsukuyomi.
Superior ride.
♪
Goddess of the
Full Moon, Tsukuyomi.
Misaki.
Did she just pull off
two superior rides
in the same card fight?
♪
First I'm activating the
Goddess of the Full Moon's
counterblast,
I draw two cards from
the top of my deck
and put one card
from my hand
into the soul.
♪
And then I
counterblast once more.
Having more cards
in your hand
isn't gonna change
the number of times
you can attack me.
I've only got
three damage.
I just have to
put up the guard,
and then I'll be
swinging the finishing blow.
I call CEO Amaterasu and Gemini.
Supported by Milk,
I'll have Tsukuyomi attack.
♪
Twin drive.
Raw trigger.
Amaterasu gains 5,000 power.
And then I draw.
♪
(grunts)
Damage trigger check.
Amaterasu attacks
with Gemini's support.
I'll use two
Red Lightnings
to guard that attack.
With Gemini's support,
Silent Tom attacks last.
Huh?
(grunts)
♪
That's five damage.
But you just
couldn't end it.
This is gonna be
the last round.
Get ready to feel the
power of my knockout punch.
Knockout, huh?
Huh?
I've got six cards
in hand and a unit
to intercept as well.
Do you really think
you can break through
my defense?
♪
Ken, the odds are bad,
but you can still win.
Fat chance.
They're finished.
Dang, boi!
Karma Queen
exits the field
and I call Death Metal!
Clay‐doll Mechanic
supports Death Metal,
and his counterblast
adds 3,000 power.
Lozenge Magus
says nuh‐uh.
Gold Rutile attacks next.
I guard with Lozenge.
Twin drive check.
It‐‐it's a critical trigger.
I'm giving all
the effects
to my other
Death Metal Droid.
I'll finish it with
this last attack.
With Clay‐doll's support,
I'll have Death
Metal Droid attack you!
I guard with Chocolat.
By discarding one
card from my hand,
I nullify the attack.
Huh?
(whimpers)
Hah!
Misaki's kicking butt.
My final turn.
I attack with Amaterasu
supported by Gemini.
I need to draw a heal
trigger or else...
There it is!
Misaki Tokura from Team Q4!
What an impressive win.
With a score of 2‐0,
Team Q4 is the winner.
Whoa.
I think that was
the best I've ever
seen her play.
Wow.
Goddess of the
Full Moon is a force
to be reckoned with.
Mom, Dad?
I just want you guys
to know I'm doing okay.
And that when I play Vanguard,
it feels like you're
right here with me.
Hmm.
Thanks to that win,
Team Q4 still has
a chance of moving on
to the final round next week.
There's only
one more match up.
We've gotta make it
to the top of our block.
Huh?
But standing in
their way is a team
with an undefeated
record coming into
this final match up.
It's none other than
last year's champions:
Team Asteroid.
♪
(grunts)
That was amazing, Misaki.
Oh, thank you.
Still, it looks like
we've got our work
cut out for us.
Now we're up against
Team Asteroid,
Ren Suzugamori's
handpicked cardfighters.
Well, we've gotta
find a way to beat
these guys and get
Kamui back on the team.
Yeah, let's have Kai
go first again,
then it'll be up
to one of us to get
the second win.
Next time,
The Strongest Team, Asteroid!
Right.
We've all got an image
of winning the first game.
Let's all focus on that.