It's Team Q4 facing off
against the Brilliant Stars.
Only one of these
two can claim
the top ranked
spot in Block C.
We have to forfeit the match.
And here's our
competitor from Q4.
No.
Aichi, you can't!
Yeah.
I feel much better now.
I'm ready to fight.
Though, I must say
I'm disappointed
in your performance today.
Seems Q4 doesn't stand a
chance without me around.
(chuckles)
♪
And here I thought you
were afraid to battle me.
Yeah, right.
Why would I be
afraid of someone
who is so much
weaker than I am?
Huh?
My power, I can feel
it surging through me.
(laughing)
♪
(indistinct chatter)
So Aichi Sendou is
the third fighter?
I thought they'd save the
best for last, you know?
♪
Hey, you guys!
How did Aichi get out there?
He's supposed to be
in bed right now.
Help, Misaki!
(sighs)
Kamui, can you?
♪
It's Aichi Sendou of Team Q4
versus the leader of
Brilliant Stars, Kiriya Bidou!
(screaming)
Bidou is the
hottest one of all.
Give us a smile, Bidou!
I won't be able to
concentrate on the match
with Bidou playing.
How 'bout you Bidou quiet?
You know, some of us
are trying to enjoy
the game over here.
Why'd you say that?
Morikawa!
Uh, please forgive me.
There's no way
this loser's mastered
the Shadow Paladin Deck.
I'm gonna destroy him
and make an example
of him for all to see.
Ren, it's very likely
Kiriya's going
to win this match.
Are you really
going to give him
the vacant spot on our team?
That all depends on
whether he impresses me
with his play or not.
And if he doesn't?
♪
The third and final match!
Fighters, at the ready!
‐Stand up, my Vanguard.
♪
Fullbau!
Hades Ringmaster.
I'm up first, so I'll draw.
I ride Skull Juggler.
And I activate Hades
Ringmaster's skill
for a Soul Charge.
In addition, I use
Skull Juggler's ability
to send one more
card to the soul.
Over to you.
I'll start my turn.
I draw and ride
Blaster Javelin.
♪
By riding Blaster Javelin
on top of Fullbau,
his ability triggers,
and I can search for a copy
of Blaster Dark and
add it to my hand.
There.
So long as Fullbau
is in the soul,
Javelin gains 2,000 power.
I call Black Sage, Charon.
Now Charon attacks
your Vanguard.
(grunting)
(shouting)
Damage check.
It's a heal trigger,
giving 5,000 power
to Skull Juggler.
Blaster Javelin attacks next.
(grunting)
Drive check.
And that's all.
I stand and draw.
First, I ride
Elephant Juggler.
♪
(elephants trumpeting)
(laughing)
♪
I call Barking Cerberus and
Midnight Bunny to rear guard.
♪
With Elephant Juggler's
skill, I Soul Charge.
Attacking Blaster Javelin.
♪
(elephant trumpeting)
Drive trigger check.
♪
Check for a damage trigger.
Cerberus attacks
with support from Bunny.
(growling)
Trigger check.
There it is, draw trigger.
Obviously, the power
goes to Javelin.
♪
Now I activate Midnight
Bunny's CounterBlast.
After boosting a
successful attack,
she can trade places
with a unit in the soul.
Nightmare Doll, Alice
joins the fight.
♪
When she enters
the battlefield,
I get to Soul
Charge once more.
Let's go, Alice!
Crush Charon.
Not so fast!
Arianrhod will
guard that attack.
♪
(whimpers)
You're up, little man.
So Kiriya Bidou only has
a Grade Two Vanguard.
And he's able to call
a Grade Three unit
out of the soul to attack.
This battle is
really heating up.
All right!
Seeing Grade Threes
makes me feel alive!
You don't say.
Show us how it's
done, handsome!
You're such an
amazing player!
I can't get enough!
Let's see that
gorgeous smile!
(cheering)
♪
Hey, something's wrong.
It's not like him to ignore
us when we call to him.
I stand and draw.
I can tell how
much you hate me.
So what gives?
I've never done anything to
deserve your anger, have I?
It just doesn't make sense.
Why did Ren give you the
Shadow Paladins instead of me?
(chuckles)
What's so funny?
The answer's obvious.
I was given the deck because
Ren knows I'm stronger.
You're what?
I'll prove you wrong!
Today, in front of Ren
and the whole world,
I'll teach you a lesson
in true strength!
Well, one of us
will learn a lesson.
You're the light
and I'm the darkness.
Huh?
And no matter how
bright the light,
the darkness will
always prevail.
Rise up from the
shadows, Blaster Dark!
♪
(gasping)
(chuckles)
I don't like it.
(sighs)
He's a totally
different person now.
I guess that's just part
of being a moody teenager.
Wouldn't you say so?
Earth to Kourin.
♪
Aichi.
Because I have
Javelin in the soul,
Blaster Dark's power
is increased by 1,000.
Charon moves back.
Then, I call
Skull Witch, Nemain.
Nemain's CounterBlast.
Discarding a Shadow Paladin
unit from my hand,
I draw two more cards.
I call Knight of Darkness,
Rugos to rear guard.
♪
First, Rugos attacks.
(shouts)
Rainbow Magician
will stop that attack.
(shouts)
Blaster Dark is up next.
I check for a drive trigger.
It's a heal trigger.
That's 5,000 power to Nemain.
And I recover one damage.
(shouts)
Damage trigger check.
With Charon's support,
Skull Witch, Nemain attacks.
♪
(laughs)
(grunts)
(groans)
Damaging Bidou and
scoring a heal trigger,
Aichi Sendou makes it clear
Team Q4 isn't going
down without a fight.
I stand and draw.
I'll start my turn by riding
Dark Illusionist, Robert.
♪
Allow me to show you
Robert's skill.
Soul Charge!
Then I check the top card of
my deck and leave it there.
♪
Sit back and enjoy
the Pale Moon Circus.
Alice, attack Nemain.
♪
Huh?
(shouts)
CounterBlast.
I move Alice to the soul
and I return
Bunny to the field.
(laughs)
Now Robert's attack.
I don't guard.
Let's see what the
Twin Drive has in store.
A draw trigger.
That's 5,000
power to Cerberus.
And the second check.
Huh!
♪
With a little
boost from Bunny...
Ah!
Cerberus charges.
I don't guard.
♪
Bunny's CounterBlast.
By moving Midnight Bunny
back into the soul,
I can have Alice
return to battle.
♪
Once more, Alice.
I don't guard.
Hmm.
♪
Alice to Bunny,
Bunny to Alice,
what a strategy!
The final match
keeps getting hotter.
And after that big round,
Aichi's damage has just
shot through the roof!
(squealing)
Don't let up,
you're almost there!
Come on, Aichi!
You gotta start guarding.
This is no time
to show off, okay?
The way he's acting,
he really doesn't seem
too worried about it.
That's just great.
He's probably out of
options or something.
Cats.
Where?
No, he's acting like a cat.
Have you ever seen one
force a mouse into a corner?
They lose interest once
they know the fight's over.
‐Huh?
♪
Ha.
I stand and draw.
Here comes Phantom
Blaster Dragon.
Ride.
♪
As long as I have
Blaster Dark in the soul,
Phantom Blaster Dragon's
power goes up by 1,000.
♪
Next, I call Dark Mage,
Badhabh Caar to the field.
♪
Using Badhabh Caar's skill,
the top card of my deck
is a Shadow Paladin unit.
I call it to the rear guard.
As luck would have it,
it's another Badhabh Caar.
I'll use that ability again.
♪
It's time.
Phantom Blaster
Dragon's CounterBlast.
(groans)
(shouts)
With his sacrifice...
my Phantom Blaster Dragon
gains an additional 10,000
power during this turn,
and plus one critical.
♪
Calling Blaster Dark and
Arianrhod to rear guard.
♪
Rugos attacks Cerberus.
(grunts)
(growls)
Spiral Master will guard that.
(shouts)
Supported by Arianrhod,
watch out for
Phantom Blaster Dragon.
♪
That's 28,000 power!
This is it, how will
Kiriya respond?
Hmm, is that the
best you can do?
I expected better.
By discarding one card,
my Hades Hypnotist
will nullify the attack.
A Hades Hypnotist in his hand.
The one card that can
save him right now.
Take him out for us!
That's too bad.
I thought I had you cornered.
Now there's no reason for me
to guard your next attack,
so fire away.
Well, that's nice of you.
Gaining support from Charon,
Blaster Dark attacks!
♪
(grunts)
Is that it?
He may have given
you his deck,
but you're not nearly
skilled enough to wield it.
I hate to tell
you, little man,
but you're way out
of your league.
♪
Huh?
He's watching me.
Ren's watching.
(sighs)
I am gonna end
this right now.
It's the final turn.
There it is.
He calls final turn!
(crowd chatter)
Yes!
(sighs)
Please watch and enjoy
as I destroy Aichi Sendou,
and once he's finished,
the world will know that
I've earned the right
to fight beside you
on Team Asteroid.
All right, little man,
let's do this.
I'm using Robert's skill
to Soul Charge from
the top of my deck.
I call Bicorn
and Midnight Bunny.
First, boosted by Bicorn,
Nightmare Doll, Alice attacks.
♪
My Darkside
Trumpeter blocks that.
♪
Hmph!
Ah!
♪
You don't know
when you're beaten.
With support from Midnight
Bunny, here it comes!
It's the end of the
line, Aichi Sendou.
Grim Reaper guards.
Huh?
And Blaster Dark is
going to intercept.
♪
No.
It can't be.
No way.
All right!
His final turn
didn't work out.
Ha‐ha, what a loser!
Morikawa, you could
at least pretend
to feel bad for the guy.
What's the point?
And here I thought
you were gonna make
this match interesting.
Hmm.
But I guess that's
all you're capable of.
What did you say?
Now Ren knows
that you're weak.
(gasps)
♪
Ren saw everything.
(exhales)
Cerberus, take out
Rugos for me.
Gah!
It's fine, it'll be okay.
I just need to
survive this turn.
I can't lose in front of Ren.
I can't!
I‐‐I end my turn.
Kai, I know that, somewhere,
you must be watching this.
I'd like to show you
my true strength.
Final turn.
Huh?
Oh, Aichi Sendou declares
a final turn of his own!
‐What?
‐Didn't he learn anything
by watching that
last guy fail?
I stand and draw.
I call Grim Reaper
and Abyss Healer.
CounterBlast.
Now, Phantom Blaster Dragon!
(gasps)
(shouts)
♪
No, you can't!
Phantom Blaster Dragon's power
just went up by 10,000,
as well as plus one critical.
I'm stronger
than I used to be...
...but I'm still
not there, am I?
I have to become
stronger for you,
otherwise you'll never
respect me, right?
I'm sending Dark Metal Dragon
to attack your Cerberus.
(gasps)
Hold on, hear me out.
Impressing Ren means
everything to me,
so please don't beat me
in front of him, okay?
I've got to get stronger.
(whimpers)
More.
Please, don't do this to me!
Feel my power!
With support from Arianrhod,
Phantom Blaster
Dragon attacks!
(laughs)
♪
(stammers)
Ah!
♪
(groans)
Oh, no!
♪
(whimpers)
(claps)
(stammers)
The winner is Aichi Sendou.
Team Q4 has clinched
the top spot in Block C!
Oh, wow, he actually lost.
I guess he wasn't
that cool after all.
You know, that Aichi
Sendou is pretty dreamy,
don't you guys think?
Yeah, he's a total heartthrob.
It figures.
Hey, is that really
our friend down there?
Hmm.
(crowd cheers)
(panting)
Well done, Aichi.
Looks like you've
lost another one, Kai.
And as for whoever
you just defeated...
Hmm, I can't even
remember his name.
Oh, well.
That's amazing, he gets
better every time he plays!
Kourin?
Ugh!
♪
(sighs)
Hurry up before
it's too late.
Stop him.
Sendou just crushed that guy.
Makes you feel bad for
picking on him, huh?
Maybe I can get
his autograph.
Aichi hardly says
anything when he's in class.
Has he always
been that intense?
‐Don't know.
Aichi, I'll save you.
I promise.
♪
Kiriya Bidou was supposed
to fill the vacant spot
on Team Asteroid's
number one squad.
He was a lot better than
Kyou, that's for sure.
It looked like a tough fight,
but the victory
was overwhelming.
Kai, are you watching?
I'm strong enough to
beat Team Caesar now,
maybe even Ren.
Next time, "Kai's Battle."
We've got time off
before the finals.
I need to card
fight some more.
I need it to satisfy the
hunger of my winning image.