(cheering)
Man, this day
keeps getting worse.
That big jerk just had to
win his match, didn't he?
And against a member of
Team Asteroid, no less.
(cheering)
But...
♪
Imagine it, this battle's about
to get a whole lot scarier.
Now ride the Vanguard!
♪
Flames of destruction
reducing this world to ashes.
Dragonic Overlord.
♪
I call Dual Axe Archdragon.
Activating Overlord's
counterblast.
♪
With support from Bahr,
Overlord attacks
your Devil Summoner.
Drive check.
Eternal flame.
(roars)
♪
After destroying
a rear‐guard unit,
my Overlord stands in
preparation for the next attack.
I‐‐I can't stop this one.
(shouts)
That was an amazing fight.
♪
(whimpering)
Seriously, I quit the
team today of all days?
♪
Listen up.
There's no way you'll
be able to beat me.
Not with that
deck you're using.
♪
Who does she
think she is
saying my deck
isn't good enough?
♪
Hm.
There's more to me than that.
I'll just have to read her
moves and perfect my strategy.
I won't lose.
♪
And begin!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
♪
I'm counting on you, Asaka.
We wouldn't want a
repeat of Kyou's mistake.
♪
(chuckles)
(whimpering)
♪
Serves him right.
I call Milk, Tsukuyomi
attacks, draw trigger.
The power goes to Milk.
Huh?
Supported by Psychic Bird,
Milk attacks Midnight Bunny.
Ha!
(screams)
Checking for a damage trigger.
The second match between
these two great teams
is already underway.
Team Q4's Misaki Tokura
is leading the race early
after dealing her
opponent two damage.
She's off to a
good start, guys.
I just know she
can win this battle.
If that happens,
Team Q4 will be
moving on to the
finals next week.
Well, looks like I'll
be taking my turn now.
From this point on,
the Pale Moon Circus
is going to show
exactly how tricky we can be.
Ride Crimson Beast Tamer.
♪
Hm.
Call.
♪
Now sit back and
enjoy our performance.
♪
A Pale Moon deck.
It's my first time
fighting against one,
but I'm familiar
with these cards.
♪
I need to stay one
step ahead of her
and the game is mine.
Okay, Skull Juggler,
show her how talented you are.
His skill is a soul charge.
♪
Worse yet, with Crimson Beast
Tamer as her Vanguard,
if she gets another Crimson
Beast Tamer in the soul,
its power goes up by 3,000.
Building the soul
quickly is a trademark
of the Pale Moon Circus.
I need to be careful.
♪
Skull Juggler, I want you
to attack her Vanguard.
Dream Eater will guard that.
♪
Crimson Beast
Tamer's coming next.
♪
Drive trigger check.
(screams)
Damage trigger.
With support from Bicorn, go.
Barking Cerberus.
♪
That's enough for now.
They seem pretty
evenly matched so far.
So far.
Well, I'm not sold yet.
There's something
about that Asteroid girl.
What's she planning?
Be careful, Misaki.
♪
This is fine, her moves
are pretty standard.
I draw.
Hm.
Tsukuyomi's skill.
I look at the top
five cards of my deck.
If one of them is Goddess
of the Half Moon...
♪
Superior ride, Goddess
of the Half Moon Tsukuyomi.
♪
With Crescent Moon and
Ichibyoshi in the soul,
I can soul charge two cards.
This is exactly what I needed.
Next turn, I can ride
Goddess of the Full Moon.
I call Silent Tom
and attack with him.
(gunfire)
(screams)
I swing in with Tsukuyomi.
♪
I check.
(screams)
With support from
Psychic Bird, Milk attacks.
Spiral Master guards!
Yeah!
Fine, your turn.
Now, let me introduce you
to the star performers
of the Pale Moon Circus.
I release him
from the chains that bind.
This beast is tamed no longer.
Ride Barking Manticore!
♪
A Grade 3, huh?
That one lets you
draw an extra card.
♪
Then you get to choose
a card from your hand
and place it in the soul.
Worse yet, if there's a Crimson
Beast Tamer in the soul,
it gets an extra 3,000 power.
♪
What's wrong?
Were you expecting my
Grade 3s to be weaklings?
The Pale Moon Circus has
the strongest performers
and the best tricks too.
Her soul is growing,
and now this Grade 3?
She's good, as expected.
Skull Juggler, move to the back.
Calling Nightmare Doll Alice.
♪
Ah!
Manticore, attack Tsukuyomi.
(snarling)
Twin Drive, first check.
♪
Second check.
Critical trigger.
5,000 power to Alice.
Manticore gains
the critical effect.
(screams)
♪
With Skull Juggler's support,
Nightmare Doll Alice attacks.
♪
I have to stop you.
Chocolat will guard.
(gunfire, shrieking)
♪
Supported by Bicorn,
Cerberus attack Silent Tom!
♪
We can't let Tom
spoil the fun,
especially with what I
have planned for later.
(grunts)
♪
What's she up to?
No, it doesn't matter.
She's at four damage,
so I'll just
finish her this turn.
I draw.
Activating Tsukuyomi's skill.
Checking the top
five cards of my deck.
If Goddess of the Full Moon
Tsukuyomi is in there...
She isn't.
Hm.
I ride.
Watch me, Mom, Dad.
Light breaks
through the shadows.
Your smile brings hope
in my darkest hour.
Goddess of the
Full Moon Tsukuyomi.
♪
Yeah!
This is her chance
to end the battle.
That's your best unit, huh?
Activating Psychic Bird's skill.
♪
Tsukuyomi's counterblast.
I counterblast once more.
♪
My hand's gotten a lot bigger.
Now I just need to call
out my most powerful units.
(giggles)
♪
Moving Milk back,
I call CoCo, Wiseman,
Milk, and Gemini.
♪
With support from Milk,
Scarlet Witch CoCo attacks.
♪
Ha!
All right!
Five damage.
Just one to go.
With support from Milk,
Goddess of the Full
Moon Tsukuyomi attacks.
♪
My Dynamite Juggler
steps in to defend.
And one more to be safe.
Oh yeah!
♪
(snarling)
(screams)
Tsukuyomi's attack has been...
♪
(laughing)
With Gemini's support,
Wiseman attacks you.
♪
Candy Clown will guard.
Every unit you've
guarded with, Grade 0.
So that's why you
destroyed my Silent Tom.
That's right.
My Grade 0s
are so talented,
I couldn't let Silent
Tom ruin their fun.
She's been one step
ahead of me this whole time.
Well, are you ready
to see the grand finale
of our performance?
The Pale Moon Circus
puts on a show
its victims are
sure to remember.
Cerberus retires.
I call Midnight Bunny
and Nightmare Doll Alice.
Wait, Cerberus and Alice
are equal in terms of power,
so why switch them?
Took you long enough.
When Alice's attack hits,
she trades places
with an ally in the soul.
And when Midnight Bunny
supports a successful attack,
she also trades
places with the unit,
unleashing the
soul's true power.
Savage creatures
lurk within the darkness
that is the soul,
and there's no way
for you to escape them.
Cower before the Pale Moon's
ultimate technique,
the Deadly Shadow Beasts.
This ruthless method of
finishing off her opponents
is why we call
her the assassin.
Nightmare Doll Alice,
attack Tsukuyomi with
support from Bicorn!
♪
(whimpers)
I won't let you.
♪
With Midnight Bunny's support,
Manticore attacks.
20,000 power?
I don't guard.
Twin drive check.
First.
Second.
No way!
She got a draw trigger.
I add 5,000 power to the
Alice that hasn't attacked yet
and I draw.
(shrieks)
Assassin lurking
in the shadows.
Embrace the spotlight.
Midnight Bunny's counterblast!
♪
Bunny moves to the soul.
And coming out, I superior
call Crimson Beast Tamer.
♪
This useless Alice
leaves the field.
With support
from Skull Juggler,
Nightmare Doll
Alice attacks.
♪
I guard with Dream
Eater and Silent Tom.
Wiseman intercepts.
♪
Reading your
opponent's next move,
it's the only way an
assassin can survive.
I knew just what
you were going to do.
You were so desperate
to stay alive,
you used all your defensive
units to block my third attack,
didn't you?
♪
Then there's no
way of stopping
my Crimson Beast Tamer from
finishing this game, right?
♪
I'd like to dedicate
this final attack
to a viewer of
today's performance,
a man like no other,
the amazing Ren.
♪
Hm.
Ha.
Go!
Fight Crimson Beast Tamer!
(giggles)
Yah!
♪
(giggling)
Ha!
(screams)
♪
The winner,
Asaka Narumi.
It was easy to tell you
were trying to read my moves,
but you've still
got a lot to learn.
Ha, you can't just
outthink your opponent.
You need the better deck.
(cheering)
You aren't ready
to play at this level.
(laughs)
(cheering)
♪
‐That's a first for you.
‐Hm?
It's not your style
to taunt an opponent
after the battle has ended.
‐Yeah?
‐Maybe you're upset
it didn't go as easily
as you expected it to.
(grunts)
♪
I'm sorry, Mom, Dad.
I hate to think like
this, but she's right.
I still have a lot
to learn about the game
and the deck
you've made for me.
♪
I...
I'm not the player
I'd hoped to be.
♪
Misaki...
She lost her match.
It was like that girl
was toying with her.
Is this how Team Asteroid
treats their opponents?
And I'm gonna have
to fight that guy?
♪
(whimpers)
I can do it, I can
do it, I can do it.
♪
There's nothing
to worry about.
You're gonna win
your matches, no problem.
That's right, no problem.
I'm not gonna win
this battle for myself.
I have to do
this for the team.
♪
Hm.
The final match is up next.
Fighters, please get ready.
(cheering)
It sure was easy getting
past the elimination round.
Yeah, but in the
finals next week
we'll be facing off
with Team Asteroid again.
Well, we all need
to remain focused.
Kamui, where are you?
(grunting)
Aw, man.
I'm sure running into
a lot of people today.
Hey, watch it, buddy.
Do you just go around
knocking over kids for fun?
No, I'm really sorry.
Well, you're
quick to apologize.
It was my fault.
I feel so bad.
Did you get hurt?
No.
That was a nasty bump.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey, you're from Team Caesar.
Huh.
You look familiar too.
Yeah, we didn't get a
chance to play last year,
but I'm Gouki Daimonji
from Team Handsome
and this is my little sister.
I'm Nagisa.
I'm Emi Sendou.
Sendou.
I get it now.
The Kamui you were shouting
about must be the one
from Team Q4.
Huh?
You've met my future husband?
Do you know where he is?
Sorry, we ran into
him a little earlier,
but we haven't
seen him since then.
That's too bad.
I wanna find out who that
little twerp thinks he is.
Disappearing on the day of
the national tournament is low.
Then you don't know the
reason that he ran away?
The reason?
They're his friends.
I don't see a problem
with telling them.
Yeah, they should at least
know why he's gone missing.
Hm.
Tell us!
Well, we were talking
about the tournament.
All right, the Block
A elimination round
with Team Asteroid
versus Team Q4.
The series is
going three games?
My, oh, my, how exciting.
I couldn't agree more.
Team Asteroid's player Tetsu
apparently doesn't
have a last name.
I love the simplicity.
He'll be facing off against
Team Q4's Aichi Sendou.
The climax is
just over the horizon.
(cheering)
I'm gonna redraw.
I'll do the same.
(cheering)
I redrew and I still
don't have a Grade 2?
I guess I'll have
to make it work.
(whimpering)
The third match begins.
Stand up, Vanguard!
♪
(gasping)
Now that's what I
call a battlefield.
This guy must be using
a Dark Irregulars deck.
Vermillion Gatekeeper!
Barcgal!
I'm up first.
I draw.
I ride Little Sage Marron.
Barcgal, you move back.
And now Barcgal
uses his skill
to superior call
Flogal from the deck.
♪
I ride Prisoner Beast.
Activating Vermillion
Gatekeeper's skill,
Soul Charge.
Prisoner Beast and
Alluring Succubus called.
♪
I activate Succubus's
skill, Soul Charge.
And then I call
Nightmare Baby.
♪
Prisoner Beast, go.
Attack Marron.
(roars)
I don't guard.
(grunts)
I check for a damage trigger.
My Vanguard Prisoner
Beast attacks next.
I don't guard.
Now I'm checking
the drive trigger.
(shouts)
Hey, the fight just started.
He shouldn't be getting
pummeled this bad already.
♪
Supported by Nightmare Baby,
Alluring Succubus attacks.
I don't guard.
♪
Hm!
Ha!
I check for a damage trigger.
He got a critical trigger.
It won't help him.
What rotten timing.
It's your turn.
I stand and draw.
♪
I didn't take all
that damage for nothing.
I need it.
It's a risky move,
but if I don't find a way
to strengthen my units,
there's no chance
of beating this guy.
♪
My team's fate rests
on my shoulders.
Kai, Misaki, Kamui.
I...
I'll win this for us.
♪
Misaki, you were doing
so well in your battle.
‐But still...
‐I lost.
She was better
than me in every way.
Now I have to fight Tetsu.
You face me without
fear in your heart,
but even so, you're
no match for the General.
I‐‐I have to win this.
Kamui, watch me.
Next time:
Demon World General.
I can't imagine the outcome.
There's too much happening.