♪
It's a pressure cooker of
excitement here at the finals
of the Vanguard
National Tournament.
And let me tell you,
there's no love lost
between these
two competitors.
At the end of
the fifth turn,
both players are
sitting at three damage.
We've witnessed waves
of brutal attacks
and stunning defensive moves.
The ups and downs,
the back and forths.
Oh, I'm getting dizzy
just thinking about it.
Winning this game would
give Team Asteroid
its third straight
National Championship.
On the other hand,
Team Q4 seems determined
to win this and force
the final match.
Oh, if only I could
see the future!
♪
They think this
game is close?
Fools!
Once they see
my next turn,
they'll be singing
another tune.
Here we go.
Hmm.
Now, what we've
all been waiting for.
The Pale Moon Circus
is proud to present...
the third act!
Hah.
♪
Ride Barking Manticore.
Thanks to his skill,
I can draw and place
one card from my
hand in the soul.
I call Barking Cerberus
and Nightmare Doll, Alice.
♪
Cerberus, show her
what you're made of!
♪
My Dream Eater
will guard that.
(elephant trumpets)
With a boost from Turquoise,
Manticore is
attacking your vanguard.
And since Crimson Beast
Tamer is in the soul,
both units receive
3,000 power bringing
this attack up to 22,000.
(growls)
I don't guard.
Twin drive check.
The first...
and the second.
A critical trigger online.
The power goes to Alice
with my Manticore
taking the critical.
(shrieks)
♪
Oh no, one more damage
and she's done for.
Get your head
in the game!
Q4 needs you
to win this thing!
Do you honestly think
I don't know that?
♪
With the support
of Skull Juggler,
Alice attacks Amaterasu.
(sighs)
♪
Battle Sister, Ginger,
and Goddess of the Crescent Moon
will stop that.
♪
(sighs)
Good, she's safe now.
Hardly.
Misaki's got herself
in a lot of trouble.
♪
I assume you can
see what's happening.
Five damage to my three?
You have to win
the game this turn,
otherwise this circus
will have no problem
finishing you off.
Hold off on
the victory dance.
Oh my, I should've
figured you'd fight
to the very end.
Hmm.
How fun.
Hold onto that
bitter smile
for as long as you can.
I'll crush you
slowly if I have to.
Cheers will ring
through the arena
in honor of
the Pale Moon Circus.
Well?
I draw.
With Amaterasu's skill.
then I get to check
the top card of my deck.
Hm?
♪
Placing this one
on the bottom,
Oracle Guardian, Gemini,
and Crescent Moon, Tsukuyomi
to rear guard.
♪
Boosted by Gemini,
Oracle Guardian, Red Eye
attacks Nightmare Doll, Alice.
(howls)
What?
Why isn't she going
for the rear guard?
She should be trying
to finish this game, yo.
I know, and she's
not even aiming
to clear out an intercept.
Alice is a grade 3.
If she doesn't get
her act together,
we'll be going home
earlier than expected.
I get it.
She's setting up
for next turn.
So, she's picking off
the rear guard in an effort
to limit the number of attacks
that come back her way.
Risky, but will it pay off?
Wow.
Is this a card fight
or a game of hide and seek?
♪
Whatever.
Red Eye's skill will let her
SoulCharge if he gets through.
An eighth card in the soul
could leave me open
to a MegaBlast.
♪
It's clear.
Protect me
Dynamite Juggler.
♪
Oh great, her
attack did nothing.
It's okay,
she's got a plan.
Yeah, I'm starting
to understand
why that blue‐haired witch
plays for Team Asteroid.
(whimpers)
It'll be just fine.
Huh?
Misaki will find
a way to win.
And when she does...
Ren's all mine.
Uh, yeah.
Hmm, we've got this.
With her out there,
it's a lock.
Gaining support from
Goddess of the Crescent Moon,
Amaterasu attacks
your Manticore.
I won't guard that.
Twin drive.
First check...
second check.
Not a single
drive trigger.
♪
I check for
a damage trigger.
Nothing there this time.
Coming for Alice once more
with Battle Maiden, Tagitsuhime.
Using her skill,
I add 3,000 power.
(grunts)
Oh dear!
Someone sure is
scared of my play toy.
Does the rest of
your team know
what a fraidy cat you are?
You guarding or not?
Speed it up.
I don't guard.
(moans)
♪
(shrieks)
My turn's over.
(sighs)
Looks like I won't
need to sleep with
a night light tonight.
Huh?
Now that she's defeated
that big, creepy doll,
it won't be able
to show up in my dreams,
'cause that'd be so freaky.
Huh?
What kind of a teenager
still has a night light?
The kind that's
afraid of dolls, yo.
Not all dolls!
(chuckles)
Well, it is
a Nightmare Doll,
so I think we can cut
Morikawa some slack
on this one.
Hmm?
She has her opponent
at four damage.
But if Misaki lets even
one more attack through‐‐
Yeah.
(growling)
Q4 could lose here.
Huh?
Draw.
Let's end this.
The curtain rises
on the grand finale
of today's stunning performance.
A cracking whip heralds
the bringer of the storms.
Ride, Mistress Hurricane!
♪
There are over eight
cards in the soul.
She gains a thousand power.
Witness...
Hurricane's CounterBlast.
Back for an encore,
Nightmare Doll, Alice!
♪
(gasps)
The doll!
(groans)
Ah!
She's come to take me off.
Misaki, do something.
Asaka's planning to unleash
the Deadly Shadow Beast.
Looks like.
I'm the Assassin,
at least that's what
my teammates call me.
Anyone I fight
becomes my mark.
And since joining
Team Asteroid,
this deck has never
allowed an opponent
to escape my grasp.
♪
Hmm.
So frightened
she can't even speak.
I'm gonna enjoy
taking her down.
Huh?
♪
Toshiki Kai?
This is a surprise.
After that embarrassing
loss to Ren, I didn't
think he'd have
the guts to show up.
♪
‐Stand up, the vanguard!
You can't change destiny.
Oh?
♪
There's always next time.
This power will give me
everything I could ever want.
And there's not a person
on earth who can stop me.
Not one.
(laughs)
♪
(grunts)
Loser.
Ren doesn't care
about Kai anymore
or Aichi Sendou,
he's done with them.
♪
Now he can finally
turn his attention to me.
♪
Winning this game
will end the match,
and bring even more glory
to the name of "Asteroid."
Then I'll take my
place at his side.
The only thing
in my way is one
measly point of damage.
Here I come!
♪
Hmm.
Midnight Bunny
to rear guard.
♪
I've got both
Alice's attack
and Bunny's boost,
either of which will
let me attack again
if they succeed.
Hope you're ready
'cause these two units
are about to steal the show.
With a boost from
Skull Juggler,
Alice attacks
your vanguard!
(groans)
Lozenge Magus
will guard that.
♪
Such a tough face
for someone barely
hanging on.
But how long can
you keep that up?
The weather forecast
is calling for a hurricane!
Battle Sister, Chocolat.
Dropping one card
to nullify it.
(sighs)
Struggling to stay alive.
Your fate lies
on the twin drive.
First check...
second check.
It's Skyhigh Walker.
A stand trigger.
(gasps)
Stand once more, Alice!
Giving her
the power as well.
Even after guarding
this next attack,
there's another
one to deal with.
Now, the Nightmare Doll marches!
Crush her dreams
once and for all.
♪
Chocolat will guard.
(shrieks)
♪
Huh?
What?
She used two complete
guards in one turn?
Well, that's it for Asaka.
Yeah.
This turn's done.
‐This game.
‐Huh?
The opportunity
to win the match
just passed her by.
Huh?
Cerberus attacks
your vanguard
with a boost from Bunny.
(growls)
Tagitsuhime,
Red Eye, intercept.
No way.
She managed to defend
her way through all
four attacks.
That's amazing.
She really did it.
Go girl, yo!
It's "You go, girl."
Yowza.
I never stopped
believing in you.
(growls)
I bet it makes
you pretty happy
to embarrass me in front
of everyone like that, huh?
Misaki Tokura,
it's obvious
you're not the same
person I beat last time.
Still, I'm the better
card fighter and there's
no way I'll lose to you.
Take your turn!
And once I defend
against these attacks,
I'll be sure
to finish you off.
Hmph.
Uh‐huh.
You probably will.
But who says you're gonna
live through this turn.
♪
(growls)
I stand and draw.
♪
Just a little more.
Wait, what's she up to?
In our last fight,
you were able to stay
two steps ahead of my moves
the whole time.
But now, the
tables have turned.
Planning a comeback?
No chance.
The Oracle Think Tank
has assured my victory.
♪
A gentle light breaks
through the darkness
following me down
my chosen path.
Behold the Rising
of the Full Moon,
Tsukuyomi!
♪
Activating CounterBlast.
Pay two to draw two.
♪
Moving one card from
my hand to the soul.
And then I activate
her CounterBlast again.
(gasps)
Nicely done.
This was her plan all along.
♪
(Asaka shudders)
Calling Psychic Bird.
Using his skill...
...I SoulCharge and draw.
Once again,
calling Psychic Bird,
same as before.
Another draw.
♪
Dark Cat to rear guard.
Okay, listen up.
♪
When Dark Cat enters
the battlefield,
as long as my vanguard is from
the Oracle Think Tank clan,
both fighters
get to draw.
I'll be drawing one card,
and you're welcome
to do the same.
All right.
♪
It's here.
Hmph.
Calling Evil‐Eye
Princess, Euryale.
Check out this ability.
Take one of the cards
in your hand...
bind it.
(gasps)
♪
That's one less card
for you to use this turn.
Ready?
I call...
a second Evil‐Eye Princess.
(gasps)
Seriously?
That is cold‐blooded.
♪
Bind!
(growls)
Stop acting like you're
gonna finish me off this turn!
I'm still sitting
at four damage
and there's no way
I'm gonna let two
of your attacks
get to my vanguard!
Two attacks?
Hardly.
I'm gonna finish you off
with only one.
(gasps)
♪
I'll show you if
you don't believe me.
I'm attacking
Mistress Hurricane
with Goddess of the
Full Moon, Tsukuyomi.
♪
18,000 power.
No choice.
Candy Clown and
Turquoise Beast Tamer
will defend the vanguard.
Are you ready?
Twin drive.
♪
Battle Sister, Ginger!
It's a critical trigger
going straight to my vanguard.
Hmm?
Your deck‐‐you can't!
Godhawk, Ichibyoshi,
Goddess of the Crescent Moon,
Goddess of the Half Moon,
and Amaterasu.
Because I use their
skills I was able to place
16 cards on the
bottom of my deck.
So now I know...
...every draw from
this point on!
(growls)
Evil girl.
She's memorized the
remaining cards in her deck?
♪
(groans)
And the second check?
It's another
critical trigger,
giving all the effects
to Goddess of the Full Moon.
♪
It's too strong to stop.
A double critical!
♪
How did this happen?
The Oracle Think Tank helps
me peer into the future.
You didn't realize...
I was in complete
control of this battle.
(shudders)
The winner from Team Q4,
Misaki Tokura!
Misaki!
She did it, guys!
We're back in this, yeah!
Your parents would
be so proud, Misaki.
(sighs)
You rock!
You just saved the day!
What an epic fight!
You really came
through for us.
Okay, you guys are
laying it on pretty thick.
Yeah, well that's
because we mean it.
Kamui's right.
You got us the win we need.
Q4 has a chance
to take this thing.
Thanks, you guys.
But it's too
early to celebrate.
Your turn.
Yeah.
Hmm.
♪
Revenge, served cold.
(crowd cheers)
Huh?
I failed you, Ren.
♪
All I ever wanted
was to be his
number one fighter.
♪
To stand at his side...
You gave it everything you had.
♪
You're not mad at me?
I'm actually glad
you lost your fight,
because now I get
to destroy Aichi.
♪
(mischievous laugh)
Unfortunately,
losing isn't tolerated.
You can no longer
play on my team.
(Asaka shudders)
Not so fast.
Huh?
Don't forget your deck.
(cries)
♪
There's no need
to run away.
What?
If I stay, I'm just
gonna cry my way
through the final match.
Your love of card fighting
is eclipsed by Ren's shadow.
Are you telling
me yours isn't?
In this match,
we might finally see it.
Ren.
I've always wondered if
someone could beat him.
(gasps)
Huh?
And with Kai out of the way,
Aichi Sendou is
the only person
that stands a chance
of stopping him.
♪
(chuckles)
Way to go, Misaki!
Now let me in there.
What an ending we'll
give this tournament.
The Battle of
Psyqualia is chosen.
Though the outcome is obvious.
I will not use
that power.
I came here today
to face you with
my own strength,
like Kai did.
Then it's as I feared,
this fight will be a bore.
Ren...
Next time,
Two Powers, Side‐by‐Side.
His image,
he's too good.
I don't know if I can
win this by myself.