Gancelot's skill,
I search for Blaster Blade
and add it to my hand.
Blaster Blade, huh?
Don't you remember?
It's your avatar.
Oh, I know,
but I don't care
about that card anymore
because now I've got a
much stronger avatar.
Wrong.
Hm?
It doesn't matter if
you threw it away or not,
your avatar is always
going to be Blaster Blade.
Hmph!
Aichi, the time has
come for me to teach you
what true strength really is.
All right!
Your quest for
power ends now.
♪
(gurgling)
Please tell me you're not
making that coffee for Ren.
Sure am.
He is one of our most
important customers.
I don't get you.
Listen, Ren is among
the few fighters
chosen by Psyqualia.
You'd be wise
to remember that.
(sighs)
Here you go.
That's too kind of you.
(sniffs)
Ah.
Nicely done.
I'm glad you like it.
Guess I should
return the favor.
‐Oh?
‐Let's see.
Hmm.
Better hold on tight.
I'm gonna show you
something special.
Can't wait.
♪
(giggling)
Oh.
So let me get this straight,
you all work at PSY Shop,
but you lead a double life
as members of the
pop group Ultra Rare.
Obviously, you don't
want anyone to know
what your
objectives really are,
but I'd like to thank you
for this wonderful power.
That's very kind of you,
but the person you want
to thank isn't here.
No, don't!
Oh, really?
Who is this stranger?
Oh, you'll meet him
soon enough, I'm sure.
Well, I'll be.
Now that's exciting.
♪
Huh?
Looks like your
friend is running late.
I wouldn't worry yourself.
It won't be much longer.
Psyqualia always
gets me what I want.
♪
Hmm.
Marron attacks first.
(zapping)
(shouting)
Then with a boost from Flogal,
Young Pegasus Knight
attacks your Vanguard.
I don't guard.
All right, I'm gonna
check the drive trigger.
Ha!
♪
Get ready, Kai.
I draw.
Who does he think he is
telling me that Blaster
Blade is still my avatar?
I've got someone stronger now.
Hmm.
Rising up from the
darkness, my avatar.
I ride Blaster Dark!
♪
(chuckling)
CounterBlast.
(zapping)
♪
Ah!
The Knight of Darkness, Rugos
and Blaster Javelin
to rear guard.
♪
With Javelin's skill...
...I add Phantom Blaster
Dragon to my hand.
Now, Blaster Dark
attacks your Vanguard.
♪
I don't guard.
Drive check.
A critical trigger,
giving the power to Rugos
and the critical
to Blaster Dark.
Hmph!
(grunts)
Boosted by Javelin,
Rugos attacks.
I don't guard.
(grunts)
Ah!
I check the damage trigger.
Just what I wanted.
♪
If Kai hadn't pulled
a heal trigger,
he would've taken three
damage in that one turn.
Aichi's stronger than ever.
Well, I, for one, hope
that Kai can keep up.
You're not gonna
beat me like this.
You know why, Aichi?
It's because I'm
using your true avatar.
I ride Blaster Blade!
♪
I'm activating Blaster
Blade's CounterBlast.
Leave the field, Rugos!
Ah!
♪
Marron moves back,
making room for Knight
of Truth, Gordon.
♪
With support from Flogal,
Blaster Blade attacks
your Vanguard.
I guard with Grim Reaper!
♪
I'm checking
the drive trigger.
All right.
Another 5,000
power to Gordon.
Ahh!
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
With Marron's support,
Gordon attacks.
(grunts)
Draw trigger.
You can't stop
the Shadow Paladins,
and now you'll see
just how terrifying
this deck really is.
Here it goes.
I stand and draw.
Spreading his black wings
to cover this
battlefield in darkness,
I'm gonna ride...
Phantom Blaster Dragon!
♪
This is bad.
Next, I call Dark Mage,
Badhabh Caar to rear guard.
Using his skill, I flip over
the top card of my deck,
and if the revealed card
is a Shadow Paladin,
then I can call it.
Hold on, every single
card in Aichi's deck
is from the
Shadow Paladin Clan.
It's only a matter
of which one he draws.
Ah!
Not another Blaster Dark!
(chuckles)
My trusty avatar.
You'll always
be there for me.
Where there is light,
there is darkness,
a darkness so deep that
even light can't survive.
Some lights were
just meant to go out.
Arise from shadows,
Blaster Dark!
♪
And I call Doranbau.
With Javelin's support,
Badhabh Caar attacks
Blaster Blade.
(shouting)
♪
Now I attack with
Phantom Blaster Dragon.
Epona will guard.
♪
Let's check my twin drive.
Heal trigger.
The 5,000 power
to Blaster Dark.
I recover one damage.
♪
Boosted by Doranbau,
I attack with Blaster Dark!
Doranbau's skill grants
an additional 4,000 power
to my avatar.
Uh, I don't guard.
♪
(shouting)
Ooh!
♪
Two more damage this turn.
He's obviously below me,
so what's with that
look in his eyes?
I stand and draw.
Enter the fray, Master of
Paladins, I ride Alfred!
(thunder crashing)
(zapping)
♪
(thunder crashing)
Next, I call Knight of
Silence, Gallatin and Wingal.
♪
I'm not the weakling
I used to be.
You've underestimated
me since we met.
It's about time I helped
you realize your mistake.
Boosted by Marron,
Gordon attacks.
I don't guard.
♪
Now, Alfred!
I don't guard.
Checking the twin drive.
♪
(shouting)
With Wingal's support,
go, Gallatin!
I don't guard.
(shouting)
♪
By this point,
it should be clear.
I don't care about your
attacks in the slightest
because I know how
this fight is gonna end.
My eyes have shown it to me.
Soon, you'll see it too.
(gasps, sighs)
I've waited so long
to say this to you.
This is it.
Final turn.
I call Skull Witch, Nemain.
♪
Using her skill,
by dropping one of
my cards, I draw two.
And, now,
Phantom Blaster Dragon's
Corrupted Charging Lance,
Badhabh Caar,
Blaster Javelin, Nemain,
it's time to make
the ultimate sacrifice.
Ah!
Ooh!
Ahh!
♪
Calling Dark Metal Dragon,
Witch of Nostrum, Arianrhod,
and Black Sage, Charon.
Come on!
♪
With support from Arianrhod,
go, my Dark Metal Dragon!
♪
I don't guard.
(grunts)
♪
He's got Kai at
the breaking point.
Ha, it's the end
of the line for you.
♪
He's moments away from
being utterly destroyed,
so how come he still has
that cold look in his eyes?
Tell me, Kai,
do you regret saying
that you thought I was weak?
♪
Stop it.
Just stop looking
at me like that.
I'm strong now!
Stronger than you!
Boosted by Charon, let's go,
Phantom Blaster Dragon!
♪
Future Knight, Llew
with Flogal and
Margal will guard.
♪
Ah.
Drive trigger check.
♪
Oh, not a critical trigger.
But that still isn't
gonna be enough.
Even if he gives it
all to his Vanguard,
the attack will fail.
That's fine.
All effects will go to
my avatar, Blaster Dark.
♪
(roaring)
All right, he survived.
Not yet.
There's one more attack left.
With Doranbau's support,
it's your turn, Blaster Dark!
Ahh!
♪
You can't deny it now, Kai.
I've gotten stronger!
All because
I wanted to fight you,
but I want to
hear you say it.
Say that I'm strong!
Marron will guard.
♪
Then Gordon will intercept,
and with his skill,
the shield doubles
in strength.
♪
No way.
Ah!
But...
it's impossible!
Ha!
Why?
I should have
beaten you this turn,
just like my
Psyqualia said I would!
This isn't the way
I pictured it!
You're still weak because you
rely on that power, Aichi.
You're kidding me.
How can you say that
after I worked so hard
to get good enough
to fight you?
If I'm so weak,
then how come we're
winning at Nationals, huh?
I defeated the Jurassic Army.
It was me that beat
the Brilliant Stars!
Is that your
idea of strength?
Psyqualia gives you an unfair
advantage and nothing more.
Allow me to show you what
real strength looks like.
Final turn.
♪
Knights of the White Light,
please show him the way.
See the king as he once was!
I ride the Vanguard!
Alfred Early!
♪
If you're using that unit,
then you're planning to...
With Alfred's skill,
I superior call Blaster
Blade to the rear guard.
♪
Blaster Blade, why?
Picture it.
The two of us have
appeared in spirit form
on the surface of
the Planet Cray.
(gasps)
You haven't forgotten,
Aichi Sendou.
Think back.
Remember the time
you almost lost me?
You were strong then.
♪
Your classmate stole
me away from you.
Morikawa, hand it over.
Come on, it means
a lot to me.
I won this in a
game of Vanguard,
so there's no way I'm
gonna give it up easily.
Mm, fine then!
I'll fight you
to get it back!
Okay, kid, it's a deal.
Challenging Kai to a fight
took a lot of courage.
Don't you get it?
The strength you've been after
was inside you all along.
It was inside me?
Really?
That's right.
You've always been afraid,
hiding from your problems
and running away
when things got tough.
That's how you used to be.
♪
But now you're the kind of
guy that faces his problems
without fear in his heart.
You see, your strength
doesn't come from
the deck you're using,
and your Psyqualia isn't
making you stronger either.
Stop it!
You don't know!
I owe everything
to Psyqualia!
Without this power,
I'd be nothing!
You don't believe that.
You were getting
stronger on your own.
Think back.
Before you got that power,
the only thing you
wanted was to fight me.
♪
You know it, Aichi.
This isn't what you
pictured for our battle.
It's true, I wanted to be
your equal and friend.
♪
Ahh!
Kai, I've always
hoped that one day
I would get the chance
to face off with you.
♪
(zapping)
(grunts)
No.
It's not right.
♪
(groans)
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
You're really strong,
but you're not my avatar.
♪
Big mistake.
No way.
This is right.
I know it because my avatar...
♪
...has been waiting
for me all along.
♪
(sighs)
No.
Not like this.
This isn't the way
it was supposed to be.
It's all wrong!
♪
Mm?
Here you go.
Why would you...
Take it.
It's yours, after all.
♪
(cries)
(giggles)
Well, guys, it looks
like it all worked out.
♪
I'm sorry to say it, Ren,
but I don't think Aichi
Sendou is coming by today.
Well, that's a real shame.
Too bad.
I thought the kid
had potential.
Thanks.
He doesn't know
what he's missing.
(giggles)
Mm!
I'm glad he stood him up.
Knock it off, Rekka.
Uh‐‐mm.
♪
Ren Suzugamori
and Aichi Sendou...
♪
...two people
blessed with Psyqualia
walking down totally
opposite paths.
♪
This should make
the tournament finals
quite interesting.
♪
‐Hey, bro!
‐Yo!
You guys, I‐‐
You'll never guess what
the manager has planned.
Woo‐hoo, it's another
shop tournament!
Yeah, and I think
I might play.
Guys, I owe
everyone an apology
for how I've been
acting lately.
Sorry.
Next time, "Golden Glow."
Hold on, something's wrong.
I can't picture the
fights the way I used to.
Ha‐ha, don't sweat it, bro.
Just have fun!
Yeah, really!