Final turn.
Corrupted Charging Lance!
Huh, sacrificing a rear guard?
Fly, Phantom Blaster Dragon!
Finish Death Rex!
The winner, Aichi Sendou.
(gasps)
♪
I've gotten so‐‐
so much stronger.
♪
This is bad.
Yeah.
Ever since we got back
from training camp
he's been passing out
after all his fights.
I don't know why it happens,
but it can't be good.
It's our job to make sure
that Aichi doesn't need
to play another match today.
♪
Welcome back to
the elimination rounds
of the Vanguard
National Championship.
Each of these teams
is trying their hardest
to earn a spot
in next week's finals.
Oh, the excitement.
We've talked it over.
Kamui and I are finishing
these fights ourselves.
But why, I'm okay.
The most important
thing right now
is for you to rest up, bro.
It's scary the way
you've been passing out
after your matches.
We're worried about you.
You can't stop
me from fighting.
Besides, you're
gonna need my strength
if you want to make
sure that Team Q4's
still in it next week.
Ugh, ugh.
Aichi!
(gasping, whimpering)
You're in no condition
to go out there.
Oh, yeah?
We're gonna take care
of this without your help.
♪
Hey, hold on.
(grumbling)
Did you have to
say it like that?
I get that you
don't want to lose,
but Aichi's still
got feelings, you know.
Have you given up on
making it to the finals?
Huh, of course
I haven't given up.
But I don't want
to leave Aichi behind.
Let's just say
we're making sure
he has a spot
to come back to.
♪
Well, when you
put it that way.
♪
Yeah, tournament finals,
here we come!
(crying)
Uh, hey, are you okay?
Why, she could
be Emi's twin!
What's up,
why are you crying?
Some very bad men stole
my puppy, Sprinkles,
and they said if I
don't win my next cardfight
I'll never get him back.
(crying)
♪
Those creeps‐‐who would
do that sort of thing?
If you were my opponent,
you could let me win
and save my
little Sprinkles.
(sobbing)
Kamui Katsuragi,
brimming with confidence,
in love with Aichi Sendou's
younger sister, Emi.
His cardfighting history
shows a clear weakness
when fighting
against females.
Hmm?
There's no point in hiding.
(footsteps)
Misaki Tokura,
works at Card Capital
while residing above the
store with her uncle, Shin.
Calm, cool, and collected,
she possesses
a magnificent memory
which she uses against
those she battles.
Who are you?
Just one of your opponents.
I'm from Team Spyder.
We took pains to investigate
everybody on your team.
Asaka had lots to say.
(gasp)
Your reaction coincides
perfectly with my data.
It must be true
that your primary goal
in this tournament
is to win a
rematch against her.
However, I wonder if
you've managed to master
the Goddess of the Full Moon?
(growl)
You lost the
first time around
because you didn't have
full control of your deck.
Will it be any different now?
Allow me to answer that.
Since the last
national tournament,
your skills haven't
improved at all.
And just like before,
you and your team
are going to lose.
♪
(gasping)
What is it, Aichi?
Nothing.
Uh.
♪
Listen, you have to stay
in bed for while.
♪
(crowd roaring)
Coming up next,
we've got team Q4
facing off
against Team Spyder.
♪
Huh?
There she is!
Lose this fight and
you know what happens.
(crying)
I've just been
informed that Aichi Sendou
is sitting out and his teammates
are planning to continue
with only two fighters.
According to the rules,
if this match
goes to three games,
and Aichi Sendou
is unable to compete,
then Team Q4
will lose by default.
In other words,
they can't afford to drop
even a single contest.
He's sitting out?
You still have
a lot to learn
about how to properly use
your Psyqualia, Aichi.
Do you think they
can pull this off?
You've got to have faith
in the great Kamui.
Take a relaxative, yo.
Kourin, come back to me.
Hold on, I wouldn't
want to lose ya.
Ah, sure.
Aahhhh!
Oooh.
Did you guys miss me?
Oh, so now you show up?
What happened between
you and Kourin?
Nothing happened, man.
I took her to speak
with Kai, that's it.
Yeah, but for what reason?
You'll know
soon enough, 'kay?
(door opening)
It's about time.
Why did you get involved?
You know it's
our job to keep‐‐
I know our job.
Please, Kamui,
you're the only one
who can save
my darling Sprinkles.
Hmm.
He‐he, what a chump.
It's ours for the taking.
As long as we can maintain
this masterful facade,
his loss is assured.
The first match
of this round begins!
‐Now stand up, my Vanguard!
♪
Blaujunger, what
happened to Battleraizer?
You're just noticing now?
He used that in
his first match.
Sounds about right.
Coming into a big
tournament like this
it's natural
that he would make
a few changes
to his deck.
♪
What a stand off!
Tied at five damage each.
Can Q4 seize the
victory here or not?
Please don't hurt me.
♪
Need a few more tears.
Ah, my eye!
Huh?
Uh, uh, my eye!
You were a dude all along!
Attack!
Stern Blaukluger,
Stardust Blaster!
♪
(giggling)
The winner,
Kamui Katsuragi!
(cheering)
That's one match down
and one to go!
(slap)
Whew.
‐We're sorry.
No worries, our first
prey man slipped the web,
but I'm going
to enjoy tormenting
this next one myself.
♪
Cardfighters at the ready.
I'm taking a redraw.
♪
(grumbling)
(gasps)
This hand doesn't have the
Half Moon or the Full Moon.
♪
Allow me to answer that.
Since the last
national tournament
your skills haven't
improved at all.
And just like before,
you and your team
are going to lose.
♪
‐Now stand up, my Vanguard.
Here we go.
I draw.
And ride
Pupa Mutant, Giraffa.
♪
With Larva Mutant,
Giraffa's skill,
I can search my deck
for Elite Mutant, Giraffa,
and add it to my hand.
That ends my turn.
I draw.
Using Godhawk,
Ichibyoshi's skill,
I can check the top
five cards of my deck.
No Goddess of the
Crescent Moon, Tsukuyomi.
I ride Goddess of
the Crescent Moon
from my hand and
I call Psychic Bird
using its ability
to move it into the soul.
I draw again.
Calling Dark Cat.
♪
Thanks to Dark Cat's skill,
you and I can both
draw an extra card.
Thanks, my hand was starting
to feel a little light.
Just what I needed.
Supported by Dark Cat,
Goddess of the
Crescent Moon attacks.
(growling)
Drive check.
Critical trigger.
That's 5,000 power
and plus one critical
to Goddess of
the Crescent Moon.
♪
Damage trigger check.
First.
Second.
Now I stand and draw.
I ride Elite Mutant, Giraffa.
I call Tail Joe,
Gloom Flyman,
and Stealth Millipede.
With a boost from Millipede,
my Vanguard attacks!
When Pupa Mutant's
in the soul,
Elite's power
increases by 1,000.
Next, I activate
Millipede's skill.
As long as all of my
opponent's units are at rest,
4,000 power is added
to the boosted unit.
Uh.
That's a tough one
to deal with.
Easy to avoid if you
don't rest your units.
But your units rest
as soon as you attack.
Then all she needs
to do is not attack.
But you can't win
if you don't attack.
‐Oh, yeah.
‐(laughing)
Aahh!
Damage trigger check.
Activating Giraffa's skill.
When his attack hits,
I can chose one of
your rear guard units
and prevent it from
standing next turn.
Dark cat.
Uh!
Looks like you've
stepped into my web.
Are you ready to
dance with the Spyder?
You're battling a true master
of the Megacolony Clan.
The way this guy talks
is really starting
to creep me out.
All that talk about Spyders
really bugs you, huh?
With a boost from Flyman,
Tail Joe attacks.
As long as your
units are at rest,
he gains an extra
3,000 power.
Argh!
Damage trigger check.
Draw trigger.
Well, at least I get a card.
It's a shame you didn't get
that trigger a little sooner.
♪
Mmm, here goes.
Using Tsukuyomi's skill,
I check the top five cards.
♪
Mmm, Goddess of the
Half Moon isn't here.
Looks like you're gonna lose.
Your team, too.
♪
I had her in my hand already.
Using Tsukuyomi's skill,
I double soul charge.
I call Battle Sister, Cocoa.
Using her skill
to check the top card.
♪
You still can't find it.
I call Oracle
Guardian, Red Eye
and Goddess of
the Crescent Moon.
♪
Goddess of the Half Moon
attacks Tail Joe.
♪
Drive trigger check.
Ya!
I'm coming for your Vanguard
with Red Eye boosted by
Goddess of the Crescent Moon.
I'll guard with
Megacolony Battler A.
Activating Battler's skill.
It moves from the guardian
circle to the soul.
My turn's over.
In an effort to
avoid my skills,
you ended your turn
with one of your units
still standing, huh?
Sadly, that isn't
going to be enough
to escape from
my web, little fly.
I ride Death Warden
Ant Lion!
♪
Activating Ant Lion's skill.
Soul charge.
This gives him
another 2,000 power
and I call one
more Ant Lion.
Two grade threes
side by side.
Misaki's in big trouble.
With support from Flyman,
I'll have Ant Lion
attack your Vanguard.
Oracle Guardian,
Nike will guard.
♪
Next up, Stealth Millipede
boosts my Vanguard's attack.
(grumbling)
Checking the twin drive.
‐Grrr.
‐Ah!
I check for
a damage trigger.
That's all for now.
♪
Using my Vanguard skill
to look through
the top five cards.
Still no Full Moon?
Your moon is waning.
I hate to say
I told you so,
but you really haven't
gotten better with that deck.
I ride CEO Amaterasu.
♪
I soul charge
with her skill.
Then I check the
top card of my deck.
♪
It doesn't matter
what you draw,
there's no way
you can escape
from the web that
I'm spinning around you.
I call Amaterasu.
♪
With Dark Cat support,
my Vanguard attacks.
♪
Hmm.
Twin drive check.
It's a critical trigger.
The critical effect
goes to my Vanguard.
And the power to Red Eye.
And because I have
four cards in my hand,
Amaterasu receives
an additional 4,000 power.
♪
(blasting)
Arrgh!
One, two...
Next, Red Eye attacks
with a boost from
Goddess of the
Crescent Moon.
(growling)
Damage trigger check.
I'll give the power
to my Vanguard.
And the rear guard,
Ant Lion stands up.
Activating Red Eye's skill.
When his attack succeeds,
I soul charge.
Amaterasu's coming at you
with Cocoa's support.
Battler A will guard that.
And using his skill,
he moves to the soul.
My turn's over.
Yeah, just hold on
a bit longer.
So you've abandoned hope
of getting Goddess
of the Full Moon
and you're trying for
Amaterasu's Megablast now.
Too bad that isn't gonna
matter in the slightest.
I'm gonna finish you off
before you get the chance!
I ride Ant Lion!
With seven cards
in the soul,
I activate Ant Lion's
skill, soul charge.
That's 2,000 power and
eight cards in the soul.
I call Evil Armor
General, Giraffa.
Here goes‐‐the time has
come for me to show you
the power of
Ant Lion's Megablast!
♪
None of your
rear guard units
will be able to
stand next turn.
♪
Uh.
(gasps)
There's nothing better
than watching another
person struggle.
The look in your eyes‐‐
it shows me that
you finally understand
how truly helpless you are.
(snicker)
I want to savor this moment
for as long as I can.
Now, let's have
some fun together.
I attack with
Evil Armor General.
Red Eye will intercept.
♪
You will never escape.
Ant Lion swings in with a
boost from Stealth Millipede.
And with Millipede's skill,
a 4,000 point bonus is added
as long as your
rear guard is resting.
Twin drive check.
Critical trigger.
That's 5,000 power to
my rear guard Ant Lion
and a plus one critical
to my Vanguard.
Yes!
Ah!
♪
You follow?
This next attack
will be enough
to finish you off
once and for all.
With a boost from Flyman,
Ant Lion charges.
Nike and Dream Eater
will guard.
♪
Guess I have
to end my turn.
She survived it,
but now...
Only your
Vanguard is standing.
You can't even activate
Amaterasu's Megablast
until she lands a blow.
And I don't think
you'll be getting past
the five cards in my hand.
He's right, one attack
isn't gonna be enough.
If only...
Come on,
just give up already.
We're going to
the finals together.
‐Uh!
‐Hmm?
And this will take me there.
Gentle light
breaking the darkness,
your smile brings hope
to the entire world.
I ride Goddess of the
Full Moon, Tsukuyomi.
♪
You finally managed to get
a hold of the Full Moon.
It won't change things.
Her Counterblast,
drawing two cards
and sending one from
my hand to the soul.
Counterblast one more time.
♪
Now it's my hand you
should be worried about.
(whimpering)
I call Goddess
of the Half Moon,
Battle Sister, Chocolat,
Lozenge Magus,
Oracle Guardian, Gemini,
and Meteor Break Wizard.
♪
She was able to
replace all five of her
useless rear
guards in one shot!
Looks like there's
gonna be three units
attacking his
Vanguard after all.
Here comes Meteor Break
boosted by Gemini.
His Counterblast
adds 3,000 power.
Sharp Nail Scorpio
and Phantom Black will guard.
Lozenge Magus supports
an attack from my Vanguard.
Lozenge's skill adds an
additional 3,000 power.
Another Scorpio will guard.
I'm safe if she
doesn't pull a trigger.
Now checking the twin drive.
First check.
And the second check.
A draw trigger.
No way!
That's 5,000 power
to my Full Moon
and I draw.
♪
(yelling)
I lost?
But my data showed me
all your weak points.
There's much more
to a game of Vanguard
than research and numbers.
The winner, Misaki Tokura.
Team Q4 has won this round.
(cheering)
Don't worry,
I'll get us there.
Aichi, Q4 won their games!
(whimpering)
Aichi!
The Brilliant
Stars have won
their second
match‐up with ease.
♪
The final spot on our team
better be waiting for me,
Ren.
Q4 and the Brilliant Stars,
both are undefeated
up to this point
but only one of them can take
the top spot in Block C.
I figured that they
would have a good record.
We've clinched our
spot in the finals,
but those guys are up next,
so just stick to the plan
and Aichi can rest.
♪
What kind of a
creep disguises himself
as a little girl
to win a game?
I can't believe you thought
that looked like Emi.
You might want to get
your head examined.
There's no time,
I've got a job to do.
Me too.
‐We've got to win this.
Kai!
I was dreaming again.
Why are Kamui and Misaki
doing all the fighting?
Next time,
Another Asteroid.
I can hear Ren calling me.
The Brilliant Stars
can't be defeated
without you, Aichi.