(background traffic)
Asura Kaiser, go!
Finishing hold!
♪
All right, did you see that?
Hey, Emi, I won my match
just like you won my heart.
‐Kamui's a poet!
‐And we know it!
Go, Vortex Dragon!
Cleanse this land as it
bathes in your flames!
(fire whooshing)
♪
Hmm.
Nice work, Kai.
You're heading to
the second round.
Of course I am.
♪
♪ Vanguard, well
it's not a lie ♪
♪ This legend will
be starting now ♪
♪ To the future, just
lead us all the way ♪
♪
♪ Go! ♪
♪ We can't hold back this
feeling just any longer ♪
♪ Come on, tear off
everything you've got ♪
‐♪ Get crazy way ♪
♪ There's no stopping,
there's no running ♪
♪ I can hear his voice
calling for me somewhere ♪
♪ I'll cross the bridge,
a head‐on battle now ♪
‐♪ Here we go ♪
‐♪ Hurry up ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
ever interfere ♪
♪ 3, 2, 1, let's go! ♪
♪ Vanguard, an image
comes rising from deep
within our souls, yeah ♪
♪ Awaken it right now
with a miracle ♪
♪ Vanguard, now we all become ♪
♪ That burning red hot
blazing flame to the future,
we'll keep on racing through ♪
♪ Final turn ♪
♪
(background conversation)
Misaki, Kamui and Kai
have all made it through
to the next round.
I'm gonna have to work hard
to keep up with them.
Oh, there you are,
Aichi, check it out!
You're not gonna
believe this match!
Huh?
Your first mistake
was fighting a ninja.
Uh, what?
♪
Secret ninja magic blaze!
Wow, this guy is
something, isn't he?
Hmm?
He's so awesome!
Huh?
♪
Huh, thank you for the
excellent battle, young friend.
Oh, man!
You should be proud
of your performance.
Facing a ninja master
like me is no easy feat.
I'd be happy to offer you
a rematch if you're interested.
No way!
I'm never fighting a
costumed weirdo
like you ever again!
But you don't think I'm cool?
How could you even
call yourself an adult,
walking around here like that?
You're an embarrassment!
Uh.
It's because of
that silly outfit
that I couldn't
concentrate on the game.
I wish your parents had
never let you out of
the basement, you
big freak of nature!
Ugh!
Oh.
(background chatter)
I pay my rent.
This tournament sure attracts
some different people, huh?
Oh, that guy, he shows
up here every six months
when we hold our big events
and he's always dressed
‐as a ninja master.
‐Yeah?
I'm not sure if he's one of
our regular customers or not.
I mean, with that mask on,
nobody knows who he is.
But why does he need
to wear a mask?
Isn't is obvious?
He hides his identity
to protect his loved ones.
That must be it.
Well, the results
from round one are in.
(marker screeching)
Oh, ho, Aichi, look
at your next match,
this is gonna be awesome!
Huh?
♪
You mean, I have to
fight ninja master M?
♪
‐Look, he's gone!
‐No, he's not.
♪
(sniffing)
Meow.
Go away, my furry friend.
You'll blow my cover!
Uh!
Oh?
♪
(clears throat)
It would appear you've
broken through my
super secret ninja
hiding technique.
Are you also a ninja?
Meow.
♪
Well, fate has selected you
as my next opponent,
Aichi Sendou.
Huh?
Just call me ninja master M.
How can you be so sure
that I'm Aichi Sendou?
Oh.
Well, I, um‐‐
My heightened ninja
senses told me
you were the right person.
Ninjas are cool!
And that is just the tip
of the cool iceberg,
Katsumi Morikawa.
Wow, you know my name, too?
Teach me your ways!
I have this strange feeling
that I know you from somewhere.
Yeah, something about your voice
sounds really familiar.
Have you guys been hanging
out with this ninja
behind my back?
No, no, it's not like that.
Exactly right.
I've never met these guys.
Is that so, Mr. Sendou?
Wait a sec.
I think I remember where
I've heard that voice.
Answer me this,
Aichi Sendou!
You're Mr. Mark, aren't you?
Ugh, no!
(laughs)
‐But‐‐
‐No, no, no, no!
(sighs)
Check, is this thing on?
(microphone feedback)
Could I have the attention
of all our winning fighters
from the first round?
We need you up here, please.
Now's my chance, smoke bomb!
‐Oh!
‐Watch out!
(poof)
That's it?
(laughs)
Can't use a real one indoors.
Your consideration for
the rest of us is admirable.
As I suspected, he's a
ninja, and a gentleman!
How do you like that, guys?
Huh?
Allow me to take a moment
and explain how the system
is going to work.
The four winners from
our next round of fights
will move on to become
the representative
for their block in the
tournament finals.
Once we have the
four finalists,
there will be a draw
to determine pairings.
You never know
who could face off.
That means if I'm lucky,
I can win this fight
and maybe get paired with
Kai in the next round!
Well then, if there's
no questions,
I say we begin our
next two matches.
Let's start with A block.
This young player
is new to the game,
but never backs down
from a challenge,
Aichi Sendou!
Ah, yeah, well, thank you.
His opponent is none other
than the mystery fighter,
ninja master M!
Onward to battle!
(crowd laughs)
And on the next table,
we've got a player
who just moved back to town
but is already making
a big impact, Toshiki Kai!
♪
And his opponent,
last year's champion,
Kasuki Inaba!
Uh!
Hey, what's up?
Wow, you won last year's
Card Captiol Tournament?
That's not the whole story.
You see, kid, I've actually
won the last three tournaments.
Oh, that's really great!
What's wrong, are you worried
I'm gonna lose my next
battle or something?
Not exactly.
Keep your mind on
your own fight.
I can handle this
guy, no problem.
What's that?
Listen man, you're just
another step for me
on the way to my
fourth championship!
‐Hmm.
‐You think this is funny, Kai?
Now, that's the fighting spirit
we like to see around here!
So, let's get to it, everyone.
Players, please take
your positions.
(cheering)
♪
‐This fight is gonna be amazing!
‐Hmm.
Looks like both of the tables
are worth watching, huh?
Hmm?
♪
Aichi.
I hope Kai wins his match.
Your absent mind betrays you.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's important to keep
yourself focused
on the battle that's
about to happen.
We both have a big role
to play here, Aichi Sendou.
Huh?
So, you really are Mr. Mark?
Ugh!
No, why would you think that?
I'm ninja master M, got it?
Now, battle me with honor.
Right.
Let the second round begin!
Stand up the Vanguard!
My Vanguard, stand up.
‐Lizard Runner Undeux!
‐And my Lizard Runner, Undeux.
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Jump down from the shadows!
♪
Barcgal!
Stealth Beast Hagakure!
♪
You're about to get
a lesson in pain,
from the Nubatama Ninjas!
♪
It begins with a card.
Check out this move.
Ninja body replacement!
Body replacement?
Stealth Dragon Dreadmaster!
Whoa, he's the real deal!
That was a special
ninja technique.
It's just a regular ride.
Now, my turn has ended.
I wasn't sure what to expect
from the ninja master,
but now I see, he plays
just like anyone else.
I ride Wingal!
I move Barcgal
back to rear guard!
And I call Little
Sage Marron, too,
I'll have her attack
your Vanguard!
♪
Ha!
Let's see, is there
a surprise waiting for us?
Next, I support Wingal
with Barcgal and attack
your Dreadmaster!
Checking for a drive trigger.
No!
I check again for
a damage trigger.
That's the end of my turn!
Ugh, this will be a
most painful burden.
As a ninja, it is my job
to withstand the pain of battle.
Throughout history,
ninjas have had
their mettle tested
over and over again.
I stand and draw.
Ninja, body replacement!
(whoosh)
♪
Now, behold my true powers
as a ninja master.
Huh?
Ninja, body doubles!
♪
Oh man, he actually
made copies of himself!
No, no, no, all he did
is play more copies
of the same card.
This is okay, he talks
differently than most players
but he's playing like
anyone else would.
I just have to fight
like I always do.
‐Don't look so relaxed.
‐Huh?
If you thought playing
against a ninja master
would be easy,
you've made a mistake
from which you won't recover.
(laughs)
Dreadmaster, arise!
(whoosh)
Supported by Dreadmaster,
I'll attack Wingal
with Chigasumi!
♪
(dog wincing)
I check for a damage trigger.
Might I ask a question,
how many cards do you
have in your hand right now?
Huh, I...
...have five.
If that's the case,
then I'll pay the cost
of one to activate
Dreadmaster's counter blast.
Huh?
I damaged you, using
Dreadmaster in support,
and currently, you have
more cards in your hand
than I do.
So I'll force you to send
one of those cards
to the drop zone!
Huh!
I have to discard one.
With this, the silent power
of the Nubatama Ninjas,
you hold more cards than me,
and I'll make you pay for that!
(metallic whooshing)
I call it the‐‐
Ninja super discard
winning move!
Oh!
That's an awful name.
♪
Oh, I'm sorry, Marron.
Is this your plan?
You're gonna make me discard
one card at a time?
No problem.
Your carefree attitude
shows that you've yet
to understand the massive impact
a single card can
have on a battle.
This is the painful lesson
I'm going to teach you.
I attack Wingal with
my Vanguard Chigasumi!
Check for a trigger?
Ooh!
Checking for a damage trigger.
It's Gancelot!
Aichi!
Your dream girl
looks kind of worried.
Comfort her, yo!
Hmm, that ninja's no pushover.
Hang in there, bro.
And finally, I attack
your Wingal with
my third Chigasumi!
I'll defend against that attack!
(whoosh)
Ugh!
With that, my turn is over.
Man, forcing Aichi
to discard cards
really weakens his deck!
These Nubatama Ninjas
are fearsome!
It's just skill.
(evil laughter)
I don't care what
cards or abilities
my opponent uses,
my royal paladins
will fight on!
Here I go, stand up, my avatar!
Ride, Blaster Blade!
♪
I call the silent
knight Gallatin!
And he attacks your Chigasumi!
Now, which Chigasumi
are you referring to?
Huh, oh!
(evil laughter)
♪
That's right, there
are three of them.
I'm attacking the
Vanguard Chigasumi!
Your call.
Guess I'll check for
a damage trigger.
Rah!
Next, I attack the
same Chigasumi
with Blaster Blade,
supported by Barcgal!
Checking for a drive trigger.
(yelling)
♪
Damage trigger, check.
Hmm.
Finally, I'm gonna
continue the attack
on your vanguard with Marron!
(lightning buzzing)
♪
Oh!
Witness the ninja art
of law and substitution.
So cool!
What's the big deal?
He just used a card to defend,
and called it
something different.
That's right!
This is where it gets
really funny for me.
Huh?
I only have two
cards in my hand,
but you have three!
No, not again!
Exactly, I activate
Hagakure's counter blast!
When called to the
Guardian's Circle,
Hagakure can make you discard.
Hmm.
I have to drop one of these.
I won't stand a chance
without Alfred,
and I need Epona to guard.
Guess my choice
is made for me.
Ugh.
I sent Solitary Knight
Gancelot to the drop zone.
Ah, you can't just throw
away a grade three unit!
This is awful!
Plus, his attack failed!
Aichi's in deep trouble!
♪
When facing a ninja,
never let your guard down.
It doesn't matter if
you're on offense or defense.
(growls)
(evil laughter)
I see you're starting to
understand today's lesson.
A single card can
change the game.
Next, it's my turn.
Ninja body replacement!
(whoosh)
Stealth Dragon Voidmaster!
Embodiment of Armor,
Bahr, enter!
I attack Blaster Blade
with Chigasumi,
supported by Dreadmaster!
This looks bad.
If that attack gets
through, I'm gonna have to
get rid of another card!
Then, choose your best option.
Dragonic Overlord's
counter blast!
Huh?
With the support of Bahr,
my overlord will
attack your Tejas!
Now, I'm gonna check
the drive trigger.
♪
Overlord stands,
and attacks Ganlu,
checking the drive
trigger again.
I've got a critical trigger.
Applying all effects
to my vanguard.
♪
My overlord stands
for a third time,
and attacks your vanguard!
Can't guard!
Check the drive trigger‐‐
(roaring)
Dragonic Overlord,
burn them all!
(roaring)
♪
(yelling)
And the winner,
Toshiki Kai!
No way, how the heck did
this guy beat me so quickly?
He's awesome.
Meow.
I guess you missed a step.
What a great way to win!
(clears throat)
I was in the middle
of my first attack,
are you going to guard it?
Eh, well‐‐
That's right, I don't have
time to waste right now.
I need to hurry up and
win so I can fight Kai.
Hmm.
If I'm gonna have to
discard anyway,
I might as well stop the damage!
I block that attack
with Epona, guard!
Ah!
♪
Looks like you've made
the right decision.
You would have lost
that card anyway.
But unfortunately, your hand
has shrunk once again
and now with only one card,
I have you backed into a corner.
Yeah, well, you also
have a one‐card hand.
So maybe, you're
the one in trouble!
Aichi Sendou,
what a big shot!
Your Dreadmaster and Hagakure.
Their discard abilities
won't affect me
as long as we both have
the same number of cards.
You are right.
Thank you.
Which means, you can't get
rid of my last one
unless you shrink your hand!
Another correct answer.
I can still fight you just fine,
even if I only have
a few cards to work with.
I love that fighting spirit,
but I think you're forgetting
something important.
I already have a grade
three vanguard.
And twin drive is about
to give me a big advantage.
Oh!
With the support of Bahr,
I attack Blaster Blade
with Stealth Dragon Voidmaster!
Ugh!
♪
I don't guard!
The power of ninja twin drive.
First check.
Second check.
Oh!
The embodiment of spear
has blessed me with
a critical trigger.
Chigasumi gets the
attack power bonus,
and Voidmaster will take
the plus one critical effect.
Ah!
Checking for a damage trigger.
Come on, bro!
See, now my hand
has three cards,
and you're still stuck with one.
I can't make you discard,
but I don't need to anymore.
I hope you paid attention
to today's lesson,
because you're about
to take the final exam.
I attack Blaster Blade
with Chigasumi!
Since my hand is
bigger than yours,
Chigasumi gets an additional
3,000 attack power this turn.
Forcing me to discard makes
his units more powerful, too!
This is unreal!
Ahh!
(wincing)
♪
So that puts him at five damage.
What could he possibly
do with one card?
I guess only a ninja
can stop a ninja.
Oh!
(all wincing)
We always play a
game of numbers,
whether you have more
cards or less cards,
we ninjas have an answer.
I can only imagine your despair,
being cornered like a rat!
Now, I pass it over to you.
This turn will be
your last, Aichi.
Think long and hard about
the move you're going to make.
But your tiny hand really limits
your options right about now.
(whimpering)
(evil laughter)
♪
♪ I feel the sunshine
lighting up the sky ♪
♪ The sea, the horizon,
feeling so alive ♪
♪ Yes, I have never
felt this way before ♪
♪ The stars in the sky
are glowing just for me ♪
♪ The wind, I've been waiting
is here and I believe ♪
♪ Now's the time,
and I will fly ♪
♪ I see the go sign ♪
♪ Take a chance, yes, no? ♪
♪ I can see my
hopes and dreams ♪
♪ I'll fight until the end ♪
♪ Just believe, you will see ♪
♪ It's time to show ♪
♪ The fire burning in me ♪
♪ Fly away, fly far away ♪
♪ Blasting rockets to the sky ♪
♪ We will soar away up high ♪
♪ Let's go together ♪
♪ Catch my star, yes I can ♪
♪ It's the moment of our lives ♪
♪ Our passion burning
blazing bright ♪
♪ Never giving up,
I trust my heart ♪
♪ Now I believe, yes we
can reach our dreams ♪
♪ Together we'll
create new miracles ♪
♪ A beautiful world ♪
♪ Now is the time ♪
♪ We are ready to fight ♪
♪ What are you waiting for,
we are dream shooters ♪
Kai managed to win
his battle in no time!
Focus on this battle.
Though it's important
to think ahead,
you must always remember to
remain present in the moment.
Yes, teacher,
I mean ninja master.
Humans live in the real world,
but these games we play
are extensions of
our virtual selves.
I see!
Next time, ninja
fighter withdraws!
I'm picturing myself victorious,
I understand now, teacher!
Excellent work, huh?