♪
Thanks to Phantom
Blaster Overlord's ability,
his power increases by 2,000.
♪
And he's gonna stay
at 13,000 power
for as long as I have a copy
of Phantom Blaster Dragon
in the soul.
(chuckles)
(grunts)
♪
Come on, bro!
(growling)
Call!
With a boost from Grim Reaper,
my Phantom Blaster Overlord's
Persona Blast.
(gasps)
♪
(roars)
(chuckles)
Attacking for 28,000?
And, as if that
weren't bad enough,
he's gone critical.
Which means if Aichi
can't stop it‐‐
Then I'm gonna have
to cancel that victory party.
♪
I can't let him beat me.
I can't.
(grunts)
♪
I need to be stronger!
Huh?
♪
Maybe he was right?
I'm‐‐
I find it very hard
to believe that this isn't
the real Aichi Sendou
that stands before me now.
You desperately wanted this gift
to make yourself stronger.
You're afraid to admit it,
but the truth has been
painfully obvious
this entire time.
Face it; you're
the same as I am.
♪
I guard.
Lien!
Kay!
Llew!
Margal!
♪
Those four cards
bumped him up to 35,000.
Should be more than enough
for him to stop Ren.
That's right,
he'll survive it...I think.
‐You think?
So, in the end,
all you were capable
of doing was putting up
that miserable excuse
for a defense?
How embarrassing.
Let me see your pain.
First check.
I got a heal trigger.
Adding 5,000 power
to Phantom Blaster Overlord.
And, of course, I recover one.
I really don't like
the way this looks.
The power boost,
it should have gone
to one of his rear guard units,
but with the Vanguard he'll need
to draw a second
trigger to make it work.
(gasps)
He knows it's coming!
Okay, it's there,
a draw trigger!
♪
Oh, no!
That's just not fair!
He's managed to force
his way though Aichi's defense!
You can't!
You're done for, Aichi.
♪
(screams)
(grunting)
♪
Can you feel it?
That overwhelming
sense of weakness?
In this world...
♪
...it's the winners
that get to make the rules.
♪
(screaming)
(chuckles)
Take a look around you
because we've come to
the moment Psyqualia
showed me before our match
even began.
(chuckles)
(gasping)
Aichi.
(grunting)
It ends like this.
You know it, Aichi.
This isn't what you
pictured for our battle.
(gasps)
It's not over.
(chuckles)
♪
Checking the damage trigger.
He's done for!
I don't think I can watch!
There's still hope.
♪
(gasps)
What?
(grunts)
Heal trigger!
5,000 power to my Vanguard
and then I recover one damage.
♪
Great, your turn.
(cheering)
♪
My word, he failed
to defend against the attack,
but a miracle trigger has
come to Aichi Sendou's rescue!
Don't forget, this
game's not over yet!
These guys are showing us
the best card fight of
their entire lives!
(sighing)
♪
It's my last chance to beat him.
Only, which side of me
should take control?
♪
The shadow
that hungers for control.
Don't get lost; the light
will help us find the way.
♪
What is this?
Amazing.
I get it; my struggle is over!
Avatar of Light and Shadow:
A new strength
borne out of compromise!
Ride, Majesty Lord Blaster!
♪
Huh?
Amazing.
♪
Blaster Dark,
crush that Fatalita!
♪
(grunts)
Boosted by Wingal Brave,
Blaster Blade attacks
Phantom Blaster Overlord!
I don't guard.
♪
(grunting)
Impossible.
How are you doing it;
beating me with that
silly hybrid deck?
Because this deck is part of me.
They're both my avatars
in their own way,
combining my best and worst:
the part of me
that searched for a new power
and the part that
found inner purpose.
The path I walked
led me to myself!
(grunts)
Supported by Marron,
Majesty Lord Blaster attacks!
♪
Activating my Vanguard's
ultimate skill.
Blaster Blade and Blaster Dark
are moved into the soul.
(grunting)
♪
Aichi Sendou, it's time
for you to make a choice.
I choose...
♪
Huh?
That card is
the perfect fit for you.
♪
I've never seen
anything like this before.
♪
With this ability,
my Vanguard gains 10,000 power!
♪
As if that weren't enough,
he also has a passive skill!
Since Blaster Blade
and Blaster Dark
are in the soul,
Majesty Lord Blaster
gains 2,000 power
and +1 critical
at all times!
Impossible!
How is it that you're able
to make two enemy clans
work so well together?
How can you benefit
from both sides?
Because Majesty Lord Blaster
opened my eyes to the truth.
Thanks to this card,
I understand what I've become.
In the past, I got scared,
I didn't understand my power,
but now, I'm the one in control.
(grunts)
♪
Using Psyqualia turned me
into a different person
and I ended up
hurting those I loved!
I won't make excuses
for my actions or
the things I said.
I jumped at the chance
to finally feel strong.
Bring given so much strength,
it was overwhelming,
but that was only a part of me.
I've accepted who I am
and it's time for you
to do the same.
What?
You were searching
for a way to get better,
and I think you lost
yourself in the process.
Think about why
you wanted that power.
Can you even remember anymore?
So you could win nationals
with your friends beside you.
♪
(all chuckling)
Stop it!
(grunting)
No!
Silence, you little fool!
I guard!
Spare me your pity.
You don't know me,
or what I'm capable of doing.
Ren.
Checking the Twin Drive.
Second check.
Now, for my winning image.
Just picture it,
try to remember
what it felt like
to count on your friends
to help you when
you needed it most.
Critical trigger!
Giving both of the effects
to Majesty Lord Blaster!
♪
What is this that I'm feeling?
That was a great match.
You're getting better.
Next, you've gotta face me.
No prob.
(chuckling)
My friends.
(grunts)
♪
Ren, I knew that the real you
was hiding somewhere in there.
(grunts)
♪
(screams)
You're fine.
Aichi.
(grunts)
♪
You're safe, Ren.
That's it...I lost.
♪
The winner is Aichi Sendou!
(cheering)
Our Vanguards have reached
the decision my people needed.
♪
(grunting, struggling)
We're defeated.
The time for fighting
has come to an end.
The other clans
are waiting for us.
♪
The royal paladins
are victorious.
Too cool, it's amazing
that the forces clashing
here on Cray were synchronized
with our card fighters
back on Earth.
It would appear the result
of the matchup wasn't
the only thing
that became synchronized.
I've never seen
those two treat each other
with such understanding.
I believe they've learned
from their connection
with Ren and Aichi.
None of this would have been
possible without your help.
On behalf of
the planet Cray, thank you.
Until next time.
Huh?
Uh‐oh.
Sorry, I totally blanked out.
Rekka?
What?
Bro, bro!
Aichi, you did it!
Wow, this means that we're...
we just won
the national championship!
I can't‐‐
(sobbing)
It's okay, Kamui.
That was
an incredible card fight.
Epic battle, yo.
That was awesome.
I knew he could do it.
Looks like my number one pupil's
been doing his homework.
(giggling)
I'm so proud of those guys.
♪
So, what now?
I dunno, I think I'd just
like to go someplace else.
And it's probably time
we changed the team policy
on losing games.
(gasps)
Don't you think, Asaka?
Really?
♪
Next time, Kai,
I'm gonna beat you
with my own strength
the way I always wanted to.
Ren.
♪
Well.
He's back; Thank you, Aichi.
♪
There are tears of joy
being shed down on
the stadium floor this day!
Team Q4 has come
from behind to win
their first
national championship.
Looks like our work
here is finally over.
What's next for the three of us?
There may come a time
when we're needed again.
But I think we deserve
to take a break and get
out of the public eye.
♪
Please join me in
a thundering round
of applause for
our top team: Q4!
(cheering)
♪
Ah!
Thank you.
Huh?
♪
Good morning.
That's not what
you said five minutes ago
when I woke you up.
Breakfast time.
Here.
Oh, thanks, Emi.
And I thought winning
the national tournament
would transform you
into someone a little easier
to live with.
Oh, don't be silly.
He's still your brother
even if he is a champion.
Yeah, after nationals,
things seemed to go back
to the way they'd always been.
See ya later!
With one major difference:
My Psyqualia,
that mysterious power,
has disappeared.
I haven't felt it once
since the tournament ended.
I'm still not sure exactly why.
Whatever, I'm happy it's gone.
I realize now that I
can be strong on my own,
and besides, Psyqualia
made me lose sight
of what actually mattered,
the reason I started playing.
Huh?
(all chuckling)
Hey, guys.
♪
(chuckling)
You took your time.
Sorry.
Kai's been waiting around
to have a game with you
all morning.
A proper game this time.
♪
Why'd you wait around
to battle with me?
'Cause you're one
of the strongest
card fighters I know.
Really?
Well, this match has been
a long time in the making.
I can't wait for Aichi
to beat that jerk.
No, on second thought,
Kai is a pretty cool dude.
You know what?
I really envy them.
There are probably thousands
of card fights going on all over
the planet right now,
but I seriously doubt
you could find anyone
that enjoys Vanguard
more than those two guys.
They're pretty lucky.
You ready, Aichi?
Mm!
‐Stand up, the Vanguard!
♪