[MERRIBIT] Still unable
to contact Tekkadan HQ,
the Earth Branch
is caught in a war
between the SAU and Arbrau.
Left in the dark,
the boys cry out,
but unfortunately for them,
no one is around to hear.
[TAKAKI]
Balfour Plain,
the border region where
the SAU and Arbrau forces
are deadlocked.
[TAKAKI] The conflict...
was started by a freak accident.
[TAKAKI] An SAU plane
was on a recon mission.
But crashed when its
systems were disrupted
by Mobile Suit Ahab reactors.
The SAU didn't
think the situation
warranted the use
of Mobile Suits,
so they were caught unprepared.
[TAKAKI] The SAU's troops
consist of their own
inexperienced defense force,
as well as Gjallarhorn's
SAU garrison force.
To compensate for this,
they're reinforced by troops
from the Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet.
[TAKAKI] On the opposing
side of the battlefield
are the inexperienced
defense force of Arbrau
and Tekkadan.
Our ragtag army also
includes a Mobile Suit team
belonging to Mr. Galan, who
joined as our staff officer.
Sporadic outbreaks
of attrition-warfare
have been going on
across the plain
for the past two weeks now.
All in all... we're just
being swept along.
Move out!
[TAKAKI]
No. Something's not right.
At this point, we've fought more
battles than I can count.
But this isn't like any of them!
There! An opening!
All right, let's break through!
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
Roger!
[ASTON yells]
[MCGILLIS]
Will this conflict never end?
Sir, originally, our plan was
to intervene with the troops
and force an end
to the situation.
However, we never imagined this.
Who would've thought
soldiers from Arbrau
would fight back
with such ferocity?
[MCGILLIS' MAN C]
General.
Please correct me if I'm wrong,
but wouldn't it be
better to resolve this
through official
diplomatic channels?
Don't be absurd. We lost
that option a while ago.
Otherwise there'd be no need
for us to be on the battlefield.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A] Arbrau's
prime minister, Makanai,
is still unconscious.
Even if we wanted
to try diplomacy,
the channels have been cut off.
And Gjallarhorn's garrison force
in Arbrau can't move, either.
Isn't it obvious?
That's exactly why the SAU came
to us to mediate the situation.
But at this rate, the
conflict will go on forever!
Sir, there's something
strange about this war.
Surely one side
should've won by now.
I have to say, their
tactics are astonishing.
They avoid large-scale battles
in favor of small skirmishes.
I sense a sort of genius
behind the timing
of their scattered deployments
and well-executed retreats.
Especially...
...the way this person
is capitalizing
on Tekkadan's lack
of leadership,
yet excellent mobility.
They're being strung along
like puppets on a string.
All right then, I think
that's all of 'em.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER D]
Aston!
There are three enemy
units heading your way!
We're pulling out.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER D]
We're not attacking?
We've finished our job here.
We'll have to come back for you.
[TAKAKI]
Okay!
All troops, we're
retreating, too!
[gasps]
Come back! Our orders are
not to pursue the enemy!
Shut the hell up,
you little punk!
If we don't finish this,
they'll just kill us later!
Is he crazy?
[LUX]
I'll get him!
Lux, don't!
[LUX]
Stop right there!
Lux, no!
[MCGILLIS]
This person has taken advantage
of the unclear
reasons for this war
and has used them to create
the perfect stalemate.
I have to wonder...
is that their objective?
This one makes 12 we've lost.
[GALAN] I'd like to pay
my respects, as well.
[TAKAKI]
Mr. Galan?
To this young, valiant
solider of Tekkadan.
Thank you, that's very kind.
[GALAN]
Want some?
Uh, no thanks.
[GALAN]
I know it's tough.
But now, it's time
for us to knuckle down.
Tekkadan is doing fine work.
Especially you two.
You're exceptional soldiers.
Without the pair of you, things
could've been far worse.
All things considered,
you're practically the captains
of the working units.
It must be degrating to have to
fight with those greenhorns
from the Arbrau Defense Force.
Keep up the great work.
Right! Yes, sir!
[GALAN laughs]
[GALAN]
Take care.
Since you're young,
some food and rest
should make you good as new.
[laughs]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
It's morning.
What day is it anyway?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
How would I know?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B] Well, how
many days have we been fighting?
I told you, I have no--
[ALL]
Huh?
Good work, guys.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
Thanks.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Be honest, Takaki.
Exactly how much longer
is this gonna go on?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER E]
And are we winning or losing?
We need to know.
According to Mr. Galan,
we have the upper hand for now.
Mr. Radice also said the boss
was happy with our work.
Can I ask you something?
What's this war about?
Both sides have battalions,
which is well over a
thousand soldiers each,
but we only attack
in small numbers,
then retreat just
when things get good.
I just don't see the point...
Well, I guess...
The point is none of
your goddamn business.
For now, just worry about
eating and sleeping
when you get a chance.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Y-Yeah...
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
We already know that.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER E]
Freaky... you almost never talk!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER F]
I know, right?
[TAKAKI] Sometimes, I feel
doubtful about this war too.
It feels like we've been on
the battlefield for years now.
Not too long ago, you and
I were eating dinner with Fuka
back in our little apartment.
It's like a dream.
[TAKAKI]
Hey.
Are you sensing anything, Aston?
Like what?
Something about this
war is different
from our other battles.
For some reason,
I haven't been able to
shake that feeling lately.
My head understands
why we're doing this.
Although, now and then,
I feel like I lose my way,
and forget what
I'm doing out here.
[footsteps]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER G]
A message!
[TAKAKI]
What is it?!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER G]
Marching orders!
Report to the command cen--
Again?! But we can't!
We've been fighting
since last night
and everyone's still exhausted!
This is a direct order
from Captain Galan!
[TAKAKI]
Captain? No!
Since when is Mr. Galan
in charge of Tekkadan?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER G]
Well... I mean...
It's just that he seems to
be the one in command
of all of our
missions these days,
so it made sense to call him--
[TAKAKI]
Understood.
Sorry. I'll be right there.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER G]
Thank you, sir!
[ASTON]
Takaki.
[JULIETA] You're quite the
workaholic, aren't you?
Do you ever stop tinkering
with your favorite little toy?
For your sake, I hope it's
gonna be ready for combat soon.
[VIDAR]
Patience.
This machine has a
rather unique system.
Unique system?
[VIDAR] I hear the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet
has run into a bit of trouble.
[JULIETA]
Of course they have!
After all, that gentleman with
the beard is in command now.
[VIDAR]
Beard?
Yep.
He's a seasoned tactician whom
Master Rustal trusts completely.
When it comes to organized
battle, there's no one better.
[VIDAR]
Perhaps.
They're up against
the new commander
of the Regulatory Joint Fleet.
It sounds as though you've
met Lord Fareed before.
[VIDAR]
Perhaps.
[JULIETA] Tell me...
who's underneath that mask?
[VIDAR]
Hmm.
I'm not sure myself.
[IOK] That McGillis
fellow was pretty cocky
when he started
the mediation job.
Although, he's not
making much headway.
[RUSTAL] It must be
weighing heavily on him.
After all, it's the
first armed clash
between the economic blocs.
The entire world is awaiting the
outcome with baited breath.
[IOK] The best part is, the
longer this war drags on,
the more his hard-earned
reputation will suffer.
Ha! I can almost see his tears.
And it's all thanks to your
clever planning, Master Rustal.
Your man is quite the operative.
That's true.
He does make it interesting
[TAKAKI]
The enemy is up ahead.
I know we're gonna defeat them.
After that... what'll
be waiting for us?
[ASTON]
Don't worry.
[gasps]
I'll always be here to
protect you... and Tekkadan.
[TAKAKI]
What's gotten into me?
As long as Mr. Chad
is in the hospital,
I have to be strong
for everyone!
[ASTON]
There they are.
Mobile Suit squad, with me!
I'll open up a path for you!
[ASTON] I wonder if
Mr. Chad has woken up yet.
He's always so reckless!
[EUGENE]
Yeah, the same as before.
We're tryin' everything,
but still can't get through
to the Earth Branch.
What's the point of
having the Ariadne
if they don't even
respond to us?
I hear ya.
I'll let you know as soon as I
get any new intel from Isurugi.
Got it?
[EUGENE]
Roger that.
[MERRIBIT] Our info comes
only from the news.
It's frustrating.
We have no insider intel,
and we still don't know
the status of our people.
And at this rate...
The Earth Branch and the guys
that I just sent over there,
I'm positive they're
up to the task.
Even if they don't hear
anything from me,
they've already prepared
themselves for the worst.
[LAFTER]
Talk about dedicated.
You do this every day.
Seriously,
is there any point to getting
bigger than you already are?
Leave me alone.
It's my hobby, okay?
I kinda get how
you feel, though.
Hell, to be perfectly honest,
I like that about you.
Well, just don't pull a muscle.
[ZACK]
Come on...
How are we supposed
to sit around eating
like nothing's
going on out there?
I know, it's weird.
If you ask me, this trip
is taking way too long.
I know what you mean.
Three weeks from Mars to Earth?
[ZACK sighs]
Something just feels off to me.
You must be worried about
Old Man Makanai, huh?
[KUDELIA]
I am.
But I get updates from the news.
I wonder if Chad's even alive.
Hard to say, given
our lack of info.
[EUGENE sighs]
We'll find out more
when we get to Earth.
No use worryin' about it now.
Yeah, that's a good point.
[HUSH]
Mikazuki.
I'm all done with the
Shiden simulation.
[MIKAZUKI]
Right.
Is there anything
else need to be done?
[MIKAZUKI] You can do
maintenance on your Shiden.
I already did the maintenance.
Then go work out.
[HUSH]
I did that, too.
Then get some rest.
Rest? Hey!
When we get to Earth,
I'm gonna be looking
at my first ever
Mobile Suit battle!
Shouldn't I be doing everything
I possibly can to prepare?!
There's no ti--!
[MIKAZUKI]
You need to rest up.
Huh?!
Now's your chance.
'Cause once we get there,
you won't be able to.
[EUGENE]
Take Mikazuki's advice.
Listen up!
Instead of worrying about
things you can't change,
you should be getting some rest.
Don't stress over a
tomorrow you can't see.
And even if Hell
is waiting for us,
we'll use every ounce of our
strength to get through it
and make it back alive!
That is the Tekkadan way!
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS mumbling]
That was quite the rousing
speech, Deputy Boss.
He's only imitating
what Orga does.
[EUGENE]
Shut your trap, Mikazuki!
[MIKAZUKI] Coming from the
one with the big mouth.
[EUGENE]
You little...
[AKIHIRO]
Stay alive, guys.
I'm on my way.
[STUDENT A]
Well, that's what mom said!
[STUDENT B]
No way!
Bye, see you later.
[STUDENT A]
You going to the hospital again?
[STUDENT B] This must be
really hard for you.
[FUKA]
I'm okay. See you guys tomorrow.
Hello, Mr. Chad.
[NURSE A]
Oh, it's you again.
About Mr. Chad,
how is he doing?
The same as yesterday.
Unlike the treatment systems
you had back on Mars,
Earth regeneration units take
longer to heal someone.
But the up-side is, once it's
done, he'll be a lot better.
[FUKA]
Is this right?
Should I really be doing this?
[FUKA]
Takaki... I hope you're okay.
[ARBRAU SOLDIER B]
They got Itagami!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Keep moving, or you'll--
No, Tori!
Takaki's what?!
You sure?!
I am!
The enemy faked them out, and
now Mobile Suits are attacking!
Get all the Mobile Suits
up and running!
Come on, we have to
hurry! Let's move!
What?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER H]
Who's that?!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER I]
They're fast!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER J]
Isn't that Mr. Galan's Geirail?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER K]
Oh, no! They found us!
[TAKAKI]
We can't give up now!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER K]
But what else can we do?!
[TAKAKI]
Fuka...
[gasps]
Wow. That's amazing.
[GALAN]
Glad I made it in time.
If we lost you, Arbrau's entire
military would fall apart.
Thank you for
saving me, Mr. Galan.
I'm sorry I have to put
you through all this,
but we have to double down
and work even harder.
Our victory is at hand!
And then, you'll
be heading home!
So be patient and hang in there.
The tough calls will
end soon enough.
[TAKAKI]
Yes, sir!
[TAKAKI] What am I
even doing right now?
[NEW TEKKADAN MEMBER D]
We're finally here!
[NEW TEKKADAN MEMBER E]
Awesome!
Oh, wow! So this is Earth.
[DANE]
Man, it sure is beautiful.
[HUSH]
Yeah.
It's right there.
Why are we standin' around
when it's so close
we could touch it?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm...
Something here
doesn't feel right.
Why the hell won't you give our
shuttle landing clearance?!
You better start
explaining, right now!
[CONTROLLER]
As it stands,
R-brau has declared
a state of emergency.
Landing clearances to
all shuttle spaceports
have been suspended.
[EUGENE] How many times
do I have to tell you?
We're Tekkadan!
You need us as military advisors
and backup for the
border conflict!
[CONTROLLER] I'm sorry, but we
cannot allow any exceptions.
[EUGENE] Don't you hang up!
I'm not done talkin' yet!
Well, that sucks.
And right when we were
about to arrive, too.
What do we do now, Deputy Boss?
[EUGENE]
Isn't it obvious?
We're not that
little gang anymore.
We'll find our own way through!
[RADICE] A report came in
from the Arbrau Spaceport.
The Hotarubi has departed
from the orbital station
and has left the area.
Everything's going swimmingly.
Having more kids here would
just complicate things.
Some of them might even be able
to put two and two together.
[RADICE]
Ha. I highly doubt that.
I must say, I am quite
impressed with your work.
Taming those irksome brats
is no small order.
[GALAN]
It's like you said,
those kids are
nothing but animals.
No different from dogs.
If you feed them and give
them a pat on the head
every once in a while,
they'll roll over
and obey their master
without a second thought.
Especially Aston.
That one's particularly fun.
Now I get it now.
Apparently, that's just the
way all Human Debris are.
Can't sleep, either?
I wasn't expecting to.
Lately, I've been thinking.
You said this was different from
other battles we've been in.
I think I know why that is.
This is all new.
It's our first time
fighting under someone
other than the boss.
That must be why.
Or maybe not...
Thanks, Aston.
I think you're right. That does
make things feel a bit weird.
[ASTON]
But is that so bad?
I don't really care who
I get my orders from.
[TAKAKI]
Huh?
[ASTON] The job of
Human Debris is to fight.
[gasps]
Don't talk like that!
[ASTON]
Hm?
This isn't like before!
It's not about orders!
We're allowed to
fight for ourselves
and nothing's gonna change that!
Takaki.
Look, I don't bring it up,
but I get scared
watching you out there.
Working in Tekkadan
means risking our lives.
I know that better than anyone.
I also know that
there's no guarantee
that we'll even live
to see tomorrow.
But I... I just don't wanna
see you accepting death
right from the outset.
Whaddya mean?
Mr. Galan is incredible.
Somehow he's able to see the
big picture of this entire war.
If we follow him,
we'll win, I know it.
He even said we'll be
home before too long.
Let's live through this and
go home together, Aston.
Whaddya say?
[ASTON]
Sounds good.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A] Please,
sir, you must reconsider!
This has gone on for
a month. Enough is enough.
If we let this stalemate
drag on any longer,
it'll cause problems
for us down the road.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A]
But, sir,
surely you don't need
to go in yourself--
There is no need to worry.
I'll be careful.
[GALAN]
What?
McGillis has gone in?
Yes! The recon squad
just reported it, sir.
Interesting. He's grown
tired of waiting.
[GALAN'S MAN A]
What should we do?
This is quite unexpected.
I planned on toying
with him for years,
until every remnant
of his status
and reputation was ruined.
I want you to prepare my Geirail
and your Scharfrichters for
battle, on the double.
And one more thing! Get those
Tekkadan kids out of bed!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER L]
Move your ass!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER M] Get the
Landman Rodis ready first!
[GALAN] Attention! This will
be the final battle!
All right, troops,
let's take their boss's head
and bask in our victory!
Takaki.
[TAKAKI] If this is
really the last battle,
I don't need to be in command.
So then I'll go.
I'll see you later, Takaki.
[chuckles]
[TAKAKI]
I'm... just being swept along.
[AKIHIRO grunting]
[AKIHIRO]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"My Friend."
Mikazuki, you ditched
training today.