[ORGA] Thanks for all
you've done for us.
And make sure to give my
thanks to Bro, as well.
Feeling's mutual.
Living here was much more
amusing than I thought it'd be.
Come to think of it,
I never beat you even once.
But that'll change by the
next time we see each other,
so you had better
stay on your toes!
[ECO] Aw, we'd miss you too
much if it took that long.
I don't think you realize what
you're getting yourself into,
my friend. It'd take years for
you to be as strong as our ace.
Heck, we might never
see you again.
That stings.
Hey, have any of you
guys seen Lafter?
[AZEE]
Hm? Oh, Lafter's...
Ya know, Akihiro,
you really scared me
in that battle we
had a while back.
You were injured, yet you still
plunged headlong into danger
without a second thought.
That may be, but everything
worked itself out in the end.
That's not the issue, Akihiro!
You have people under you now,
so being that reckless
isn't an option!
That's true...
And you're not gonna
be around anymore.
[LAFTER]
Uh?
To be honest, the only
people around this place
I could really trust to watch
my back were you and Mikazuki.
And you're right, I do need
to think things through.
I suppose...
That's good enough for now.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm? What is?
Here, let's shake on it.
[AKIHIRO gasps]
[AKIHIRO exhales]
[AKIHIRO] Thanks for all of
your help. Take care, okay?
You too, Akihiro.
[IOK]
What do you mean, impossible?
[JASLEY] While I admit it's a
great honor to have the son
of the Kujan family come
directly to us for assistance,
a direct confrontation
with Tekkadan
wouldn't be the wisest
course of action for--
Enough posturing!
I was a fool to rely
on someone like you!
No matter the personal cost,
I must have my revenge against
Tekkadan to repay the loyalty
of my subordinates who lost
their lives in that conflict.
[JASLEY] Please don't
misunderstand me, sir.
[gasps]
[JASLEY] I'm simply suggesting
that there might be
a more effective strategy
for us to utilize.
[gasps]
[JASLEY]
Tekkadan is merely an enforcer.
The real enemy isn't them,
but rather the ones who
are pulling their strings.
[IOK growls]
Out with it!
Who are these mongrels?!
[JASLEY]
The Turbines.
Tell me more.
[JASLEY] They're one of Teiwaz's
subsidiaries led by Naze Turbin,
who's like Tekkadan's
older brother.
Truth be told, the only thing
currently allowing Tekkadan
to hold on to their position
is the support they're
getting from the Turbines.
The Turbines, huh?
I get it now!
They're the target!
[IOK'S MAN 39A]
Master Iok,
what are you going to
do with these things?
Their use is prohibited under
the weapons ban treaty.
I'm well aware of that fact,
which is the very reason
why they're crucial to
the success of my plan.
Apologies, but shouldn't we
get Master Rustal's approval
before we begin?
That won't be a problem.
This operation will be for
Master Rustal's benefit
as well as ours.
We'll kill two, no,
make that three birds,
with the proverbial stone.
[IOK'S MAN 39A]
Are you certain things
are going to go your way, sir?
[IOK laughs] You couldn't
possibly comprehend this, but...
...this is just the
way politics work.
[IOK'S MAN 39A]
I see...
[JULIETTA]
Master Iok.
Don't try to stop me, Julietta!
I have to do this!
[JULIETTA]
I shall go with you.
The prototype machine has just
completed all of the necessary
bench tests. Now we only
need to try it in the field.
I want an opportunity to
evaluate its full capabilities.
[IOK]
But Julietta--
Give me this chance.
Please, I beg you. I must
become strong as fast as I can.
[gasps]
I understand, Julietta.
Let's defeat the
Turbines together!
I will bear full
responsibility for this!
The only thing I ask is that you
obey my orders no matter what!
[RUSTAL] I don't know
what to do about Iok.
Certainly, there's a right
job for every man,
but my plans for him do not
involve his strength.
[VIDAR]
Then what precisely do you want?
The Kujan family admires Iok.
Any member would gladly
lay down their life for him.
Although, this devotion
isn't purely out of loyalty
for their lord. His passion
have the uncanny ability
to motivate people in
ways they never expected.
If you would only remove
that mask of yours,
Iok wouldn't have to resort
to such unsavory methods.
[VIDAR] I am indebted to you
for saving my life, however,
until I can ascertain that
man's real intentions--
Of course, I can certainly
understand that.
And yet, comprehending the
depths of another man's mind
is no small task.
Especially of a man like him.
[VIDAR] I believe I have
the right to understand him
better than anyone else.
After all, I was killed by him.
[MCGILLIS] Iok Kujan is cracking
down on the Turbines, is he?
[ISURUGI] Yes.
He's taken control of every
backdoor route the Turbines use.
Even the Krate Corridor.
So, someone within Teiwaz
leaked that kind of valuable
information, did they?
Anything else to report?
While at headquarters he
stopped at Warehouse Four
and took something
upon his departure.
From Four?
Tell me something, do you
remember it, Isurugi...?
The weapon Tekkadan used
to halt the Mobile Armor's
advance on Mars.
Sir?
Their long-range weapon
that it was a Dáinsleif.
Its power is so great it can
even pierce Nano-laminate Armor.
Because of its destructive
faculty, Gjallarhorn has banned
possession and use of
this massive railgun.
But they appeared to use
conventional warheads,
so they're in a grey area
as far as the terms of
the ban are concerned.
[ISURUGI]
So that means Lord Kujan is--
A Mobile Armor, a legacy
of the Calamity War,
has been discovered.
And a Gundam Frame,
piloted by Mikazuki Augus,
has displayed to the world the
power of the demons of old.
The resulting hysteria
and dread will no doubt
drive the people into
a state of frenzy.
Eventually, our entire
era might be engulfed.
Curious...
It feels as though
ancient weapons
are being brought out in droves.
However, these events might be
caused by the tide of the times.
[ISURUGI]
Then...
Get in touch with all of
our dedicated comrades.
Inform them that the moment
has come to take action.
Yes, sir!
[footsteps]
[MCGILLIS]
If the person behind that mask
is truly whom I think it is...
then it would mean Rustal Elion
already has his claws
around my throat.
And yet, he will never
be able to seize my soul.
[ATRA]
Is floating like that easier?
Uh?
I brought you something to eat.
[MIKAZUKI]
Nice.
[ATRA]
Oh!
Here ya go.
It looks like an umbilical cord.
What does?
Oh! Ms. Azee and Lafter's trip.
They should've made it back home
to the Turbines by now, right?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[ATRA] Things are a little
quieter at Tekkadan
without them.
But I bet the Turbines are
happy they're finally back.
Especially the children,
and the little babies, too.
[ATRA]
It's really simple!
I want you to have
a baby with Mikazuki!
Uh? Uh!
What?!
[ATRA chugging]
[sighs]
Do you feel a bit better now?
I do...
That's good, but what came
over you so suddenly?
Uh...
[laughs]
[KUDELIA]
Hmm?
[ATRA] I was thinking about
something the shop manager
told me a long time ago.
That children are like tethers.
[KUDELIA]
"Tethers"?
[ATRA]
She said that when her husband
wouldn't commit to settling
down, she was able to
convince him to because she
was pregnant with his baby.
Oh... Huh?!
Is that why you...?
Yeah...
Mikazuki might be
going far away,
so I was thinking you
could be his tether.
Well, if that's the case,
couldn't you do it Miss Atra?
Uh?! No way, that's impossible!
[ATRA]
I couldn't... because...
...Mikazuki is a really
amazing person.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[ATRA] I'm obviously
nowhere near good enough
for someone like him.
[KUDELIA]
You are also wonderful, Atra.
[ATRA]
Huh?
[KUDELIA] When I look at this
bracelet you gave me,
it makes me feel
connected to you.
And that connection
gives me courage.
Miss Kudelia...
And just think about it,
Mikazuki always wears his.
I'm sure he feels the
same way as I do.
Ya know?
Oh, I see.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, then I'll try
my hardest too!
Huh?
Let's both promise that we'll
tether Mikazuki to us!
[chuckles nervously]
And regardless of which
one of us manages to do it,
there won't be any hard
feelings, okay?
Huh? I... Wait!
Wh-What?!
Uh?
Uh...
So, about babies!
They sure are...
great, aren't they?!
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah, that line
around their wrists is neat.
That's true! Babies're really
cute, don't ya think?!
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm-hm.
They look like a tasty ham.
[ATRA growls]
What?
No more food for you.
[MIKAZUKI]
I can't reach.
[ATRA]
I said no more.
[MIKAZUKI]
I... I can't... reach it...
What the heck are they
doing down there?
[ECO] All right, girls! I
think that did the trick!
We might've finally gotten
the right settings dialed in!
It's about damn time.
This Hekija is turning out
to be a lot more troublesome
than I thought it would be.
I know, right?
It's as if its lack of
quirks is its quirk.
That's true, but for a ragtag
group like Tekkadan,
with all sorts of crazy pilots
and intense missions,
this might be the best machine
for them in the long run.
[AZEE]
Hmm?
[LAFTER]
Hm? What?!
Oh, no. It's nothing at all.
[AMIDA] Thanks for your
hard work, girls.
[BOTH gasp]
[LAFTER]
Good to see you!
Sorry to put you
to work so soon.
Hopefully you've had
some time to rest up.
We're doing just fine.
Besides, keeping
busy is a good way
to keep my mind off of things.
[AMIDA]
Hmm?
[ECO]
Hey, Lafter!
I've changed the setting the way
you asked me to, so what now?
[LAFTER] We're all set!
I'm going out again!
Seems like a lot
happened out there.
While you were living
with Tekkadan, I mean.
Oh, well...
It's sort of hard to describe.
It's all over your faces.
You're such good honest kids.
Don't ever forget that
you're my pride and joy.
We won't, Ma'am.
[NAZE]
Really?
So I guess the time has come
for Lafter to be taken
away by another man.
[AMIDA] You almost seem
happy about it, Darling.
Now that you mention it,
I am in a way.
Lafter and the others
aren't just wives to me.
In some respects, they're
like my daughters, too.
And, if one of them
were to select
a boyfriend from Tekkadan,
it would mean that my daughter
had grown into a savvy woman
who knew what to
look for in a man.
Of course I'm happy.
You're really bringing
up Tekkadan, again?
Every other word you say
is about them these days.
Huh? Oh, you're drinking
the cheap stuff again?
[NAZE]
I like it.
It's the drink we had
when we first met.
That brings back memories.
It was a cheap little spaceport
bar on Mars, as I recall.
[AMIDA]
You want me as your bodyguard?
[NAZE]
Will you do it?
There's a big, slightly
dangerous score coming up.
You sure about this?
Many in this line of
work tend to back out
the instant they
learn I'm a woman.
[NAZE]
That's a strange thing to say.
Given a choice between the two,
I'd choose a woman
every day of the week.
[laughs] And you say
I'm the strange one.
[AMIDA]
You were a maverick trafficker,
and you hired me, a mercenary,
to stand by your side.
And that's how
our journey began.
[NAZE chuckles]
Man, she sure is somethin'.
[NAZE] I fell hard for you,
both on the job and off.
I pressed you to make our
partnership permanent, but...
I can't do this anymore.
I have an escort job
for the Peinnutz Company.
Wait, are you talking about
that all-girl shipping company?
[AMIDA] The long-distance
freight business was
where women running away
from various bad situations
would end up.
It was one of the worst
destinations you could have.
[NAZE] Those poor souls
worked for dirt cheap,
and had to take on
dangerous jobs
that the men were afraid to do.
And you were willing to escort
ships belonging to these women
whenever you could.
[AMIDA whimpering]
[AMIDA] Scars like these are
an occupational hazard.
[NAZE]
Yes, and they're beautiful.
[gasps]
[AMIDA laughs]
[NAZE] Tell me. Is there
anything I can do to help?
[AMIDA] And that's how
the Turbines got started.
You saved women who were being
exploited in the underworld
by making them
your nominal wives.
You also gave them jobs
and made them your crew.
Of course, you did enjoy
the fringe benefits.
[NAZE]
What can I say?
I never look a gift
horse in the mouth.
[AMIDA] To ensure the
safety of the women,
you chose to become
a Teiwaz subsidiary
so you'd have a strong supporter
during dangerous times.
[AMIDA] After that,
you gathered together
all of the women-only
shipping companies
I'd ever had dealings with and
found a way to organize them.
You built a massive
transportation network
reaching from Earth to Jupiter.
We became a huge organization
with over 50,000 members.
Even Mr. McMurdo acknowledged
your achievements,
and you began to rise up
the ranks within Teiwaz.
[JASLEY'S MAN 35A] Using women
to make his way in the world...
Ha. He should be ashamed.
Heh. My thoughts exactly.
[growls]
[gasps] What're you...?
Hey, let those fools
say what they want.
[AMIDA gasps]
Naze!
[babies laughing]
[NAZE]
Are you still sulking?
[AMIDA]
Why did you stop me back there?
[NAZE] Well for one, they didn't
say anything that wasn't true.
The thing is, I've been able to
make my way in the world
because of you.
Don't give me that!
[NAZE]
Women are the sun, you know.
And if the sun doesn't
keep shining its light,
we men will wither and die.
[AMIDA]
Naze...
Ew.
[BOTH gasp]
[NAZE]
Oh no, she peed!
[cries]
[NAZE] Now that I've had
some time to reflect on it,
saying I have women to thank
means something
a little different
than it did before.
[AMIDA]
Uh?
[NAZE] I've been thinking about
something I told Orga once.
[NAZE]
It's funny...
You talk about your blood mixing
and your connection
with each other.
But you don't call people
like that your "friends."
[BOTH gasp]
That's "family."
[ORGA gasps]
[NAZE] I swear...
You should've seen Orga's face.
He looked so astonished when he
heard me use the word family.
Can you blame him? I'm sure
he didn't know what family was.
Then again, we women
were the same way.
Yeah, it was like
that with me, too.
That's the reason why every
time I look at those kids,
I can't help but see younger
versions of us.
I've only been able to
come this far because you,
and the rest of
our dear Turbines,
taught me the true
meaning of family.
Which is why, now that
they've finally found
a family to call their own,
I want them to cherish it,
and not do anything that might
put that precious
gift in danger.
[alarm blares]
[AMIDA gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE 39A]
There's an emergency!
What's going on?
[FEMALE VOICE 39A] We've just
gotten word that our
transportation teams and offices
are being raided by Gjallarhorn!
[BOTH gasp]
[MCMURDO] I'm thrilled that
you came by to see me,
Mikazuki my boy.
I heard what happened with
you and that Mobile Armor.
Eliminating a monster
from the Calamity War...
My, my, it appears you're
full of surprises.
I don't know if I
would go that far.
[MCMURDO]
Don't talk with your mouth full.
I thought this guy was
gonna be a lot scarier,
but he's just a normal old man.
And he seems to have a
soft spot for Mikazuki.
--[door creaks]
--[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A] Old man!
[MCMURDO]
What's wrong?
[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A]
Sorry to intrude,
but it's about the crackdown
by Gjallarhorn.
[MCMURDO] Ah, that matter
with the Turbines?
The usual harassment, I'm sure.
Naze's well equipped
to handle it--
[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A]
That's just it, sir!
Naze's gone into hiding!
He did what?
They weren't dealing in
anything illicit, were they?
[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A]
No, sir.
However, we did receive a report
about a banned weapon
being found aboard
their freight ship.
A banned weapon, you say?
[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A]
Something called a Dáinsleif.
Apparently, they were used
during the Calamity War.
It appears the Turbines had
prepared it for Tekkadan
to use on Mars.
[HUSH]
You're kidding!
I had no idea we used dangerous
weapons like that!
[ATRA]
Yeah, it's news to me!
From what I gathered, sir,
that weapon is what
triggered the crackdown.
Begin gathering the
top brass at once.
[MCMURDO'S MAN 39A]
Yes, sir.
[door creaks]
[BOTH gasp]
[MCGILLIS]
They probably meant the Flauros
you used against
the Mobile Armor.
It's the same kind of
weapon as the Dáinsleif.
[gasps] Then it's
our fault that Bro is...
Isn't there something you
guys can do on your end
to help fix this mess?!
[MCGILLIS]
I'll do what I can, of course,
but this situation falls
under the purview
of the Arianrhod Fleet.
Unfortunately, the Outer
Earth Orbit Regulatory
Joint Fleet won't be
able to do much.
[ORGA whimpers]
[JASLEY] Never thought I'd
say it, but that spoiled brat
is actually doin' a
pretty darn good job.
However strong those
girls may be,
they won't stand a chance
against Gjallarhorn.
What're you gonna do
about the old man?
If he gets wind of
what you're up to--
I can assure you he's
not that stupid.
At his age, he knows a dead son
can't take care of his father.
It doesn't matter if
he has a favorite son
amongst the bunch, in the
end he'll have to rely on
the one that lives.
[AMIDA] Our enemy this time
isn't just Gjallarhorn.
If they've uncovered the
locations of our secret routes
and disguised offices,
then it means...
Yes, it means that we
were stabbed in the back
by one of our own.
Do you think that
Jasley's behind this?
It's horrible to even think it,
but it could be the old man.
Either way,
it looks like the time has come
to start preparing for
the worst, my dear.
--[ding]
--Huh?
I-It's a QCCS call.
[gasps] From Tekkadan!
[NAZE]
Heh.
Go ahead and put it through.
[CHLOE]
Right away!
Good, I reached you!
Send over the Hammerhead 's
flight path!
We'll head out right now--
[NAZE]
Stay out of this.
[gasps] Bro!
We've become somewhat of
an illegal organization.
If your connection to
us were pointed out,
what do you think would
happen to Tekkadan?
Listen, you're only in this mess
because we used the Flauros to--
That has nothing
to do with this.
The Flauros was only the pretext
they chose to frame us with.
That's all there is to it.
[ORGA gasps]
[NAZE] My guess is whoever put
this into motion is expecting
you guys to get
wrapped up in it.
Doing something rash is the same
as playing their
sick little game.
Anyway, this is all a result
of Teiwaz's internal strife.
To be perfectly frank, it has
nothing to do with you guys.
[ORGA]
Hey, we're part of Teiwaz, too!
It has everything to do with us!
No.
It wouldn't matter if
this didn't involve us!
I'd do anything to save you!
Even if I--
[NAZE]
Just hear me out would ya?
It's true that I exchanged the
cup of brotherhood with you.
But even so... I'm not
really your family, Orga.
What're you saying?
You can't lose sight
of your objective.
Above all else,
you must remember
what it is you have to protect.
Everything else
takes a back seat.
But, Brother--
[NAZE]
Remember this. It takes more
than just your average resolve
to make your family happy.
You don't have time
to get bogged down
by other people's petty details.
Don't forget that becoming
Sovereign of Mars
is to make life easier for the
members of Tekkadan.
Those were your words, right?
[NAZE] So, I want you
to keep looking forward
and protecting your
family, Tekkadan.
Put everything else
out of your mind.
You got that... Orga Itsuka?
[ORGA]
Brother...
[NAZE]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans,
"Lit By A Blazing Sun."
Question: What does a flower
need in order to bloom?
Water? That's not wrong, but
the correct answer is the sun.
I love you.