[MERRIBIT] In the chaotic battle
against the fallen angel,
it makes no distinction
between enemies of the past
and those of the present.
Does the dying scream
echoing across the gorge
belong to one of us, or to it?
[RIDE]
Mr. Mikazuki...
I... I did something
I shouldn't've done.
And now it's...!
[MIKAZUKI]
Ride, can you move?
[RIDE] Huh...? Oh, yeah.
I'm not too banged up...
My Shiden's another story.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hang tight.
Huh? What is this?
[RIDE]
Mr. Mikazuki?
You okay, Barbatos?
[beeping]
Mr. Mikazuki, watch out!
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[HUSH] Mr. Mikazuki! We couldn't
find any survivors at the plant.
What should we do next?
Mr. Mikazuki...?
[MIKAZUKI]
That's weird.
[HUSH]
Huh? What's weird?
[MCGILLIS]
Hm... Another Gundam Frame.
[ISURUGI] This machine doesn't
correspond to anything
in Gjallarhorn's database.
But according to the frequency
fingerprint I'm reading,
its reactor is similar to
those used by Gjallarhorn.
Could it be one of
Rustal's soldiers?
If you would, General,
please stand back.
[ISURUGI]
You there, in the Mobile Suit!
State your unit and rank!
[VIDAR] To think we'd
meet again on Mars.
But here we are,
in the land where all of
your betrayals began.
And yet...
[JULIETTA] Vidar, what
are you doing out there?
I've already managed to
rendezvous with Master Iok.
Hurry up and join us! Fall in!
[VIDAR]
Understood. I'll be right there.
[ISURUGI] Identify yourself now,
or we will respond with force!
[VIDAR]
Something puzzles me...
[gasps]
[VIDAR] How can you pilot the
same model that Carta Issue
perished in, as she cried
out for your love...?
Do you even care?
[MCGILLIS grunts]
[ISURUGI]
Answer!
If not, we'll have to--
[ISURUGI]
Stop!
[MCGILLIS]
No. Leave him.
[ISURUGI]
What? But General, he...
[AKIHIRO]
What happened to Ride?
[CHAD] Apparently,
Mikazuki headed over,
but it sounds like they
ran into some trouble.
[AKIHIRO]
What?!
I'd like to go help them out,
but we have to make that
thing head towards us.
Damn it! If that's the
case, I'll act as bait!
[CHAD]
Akihiro!
[AKIHIRO yells]
[AKIHIRO groans]
[gasps]
No, Akihiro!
[CHAD] What happened?!
Say something, Answer me!
[SU MEMBER 37A]
Mr. Chad!
[CHAD]
Report this to the Boss! Hurry!
[SU MEMBER 37A]
Roger!
[CHAD]
Look after Akihiro.
[SU MEMBER 37B]
Yes, sir.
[SU MEMBER 37C]
What about you?
That's simple. I'm gonna
that thing's attention!
[SU MEMBER 37C]
By yourself?! But you can't!
[CHAD]
Now get moving!
Eat this!
That's it, come after me!
It's so hot... So, that's
the beam weapon, huh?
Well, at least I finally
got its attention!
[MERRIBIT]
A report from the Second Unit!
They've successfully lured
the Mobile Armor
back to the planned route.
That's great.
We might be able to
pull this off in time.
Boss, wait. The Gusion
is out of commission.
Barbatos has also
stopped responding
and is standing by
on the sidelines.
[YUKINOJO]
Both Akihiro and Mikazuki?
That's right.
They have no idea
why their machines
suddenly stopped working.
The Mobile Armor's our priority.
But without Akihiro and Mika, we
just don't have the firepower.
Let's have the
First Unit head out!
We'll also send
Ms. Lafter and Ms. Azee.
One more thing.
Get in touch with McGillis.
Yes, sir. Understood.
[ORGA] And Tell Eugene to get
the explosives ready ASAP!
[MERRIBIT]
Will do!
[ORGA] Listen... I need you to
check on Mika and Akihiro.
[YUKINOJO]
You got it, boss.
I'll let you know when
I learn something.
[EUGENE] Listen up!
We need to hurry, people!
That Mobile Armor's gonna
be passin' through here
before we know it!
The plan's success
is in our hands now!
[JULIETTA]
Is that clear, Master Iok?
We'll move out as soon
as Vidar gets here.
Is your machine still
operational, sir?
[IOK]
Thank you, Julietta.
I had no idea that you
cared so much about me.
Pardon?
[IOK] And yet, I must still go
and fulfill my obligation!
If I don't do this,
I'll never be able to
face my men in Heaven!
Wha--? Oh, you have
got to be kidding me!
I came here to rescue you,
not help you--!
[JULIETTA]
Oh, no!
[IOK] The tears that
were shed by my men--
those tears have now
become my flesh and bone.
Those men died for me,
so it's my duty to show
that heartless Mobile Armor just
how precious life really is!
[gasps]
[IOK]
Farewell!
[JULIETTA]
Of all the...
I have better things
to do than babysit!
Just where the hell
are you, Vidar?!
[YUKINOJO] What's the deal
up there? How's Akihiro?
[ZACK]
Not good, Pops.
It looks like he's
down for the count.
[YUKINOJO]
Damn, we can't even
take him off the Alaya
Vijnana in that condition.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hey Pops, where's Ride?
Oh, he was hurt,
so I sent him on back to
headquarters, earlier.
What about you?
How are you holding up?
I'm doin' okay.
Although, ever since
it saw that bird,
Barbatos hasn't been
listening to me, at all.
[YUKINOJO] You mean the
Mobile Armor? I wonder why?
[ZACK]
I might know.
Huh?
Honestly, I think the
system shut down happened
because of the two different
kinds of limiters.
Where'd you get that info?
Why don't you take
a look at this?
These are the system logs for
the Barbatos and Gusion.
[YUKINOJO]
Hmm?
Well, the Alaya Vijnana
system usually feeds back
lots of data to the pilot.
But in these cases, it's been
excessively restrained.
However, the output limiter on
the machines themselves have
been disengaged.
To put it in layman's terms,
we've got a situation where the
system that protects the pilots
is butting heads with the suits,
who want to go full throttle.
So, if I had to guess,
that's the reason why
neither of the machines
are working properly.
Where in the world did you learn
about all this stuff, Zack?
I used to study this stuff,
but that was before I
joined up with Tekkadan.
I mean, you'd never guess it,
but I was a pretty good student.
Well, then do something,
book worm!
In case you forgot,
we're about to go toe-to-toe
with that Mobile Armor!
[ZACK] Oh, you're right.
That is a problem, isn't it?
[YUKINOJO]
Hmm.
[radio static]
[YUKINOJO] Orga, it looks like
we won't be able to send in
Barbatos or Gusion to
fight the Mobile Armor.
[ORGA]
What're you talkin' about?
[YUKINOJO]
From what I understand,
there's some kind of system
in Gundam Frames
that reacts to
the Mobile Armors.
As long as they're
fighting those things,
these symptoms will keep
rearing their ugly heads.
A system, huh?
[YUKINOJO] Yeah. Even if we were
to get them to work somehow,
if we send the Gundams
out there again,
it could end up being
a repeat of Edmonton.
If that's what we're lookin' at,
we can't let Mika and
Akihiro go up against it.
[YUKINOJO] You're right,
as much as I hate to say it.
[MERRIBIT] Hey Boss,
we have a call from Ms. Lafter.
[ORGA gasps]
[LAFTER] Aren't Eugene
and his team ready yet?!
[AZEE] These bastards
are moving a lot faster
than we thought they would!
We can't hold them off for long!
[ORGA]
Eugene, you good?
[EUGENE]
Already?! Crap!
I guess we've got no choice...
Change of plans!
Try to get 'em scattered!
They're almost on top of us!
[CHAD] All right people,
stand your ground!
[LAFTER]
Just a bit more!
We can make this work!
I know it!
Yeah, we might be
able to do this.
[gasps]
What the--?!
No, the Mobile Armor is...
[DANTE]
Hey, guys...
The Mobile Armor along with
its sub units just sped up!
[EUGENE]
Huh?! Why would it do that?
I'm so sorry Eugene.
They got through!
Are you ready, yet?!
[MEMBER 37B]
Almost!
[MEMBER 37C]
Who is that?
Is that the one that just fired?
[EUGENE] Wait, is that...
Gjallarhorn?
The barrel has burned out.
That was my last shot.
I'm well beyond my limit.
Did you feel it?
That is the pain of those who
believed in me and died!
This is it for me.
But I regret nothing!
I shall die a magnificent death.
I have done my family proud.
[JULIETTA]
No.
Even in death, there's no
cure for your stupidity.
[JULIETTA]
So you might as well live.
[groans]
[MEMBER 37B] The target has
passed the ambush point.
[EUGENE growls]
[EUGENE]
What the hell?!
[EUGENE] I'm sorry, Orga.
It broke through.
[ORGA]
Are you ok?
[EUGENE]
Yeah.
But I can't believe that
Gjallarhorn idiot...
What do they think
they're doing?!
I'll come up with our next move.
As for you guys, get back to
headquarters and resupply.
Lemme guess, we still can't
get through to McGillis?
[MERRIBIT]
No.
Well, keep trying.
[MERRIBIT]
Yes, sir.
If this battle is
Tekkadan's last stand,
then we'd never become
equal to Gjallarhorn.
[door creaks]
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia?
Please try not to worry.
If there's anyone who can
save Chryse, it's Mikazuki.
[KUDELIA]
That is what I asked him to do.
I asked him to,
and yet I'm still...
No, it's because I asked,
that I'm so worried.
[ATRA]
Be honest with me, Miss Kudelia,
you like Mikazuki quite
a bit, don't you?
[gasps]
[KUDELIA]
Uh. Well, I...
Yes. I like him.
[gasps]
Oh, you do?
[KUDELIA]
Of course.
And, I like you as well, Atra.
I like you too, Miss Kudelia.
And I like Mikazuki.
[KUDELIA laughs]
That's great.
[ATRA] Everything's going
to be fine. I know it.
Mikazuki always comes back...
[ATRA]
...back to us.
[MERRIBIT] Our plan to
separate the Mobile Armor
and Plumas failed.
Also, the Mobile Suits
took a great deal of damage
trying to hold them off.
Half of them are out of action.
There's absolutely no way
we can throw in the towel.
We're just gonna have
to try it again.
Boss. How can we?
Even if we attempted to
collapse the gorge again,
there's no time to
rig an explosion.
The Mobile Armor is still
on a course for Chryse,
and its speed is accelerating!
[growls]
[MIKAZUKI]
What now?
[MERRIBIT]
Mikazuki?
You want me to go?
Listen, I told you--
For once, I want you to
watch from the sidelines.
Get in touch with
Shino, would you?
[MERRIBIT]
Huh?
[YUKINOJO]
You mean were gonna...?
Yeah.
We're usin' the Flauros.
[gasps]
Ah, I follow you.
[MERRIBIT] Just a second.
You said it's dangerous
for a Gundam Frame to get
close to a Mobile Armor.
Yeah, that may be,
but it's the perfect machine
for this kind of job.
Uh. How do you mean?
And after you split them?
We attack the Mobile Armor
with everything we've got left.
Are you sure that'll be
enough to take it out?
[ORGA]
Well...
[alarm blares]
[ORGA, MERRIBIT gasp]
[MERRIBIT]
It's a call from Lord Fareed.
[ORGA]
Finally!
[MCGILLIS]
I see. Roger that.
I'm sure that we'll come
up with something,
in the place of your ace pilot.
[ORGA]
Thanks.
[ISURUGI]
What a disappointment.
No, it's fine.
They're still a necessary
means to achieve my goal.
I have faith in them.
But to maintain the proper
dynamic in our relationship,
I must make it perfectly clear
to them where we both stand.
So, if I'm to perceive
this correctly,
the honor and glory
must be ours.
Is that what you mean, sir?
Let's get to the mission point.
[ORGA]
It'll work out now.
With those guys on our side,
we'll have enough firepower--
[YUKINOJO]
And you're okay with this?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't this supposed to be
our big chance to show them
just how strong
Tekkadan really is?
"Sovereign of Mars"
has a nice ring to it,
but one slip-up and that title
will be more trouble
than it's worth.
Our next move will determine
whether or not we'll
be equals with them,
or just tools to be used
at their convenience.
This is going to
affect the entire
balance of power between us.
We'll just have to deal with it.
There's no way that we're
gonna abandon Chryse.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll go.
[gasps]
I told you, you're watchin'
from the sidelines.
If we're able to split the main
body from the smaller units
then this plan will be
a fair enough success.
You don't need to endanger
yourself for us to save face.
And besides, the Shiden
that I got from Teiwaz
is bein' delivered as we speak.
So, if need be--
[MIKAZUKI]
No.
"No"?
[MIKAZUKI]
I won't let you.
[VIDAR] Sorry for the wait.
I was held up.
[JULIETTA]
Forget it.
But since you're here,
you might as well watch
over Master Iok for me.
Julietta...
[JULIETTA]
I'll handle the Mobile Armor.
[IOK]
I get it!
You're gonna get revenge
for me, aren't you?!
Incredible!
You're so loyal!
[VIDAR]
If you don't hurry up and leave,
Tekkadan and Lord Fareed
will beat you to it.
[IOK]
You shall hold my pride!
[JULIETTA]
Please shut up, Master Iok!
[SHINO] Jeez, the Boss
sure says some crazy stuff!
That's for sure.
But why did you have to pull
me into the cockpit with you?
[SHINO] To be blunt,
I don't know the first thing
about working the new equipment,
so it's not like I had
any other option!
There's no time to lose, so
you're gonna be my manual!
Oh, man!
[SHINO]
But seriously, level with me.
Can this thing actually
get the job done?
[YAMAGI]
Yeah.
The Flauros' cannon will
be able to separate
the Mobile Armor
from the Plumas.
[SHINO] Why don't we fire it at
the Mobile Armor itself, then?
[BOTH groan]
[SHINO]
Whoa...!
Unfortunately, since we can't
get into close proximity,
it'll be next to impossible
to land a killing blow
on its nanolaminate armor.
[ORGA] Shino, the Mobile
Armor's almost here!
Get a move on!
[SHINO]
I'm on it!
[MW UNIT MEMBER 37A]
It's here!
[MW UNIT MEMBER 37B]
This is lookout point two!
The Mobile Armor's
passing by as we speak!
[MERRIBIT] Roger that.
Now, clear the area at once.
[LAFTER] Hey, are you positive
it's gonna work this time?
Yeah, we'll just
have to trust them.
I hate having to ask
them for help, though.
Oh, well...
[MERRIBIT] Ten seconds until
the Mobile Armor arrives.
[ORGA]
Did everyone hear that?
We're bringin' it down
right here and now!
No matter what it takes!
[MERRIBIT gasps]
It's here!
[LAFTER] Look at how packed
those things are!
How are supposed to
separate them?!
The walls are closer
together here,
so the Plumas are
huddled even tighter!
[MERRIBIT] Do what you
can to split them up!
[LAFTER] We're throwing
everything we have at them!
[AZEE]
There are just too many!
[SHINO] What do you want
us to do now, Boss?!
We've reached the mission area!
But I can't get eyes on
the target from here!
[growls]
[RIDE]
Leave it to me!
[gasps]
[SHINO]
Huh?!
Hey, that's...
...that's my Ryusei-go III!
[RIDE yells]
[RIDE groaning]
[RIDE] Catch me if you can,
bird monster!
Way to go Ride, you did it!
[AZEE] Now's our chance
to thin the herd!
All right, let's do this, Shino!
Yeah!
[YAMAGI] This is a
transformation mechanism
that neither Barbatos
nor Gusion have.
[YAMAGI] It's some kind of an
electromagnetic launcher...
[YAMAGI] ...that uses the
output of two reactors.
Ready when you are!
[ORGA]
You got this!
[SHINO]
Let's hear you roar!
Galaxy Cannon!
Fire!
[LAFTER, AZEE scream]
[SHINO]
Did you see that?!
This here's my
Ryusei-go IV!
And now, the rest
is up to you guys!
[MCGILLIS]
Is that a new Gundam frame?
It has astonishing power...
[ISURUGI]
Sir!
[RIDE grunts]
[RIDE yells]
[JULIETTA]
Rest assured Master Rustal,
I will deliver the Order
of the Seven Stars.
[ISURUGI]
That's one of the Arianrhod's!
[MCGILLIS]
We can't let them finish it.
[ISURUGI]
Right!
This is for Master Rustal!
[yells]
[grunts]
[MCGILLIS]
Amazing strength!
[MCGILLIS grunts]
The Mobile Armor has broken
through our defensive line!
Hey, Chad!
[CHAD] Sorry, but we
have our hands full!
[ORGA grunts]
Boss, where are you--?!
Orga, wait!
[MCGILLIS]
So this is it...
This is the true nature
of the Mobile Armors...
The horrors that nearly
annihilated mankind!
[RIDE groaning]
Damn it.
[RIDE grunting]
[JULIETTA grunts]
Wait, is that...?
He's here. But why?
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
I won't let you.
If things are really
that bad, I'll go in.
[ORGA]
Give it a rest, Mika!
Were you not listening
to what Pops said?!
You're not piloting Barbatos!
Don't you get it?!
If it's limiter starts
malfunctioning again, you'll--!
[MIKAZUKI]
It's okay. I've got this.
If I can still pilot Barbatos,
things won't be any worse
than they are now.
Mika...
[MIKAZUKI] Don't you remember
what you told me, Orga?
We'll take the shortest route.
But this is something
else entirely.
What if it means...
...you going out there leads
to losing you forever?
What are you even
talking about?
[ORGA]
Huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
The life that I have now
was given to me by you, Orga.
What that means is,
I have to give everything
I have for you.
All right. See that, Barbatos?
Your prey is right
in front of us.
I'm gonna take these
chains off of you, okay?
So, show me everything
you've got.
[MCMURDO]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans,
"Hunter of Angels."
Mikazuki. Don't stuff
yourself full of snacks.
I'm gonna prepare a
delicious meal for you.
And just who are you
calling an "old geezer?"