[IOK] Let's discuss the
war between the SAU
and the Arbrau Defense Force.
It's plain as day!
All responsibility lies
with the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet!
Thanks to this incident,
lingering tensions
between economic blocs
will surely break out
into open conflicts.
In its current state, what
could Gjallarhorn possibly do
to deter the fighting?
Lord Kujan, calm yourself!
Try looking at the
situation from this angle.
Collateral damage was
kept to a minimum
thanks to Lord Fareed.
However, given the number of
issues Earth currently faces,
I'm not sure if it's wise
for the Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet
to spread its reach to Mars.
Yes, now that you mention it,
perhaps that is a decision
that we ought to reconsider.
Even more troubling is
the man who they say
led the Arbrau Defense Force.
[IOK]
We've investigated!
There's not a single record
of the man in question
in any of the
databases on Earth.
Well, if you ask me,
I doubt such a man
existed at all.
It's more likely that Arbrau
concocted this fabrication
to cover their blunder.
[BAKLAZAN]
You have a point.
[GALLUS]
But according to the testimonies
of several witnesses,
someone was at the scene.
[FALK]
But we can trust the credibility
of these witnesses?
[GALLUS]
Well, it's all we've got.
That was quite the
ordeal you went through.
Still, it's just as
Lord Bauduin said.
Out of everyone,
you're the only one
who could've extinguished
the brushfire.
No.
Thank you, but this conflict
never should've happened.
It was my blunder.
I'll be. You've
matured quite a bit.
[RUSTAL]
Lord Fareed is here?
[RUSTAL'S MAN A]
Yes.
Apparently, he wants
to introduce us
to his newly-appointed heir.
Oh, that child his
mistress bore him.
Well, sir, rumor has it
that he and the child aren't
really related by blood.
[RUSTAL]
Are you serious?
If that's true, then why
would he choose him?
I've no clue.
Speak of the devil.
[RUSTAL]
Hello, boy.
How adorable, a physical book.
What are you reading?
Say, following your dad
everywhere must get boring.
Why don't I have someone
bring you something?
Is there anything you want?
Toys or snacks?
Just Bael.
[RUSTAL] Never in a million
years did I imagine
I'd hear a child say that name.
Still, you continue to surprise
me even to this day.
Especially with the way
you expertly handled
Iznario Fareed's downfall.
I haven't a clue what
you're talking about.
My apologies.
[RUSTAL] If you wanna
play dumb, so be it.
I have no intention of
denouncing you over that.
That said, there's something
I can't wrap my head around.
I was always under
the impression
that you were motivated
by a personal grudge.
But now that Iznario
is out of the picture,
what exactly are you planning
to accomplish with Gjallarhorn?
Well, I bet I'll find
out soon enough.
Although, when that day arrives,
something tells me that
our circumstances
will be vastly different.
And so, General?
[MCGILLIS] What did our
internal investigation
into Galan Mossa reveal?
As was expected, we
couldn't identify him, sir.
Taking a man and concealing
his actual identity...
That's not beyond the
scope of the Elion family.
Those were my
thoughts as well.
But what other tricks does
Rustal Elion have up his sleeve?
[MAKANAI]
I have to say,
I feel like Rip Van Winkle.
I woke up to find that a war
had started and ended.
It's more than a little jarring.
Both the SAU and
Arbrau Defense Force
have agreed to a peace treaty.
Tekkadan is going to
withdraw from Earth.
And Orga's here,
finalizing the paperwork.
[MAKANAI]
Hmm.
On a more uplifting note,
Chad Chadan is out
of the hospital.
Yes, he's already
gone back to work.
That's good. And
quite a relief too.
I couldn't rest in the afterlife
if a young man died
saving a geezer like me.
I always thought you were
more... cold-hearted th--
Wh-What I mean to say is,
you've always come
across as someone
who was level-headed
and impassive.
[MAKANAI chuckles]
A product of getting
older, most likely.
Well, it's wonderful to see.
[MAKANAI]
No.
At this age, change
doesn't really feel like
a positive improvement.
By some miracle, I got lucky
and survived this one,
but I can see now that
my time is limited.
Mr. Makanai...
[MAKANAI] But if I could
pass on the connections
I've built up over my lifetime,
I'd give them to those who still
have their lives ahead of them.
So, Kudelia Aina Bernstein...
...what do you say?
Could I talk you into
staying here on Earth?
[gasps]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
Those aren't strapped down yet!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Anybody know where my stuff is?!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
The mobile workers need their
fuel drained first!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER D]
There are live rounds in there!
Be careful!
[CHAD]
Hmm...
[AKIHIRO]
The list of casualties?
[CHAD]
Yeah...
Every one of these people died
because of my shortcomings.
[AKIHIRO]
You can't blame yourself.
[CHAD sighs]
[CHAD] This must be how the
boss feels all the time.
Oh, Chad...
[CHAD] Every second I'm
alive is agonizing...
I can't stand it.
It would've been much
better to step forward
and take the hit myself.
[LAFTER]
I didn't know you and Aston
had the same last name, Akihiro.
He was Aston Altland.
Yeah. Many Brewer boy
soldiers had no surname.
They were just Human Debris.
[LAFTER]
Uh, then...
[AKIHIRO]
My brother, Masahiro,
they were the ones that looked
after him when he was alive.
[LAFTER]
I see.
I should've talked to him
a lot more than I did.
[LAFTER]
With Aston?
Yeah.
It's too late after
they're gone.
[ORGA]
Hey, Takaki.
What's the story behind
these accounts?
[TAKAKI]
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Radice
handled those himself.
What about these?
[TAKAKI] Oh, those accounts
were his responsibility, too.
Well, that's a bust!
Radice was more clever
than I thought.
Even before the war,
the bastard had the Earth
Branch under his thumb.
[ORGA]
It couldn't be helped.
It's our fault.
We always let him
handle the office work.
[TAKAKI] I'm really sorry
for all of this, Boss.
You and Ms. Merribit were forced
to come to Earth because of me.
But now everything's so--
Hey, don't sweat it.
Ms. Merribit, can you check
these payment vouchers?
Will do.
I'll be going, then.
Poor Takaki, he's takin'
this pretty hard.
He lost a lot of his
comrades out there.
I don't blame him.
[MIKAZUKI]
What's wrong?
You seem like your kinda down.
[TAKAKI] I don't...
deserve to be in Tekkadan.
I bought all of
Mr. Radice's lies
and blindly followed the
orders of a total stranger.
Even though I knew
the boss's orders were
the most important, I...
[MIKAZUKI] The only thing you
did was carry out the work
that was assigned to you.
B-But I--
You obeyed those orders
because you thought they
came from Orga, right?
Yeah, but that's
still no excuse.
Besides, you settled it
with your own hands.
Are Orga and the
guys still at it?
Yeah, they are.
All right then.
[KUDELIA]
Takaki.
[TAKAKI]
Mr. Mikazuki is amazing.
[KUDELIA]
Uh?
Back then, we were still
in the Third Group of the CGS.
And one day, Mr. Mikazuki
shot the First Corps guys.
Everything changed
for us that day.
I did the same thing
that he did,
but nothing's
gonna change for me.
[KUDELIA] It might not be
my place to say this,
but hear me out.
I think all of you still
have a lot more to learn.
Really?
Yes, really.
For example, you may think
your choices are limited,
but actually, you have
a number of options,
though you can only choose one.
[TAKAKI] I don't think I could
ever make a decision like that.
[KUDELIA]
You know, making the right call
is difficult for everyone.
However, the more
you experience,
the more knowledge
you'll acquire.
And the more sensible
you become,
the easier it'll be to decide.
And you'll do it
all on your own.
[JULIETTA]
No good!
Work up a new simulation
that's actually a challenge!
This is useless for training!
[WORKER A]
Y-Yes, ma'am!
[VIDAR] A simulator?
Aren't you the workaholic.
[JULIETTA]
That may be,
but if Master Rustal
thought I was ready,
then surely he
would've allowed me
to join the front lines by now.
If only I would've been there,
we wouldn't have lost
the bearded gentleman.
[VIDAR]
You think your presence there
would've shifted
the tide of battle?
Of course I do!
[VIDAR] Do you realize
that saying such a thing,
in essence, is making
a mockery of the dead?
[gasps]
[grunts]
[JULIETTA]
The bearded gentleman taught me
every single thing
I know about combat.
He's the one who recommended
me to Master Rustal,
even though I had no family.
And therefore, I have to
stay at the top of my game
if I'm to repay
these two great men.
[VIDAR] You remind me of
someone I used to know.
Ever grateful for being
plucked out of the void
by a respected senior officer,
he fought out of pride for
the one who rescued him.
Where is that person now?
[VIDAR]
At the moment... rather close.
[JULIETTA]
Close, huh?
I see.
If you're really friends
with such a fine person,
then perhaps you might
be more of a decent man
than I originally
thought you were.
[VIDAR]
And if that's your criterion,
then perhaps you have a
simpler mind than I thought.
Was that... you
giving me a compliment?
[VIDAR]
Of course.
[chuckles]
[JULIETTA]
Thank you.
Hey there, how's
it goin', boys?
I heard that a bunch of your
guys bit the big one again.
As your big brother, I thought
I'd swing by and cheer ya up.
Big brother?
You're just some old geezer.
[TODO]
Ah, screw you guys!
Hurry up and show us in!
We are guests, ya know!
[MCGILLIS] I received word
that you'd arrived on Earth.
I thought I owed Tekkadan
a personal thank you
for saving us from that
horrid predicament.
[ORGA]
No.
Unfortunately,
our internal affairs
were partly to blame for this.
And some mystery man
used it to his advantage.
Galan Mossa.
And it's safe to assume that he
was working under Rustal Elion.
We're dealing with
that guy again?
We must deal with his faction.
Otherwise, we can't
reform Gjallarhorn.
Given the fact that they've
made the first move,
an all-out war with
them isn't far off.
An all-out war, huh?
[MCGILLIS] We will continue
to need your assistance
in this conflict.
Tekkadan's already
promised you our support.
We stand behind
that... like always.
Something the matter?
Returns not worth the risk?
[ORGA]
It's not that.
I've asked before,
but why the hell do you think
so highly of Tekkadan?
If there was a
Gjallarhorn civil war,
I honestly doubt that
we'd be much help to you.
I've been impressed with you
ever since the first time I saw
your people fighting on Mars.
Why?
[MCGILLIS]
Seeing the actions of young men
piloting Gundam Frames and
fighting with so much vitality,
I saw the likeness of Agnika
Kaieru in your group.
[ORGA]
Agnika?
There's something
I'm quite certain of.
Provided I can secure the
assistance of Tekkadan,
I know beyond a doubt
that I can attain
the highest position
in Gjallarhorn.
And when that day
finally arrives,
all authority over the
Gjallarhorn Mars Branch
will be transferred to Tekkadan.
What?
Mars has been colonized
by all the economic blocs.
However, it is Gjallarhorn
who actually coordinates
and governs those colonies.
And if Tekkadan were ever
to obtain that power,
well, my friend, such an
event would allow you
to control all of Mars.
We'd rule over Mars, huh?
Yes, that's right.
Your people will become
the sovereign of Mars.
The sovereign of... Mars...
[TAKAKI] C'mon Fuka,
you need to eat something.
Hey, Takaki.
The day that we took this
picture, do you remember it?
[TAKAKI] It was the day we
decided on as Aston's birthday.
I remember you making
him a massive feast.
And if recall, Aston opened
up a little that day.
[ASTON]
I honestly wish... that I'd...
...never met any of you guys...
Because...
Takaki?
Do you think...
...it would have been better
if we weren't friends?
[FUKA]
Huh?
It's just that I...
I wanted more good
times together...
And yet, because we
had those times,
I made Aston suffer
in his last moments...
Because of me...
[FUKA]
Don't talk like that!
I had so much fun when the
three of us were together.
Just you, me, and Aston.
I never wanna
forget those times.
[TAKAKI]
Fuka...
[FUKA]
So please,
you have to promise
not to leave me behind
with all of those memories.
[ZACK]
Jeez, this was so boring!
Our first time on Earth,
and now we're heading home
without having
done anything fun.
Hey! Stop acting like Akihiro.
What's gotten into you?
Are trying to bulk up?
Shut up!
I have to give my
training 110%,
or else I'll get in
Mr. Mikazuki's way.
Oh, so it's "Mr.
Mikazuki" now, huh?
[HUSH]
You got a problem with that?
[ZACK]
Nope, no problems here.
I think it's important to
respect the chain of command.
[HUSH yelps]
Here.
Since you're workin' so hard,
I thought I would help you out.
[HUSH] Thanks, man...
but I think I got it.
[EUGENE] Sovereign of Mars?
What does that mean?
[CHAD] Well, a sovereign is
a real bigshot, isn't it?
Why transfer the powers of
the Gjallarhorn Mars Branch?
Hold on, guys. Jeez,
my brain can't keep up.
So whaddya wanna do, Orga?
To be completely honest,
I may take him up
on it to accept.
But, Boss!
[ORGA] Considering your goal
about Mars's independence,
it's probably the best shot
we're ever gonna get.
Yes, but...
[MERRIBIT]
Wait.
But how would that
effect us and Teiwaz?
[ORGA]
Would that cause a problem?
Yes, a big one!
If Tekkadan grows too
large too quickly,
it might cause outsiders
to see us as the top group.
You're right.
I'll see what Naze
has to say about it.
Then I'll decide what
needs to be done.
But right now, I just have
one thing on my mind.
We've always been looked down
upon, treated like garbage,
and taken advantage
of our entire lives.
But now we can be kings.
It can all be ours.
Power and reputation.
Come on, can't you all see it?
The ultimate finish for us.
[ORGA]
So whaddya think?
If that's what you want.
Mikazuki!
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm?
Yeah, uh... I don't
get any of this,
but as Deputy Boss,
I'll follow the boss's orders.
Same goes for me.
Maybe you should
think this through.
I'm sorry, but
I can't go with you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means... that I'm
going to quit Tekkadan.
You sayin' that you won't be
joining us on this, Takaki?
Sovereign of Mars...
I'm not sure what
the job would entail,
but it's safe to say more people
would end up dying, right?
[EUGENE] Hey, don't
start with that again.
[TAKAKI] I totally understand
that the only reason
Boss is going
through all of this
is because he wants to
give us a better future.
But... I...
I don't wanna make Fuka cry.
Being sovereign of Mars
might mean we'd attain
some great happiness,
but that would mean
throwing away the happiness
we already have
right here and now.
And I... I just can't
bring myself to do that.
Takaki...
I understand.
What?
But, Boss, we can't just--
[ORGA] What right do
I have to stop him?
Thanks for all
you've done for us.
And for stickin' with
Tekkadan this long, Takaki.
Boss, I don't...
[TAKAKI]
Thank you... for everything.
[CHAD] The boss said
he's gonna ask around
and find you a good job
right here on Earth.
Sorry about this. I just--
[CHAD]
Don't be.
The Earth Branch was saved
thanks to all of your hard work.
We're family and we're
always gonna be that way
[MIKAZUKI]
No, we aren't.
The only family that you need
to worry about is Fuka.
We can take care of
ourselves without you.
[AKIHIRO]
Don't mind him.
[CHAD]
Yeah...
For him, that's just his
way of showing kindness.
From now on, don't
think about Tekkadan.
Just treasure your life
with your sister.
Also...
...you were a good
friend to Aston.
Thanks for that.
[KUDELIA] I'm heading
back home to Mars.
[sighs]
[MAKANAI]
I understand.
Without the proper knowledge,
we can't make
the right decisions.
I wish we had more time because
there are so many things
I wanna learn from
you, Mr. Makanai.
However, even if my
lack of knowledge
leads me to the
wrong conclusions,
the time has already come for
us to make some hard choices.
For both me and Tekkadan.
[MAKANAI]
That young lady has become
quite the force of nature.
Even so, when all
is said and done,
I can't guarantee that you
and your friends will like
what awaits you down the
path you have chosen.
[AKIHIRO]
This everything?
[CHAD] Yeah, these are
all the personal effects
of the dead Earth
Branch members.
I'll leave the rest to Takaki.
At this point, it feels
like Earth has become
something of a
second home to us.
[CHAD]
It's strange.
When I was Human Debris,
I never thought I'd ever find a
place where I truly belonged.
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah, I hear ya.
[AZEE]
Hmm?
Where's Akihiro?
[LAFTER]
Hmm...
Hey, is everything okay?
He thought of Aston
as his little brother,
so I guess it's
still tough for him.
But he's okay.
No, not him. How're you?
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
I won't tell Naze.
[LAFTER grunts]
[LAFTER] It's not like that!
We're just... uh...
For now, whaddya say we keep
this between you and me?
[AZEE]
Heh. Sure.
[ORGA]
Once we're on Mars,
I'll be back to
business meetings
with those stuffy execs, again.
I see.
[MIKAZUKI]
When Takaki quit...
Huh? What about it?
[MIKAZUKI] I'm not sure why...
but I was kind of...
...relieved in a way.
[gasps]
Which I don't understand.
Do you know why?
That's because...
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm?
Uhh... Forget it.
We'll find out the answers
to everything soon enough.
I know it. We just have
to get to our goal, okay?
Seems a lot farther
than I thought.
Sorry.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm?
You don't need to apologize.
Right.
Hey there, big brother!
Hey, Fuka.
I figured you'd come home
soon, so I waited for you.
How was work, today?
Uh. Well...
[TAKAKI]
Come on.
Let's go home.
[CHAD]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam: Iron-Blooded
Orphans , "Vidar Rising."
To protect the place I belong,
I have to start training again
as soon as we get back to Mars.
Akihiro, let me do
sit-ups with you!