[MERRIBIT]
Jasley Donomikols.
Have you finished
saying your prayers?
Tekkadan will never forgive you,
and they will never let you go.
So, the time has arrived to
scatter your red flowers
upon the graves of the fallen.
[KUDELIA]
Did I hear you correctly?
Tekkadan is cutting ties
with the Admoss Company?
That would mean relinquishing
all jointly-owned assets
on Mars, as well as
dissolving the affiliations
with the security and
shipping businesses.
I've tried calling Teiwaz
for an explanation,
but I'm not getting any answers.
What in the world is going
on with Tekkadan right now?
Is it possible to view Earth
Sphere broadcasts from here?
Huh?
Uh?
[KUDELIA]
What is this?
[OPERATOR 42B] Hugo's One, Two,
and Three have been hit!
They're withdrawing
from the front lines!
[OPERATOR 42A]
Not good! More troops lost!
We're down by almost 15%!
[JASLEY growls]
These punks are really
pushin' their luck!
Filthy space rats!
[OPERATOR 42A] Hugo Eight
and Nine have been destroyed,
and our forces are
rapidly decreasing!
At this rate,
they'll break through
our first line of defense!
[JASLEY growls]
I get it!
They finished repairing
that machine!
[JASLEY growls]
Hey! Where is Iok Kujan?
[JASLEY'S MAN 35A] Uh, there's
been no word from him, sir.
That little bastard.
He was supposed to be here,
helping us, ages ago.
Of course, I've taken care
of all the preparations.
Now that I've lit a fire
under those little rats,
they'll be sure to come
after us, guns a blazin'.
And once those punks
come scurrying out...
[IOK] ...it will be my job to
exterminate them from behind,
thus completing my
quest for revenge.
Exactly right.
And then, I'll take you to the
Saisei, just as we discussed.
[IOK]
Yes, I understand.
The plan is for me to arrest
McMurdo Barriston, right?
It is indeed.
That geezer has plenty of
skeletons in his closet.
You'll be able to pin him
with any number of crimes.
[IOK]
Got it. Leave everything to me.
[JASLEY]
Heh.
This'll get rid of all
the thorns in my side!
And all in one fell swoop!
I was supposed to become the big
boss of Teiwaz using his help!
That spoiled, little brat.
Mobile Suit teams,
do you read me?
Lord Kujan's backup will come.
Remember, we have more
Mobile Suits than the enemy,
so hold out until they arrive!
He's latched onto me?!
I've got you now!
[MCGILLIS] it looks to me
as if their battle has begun.
[ISURUGI] But if we're looking
at sheer numbers, sir,
the JPT Trust has the advantage.
[MCGILLIS] They're a ragtag
group of mercenaries.
They'll never be able
to stop Tekkadan.
Now then, it's time
for us to get going.
[SOLDIER 42C groans]
[SOLDIER 42D] Whoa! Nobody
said anything about this!
These people are crazy!
Go to hell!
[SOLDIER 42B grunting]
[SOLDIER 42C] Hugo team,
we need reinforcements, stat!
[HUSH]
Mr. Mikazuki!
You can leave these guys to me!
If you're sure.
They're all yours.
[gasps] Yes, sir!
Hey! Where do you
think you're go--
[HUSH]
So this is a Hekija.
It reacts much faster
than a Shiden...
...and so easy to control!
[DANTE] That machine is a
keepsake from the Turbines.
[HUSH]
Oh, right.
If you don't do it justice,
you'll regret it.
Hush!
[HUSH]
Yes, sir!
[OPERATOR 42B]
Hyakuri Two is down!
Hyakuren Four and
Six have been hit!
They're withdrawing, sir!
Damn it, they're useless!
Why the hell do I
pay these idiots?!
Hey why isn't the
rich boy here yet?!
[JASLEY'S MAN 35A] We've done
everything in our power to reach
him, sir, but he's not
answering our transmissions!
Don't tell me he
turned tail and ran.
That worthless loser!
What should we do now, sir?
Use the Debris!
[gasps]
[JASLEY] Send out every
Human Debris we have!
Where's Mr. Mikazuki?
--[beeping]
--[gasps]
[HUSH]
You're mine!
[HUSH gasps] These moves...
the Alaya-Vijnana?
[HUSH grunts]
Mr. Shino?
[SHINO]
Don't chase 'em too far!
Try to remember that you're
piloting a precious machine.
Fall back for now!
Yes, sir!
Hey Derma, cover our backs!
[DERMA]
Roger!
I'll go over and
check the Flauros.
Dane, handle the Hekija.
The good news is it only
needs the units replaced.
It'll take about 20 minutes to--
[YAMAGI]
No, we need it in 10!
Yes, sir!
[panting]
Good work out there!
Here ya go.
You need to eat all you can
while you have the chance.
Right, thanks a lot.
[ZACK]
Drink up.
The enemy's movements
have changed a lot.
That mobility...
From the looks of it, they've
brought out the Human Debris.
Wait, hang on.
You're gonna go up
against those guys?
Even though you know
what they are?
Of course.
[gasps] I see.
But weren't you and
Mr. Chad, I mean...
Ya think we're not gonna
fight those guys
'cause we were
once like them?
[ZACK]
Well...
That stuff doesn't
mean anything.
Their standings and
backgrounds don't matter.
If they pick up a weapon,
they're all the same.
And we're gonna crush them.
If you hesitate, you die.
But isn't that...
[YAMAGI] Both Landman Rodis
have been refueled and rearmed.
They're ready to move out.
Let's do this.
Right.
How are they so cool-headed
about killing people?
The guys we're fighting
are still human.
Aren't they?
[HUSH]
Even so, they're our enemy.
[gasps]
If I don't kill them,
they're gonna kill me.
But still, I--
Why, you!
[AKIHIRO]
How many times
have I had to let go of
someone I cared about?
[GALAN] Having something to
protect--that's admirable!
As is taking revenge when
it's been taken from you!
But the thing is--
On the battlefield, it's always
the decent ones who die first!
[AKIHIRO]
To hell with that--
If it means losing more people
who are precious to me!
[RIDE yells]
[AKIHIRO]
I'm done with being decent!
[RIDE]
Damn it, this guy is--
[AKIHIRO]
Ride, fall back!
What?!
[AKIHIRO yelling]
Mr. Akihiro!
Thanks for the save!
[AKIHIRO]
Don't sweat it.
Masahiro. Aston. Lafter.
Forgive me.
If we meet again
in another life,
allow me to ask for your
forgiveness, then.
[YAMAZIN]
Wouldja look at that.
She's taken quite
a pounding, huh?
[JULIETTA] What do you
suppose I was lacking?
[YAMAZIN]
Mmm?
[JULIETTA]
Julia is a powerful machine.
I trained three times
harder than any other pilot
to unlock the full
extent of that power.
And yet...
...I was no match.
Hey, you and Julia came
back in one piece, right?
But, your opponent
wasn't so lucky.
Based on that alone,
I'd say you're plenty strong.
[JULIETTA]
You're missing the point!
My skills and strength
were no match for hers!
If I don't find a way
to become stronger,
there will be no reason
for me to exist!
If you wanna get even
stronger than you are now,
then you might have to
give up being human.
[gasps]
[YAMAZIN] The human body
is unreliable, parts-wise.
You'd have to remove the
shackles of flesh and blood.
[JULIETTA] The very
thought of that is taboo!
As a member of Gjallarhorn,
I cannot approve of such
repugnant thinking!
[YAMAZIN] I guess it all
depends on how you look at it.
Sometimes, you have to
make a deal with the devil
in order to fight
him as an equal.
I know some people
who think that way.
[JULIETTA]
Who... do you mean?
Well, it's...
[MECHANIC 42A]
Ms. Yamazine, we need you!
Yeah, on my way!
Sorry, talk to you later.
[OPERATOR 42A]
The escort Hyakuren.
[OPERATOR 42B]
Over 50% of our Mobile Suits
have been incapacitated!
[JASLEY'S MAN 35A]
This is bad!
If we don't do something,
we're dead!
This isn't worth
losing over lives!
We should just apologize and--
Don't give me that nonsense!
I'll never bow to those--
[CREW gasping]
[OPERATOR 42A]
Our starboard's been hit!
If you don't wanna surrender,
then at the very least make
things right with the old man!
Come on, this is not the time
to obsess about saving face!
[JASLEY growls]
[JASLEY]
U-Uh. Old Man.
[MCMURDO]
What's the matter?
Why are you stammering
like that?
[JASLEY] We're in the midst
of a battle with Tekkadan.
They just attacked
us out of nowhere!
[MCMURDO]
Really?
[JASLEY]
Please, Old Man!
Ya have to tell those
insolent brats to--
[MCMURDO]
We both know that you're the one
who provoked them.
[JASLEY]
Uh!
[MCMURDO]
I knew from the start.
After crushing Tekkadan,
you wouldn't need me.
Your plan was to set me
up and make me your fall guy
once Gjallarhorn came
knocking at our door.
[JASLEY whimpers]
[JASLEY]
I, uh, I have no idea what
you're talking about, Old Man!
[MCMURDO]
Oh, one more thing.
The Kujan family
heir isn't coming.
Uh!
[MCMURDO]
Ya see, I struck a deal
with the boy's guardian,
Rustal Elion,
to make the illegal weapon
transport charges disappear.
He'll turn a blind eye
to the entire thing
if we forget about their
attacks on the Turbines.
[JASLEY]
O-Old Man, wait a minute!
[MCMURDO]
Hate to break it to you,
but you'll have to clean
this up yourself.
[JASLEY]
Please, don't do this, Old Man!
I'll explain everything
to you later!
For now, just talk
to Tekkadan and--
[MCMURDO]
Enough!
[whimpers]
[MCMURDO] They're no longer
part of Teiwaz.
[JASLEY]
What do you mean?!
Old Man?!
[MCMURDO]
Tekkadan, huh?
They're hot-headed
and tend to think little
about the consequences.
They're a lost cause
when it comes
to being a real organization.
But trying to avenge
their big brother
makes those kids
pretty admirable.
Isn't that right, Naze?
[JASLEY growls]
You have got to be kidding me!
I am Jasley Donomikols, dammit!
Second in command
of all of Teiwaz!
That sneaky bastard!
Doesn't that decrepit fossil
realize how much money he's made
because of me?!
[JASLEY'S MAN 35A]
So, what's our next move?
[JASLEY]
It was all for nothing.
I'm surrounded by a bunch of
idiots who just sit around
and don't even pay attention!
[JASLEY] It's like these
insufferable fools
have straw in their heads
instead of brains!
[screaming]
[JASLEY] Curse you fight-loving,
man-eating rats!
[JASLEY]
You bastards aren't even human!
Your wretched lives
are worthless!
[JASLEY]
How dare you?
[JASLEY] You rats can't
kill a real human like me!
It'd be against
the laws of nature!
[CREW gasping]
[OPERATOR 42A]
The port side's been hit!
[OPERATOR 42B]
Our output level is down to 52%!
[screams]
[Jasley's Man 35A
Uh... Jasley, sir!
[JASLEY'S MAN 35C]
What do we do?!
[JASLEY sighs]
Get Tekkadan on the line.
[JASLEY'S MEN gasp]
What's up?
How's everything goin', Jasley?
Why you...!
I mean, Orga Itsuka.
I now understand how
powerful you are.
So, how 'bout it?
Don't'cha think the time
has come to call a truce?
I would be sure to make
it worth your while.
After all, if you did away
with me here and now
you wouldn't gain
anything from it.
This'll benefit
us both in the--
[ORGA]
What are you talkin' about?
Huh?
[ORGA] I only answered
your transmission
because I wanted to watch you
beg for your pitiful life.
Although, watching you grovel
isn't as fun as I'd hoped.
You bastard! Just who the
hell do you think you are?!
[CREW gasps]
[JASLEY]
Uh!
What should I do now, Orga?
Finish them.
[gasping]
Let's not be too hasty!
If it's not money, then what?!
An apology?! I'll cut
off all my fingers!
And all my toes, if you want!
Please, don't do this!
[cries]
[exhales]
[BAKLAZAN]
Lord Fareed, isn't it curious
that Lord Elion and Lord
Kujan aren't present?
It's not a problem.
We can begin without them.
Can we?
This meeting needs the unanimous
decision of all seven lords.
[ORGA]
You did good out there.
Now we finally have something to
offer, to the Turbines who died.
But there's no way of tellin'
if this made them happy, though.
[ORGA]
Yeah.
But still,
I think we honored the fallen
only as Tekkadan could.
And as a result,
we're now an organization
cut off from Teiwaz.
That's just how it is.
We don't have anyone
to back us up anymore.
[CHAD]
Forgive me if I'm wrong,
but, aren't we teaming up with
that McGillis Fareed guy?
Eugene. It's almost time.
[CHAD]
For what?
The time has come
for us to rise up!
[ALL]
Huh?
A revolution's coming
comrades! The fight has begun!
We shall stir up a new wind
and blow away the rot
that has consumed Gjallarhorn.
The time has arrived to reform
a world that has become rife
with treacherous lies, and take
it back with our own hands.
[gasps]
Gjallarhorn was known as the
keeper of peace and order.
However, that notion was nothing
but convenient self-serving,
prattling used by the Seven
Stars for personal gain!
The border dispute on Earth
between Arbrau and the SAU,
our investigations have
revealed that Gahlen Mossa,
the mercenary believed to have
engineered the entire situation,
was actually working in
league with Rustal Elion!
Which brings me to this.
Lord Iok Kujan
set up the Turbines,
a civilian company to be
an illegal organization.
And after conducting
a warrantless raid,
he used the banned
Dáinsleif to butcher
multiple non-combatant workers.
These men only focus on
petty political squabbles...
[VIDAR] I take it this is your
answer, McGillis Fareed.
In that case, I know what to do.
[LIZA] Gjallarhorn was known the
keeper of peace and order.
However, that notion was nothing
but a convenient excuse
used by the Seven Stars
for personal gain!
I implore you to open your eyes!
Let us rise up
together, comrades!
So it begins.
[KUDELIA] Tekkadan is going to
take part in this revolution.
And in doing so, they're cutting
ties with us and Teiwaz,
and joining Lord Fareed.
Ms. Merribit.
I know they're doing this,
but what about you?
You're a Teiwaz
employee, aren't you?
[MERRIBIT] Actually, I've
already resigned from Teiwaz.
Sometimes, when I'm
with those kids,
I realize how truly
powerless I am.
And yet, I would
really like to think
that there's something I can
do for them as an adult.
And besides, there's someone
dear to me in Tekkadan, too.
[gasps]
[MERRIBIT]
Wherever those children go,
I'll be right there with them.
[CUCUBITA]
President...
[KUDELIA] There's also someone
very dear to me in Tekkadan.
[CUCUBITA]
Huh?
I thought I was part
of Tekkadan's family, too.
[CUCUBITA] Families come
in many different forms,
Madam President.
[SHINO] We're supposed to help
them change the world?
Do you really think
we can do that?
[EUGENE] Hey Orga, you mind
if I ask you somethin'?
[ORGA]
Hm?
The thing these guys
are organizing.
Are you positive it
meshes with your plan?
[EUGENE] Sometimes it
seems too complicated
and goes over our heads.
So tell us, the objective
they have on this,
is it the same as what
we're aimin' for?
It is.
In order for us to survive,
and also to become
sovereign of Mars,
we're gonna head for
the same place as them.
It's the only choice.
That's true.
All right! Let's do this!
Are ya ready boys?!
[EUGENE]
Yeah!
[SHINO]
Come on, I can't hear ya!
[CHAD]
Yeah.
Hey, Mika.
How'd this guy feel out there?
[MIKAZUKI]
It was great.
Kinda strange, though.
I'm so used to having
this tail now,
it's hard to believe I
didn't have one before.
I see.
I wonder what
Brother would say?
He'd be mad.
[ORGA]
Probably.
I wanna laugh.
King of Mars, or whatever.
I don't care about the title.
All I want is to laugh
when I get there.
Together.
With everyone.
Sounds good. Yeah.
[KUDELIA]
And with that,
Tekkadan set out
on their new road.
One that would lead them
to that fateful day.
[VIDAR]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans,
"Revealed Intentions."
McGillis. The time has come to
ascertain your real intentions.