[HUSH] All right, as soon
as we drop these guys off,
I'll come right back
to pick you up.
No need. Atra's
comin' by later.
[HUSH]
But I was--
Don't you have some
training to do, Hush?
Uh.
Yes, sir!
[SAKURA] Are you positive that
you didn't need to go with him?
There's nothing I can
do over there, yet.
Honestly, I wish I could
keep you here forever.
[RUSTAL] I'm told that
you've finally finished
regulating the system that
was giving you trouble.
That's good.
Because I have a
mission for you.
Ever since the Dort incident,
colony independence
uprisings have intensified.
We thought allowing them
to have defense forces
would bring them down,
but now it's up to us.
There's someone funneling money
and arms to the activists.
And as long as--
[VIDAR] It doesn't matter
who's behind the scenes.
There are armed parties out
there disturbing the peace.
Tell me, what other reason
does Gjallarhorn need
to bear down its
might upon them?
You're certainly chatty today.
[VIDAR] I suppose I'm
just in high spirits.
My friend and I finally
get to fight together.
[YUKINOJO]
That's it! Nice and easy!
[DERMA] Have they decided
who's gonna pilot these?
[YUKINOJO] Of the three
suits that came back,
Chad's supposed to
be the pilot of one.
I don't know about
the other two.
Then let me pilot one of them.
Huh?
It's a Man Rodi we
snagged from the Brewers,
that group you were workin' for.
Wouldn't it bring up
bad memories?
For those of us
called Human Debris,
these were pretty
much our coffins.
But if Aston piloted
one of them, so can I.
[DANTE]
Akihiro figured you'd say that,
so he's already made
the arrangements.
[DERMA]
Mr. Dante?
I'll be piloting the other one.
Whaddya say we show 'em
what former Human
Debris are made of?
Yeah.
[ZACK] Man! There's just no
end to all of this work!
This is Hell for mechanics...
I think it's fun.
Then you're a weirdo.
I've had it up to here with--
All right, Dane,
enough slacking off!
Get back to work, wouldja?!
[EUGENE]
Hey!
Have you finished tuning
up those Sheedins
that came in the other day?
Yeah, finishing up as we speak!
[EUGENE] Good, we'll be gettin'
more from Teiwaz tomorrow.
Huh?! We're getting more?!
[EUGENE] That's right, so we've
got no time to sit around!
[DANE]
Right.
Yes, sir...
[SHINO] Hey, Deputy Boss,
got some news for ya.
The guys are back from the farm.
So this is the king's throne
I've heard so much about.
[EUGENE]
Yeah.
Well, no turnin' back now.
[EUGENE] You were
thinkin' of turning back?
Nah, I was just
babblin' to myself!
We don't know how Orga's
meeting on the Saisei will go,
so all we can do
is wait for now.
Well, in the meantime,
let's make sure to
whip these grunts
into proper fighting shape.
[grunts]
It's fast for something so big!
I'm just getting started!
Chad sure is pretty amped up.
He had a pretty rough time
of it back on Earth.
Though the same could be
said for that rookie.
He went straight into training
the moment they all
got back from the farm.
But it looks like he's
shaping up nicely.
At the rate they're going,
they'll master their
training with the Shidens
in no time flat.
[AZEE] Once that happens, our
mission here will be complete.
[LAFTER]
Yeah.
[MERRIBIT] Here's the a list of
all the equipment we recovered
from the Earth Branch.
[YUKINOJO]
Much appreciated.
We don't have many
people who can handle
this kind of
detail-oriented work.
I wonder how many more
arms we'll have to add.
[YUKINOJO] If my hunch
is right, enough to win.
Though, I can understand
why you're worried.
But think of it this way, with
all of the firepower we have,
no one's gonna mess
with Tekkadan now.
By the way, have you
heard from Yamagi?
[MERRIBIT] Yes, they arrived
at the Saisei a while ago.
I wanted to ask you more
about the Mobile Suit
we found at the mine.
It's another Gundam
Frame, isn't it?
Yeah?
That makes three,
with Barbatos and Gusion.
Mobile Suits named after demons
keep finding their
way to Tekkadan.
I have a bad feeling about this.
[gasps]
There ya go
overthinking things.
Oh, stop!
[ECO]
Chief!
[CHIEF MECHANIC]
Hey, you're here!
[YAMAGI]
It's been a while.
[CHIEF MECHANIC] How are the
Lupus and Full City doing?
[YAMAGI]
They seem to be doing fine.
Though, we don't
really call them
by those names much anymore.
Any luck with this one?
We tried everything
we possibly could,
but we just couldn't
get it to work.
The frame of a Mobile Suit
wouldn't degrade in
a mere 300 years.
Their reactors last
even a bit longer.
The reason you
couldn't get it to work
was because the reactor
was in sleep mode.
We're running it through its
startup sequence right now.
Oh, right.
About that mobile
worker-like thing
you sent up along with this.
there wasn't anything in the
Teiwaz database that matched it.
Oh, is that so?
[MECHANIC A]
Chief!
We are now connected to the
reactor's controls. Booting up.
And here we go!
Fantastic. I've got the
frequency of the Ahab Wave.
And its name appears to be...
Gundam Flauros.
[MCMURDO]
So he's signing over the power
to govern Mars to them.
This is another huge deal
you've landed for us.
[NAZE] Apparently, McGillis
Fareed and Tekkadan
made this secret
agreement while on Earth.
[EXECUTIVE A]
Hey,
is Gjallarhorn as a whole
on board with this?
[EXECUTIVE B] The last thing we
wanna do is get tangled up
in their internal affairs.
And not to mention,
until recently,
we hadn't even heard
of this McGillis cha--
[JASLEY]
Hold it.
Come on, gentlemen, let's
not get ahead of ourselves.
We all know that we have
far more pressing
matters to discuss.
Such as, saving face.
Hate to break it to you,
but Tekkadan's nothin' more
than a charity case
for the old man.
Those kids had the audacity
to negotiate a deal
with Gjallarhorn and accept
it without consulting us.
Listen well, Naze.
There's a procedure to
these kinds of things.
Are you just gonna keep ignoring
protocol for these little punks
and allow them to
embarrass the old man?
Well?
That's not--
[MCMURDO] Jasley makes
a valid point, Naze.
I don't like trouble
dropping in my lap.
Especially when it's a problem
I wasn't previously
consulted about.
But we can benefit from this.
If this arrangement
lets us take a cut
of all business done on Mars,
it'll be a huge
moneymaker for Teiwaz.
But, Old Man!
[NAZE]
You've my word.
Should the affair with Tekkadan
cause you even the
slightest bit of grief,
you can cut them off
without any resistance.
That's how committed Orga is.
Who cares about that jackass?!
We're talking about you!
[NAZE] Should that happen,
I will pay with my life.
Don't worry, Old Man,
I'll protect Teiwaz's
interests in my own way.
[MCMURDO] Yes, take any measures
you see fit to prepare us
for a possible fallout.
Just like always.
[AMIDA] Judging from that
sinister grin of yours,
I assume that you
had a good day?
[JASLEY] It's rare for you to
start a conversation with me.
What, did you get tired
of that loser Naze
and wanna be my pet now?
Oh, you wish. Don't
even joke about that.
[JASLEY]
What do you see in a playboy
who uses women and kids
to climb to the top?
Someone who only sees
women as things to be used
wouldn't understand.
I assure you Naze
isn't using us.
If anything, he's our home.
If you ask me, that sure
sounds like somethin'
a woman would say.
And you sound like
a typical man.
We Turbine girls were once
used by men like you.
We were forced to
do dangerous work
and the risk was hardly worth
the pay we were getting.
We Turbins are a group
of girls Naze took in
out of the goodness
of his heart.
Though, I suppose a man like you
wouldn't know about that at all.
You're absolutely right.
I'm not the kind of man
that makes his girl
fight in a Mobile Suit.
There, you see? I told
you you wouldn't get it.
[NAZE]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[AMIDA chuckles]
[AMIDA]
Oh, darling,
waiting for you is just
one of my many pleasures.
[JASLEY grumbles]
Where's Orga?
Patiently waiting for you.
[door opens]
Hey, brother.
[NAZE] There's certainly never
a dull moment with you around.
[ORGA]
Please forgive me.
Why are you apologizing?
You made that decision for
your family, didn't you?
That's not the point!
I caused trouble for--
You've caused trouble for me
more times than I can count.
Don't start the
goody-goody act now.
But you--
[AMIDA] You need to watch your
back from here on out. Got it?
Yeah.
Not all of Teiwaz's top dogs
are as enlightened as others.
It's safe to assume there'll
be some kinda move against us.
Orga.
This is the last time I laugh
it off and forgive you.
I can't betray the old man.
Right.
[IOK] Have you finished
loading your machine?
[VIDAR]
Yes.
[JULIETTA] This will be
our first opportunity
to see what you're capable of.
For your sake, I hope
that fancy mask of yours
isn't just for show.
Hmm?
Which reminds me of
something you said earlier.
You mentioned you had
a friend who fought for pride.
So what is that
you fight for then?
[VIDAR]
Revenge.
This is a crucial
mission entrusted to us
by Master Rustal!
Enough with the small talk!
Now... to battle!
[CHAD]
Oh, hey, Pops!
[YUKINOJO]
Hmm?
Ah, Chad, I see
you're feeling better.
And from what I hear,
you've upped your game
since being on Earth.
Well, it's all thanks
to your maintenance.
That Landman Rodi handled
really well out there.
Heh. Come on, none of that.
We'll be counting
on you, ya hear?
[CHAD]
Hmm?
Finally, we're done
dealing with the contracts
concerning the transfer
of the farm business.
I apologize again for dumping
everything on you like this.
Miss Sakura is there,
so we'll make do somehow.
And the children
from the orphanage
are helpin' us out, too.
It's a shame, though.
Huh?
Miss Kudelia loved spending
time there with the kids.
It's too bad that she won't
be able to anymore.
We'll do everything
we possibly can
to resume our work on the farm.
Hopefully, it'll be soon.
[CUCUBITA]
You'll be in my prayers.
[ATRA]
Here you go, Miss Kudelia.
Thanks a lot, Atra.
I'm sorry, I know you're busy.
Don't worry about it.
You're the busy one, dealing
with all that paperwork.
Just thinking about it
makes my head spin.
[HUSH]
Mr. Mikazuki!
Would you like some more food?
Not really, no.
But you--
[ATRA] The two of you have
been joined at the hip
ever since you made
it back from Earth.
Did something happen there?
Yeah. I've been studying
under Mr. Mikazuki.
And it's really annoying me.
Just pretend I'm not here.
--[MIKAZUKI] I said I do--
--[HUSH] I'll get some tea.
Oh, the tea's in the back...
He's certainly become
attached to you.
He's becoming a real pest.
[chuckles]
About this plan...
Huh?
Life on the farm,
that's your dream, isn't it?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mh-hm.
Then...
No.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm?
[KUDELIA]
Okay then.
I promise to you to keep
your dream safe and sound.
[MIKAZUKI]
Thanks, I guess.
That's true, Mikazuki,
you'll have to come back
someday and get it.
Miss Atra.
What is going on with you two?
[CHAD]
Hey, guys, it's Pops.
Something's not right.
Whaddya mean?
Well, he doesn't stink anymore.
[KUDELIA] Yeah, that
certainly was a problem.
[ATRA]
It made our eyes water!
He's been a new man since he
started dating Ms. Merribit.
[ATRA]
Yeah.
[CHAD]
Huh?
[OTHERS]
Hmm?
You're saying that Ms.
Merribit and Pops are...?
[HUSH] Mr. Mikazuki,
I brought your tea--
--[CHAD] What?
--[HUSH] Whoa!
Don't push yourself too hard.
Mr. Akihiro.
You should also eat
before you start training.
Yeah, I would've, but they're
serving bean stew for dinner.
Besides, now's the time to
push myself to the limit.
Huh?
I'm the one leading
the Youth Corps now.
I'll give it my all for them.
And rise above Takaki,
who stayed on Earth.
[AKIHIRO]
Hmph.
All the more reason
to eat something.
Picky eaters don't
become big and strong.
Right!
[CHAD]
Akihiro!
You're never gonna believe this,
but Pops and Ms.
Merribit are dating!
What, you didn't know that?
Oh, I guess it started while
you were still on Earth.
Wait a minute!
You all knew about it?
Why didn't you
tell me anything?!
[AKIHIRO] I really didn't
think we needed to.
[CHAD] I'm still one
of the guys, right?
[ISURUGI] How'd the talks
on the Saisei go?
[ORGA]
Well...
I know I won't be causing any
trouble for your people.
[ISURUGI]
Orders from the General.
As of now, you'll have full
access to the Second Pier.
Wait, are you serious?
We don't have nearly enough
ships to fill it up.
[ISURUGI] He must be preparing
you for the future.
There he goes
overestimating us again.
That's not what he's doing.
He has high hopes for you.
We'll start with an introduction
to Chief Proto Arae.
He is the man in charge of Ares.
And after that,
you'll meet with the
representatives from the blocs.
Then a meeting with
the head of the
Outer Sphere
Development Corporation.
I'm doin' an entire
week of this?
Is it possible to squeeze in
a quick trip back to Mars?
Maybe later.
For now, we must focus on
defeating Rustal Elion.
Please, bear this in mind:
Everything fails
unless you succeed.
Understood.
Reformations are underway.
We've now passed the
point of no return.
I never planned to
turn back anyway.
[KUDELIA] I apologize
for this blunt request,
but is it possible for you to
provide additional funding
for the Admoss Company?
[NOBLISS]
I've been hearing rumors.
Tell me, Kudelia Aina Bernstein,
is it true that you've
managed to secure
safe and reliable
distribution channels?
Yes.
I'm planning on
expanding the business,
and I'm moving up my
timeline significantly.
[NOBLISS] Then I'd be more than
happy to lend you my support.
Thank you, Mr. Nobliss.
This means a lo--
Please, you're the Maiden
of Revolution, aren't you?
Right now, the SAU and
Oceanian Federation colonies
are seeking freedom.
To that end, vigorous
independence movements
have broken out.
Once the combatants catch
wind of your exploits,
it'll serve to embolden them.
When that happens,
those in my line of work
can provide them
with our services.
Yes, I can assure you
the pleasure is mine.
Well then, thank you
for financing us.
[click]
[sighs]
[CUCUBITA] This is why I despise
those who profit off war.
They're such vile people.
And yet, I still
go to them for money.
Which is far more
vile than they are.
[IOK]
Take your punishment!
Oh? So you dodged, it.
I'm impressed!
Are they really on par with me?!
Don't get in my way, Julietta!
You're the one who's in my
way, sir. Please fall back.
I was just about
to beat those guys!
[beeping]
[IOK gasps]
[IOK'S MAN B]
Please withdraw, Master Iok!
That machine is...
A friendly IFF... Is that...?
[VIDAR] Look, the battlefield
you were yearning for.
His machine's name is
Vidar. The same as him.
Does that mean he's taken
his Mobile Suit's name,
and completely cast
away his own identity,
all for revenge?
[VIDAR]
Hmm?
Beautiful.
[VIDAR]
Hmm?
[MAN A]
Huh?
[yelps]
[JULIETTA]
I see that mask of yours
wasn't just for show, after all.
[VIDAR]
Thank you.
By its very nature,
revenge is a dark and
repulsive emotion.
However, having seen
you fight just now,
your moves don't seem to be
fueled by revenge, at all.
They were powerful...
and beautiful.
[VIDAR]
Is that so?
I'd forgotten.
[JULIETTA]
Uh?
[VIDAR]
I'd forgotten all about that,
and was enjoying fighting
in this machine.
You're a strange man,
you know that?
[VIDAR]
Am I?
Just so you're aware,
I still don't trust you.
Or your motives.
But at least I've put to
bed any reservations
about fighting alongside you.
Oh, were you reading
that old book again?
[MCGILLIS]
Yes.
This book saved me.
Agnika Kaieru's principles
made me the man I am.
In order to build a world
where humans could
live like humans,
he created the
organization Gjallarhorn.
I wasn't born into the Fareed
family, do you remember?
Oh, that's right.
You were adopted by
Master Iznario as a child.
Back then, I was
looked down upon
for being a child of low birth.
No matter where I looked, there
was no happiness to be found.
I cursed this world,
and at times, considered
taking my own life.
Macky...
[MCGILLIS] But this book
prevented me from doing so.
Agnika had a dream
he wanted to realize.
A world where humans
could compete fairly,
regardless of background.
In his world, anything
would be possible.
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
I'm sorry, but I'm not
sure I fully understand.
And for us, it would mean
a world free of judgment.
We could love each other
without anyone objecting to it.
Macky...
If we lived in that world,
do you think people
would stop laughing at me
and saying I'm a child?
Yes.
And nobody would
make fun of you
for having a child as a fiancée?
Of course not.
Then that settles it!
I wanna go there!
Sure. I'll take you
there, Almiria.
That I promise.
[MCGILLIS] The time has come
for me to pry open the door
to that world with
my own two hands.
[YAMAGI]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"Awakening Calamity."
[YAMAGI sighs]
[YAMAGI]
I swear,
Shino is always pulling
these crazy stunts.
Moron.