[MERRIBIT]
Mobile Armor,
a silent angel that has awoken
from its 300-year slumber.
It's merciless wings solely
crave the slaughter of humanity.
Only something inhuman
will be able to stop it.
[MCGILLIS]
That fool!
He has awoken the monster.
[IOK] Wh-What in the
world is that thing?
Whoa.
[gasps]
[IOK'S MAN B]
Master Iok!
[IOK'S MAN B yells]
[IOK gasps]
So that's it...
[IOK]
A Mobile Armor!
[ORGA]
Damn it!
What the hell are we
up against here?!
[MCGILLIS]
Let's leave while we still can.
Wait a sec!
If we don't do something,
the mine's gonna be
ripped to pieces!
I've called HQ for back-up!
Once they get here--
It's no use.
It's not going to be that
easy to defeat this.
[ORGA]
Then how do we stop it?
[MCGILLIS] Our only recourse
is to destroy it completely.
That is, if we can.
And after all the
precautions I took
to ensure that this very
thing wouldn't happen.
Iok Kujan. How
foolish can you get?
I don't care if it
is a Mobile Armor!
It's just scrap metal
from 300 years ago!
I'm not afraid of it!
[IOK'S MAN F] Don't be
so reckless, Master Iok!
We need to fall back
and regroup!
[IOK yelling]
What the...?
[beeping]
[IOK'S MAN E
Master Iok!
[IOK'S MAN C]
Damn it! Over here!
[IOK'S MAN A yells]
[IOK'S MAN A]
I've got 'im!
Damn you!
These things, what are they?!
There's a ton of them!
[ORGA]
What the hell are those?
[MCGILLIS] They're sub-units
of the Mobile Armor.
They're called Plumas.
Though, I didn't think
there'd be so many.
[ZACK]
Hey, Boss!
We're all set!
We just finished rounding up
the rest of our members!
[ORGA] All right!
Let's get out of here!
[IOK'S MAN A]
Please fall back, Master Iok!
Your machine's too
damaged to fight!
I can still do this!
The right side works!
[IOK'S MAN A] They can't be
beaten with spirit alone, sir!
Please, sir, you have to retreat
while we hold them off!
[IOK]
Nonsense.
Are-Are you telling
me to abandon you?
[IOK'S MAN A] Consider the
Kujan family's future!
I'm sorry, sir, but
I'm afraid your life
doesn't just belong to you!
[IOK]
Men... Forgive me!
Just know that I'll avenge you!
On my family's honor...
I swear it!
[ZACK]
Huh?
What're they...?
[HUSH]
Zack, stay on watch.
Yeah, yeah, I'm watching, okay?
[RUSTAL] We've lost all contact
with Iok's advance team.
[JULIETTA] Do you think...
that they've been wiped out?
Not sure.
But I do know that
the Mars Branch
has no idea what's
going on, either.
This is such a mess.
[VIDAR] Still, I think it's
premature to assume
they've all been annihilated.
The Mars Branch is under
Lord Fareed's command.
It could be false information.
[RUSTAL]
Hmm.
[JULIETTA]
Just great!
I was hoping that we'd have
some peace with him away,
but now he's gone and
caused even more trouble.
Whatever the case,
we need to investigate
this Mobile Armor
as well as the status
of Iok's team.
Reliable intel is
a must. Got it?
Understood, sir!
[RUSTAL]
Don't fail me.
[CREW A] We're entering
Mars' gravitational field.
[VIDAR]
Captain...
[JULIETTA] This could
also be my big change.
If I'm able to defeat this
Mobile Armor contraption,
it might just be my ticket
to securing an Order
of the Seven Stars
for Master Rustal.
[CAPTAIN A] What about
our resupplying, sir?
[VIDAR]
You won't be waiting long.
[SHINO]
Hey, Boss, it's me.
I just got to the mining plant.
How's it lookin' there?
[SHINO] Well... it seems like
that Mobile Armor thing
is long gone.
Want me to look for it?
No, don't.
Head back over here
and meet up with us.
[SHINO]
Roger!
[DANTE] All that was left
at the mining plant
was the wreckage of those
Gjallarhorn machines.
Not a single survivor.
[ORGA]
No one made it out of there?
And you checked it all?
We didn't have to.
Every cockpit was crushed,
as if those things were making
sure the pilots were dead.
[MCGILLIS]
I knew it.
[ALL]
Huh?
[ORGA]
Knew what?
Mobile Armors are programmed
for thorough extermination.
[SHINO]
Huh?
[MCGILLIS]
And what was your opinion
about this deadly machine,
Mikazuki Augus?
It was pretty amazing.
And it was quite beautiful too.
Like one of those
birds I saw on Earth.
[MCGILLIS]
It's no bird.
But more like... an angel.
A humanity killing
machine known as "angel."
Long ago, these monsters
went on a rampage
and managed to slaughter a
fourth of the human population.
[ORGA]
Unbelievable...
[MCGILLIS]
It's true.
As I said before,
the Mobile Armors' sole priority
was the destruction of humanity.
They were specifically
designed for that task.
Those machines are
the enemy of mankind
that Agnika Kaieru,
the founder of Gjallarhorn,
fought 300 years ago.
The catastrophic event
known as the Calamity War
was brought about by those
monstrous Mobile Armors
and their destructive actions.
What's the Calamity War?
You don't know?
[MCGILLIS] Mobile Armors.
Angels that hunt humans.
And in order to hunt
down those angels,
demons were created.
Mobile Suits.
And the Alaya-Vijnana System
was made to control them.
[ORGA]
Anything else?
Oh, yeah, the warehouse
that was holding
all the fuel and materials
was completely destroyed.
And you didn't see
any people there?
[DANTE]
No, no one.
[ZACK]
Oh, right.
I saw that place, too.
These little machines
were running around,
ransacking everything in sight.
Why would they do that?
[MCGILLIS]
To resupply.
[ORGA]
Huh?
[MCGILLIS]
Unlike Ahab Reactors,
which are able to
run indefinitely,
propellant and fuel can
only last for so long.
[ORGA]
I get it.
Even if it's a monster, in
the end, it's just a machine.
And that means Tekkadan
can eliminate it. Right?
if that's what you
want me to do,
then I'll take it out for you.
You're absolutely correct.
Agnika Kaieru, too, managed to
put an end to the Mobile Armors
and went on to
found Gjallarhorn.
[ISURUGI]
General.
We've just now gotten word
from Chief Arae up in orbit.
It would appear that
the Third Ground-Base
has come under attack
by the Mobile Armor.
[ORGA]
And where's that?
[MCGILLIS]
Where we just were.
I'm sure it's objective
was to take all of
the resources there.
It must've topped
off its supplies
given the size of the base.
Also, a Halfbeak-class
ship from the Arianrhod
is headed this way.
[SHINO] So? Whadda we
do at this point?
Are we gonna go
and back 'em up?
[MCGILLIS]
No need.
We'd never make
it there in time.
And besides, that's a flat
area with an open view.
Hardly an ideal location
to ambush the enemy.
So that's your plan? An ambush?
It's our plan.
You will help, won't you?
Awakening that horror
from its slumber
is a blunder directly
caused by Gjallarhorn.
As such, it's up to me
to make this right.
That said, the ones who
unearthed it in the first place
were you, Tekkadan.
Yeah, I know. We're
not gonna run from this.
[MCGILLIS]
Then you'll help.
We have no choice here.
Listen up! Bring me
a map of this area!
[ZACK, HUSH]
Yes, sir!
[ORGA]
Also, get confimation
on the Mobile Armor's
current location!
Send Akihiro's team to do recon!
[SHINO]
Roger!
General.
We've laid the foundation
for our plans on Mars.
We mustn't let go of that.
And then there's the matter
of the Order of the Seven
Stars Iok Kujan mentioned.
I think I want one.
[ISURUGI]
The most dangerous aspect
of Mobile Armors are the Plumas,
the swarm of smaller
units that accompany them.
In addition to offense,
the Plumas have another
important function.
They can repair the main body.
How so?
[MCGILLIS] They're able to
mend it without external help.
Huh? You're kidding me.
And that's not all.
The main body can
manufacture new Plumas.
Given enough time and materials,
Plumas can multiply
indefinitely.
Man, that's a scary thought.
Yeah.
[MCGILLIS] That's how
they were able to keep
killing people without end.
So then, to beat it,
we have to separate it
from its pack, correct?
That's right.
Once repairs are completed,
it will head for a more
populated area.
To seek out and destroy humans.
That is the most basic
protocol for Mobile Armors.
Their instinct, you could say.
Instead of chasing
after it directly,
setting a trap along its path
would prove more effective
in terms of an ambush.
But where's the nearest
populated area?
Oh!
There's only one place around
here that's populated!
It's heading for Chryse!
[ORGA]
We're movin' out for Chryse!
[MIKAZUKI] Can you take
Barbatos there for me?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
Yes, sir!
We'll have our Mobile Suits
brought down from
orbit, as well.
Let's meet up again
in three hours.
Got it.
When the Second Unit gets here,
tell 'em to keep an eye on those
things, from a distance.
And while they're at it,
find an ambush point!
I want the First Unit
to go back and resupply!
My Ryusei-Go has enough
juice to run for a while!
Do you want me to go on ahead
and wait for the Second Unit?
No, wait. I've got another
job in mind for you.
Huh?
Here's the plan.
We'll start the search at
Master Iok's landing point
and work outwards from there.
[VIDAR] Let's split up. It'll
be more efficient that way.
[JULIETTA]
Sounds good.
[KUDELIA]
A Mobile Armor?
[HUSH]
Apparently, it's a monster
that killed a lot of people
in the Calamity War.
And they say it's
on its way here.
Orga's explaining it
to the city leaders.
He wants 'em to evacuate
all the residents.
You guys should leave, too.
Yeah, but... if we did,
where would we go?
I] I heard that
there's a shelter
not too far from the
outskirts of the city.
You're right, there
was one constructed
back when this area was
first being settled.
But even so, it's not
large enough to house
the entire city's population.
Well, in that case, you
really need to get moving!
[KUDELIA]
No.
I won't evacuate.
Miss Kudelia?
If I were to leave,
people who are less
fortunate than myself
would surely be left out.
I originally founded
the Admoss Company
as a way to help
those very people.
If I were the first to run away,
I doubt anyone would
trust me again.
Just as you and the others
always risk your
lives, Mikazuki,
I want to risk mine in order
to do my job properly.
In that case, I'm
not leaving either.
After all, the shop manager
and her family are here.
I can't just leave
you all and run.
[KUDELIA]
Miss Atra...
But... Mr. Mikazuki!
All right, then.
[HUSH]
Huh?!
[ORGA]
What?
So then they're not gonna leave?
[MIKAZUKI]
Nope.
She said she's not evacuating
unless everyone can.
[ORGA]
Damn it.
Have they decided where
we're gonna ambush that bird?
[ORGA]
Yeah.
If it's comin' for Chryse,
then it'll have to
pass through here.
We'll attack it in this gorge.
[YUKINOJO] Hey, sorry to
keep you boys waiting!
Mr. Mikazuki! The Barbatos
Lupus, it's here!
Don't worry.
I'll stop that thing.
Countin' on ya,
Commando Unit Leader.
[YUKINOJO]
Okay, raise it up!
[MERRIBIT]
Boss.
This is yours.
Have we received any word
from Akihiro's group yet?
Make sure that he
keeps callin' out
that Mobile Armor's position!
As well as how the
plan is progressing!
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
Yes, sir!
[MCGILLIS]
Well, well,
I never expected to
have to use this here.
The upgraded version
of the Grimgerde.
The Helmwige Reincar.
It wouldn't be wise for me
to pilot this machine,
given my sordid history with it.
Master it well.
[ISURUGI]
Sir!
[YAMAGI]
Wait a sec.
Those machines...
[ECO]
Huh?
Gjallarhorn's Mobile Suits?
[YAMAGI] Why are they at
a civilian spaceport?
[WORKER A] You guys are carryin'
around some scary cargo, too.
You're not attempting to start
a war or anything, are you?
[RIDE]
Whoa, look at all of 'em!
Is that the thing we're after?
[AKIHIRO] That's it, all right.
Don't get too close.
We're dead meat if it
detects our reactors.
[RIDE]
Huh...
It's moving slower
than I expected.
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah...
Maybe it's tryin' to keep
pace with those sub units.
Send this data to HQ.
[RIDE]
Roger!
How nice.
This means we'll have plenty of
time to set up for the plan.
[beeping]
[AKIHIRO]
An attack?
[RIDE gasps]
[RIDE]
The Mobile Armor changed course!
[AKIHIRO]
Son of a--!
Who the hell is that
freakin' moron?!
Did you see?! That was
a blow for justice!
[ORGA] Even if everything
goes well in the gorge,
we're cutting it close on time.
I know McGillis is sending
in his Mobile Suits,
but how much good is
it really gonna do
against something
like that monster?
[MERRIBIT]
Boss!
We have a problem. The Mobile
Armor has changed its course.
It did what?
Apparently, someone has attacked
it from the southeast.
It's begun moving
in that direction!
From the southeast?
That means...
[gasps]
[ORGA] It's headed for
the agricultural plant.
Ride, wait!
[RIDE]
I'll get ahead of it
and try to make the workers
at the plant evacuate!
Got no choice.
We're gonna back him up!
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
Roger!
[MIKAZUKI]
It changed course?
[HUSH]
That's what they say.
The Second Unit is
responding as we speak.
Barbatos, heading out.
[HUSH]
Hey!
Don't you need
to tell the boss
before you take
action like that?!
[YUKINOJO]
It's fine.
He is the leader of the
Commando Unit, ya know.
[IOK laughing]
[IOK]
I did it... I actually did it!
It was an offering
to my men.
Because of their
steadfast loyalty,
I delivered a decisive blow
against that Mobile Armor.
[JULIETTA] Was that attack just
now from you, Master Iok?
[IOK]
J-Julietta?!
Did you see what I did?!
I retaliated against that beast!
Are you that much
of an idiot, sir?
From that range you wouldn't
have even made a scratch on it.
No! You're wrong!
That was the Reginlaze's
maximum power output!
[JULIETTA] If something like
that were enough to do the job,
Mobile Armors wouldn't be known
as the most savage
weapons of all time.
[JULIETTA]
What are you doing?
Go away!
My men laid down their lives
to provide me with
this opportunity!
You can't ask me to turn tail
and run without avenging them!
Oh, give it a rest already,
and just do what you're
told for once in your life!
[RIDE] Do we know how many
people are living at that plant?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER E]
According to the data, not many,
but none have evacuated yet.
[RIDE]
Understood!
[AKIHIRO] All right,
let's cover Ride's back!
Do whatever it takes
to make it focus on us!
[MEMBERS]
Yes, sir!
There's an update!
The Second Unit is
defending the plant!
[ORGA]
Tch!
Hey, Mika!
[MIKAZUKI]
I heard.
[ORGA] It's too late to change
the ambush point now.
You're gonna have
to do something
to get it back on
its old course.
[MIKAZUKI]
Got it.
[CHAD] Damn it! That thing
is completely ignoring us!
It's headed straight for the
area where there's more people!
My god... what is--?
Don't you even try it!
[RIDE]
Huh?!
What the heck's going on?!
[CHAD]
It's got...
...a beam weapon?
[AKIHIRO]
A what?!
Hey, is Ride gonna be okay?!
[CHAD]
It's an ancient weapon.
I'm sure the Mobile Suit's
Nanolaminate Armor
can handle it.
[RIDE] Wh-What the hell did
that thing just hit me with?
[gasps]
Huh?
[RIDE]
It can't be...
I tried to... protect them...
[AKIHIRO]
Hey, Ride!
You okay? Answer me!
Ride!
[yells]
Damn it!
Damn it, damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it!
What the hell are you things?!
And why'd you have
to show up now?!
You should've just stayed
buried. You bastards!
Son of a bitch!
[RIDE]
Wh-What's going on?
You alive?
Mr. Mikazuki!
[MCGILLIS]
An unexpected change of course.
If we've learned
anything from this,
it's that things don't always
work out according to plan.
[ISURUGI]
I have to say,
it sounds like you're
having fun, sir.
[MCGILLIS]
Does it?
Even so, I can't say that
I'm particularly happy.
Unexpected pawn movements
tend to throw the
game off-kilter.
[beeping]
[ISURUGI]
An Ahab Wave?
[MCGILLIS]
Who is it?
[ISURUGI]
Confirming the IFF.
It's a Gjallarhorn machine code!
But, sir, isn't that...?
A Gundam Frame.
[SHINO]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"Battle For Chryse."
Sorry to bust in
on you like this,
but I need your help!
I'll keep you safe and sound,
so hold on to something!
Or should I carry you in
my arms like a princess?