[MERRIBIT] One must accept
the call to battle.
Tekkadan faces a huge pirate
organization known as the
Dawn Horizon Corps.
Gjallarhorn also
joins the fray.
As they take to the skies,
it's clear more young
blood will be shed.
[COOKIE]
And Right here too!
[CRACKER]
Look at this!
[KUDELIA]
Are those...?
[CRACKER] Mikazuki is checking
to see if we can grow anything
around here besides corn!
[COOKIE] He says it's what we
have to do to make a living
off the farm.
[KUDELIA] It's hard to
picture him farming.
[CRACKER]
Although most of them wither up.
[COOKIE] But he told us
he'd plant a new crop.
I wish we could help out more,
but our break's almost over.
Hey Kudelia, after we
head back to school...
...won't you feel...
[KUDELIA]
It's okay.
[COOKIE gasps]
There's nothing
to worry about.
After all... Mikazuki and
the rest are on top of it.
[COOKIE, CRACKER giggle]
[CUCUBITA]
I'm heading back to the office,
so keep an eye on the president,
if you'd be so kind.
Sure thing. We were told to
hide her here until the boss
and company return,
so that's what we'll do.
[COOKIE, CRACKER chatter]
I just hope this
blows over soon.
[DEXTER]
Indeed.
[LAFTER] Being able to freely
use Gjallarhorn's shipping lanes
makes the hair on the
back of my neck stand up.
Yeah, in the old days we'd
avoid the Ariadne security net
whenever possible.
Hey, you don't see
me complainin'.
It is better...
We've detected
an Ahab Wave!
[TROW]
Verifying frequency fingerprint.
[HIRUME] It matches
the Gjallarhorn ship
we're supposed to
rendezvous with.
They're here ahead of schedule.
[MERRIBIT]
Yes.
I see So that's Tekkadan.
♪
[ZACK]
Tekkadan is so cool.
I mean getting a job offer
straight from Gjallarhorn.
[ZACK]
Hey! Are those Grazes?
[DANE]
Yeah.
[ZACK]
Not too long ago,
they were enemies we
needed to kill, right?
I'm amazed that they
can get along so well.
[HUSH] I can't wait to
pilot a Mobile Suit.
[ORGA]
So then you only have one ship?
We were supposed to be meeting
up with a fleet of five ships.
Something came up,
so I had our fastest ship fly
ahead of the rest of them.
[EUGENE]
What kind of "something"?
[ISURUGI]
Take a look.
[ISURUGI] This data shows
Dawn Horizon Corps ships
within 12 hours of
these coordinates.
There's a flotilla
of three ships
on an outbound course from Mars.
I see. So did those ships
bring in the force that
struck the plant at Chryse?
Most likely.
What concerns me
is the flagship.
It's carrying their leader,
Sandoval Reuter on it.
He needs to be taken out before
he can amass his forces.
So what you're
suggesting is that we
pick the bastard off
while he's isolated.
Well, that's Warfare 101.
[ISURUGI]
Will you help?
You came here with
only one warship.
Sounds like the plan is to put
our lives on the line, right?
[ISURUGI'S MAN grunts]
[ISURUGI grunts]
You'll be suitably paid
for taking the risk.
The Brigadier
General swears it.
Just a minute. Wouldn't it
be more prudent to wait
for your main force to arrive?
[ISURUGI]
Sandoval is a cunning opponent.
We cannot afford to
waste this chance.
[ORGA grunts]
Whaddya say, Orga?
We're in. We'll help
you win this.
But Boss, we--
[ORGA]
However...
We're gonna be in
charge of this operation.
[ISURUGI] Understood. Then
we'll follow Tekkadan's lead.
I'll make arrangements
for a datalink
as soon as I return to my ship.
Eugene.
Huh?
Get yourself ready, then.
You'll be in control of the
entire fleet from the Isaribi .
Yeah, you got it, Boss!
Let's get to it then.
[MERRIBIT] What's your take
on what he had to say?
[ORGA] He seems to
be tellin' the truth.
But he is definitely
hiding somethin.
And for some reason,
he's in a rush.
[MERRIBIT]
If you had suspicions,
why did you agree
to his request?
Because if we do this, Tekkadan
will be running the show.
Which means we'll
get the credit.
[MERRIBIT grunts]
Sounds like that man isn't
the only one in a rush.
That gonna be an issue?
Yes, it is. Although, I doubt
you'd hear me out.
But I'm used to it.
I'll have the crew
rest in shifts
until we're ready to
begin the operation.
Sure, I'll let you
handle that then.
Well in that case,
I order you to get
no less than six hours
of rest, starting now.
Huh?
[MERRIBIT] You'll need it since
you've worked 36 hours straight.
[ORGA gasps]
You've been keepin'
track of that stuff?
[MERRIBIT]
If my doing so bothers you,
maybe you should learn to
take better care of yourself.
[ORGA grunts]
[mechanical humming]
[ORGA] Mika, I've been
lookin' all over for ya.
Hey Orga, what are you
doing on the Isaribi ?
I was told to take a
break and got bored.
Oh, really? You too, huh?
That lady is
something else, isn't she?
Has Eugene filled you
in regarding the plan?
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah. He said It's
our chance to capture
the enemy's boss.
If we beat them to it,
Gjallarhorn can't
take the credit.
And the Dawn Horizon Corps
is just as big a thorn
in Teiwaz's side, too.
Taking them out would make a
nice gift, don'tcha think?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm.
And, to be honest, I get
the feeling that Gjallarhorn
has their own reasons
for teaming up with us.
Even if it's unsafe,
it may still be a bridge
we have to cross.
Don't worry about it. I'll be
sure to pave the way for you.
[ORGA]
Hmph.
All right, I'm counting
on you. Just like always.
[ATRA] I'll always be
just a third wheel.
[ISURUGI'S OPERATOR] Sir,
We're entering the sector where
the Ariadne picked up those
Dawn Horizon Corps ships.
I want all hands
to stay alert.
--[computer beeps]
--[ISURUGI gasps]
[ISURUGI'S OPERATOR]
Ahab Waves detected.
[HIRUME] They match the
frequency fingerprints
we received from Gjallarhorn.
It's the Dawn
Horizon Corps, Boss.
Their intel was right. Is there
any word from our scout team?
[SHINO]
Come on, are you kidding me?
What is it?
[SHINO grunts]
[DANTE] What the hell man?
I thought they said three ships!
Oh, this is bad...
[MERRIBIT]
Impossible!
What's going on?
[SHINO] Orga, there are
ten of 'em! Ten enemy ships!
[ORGA grunts]
I'm getting a video feed
from the scout team!
[AZEE] They tricked our
Ahab Wave sensors by using
three of their ships
to tow the others.
So that's how they did it
They managed to pull
one over on us...
[SANDOVAL chuckles]
Hmph.
Picking off your enemy while
they're isolated is warfare 101.
Hey Boss, we have an LCS
call from the enemy ship.
Put it through.
[SANDOVAL]
I am Sandoval Reuter,
the boss of the
Dawn Horizon Corps.
With whom am I speaking?
[ORGA]
Orga Itsuka. Tekkadan boss.
As a show of mercy,
I will give you and your
forces the chance to surrender.
Thanks, but I think we'll pass.
You can apologize for starting
this whole mess, though.
[SANDOVAL chuckles]
[SANDOVAL] It sounds to
me like getting in bed
with those Gjallarhorn weaklings
knocked a screw loose.
[ISURUGI'S OPERATOR]
Filthy pirate! How dare you?!
[EUGENE chuckles]
[ORGA] Funny, 'cause I'd say
you're the crazy one if you
think that chump fleet yours
has a chance of beating us.
[growls]
[MERRIBIT]
Boss, don't--
[MERRIBIT gasps]
I'll let you run your
mouth for now, but remember,
the more annoying the fly,
the more satisfying the swat.
Hey, Eugene! The fleet is
in your command now. Got it?
Yeah, I read ya loud
and clear, Boss!
[EMBI] Enemy's deploying
to our left and right!
[AZEE] They're trying
a crescent tactic!
[EUGENE] Shino, get your
team back to the ship!
Hurry and send out Mikazuki!
Let's break through their front
before they completely
surround us!
[MIKAZUKI] So I'm distracting
their Mobile Suits then?
[EUGENE]
They're all yours.
[ELGAR] Catapult deployed.
Launch when ready!
Mikazuki Augus.
Gundam Barbatos, launching.
Handing over control of
the Hotarubi to the Isaribi .
If we disengaged
from this right now,
we'd be able to get
away with minimal damage.
Maybe, you're right.
But there'd still be casualties.
I won't let any of
our boys die in vain.
If we're risking lives,
let's move forward with
everything we've got.
[MERRIBIT grunts]
[MERRIBIT] What's the
situation with your fleet?
[ISURUGI] My main force
is already on its way.
If we can hold out,
we'll catch the enemy off guard.
[HIRUME] Enemy Mobile
Suits are heading this way!
We'll have to
continue this later!
[ORGA chuckles]
Get Akihiro's team
launched ASAP!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A]
Enemy ships are charging
in close formation!
So they're trying a desperate
frontal breakthrough.
Concentrate all of our
fire on the lead ship!
Let's make it clear how
outgunned they really are!
[ALL grunt]
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A]
Enemy mobile suit closing in!
[ENEMY LEADER A grunts]
At this range?! It must
be the infamous Devil!
Team One, on my mark!
The rest of you, destroy their
ships as planned!
Akihiro, you have company
heading your way.
[AKIHIRO]
I see 'em. Leave it to me.
Akihiro Altland. Gusion Rebake
Full City, launching!
[AKIHIRO] Our job is
to protect the ships!
Do whatever it takes!
Right!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
Yeah!
What kind of mobile
suit is that?!
[grunts] Spread out and
attack from both flanks!
[ENEMY LEADER B gasps, yells]
Well, look at that!
The new and improved Gusion
is lookin' pretty sweet.
It'd be nice to pilot one
of those Gundam Frames--
[gasps]
[SHINO grunts]
[ENEMY SOLDIER A shouts]
You can't just rush in
by yourself, Captain!
I can when I know
you've got my six!
[DERMA]
There's another!
[SHINO]
Huh?
[DERMA]
What are they? Grazes?
[SHINO]
Hey! Thanks for the save!
But, I gotta say,
it feels kinda weird.
All of a sudden we're fighting
alongside them like this.
He's got the edge
in maneuverability!
Get some distance
and surround him!
[grunts]
[SANDOVAL]
You're in the line of fire!
We're only dealing with
a single Mobile Suit here!
Hurry and finish it off!
[ENEMY SOLDIER B groans]
[ENEMY SOLDIER C]
Eat this!
[ENEMY SOLDIER C shouts]
That machine... I know it.
I'll cover you.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A]
We can't take out the enemy's
Mobile Suit!
[SANDOVAL]
Enough!
Pull back the Garm Rodi
teams that are ahead of us!
We'll barrage that suit with--
[ALL grunt]
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B]
We have missiles inbound!
Shoot them down at once!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A]
Smoke?
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B]
It's a Nano-Mirror Chaff.
We've lost visual
of the enemy ships.
[SANDOVAL growls]
[EUGENE]
Here we go!!
[AKIHIRO]
You don't have to hit 'em!
Just keep 'em off our backs!
If that's all you need,
I've got you covered!
[SANDOVAL] Ignore the
smoke and keep firing!
[SANDOVA grunts]
[EUGENE chuckles]
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B] We've
made it out of the chaff range.
Sir, the enemy ships
are circling back!
[SANDOVAL] What are those
little punks up to?
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A] They're
moving behind our left flank!
All right, light 'em up!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A] Ship
Seven Mobile Suit deck damaged.
Ships Eight and Nine,
propulsion dropping!
We can't maintain battle lines!
These guys are
trying my patience!
Circle around and
get their rear!
[ORGA]
Good work, Eugene!
[EUGENE]
My pleasure!
He's as reckless as ever.
All hands, prepare to
resupply the Mobile Suits!
This is a battle
of endurance!
Stay back! Stay back, stay back!
[RIDE grunts]
[RIDE]
Crap!
No! I'm out of ammo!
[RIDE gasps]
[RIDE shouts]
[LAFTER]
Gotcha!
[RIDE gasps]
[AZEE]
You've got guts.
That was some good
work out there, Ride.
[RIDE] Well Akihiro did say
whatever it takes...
[LAFTER] Yeah, but I wish you
wouldn't take everything he says
so literally.
[AKIHIRO shouts]
Of all the times to
run out of ammo!
--[computer beeps]
--[AKIHIRO grunts]
[AKIHIRO shouts]
[ENEMY SOLDIER D]
He's out of amo and helpless!
[AKIHIRO shouts]
[AKIHIRO] Who do you think
you're calling helpless, huh?!
Wh-What is that?!
[ENEMY SOLDIER D screams]
Nice to know this
thing works!
--[computer beeps]
--[AKIHIRO grunts]
[AKIHIRO]
A surrender signal?
Tch! This crap again?
We don't need the pilot.
Just take the suit
and set him adrift.
After you do, go back
and get resupplied.
[AKIHIRO]
No need, I'm fine.
[LAFTER] But Ride's almost
burned out. You're his C.O.
Head back and leave
this area to us.
[AKIHIRO]
Roger.
Defenses on the boss's ship
are tougher than I thought.
I guess I ll have to I'll
pick 'em off one by one.
[YOUNG ENEMY SOLDIER A]
I'm not done yet!
[SANDOVAL] Our human
debris work even harder
than the rest of the men.
Because we don't
allow them to surrender.
And if they lose,
they have no home to go to.
Which is why they fight
like cornered animals.
[SANDOVAL] They certainly
are a convenient lot.
But we won't make any
headway like this.
Go out there and show them what
real pirates are capable of.
[TWINS]
Hmph! Roger that.
[MIKAZUKI]
Oops, no ammo.
[SHINO] Mikazuki! Head back
and get resupplied!
We'll take over for you here!
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
Thanks.
[SHINO]
No problem! Leave it to us!
[gasps]
[DANTE]
Something's coming...
Derma, get back!
[DERMA]
Dante!
[DANTE shouts]
Not so fast!
[TWIN B grunts]
Quick Dante, detach your arm!
[DANTE]
Dammit!
[SHINO] I've never seen
suits like those before!
Fall back and regroup!
[YUKINOJO] Top off their
propellant and ammo!
If an armor plate is
damaged in any way,
swap out the
whole thing!
[CREW]
Yes, sir!
Mikazuki!
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm starving...
[ATRA chuckles]
I knew you'd say that.
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[ATRA]
Here!
Drink some of this, too!
[ATRA gasps]
[ATRA grunts]
[MIKAZUKI]
Is there more?
[ATRA gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
Oh, yeah! Tons more!
Eat as much as you want!
[ZACH]
Ammo, ready!
[CREW A]
Oil check, done!
He moved around more than
anyone else out there
but somehow he still managed
to use the least propellant.
Is it...? Dammit.
[YUKINOJO] We're all done here,
Mikazuki. Atra, come on out.
[ATRA]
Coming!
A hot meal would be nice...
for next time.
[ATRA chuckles] In that case,
I'll have lots waiting for you!
[YUKINOJO]
Get a move on!
Make some room, Lafter's
Shiden is coming in next.
[ZACH]
There's more?!
[YUKINOJO] We shouldn't prolong
this battle for too much longer,
Orga.
[YAMAGI]
Boss!
We just need a little more
time to patch up the Gusion!
Its loadout is pretty complex.
[ECO] Ride's in no condition
to go out, either!
All right, but you're gonna
have to make it quick!
We need as many out
there as we can get.
Victory's within our reach!
[ORGA] Just one more push...
and then we've got 'em!
[SANDOVAL CREW grunt]
[SANDOVAL]
The hell was that?!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B]
Warships!
I've detected five of
them on the port side.
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B]
Sir, Its Gjallarhorn!
What?!
It's Isurugi's main force!
[ISURUGI] No... it's the...
Arianrhod Fleet.
[IOK'S OPERATOR A] Sir, I'm
showing a Halfbeak-class ship
belonging to the Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet
and two civilian ships.
Civilian?
Who are these people?
How should I know?
[RUSTAL'S MAN A] We have
confirmation that Master Iok's
Second Fleet has
engaged the enemy.
I see.
[RUSTAL'S MAN A] We've also
detected vessels belonging to a
civilian organization
in the same sector.
Civilian, you say?
[RUSTAL'S MAN A]
"Tekkadan," I believe.
[RUSTAL] They were involved in
the Arbrau incident, right?
It would appear the rumors
that they have ties to
McGillis were actually true.
[RUSTAL'S MAN A grunts]
[RUSTAL]
Tekkadan and McGillis.
You can't help but get worked
up at the sound of those names.
[VIDAR]
I'm coming for you...
...McGillis.
[DERMA]
What the hell?!
Aren't these guys sopposed
to be on our side?!
Derma, are you okay?!
Damn it all!
What's going on, Orga?
[ORGA]
Who are those guys?!
[ISURUGI] The Outer Lunar
Orbit Joint Fleet.
Rustal Elion is their commander.
[MERRIBIT] In other words, they
belong to an entirely different
chain of command from you.
[ISURUGI]
Yes.
[MERRIBIT grunts]
Tch. So that's why he
was in such a big hurry.
[ISURUGI] It's imperative
that we capture Sandoval.
Right about that!
All Mobile Suits, listen up!
Avoid fighting the Gjallarhorn
forces that just showed up!
Focus on the enemy boss!
[SANDOVAL]
Unforgivable Tekkadan!
You would stoop so low as
to suck up to Gjallarhorn
and call in reinforcements?!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR A]
Sir, if this keeps up,
there's no way we'll--
[SANDOVAL]
Sound the retreat!
Set a course for
the debris zone!
[SANDOVAL'S OPERATOR B]
What about you sir?
I'll draw them away from us!
[grunts]
Give a message to the men!
Tell them Sandoval is launching!
[IOK'S MAN A]
Please wait, Master Iok!
You should really
let us handle this!
There's no need for you
to sully your hands
with these thugs, Sir.
Lowly pirates they may be,
but it is the creed of the Kujan
family to crush your foes.
[IOK'S MAN A] But what if
something were to happen
to you, sir?!
I'll be just fine. After all
I have my Reginlaze.
[IOK'S MAN B]
Yes, but, sir...
[JULIETA] I'll babysit him,
just hurry up and launch me!
We can't let them
get ahead of us.
This is Julieta Juris,
taking off in the name
of Master Rustal!
[SANDOVAL] Sandoval Reuter,
launching in the Yugo!
[SANDOVAL] I've had enough
of this, Gjallarhorn!
I'll be the one
claiming victory, Tekkadan!
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER A]
You're finished!
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER A grunts]
What the--?! Let go!
Out of my way!
"Just take out the
enemy boss," they said!
But he's cooped up
in that ship there!
[DANTE] Not anymore.
He's in a mobile suit.
I'm sending over
some data pulled
from the suit we captured.
Here!
[ORGA]
Mika, you seein' this?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah. That one there.
[SANDOVAL]
Listen up!
You're fools if you honestly
think you can get away
with defying the
Dawn Horizon Corps!
[MERRIBIT]
He's in that suit.
The time has come for
you to meet your end!
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER B screams]
[SANDOVAL] If you're ready
to throw your lives away,
then come at me!
Filthy pirate...
The mighty Sandoval
welcomes you!
[ORGA]
Take this guy out, Mika!
What was...?!
This one... belongs to me.
You're in my way... Move!
♪
[ZACK]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam :
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"The Trigger Of Success."
I wanna move up
in the world too!
This has been Zack Lowe!