[MIKAZUKI]
The sun's about to rise.
[ORGA] Yeah... It's almost
time to leave for Saisei.
Once we drink to pledge our
loyalty to Teiwaz at the
sakazuki ceremony, we'll be
on equal footing with Naze.
A Teiwaz subsidiary.
[ORGA] A farm this size
won't be able to pull in
the money we need. Lots of
guys with nowhere to go
will wanna join
up with Tekkadan.
[ORGA] Eventually... we'll go
completely legit.
But Until that day...
we go all-in.
I'll take the shortest route
possible to make that dream
a reality.
There's no time to hesitate.
[ORGA] Do you think...
that Biscuit have stopped me?
[MIKAZUKI]
I honestly don't know.
[ORGA]
Hm.
[MIKAZUKI]
That being said...
if you're not stopping,
then neither am I.
I Never have... never will.
[ORGA]
Hm.
Sun's up.
[ATRA] Mr. Makanai had become
Prime Minister of Arbrau,
and thanks to Gjallarhorn's
corruption being exposed,
the world had finally changed.
It was slow, but progress
was happening.
[ATRA]
Tekkadan.
They were thrust into the
spotlight during the fighting
surrounding the prime
minister election,
And after offering half-metal
mining rights as a gift,
they became a direct
Teiwaz subsidiary.
In order to strengthen Arbrau's
defenses that had been dependent
on Gjallarhorn, Tekkadan was
made an official military
advisor with a branch on Earth.
Their heroic deeds during
the turmoil were recognized,
and they became a
promising company,
with a slew of envious rivals.
Their biggest ally,
Miss Kudelia,
partnered with Teiwaz to
establish the Admoss Company.
Its purpose was
to mine, process,
and ship the half-metal
of Arbrau's colonies.
In addition to that,
she also worked closely with
Tekkadan to open an orphanage
at the Sakura Farm.
Miss Kudelia has done
everything in her power
to help the socially vulnerable
and realize Mars'
economic independence.
[ATRA]
In contrast,
Gjallarhorn lost
the public's trust,
which resulted in even
further deterioration of
law and order around the world.
And, unfortunately,
during the conflict,
Tekkadan proved the
value of child soldiers.
Masses of children
have been sent to war
and the number of
Human Debris has grown.
And Mobile Suits were
once again recognized
for their military value.
Every country has begun to
restore and upgrade Suits
from the Calamity War.
The number of Mobile Suits
has since rapidly increased.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[ATRA] The world where powerless
children are exploited...
...continues to exist.
[metallic creaking]
[YUKINOJO]
Easy, easy now.
You scratch this thing
and your ass is grass.
[HUSH]
Yo, anyone here?
Name's Hush Middy. I'm here
from the Reserve Corps.
I'm supposed to let you know
the operation tests for the
Shidens are about to--
What the hell?
Nobody's here. Jeez.
[HUSH gasps]
[HUSH scoffs]
This guy again?
What is with him?
All the guy does is sleep.
People around here call
him the "Fiend" or "Devil."
He's more like industrial waste.
[YAMAGI] I'd be more careful who
I say that kind of stuff around,
if I were you, newbie.
Seriously, man...
[HUSH]
Yeah... sorry...
[YAMAGI]
Can't blame you, though.
The Barbatos and Gusion are both
being worked on back at Teiwaz.
And you're new, so you
still haven't had a chance
to see the real
Mikazuki in action, yet.
[HUSH]
Huh?
[YAMAGI] And Roger on
the Shidens. Let's go, Dane.
[DANE]
Yes sir.
[YAMAGI] You can go
straight to the training
for new recruits
once that's done.
[DANE]
Will do.
[HUSH] What did he mean by,
"the real Mikazuki?"
[SHINO] Come on!
You call that running?!
Pick up the pace newbies!
I wanna see some hustle!
[NEW MEMBERS pant]
[ZACK] Huh. It's as if his
yelling has inspired me
to be a good soldier.
[SHINO] Hey, Zack! You wanna
do another lap, or what?!
[ZACK]
Huh?!
[EUGENE]
Yo, Shino.
[SHINO]
Huh?
Try takin' it easy on 'em.
You're starting to sound just
like those First Corps geezers.
I know, but the thing is...
I'd feel terrible if
these rookies died
because I was
too soft on them.
[SHINO]
You can be nice to them, though.
I mean, after all, these guys
only need one jackass to hate.
Am I right, Deputy Boss?
Cut it out...
[SHINO gasps]
[ZACK]
Huh?
[SHINO]
A mock battle already?
[LAFTER chuckles]
[DANTE grunts]
Damn!
[AZEE] Dante, you need
to react quicker.
[DANTE]
I'm doing my best.
--[LAFTER] Pay attention!
--[DANTE] Dammit!
[YUKINOJO] That Dante
doesn't change does he?
The Shiden's Io Frame is based
on Hyakuri and Hyakuren.
It's a mass-production model
developed by Teiwaz
[YUKINOJO]
It's like I thought...
Operating on different levels.
Jeez! All of you guys
need to sharpen up
and get your acts
together already!
If you don't, we won't be able
to go back home to Naze!
[DANTE]
Really?
I kinda feel sorry for 'em.
That's okay...
--[NEW MEMBERS gasp]
--[MAIL] That's so cool!
[NEW MEMBER B]
I know watcha mean!
[MAIL]
Real Mobile Suits!
[ZACK gasps]
Man, that's impressive.
Is it their first time
piloting Shidens?
[DANE grunts]
[HUSH] So that's the
Alaya-Vijnana System?
Oh yeah, you're right. I forgot.
So that's how they're
flying around like th--
[SHINO] Those Shidens don't
have the Alaya-Vijnana.
Huh? Are you serious?
The Alaya Vjinana system
is from the Calamity War.
We don't know that much about
it, yet, so people using them
in Teiwaz's new systems
is a no-go for now.
It can be used... for things
besides Mobile Suits, right?
[SHINO]
Hm?
Can't you use them for Mobile
Workers and jobs out in space?
[MAIL]
He's right.
[NEW MEMBER B] It's crazy to
think about it, but you end up
getting all of that power
from just a little surgery.
Come to think of it,
why doesn't the Boss
let us have the surgery?
[NEW MEMBER B]
I know right?!
Ah, you have got to
be kidding me...
[EUGENE]
That's enough!
We didn't have the surgery
because we wanted to.
You shouldn't have to gamble
on such a risky operation.
The world we're
buildin' here...
...is one where no one
has to take that risk.
[ZACK]
Ah...
[SHINO chuckles]
Okay then, I hope you
slackers are all rested up,
because I think another
ten-lap run is in order!
Huh?!
[SHINO]
All right, men, get going!
[NEW MEMBER B]
Ten laps?
[SHINO]
Gotta say...
...that was a real nice
speech you gave, Deputy Boss.
So about Orga...
[SHINO]
Hm?
The boss is doin' work
that's not fit for him,
so I have to do my
part to help out.
[SHINO]
I know what you mean.
[ORGA]
Hey, I hate to break it to you,
but these numbers aren't right.
[NEW Member C]
Oh, uh, sorry, Sir.
[ORGA]
The other two are good to go.
[DEXTER]
Yes. Thank you sir.
You have a call from
Mr. Naze on the QCCS--
[ORGA] Brother?!
Thanks for, uh, tellin' me.
I'll take it in the other room.
[MERRIBIT]
Sure.
[ORGA]
Oh, and one more thing.
Don't forget to send flowers
to the Eizen Company
for their new office.
[NEW MEMBER C]
Will do, sir!
The boss sure is working
really hard, isn't he?
It wasn't too long
ago that he hated
sitting behind a desk all day.
Indeed. Times have changed.
[NAZE]
So, Orga... how's it going?
[ORGA]
It's goin alright, I guess.
[NAZE]
Oh, come now.
You're the hero that brought
half-metal to Teiwaz.
A very lucrative deal.
Though, I suppose, some might
view that with a bit more envy.
[ORGA]
Right.
We're in the same boat.
See, everyone hates
young upstarts,
no matter who they are.
[ORGA] Our rank is way
below the Turbines,
which control Teiwaz's
entire transport network.
We're only recognized for
our strength.
If we hadn't
overpowered Gjallarhorn.,
we wouldn't get the time of day.
Ya not satisfied?
[ORGA] No, you guys know
I'm grateful beyond words.
You got us Teiwaz's latest
Mobile Suits at a bargain.
And besides that, you're working
on our two Gundam Frames,
Barbatos and Gusion, for free.
Honestly, grateful is
an understatement.
That being so... we have no
intention of stopping just yet.
[NAZE chuckles]
Cheers then.
I'm looking forward to what you
have planned, Blood Brother.
[ALLIUM] You, my dear,
have made us very proud.
You've no idea how glad I am
that I granted you time to
speak at the
Naochis July Assembly
when you were still an unknown.
Kudelia Aina Bernstein,
Maiden of the Revolution.
Thank you for allowing me
to speak to the assembly,
Mr. Gyojan.
Not a problem.
Now, we have a lot of work
to do, so let's get to it.
The first order of
business involves another
mass meeting that I'm
holding next month.
The location will be Chryse.
I'd love for you
to give a ta--
Forgive me, Mr. Gyojan,
but for the time being,
I'm refraining from
speaking publicly.
[ALLIUM]
Hm...
I understand.
For the time being.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[ALLIUM] Correct me if
I'm wrong, Miss Kudelia,
but I've heard you're
going to invite people
from other colonies
to tour around
your half-metal mines
at the end of this month.
Where did you
hear about that--?
[ALLIUM] I'll assist you.
After all, your tour could
benefit from the help of a
noted intellectual from Chryse.
[KUDELIA]
Sorry?
[ALLIUM] Well, it's clear that
your original philosophy
was greatly influenced by mine.
Naturally, if I
stood by your side,
I'd be able to offer
some assistance.
[KUDELIA grunts]
Look...
--[knocking]
--[CUCUBITA] Excuse me.
Sorry, but it's time for
your next appointment,
Madam President.
[ALLIUM] How dare you?
We're in the middle of a--!
[KUDELIA] Thank you, Cucubita.
[ALLIUM grunts]
[KUDELIA]
Mr. Gyojan...
Respectfully,
I decline your offer.
[ALLIUM gasps]
[KUDELIA] My current activities
don't require anything as lofty
as philosophy.
Nowadays, as sad as it is,
words will get you nowhere.
[ALLIUM grunts]
[CUCUBITA] At this point, his
organization, Terra Liberionis,
is virtually hanging
on by a thread.
It seems he wanted one
last shot at the limelight
by using your fame. Ha, ha.
like there's a chance
in hell of that working.
Even so... He knew all
about the mine tour.
[CUCUBITA]
Huh?
[KUDELIA] We shouldn't take him
lightly.
[DRIVER]
How did she react?
[ALLIUM]
Unacceptably.
[DRIVER]
Then...
Get in touch with
you-know-who immediately.
We need to reach out
to Tekkadan, right away.
[CLASSMATE A]
Seriously?
Tekkadan is actually coming
here to pick you up?
Yeah, probably.
Definitely!
I'm sure they're coming,
especially since their brother
was one of Tekkadan's
bravest soldiers
and died a heroic
death for Mars!
[CLASSMATE C]
He was so brave!
[CLASSMATE D]
So cool!
[CLASSMATE C] I wish
I could join Tekkadan.
[COOKIE gasps]
[CLASSMATE D] I wonder
if girls can join too?
[CLASSMATE A gasps]
Isn't that them?
[CLASSMATE C]
Yeah!
[CLASSMATES chatter]
[CRACKER gasps]
[COOKIE]
Is that...?
[ATRA]
So tell me,
have you gotten used
to the new dorm, yet?
They're all rich kids, from
what everyone tells me.
Do they bully you?
No, not at all.
They're great!
Our brother sent us
to an amazing school!
[MIKAZUKI sighs]
I can read harder books
than you now, Mikazuki.
You're not the only one who
can read better now, you know.
[COOKIE]
I'm so excited to see Grandma!
We're gonna help Grandma
out as much as possible
during spring break.
[COOKIE, CRACKER, ATRA scream]
A-An explosion?
Atra, just keep the
car running, okay?
And take off your seatbelt.
A car blew up from
the looks of it.
The good news is
none of us are hurt.
We're still trying to
figure out what happened.
[MIKAZUKI]
Roger. I'll check it out too.
[COOKIE, CRACKER]
You can't go!
Don't go out there, Mikazuki!
I'm begging you.
Please don't run
off into danger.
[MIKAZUKI sighs]
[BYSTANDER A]
Another terrorist attack?
[BYSTANDER B]
Why isn't Gjallarhorn
doing something about it?
[ORGA]
How were the twins?
[MIKAZUKI]
They're doing real good.
[ORGA]
Glad to hear it.
[MIKAZUKI]
So...?
[ORGA]
First thing tomorrow,
I want you and Pops
to go get the Barbatos.
Roger that.
Is that it.
Not gonna ask me why?
[MIKAZUKI]
Work, right?
[ORGA chuckles]
[ORGA] It's for Kudelia's
job in two weeks.
Something's fishy about it.
I'm not sure it'll
be on time, but...
[MIKAZUKI]
Leave it to me.
[ORGA]
Hm?
Don't worry I'll make it.
Anything that you
order me to, Orga.
[ORGA] Right. Then I'm
countin on you,
Commando Unit Leader.
[ORGA]
All right, listen up, everyone.
Next weekend, Admoss Company is
holding a tour of the mines.
And so...
[EUGENE] So that means
our next mission is gonna be
escorting the visitors
during the tour.
[ZACK] W-Wait, you mean,
with the princess?
[SHINO]
Huh? Who's the princess?
Miss Kudelia, of course.
Doesn't everyone know that?
[SHINO]
Huh?
[EUGENE]
Listen up.
This'll be your first
time on the battlefield.
[ALL gasp]
[HUSH]
My first time out...
All of you will be joining
Akihiro's Second Unit
and piloting Mobile Workers.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm. Uh... Listen--
Listen up, maggots!
This isn't training!
So look alive out there!
The Second Unit is
not for pushovers!
[NEW MEMBERS]
Yes sir!
[HUSH]
Finally...
[GALLUS] You've done a
great job reorganizing the
Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet,
and regrouping our Earth
activities that were made
difficult after the
Arbrau incident.
What's more, you've also
built new ties
with each economic bloc.
Brilliant work, McGillis Fareed,
new fleet commander and
Fareed family patriarch.
No, no, any success on my part
was due to the help of everyone.
[ELEK]
Oh, pish posh...
because of you The Outer Earth
Orbit Regulatory Joint Fleet
won't just be a piece of
ceremonial decoration.
You're giving me far more
credit than I deserve.
I'm merely following in the
footsteps of my predecessor,
Carta Issue.
Morever, I carry a tremendous
burden from my past.
[IOK gasps]
[IOK]
Burden?
And as you may know, while in
the Inspection Bureau,
I directly exposed a
great deal of corruption
within the Mars Branch.
But as a result, the Mars
Branch was weakened.
It's regrettable to say,
but that area has now become
lawless and pirates have
begun to dominate the region.
Although it was my aim
with the Mars Branch to
carry out justice, I'm the one
who caused this problem.
As such, I would like your
permission to resolve this
matter personally.
That being said I request
that you authorize my
Outer Earth Orbit Regulatory
Joint Fleet to intervene
within Mars territory,
in order--
Impossible! That would
be trampling on the
responsibilities of
Lord Elion's Fleet.
[GALLUS]
Please, Lord Kujan!
[IOK] Is it not our duty to
maintain law and order
in the outer spheres?
You must maintain composure.
[RUSTAL laughs]
[RUSTAL] I think it's a
fine thing to see a youth
with such passion in his heart!
Master Rust--Apologies,
I mean Lord Elion...
[RUSTAL] Lord Kujan,
the reason for Gjallarhorn's
very existence is to
maintain order in the world.
To be perfectly frank with you,
who ends up doing that job
is of little consequence.
What is most important is
that we continue to have
the power necessary to
maintain peace and order.
[JULIETTA]
Master Rustal.
[RUSTAL]
Hm?
There you are.
Sorry to keep you, Julieta.
So how did it go?
Actually...
[JULIETTA grunts]
[JULIETTA] ...that's something
of a silly question.
Master Iok's face tells me
everything that I need to know.
[IOK grunts] What's that
supposed to mean--
It was very interesting.
McGillis was looking for
an opportunity to let the Outer
Earth Orbit Regulatory Joint
Fleet operate in
the Outer Spheres.
It would appear he's
set on using Mars
as a starting base
to attain that goal.
Master Rustal, if you understood
so much of his plan, why didn--
[RUSTAL] Have you forgotten?
I'm the commander of
Gjallarhorn's strongest Fleet,
the great Arianrhod,
Outer Lunar Orbit Joint Fleet.
If it's a challenge he wants,
then I'll accept it head on.
[IOK chuckles nervously]
[RUSTAL]
Who wants some meat?
[JULIETTA]
Meat? That's my favorite!
[IOK gasps]
Mine too!
[ISURUGI] How do you
think Mars will respond?
[MCGILLIS]
Don't worry.
The provisional commander
of the Mars Branch
is a man I nominated while
at the Inspection Bureau.
[ISURUGI]
I see.
[MCGILLIS] Also, I have
an associate on Mars
whom I trust implicitly.
A friend, I take it, sir?
[MCGILLIS] Isurugi you
should know by now.
I no longer have friends.
[HUSH] I thought we came out
here to fight a real battle.
I know, right?
We've already been here for a
week and all we've done so far,
is escort some VIPs during
the day and take turns
patrolling the area at night.
[MAIL] We're gonna have
to go home tomorrow
without seeing any action.
[ZACK] But the princess
sure was pretty, though.
[HUSH]
Huh?
[MAIL]
Yeah, she was.
[ZACK gasps]
All right, man your positions,
on the double!
[ZACK]
Huh?
[RIDE] We got a
call from the Boss.
What did he say to you?
The enemy's coming. Let's move!
[HUSH chuckles]
[KUDELIA] It's awfully late,
isn't it? What's going on?
[ORGA]
Where are your guests?
[KUDELIA gasps]
They're having a meeting
about tomorrow' last tour.
[ORGA] Sorry, but we're
gonna have to cancel that.
[KUDELIA gasps]
Right now, we're focusing
on the Dawn Horizon Corps.
It seems they landed on
Mars three days ago.
Dawn Horizon?
Yeah, they're pirates.
They have ten ships and
twenty-five hundred members.
They're a massive group that
even Teiwaz has trouble with.
Sound like they were hired
by the Terra Liberionis Group
you told me about.
[KUDELIA]
I can't believe he--
[ORGA grunts]
[ORGA]
Damn... they're already here.
[ORGA] Sorry it took us so
long to gather the intel.
But I'm gonna need
you and your guests
to get to the shelter now.
[KUDELIA]
Where is Mikazuki?
He's currently on
a business trip.
He should be on his
way back though.
But... There's no need
for you to worry about it.
Because we are...
[ORGA]
...Tekkadan.
[HUSH] Zack, we gotta find
a way to move up front!
We're not gonna get any credit
hangin' out back here!
Yeah, you're right!
[gasps]
[RIDE]
Captain, are these the...?
[AKIHIRO groans]
Of course they have those!
[ZACK] Hey! Doesn't this
alarm mean...?
They're Ahab waves...
[MAIL] Mobile Suits!
They have Mobile Suits!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT  A]
Mobile Workers, fall back.
Mobile Suits,
continue with the charge!
Come on out,
you so-called Devil.
I'll show them how fake you are
and give your suit
to our leader.
[MAIL]
Retreat!
[RAIL] I give up!
Please, I don't want to di--!
[ZACK]
Oh my God!
Oh, no way... Is this
where I'm gonna die?!
[SHINO] Sorry to keep
you guys waiting!
It took you long enough.
Get to work already!
[SHINO]
You got it!
Here comes Tekkadan's
First Working Unit!
Scratch that!
Ryusei Unit. Let's go!
Who's the Ryusei Unit?
Is that what he's
calling us now?
[HUSH]
Whoa...
[EMBI]
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Now's your chance
to refuel. Hurry!
Yeah, but uh...
we're winning, aren't we?
What's the big rush?
[EMBI] Just get a
move on, wouldja?!
[DANTE grunts]
[DAWN HORIZON PILOTA]
This is getting boring!
Where's your Devil or
whatever he's called?
Screw you! Just watch, we can
wipe you out without him!
Don't underestimate us!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT A]
Now what fun would that be?
Especially after all the
preparation we went through
to welcome him.
[gasps]
A separate force?!
[EUGENE]
Dammit. How many are there?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
I'm reading six reactors.
contact in five minutes--
no, four!
[EUGENE groans]
Shino!
I'll finish this in a minute
and head toward you!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT A]
Like hell you will!
[SHINO grunts]
This bastard's armor is tough!
[DERMA shouts]
[DANTE]
Thanks for the save, Derma.
Anytime man...
Let's get the next ones.
How're your thrusters?
Low, but there's no time for
me to refuel. I'll make do.
Let's go!
[DERMA]
Right!
Mobile Workers, form up
and make another line!
We've got to hold them
off until Shino gets here!
Does he seriously want
us to fight Mobile Suits
with Mobile Workers?
[TROW] Stop complaining and
get a move on, already!
[ZACK] Are you kiddin' me?
Those things are Mobile Suits!
What choice do we have?
If we lose this place, then
we've got nowhere else to go!
What's with these guys?
They got a death wish?
[KUDELIA]
Boss.
The tour group is safe
and sound in the shelter.
[ORGA] Good. you should
go and join them.
I'm sorry, but I'm not
leaving unless you are.
The members of Tekkadan
aren't like you.
[ORGA] We don't have any
grand ideals or aspirations.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[ORGA] We have no foundations,
or anything to fall back on.
The only way we can
protect where we belong
is by moving forward.
[KUDELIA] You're all
trying to move forward.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[ORGA chuckles]
[ORGA]
Yeah, but either way...
[RIDE gasps]
Wait, is that...?
[DERMA]
Is he really gonna...?
Can you believe it?
[EUGENE]
It's about time.
[YUKINOJO]
If we go any lower,
the shuttle will become
a target. You sure about this?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah, it's fine.
[YUKINOJO]
If you say so!
[MIKAZUKI] Inertial Control
System, and thrusters,
full throttle.
[HUSH]
What the...?
[ORGA]
As long as he's with me,
running away isn't
one of my options.
[ORGA chuckles]
[MIKAZUKI]
Five more, huh?
[ORGA]
Yo, Mika...
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[ORGA]
Welcome back.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm. Good to be back.
♪
[ATRA]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam :
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"In the Midst of Jealousy."
I think it's about time I
washed Mikazuki's bracelet.
Mine still smells okay
because I smell like flowers.