[ZACK]
Seriously?
What's with the freakin'
horde surrounding us?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 48A]
It doesn't matter.
We quit Tekkadan, so it
has nothing to do with us.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 48B]
I don't think they got the memo!
If they see us,
they'll hunt us down, for sure!
[ZACK grunts]
So that's how it is, huh?
We're always gonna be
part of Tekkadan
no matter where it is we go.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 48A]
Zack...
[IOK]
Your orders were to stand by
once we'd surrounding
Tekkadan's main base,
but are you sure that's wise?
[RUSTAL]
I am indeed.
In order to revive Gjallarhorn's
tarnished authority,
we must make a show
of our righteousness
to the entire world.
Maintain the current situation
until I get to Mars.
--[IOK] Yes, sir!
--[beeps]
So you've heard it.
Control of the civilian press
shall be at your discretion.
[NOBLISS]
Leave it to me, sir.
[PRESS OFFICER 48A]
In order to reestablish peace
in the Earth Sphere, we
of the Arianrhod Fleet
are announcing that we will
launch a mop-up operation
against both the traitor,
McGillis Fareed,
who took up arms
against the Seven Stars,
and Tekkadan, the armed
organization that's aiding him.
We've already surrounded
Tekkadan's headquarters on Mars
and have issued
calls for their surrender,
but they have yet to respond.
And so, we expect to begin
the operation as planned
tomorrow at noon, Mars time.
Madam President...
[GAELIO]
Now you have nowhere to run.
What's you next move, McGillis?
[MCGILLIS] The situation
has become much simpler.
If we wipe them out here,
this will all be over.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
I'd think you'd want to
fight them on your home turf.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'll fight...
...if and when Orga tells me.
But what do you want to do?
[MIKAZUKI]
I do what Orga wants me to do.
End of story.
[MCGILLIS]
This isn't about Orga Itsuka.
I'm asking what you think.
[MIKAZUKI]
I already told you.
Whatever it is
Orga decides to do,
is what I want to do.
[CHAD] All our communication
cables have been cut.
And they shoot down
our LCS drones
as soon as we launch them.
If we can't use the QCCS either,
it'll be impossible to get any
information from the outside
much less contact Mr. Makanai.
Gjallarhorn might be sittin'
tight for the time being,
but they could attack us
any minute now.
Look like we're at a dead end.
Why don't we just
go after them first, then?
Oh, come on.
We're outnumbered so bad
it's not even funny.
Up to you--your call.
There's nothing that we can do.
Our only option
is to run, so we run.
Haven't you heard
anything we've said?
Even if we managed
to get away from them
we'd be on the run
till the day we died.
[ORGA] As long as we make it
out of here, we win.
After that,
we'll destroy this place
to make it seem like
we were wiped out.
Wiped out, Boss?
Yeah. All we gotta do is
make them believe that we died.
We'll call Old Makanai after
that so he can help us out.
Good idea. That way,
they won't keep looking for us.
--Let's do it.
--[EUGENE] That's impossible.
If you think we can make it out
of here without being noticed,
then you're insane.
Actually, there might be
a way to do just that.
If I'm remembering correctly,
there were old power cables
running under the base
that date back all the way
to the Calamity War.
So, if those tunnels
are still down there,
we could use them to make
our escape to Chryse.
Do you think
that's even possible?
[EUGENE]
Seriously.
It's worth a try.
Eugene, go with Pops
and check out those tunnels.
[EUGENE]
You got it, I'm on it.
All right, listen up.
This battle isn't about
just killing someone
and it being over.
It's about
every single one of us
getting out of this mess alive.
That is our objective.
We're gonna get through this.
And our surviving
is what's gonna beat them.
You all got that?
Don't ever back down!
[EUGENE]
Man, he sure is ballsy.
Yeah, that's true.
But he is starting to act
like the old Orga again.
[CHAD]
I thought so, too.
He's full of confidence
for some reason.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm.
[EUGENE] You know, I said
something to Orga once.
That nobody here seriously
thought doing what he said
was gonna be a sure thing.
I meant it, but it was
only half true.
[CHAD]
Huh?
'Cause you can't help
but think that if you
stick with him and his orders
things will just
work themselves out.
Yeah. True.
[DANTE] In that case,
let's get to work.
[AKIHIRO, CHAD, EUGENE]
Right.
[MCGILLIS]
I see. So you're making the call
to sneak away from here.
The Tekkadan I know
would never back down.
You would just
fight without giving it
so much as a second thought.
[ORGA]
We're not dumb enough
to get into a conflict
we can't win.
We have a different
battle to fight.
A different battle, you say?
And what exactly is it
that you're hoping
to get out of that battle?
[ORGA]
The only thing I want
is for all of us to be alive
at the end of it.
We'd use whatever
was at our disposal.
And put our heads together
to figure out
what our next move should be.
That's how we always managed it.
I'm not sure when,
but I lost sight of that.
A rather pointless realization,
don't you think?
[ORGA] You can call it
whatever you want.
It's not pointless, though...
if I'm with my buddies.
--Buddies, eh?
--[radio clicks]
[EUGENE]
Hey Orga, we found the tunnel!
Are you serious?!
[YUKINOJO] Yeah, but I gotta
say it's seen better days.
We can't just haul off
and blast it.
We're gonna have to dig
through this mess by hand.
Fine, grab anyone who's free
and get to work right away.
[YUKINOJO]
Got it. Oh, and one more thing.
Some of these cables still
seem to be in working order.
If the terminal on
the Chryse side is functional,
it should be possible to get
a call through to the outside.
Understood. All right.
Let's start by clearing out
that tunnel A-SAP.
--[YUKINOJO] Roger that.
--[radio clicks]
If it turns out we can't
leave anytime soon,
then I'd like to at least
try and get the word out
to Old Man Makanai so he has an
idea of what we're planning.
You're saying you want
to contact Earth?
[ORGA] Yeah. And if we
could make it to Chryse,
there's also
Kudelia's Admoss Company.
We could make things
work over there.
But... with us
surrounded like this...
If it were just a few men,
you might actually have a shot
at temporarily breaking
through their blockade.
[ORGA]
Huh?
[MCGILLIS] I'm heading out.
I'll find a way
to break through Gjallarhorn's
blockade on my own.
What?
[MCGILLIS]
By going out there,
it'll focus all of
their attention on me.
While they're distracted,
it should be possible
for you to escape.
You'd actually do that for us?
[MCGILLIS]
Don't misunderstand.
I'm just taking
the necessary steps
to ensure my objective
is realized.
Whether you use that
to your advantage or not
is of no concern to me.
But you'll--
As a matter of fact,
your strategy is
quite beneficial
to my goal, as well.
By making it appear
as though you're still here,
we'll have a chance to lure
Rustal Elion into a trap.
You see, I plan on
using you to destroy him .
--[computer beeping]
--[ORGA] Listen, Chad.
Have Ride get a car
prepared for us.
We're heading to
the Admoss Company.
[CHAD]
What? But how?
[ORGA]
We have a way to get through.
We're taking Kudelia
and Atra along with us.
Go get them right away.
There's not much time,
so do it now!
[ATRA]
I'm not going with you.
[KUDELIA]
Miss Atra...
[CHAD] This will be
a battleground soon.
Trust me when I say
it's safer for you
to leave with Miss Kudelia.
[ATRA] But I... I don't want
to leave Mikazuki
and everyone else behind.
There's no time
to debate this, Atra.
[ATRA]
I know, but I...
Come on, Miss Atra.
[KUDELIA]
Let's go. Together.
After all, I made
a promise to Mikazuki
to watch over you
and your child.
--[CHAD] Uh.
--Wait, Atra's pregnant?
[KUDELIA]
So please, Miss Atra.
Help me keep the promise
that I made to Mikazuki.
My promise to the man I love.
[ATRA gasps]
[ATRA]
Okay...
You should probably go pack
and get ready, then.
[KUDELIA]
What about you, Ms. Merribit?
I still have quite
a bit of work to do,
so I'll be staying here.
[KUDELIA]
But you...
Please don't worry.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
The iron flower
known as Tekkadan
won't wither and die
that easily.
[MCGILLIS]
Barbatos Lupus Rex.
The king of the wolves.
What a valiant name.
Why are you dressed like that?
Going somewhere?
I am.
Mikazuki Augus, how would
you feel about joining me?
[MIKAZUKI]
Why?
Oh, right. I understand.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[MCGILLIS] I thought the way
you fought was beautiful.
Power that I saw as my ideal.
Power with which I could
secure a bright future.
You and your gang don't know
how to make use of that power.
So I thought that
I could lead you.
I believed that
I could guide you
toward our common goal.
However, I was mistaken.
Tekkadan's brilliance
has no ideals.
They lack a true
sense of purpose.
And they have no destination.
This fleeting nature...
[MIKAZUKI] You talk
too much, ya know that?
Every one of us
is gonna make it there.
Make it where?
[ORGA]
Hey. You know better than to
try and poach
one of our members.
Yes, indeed. My apologies.
Well then,
I think I'll be going.
[MIKAZUKI] Orga, do you
need me to go out, too?
It's not time for that yet.
There's another job that I need
you to take care of for me.
Yeah, okay.
Kings of Mars we said.
So much for that.
[MIKAZUKI] Was that it?
The place we belonged?
Well, that's what I always
told myself anyway.
We'll just have to
start lookin' again.
And I'm gonna
make sure that happens
by heading over
to Chryse with Kudelia,
and making arrangements
with Old Man Makanai.
That worries me a little.
[ORGA]
Hm?
If I'm not right there with you,
there's no telling
how you'll mess up.
Hey, watch it.
It ain't like you can
go charging into
the city in Barbatos.
Yeah, but still...
[ORGA] So, whaddya say
you just let me borrow
your gun instead, then?
[MIKAZUKI]
This?
[ORGA]
Yeah.
Brings back memories.
That day, I'm not gonna lie,
I was absolutely
terrified of you.
But I thought:
As long as I have
this guy by my side,
there's nobody in the entire
world who can beat me.
Even now?
Yeah.
Same as always.
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga.
Make sure that you
bring that back.
I plan to, Mika.
You don't have to worry.
[ATRA] Okay, I'll be
going now, Mikazuki.
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm.
Make sure
you're careful, Mikazuki.
I don't think I should
be lookin' at this.
[HUSH]
Are you done yet?
[ORGA] All right, guys,
Bael is heading out!
We need to go!
[SOLDIER 48A]
We've detected an Ahab Wave
from the enemy base!
--[COMMANDER 48A] The pattern?
--[SOLDIER 48A] Bael!
There you are, McGillis.
[COMMANDER 48A] All forces,
stay put! Don't move!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
Master Iok!
We have our orders, men!
We have to obey the commander!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
But, sir!
[IOK]
Mars' media is watching us!
It's Master Rustal's order!
We're not to move
until the enemy attacks!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
So we're just supposed to watch
as our comrades get taken out?!
[IOK grunts]
Exactly! You mustn't
take any action!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
Master Iok!
[COMMANDER 48A]
Lord Kujan, what are you doing?
[IOK]
Please forgive me, Commander!
But, if blood must first
be shed by someone...
[MCGILLIS]
He disarmed?
I see. You're trying
to force me into
drawing first blood, aren't you?
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
Master Iok, retreat!
[IOK]
Don't interfere!
My men have saved me
from the jaws of death
more times than I can count!
And if not for the noble
sacrifices of those men,
I wouldn't be alive today!
And that's why...
...the time has come
for me to lay down my life
in order to ensure
the safety of yours!
Quite the commendable
sentiment, Iok Kujan.
However, my purpose here is to
cause a fair bit of commotion.
You're trying to bait me...
[yells]
[MCGILLIS]
...so I may as well bite!
[IOK yells]
Dammit! Where is he?!
[gasps]
McGillis!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 48A]
Master Iok!
Now, Commander! Give the order!
[COMMANDER 48A]
Understood, Lord Kujan.
[COMMANDER 48A] All squads!
Commence counterattack!
[MCGILLIS] I'm in a rather
foul mood at the moment.
So, if you don't mind, I believe
I'll take it out on you.
[MCGILLIS]
Lupus Rex.
The king of the wolves.
[MCGILLIS]
That's right.
Wolves move in packs.
But that way of life
isn't for me.
[beeping]
[MCGILLIS]
Mission accomplished.
Time to part ways, Tekkadan.
[clanging]
[DANE]
Zack?
Wow, I never thought I'd
see you back here, again.
Like I had a freakin' choice.
I'll do whatever it takes
to stay alive.
Now hurry up and get to work!
[EUGENE] After you take over
for the guys working below,
--make sure that you keep--
--[ELGAR] Deputy Boss!
[ELGAR] The boss and the
others just broke through
--the enemy blockade!
--That's great!
Okay guys,
let's get to work!
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
Yeah!
--[door knob clicks]
--[CUCUBITA] Madam President!
Thank goodness
you made it out okay!
Oh, I thought I'd
never see you again!
Come now, you're overreacting.
[CUCUBITA]
Can you blame me?!
Gjallarhorn said Tekkadan was
refusing their order
to surrender!
They're planning an all-out
attack on them tomorrow at noon!
[ORGA]
They said what?!
[RUSTAL]
That's McGillis for you.
Acting before all
our pieces were in place.
[NOBLISS]
You're not concerned by this?
It's nothing but
a single Mobile Suit.
You just stay focused on
controlling the civilian media.
Trust me, sir, I am.
Even with this latest incident,
they're eating out of
the palm of my hand.
I'm quite certain
Gjallarhorn will never lose
its moral high ground.
I shall be waiting for you
here on Mars, then.
[beep]
[GAELIO] Is this wise? Letting
McGillis do as he pleases?
Mars is a big place.
Though the Mars Branch's
negligence is an issue.
If he were the kind of man
who would simply run away,
we wouldn't have
been faced with
a situation like this
to begin with.
He'll come.
We just have to be patient.
Then it'll be up to you.
Yes.
That is the only thing
I have to live for.
[RIDE] Those bastards never
gave us any calls to surrender!
[CUCUBITA] But that's what
the news keeps saying.
So that's the reason they cut
off all communications from HQ.
[ATRA]
What does that mean?
It means they don't plan
on letting us surrender.
Looks like they
intend to kill us all.
Oh, no...
But there's still time
to prevent that.
So let's get started!
[MAKANAI] How can you ask me
to do such a thing?!
Deliberate tampering
with personal information
is a serious offense!
I understand that.
But I'm not seeing
any other way out for us.
I'll do anything
to protect them.
I'll give my life to
save them! I'm begging you!
[MAKANAI] It's difficult
to turn down a request
from a man you owe your life to.
Mr. Makanai, are you...?
So, you'll help?
[MAKANAI]
Before I can do anything,
you must come to Earth to
finalize the formal paperwork.
Go back to Earth?
I understand.
We'll make it there.
[MAKANAI]
But be quick about it.
There's someone here
who is so worried about you
that he can't
do his job properly.
It's caused me to
fall behind in my own work.
[TAKAKI]
Don't say that, Mr. Makanai.
Wait, that voice!
Am I hearing, Takaki?!
Ride? Is that you?
What the heck are
you doin' over there?!
[TAKAKI chuckles]
Oh, I managed to get a job
at Mr. Makanai's office.
Are you serious?
[TAKAKI] And it's all
thanks to you, Boss.
Me and Fuka
owe everything to you.
And so I wanna do
what I can to repay you.
[ORGA]
Takaki...
[ATRA] So, if we can just make
it to Earth, we'll all be saved?
Yes.
[CHAD] You say that as if it's
going to be a walk in the park.
But I bet Gjallarhorn
will be watching the Isaribi.
Oh, that's right.
I completely forgot.
I received an email addressed
to Tekkadan while you were away.
It came for us?
[ORGA]
This... is from Miss Azee?
[AZEE] Since we can't
get hold of you guys,
we're sending a message
via Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
We saw what's happening
on the news.
If there's anything
we can do to help,
go to Teiwaz's office on Mars.
We can smuggle
anything, anywhere.
We already have
Mr. McMurdo's consent on this.
We'll be waiting for your reply.
[ECO]
Listen! You guys can't die!
You need to survive
for those we lost,
like Darling, Ma'am, Lafter,
and everyone else!
We'll be waiting!
You okay?
So what does Miss Azee say?
--[ORGA] We're all set.
--[CHAD, RIDE] Huh?
[ORGA]
It's gonna work out.
The road's opened up.
We just have to move forward!
First, we need to find out
where that tunnel comes out!
We'll use that cable
to let everyone know...
...we now have a plan
that'll save us all!
[BOTH]
Yeah.
[ORGA] Chad, Ride,
bring the car around back!
[CHAD, RIDE]
Yes, sir!
[ORGA]
Are you sure about this, Atra?
[ATRA] Yes. I'm going to
hide out at Miss Kudelia's
until this all blows over.
I'll keep her safe and sound.
It's what Mikazuki
asked me to do.
He did? I see...
Well then, I guess
this is goodbye for a while.
Guess so. And please,
take care of Mikazuki for us.
Sure.
[ORGA]
Now that I think about it,
Tekkadan really began when we
were hired to take you to Earth.
You deliberately chose us
for the job, didn't you?
Yes. I wanted to work
alongside children
who were around my age
and less fortunate than I was.
So I could somehow
share in their pain.
[KUDELIA, ORGA laughing]
Boy, what an arrogant
notion that was.
No, I'm grateful that you did.
So make your dreams come true.
I will.
[RIDE]
Boss!
The car's ready
whenever you are!
[ORGA]
Right!
We're off.
Okay. Please be careful.
[RIDE]
It almost seems too quiet.
There aren't any Gjallarhorn
soldiers in the city,
unlike our headquarters.
[ORGA] Yeah. They probably
sent every last soldier
they had over there.
[RIDE] Well, that doesn't
matter anymore now, does it?
[ORGA]
You're in a good mood.
[RIDE]
Of course I am!
Everyone's gonna be saved
and Takaki's hard at work!
So I gotta work hard, too!
Yeah.
[ORGA]
You're absolutely right.
Everything that we've built up
wasn't for nothing.
And from now on,
as long as we don't stop,
the road will continue.
[tires squeal]
[door handle clicks]
--[gunshot]
--[CHAD groans]
[gunfire]
[RIDE]
Boss! What are you doing?!
Boss!
[ORGA yelling]
[ORGA panting]
How 'bout that?
I'm a pretty good shot.
[chuckles]
[RIDE]
Hey...
Boss, are you...?
[RIDE whimpering]
[ORGA] Hey now, Ride,
what's with the whimpering?
[RIDE]
But... But you're...!
[ORGA] I'm the...
boss of Tekkadan, aren't I?
Orga Itsuka.
Dammit. This is nothing
but a scratch.
But why did you...?
You shouldn't
have done that for me.
[ORGA]
Protecting you is my job.
[sobbing]
--[RIDE] No!
--[ORGA] We have to go!
[ORGA]
Everyone's... waiting for us.
And besides...
[ORGA]
Mika, I finally get it.
We don't need
any goal to reach.
As long as we keep moving
forward and never stop,
the road will continue.
[MIKAZUKI]
I'm not gonna let you be sorry.
[ORGA]
Yeah. I know.
Believe me,
I'm never gonna quit.
So as long as you all
keep moving,
I'll be at the end
waiting for you!
[ORGA]
So listen up.
Don't you ever stop.
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga?
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans,
"McGillis Fareed."
Hey, Atra asked me to
think of a name for the baby.
What do you think it should be?
Oh, right. I'll ask Orga
when he gets back.