[MERRIBIT]
Rustal Elion,
supreme commander of
the Arianrhod Fleet.
In an attempt to
outmaneuver him,
McGillis comes to
Tekkadan for help.
What will await them once
they finally make their way?
The next stage is
Tekkadan's Earth Branch.
[MAKANAI]
I'm pleased to say
the Arbrau Defense Force
is starting to come together
very nicely thanks to Tekkadan.
And we have plans to hold
an inaugural ceremony.
[KUDELIA] Yes, I received an
invitation from Mr. Alesi.
However...
[MAKANAI] I suppose the timing
is a bit inconvenient.
I've heard various
rumors on my end.
I'm so ashamed, Mr. Makanai.
By now, we should be
making steady progress
toward Martian independence.
I even went so far as
to set goals for myself
in regards to economic
and employment problems.
And yet...
[MAKANAI]
Try to be patient.
To reach your goals,
you have to go through
the proper steps.
If one takes shortcuts,
it's sure to backfire
sooner or later.
[KUDELIA grunts]
[MAKANAI] if you
change your mind,
you know where I'll be.
[KUDELIA]
Yes.
[TAKAKI] Hey, where are
the Arbrau guys today?
Oh yeah, the inaugural
ceremony meeting.
It's for the
Arbrau Defense Force.
So, because of that, they're
taking a break from training.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30A]
As if those geezers could be
a "Defense Force."
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30B]
Hey, Takaki.
What's gonna happen
with us after all this?
You don't think we're gonna
be shipped back to Mars
once we're done training
those guys, do you?
Well... no one's
said anything...
I'm starting
to like Earth.
[TAKAKI]
Huh?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30B]
Same here.
The food's good, and
Tekkadan's always welcomed
with open arms when
we go into town.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30A]
Though, I could do without
that obnoxious old guy.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30B]
Tell me about it.
How long is that Radice
jerk gonna be here?
Take it easy, you guys.
He's now part of Tekkadan,
so try and cut him some sl--
That jerk will
never be one of us.
Teiwaz only sent him here
so he could be our chaperone.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 30B]
And he's always on our case
about everything!
[TAKAKI]
Mm.
[knocking at door]
--[CHAD] Huh?
--[door opens]
[TAKAKI] Mr. Chad, that suit
looks really good on you.
[CHAD]
Y-You really think so?
I'm way out of my depth here.
Are you positive that you
want me going to this,
instead of Mr. Radice?
[TAKAKI]
Well, you are the one
who's in charge of
the Earth Branch.
Besides that, Mr. Makanai
himself appointed you,
so you should be
more confident
[CHAD chuckles]
Uh, I suppose...
I look pretty dumb.
No. That's not what I meant.
[ASTON gasps]
Pardon me.
Please have someone
confirm the final schedule
for the Arbrau Defense
Force inagural ceremony.
You can leave that to me.
My associates and I will be
handling the venue security
while Chad is attending
the ceremony.
Actually, Arbrau will
be handling security
inside the venue-proper.
[CHAD]
Yes, we're aware of that.
We'll take care of
external security.
Your primary function is backup,
so please refrain from
doing anything flagrant.
I ask that you use
the utmost care
in avoiding any
further friction
with the Arbrau Defense Force.
The particulars of the
ceremony are in that file,
so look over it carefully.
Good day.
[door clatters]
What a jerk.
Now, let's not be
so quick to judge.
He's just thinking about
us in his own way.
[TAKAKI] That's true.
At least he's not rejecting
every idea we come
up with anymore.
[TAKAKI] Recently, he's been
a lot more receptive
to our suggestions.
[CHAD]
On the other hand,
maybe he thinks we're too
dumb to waste his time on
and has just written us off.
Took the words
right out of my mouth.
Mr. Chad looked really good
in that suit, didn't he?
Yeah.
About him...
[TAKAKI] Hmm?
[ASTON] He used to be called
Human Debris like me, right?
Yeah, that's right.
[ASTON]
I see...
Hey, would you like to
come over again, tonight?
I'm sure Fuka would
love to see you.
[TAKAKI]
Uh...
Fuka has a test to
study for, doesn't she?
I saw her studying
for it the other day.
[TAKAKI] O-Oh, yeah.
But at least have dinner.
Whenever I'm there,
all she does is fuss over me.
So I'll pass today.
Okay.
[TAKAKI]
I'm home.
Hey Fuka, I'm back from the...
[FUKA breathes softly]
[FUKA]
Uh...
[FUKA gasps]
I didn't even hear you come in.
I fell asleep while studying.
Give me just a sec and
I'll get dinner ready.
[TAKAKI]
That's okay, I'll do it.
But, I...
You can go ahead
and keep studying.
[FUKA]
Isn't Aston with you?
He's not coming over today.
Really?
Well, if he's not
gonna join us,
feel free to cook away.
Oh yeah? Why's that?
Ya know,
I never realized
how much you liked
studying, Fuka.
[FUKA] Yeah, it's
actually really fun.
And not just studying.
Every single day since we've
come to Earth has been fun.
[TAKAKI]
That's great.
I mean, having to say goodbye to
the other kids at the orphanage
was hard, but I'm
glad that I've made
lots of new friends
here on Earth.
Plus, Aston and everyone else
have been really sweet to me.
[TAKAKI]
Huh?
But, the best part is spending
lots of time with you!
Heh! I really like it here!
Yeah, I like it here, too.
[rainfall]
[FUKA] Oh no, I forgot I
left the laundry outside!
Wait, let me help
you with that!
[FUKA] Okay, could you
bring me the basket?
[TAKAKI]
Right away!
♪
[SHINO]
Aw man!
I bet Chad is feeling pretty
fired up right about now!
And there we go!
If the ship to transport
the Shidens to Earth
had only left
a little earlier,
we could've made him
look even more important!
That's for sure.
[LAFTER]
You're looking happy, Akihiro.
Yeah...
Not too long ago, Chad and I
were both called Human Debris.
Yes, I know.
There's not a doubt in my
mind that he'll do us proud.
[RIDE]
You know it!
Although, I bet if
it were you Akihiro,
you'd get all nervous
and totally freeze up!
[AKIHIRO grunts]
[RIDE gasps]
[SHINO]
Ride!
You comin' with, or not?
[RIDE]
Nah, not this time.
I have a lot of work that
needs to get finished here.
No way in hell am I
getting shown up by Takaki.
[SHINO chuckles]
[RIDE]
Hey, how's it coming?!
[ZACK]
Yo. What's up?
Is Mikazuki going to earth, too?
We're just delivering Shidens
at the moment, so I doubt it.
Why do you ask?
If there's even the
slightest chance
there's going to be a battle,
then I wanna be there
when it happens.
[ZACK] Huh? Are you still
going on about that?
Dane, there's somethin'
wrong with this dude!
[DANE]
Mm.
[ORGA]
Sorry, Atra.
You were just about to
close up shop, weren't you?
[ATRA]
Not a problem.
But, are you sure you
want it like that?
I can reheat it if you'd like.
That's alright.
[ATRA]
Oh, I have fruit, too!
Hey. Why didn't you
reheat the food?
Huh?
[ORGA chuckles]
I'm fine with
eating it as it is.
Yeah, and why is that?
It goes the same for food,
work, or trouble.
You gotta deal with what's
in front of you, as is.
Otherwise, it becomes
impossible to move forward.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[ORGA]
Hm? What's wrong?
I can't eat with you
staring at me like that.
You've lost weight.
Huh? Think so?
[ORGA gasps]
What the hell's that?
[MIKAZUKI]
Nutrients.
[ORGA gasps]
I don't wanna see you getting
too skinny. So eat up.
[ORGA chuckles]
[ATRA] Hey, you want
some fruit, Mikazuki?
[MIKAZUKI] No, thanks.
Peeling them is a hassle.
[ATRA]
Hm?
[ORGA grunts]
What's wrong?
Did it taste bad?
Oh, uh... no.
[ORGA]
Thanks though, Mika.
[IOK]
My apologies, sir.
I overlooked all the
warning signs,
regarding McGillis's
intentions.
[JULIETA]
Why stop there?
It's probably more
accurate to say that you
helped him along.
[IOK grunts]
[RUSTAL]
No matter...
They got the better of
us in the Mars-sphere,
but it'll be our turn next.
[IOK]
Our turn, sir?
Our next battleground
will be on Earth.
[JULIETA]
Huh?
Earth is the home base of
the McGillis faction, is it not?
I would assume that
us taking action there
would stir up trouble
within the Seven Stars.
[RUSTAL]
True.
Which is why I've requested
assistance from that man.
By that man...
you don't mean...?
The bearded gentleman?
[RUSTAL chuckles]
[IOK] I always feel weird
around that bearded man.
His personality is
a bit oppressive.
I agree, he possesses
an impressive mind and
an equally powerful body.
Merely looking
him in the eye
must be a daunting prospect
for one as feeble as you.
[IOK grunts]
[JULIETA] I should get going.
[IOK scoffs]
Monkey bitch!
[JULIETA]
I want him to watch me!
To see what I'm capable of now!
[JULIETA gasps]
[JULIETA] I still can't
wrap my brain around it.
There's no shortage
of able bodies
within the ranks
of Gjallarhorn,
and yet...
[JULIETA] ...he still
chose a nobody like you
to be his right-hand man.
Surely you must see
how alarming that is.
[VIDAR]
Alarming?
To put it simply,
Master Rustal is
showing favoritism.
[VIDAR chuckles]
[JULIETA gasps]
Did I just hear a
laugh from you?
[VIDAR] You did indeed, as the
people of this fleet once said
the very same thing about you.
[gasps]
You're right... they did.
I have no rank or supporters.
[JULIETA]
However, I can say this.
I was acknowledged by Master
Rustal for my exceptional
ability to pilot a
Mobile Suit.
[VIDAR]
I take it you trust Rustal?
[JULIETA]
Mm? Of course I do!
I'm proud of Master Rustal.
He's a respected
superior officer.
[VIDAR]
Hm... I see.
[JULIETA gasps]
[VIDAR]
Proud of him, you say?
[CHAD]
The ceremony will begin at ten.
VIPs will start
arriving at nine.
If you see anything
remotely suspicious,
report it to me immediately.
That clear?
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
Sir!
All right, that's it then,
go take your positions.
[TEKKADAN MEMBERS chatter]
Takaki.
[TAKAKI]
Huh?
[CHAD] I'm putting you in
charge of things around here
while I'm away. Got it?
Yes, sir!
[MINISTER A] This grand
occasion marks the formation
of the new Arbrau
Defense Force.
Until now, we've had no
means of defending ourselves
besides hiding under the
umbrella of Gjallarhorn's
military might. Given this fact,
I would say we've achieved
a tremendous feat...
Sounds like the
ceremony is underway.
[TAKAKI gasps]
Aston?
Huh? Yeah?
You know you've been
acting kinda weird lately.
I'm not exactly a brainiac,
so I can't really put my
thoughts into words.
[TAKAKI grunts]
I guess I was just a little
shocked when I saw Chad
all dressed up.
It made me wish
that everyone else
could see him, too.
[ASTON grunts]
So you're saying that
you're proud of him?
Yeah, I guess I am sorta proud.
Sounds to me like you
were feeling happy too.
[ASTON]
Mm.
[TAKAKI]
[MAKANAI] Tekkadan has been
doing a remarkable job
of fulfilling its military
advisor duties.
It's because of you all
that we're able to
have this ceremony.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome, sir.
[MAKANAI]
I will continue to count on you
as the man in charge of
this branch of Tekkadan.
Chad Chadan.
[gasps]
He knows my name...
[knocking]
[AIDE A]
Excuse me.
Mr. Makanai, they're just about
ready for your speech, sir.
Huh?
[MAKANAI]
Hm?
[AIDE A] How long have
those been there?
They weren't there
during our sweep.
[MAKANAI]
You mean these flowers?
[CHAD]
Mr. Makanai, wait!
--[beeping]
--[MAKANAI] Huh?
[CHAD grunts]
[ASTON]
Huh?
[MAN A]
An explosion?
[MAN B] It came from
inside the building!
[TAKAKI] Aston, would you
wait for a minute?!
Arbrau is on internal
security, remember?!
So don't worry.
Plus, Chad's also in there.
But we...
[TAKAKI] Our job right now
is to check the area
around the building
for anyone suspicious!
[MAN C]
How bad is the damage?
[MAN D]
Can't tell.
[STAFF A]
Was anyone hurt?
I've already told you
everything that I know!
[MAN E]
Apparently, Mr. Makanai is hurt!
[STAFF B gasps]
Seriously?!
What?
[ASTON]
Hey, where is Chad?
What? Chad who?
[ASTON] He's part of
Makanai's security team!
[MAN F]
Well...
I heard some security people
were injured as well.
[MAN G]
What happened?
[MAN H]
An explosion.
[WOMAN A]
Look! Over there!
[GALAN]
There's the starting signal.
Now it begins.
Smoke from a much bigger
blast will soon rise.
Before anything
else happens,
I think we should discuss
the matter of my payment.
[GALAN]
Not to worry.
I fully intend to honor
each and every one of
your proposed terms.
[RADICE]
Mm.
[GALAN] But doesn't this
nag at your conscience
in the slightest?
You're essentially taking a
bunch of kids you've lived with
and throwing them
into the chaos of war.
[RADICE]
Space rats, like them,
without the least
bit of education,
are no better than animals.
And due to my allergies,
I hate being around animals.
[GALAN laughs]
That's a good one!
You're a really funny guy,
you know that?
[GALAN]
Hm.
Luckily, I happen
to like funny guys.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A]
Investigations are currently
underway to determine if
this was the act of a group
or a lone perpetrator,
as well as possible
motives and goals.
[MCGILLIS]
Hm.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A]
There's been some speculation
going around that
it might be the act of
a terrorist group
that's opposed to
the formation of the
new defense force.
As of late, a reliance
upon Gjallarhorn has fallen.
And there's been a
global rush to establish
independent military forces.
If that's the underlying cause
of this, it's understandable.
Arbrau guarded the
ceremony venue,
along with a bit of assistance
from our friends, Tekkadan.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A] Come on,
it's been three days already!
What's going on with Mr. Chad?
[TAKAKI]
According to Mr. Radice,
he still hasn't
regained consciousness.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B] No way!
What does the Boss think?!
Mr. Radice is HQ's
go-between, so I'm not sure.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A] I am so
sick of hearing that guys name.
[TAKAKI gasps]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B] Let's just
go avenge Chad ourselves!
Nothing's stopping us!
No, you can't act on
your own like that!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B]
Why the hell not?
If Boss were here,
you know that's what
he'd order us to do!
That's exactly my point,
he hasn't given any orders yet!
So we can't run off and
act on our own authority!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER B groans]
[TEKKADAN MEMBER A]
This sucks...
[TAKAKI]
Tch...!
There's been no change
in his condition.
Mr. Makanai is
still unconscious.
Even so...
[RADICE] Arbrau doesn't have
any leads at this point,
so they're looking into
a lapse in security.
[TAKAKI gasps]
[RADICE]
It's possible they'll start
pointing the finger
at us before long.
--[TAKAKI] Umm...
--[RADICE] Hmm?
[TAKAKI]
I have a question,
and it's something I need
to ask the Boss directly.
[RADICE] As I've said,
Chad put me in charge
of all communications
with HQ in his absence,
which means any messages
are to be sent through me.
Do you honestly think
that story is gonna fly
with the rest of
the members?!
Unless I'm mistaken, it's your
job to make sure that it does.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have paperwork to finish.
[TAKAKI]
Understood.
[TAKAKI] You heard Chad,
just like I did.
I'm in command while he's gone.
That's why I have to
keep a level head
and not act selfishly.
Even if it doesn't sit
well with the guys.
I can't endanger everyone's
lives over my personal opinions.
I'm with the others on this.
Somebody's gonna
have to pay for Chad.
Aston...
But, what I want even
more is to be your ally.
[TAKAKI gasps]
Thank you, Aston.
[EUGENE] Damn it! We're totally
out of the loop, here!
What're we hearing
from the Earth Branch?
All they're doing is
repeating the fact
that Chad and Mr. Makanai
have been injured.
"It's all under control,
let us handle it," they say.
Besides that,
we don't know jack!
Well isn't it possible
to talk to Takaki?
[EUGENE] They said he doesn't
have time to stop and talk
because he's
filling in for Chad.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm.
My gut's sayin'
something's wrong.
Oh yeah?
[ORGA] Eugene, can you
take off right away?
I guess, but where am I going?
[ORGA] Earth. We're gonna
bump up the Shiden delivery.
Huh?
[ORGA] I want you on
that ship... Both of you.
[AKIHIRO]
Hm.
[TEKKADAN MEMBER C]
Looks like there's trouble.
[TAKAKI]
Hm?
Yeah? What's going on?
I just overheard some of
the guys from the Arbrau
Defense Force talking
about something major!
They said if this keeps up,
it could lead to a war!
[ASTON gasps]
A war?!
[TAKAKI]
Mr. Radice!
Is it true that the SAU
was involved with
the bombing incident?!
And that the economic
blocs are discussing
going to war with each other?!
Well, I'm not going to deny
that it is a possibility.
Come back! What's the boss
saying about all of this?!
[RADICE] I spoke with
him about it earlier.
[TAKAKI] And...?
What did he--?
[RADICE] If those of us on
Earth are in the dark,
what makes you think
the people on Mars
would know any more?
Well, I...
[RADICE] It's certainly true
that this situation is volatile,
but understand.
If war really is right
around the corner,
then time will be
of the essence.
We have to think and
act for ourselves.
Do you even realize
how far away Mars is?
I know, but...
[TAKAKI gasps]
Now that Chad is
no longer with us,
you're the only one
who can be entrusted
to make those judgment
calls, Takaki Uno.
[TAKAKI gasps]
[RADICE]
The Earth Branch of Tekkadan.
Its fate now rests
upon your shoulders.
As does the fate of
your lives here on Earth.
[TAKAKI gasps]
[TAKAKI grunts]
[YUKINOJO] All right.
Do we have everything loaded?
[MIKAZUKI]
There's also--
[MIKAZUKI gasps]
[MIKAZUKI]
Uh, Kudelia?
I'm going to be
traveling with you.
Oh, yeah, we heard
about that.
You must be worried
sick about Mr. Makanai.
[AKIHIRO] Let's hurry. I have
a bad feeling about this.
[EUGENE]
Yeah.
[ASTON] Fighting a war
without any help from HQ?
[TAKAKI]
Yeah. Mr. Radice is right.
We're gonna have to
handle this ourselves.
And you think that guy is
worth putting your trust in?
[TAKAKI] Tekkadan is
a family, right?
Like it or not, Mr. Radice
is a part of that now.
But if we can't trust
our own family,
who can we trust?
[FUKA whimpers]
[ASTON, TAKAKI gasp]
I want things to work out.
I wanna stay on
Earth for Fuka too.
Okay, then I'll do anything if
it means making you two happy.
You'd do anything?
[ASTON]
Well...
I could kill for you...
or die, if it came down to--
Don't say that!
Takaki?
Please, don't talk about
killing and dying
as if it were just
an afterthought!
[ASTON]
I didn't...
[FUKA whimpers]
Takaki?
[ASTON grunts]
[TAKAKI] Sorry. All of this
must finally be getting to me.
[TAKAKI] At the time,
I didn't fully understand
what was happening around me.
[MCGILLIS]
It appears the SAU has filed
an official mediation
request with Gjallarhorn.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A] Do you really
think they intend to go to war?
[MCGILLIS] Unfortunately, with
matters as bad as they are,
war might be unavoidable.
[MCGILLIS' MAN A] Will you
accept the request, then?
It's an official request,
so what choice do we have?
[MCGILLIS' MAN A] But, if the
mediation process drags on...
Yes, I'm aware. And there
are groups out there.
Those that would take advantage
of it and try to sabotage us.
[TAKAKI] At the time, I didn't
realize some unknown party
was pulling the strings
and forcing us into
an unthinkable situation.
[EUGENE]
A war with the SAU?!
It's not happening yet,
but it is a possibility.
What I do know for sure is
that the situation is critical.
It can't be...
You're kidding me!
And even flying at
our fastest speed,
reaching Earth is gonna
take us at least--
[ORGA]
I know...
It'll take a minimum
of three weeks.
[AKIHIRO growls]
[TAKAKI] And so...
try as we might...
[knocking]
[TAKAKI]
Excuse me.
[gasps]
[RADICE] We've been
waiting for you, Takaki.
This man will be the commander
of the Arbrau Defense Force
for the duration of this crisis.
[GALAN]
Galan Mossa.
Good to be working
with you, young man.
[TAKAKI] ...there was no
escaping, from the corner
we had been forced into.
♪
[GALAN]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"Silent War."
There's a theory which suggests,
when offered food,
most people will decline.