[whistling]
[gasps]
[HUSH]
What's that?
[HUSH grunts]
[HUSH gasps]
What the hell?
[DANE]
It's The Barbatos.
[HUSH]
Huh?
That's the Barbatos?
[DANE] The shape's
a little bit different,
but there's no doubt about it.
[DANE]
It's Mr. Mikazuki...
He's come back.
[MIKAZUKI exhales]
[HUSH]
Mikazuki? That useless kid?
[DANE] Oh I guess The Barbatos
must've already been out for
repairs when you joined up.
[HUSH] Quit acting like you're
better than me because you've
been here a month longer.
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[DANE]
"The Devil of Tekkadan."
That's the nickname his
enemies gave him because
he's always fighting
on the front lines.
His Alaya-Vinyana connects
him to the Barbatos.
He's very special.
So that's it...
--[computer beeps]
--[MIKAZUKI] Hm?
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT B grunts]
What the hell is this guy?!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT C] He took
out three mobile suits at once!
What do we do?
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT B]
You're asking me?!
Damn, he's a monster...
[SHINO] Pay attention!
Your opponent's over here!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT A]
Damn! That thing's fast!
[SHINO grunts]
[SHINO]
Of course it is!
This baby inherited my old
Ryusei-Go's battle data!
And it also got the
Alaya-Vijnana System!
[DAWN HORIZON PILOT A grunts]
Let's get out of here!
Oh no you don't!
[DERMA]
Yeah!
[MIKAZUKI]
Wait, Hold on.
[DANTE gasps]
What? Why?
[MIKAZUKI] For some reason, my
Barbatos has stopped working.
[DANTE]
Huh?
[DERMA] What'dja think
was gonna happen,
dropping in at that speed?!
[DANTE] Man, we just got
the damn thing fixed up!
They report all enemy forces
have left our detection range.
What now?
Let's regroup. Our boys need
time to get back on their feet.
Damn it, the Dawn
Horizon Corps, huh?
[MERRIBIT] We've caught
the eye of a nasty bunch.
[HUSH]
Whoa... the Barbatos...
[SHINO] Dammit, Mikazuki,
how are we supposed to up clean
this mess with you still
in your gundam?!
♪
[ALLIUM]
How pathetic!
You let children mop
the floor with you!
It's a fiasco that will only
serve to further embolden
that little girl! What do you
intend to do about this?
We have no obligation to
reveal our plans to you.
What?
[SANDOVAL] This matter
with Tekkadan no longer
has anything to do with you.
To restore the honor and pride
of the Dawn Horizon Corps,
we won't rest until
we eliminate them.
[ALLIUM gasps]
[ALLIUM] I'm glad you're
determined to see this through.
Having said that, you're up
against a group that's backed
by Teiwaz and Arbrau's Makanai.
For what I'm paying you,
I would think you'd be a little
more forthcoming in regards
to sharing the information
you've gathered--
Watch your mouth, activist!
Just who do you think
you're talking to?
But I--
[SANDOVAL] I don't care if we're
facing Tekkadan or anyone else,
for that matter. The job of
a pirate doesn't change
no matter who the opponent.
We kill, we pillage, we plunder!
[NOBLISS'S MAN A]
Excuse me, Mr. Nobliss.
[NOBLISS]
Hm?
[NOBLISS'S MAN A] You have
a call from Allium Gyojan
of Terra Liberionis.
He says it's urgent.
Again? At first, I thought I
could use him as I did Kudelia.
However, that man's
of no use to me now.
[NOBLISS'S MAN A]
Then...
[NOBLISS] Ignore him. Oh, and
bring me a refill, would you?
[NOBLISS'S MAN A]
Yes, sir.
[ORGA] You'll have to
take refuge at Sakura Farm
for the time being.
No way the Dawn Horizon Corps'
gonna turn the other cheek.
So lay low...
'til things settle down.
Got it.
[EUGENE] So while she's doing
that, what're we gonna do?
Go at it with the
Dawn Horizon Corps?
You think that's possible?
Not likely. The Dawn Horizon
Corps is a huge outfit
with ten ships
always at the ready.
And a ton of Mobile Suits too.
[ORGA] But that doesn't
change the fact that Tekkadan
is now in their crosshairs.
[EUGENE gasps]
You're right.
Like it or not, we'll have
to face them at some point.
If we don't make the impossible
happen, Tekkadan is finished.
[gasps]
[SHINO] If you see any problems,
report them right away!
The tiniest oversight
could cost you your life!
We'll eat once we're done,
so hustle!
Put your backs into it!
[ZACH] As if I
could eat right now...
Huh?
[ZACH] I was hell-bent
on seeing combat
even if it cost me my life.
But... I didn't think
we'd really die.
[SHINO sighs]
[AKIHIRO] If you want to quit,
there's the door.
[ZACH]
Huh?
Akihiro.
In Tekkadan, staying or
quitting is up to you.
Living or dying?
That's up to you, too.
[SHINO chuckles]
[AKIHIRO] Got it? That goes
for all of you as well!
It's your choice!
[DANTE] Come on,
what's it gonna hurt?
I just wanna use this
with a bit of spray paint.
Huh? What's it for?
[DANTE] Nothing weird, It's for
a kill tally on my Shiden!
[LAFTER]
Dante!
You didn't take him down
by yourself, ya know!
[DANTE]
I, uh...
You do realize it's all
on the recorder, right?
[ECO] I figured you'd try
something stupid, but come on...
Hey, I was just--
[RIDE]
They're right, Dante!
You can't let this
stuff go to your head!
[DANTE]
It doesn't! Honest!
Besides that, until those extra
Shidens Mr. Mikazuki brought
with Barbatos arrive here,
don't get the idea that that
one's your personal unit!
[DANTE] Seriously? But they're
already in orbit along with
Akihiro's Gusion, aren't they?
And they have the ones
we're sending to Earth!
[RIDE] Yeah. If they'd
gotten here a day earlier,
we Second Unit members
could've seen some action, too.
[LAFTER]
If you want some action,
what do you say I run you
ragged with a bit of training?
[RIDE]
What?!
[AZEE]
You're also coming along, Dante.
[DANTE] Wait, I've already seen
action on the front lines!
[AZEE]
Shut up.
[ECO] Yeah, Less talking
and more working!
[YUKINOJO groans] We just got
our new Barbatos Lupus
up and running, and it's
already in this sorry state.
Damn it...
I wish you'd show a little
restraint with your gear.
So how'd the Lupus
do out there?
Lupus?
[YUKINOJO] You know good
and well that's the new name
the Teiwaz chief
mechanic gave it.
The Barbatos is the Barbatos.
The repairs were good.
--You never change.
--[footsteps]
[gasps]
Hello, everyone. How are you?
[YUKINOJO]
Hey.
[KUDELIA] Hi Mikazuki.
It's been a while.
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm. Good to see you.
[YUKINOJO] Why don't you go
and get some air, Mikazuki?
You two must have
some catching up to do.
[MIKAZUKI]
We do?
[YUKINOJO]
Just go, already.
[KUDELIA]
Have you been well?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[KUDELIA] I've stopped by
to visit a few times now,
but you've always been away.
[MIKAZUKI]
Oh... yeah.
[KUDELIA] Orga tells me
whenever there's fighting,
you and the Barbatos are
always on the front lines,
leading the charge into battle.
[MIKAZUKI] Well... unlike all
the other guys...
...fighting is the only
thing I'm good for.
[KUDELIA gasps]
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia.
Good, you're here!
Perfect timing!
[KUDELIA]
Miss Atra!
[ATRA] There's, uh, something
that I'd like to give you.
[ATRA]
Here.
This is for me?
[ATRA] Yep! Now we
have a matching set!
This way, no matter where
we are in the world,
we'll stay connected.
[gasps]
[MIKAZUKI] Lately, mine has
started to smell a little.
[ATRA]
Really?
Honestly, it smells like you.
Sorta like blood.
[ATRA] But if it bothers you,
I'll wash it. I will!
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm.
[ATRA]
Miss Kudelia.
[KUDELIA]
Huh?
Shall we go?
[KUDELIA chuckles]
[EUGENE]
This had better be important.
I have work to do.
[NEW MEMBER A]
Sorry to bother you,
but there's this
strange old dude...
Old dude?
[TODO]
Hello there!
Hey there, Deputy Boss Eugene.
[EUGENE]
Great... It's you.
[TODO]
so, are these new recruits?
You need to make sure they
know the names and faces of
your business associates.
This kind a thing won't do.
[NEW MEMBER B]
Is he a VIP?
You could say that.
Very Irritating Person.
[TODO laughs]
That's the witty Deputy Boss
we all know and love!
Always with the witty retorts!
I knew taking you under
my wing was a good idea.
I wanna kill you.
[TODO]
Oh, lighten up.
This is what happens when
you don't have a proper diet.
Speaking of which,
want some candy, little boy?
Seriously?
Don't fall for that crap.
[TODO]
Now, now...
I come with news that'll put
a smile even on your face.
Directly from my boss.
Huh?
[ORGA] It's not that I don't
appreciate the job offer,
but our hands are pretty
full for the time being.
Mister...?
[MCGILLIS]
Montag. Call me Montag.
I'd rather you used that
name when referring to me.
Though it's an open secret that
you've been lending me a hand.
Fine... what's the job?
[MCGILLIS] To eliminate
the Dawn Horizon Corps.
[gasps]
Heh. That your way of saying
you know what's going on?
Why the interest
in pirate hunting?
[MCGILLIS] The Dawn Horizon
Corps is an enormous,
yet elusive,
pirate gang whose reach,
extends all the way
to the Earth Sphere.
Tracking them has proven to be
a difficult task, even for us.
[ORGA sighs]
[MCGILLIS]
I'll help however I can.
My assistant, Isurugi, is
already heading over to aid you.
He's familiar with the
inner workings of the
Dawn Horizon Corps
and very skilled.
So you're using us as bait, huh?
[MCGILLIS]
Such a lack of trust.
I never trusted
you to begin with.
[ORGA] However... I'll take
you up on your offer.
Oh? Why would you accept it,
if you don't trust me?
Because accepting your
offer means taking the
shortest route
possible to our goal.
[MCMURDO] You want to fight
the Dawn Horizon Corps?
[ORGA]
Yeah. They raid shipping lanes,
so I believe they're also
a nuisance to Teiwaz.
[MCMURDO]
That's true... But still...
[ORGA] And we can promote
Teiwaz's latest frame
by showing off the
power of our Shidens.
[JASLEY]
Hmph.
[MCMURDO]
I see your point.
Very well, do as you wish.
[ORGA] Thanks. You're not
gonna regret this.
[JASLEY]
Old man...
...why do you always let that
guy do whatever he wants?
There's no point putting
on the "nice grandpa"
act with those kids.
What are you saying exactly?
Will you hunt down the
Dawn Horizon Corps?
Are you kidding?
I'm not that crazy.
Let the newbies take care
of those idiot pirates on
their own, it's not like they
can't handle it by themselves--
Then why are you complaining?
[JASLEY gasps]
[MCMURDO]
Hm.
They're shaping up to
be an interesting bunch,
aren't they, Naze?
Those kids are quite something.
[RADICE]
This isn't what we agreed on.
I thought that the plan was
for them to send Shidens
to the Earth Branch no later
than the end of the month.
Surely they know
we can't hold out
with just the Landman
Rodis we have.
[CHAD]
Of course they do.
But HQ is taking on the
Dawn Horizon Corps,
so they need the firepower.
I would think you'd be a little
more understanding about it.
[RADICE]
Not my problem, I'm afraid.
[he Earth Branch will have no
involvement in that conflict,
so it's none--
If I'm being frank, they're the
ones who need reinforcements.
But the boss doesn't ask
because he's worried
about our situation.
[RADICE grunts]
[CHAD] So keep that
in mind before you--
Orga's worried. Is he?
[CHAD gasps]
[RADICE] The equipment
shortages and our relations
with Arbrau's
regular soldiers.
That's what we're worried about.
And yet... HQ doesn't
help us, at all.
They just keep
making things worse.
And at this rate...
[CHAD]
Mr. Radice.
[RADICE gasps]
[CHAD] Both the Earth Branch
and HQ are part of Tekkadan.
We all trust Orga.
And we know our boss'll
lead us down the right path.
That's how Tekkadan works.
[RADICE grunts]
What nonsense.
[CHAD sighs]
[SOLDIER A]
What did you just say?!
Wanna run that by
me again, you little--
As long as you're here,
you're gonna do things
the Tekkadan way.
[SOLDIER C]
Calm down, already!
[TAKAKI]
What's going on?
[SOLDIER A] Oh, I'll tell
you what's going on!
This little know-it-all
punk here doesn't know
who he's talking to!
Since when do you call the
guy who's teaching you
the ropes a "know-it-all?"
Aston come on!
Sorry about this.
I promise talk with him.
You apologize too.
[ASTON]
Hmph.
[TAKAKI]
Aston!
Here, eat up.
This?
Just dig in, okay?
[ASTON grunts]
I was expectin' to get
chewed out or somethin'...
[TAKAKI] You know,
you weren't wrong back there.
[ASTON grunts]
But I don't think
those regular soldiers
were in the wrong, either.
They have their pride,
just like you.
[TAKAKI]
That's how it is.
[FUKA]
So...?
[ASTON]
Hm?
How's it taste?
Good.
Do you really mean it?
[ASTON grunts] Growing up, there
was nothing to eat but garbage,
so everything tastes good,
compared to that.
Well, I'm glad it's
better than garbage...
[ASTON]
No! That's not what I meant!
Don't worry about it,
you're fine.
Fuka, is there tea?
Yep.
[ASTON]
Don't you ever get lonely?
[TAKAKI]
Huh?
Being away from Mars.
[TAKAKI] Not really. My life
here is actually pretty great.
I get to live with Fuka and I
can even send her to school.
Plus, I've got
friends here, too.
[ASTON gasps]
Sorry... was that too
presumptuous of me?
Oh... no...
Can you set out
some cups, Takaki?
[TAKAKI]
Sure.
Are the red ones okay?
[FUKA]
No, the good ones for guests.
[YUKINOJO] Mm! Today's soup
sure is delicious.
[ATRA chuckles] It was
prepared with real chicken
for our hard-working
maintenance crew!
[YAMAGI]
Meat from a living creature?
I'll pass, thanks.
yum.
[ATRA] Come on! You're starting
to sound exactly like Mikazuki.
[YAMAGI]
I'm not that bad, am I?
Got a sec?
Oh... Hush, right? Did you
not get enough food to eat?
What's wrong?
Nothing, I...
Would it be all right if
I piloted a mobile suit?
Huh? Are you serious?
[HUSH]
I've read all the manuals.
[DANE]
Yeah.
You're kidding, right?
It takes more than that
to pilot a mobile suit.
Which is why I... I wanna
get the Alaya-Vijnana.
[ATRA gasps]
[YUKINOJO] Hush, was it?
How old are you anyway?
Seventeen, sir...
Well, if that's the case,
then you're too old to get
the Alaya-Vijnana surgery.
I'm sorry, kid.
Too old?
You heard me. At your age,
it'd be impossible for the
nano-machines to take root.
You could at least try
it on me, couldn't you?
I don't care if it
doesn't work out.
Don't say that!
[gasps]
[ATRA]
It's not to be taken lightly!
The Alaya-Vijnana surgery...
is a really dangerous one!
And if it doesn't work,
you could die!
I understand that.
[ATRA gasps]
You do not!
There's a reason the boss
banned the surgery.
He's looking out for you guys!
What do you know
about it, anyway?
Get out of my--
[HUSH gasps]
[YAMAGI]
Mikazuki.
Hold on, Mikazuki,
it's not what you think--
What are you doing?
Why is he--
[HUSH groans]
[MIKAZUKI] What were
you doing to her? Talk.
[HUSH groans]
Let go!
[YUKINOJO]
Hey.
[ATRA gasps]
Dial it down before you
break the poor kid's arm.
Yeah, we were just having
a conversation, really!
So, wait...
...he wasn't picking on you?
[ATRA] Hey You know
I don't get bullied!
Why on you...?
[MIKAZUKI]
Huh?
[HUSH grunts] Why did it
work on you but not him?
[MIKAZUKI]
"Him"?
[HUSH grunts]
[HUSH] Just forget it.
Sorry I bothered you.
[MIKAZUKI]
Sorry, I guess.
[HUSH]
It's fine.
What was that about?
[ATRA]
Hmm. He's pretty strange.
[DANE] So what,
you're not afraid to die?
[HUSH]
Hm?
Everyone's afraid of dying.
That's true.
[HUSH]
But...
[DANE]
Hm?
Something else scares
me even more...
[DANE grunts]
[HUSH]
I come from the slums.
All of the kids that lost
their parents stuck together
to survive.
[BOY A giggles]
[BOY B]
We sure got a major haul!
[BOY A]
Major haul!
[HUSH]
Hey guys, don't run so fast!
Huh?
Builth...
[HUSH] Builth was
like our big brother.
He always said he wanted
to make our lives easier.
So he left the slums
to become a soldier.
[HUSH]
But it didn't work out,
and Builth came back
paralyzed from the waist down.
[HUSH]
Builth!
You must be starving!
It's the usual scraps,
but the cafeteria owner
threw in some extra!
[BUILTH grunts]
[HUSH gasps]
[BUILTH]
Apparently,
my surgery for the
Alaya-Vijnana didn't take.
They called me
"Industrial waste."
[HUSH]
Huh?
[BUILTH] And they said
I was worthless now.
[HUSH gasps]
What're you talking about?
That wound'll heal
up in no time!
I mean, come on, you're the
toughest guy I know,
and I'm not just sayin' that.
[BUILTH]
You're wrong...
If I were tough,
this wouldn't have happened.
[HUSH]
Builth...
[BUILTH] There were tons of
guys who were tougher than me.
Like this kid who was
in the bed next to mine.
He was way smaller than I was,
but he had the same
surgery three times,
and was as good as new.
Unlike me.
Don't think like that!
[BUILTH]
I didn't make the cut,
[HUSH]
Come on, don't!
[BUILTH]
I'm sorry.
I wanted to make life
easier for you guys.
[BUILTH]
But instead...
...I'm just a burden.
Nothing but industrial waste.
Forgive me... I'm so sorry.
[HUSH] We all thought
the same thing, back then.
That if we stuck with Builth,
everything would work out.
But he... That's why...
I have no choice but to
become the next Builth.
I'm gonna pilot a Mobile Suit,
mark my words.
And I'll make Mikazuki
Augus eat my dust!
I'll show them that
if they stick with me,
we can make this hellhole
of world worth living in.
[HUSH]
Huh? H-Hey...
[DANE]
Good luck on that.
Wasn't expecting that.
[IOK] Who could've imagined that
we'd get stuck battling it out
with pirates on Mars?
And McGillis Fareed.
I wonder what the heck
is going through his mind.
There's no need to worry.
I am here so that I may
protect you, Master Iok.
[IOK]
Hm?
Truth is, I am repaying
Master Rustal for taking me in.
I feel no particular sense
of devotion toward you,
but for Master Rustal's sake,
I shall keep you safe.
[IOK gasps]
Honestly, I find it
very unlikely McGillis
could ever prove to be a
threat to Master Rustal.
However, that other
man does concern me.
Oh... that one.
Trust him or not,
he has been useful.
Because of him, we now
know what McGillis is up to.
But, even so...
...there's something about
him that doesn't feel right.
[RUSTAL]
How are you doing?
I've sent Iok and Julieta...
...to the battle sector.
Seems like McGillis
sent Isurugi.
Exactly as you
predicted he would.
[ORGA]
Yo. There you are.
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga? What's up?
[ORGA]
Nothin'.
But it looks like things
are about to get hectic.
[ORGA]
I'll be counting on you, Mika.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm.
♪
[IOK]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam :
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"Battle Before Dawn."
Iok Kujan,
Kujan family patriarch!
Reginlaze, launch!
Let Iok Kujan's valiant
figure burn into your mind!