[GAELIO] I, Gaelio Bauduin,
declare here and now.
I will kill...
...the traitor of Gjallarhorn.
McGillis!
[MCGILLIS] Rustal Elion put
you up to this, no doubt.
Very well. Challenge accepted.
[RUSTAL]
This is Rustal Elion,
commander of the
Arianrhod Fleet.
Our Fleet has been
keeping Gaelio Bauduin
under our protection
for quite some time.
He informed us about
McGillis Fareed's offenses
and exposed him for
the criminal he is.
In one of these heinous acts,
Fareed plotted to gain control
of the Outer Earth Orbit
Regulatory Joint Fleet.
And in doing so, he caused the
death of Commander Carta Issue.
What?!
[RUSTAL]
He also took over his family
from his adoptive father,
Iznario Fareed,
McGillis also conspired
to take possession
of the Bauduin family
by killing Gaelio Bauduin
and making Almiria
Bauduin his wife.
[gasps]
It's okay, Miss Almiria.
[RUSTAL] If that wasn't enough,
his current actions
have brought dishonor
upon Gundam Bael,
which is the very
symbol of Gjallarhorn.
In it sleeps the soul of
our founder, Agnika Kaieru.
McGillis Fareed tainted
it with his myopic
and treasonous ambitions.
[ORGA]
This isn't good.
Are things still going
according to plan?
Uh--
Yes, they are, without a doubt.
The old men of the Seven
Stars will have no choice...
[RUSTAL] Even if we must
break Gjallarhorn's laws,
we will not rest until the
traitor, McGillis Fareed,
is brought to justice!
Huh. You sure about that?
There's no need to worry!
Gjallarhorn has rules that
you would only understand
if you were an actual member.
We'll discuss everything
in more detail
once we've met up
with the General.
Now, if you'll
excuse me, comrades.
Who's he callin' his comrades?
Hey, Boss, what did he mean
by rules only
Gjallarhorn understands?
Our hands are tied.
That is, till Mika comes back.
We'll have to wait.
[MCGILLIS]
Sorry to keep you.
Once the shuttle arrives,
why don't you head back, first?
We'll be right behind you.
Hey, you had the
surgery, didn't you?
I thought it didn't
work for adults.
Tell me. The black Graze
you fought at Edmonton.
Exactly how well do you
remember that fight?
Well, I wouldn't say
that I remember it,
but it popped into
my head, earlier.
[MCGILLIS]
A Gjallarhorn soldier
was connected to
that Mobile Suit.
It was all part of a
series of experiments.
Experiments that would
lead up to the day
I'd be able to pilot Bael.
So that... the Alaya-Vijnana
surgery could be performed
on an adult, like myself.
The Alaya-Vijnana
System was originally
developed by what
is now Gjallarhorn.
They came to view body
modifications as taboo
and prohibited them
within Gjallarhorn,
yet they failed to recognize
one important fact.
Something they had
completely forgotten.
The legendary Mobile Suit
required the Alaya-Vinjana.
Now, whether they
know it or not,
their selective amnesia
and self-preservation
is what will make my ascent
as Gjallarhorn's leader
that much easier.
[ISURUGI]
General, we should be going.
[MCGILLIS]
Right.
We'll meet again,
Mikazuki Augus.
[SOLDIER 44A] So General Fareed
was really accepted by Bael?
[SOLDIER 44B]
I thought it was just legend.
[SOLDIER 44A]
Apparently, only those chosen
by Agnika Kaieru's
soul can pilot it.
[SOLDIER 44B] Are you saying
Lord Fareed was selected?
Whether you choose
to believe it or not,
Agnika's soul selected me.
You must accept that I'm now the
official leader of Gjallarhorn.
Wait, but that's...
That's nothing but a
self-indulgent fairytale!
[MCGILLIS]
And yet...
Many in Gjallarhorn have
tried to activate Bael,
but throughout its long history,
not one has succeeded
in accomplishing this task.
You can't deny that fact.
Bael has permitted
me alone to sit
atop its prestigious throne.
This, too, is an
indisputable fact.
You all have no choice
but to obey me from now on.
Disobeying me means
disobeying Agnika Kaieru,
or even worse denying the very
existence of Gjallarhorn itself.
B-But Lord Elion's
broadcast earlier presents
a major problem that
cannot be ignored.
[GALLUS]
Exactly!
Was Lord Elion speaking
the truth, McGillis?!
Did you try to kill Gaelio?!
My dear father.
[growls]
You have nothing to fear.
Now that I have been
chosen to pilot Bael,
all these trivial accusations
are nothing more
than a nuisance.
Trivial accusations?!
How dare you say that
after trying to kill my son!
Have you forgotten
that I'm also your son?
[gasps]
[MCGILLIS] Everything I've
done has been to protect
the reputation of
the Bauduin family
and the name of Gjallarhorn.
[GALLUS]
You're not making any sense!
Unfortunately, there's no need
for you to understand this,
or for us to speak
to each other at all.
My words are now the
words of Agnika Kaieru.
As members of Gjallarhorn,
you have but one duty
at this point.
Obey me without question.
[BAKLAZAN, FAROOQ gasp]
So let's begin.
All ground forces under
your control are now mine.
Relinquish them immediately.
[gasps]
[MCGILLIS] Gjallarhorn
will be united as one.
And our first mission will
be removing the traitor,
Rustal Elion, who defies Bael.
[RUSTAL]
Allow me to congratulate you
on your safe return,
Gaelio Bauduin.
Your face looks more
determined than before.
It took a while
to decide. I'm sorry.
Bael is in his hands
now because of me.
Every large organization
has hidden, pus-filled wounds.
It comes with the system itself.
This uprising coming from
the young officers
is exactly that.
From time to time,
the pus must be drawn out.
This is going to be
a massive battle.
If we are to pass Gjallarhorn
on to future generations,
then it's one we must fight.
You'll help me, I trust?
[GAELIO]
Of course.
[GAELIO] Chief, please see
to my machine's conversion.
Will do!
All hands, remove
Vidar's camouflage.
And don't forget the
dummy reactors! Hurry!
Pardon the interruption, sir,
but Master Iok has arrived.
I am truly sorry, sir.
[RUSTAL] You certainly are
quite the foolish family head.
[IOK] You speak nothing but
the truth, Master Rustal.
Many of your subordinates died
because of your
careless judgement.
But, in spite of that,
your men still look up
to you with reverence.
And do you know why?
Because of history.
[IOK]
History?
Your father,
the late Lord Kujan,
was an incredible man.
The subordinates who
admired him in the old days
hope to catch a
glimmer of him in you.
They've been with you
since your youth.
Even if you were to
continue going about things
the wrong way,
they've seen how you love
your people and act
with blatant honesty.
McGillis boasted that he'd
reform the obsolete ways
of the organization,
but despite his claims,
he still relies on an
old Gjallarhorn legend.
Legend and history
are alike, but different.
[gasps]
It's true that Gjallarhorn
began its existence
with Agnika Kaieru.
But the history of
our great organization
was built without
the help of Agnika.
Harmony with those around us...
Unity...
All this is possible because
we're an organization.
Master Rustal...
If he valued this,
he could've proven it
by respecting history
and denying Agnika.
[ALMIRIA gasps]
[MCGILLIS]
There you are,
my dear Almiria.
What are you doing with that?
[ALMIRIA]
My brother was alive all along.
Listen, Almiria--
[ALMIRIA]
He was alive!
And apparently you
were the one who tried
to have him killed
in the first place.
So that's why...!
I'm going to...
I'm going to kill you, Macky.
I understand.
Go ahead. Kill me if you must.
[gasps]
I welcome it...
...if it's at the hands
of one who's life
is more precious than my own.
[ALMIRIA]
Liar!
When did I lie? I love you.
[ALMIRIA]
That's a lie! It's all a lie...
You've been tricking me
this entire time!
Your kind eyes and
words were nothing
but a pack of lies!
[MCGILLIS]
Almiria.
[ALMIRIA]
I can't...
I can't. I don't understand.
Why, Macky? Tell me.
I love you with
all of my heart.
Even after...
...everything bad
that you've done!
And that's why, I...
I... I...!
I'll be the one to die!
[slice]
[ALMIRIA]
Macky...
My dear Almiria...
...even if your precious
heart yearns for death,
I cannot let you
have what you want
under any circumstances.
[ALMIRIA gasps]
Don't you recall?
I made you a promise long ago.
I promised that I'd
make you happy.
I gave you my word.
[ALMIRIA]
How can you say that?
I can never be happy
again. Not after this.
Yes, I know.
You can hate me now,
if that's your wish.
But in spite of that,
if you stay alive for me,
one day in the distant
future, I'll make sure
that you look back at this time,
and regardless of everything
that has happened,
you will be happy in the end.
[ALMIRIA gasps]
[ISURUGI]
Excuse me, General.
[gasps]
Lord Baklazan wishes
to see you, immediately.
Very well. I'll be right there.
[ALMIRIA]
This doesn't make any sense.
Nothing Macky says
makes any sense.
And I'm crazy...
...for still loving him.
[ATRA]
Oh, Hush!
They're saying Mikazuki's back!
What's wrong, guys?
Well, it seems as though
things aren't going
the way they expected.
Huh?
What kinda game are you playing?
I heard your plan was a success.
So explain yourself.
Why do we have to
fight the Arianrhod?
While it is true we
Gjallarhorn members
cannot defy Bael.
It's also true that
we cannot obey you
and your orders, either.
[gasps]
[FAROOQ]
Given the unique situation,
we will remain neutral
throughout the duration
of this affair.
So you're intent
on defying orders
from the one who pilot's Bael?
You realize this means
you're disobeying
the rules of Gjallarhorn.
Those rules are from
a time gone by
where we needed
a powerful individual
to defeat the Mobile Armors.
That's right!
We won't let you use others
like pawns in some twis--!
In any event, the Seven
Stars have no intention
of rebelling against Bael.
Which is precisely the
reason we don't intend
on helping the
Arianrhod Fleet, either.
[MCGILLIS] Failing to
secure their cooperation
came as a surprise. But...
...this is why we must
show our power.
They need to know
just how strong we are,
and how strong Bael is.
[EUGENE]
How're we gonna do that?
Since we can't count on the
forces of the other lords,
we'll have to confront
the Arianrhod Fleet
with what we currently
have at our disposal.
We don't have enough.
I've arranged for
equipment to be sent over
from my fleet, and I'll
join you as soon as I can.
Hold on...
Listen to my words
carefully, Orga,
as this will be the last
battle for us, and for you.
[growls]
Orga?
[ORGA]
We've got nowhere to go back to.
[BOTH gasp]
[ORGA] If the Arianrhod
Fleet is our enemy,
we'll just crush
them and move on.
All hands, prepare for battle!
[YUKINOJO] All right, boys,
let's take Barbatos
to the main deck!
[YAMAGI] Containers Seven
and Eight are ammunition.
[DANE]
What about this?
[YAMAGI]
That's... uh...
...one of the units
I ordered from Teiwaz.
[DANE] It was in the
equipment storage area.
And if I'm not mistaken,
it's one of our weapons, right?
[YAMAGI]
Uh... Yeah, you're right.
Send it over to
Ryusei-Go just in case.
We're gonna have another
battle on our hands, huh?
[gasps]
That's right.
Mr. Dexter,
I see that you've decided
to stay on with Tekkadan, too.
Yes, well, it's not like
I have anywhere else
to work at the moment.
And besides...
I wasn't able to do anything
to help those kids
when they were being
abused by the adults
during the days of the CGS.
Back then, I thought there
was nothing I could do,
so I just blamed
it on the times.
But despite their
horrid treatment,
they kept fighting with
all their strength.
I felt like such a coward.
So I decided to stay here,
hoping to be of use,
if even in a small way.
That's very noble of you.
But I still wonder if there's
anything I can do to help them.
Those kids are the ones
who're doing the fighting.
As for me, the only thing I
can do is sit here and watch.
I feel like there's something
we should be doing for them.
There has to be
at least one thing
we can offer them as adults.
[DEXTER]
Hmm?
But, whenever I go to them,
they're so earnest
and intense...
It feels like whatever
I was going to say
would be a lie.
Oh, Ms. Merribit.
So, at the very least,
I wanna stand by their side.
I believe he stays
with Tekkadan
because he feels
the same as I do.
[YUKINOJO]
Hey! Watch it over there.
[MEMBER 44A]
Yes, sir!
And be sure to check
all the bolts!
We've gotta move quickly,
but thoroughly!
[ZACK] What do you
think about all this?!
They're crazy, right?
Like, totally insane!
I mean, the enemy
has twice as many
freakin' ships as we do!
You know as well as me,
we're not gonna win this thing!
So why's everybody so gung-ho?!
We don't have another
alternative, so the only choice
is to work harder.
That's what I'm sayin'!
Thinking we can win this
by playin' it by ear
is the stupidest
thing I've ever--
[BOTH gasp]
[ZACK gasps]
Sorry about that!
I'm beggin' you, please don't
tell the Boss what I was--!
[YUKINOJO] Man, if there were
more guys like you in Tekkadan,
I bet it would've made Orga's
life a helluva lot easier.
So, no matter what you do,
never stop thinkin'.
[ZACK]
Huh?
O... kay...
[JULIETTA] I must say,
your face is more handsom
than I'd imagined.
[GAELIO]
Really?
Why, thank you.
[JULIETTA]
You're like me.
Someone who is in search
of greater strength.
Alaya-Vijnana Type E.
It looks like you've
found your strength
in the form of inhuman powers.
[GAELIO] The only thing
that can draw out
the true power of this
Mobile Suit is a human.
[gasps]
Remember what I told
you a while back?
The soldier who had a lot
in common with you?
It's my belief that the passions
and emotions we all exhibit...
Show us that we're human.
Why are you t...?
[GAELIO]
Don't deny yourself.
And never forget there's someone
you trust and respect.
And your wanting
to better yourself
for his benefit...
...is the right thing.
[SHINO]
Right, King of Mars, my ass.
Hasn't he heard that,
if something sounds
too good to be true,
then it most likely is?
Yeah, but we're probably
the ones who made
Orga go down this path.
[SHINO]
Hmm?
[EUGENE] We've made him
decide every last detail
about Tekkadan's future
all by himself.
Not to mention we've
hustled him around
and egged him on.
All our worries and stress
got dumped onto him.
So what if we make
trouble for him?
Orga's job is to take care
of things, isn't it?
Yeah, but...!
And because of all
of Orga's hard work,
our job is easy.
When Orga tells us
not to worry,
we throw away our doubts and
do what's right for Tekkadan!
[EUGENE]
You're right.
[MCGILLIS] The plan is to engage
Rustal Elion in Earth's orbit.
Of course, I'll need Tekkadan
to join us in the battle line.
[ORGA]
Yeah, got it.
But here's the thing gets me.
From what you're saying,
wouldn't this have turned into
a fight with the Arianrhod,
no matter what?
I admit, it was
always a possibility.
Rustal Elion and the
Arianrhod Fleet he commands
have established something
of a unique position
within the ranks of Gjallarhorn.
However, I thought,
with the combined forces
of all the families behind me,
they wouldn't be such
a tough opponent.
After all, we still have
you and your people.
There may be casualties--
General!
[ORGA]
"Casualties"?
Every man, woman,
and child in Tekkadan
is a member of our
family, understand?!
Don't just write them off
as faceless nobodies!
What do you think
you're doing, you--
[ORGA] Listen to me.
Tekkadan won't betray someone
we've joined up with.
That was just to make it clear.
[ORGA] But we're not gonna
risk our lives on something
that doesn't make sense to us.
So why don't you cut
the crap, already?
Sure.
[MIKAZUKI]
Orga?
Just one more battle.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm.
[MECHANICS chattering]
[MEMBER 44C] They say it's
gonna be an all-out war!
[MEMBER 44E] Where are
the Shidens' spare parts?
[DERMA]
It's actually happening.
[RIDE] Yeah, but this
is the final battle.
Just one more to go.
One more.
[MEMBER 44F]
This is the last fight.
[MEMBER 44H] Once you're
done, go to the Hotarubi.
[MEMBER 44I] Hurry up!
This is the final battle!
[YAMAGI]
I'm finished.
[sighs]
[SHINO]
Hmm?
You're not gonna eat that?
I've been so busy working
that I've lost my appetite.
Come on! You'll never
last if you don't eat!
This is our last
battle, you know!
[gasps]
Listen up, people!
One more fight and
we'll get to our goal!
Give it your all, got it?
[MEMBERS]
Yes, sir!
[ATRA] They keep saying
it's the last battle,
and hearing them talk like
that kind of scares me.
I'm sorry for calling you
out of the blue like this.
[KUDELIA chuckles]
[KUDELIA]
It's okay.
I can't stop Mikazuki
from leaving us behind.
It's like I thought.
I'm not good enough
to keep him here.
[KUDELIA] No, more so
than me or anything else,
the only one who can keep him
there is you, Miss Atra.
Huh?
[KUDELIA] My dream is to
make a world where children
like Mikazuki never
have to exist.
I've always worked towards that.
But...
...for a while now,
I've been sensing
a contradiction.
The strong bond that
holds them together
could only have come about
under these harsh conditions.
And I've even longed
for a family like that.
But, Kudelia, you're
part of our family, too.
[gasps]
[KUDELIA chuckles]
[KUDELIA]
Thank you, Miss Atra.
Of course I feel like
part of the family.
I'll keep walking along
the path I believe is right.
And, in the end, that will be
what's best for my family.
And I believe that feeling
will never change.
Which is why...
...the only one who can be
by Mikazuki's side right now
is you, Miss Atra.
Seriously?
Me?
[MIKAZUKI]
Mm?
Were you asleep?
[MIKAZUKI]
Nah.
[ATRA chuckles]
[MIKAZUKI]
What is it?
Oh, nothing, it's just
really quiet in here.
[MIKAZUKI] Yeah, they all
went to the Hotarubi.
[ATRA]
Oh... That explains it.
Are you okay?
[ATRA] So, is this really
the last battle?
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah.
[ATRA] And it's gonna
be a tough one, huh?
[MIKAZUKI]
Well, if I had to say,
it's a little easier for me.
[gasps]
As long as I'm in Barbatos,
my body can move normally,
and I don't have to think
about anything like--
[ATRA]
It's easy?
[MIKAZUKI]
Hmm?
[ATRA] While you're out there
putting your life on the line,
all I can do is wait here.
If it's easier on you
to fight, does that mean...
...that I haven't been able
to do anything for you
in all this time?
[ATRA]
I...
I love you, Mikazuki.
I-I love the Mikazuki
that's here,
right in front of me!
You don't have to do this.
I might've told you to hug
girls when they're crying,
but now isn't the time
to do it, if you don't--
[MIKAZUKI]
That's part of it.
But also, I've realized just
how precious you are to me.
Do you mean it?
[MIKAZUKI] I don't know
of a world for myself
that doesn't involve fighting.
All I've known are the
battlefields that I've chosen,
and the ones chosen for me.
That's all.
What about now?
[MIKAZUKI] I'm fighting
so you can stop crying.
[KUDELIA]
I love him.
Mikazuki... but not
only Mikazuki.
Miss Atra, and everyone
else in Tekkadan, too.
They're my family.
If it's true,
and this battle is really
going to be the final one...
[RUSTAL] Starting now,
we, the Arianrhod Fleet,
will work toward defeating
the traitor, McGillis Fareed.
And reclaim Bael!
[KUDELIA]
...then may this ending
also be a beginning...
...to their future.
[EUGENE]
Next time on
Mobile Suit Gundam:
Iron-Blooded Orphans ,
"If This Is The End."
I know they say
money can't buy love,
but I'd sure love to visit
the ladies one last time!
Hey, Shino, when all
of this is over,
be a pal and take me there!