[TEKKADAN MEMBERS]
And push!
We did it!
[rumbling]
C'mon, Hush.
[ZACK]
I'll be waiting.
No!
[gasps]
[EMBI]
Elgar!
[grunts]
Dammit!
[EUGENE grunts]
Hirume! Support Embi!
Trow, fall back for now and--
[MIKAZUKI]
You too, Eugene.
[EUGENE] Mikazuki?
What are you talking about?!
--[EUGENE] I can still--
--I just got word from Pops.
[MIKAZUKI] They've finished
clearing out the tunnel,
and everyone's starting
to move through.
The first ones in
are about to reach Chryse.
Really? Then we'll
make one last push--
[MIKAZUKI]
Not "we."
This isn't gonna end
just because
they've all reached Chryse.
Now get going and
do your job, Deputy Boss.
[DANTE]
Dammit!
[AKIHIRO]
Dante, you fall back, too!
Like hell I will!
Who do you think you're...
[AKIHIRO] How can you help
with an armless Mobile Suit?
Just leave everything
to the Muscle Team.
Now get a move on, Ryusei Team!
--[DANTE] Akihiro...
--[AKIHIRO] Save it, all right?
[AKIHIRO]
Your job ain't over yet!
Go and carry out Orga's orders!
[EUGENE]
Pops!
[YUKINOJO] Hey, Eugene!
I'm glad you're back!
[EUGENE]
What's the situation?
Everybody's gone into
the tunnel except for us.
We just need to
rig this place to blow.
I'm finished on my end.
Well then, I say we should
all get the hell outta here.
But Mikazuki and the others
are still out there.
[DANTE] Don't worry about them,
they'll catch up with us later.
They still have some work
that they need to take care of
out on the battlefield.
And while they do,
we'll take care of our business.
We can't stop moving. Not until
we carry out Orga's orders.
[EUGENE]
Right, Mikazuki?
You can go, too, Akihiro.
[AKIHIRO]
Yeah, right.
Like I could take off
with you still here.
[MIKAZUKI]
Fine. Just don't get in my way.
[grunts]
Why you--!
Well, I'm not
carrying you out of here
when this is over, ya hear?
[inhales]
Akihiro Altland!
Gundam Gusion Rebake Full City!
And Mikazuki Augus.
Gundam Barbatos Lupus Rex.
[MIKAZUKI, AKIHIRO] Let's go!
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER 50A yells]
[AKIHIRO grunts]
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER 50B]
What the--?!
These two are like
monsters or something!
It looks like they're
beginning to back down.
[AKIHIRO]
No surprise there.
From where those guys
are sitting,
the two of us are
the last men left standing.
They think they've already won.
And nobody wants to die in a
battle that's already been won.
Oh, is that why?
Just what do you think
you're doing, Master Iok?!
You can't fight
with that injury!
[IOK] The morale of
our troops is falling fast!
I have no choice but to go in
and lead by example.
But, sir!
[JULIETTA]
Stand down, Master Iok.
We don't require
your help just yet.
Julietta? But I ...
We have a cause
that must be seen through
to the very end. No matter
how ruthless it may be.
[MERRIBIT panting]
[MERRIBIT]
Ride!
[RIDE] I'm really glad
you're safe, Ms. Merribit.
--I was...
--You did a wonderful job.
Yeah. But...
it's my fault Boss is--
If you hadn't gotten word
to us about the situation,
none of us would
be here right now.
You did your job so well, Ride.
[sobbing]
[ZACK]
How's it goin' over there?
[CHAD]
Eugene and the maintenance crew
are on their way. They just
started down the tunnel.
Hold on, you're sayin'
the fighting is over?
Not quite.
Mikazuki and Akihiro
are keeping the enemy at bay
until everyone reaches Chryse.
[MIKAZUKI]
Hm?
[AKIHIRO]
What the hell?
--[DANE] Huh?
--What's the matter?
[YAMAGI]
Dane, what is it?
You hear that?
The fighting sounds.
They've stopped.
[RUSTAL] A monster that can
overcome a Mobile Armor
single-handedly can hardly
be called human anymore.
But there are appropriate
ways of putting down
such a dangerous beast.
Dáinsleif Team, fire!
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 50A]
What's that noise?
[TEKKADAN MEMBER 50B]
Is it Gjallarhorn?
Is this from the explosives
we set in headquarters?
[MERRIBIT] They would've
given us a warning.
Plus, that blast is far too big.
[CHAD]
They wouldn't!
I noticed that the news reports
from the site stopped today.
Does that mean they used it?
[MIKAZUKI]
It's dark.
I wonder... if I'm dead.
But... this place
is familiar somehow.
Oh, yeah.
This is... that day.
It's... my memory...
of the day I was born.
My life was given to me by Orga.
That means I...
Yeah.
I know what to do.
[rumbling]
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER 50C]
Huh? What's that noise?
He's still... alive?
[MIKAZUKI grunts]
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER 50C]
That's not possible!
Wh-What are these things?!
Could they really be demons?
[IOK]
Don't panic!
They're on the brink of death!
And I'll be the one to
put them out of their misery!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 50A]
Master Iok!
--[MIKAZUKI] You alive?
--[AKIHIRO] Y-Yeah...
Don't know how, but yeah.
If this is how
it's gonna be then...
...let's live until we die...
...and... finish carrying
out Orga's orders!
[AKIHIRO yells]
[MIKAZUKI]
Yeah, you're right.
We can't stop moving yet.
Hey, Barbatos.
You don't wanna
stop either, do you?
[MIKAZUKI]
Then let's get to it!
Aah!
[GJALLARHORN SOLDIER 50E yells]
[MIKAZUKI]
Come on.
Wait! Stay back!
Leave this one to me!
[AKIHIRO grunts]
[IOK grunts]
[AKIHIRO coughs]
Why don't you die already?!
[IOK] Accept the judgment that
Iok Kujan delivers upon you!!
I recognize that name.
[AKIHIRO groaning]
[yells]
It was you?!
How can he--?
[yells]
[AKIHIRO]
Damn you!
Uh! I can't die
in a place like this!
It's impossible!
[IOK'S SUBORDINATE 50A]
Master Iok!
If you live long enough,
I guess good things
really do happen.
I never thought I'd get to
crush you with my own hands.
[AKIHIRO exhales]
I'll have to tell the guys
when I see em.
[JULIETTA] Why?!
Why are you still resisting?!
You're fighting for nothing!
What cause could possibly
be served by fighting
a meaningless battle
such as this one?
What kinda cause? Whaddya mean?
Meaningless, huh?
Maybe you're right.
My life never had
any meaning. Still...
Get away! Don't go near him!
[JULIETTA]
You demon.
Maybe so... but now...
...I have the meaning
that Orga gave to me.
I used to have nothing at all.
But now I have so much.
I have so much that
I can't hold it all.
[MIKAZUKI]
And I see...
...that we'd...
already made it there.
I don't understand you!
You don't have a single cause
to commit to, so why?!
[clang]
[JULIETTA]
Is he... passed out?
[MIKAZUKI] We made it... to the
place where we truly belong.
[MIKAZUKI]
Right, Orga?
[ORGA]
Yeah. That's right, Mika.
[MIKAZUKI groans]
[MIKAZUKI]
I got it dirty again.
Atra's gonna be mad at me.
I wonder... if Kudelia
will help me apologize to her.
[JULIETTA] Here and now,
by the grace of Rustal Elion,
commander of
the Arianrhod Fleet,
the demon has
finally been slain!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[ATRA]
The series of events known as
"the McGillis Fareed Incident"
ended with the death
of McGillis Fareed himself.
Gjallarhorn, which was
once on the verge
of losing the public's trust,
demonstrated its
power to the world
by resolving the conflict
before it could get any worse.
What's more,
with Gjallarhorn having lost
the Issue, Kujan,
and Fareed families,
they did away with the
Seven Stars council system.
It was restructured into
a more democratic organization,
and Rustal Elion was
sworn in as its first leader.
In the wake of the incident,
Elion scaled back
Gjallarhorn's Mars Branch.
And In response, the various
Earth economic blocs
that had practically let
Gjallarhorn govern the planet,
relinquished their
control of Mars.
Once free of the
economic blocs' rule,
the cities of Mars
founded the Martian Union.
Kudelia Aina Bernstine took
office as the Union Chairperson.
It's said that this was not
only because of her popularity,
but also due to
heavy support from Teiwaz,
which had grown even more
powerful after making
a secret deal with Rustal Elion
over the Turbines incident.
A world where rights are
equally bestowed upon everyone.
Ironically, a small
part of the ideal
that McGillis Fareed
strove for is about to be
brought to fruition
by the hands of Rustal Elion.
After that, people will
begin to forget.
No one will remember that
the incidents set in motion
by McGillis Fareed involved
a group of children
known as Tekkadan,
who knew only how to fight.
Much like people who don't
notice flowers blossoming
on the side of the road,
they'll simply walk on by.
[NEWSCASTER 50A]
I'm bringing you live coverage
from Makanai Memorial Hall
where the Human Debris
Abolishment Treaty
is in the process
of being signed
by Gjallarhorn Leader
Rustal Elion and
the Martian Union Chairperson
Kudelia Aina Bernstein.
The two leaders have pledged
to work hand in hand
to save children who are
being unjustly exploited
and whose human rights
are being ignored.
This treaty is something
that the late
Arbrau Prime Minister Makanai
devoted all his energy to
in his final years;
one of the reasons why this
auditorium was chosen for such--
[KUDELIA] Thank you very much
for today, Mr. Elion.
[RUSTAL] Not at all.
It was an honor and a privilege
for me to finally meet
The Maiden of Revolution.
[KUDELIA]
"Maiden"? You flatter me.
You know the Human Debris issue
has been a heartbreaking
matter for us, too.
I promise, Gjallarhorn fully
intends to use every resource
at its disposal to help you
realize your dream.
My dream, you say?
[RUSTAL]
Hm?
[KUDELIA] Actually, I used to
have a family that was
made up of Human Debris.
Did you?
[KUDELIA] He... No, they fought
their circumstances head-on.
They died honorable deaths.
I hope that I can live
each day of my life
in a way that would
do them proud.
I understand.
Excuse me. Your car
is waiting for you.
We should go.
[KUDELIA]
Thank you.
Good day, sir.
[RUSTAL]
Hm.
That explains a lot.
[JULIETTA] For the life of me,
I can't understand why
he would allow
Kudelia Aina Bernstein
to become the
Martian Union's chairperson.
If Teiwaz was involved
behind the scenes in some way,
surely they would've
consulted Master Rustal
at some point, wouldn't they?
[GAELIO] I assume they each
expect something in return.
Don't let her fool you.
That woman was fully aware
when she took the position.
[JULIETTA] "Be tolerant of
people of all shades," right?
It's all for the realization
of a new Gjallarhorn
that Master Rustal envisions.
[GAELIO] There's a rumor going
around that you'll be the one
to the take the reins
of that new Gjallarhorn.
The gallant female knight who
claimed the head of the demon.
[JULIETTA]
You said something to me once.
You told me that if I wished
to attain true power,
I must remain human.
I said something like that, huh?
I've realized that...
...the members of Tekkadan
weren't demons after all.
They were more human
than anyone.
The only place they belonged
was on the battlefield fighting.
Not to achieve
some ambition or goal,
but to live on as human beings.
They fought just to survive.
[GAELIO]
You're right.
That's the reason they elicited
so much fear from us.
Because if you can understand
the enemy's purpose,
you're closer to
finding their limits.
I wish... I could've found
a way to understand him
a little earlier. Hm.
So Julietta, are you busy later?
Surely you have time
to eat with me.
My, you've become quite
friendly over the years,
haven't you?
Back when you wore
your mask, you--
That feels like an eternity ago.
I was this kind of man
my before it put it on.
Or is it... that the other me
was more to your liking?
Let's go eat some meat.
That's a terrific idea!
I actually prefer women
with a little more
meat on their bo--
Whoa, slow down, would ya?
Come on, at least
try to be careful!
[ALESI] I am positive that
Mr. Makanai would have been
brimming with pride
if he could've seen you
at the ceremony today.
[KUDELIA] I owed so much to him,
right up until the very end.
And thank you, Mr. Alesi.
Or rather, thank you for your
continued support,
Mr. Prime Minister.
You too, Takaki. Thank you.
Well, I haven't really
done anything.
Hey, Takaki. You better not be
making trouble for Mr. Alesi.
Back at you, Deputy Boss.
You'd better not be making
trouble for Miss Kudelia.
[EUGENE] How many times
do I have to tell you
not to call me that?!
Who knows who might
be listening?
[ALESI]
To be perfectly honest,
Takaki is doing a
great job as my secretary.
I'm even hoping that one day
he'll take over my constituency.
[EUGENE]
This guy? A Parliament member?
[TAKAKI] I remember something
you told me, Miss Kudelia.
You said the more I experienced,
the more knowledge I'd acquire.
And with knowledge,
I'd have more opportunities.
I think I understand
what you meant now.
Takaki.
[TAKAKI] I'll keeping trying
to find things that I can do
for the children of Mars,
and for children everywhere,
so that I can work side by side
with you someday, Miss Kudelia.
[KUDELIA]
Okay. I'll be waiting.
[CHAD]
Welcome back, Miss.
I watched the live broadcast
of the signing ceremony.
[KUDELIA]
Thank you.
How's the company? Anything new?
[CHAD]
Ms. Cucubita and Mr. Dexter
have kept the business
running without a hitch.
No problems
at the mines, either.
What about the school?
[CHAD]
All is fine.
Though, the orphanage is
asking for more staff members
as they're shorthanded.
Come on, Dante? Not again.
[KUDELIA]
He's doing a great job.
When the treaty takes effect,
there are going to be
many more children
with nowhere else to go.
Let's do what we can to help.
[EUGENE sighs]
[CHAD] And concerning
Ride and the other guys...
Did you locate them?
[CHAD] No. Ever since
we received the intel
that Nobliss Gordon
had returned to Mars,
it's like they've been
deliberately avoiding us.
He still hasn't
gotten over what happened.
I'd like you to keep looking
for him for the time being.
For now, let's just have faith.
After all, we're still a family.
[NOBLISS exhales]
Thanks to Gjallarhorn
my business is flourishing.
It's hard to find time
to even use the bathroom.
Go ahead and
bring the car around.
[door lock clicks]
[metal jingles]
[NOBLISS sighs]
[knock, knock]
Huh, what do you want?
It's occupied!
[RIDE]
Do you remember Orga Itsuka?
[NOBLISS]
Huh? Who the hell is that?
And who are--
[thud]
[distant gunfire]
[FORMER TEKKADAN MEMBER 50A]
Ride,
we've wrapped
things up on our end.
[RIDE]
All right. I'm done here, too.
[KUDELIA]
No matter how far we are,
even if we never
see each other again,
every one of us
is walking forward
trying to reach the light.
We must keep walking.
In my heart I believe
that is our duty.
For the family members
who gave their lives,
in the hopes that
we would find happiness.
--[CHAD] Mm.
--You're right.
Oh yeah, speaking of family!
Huh?
[CHAD] It seems Pops and
Ms. Merribit's second baby
is going to be born any day now.
That's great!
[CHAD] So, Yamagi and I
thought we should go
and plan the
celebrations tonight.
[EUGENE] "Plan" my ass.
You guys just wanna go drinkin'.
And what's so wrong about that?
[KUDELIA] Sorry, but tonight's
no good for me.
Oh, really. Did you have
other plans or something?
[EUGENE]
Well, of course she does!
She's the chair of the Union.
[KUDELIA]
It's not that.
I've just been away
for such a long time
that I'd like to
go home for a bit.
Sure you would.
I don't blame you.
The man you love
is waiting for you.
[ATRA humming]
Darn it! Stop that, Akatsuki!
[KUDELIA giggles]
Gotcha!
--Kudelia?
--That's right.
Hi there! Welcome back, Kudelia.
That sure was a quick trip.
Yes, it was.
And have you been a good boy
for Mommy, Akatsuki?
[AKATSUKI]
Mm-hmm.
You liar! Good boys
don't run around and
play with the clean laundry,
now do they?
[AKATSUKI]
I'm good!
Yes, I can see that.
Jeez, you've always
been way too soft
on this little rascal, Kudelia.
[KUDELIA] Akatsuki's hands
sure have gotten
a lot bigger since last time.
They must come from Mikazuki.
Hands that will hold the future.
I'll go and make us some tea.
Cookie and Cracker have
just gotten back, too.
[KUDELIA]
Great.
I love it.
Even if it will be forgotten
with the passage of time,
I love the world that
the members of Tekkadan
made for us.
I love this world.
This beautiful world
that you left for us.
[ATRA]
Akatsuki!
[KUDELIA]
The tea is ready!
[ATRA]
Hey, no running indoors!
--[KUDELIA giggles]
--[ATRA] Where are you going?
[ATRA]
That boy is such a rascal!
[KUDELIA]
But he sure is adorable.