[MARTIN] It wasn't
supposed to be like this.
I screwed up.
I just wanted things
to be how they were.
But it's all a lie.
Heh.
None of it's real.
Not you.
Not me.
I might as well not
even have a sister.
We should all disappear.
[SOPHIE gasps]
Sophie.
[BISHOP]
Hm...
What an interesting fellow
he turned out to be.
[BISHOP] Not a shred
of darkness in the boy.
I didn't think such
creatures still existed.
If his mind is up to the task,
I could care less about
his moral constitution.
Our only concern
is that the job gets done.
Yes.
I suppose you do
make a valid point.
Regardless,
protecting the ring's current
owner takes precedent.
Our duties are clear.
I for one shall embrace my role.
Well, that goes without saying.
Duty or not, our hands are tied.
One doesn't simply go
against the will of the ring.
[BISHOP] I only wish
I knew his master plan.
You're kidding me, right?
That's wonderful news!
At last he shows
his face in all its glory.
King.
[SOPHIE]
No.
This can't be.
This isn't real.
Where is my brother?
You've surpassed
my expectations.
Well done, Sophia Hennes.
[gasps]
What does that
mean, "well done"?
Come now, don't be modest.
Your brother is
exceptionally proud of you.
This is all on me.
I did this.
It's my fault.
Look who's here!
The Golden Knight himself.
Sorry if I kept you waiting.
You bastard.
[laughs]
Huh? Oh god, Martin!
Sophie.
[MARTIN]
Please, Sophie.
Sophie.
[SWORD grunts]
Damn it all.
Is one not enough?
[SWORD]
I hate these things!
Here we go!
You can run, but you can't hide.
What the hell is going on?
[BISHOP]
Heh.
Not quite what I was expecting.
This is him, is it?
If he's the King, one shudders
to think what we are.
Dear, oh dear.
Oh, hello.
Please tell me
they made it out of there.
[LUKE] Looks like
Sophie escaped the tower.
Sword arrived just in time.
'Kay, then.
Let's focus on
evacuating whoever's left.
Right.
[motorcycle engine]
There you are.
[SOPHIE]
I did this.
My brother's become one of them.
He's a Horror,
and it's all my fault.
[SWORD]
You're wrong.
'S not your fault.
So knock it off with this
"blaming yourself" crap.
C'mon, let's go.
Sophie.
Whatever happens, stay close.
[motorcycle engine]
Good to see
you're finally awake.
Just my luck
it'd have to be now.
[SWORD] Long as you
hit the ground runnin'.
No matter.
In every era they stand against
me, and in every era they fall.
[ZARUBA]
What's wrong?
It's not like you to be
looking so grim, Sword.
Try to ignore me.
[ZARUBA]
No witty comeback?
Heh.
So what's with the new chassis?
Just a little something
they threw together
for yours truly from
the Land of Guidance.
Way to go, Gina.
[ZARUBA]
Indeed.
Sophie.
You've been unusually quiet.
Is everyone out of character?
How bad was it?
[GINA]
Sophie!
You're okay.
Thank goodness!
What'd they do to you?
Talk to me, sweetie.
The hell happened?
Oh, Sophie.
That was the King's
plan all along?
You're kidding me.
Come on, he manipulated
Sophie to possess Martin?
Pretty much.
[LUKE]
That's enough.
It's unconscionable to
involve her in this any longer.
Whole thing was a trap.
They counted on us
to bring her here.
All we can do now
is regroup and...
[LUKE]
...eliminate the Horrors.
I agree.
[KING snickers]
The time has come.
[multiple rings and beeps]
[MAN A]
Now what?
Aw, man.
Automatic updates.
At long last,
I'll see my greatest
desire come to fruition.
Hear me, my Sacred Blades!
I command you to destroy those
who stand against
the glorious new world!
Well, my dear.
I do believe
it's our time to shine.
"Queen."
'S going on?
Hell if I know.
[LIZZY]
Sword!
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
Wait. Who is that?
[LIZZY]
Listen closely.
ELDO NET's gone live, worldwide.
Lizzy!
[LIZZY]
There's no time to waste.
Fresh souls are being
harvested as we speak.
Anyone with internet
access is in danger.
They'll be absorbed into
the system against their will.
Say what?
[LIZZY]
The ancient one grows stronger
with each soul he devours.
The stronger he becomes,
the more ELDO NET spreads.
A vicious cycle.
There's got to be a way
we can stop him!
[LIZZY] Not from engorging
himself on the innocent.
[groans]
[LIZZY]
But once they've been consumed,
there's a special storage unit
where the souls are housed.
Access the storage unit
and they can be released.
The only problem,
it's easier said than done.
Tell me what we have to do.
[LIZZY] Only someone with
administrative privileges
can get you in.
Obviously the project manager
himself is out of the question.
[LIZZY] That said,
there's one other person
beside Martin Hennes
that can grant access.
Sophie.
[ZARUBA] You must be awfully
fond of that particular spot.
Will something come to you
if you sit there long enough?
Sorry if I'm quiet.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
It's just, I...
If this happens to be
about my riding into
the Dark Knight,
I highly recommend
you let it go.
But I'm so...
[ZARUBA] Souls across
the world are in jeopardy.
ELDO NET is
spreading like wildfire.
The King hungers.
The power he gets from
harvesting souls
he'll turn around
and use to harvest
even more in a
never-ending cycle.
But there's hope.
Seems your brother gave you
the keys to the kingdom.
It just so happens the souls
being harvested are stored
in a special unit you alone
can give us access to.
[ZARUBA] Sword and the others
are loath to see you endure
more than you
already have, of course.
They prefer to spare you
and do this themselves.
Futile endeavor if you ask me.
[CHILD]
Hey, Sophie!
[ZARUBA]
That's an encouraging sign.
[LIZZY]
Sword!
I found an infiltration device!
That's great.
Now what about access?
[LIZZY]
No luck.
There doesn't seem to be a way
without administrative
privileges.
[SWORD]
Hmm.
Of course there isn't.
Well, keep looking.
[LIZZY]
Sure thing.
Just swear to me
you'll be careful.
Your brother couldn't
ask for a better entourage.
I'll have this lug's
back to the bitter end.
I promise.
I know I can count on you.
Oh, and uh,
goes for you to, Zaruba.
[SOPHIE]
Take me with you.
I can't just sit here.
I don't know if I can help.
But it's wrong
for you to go alone.
Sophie.
[SOPHIE] After everything
you've done for me.
It's the least I can do.
Honey, 'less
you want to get eaten,
I suggest you stay here.
It's not about me.
I can't undo the
damage I've caused.
We're beyond that now.
Still, though.
I can follow your
example if you let me.
For once, like you guys,
let me protect someone.
I have to try!
Give me a chance!
Let's ride.
Ah! Yeah!
[gasps]
Just so you know, darling.
I expect to get that back.
Good to go?
Let's do it!
Hell yeah!
[LIZZY]
Which gate do you want?
[SOPHIE]
Huh? Who's that?
[SWORD]
My sister.
[SOPHIE]
Seriously?
[SWORD]
Watch out!
Perfect timing.
You two get out of here!
This asshole's our problem now!
Just go.
We got this.
I won't make
the same mistake twice.
You must be destroyed.