[SWORD] You always did know
how to throw a guy off balance.
Hey, Gina.
[GINA] Makai Alchemists
tend to be busy people.
[SWORD]
Saw this comin'.
Happens every damn time
I let myself get caught up
in one of her pet projects.
[SOPHIE] If his disappearance
has anything to do
with these creatures,
whatever they are,
then I need the help
of someone like you!
I'm begging you, Sword!
Please help me find my brother!
[WAITRESS] Sorry. We've been
over this, honey bun.
House rules. If you can't
pay, you can't stay.
[SOPHIE]
One orange juice, please.
Found me some pocket money.
Can I possibly interest
you in a cheese dog
and an avocado salad with that?
Just the orange juice.
[WAITRESS]
Here ya go.
[SOPHIE] Today's the day
I get a yes out of that guy.
El Dorado here we come.
I don't know what you are,
but my brother did.
[bell chimes]
Howdy-do!
Yeah, how you doin'?
My usual, please and thank you.
--Swo--!
--[GINA] Morning, sweetie.
[SWORD gasps]
[GINA] Sorry to ambush you
like this. I need your help.
What do you think...
about getting married?
Sweetheart, don't you think
our precious baby girl
would like to hold on
to daddy's hand?
[SWORD]
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
[gasps]
Sure.
[CAT meows]
[SOPHIE gasps]
[VIOLA]
Oh, my. All apologies.
Savage little beast,
scarcely housebroken.
Speaking of which, welcome
to my humble home.
I am Lady Viola.
Ah, yes. I contacted
you the other day.
We're the Browns.
This is my husband and
our lovely daughter, Emily.
Ma'am.
Pleasure to meet you.
What a beautiful family.
Enchante .
[SOPHIE]
So this is her.
She gives me the creeps.
[chuckles]
[SWORD]
A ring that controls Horrors?
[GINA] To be fair,
it's still just a rumor.
Lady Viola--silver screen
hopeful when she was younger.
Sadly, she tended to
blend in with the extras,
'least till her rivals
started dropping out.
Scandal. Injury.
Bit by bit, the path
to stardom opened up.
She rose to fame on the
backs of others' misfortune.
Married a industy high roller.
When he died a few years later,
she came into a lot of money.
Started work as an education
consultant, of all things.
She essentially listens to rich
parents whine about their brats,
all while staying relevant
and raking in the dough.
A rags-to-riches story
if I've ever heard one.
So what I'm hearing is you think
she owes it all to
a Horror, right?
Well, word on the street
is the lady possesses a ring
that controls demons.
Pretty good retirement
plan if you ask me,
provided you don't give
a damn about your soul.
Does a ring like
that really exist?
How long have you been there?
Hey. Why don't you finish
your juice and go home, kid?
Screw you! You're not getting
rid of me that easily!
What is El Dorado?
[GINA] That's just what
we're hoping to find out.
[VIOLA] You'll have to
tell me all about it
when we have a chance later.
I'd be honored beyond
words to offer my services
to such a charming
household, if you'd like.
Thank you so much, madam!
Household matters are not
my husband's strength.
[SWORD grunts]
Uh, damn it all.
I'm a busy man!
Ugh, you see how he is.
Always blaming work for why
he can't help me with Emily.
Stop it! God!
All you do is fight!
Why did we even come
to this stupid party?
[GINA]
Emily!
[VIOLA]
Pumpkin, I know you're upset,
but I only want to
be your friend.
Come, parties are for
enjoying yourself.
There are quite a few
girls your age here.
Go mingle with them.
Ah, yes, so I hear.
M and A's good, but
what about Indonesia?
[GENTLEMAN B]
It's been rough-going.
We were able to legally prevent
the sale of Crown Jewel,
but then, there's the whole
brand-imaging debacle now.
[GENTLEMAN C]
I've been saying for years
our foreign policy
is a laughing stock.
[GENTLEMAN B]
Isn't that the truth.
[GENTLEMAN A]
Care to chime in?
Uh. Well...
We're doin' all right.
[MOTHER A]
My child is a lost cause.
Good luck trying to whip
that one into shape.
The woman had better
not rely on luck.
For the money we're paying,
she should have it
down to a science.
Didn't you hear?
That dreadful hellion
of a Spencer girl
is quiet as a
month-old kitten now.
Science be damned. Lady Viola
must be using witchcraft.
Long as all she needs
from me is cash,
I couldn't care less
what she uses.
[CHILD A]
Ow! Stupid cat scratched me!
[VIOLA]
Hello there, Emily.
Are you finding everything
to your liking?
Oh. Uh. Well, actually, no.
Why are there cats everywhere?
Ah. Well, I have no children.
That's why it pleases
me ever so much
when young people like
yourself come over to play.
[SWORD groans]
I'm exhausted.
You're doing fine.
The hell was going
through your head?
[GINA]
Hm?
You involved a kid who had
nothing to do with us.
[GINA]
Nothing?
She asked you to help
find her brother,
which I think is adorable.
We both know you could've
pushed her away if you wanted.
If she's serious
about getting herself
wrapped up in this world,
let her have taste of
what it's really like.
She wants your help,
she should know what
it is you do, right?
[ZARUBA]
Heads up.
[SWORD]
Huh?
I smell a Horror.
Is it Lady Viola?
[ZARUBA]
The stench is pervasive.
I can't quite tell
where it's coming from.
[sighs]
Fine. Guess we'll just have
to confirm it directly.
You're the one who
brought the kid along,
she's your responsibility.
Yes, of course.
Aw, Emily. Don't be such a
shrinking violet, my dear...
[SWORD]
Hey, uh, Emily.
Your mother wants to see you.
Whatever.
[VIOLA]
Mr. Brown.
[SWORD]
Oh, shit, that's me.
Uh. My apologies.
Beguiling child.
A bit rough around the
edges perhaps, but lovely.
Who, Emily? She's a hellcat.
Just like her mom.
Neither of 'em listens
to a damn word I say.
Em's been skipping school.
I caught her stealing
money, too.
I try being a good dad,
but I'm at my wit's end.
[VIOLA] Don't fret,
Mr. Brown. There, there.
It's important for me that
you know I'm your ally.
[SWORD]
Thank you, Lady Viola.
They all say you have
the magic touch.
I can see now it's true.
Please, work your sorcery on us!
[VIOLA chuckles]
[VIOLA]
My, such hyperbole!
I'm not a sorceress.
I determine the appropriate
method for a child's needs
and proceed accordingly.
It's very much a team
effort, I assure you.
A team effort,
isn't that something.
Oh, it is, sir. Believe me.
Why don't we begin
with you telling me
some things about yourself?
Establishing a relationship
built on trust
is vital for your
daughter's future.
Trust, as in?
[VIOLA]
Indeed.
Speaking of built,
you're a mountain.
Not to change the subject,
but what sort of curriculum
do you have the kids on here,
if you don't mi--
Let us save that discussion
for later tonight.
Ugh. Lady Viola's at it again.
Poor man. Someone
should save him.
[WOMEN chuckle]
One has to respect her charm.
Seems children aren't the only
thing she's capable of taming.
[MOTHERS chuckle]
[MOTHER G]
Careful, she'll hear.
[MOTHER C] She should write a
handbook for the rest of us.
[MOTHERS chuckling]
Let's find somewhere
more... intimate.
[SWORD chuckles]
[SWORD] Thank you for this
bounty, but no thanks.
Oh, man. I'm so tired.
Really? Night's still young.
This is gonna get serious.
Are rich people all like that?
Jerks, I mean.
They seem way more
into money and gossip
than they do raising
their own kids.
It has less to do with wealth
than who they are
as human beings.
Some folks just prefer the
path of least resistance
over actually working
to solve a problem.
When it's their kid?
Terrible parents come
in all varieties.
Nothing to do but pity them.
[SOPHIE] You do this
kinda thing all the time?
Horrors are so,
I dunno, horrible.
Aren't you scared?
[GINA]
You kidding? Petrified.
Then, why d'you do it?
So I can be a rich person.
[GINA]
What do we have here?
Must be the wing where
she keeps her charges.
[SOPHIE]
Where is everybody?
Hang on.
Hey, Gina, look at this.
Something about that shelf.
Good catch, Sophie. Well done.
I did the same thing in my room.
It's how I used to
hide letters to Santa
so my brother wouldn't
make fun of me.
Looks like some kind
of secret diary.
[SOPHIE gasps]
"Everything they say
about her is true.
The demon servant is real.
Whatever Lady Viola
asks for, it just does."
[SOHPIE] "If it catches you,
you become empty.
The demon takes you away
and replaces you
with a soulless doll.
I won't let that happen to me
like it did to the others.
The demon got Will today.
He tried to run,
but it was too fast.
No. I can't un-see
what it did to him.
Someone help me!"
"It won't be long now before
it eats me like the rest."
Wait, so this means all the kids
she supposed to be taking care
of were eaten by a Horror?
What about the parents?
Don't they know
something's wrong?
They just look the other way?
Yeah. Not all parents are good.
Frequently, Sophie,
human beings and demons
aren't easy to tell apart.
[SOPHIE gasps]
Certain people who sought
Lady Viola's help vanished.
It's as though they walked off
the face of the Earth entirely.
Prominent socialites one minute,
complete non-entities the next.
Granted, the upper echelons
are notoriously fickle.
It's common to fall
from grace overnight.
[GINA] But that can't
always be the case.
Some parents had to raise hell
when their child went missing.
Let's hope.
But then, you think
she... maybe...?
[SOPHIE]
What kind of place is this?
[GINA] A fairly standard
altar for demon worship.
Seen it a thousand times.
Our buxom friend made a pact
with a demon. A Horror.
[SOPHIE] For real, though?
That's a thing?
[GINA]
Nibe-lung. Solomon. Prometheus.
Think for a moment,
remember her rings?
Rings are often thought
to hold magical power.
Legends of one able to
summon and control a Horror
have been with us
from time immemorial.
Imagine if something
like that were true,
it'd be the find
of the millennia.
Collectors would pay
through the nose.
Gina!
Damn it. I ought to
have known better.
[VIOLA] This is going to
be the night of your life.
[SWORD]
Get a move on, Gina, hurry!
Wait right there for
a moment, darling.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
[sighs]
Sophie. This is the
reality of what we do.
Get mixed up with Makai Knights,
the world turns upside down.
Tonight won't stand out.
Hell, before long this will
just be one of many.
Prepare yourself for it.
There's no going back.
Wandering where you're
clearly not welcome.
What meddlesome guests we have.
Uh-oh.
Please tell me there's not a
Horror for each of those rings.
Heavens me.
There's more to you little
pests than meets the eye.
Indeed.
I'm a Makai Alchemist
who's come to kill you.
Poor fool.
Brimming with an excess
of confidence, I see.
Do you believe someone
contracted with so many Horrors
can be quashed that easily?
My friends are hungry a lot.
Bon appetit!
[VIOLA yells]
[GINA]
Costume jewelry.
Something capable of wrangling a
Horror wouldn't break like that.
I figured it sounded
too good to be true.
There's not a single Horror
under your control!
You are the Horror!
[GINA] That's what you get
for trying to bind one
with some cheap trinket.
Play with fire, milady,
and you get burned.
[VIOLA]
You're wrong! You're wrong!
[gasps]
[HORROR A laughs]
I'm guessing that's the
parlor trick you used
to turn those children
into kittens.
Nice one. What
took you so long?
I had a close call of my own,
just so we're all
aware, thank you.
What? C'mon. You had
this in the bag.
[GINA]
Fair enough.
I was just about to
finish up, actually.
[SWORD chuckles]
You barely even
needed me here. Hm?
Tough luck, huh?
Sucks you didn't get
anything valuable out of it.
The good stuff's
hard to come by,
which of course is what
makes it worth chasing
in the first place.
Chasing. Yeah. Right.
For the privilege of
dangling rare items
in front of rich weirdos.
What a thrill.
Oh, it is.
'Specially when the item's
not as rare as they think.
Sword, please. Just stop.
She's smarter than you.
[SWORD]
Hm? Sophie.
You've decided, then?
Yeah.
What's going on?
[ZARUBA]
Brace yourself.
When women band together,
you'll never get
the better of them.
Trust me.
Right. So today's the day
I finally get a yes.
We follow the El Dorado
lead together. Period.
Ugh, seriously?
We'll start real simple:
Tell me everything you know.
Where is it? What's it do?
When'd you start looking
for it and for how long?
[SWORD]
Uhh...
Where d'you think you're going?
You can't leave me here!
Hey! Focus! I want answers!
And don't even
think about trying
to skip out on me
like last time!
I'm on to you, mister!
You're stuck with me!
[SWORD]
Wait!