[WAITRESS]
Still no sign of him.
Aw! But he always comes here!
Where could he be?
[WAITRESS] I appreciate
your persistence,
but I'm not psychic.
Whatever. I'll look
for him myself.
Would you care to
look at the menu?
There's the avocado
cheddar sandwich.
Hot and sweet hash browns.
And our brand new
three-fruit smoothie
with double the toppings!
Hmmm-mmm!
Available for a limited time.
Highly recommended.
Uh-oh! Sorry, sweetie.
House rules. If you can't
pay, you can't stay.
Shucks! Thanks for stoppin'
by, hon. Toodle-loo!
[SOPHIE]
Please?
[SISTER]
No!
You've been given your
allowance for the month.
Learn to budget yourself.
Whatever luxury you
think you need can wait.
It's not about luxury!
Why on earth must you
frequent a restaurant
when we feed you here?
If that's not luxury,
I don't know what is!
[SISTER]
Is life with us so unbearable?
My dear, I realize
you're doing all this
for your brother Martin.
Why not be patient and let
the police do their job?
Unless they know what El Dorado
means, what can the cops do?
What?
[SOPHIE]
Never mind.
[ANNE]
What'cha doin', Sophie?
[SOPHIE]
I dunno. Nothin'.
Hey. You even started
writing your essay yet?
Deadline's soon.
Like, day after tomorrow soon.
[SOPHIE] I need to know
if anyone saw it
with their own eyes.
[LIP AVATAR A]
No idea.
[POODLE AVATAR A] What, did you
get ripped off or something?
[SOPHIE] No. I'm just
looking into a rumor.
[OWL AVATAR A]
What's the rumor?
[SOPHIE]
There's a man in golden armor.
He's connected to a string of
people who've gone missing.
At least, that's the story.
[OWL AVATAR A]
C'est quoi ?
[MONKEY AVATAR A] This the first
I heard about this rumor.
[SOPHIE]
He calls himself a Makai Knight.
[LIP AVATAR A]
Sounds like a mental case.
[POODLE AVATAR A]
Mmm... try asking around
on the occult thread.
[SOPHIE]
Wait, there've been incidents.
[ANNE]
Hello? Sophie?
[gasps]
Gee, thanks.
Way to pay attention.
[SOPHIE]
Hm?
I said the essay's due
the day after tomorrow.
The nuns are gonna blow a
fuse if you forget, for real.
Crap. They seriously
want it that soon?
Consider yourself warned.
Hey, do you remember
Father Ripley
who performed mass
for us that one time?
He was super nice?
[SOPHIE]
Kind of, I guess.
[ANNE]
Well, I heard he disappeared.
Disappeared?
[ANNE] Yeah. They were talking
about it in the cafeteria.
No one knows where he is.
But they say at night
from his house,
you can hear this
sinister voice.
How creepy is that?
I can't sleep by myself anymore.
It's like something out
of a horror movie.
[knocking]
[SISTER]
I'm coming in.
Where's Sophie?
[ANNE]
Curled up on the--
[gasps]
[SISTER]
Unbelievable.
[SOPHIE] There might be
a Horror behind this.
Just like with the
Moon Wizard guy.
Which means Sword
will get involved.
Just keep heading up
the road a bit further.
Yeah, nice fella.
He and Miss Marie
were always so sweet.
Fixed up an old
church and everything.
Miss Marie, you said?
[OLD MAN A]
Father Ripley's little sister.
Now there's a gal who turned
a few heads in her day.
She's a bit of a recluse now.
Doesn't show her face
around town much anymore.
You'd never find a man more
devout than her brother, though.
The priesthood was his calling.
[LITTLE GIRL A giggling]
--[LITTLE GIRL A] Over here!
--[BOY A] Be careful!
--'Scuse me, I'm sorry.
--[BOY A] Sorry about that.
[SOPHIE]
How did you pay for this?
[MARTIN] The reward money
from my programming competition.
It's huge!
[MARTIN]
Yup. And all yours.
The whole thing's mine?
[MARTIN] Sophie. It's
special now, I know.
But one day you'll be
able to eat this stuff
whenever you feel like it.
--[BOY A] Keep up, sis!
--[LITTLE GIRL A] Hey! Wait up!
[SOPHIE]
Um, pardon me.
Who're you?
Uh. Sorry for just showing up.
[SOPHIE] Hi there, my
name is Sophia Hennes.
I'm from the Catherine
Home in Russell City.
Father Ripley did mass
for us a while back.
You're, uh, Miss
Marie, aren't you?
As a matter of fact, yes.
Pleasure to meet you.
I, um, thought... maybe
we could talk, or...?
Yes, that'd be lovely.
Come on in.
Okay!
[SOPHIE]
He just up and vanished?
[MARIE]
Yes.
The reality of it still
hasn't quite sunk in.
What do the police say?
Nothing very comforting,
I'm afraid.
I get the impression
that there are
quite a few cases like Tom's.
The detective warned me
not to hold out much hope.
What a jerk.
I mean, seriously.
Where do they get off
talking to people like that?
They don't know what it's like!
And you do?
[SOPHIE] My brother's been
missing for a while now.
I'm looking for him.
[MARIE] Oh, dear.
I'm sorry to hear that.
[MARIE]
You poor thing.
Hey, uh, you haven't been
eating well lately, right?
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
It's delicious!
Glad you like it!
You think it's good now,
wait till we let it
simmer for a bit.
Hey, neat-o!
Look at that. Do you dry
those flowers yourself?
[MARIE] I sure do.
Something of a hobby of mine.
I pick fresh ones every morning
and dry them right
here in the kitchen.
Helps pass the time.
Cheers the house a
bit, too, I think.
Whoa. They're all
over the place.
Oh, wow. Is that you
in the picture? Cool.
[MARIE]
Oh. Ancient history.
That was taken at the
town festival ages ago.
[SOPHIE]
You were a knockout!
[MARIE]
Don't look too closely, now.
Aw, come on.
You're still just as beautiful
as you were back then.
Throw on some nice
clothes. Get out there.
You'd be the belle of the ball!
Uh, I'm sorry, Sophia.
That ship sailed long ago.
[banging]
Wait, I'll get it for you.
Coming!
[gasps]
[SOPHIE]
Sword?
What the hell are you
doin' here, kid?
Um, excuse me?
Back up. I happen
to have a name.
Don't you dare've forgotten!
Ugh. I've been looking
for you, ya know!
Uh.
Yeah. Sure, fine.
So, why are you here? Snooping?
Curious about the
Father Ripley case?
[SWORD]
Huh?
What? Ugh. Sword! C'mon!
You and I both know a Horror's
gotta be involved somehow!
What's that s'posed to mean?
All right, honestly?
Word is, the man's younger
sister is quite a catch.
You've gotta be kidding me.
[MARIE]
Who is it?
Oh, uh.
Do you two know each other?
Well, actually.
[SWORD] Ah! You must be
the famed Miss Marie!
Yo, get lost, huh?
I can't believe you're
trying to-- Hey!
It's a pleasure to meet
you. Sword's the name.
My condolences.
I'm sorry to hear about your
brother's disappearance.
Such a shame.
Feel free to lean on
me whenever you need.
Single woman, living alone...
I imagine it must be difficult.
If you ever need any help
around the house or anything,
I'm you're man.
Here, these're for you.
Thank you, sir.
Alrighty, then.
Sweet.
Excuse me?
See? I only dropped
by to say hello.
Now, run along home
before it gets dark.
Uh. Yeah.
Behave yourself.
[SOPHIE gasps]
Ugh! What is wrong with me?
Wait here. I'll be
back in a second!
[bell tolls]
Marie.
[SOPHIE] Where d'you
think you're going?
You can't just walk away!
I need to know
what El Dorado is!
Good grief. You're
like a mosquito.
Thing is--
Oh. Hey, Miss Marie.
[SOPHIE]
Hey!
Later days!
[ZARUBA] That little spitfire
is nothing if not determined.
[SWORD]
Yeah, well,
she's throwin' a monkey
wrench into my plan.
Looks as though you'll have
to speed things up a notch.
Yeah, I know.
[MARIE humming]
[SOPHIE]
Sorry about that.
Took a little longer
than I thought it would.
Hope you weren't
worried or anything.
[MARIE]
Perfectly all right.
You figure things
out with your friend?
[SOPHIE]
Meh.
One way or another I'm gonna
have a talk with that man.
You put 'em in water.
Of course.
Awfully nice of him to bring
them, don't you think?
Say, Sophia, would
you stay for dinner?
Sure! Wow, someone's
in high spirits!
Oh? Yes, I suppose I am.
[SOPHIE sighs]
[SOPHIE]
You're a good cook.
Is it rude of me
to ask for seconds?
Oh, my goodness, you
must've been starving.
[SOPHIE chuckles]
I have to be careful when I eat
'cause it makes me kinda sleepy.
Stay the night, then.
I have an extra bed.
[SOPHIE]
Uh.
[MARIE]
Oh, that's right.
The nuns must be
wondering where you are.
Prob'ly.
You should get home
before too long.
This was our quiet hour.
Breaking bread together,
my dear brother and I.
He preferred to take a
shower right after dinner,
then fall asleep reading a book.
I'd always find him conked
out with the lights still on.
For years it was my nightly
ritual to switch them off.
It's odd being just me.
Not sure what to do all alone.
[SOPHIE]
I know how you feel.
Huh?
When I was a kid,
I couldn't fall asleep unless
I knew where Martin was.
That's your brother?
I needed him.
I was afraid of the dark,
but it was fine if he was there.
[MARTIN]
What's so scary?
I just don't like being
by myself at night.
It's too quiet. Makes me feel
like I'm the only person here.
[MARTIN]
Huh.
Hey! What's that?
[MARTIN]
Hi! I'm your bear buddy!
[SOPHIE gasps]
Cute!
There, see? You've got
nothing to be scared of.
I'm here, right?
[MARIE] Your brother
seems exceptionally kind.
You were lucky to have him.
[SOPHIE]
Um, yeah.
I know. We were inseparable.
He's the one who taught
me about computers.
Really?
I remember Father
Ripley being nice.
Yes, um. He was. Very.
In fact, I dare say, my Tom used
to treat me like a princess.
Beautiful. That's what
he used to call me.
Said I was simply too
beautiful for this world.
Sounds like he was
super proud of you.
That's why he always forbade
me from leaving the house.
Why I was never allowed to
wear a proper lady's dress.
Why he never let
me speak to men.
You... You're hurting me. Stop.
Let go!
[SOPHIE]
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
I... You wouldn't--
[MARIE]
It was all my brother's fault.
He was jealous.
Because of him,
I couldn't even...
[SOPHIE]
M-Marie.
You don't understand because
you're still so young.
The world's your oyster.
Stop! Stay where you are!
I will die a lonely and
shriveled old crone,
trapped in this house!
[SOPHIE]
Help!
[MARIE]
He did this to me.
[gasps]
[creak]
Look at me! You did this!
[MARIE]
You turned me into this thing!
[MARIE] I want to eat your
future. Give it to me!
[SOPHIE]
No!
You-You came back!
Idiot. I tried to
warn you, damn it!
Want me to spell it out for ya?
The priest went missing
'cause his sister devoured him!
Stay here! Don't move!
I've gotta help him.
[yells]
[screams]
That was really dumb.
[SOPHIE]
Don't go!
You can't just leave. Not yet.
Tell me what El Dorado is!
[SWORD]
Damn it, girl.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
[SOPHIE] My brother fell off
the face of the Earth.
I... I think a Horror took him.
[SOPHIE]
What's that about?
And if his disappearance
has anything to do
with these creatures,
whatever they are,
then I need the help
of someone like you!
I'm begging you, Sword!
Please help me find my brother!
[SWORD] First things first.
What's his name?
[SOPHIE]
It's Martin. Martin Hennes.
[SWORD]
Hop on.
Let's go get us some tacos.