Yeah, I thought,
"Why starve myself?"
[GANG MEMBER C]
Right? No thanks.
[clanging]
What the hell's up with this?
--[thudding]
--[GANG MEMBERS grunting]
[GANG MEMBER A screams]
We've got trouble.
Lift six, section B.
They're headed up to 60.
[elevator dings]
[GANG MEMBER I]
'Kay...
[thudding]
[alarm blaring]
--[GANG MEMBER J] Freeze!
--[GANG MEMBER K] Hold it!
[GANG MEMBER L]
Hands in the air!
[GANG MEMBER M]
That's it.
[GANG MEMBER N]
Nice and slow.
Chalk it down to a
life lesson, boys.
Can't win 'em all.
[chuckles]
All right, turn
around real slow.
[WOMAN A] Damian, baby,
what's with that look?
Eh, nothin'. Dwellin' on some
unfinished business is all.
'S not a problem.
I've still got this city
by the short hairs.
Little kitten might've
given us the slip,
but sooner or later,
she'll be mine.
[WOMAN A] Oh! I love it
when you talk like that!
This town is yours
for the taking!
So, uh, what's he
got up his sleeve?
Trust me, you'll see
soon enough, kid.
Gonna be a tough job
to do on my own.
Hey, honey. Wanna
have some fun?
Screw you, then.
Jerk.
Likin' the bod. Lemme
have a crack at it.
Stop by sometime. Me and my
girls know how to treat a man.
Hi. So, what rings your bell?
What're you doing?
Paying my respects.
[PROSTITUTE A]
Oh my God! He's dead!
You always did know how
to throw a guy off balance.
Hey, Gina.
Hey, Sword. You're
looking healthy.
[SWORD]
Been a while, hasn't it?
Kinda lonely not having you
around like the old days.
Makai Alchemists tend
to be busy people.
Seems you still
miss no opportunity
to cavort with the ladies.
I do all right.
If I'm lucky, I'll be
cavortin' with you.
[SWORD yelps]
[SWORD] Still got the
same a Ma-juu, huh?
Mia happens to be the best
bodyguard I've ever had.
Slow down, big guy.
I didn't come here
to play with you.
Mia.
Duly noted. I'm guessin' you're
here on account of a job?
[GINA]
Damian Steward.
Not long ago, your
garden variety thug.
Now, one of the top crime
bosses in the city.
Heads a blue-chip,
fortune-500 company.
Soaring through the
ranks like a flare.
Yeah? So?
'S not a terribly unusual
story in his line of work.
Outwardly, no.
But his methods, I have
a sneaking suspicion
Damian's taking
advantage of info
he shouldn't have access to.
The sheer amount is more than
anyone could get their hands on,
let alone process.
So he's a Horror?
Afraid not.
You'd think so, but
I've done the legwork
and everything's
coming up negative.
These are his digs. State
of the art security system.
This room on the top
floor piqued my interest.
I tried breaking into
it on my own already.
Damned if the obstacle
course I was prepared for
hadn't been rearranged.
I don't know how,
but he was expecting me.
That's bizarre.
Sounds to me like a Horror's
gotta be behind it somehow.
Yep. That's always a stickin'
point when dealin' with folks
who ain't on the
straight an' narrow.
They like to keep it low.
Well, all right, then.
I suppose it's a good
thing I didn't come here
to ask for your help.
I say somethin'?
Why you so pissed off?
[GINA]
I just thought,
given Damien's talent
for fact finding,
you might learn a thing
or two about El Dorado.
Hang on a second.
[GINA] Don't say I never
show you a good time.
[MAFIA ELDER A] Thank you
all for coming, gentlemen.
As you're aware,
we have a mutual problem.
This Damian Steward is
overstaying his welcome.
Don't ask me how,
but the simple truth is,
the cocky son of a bitch
is pulling a king's
ransom on our turf.
He's cut into the bottom line
of every man in this room
and it has to stop.
Yeah, he's too comfortable for
my tastes, that's for sure.
I say teach him a lesson,
take him down a few pegs.
If we joined forces, his gang
wouldn't stand a chance.
[gunshots]
[MAFIA ELDER A]
What the--?
The guards! They're dead!
[MAFIA ELDER A]
Fire!
[DAMIAN] Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
Quite a few powerful
old farts for one room.
Huh. Shame I wasn't invited.
Seems like a party.
[gunshot]
Woo. Nice shot.
Good eye, greenhorn.
Bastard. How did you know this
meeting was even taking place?
[DAMIAN chuckles]
I could tell ya.
But showin' you would be
a hellava lot more fun.
Where the hell am I?
[CLEMENZA]
Go on! I know you're there!
Don't toy with me.
If I'm a dead man,
get on with it!
[DAMIAN] This is your
first time, right, kid?
Uh. Yes, sir.
What exactly's
about to happen?
Only the best show in town.
[CLEMENZA]
Huh? What?
[grunting]
Another tasty morsel for
our friend, eh, boys?
[SUBORDINATES laughing]
What did I just see?
Hey, no worries.
Pretty simple, really.
See...
The computer's alive.
[NERO]
What do you mean? Alive how?
What are you talking about?
I had trouble
believing it myself.
Hell, at first,
I figured the damn thing
had to be infected with
some kinda crazy virus.
Till the information
it started bringing me
made spyware look
like child's play.
How do you think
I've come this far?
From third-rate goon to
king of the gahddamned hill.
Insane, I know. But its's true.
See, I knew that
little pussy cat
was gonna break into my place.
I knew those geezers
were meetin' today
to talk about bumpin' me off.
I know it all.
Thing is, though,
if I learned one thing,
it's mana don't come from
heaven without a catch.
[phone buzzing]
[DAMIAN]
The golden goose gets hungry.
In exchange for
priceless information,
I gotta keep it well fed.
As you can see, my friend's
appetites are rather particular.
Yeah?
[SUBORDINATES chuckling]
[DAMIAN]
Everyone!
A toast to the old schoolers
who finally stepped aside!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[DAMIAN] Enjoy yourselves
tonight! Drink up!
[chuckles]
[gasping, chattering]
What's wrong?
[PARTY GIRL A]
Who is that?
[GINA]
Our objective is the top floor.
But there are two hurdles
we have to clear.
First off, we shut down
the security system,
whole building goes offline.
[SWORD]
Makes sense.
Figured as much,
under the circumstances.
Even if he sees us comin',
not much he can do about
it with his defenses down.
[GINA] Won't be a
straightforward cut 'n run.
Only way to shut off the network
is with a keycard
containing Damian's DNA.
That seems a bit complicated.
Worry about your part, I'll
worry about the secret sauce.
[SWORD]
I'm not allowed to be curious?
Sure. Open the
glove compartment.
[gasps]
Hello.
Hello. Haven't seen
you here before.
Sorry. Angie couldn't
make it tonight.
I'm just filling in for her.
Looks like somebody could
use a fresh drink.
What do you say we get you
one so you can talk me up?
You seem interesting.
I'm not gettin' much
sleep tonight, am I?
[DAMIAN chuckles]
[SWORD]
Okay. What's the second hurdle?
[GINA] Once the system's down,
there's a time limit.
We won't have much of a window.
How not much?
[GINA]
Sixty seconds.
Oh, great. Sounds fun.
After that, the security system
will reboot automatically,
so work fast.
It's not ideal, but if
you haven't accessed
the top floor by
the one minute mark,
for all intents and
purposes, we're screwed.
[SWORD]
No, I got it.
I find what Damian's got tucked
away in there, then what?
Heads up: If it's a Horror,
I'm goin' beast mode.
What's my path?
Don't worry.
I've got your access route
planned out to a tee.
[groans]
[thud]
Saw this comin'.
Happens every damn time
I let myself get caught up
in one of her pet projects.
So, what'cha wanna
know about me, babe?
Heh, Let's get that drink first.
Bourbon! Neat!
[GINA]
Or you could try a sip of this.
The flavor really pops.
[DAMIAN] I'm more of a straight
no chaser kinda guy.
Too bad. Straight
is such a bore.
D'you know what
this one's called?
Search me.
[GINA]
Tequila sunrise.
As in, "after a
night of passion."
Well, now, I should be open
to new experiences, right?
Heh. Not everything pans
out the way you want.
Hang on. We're just
gettin' started.
Women take more work than
that, big boy. Stay here.
[WOMAN A]
Earth to Damian.
[DAMIAN] Damn it! Get out
of the way. I can't see!
[WOMAN A]
What's your problem?
[NERO]
Don't move.
What d'you think
you're doin' here?
Your hobby must be stalking.
[NERO]
Shut up!
What is this s'posed--?
[GINA] Why do I get
the feeling you know
precisely what Damian's
hiding up there?
Believe me, you may think you
wanna see it, but you don't.
That a fact?
It's not just a computer!
Son of a-- It may look like
one, but it's not, all right?
It's a monster!
[GINA] Then I suggest
you stay out of my way.
Unless of course you
and your buddies
care to end up on the menu.
[NERO]
What do you mean by that?
Yeah! You believe that crap?
[SUBORDINATE U]
Harsh, man. She's playin' you.
[DAMIAN]
Uppity bitch.
What?
Okay, here goes.
[DAMIAN]
Solid plan you had there.
Then again, I am a
sucker for a pretty face.
You wanna tell me what
all this is about?
[GINA]
Um, actually,
I was just trying to
find the bathroom!
Then, that man, right there!
He told me to swipe this card
when he gave me
the signal or else.
[DAMIAN] Sweetheart, c'mon.
Have some dignity.
[GINA] I'm sorry!
What was I supposed to do?
He was terrifying!
--[GINA crying]
--[NERO] Huh?
[DAMIAN]
I'll bet.
No worries.
I'm gonna take my sweet time
gettin' to the bottom of this.
Besides, seems the big scary
man is about to meet my friend.
Perfect timing.
Alrighty, then.
[SUBORDINATES chuckling]
[SWORD]
You gotta be kidding me!
[yells]
What the--? How did he--?
[SWORD]
Hm?
[SUBORDINATE W]
Boss. What are you gonna do?
[DAMIAN]
Oh, no!
Run, you idiots!
Don't just stand there!
[SUBORDINATES screaming]
Damn it, Sword!
What's taking so long?
[SWORD]
Huh?
That's your true form.
You really think now's
the best time for this?
Shut your mouth!
This is on you! All of it!
[GINA] That thing would've
devoured you eventually.
You do understand that.
So be it! Law of
the jungle, babe!
First you eat,
then you're eaten!
[DAMIAN]
Nero. You son of a--
Okay. This is bad.
[NERO]
Wait!
What for? Why save
a guy like that?
I don't understand.
Who-Who are you?
What is it you're after?
I can't thank you
enough for the help.
[GINA] Sorry you couldn't dig
anything up about El Dorado.
[SWORD groans]
[SWORD]
"Prominent gangster Damian,
shot as retribution by mafia."
[GINA]
So much for sparing his life.
Best not to get tangled up
in the affairs of humans, right?
Takin' off already?
I'll come back around
when a job warrants it,
if it's interesting.
Hit me up, huh? It's
always good to see ya.
And maybe bring that bikini.
[SERVER A]
Um, excuse me, sir?
If I may say so,
it's awfully nice of you
to square the lady's bill.
She'd run up quite a tab.
[SWORD]
Thanks, Gina.