[bird squawks]
[MAN 12A]
Sorry to bother you.
I'm looking for my friend.
I haven't heard from him
since he came out
this way a while back.
[MATTHEW]
Yeah, he stayed the night.
When was that?
Took off first thing in the
morning, if I remember right.
Where in the world did he go?
I appreciate the help, sir.
Dusk before you
know it out here.
[MAN 12A]
Uh?
Why risk your neck? I recommend
you take one of our rooms.
Only a fool lets himself get
caught outside after dark.
There's no one else here.
I can give you a suite
for next to nothing.
[MAN 12A]
How can I say no?
Thank you.
[MAN 12A sighs]
[MAN 12A]
Mm?
The hell?
That's weird.
[MAN 12A screams]
[GINA]
Hard to stomach, isn't it?
[gasps]
I take it you've never
been this far west?
These days it's basically
a demilitarized zone.
It's depressing.
[GINA]
You're looking at the product
of a deregulated
chemical industry.
Corporations ravaged
the environment.
People migrated east in
search of a better life.
Cities, towns, land,
everything went belly up.
Some folks hauled up
stakes for elsewhere,
while others stayed behind.
But can't we do
something to help?
Aside from eliminating Horrors?
Not really, no.
It's not our job to save
humanity from itself.
Kinda messed up way
of seein' things.
[SWORD]
I've got some bad news for you.
It's 300 miles to the next town.
S'pose we'll have
to rough it again.
Come on! That'd make
three nights in a row!
We're in the middle of nowhere,
you were expecting a spa?
Gimme a break.
At least you ladies
get to snooze with a
roof over your heads.
You've got a car.
I've got a ratty
ol' sleeping bag.
My back's killing me.
No one cares about
your stupid back.
[SWORD] Oh, really? Keep
giving me lip, short stuff.
Gina an' me'll take the car and
you can have the sleeping bag.
See how you like it.
[SOPHIE]
Whatever.
[SWORD]
Quit being a brat!
[GINA] I'm not sharing
the car with you.
[SWORD]
Ouch.
[SOPHIE] There's gotta be
something around here.
[SOPHIE]
Uh. Jackpot!
Huh?
[SOPHIE]
Over there! Look!
Way out toward the highway.
I think it's a motel.
[SOPHIE]
Hello!
[GINA]
Any vacancies?
[MATTHEW]
You're in luck.
Room number one.
[SOPHIE gasping]
Awesome!
--Sophie...
--[SOPHIE laughs]
Thank you very much.
Drop by the front desk
if you need anything.
My name's Matthew, by the way.
[SWORD]
Why is this place even here?
[SOPHIE]
Sword!
Huh?
They've totally got a room!
[SWORD]
Cool.
Yes! I can finally
take a shower!
Oh my god, they'll have pillows!
You'll have to sleep on
the floor, though.
Me and Gina are calling
dibs on the beds.
[gasps]
Who was that guy?
[SOPHIE gasping]
Hello, bed!
Hello, chair! Hello, fridge!
It's like I'm in heaven.
[SWORD yawns]
I'd settle for dreamland.
Me, too. Who'd have thought
we'd find a motel out here.
Talk about a snowball's
chance in hell.
[SWORD sighs] My lumbar's taken
just about all it can stand.
Hey, Gina.
Grab me somethin' cold, huh?
[SOPHIE]
Same, please!
I look like waitress to you?
[SWORD, SOPHIE]
No.
[GINA]
Heh.
[SOPHIE]
Which bed d'you want?
This one's comfy,
but I bet both of 'em are.
Yeah, makes no difference to me.
For real? You're cool
with letting me pick?
[SWORD snoring]
Okay. Didn't take him long.
He must've been exhausted.
[SOPHIE]
Mm?
What's your name?
I'm guessing you're
the owner's kid?
I'm Sophie. We just
got in a little bit ago.
[GEORGE grunting]
[SOPHIE]
Hand ball!
[laughs]
She'll be fine.
It's just the parking lot.
[SWORD] How do they
stay in business?
They're in the
middle of nowhere.
Who's the clientele?
That's the million-dollar
question.
Yeah. Well, we'll just have
to keep our eyes peeled.
[SWORD gasping]
[SWORD whimpers]
[MIA growls]
I deserved that.
[MIA grunts]
[SOPHIE]
Wow.
Super cool we're the same age.
Those two people
you're traveling with,
are they like your
brother and sister?
Who, them? No way.
Just friends of mine.
Actually, we've come all
the way from Russell City.
You're joking, right?
That's where we used to live
before my dad
dragged us out here.
Whoa, seriously?
You ever been to that hotdog
stand over on Third?
You know the one
I'm talkin' about?
[GEORGE]
Yeah! All the time!
Dad used to take me there!
[SOPHIE] So, why'd you move,
if that's not too personal.
[GEORGE] The company he
worked for went bankrupt.
We pretty much lost everything.
[SOPHIE]
Oh. Must've been rough.
[GEORGE] It changed him.
Not in a good way, either.
Since we've been here, he's
always worried about money.
But, I mean, things
could be a lot worse.
At least we're together.
Family's good.
My bad.
I shouldn't have brought it up.
I don't get to talk
with very many people.
[SOPHIE]
I know how you feel.
I have a brother.
He went missing.
I'd give anything for us
to be together again.
Live the way we used
to when we were little.
Us against the world.
Cheer up!
I have a feeling your dad'll
come around eventually.
[SWORD]
The life's returning!
[MATTHEW]
Where you goin' from here,
if you don't mind my asking?
[SOPHIE]
Oh, uh.
The idea's for us to
head out further west.
Oh, I see.
So Eldorado, then?
[gasps]
Don't suppose you've
ever been there yourself?
[MATTHEW] No, no. Just had
more 'n handful of customers
mention the name
recently. That's all.
Seems, uh, like quite
the happy place,
'least to hear them tell it.
So they say. To be fair, we're
a bit sketchy on the details.
Helluva lot of rumors
flying around, though.
We got curious.
[MATTHEW]
Can't say I blame you.
Honestly.
Whatever it is, I'm grateful for
the customers it's brought me.
Good night, folks.
[MATTHEW]
Not enough. Not even close.
We need more.
Living in the city is expensive.
Raising a family is expensive.
[knob squeaks]
Assholes. I'm a joke to them.
They think it's funny
what I'm going through,
bending over backward
to make ends meet.
It's late.
Honey, please. Let's go to bed.
How the hell is this
supposed to be enough
to get us in the black?
Sweetheart.
I couldn't help
but notice the safe.
Where did that money come from?
[MATTHEW]
Don't worry about it.
[SARA] Why don't I ever
see our guests leave?!
[MATTHEW] I told you.
They check out early.
What's wrong?! You're so
distant with us now!
You treat your own son
like some kind of stranger!
I'm trying to work.
You're involved in
something dangerous,
don't think I don't know!
Stop it! You sound--
What? Go on, tell me
I'm out of my mind!
Tell me I'm crazy
for wanting
the three of us to be
a family again!
[MATTHEW] Shut up! I don't
have time for this bullshit!
That's what we are to
you? Huh? Bullshit?
If you think I'm going
to let you do anything
to that little girl, you're
the one who's crazy!
There! Satisfied?
I'm doin' this for you!
[SARA]
Is that what you tell yourself?
We never wanted this!
Don't you dare!
Oh, yeah?
You're not livin' the dream?
[SARA groaning]
[MATTHEW] What have I been
busting my ass for, then?
You parasite! All you do
is take, take, take!
If you want to die like
an animal in this shithole,
go right ahead!
Please stop...
This isn't us.
This isn't us!
I have to go back.
Have to get out of here.
This place is eating me alive.
It's a wasteland.
There's nothing.
[SWORD]
I'm sleeping next to Gina.
End of story.
As if. You just want an excuse
to stare at her chest all night.
You don't get it, do you?
You think I'm just
some kind of creep.
Try to see things from
my perspective, kid.
What are you talking about?
A'right, look.
Boobies are holy.
When I gaze at a pair I'm taking
part in an age-old sacrament.
Without boobies, you an'
I wouldn't even exist!
They're the wellspring
of humanity!
The source from
which all life flows
like a river of mother's milk!
The literal bosom of all
that is pure and good!
One has only has to consider
Western art's lionization
of the female form.
Boobs, bazongas, breasts!
Worshipped as the symbol of life
since the dawn of mankind!
They're a beacon.
The linchpin of the world.
The twin pillars
of civilization.
Ignore them, and life as we
know it shrivels up and dies
like a melon without water.
Boobies are the single most
revered and precious thing
in the universe!
You're a creep.
[SWORD] Strike that.
Boobies are the universe!
[SOPHIE] Welcome back!
You're just in time.
Where'd you go?
Just looking around.
I have an idea.
What do you say we ditch this
weirdo and have us a nice bath?
Sounds wonderful.
Awesome! Let's wash our hair!
[SWORD]
As a matter of fact--
[SOPHIE]
Pervert.
I'm no pervert, Sophie.
Merely a devotee.
As I've explained,
boobs are a holy thing.
Disagree if you want,
but the reality is
we wouldn't be
here otherwise.
Every man, woman and
child owes them a debt.
Heh.
[MATTHEW growls]
Son of a bitch!
[GINA]
Hey.
You sweet on the motel
owner's son yet, or what?
Huh? Oh, you're talking
about George.
[GINA] Mm. You already
remember his name.
[SOPHIE]
Yeah, so?
So? Is he cute?
[SOPHIE]
Ew! Don't be gross!
--It's not like that!
--Alright, fine. Calm down, hon.
[SOPHIE]
Besides, I just met him.
Easy there, Mia!
Were you eavesdropping?
[SWORD]
...their shape alone
has inspired many an
accomplished artist.
So, uh, do you have
crush on anyone, or?
Oh-ho. That's a very
personal question.
[SOPHIE]
C'mon, you can tell me!
There has to be someone!
I'm sorry, darling.
You're too young.
Details are strictly
adults-only.
[HORROR 12A growls]
[GINA]
Sophie.
[SOPHIE]
Yeah?
You remember what we told you
on our way out here, don't you?
Sure.
We can only protect people
by eliminating Horrors.
Even then, the price
they pay is high.
In the end, no battle
can help but leave
a trail of collateral
damage in its wake.
There's nothing we can do
about the pain victims
feel afterwards.
I don't understand.
[MIA growls]
[GINA grunts]
[HORROR 12A roars]
[GINA]
Get back!
[HORROR 12A growls]
[HORROR 12A roars]
Girls! You okay?
Yes. Looks like we're dealing
with a liquid-form Horror.
[SWORD muffled]
Interesting.
You didn't waste
much time tonight.
[MATTHEW] What's wrong?
Did the prey not taste good?
[SARA gasping]
Sara. I thought I told you
never to come down here.
Wha... What is that thing?
[MATTHEW]
Ah. Just a friend.
My ticket back to the life
we had to leave behind
when the company tanked.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
Then listen closely.
After we came here,
I saw this creature
attack a guest.
Gruesome sight to walk
in on, let me tell you.
I was terrified.
[MATTHEW gasping]
[MATTHEW whimpers]
[MATTHEW]
When I saw it,
I thought to myself: why me?
I'm just trying to
run a motel here.
How am I supposed to make a
profit when my guests get eaten?
But you know what?
It didn't take long for me
to see the potential.
This was manna from heaven.
My shot at finally
turning it all around.
I never belonged here.
Russell City is the
only place for me.
[gasps] Matthew. Stop this.
You've gone insane!
Can't you see what
this means for us?!
This is it! Our once-in-
a-lifetime chance!
[HORROR 12A]
Tell me what you wish for.
[gasps]
[HORROR 12A]
What do you desire most?
I have the power
to make it real.
[MATTHEW]
Then...
...I cannot bear to keep
living this way any longer!
Please! Help me!
Let me start over!
Don't let me die out here
in the desert with nothing!
Matthew...
[MATTHEW]
I don't care what it takes!
Let me ride your wave of glory
all the way back
to Russell City!
[MATTHEW screams]
No!
Matthew! No!
No! Please stop!
[SARA gasping]
[whimpers, screams]
Leave it to us.
[HORROR 12A growls]
[SARA]
What is this?
What in God's name is going on?
Stay where you are.
[SWORD]
We've got this.
[gasps] Oh, no!
Where's my son?
[HORROR 12A roars]
C'mon, Mom!
Get in!
[HORROR 12A growls]
[HORROR 12A roars]
[SWORD]
Fade away into the darkness!
[HORROR 12A roars]
[SARA cries]
Matthew.
[SARA sobs]
Matthew...
[GINA] They don't remember it
as it actually happened.
They think the motel
was hit by a storm.
It's sad, Matthew got crushed.
That's all we could do?
We couldn't try to save him?
Once you're possessed
by a Horror,
reverting to your old
self isn't a thing.
You just go on devouring
innocent bystanders.
[GINA]
Let's move.
Right.