[BISHOP hums]
Doctor Stanley, my friend!
How goes the work?
[DR. STANLEY]
Quite well.
My control simulations suggest
the fusion experiment's
objective is in sight.
[BISHOP laughs]
Don't go too easy
on the tests, now.
We want this stage to
be an extravagant one!
[SWORD] If Gina's intel checks
out, there's a giant mountain
'tween us and El Dorado.
You need gas?
No need to worry about me.
You're the one who looks
like you've been hung out wet.
Huh?
Aw, c'mon.
What is that about?
She's been ticked
off since this morning.
[GINA]
Quit leaning out the window.
Sorry.
I'm just trying to get Sword
to pay attention for once.
He's gonna get sick
of that real quick.
[SOPHIE]
Eh!
He's the one
who ate all my chocolate
without even bothering
to ask if it was okay.
Typical MO.
I know, right?
What's worse is that
it was the stuff I got
from Ferre Salé Dessimo,
which is like, rare or whatever!
And I didn't just get
it for myself, either.
It was for us three to share!
Ugh. Is there a worse
crime in existence?
Hey! Don't be sarcastic!
Huh?
Gina, look!
Is that?
[SOPHIE]
Wow.
Not really what I was expecting.
Miiyaaahh!
What? You weren't hoping for
paradise this far out, were you?
It'll only get bleaker
the further we go.
This is probably the closest
thing we'll have to a rest stop
before El Dorado, so I advise
you to gird your loins.
[SWORD] Stay here overnight,
head out at dawn?
Sounds like a plan.
Cool?
Gimme a break.
How long are you
gonna stay pissed off?
You ate my chocolate
without asking.
Ugh, look,
I told I'm sorry, a'right?
That's just it, though:
you're not!
You pulled the same
thing the other day
when you drank
the last of my juice!
Plus your snoring
keeps everybody awake,
and you use way too
much toothpaste!
'Kay, I get it.
Calm down.
Let's go find a
convenience store.
Go by yourself!
I'm staying right here.
Sweetie, don't.
[SWORD]
Hmph!
Have at it.
[SOPHIE]
I will, thank you very much!
You're not the only human
being in the world
who likes a little solitude.
Man, this is the last time
I agree to a babysitting job.
[SOPHIE]
Huh?
Babysitting?
Uh!
That's not...!
[sighs]
Let's push it back to ten.
Just, do your own thing
for tonight and relax.
We'll meet up back
here in the morning.
Miyaah!
[GANG MEMBER A] Yeah!
That's right. You better run!
[RUFFIAN B]
Hola.
Huh?!
[RUFFIAN C]
Hey, chiquita.
You all by yourself?
Come 'ere.
Look, I know you're mad.
But this place
will eat you alive.
I'm a moron.
What do you say we find
a hotel room with a bath?
'Kay!
So cute.
Bet eet's good.
Sí, I know.
But eet's way too much.
We don't have the money.
[GIRL]
But I'm so hungry.
Wow!
Muchas gracias, señor!
[BOY]
Adios!
Gracias!
Choco-Choco-Chocolate.
Huh?
[GANG MEMBER B]
Where you goin', maricon?
[GANG MEMBER A]
Run all you want!
You're dead man, Pedro!
[GANG MEMBER B]
I'll give you this, cabrón:
you've got cojones.
Brains?
Not so much.
[GANG MEMBER A]
Think you can take Gordon?
En serio?
Carajo.
M-M-Monica.
[GANG MEMBER A]
Wha?
Who you s'posed to be?
Huh?
Ah!
[GANG MEMBER B]
Huh? Que? Donde?
[groans]
So think before you leap, huh?
Uh... What the...?
Whoa! Hold on a second!
What are you? Like a fighter?
C'mon, what the
hell's your story?
Oye!
You local or what?
Hey! Espera!
Let me at least
buy you some food
for saving my ass
back there, man!
I know some people
who run a place.
[SWORD]
Don't worry about it.
You can't be serious.
What if I said
the owner had curves?
[SWORD]
Hmm?
Trust me, her body doesn't quit.
Idiota. Would it kill you to
use your head for once, chico?
What's wrong?
Hey, show some respect, amigo.
I swear, she was the prettiest
woman around, back in the day.
Twenty years ago.
Ay, Pedro, if you don't stop
with this revenge nonsense
that gang is going to kill you.
So? Let 'em do what they want!
And I...
I'll make sure
they go down with me!
[SWORD]
Hmm.
[WOMAN]
Hmmm.
Keep telling yourself that.
Uno más, señor.
[PEDRO] So, uh,
you traveling alone, or..?
[SWORD]
Something like that, yeah.
[PEDRO]
That's perfect.
There's actually a favor
I wanted to ask you.
That's good.
I know!
Hey! Look, guys! It's Pedro!
[CUSTOMER B]
Oh-ho!
Crybaby Pedro!
Wow. Look at you.
Someone was trying to be
a one-man army again.
Ha! That's pathetic!
What's the matter with you?
You keep picking fights,
Gordon and his boys will
feed you to the pigs.
Get a life, hombre!
Think you're
crying now, chillon?
Wait till you end
up like Monica!
Take it easy, cabron.
I'd stay down if I were you.
[laughter]
Culeros!
I'm not playing games!
Gordon will pay for what he did!
I swear it!
I... I will drag to him hell!
T' hell!
[GINA]
It's just for one night.
He's more than capable
of handling himself.
I acted like
such a brat, though.
He's probably sick of me.
I didn't mean to say
all that stuff, I just.
We're all tired, sweetheart,
you get a Mulligan.
[SOPHIE sighs]
Still, though,
I wouldn't blame him
for abandoning me.
[GINA]
Sword?
Abandon you?
Not a chance.
Sure, it's his job to protect
people, but you don't
really think that's all
this is for him, right?
Don't worry too much, okay?
I can personally guarantee you
he'll be there when we leave.
Hey, I think somebody
could use a pedicure.
Yes!
I want pink toenails!
I don't do pink.
Pick something else.
Seriously?
[PEDRO chuckles]
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to make
a scene back there.
Sit down, please.
Least the alcohol was cheap.
Huh?
[PEDRO]
That's Monica.
[PEDRO] My future never
looked all that bright.
But as long as she was
with me, things were good.
Last year, she was murdered.
In this town, Gordon
and his gang call the shots.
All the girls here have to be...
Gordon thinks of them
as his property.
Bastard.
I'm just gonna come right
out and say it.
I wanna take him down,
and I'm gonna need your help.
Look, I swear,
all you need to worry about
is distracting his guys.
I'll worry about their jefe.
You're just going
to wind up dead.
So what--I don't care!
I'll die happy knowing
I killed the son of a bitch!
No, seriously.
I am serious!
I've got nothing, look at me.
If I die, no one gives a damn.
Monica was my whole world.
Without her there's
no reason to live!
Listen to yourself.
You think that's how Monica
would want you to go out?
Oh. Callate!
She's not here!
Who knows what
the hell she'd want?
I wanna finish this!
I will finish this!
When Lizzy died I felt
the exact same way you do.
[gasps]
A world without her in it
had no place for me either.
The thought of facing the future
alone was like stepping up
to the edge of an abyss.
Thing is...
There's no one left to remember
her if I let myself die.
Huh?
Yeah. That's right.
It's all up to me.
I have a responsibility
to keep her memory alive.
But how can I just...
I don't have to
listen to you, man!
You don't even know me.
I didn't...
I didn't expect you
to help me anyway.
Deep down, you're just a coward!
[SWORD]
Sorry.
I'll go.
[PEDRO sobs]
[SHOP OWNER] We have evidence
that strongly suggests Horrors
were involved in the massive
explosion at Cygnusram-Tech.
Sadly, our database
was unsalvageable.
The only piece of
information recovered
was the as yet unknown
term: El Dorado.
Needless to say, your training
will proceed as planned.
We have every hope you'll become
an incomparable Golden Knight.
My condolences
about your sister.
[ONLOOKER A] Some kind
research facility, wasn't it?
[ONLOOKER B] Yeah. Part of
Cygnusram-Tech, apparently.
The fire came out of nowhere.
I've never seen
anything so awful!
[ONLOOKER C] Worst part is
there was a school next door.
Dozens of kids in
the middle of class.
[ONLOOKER D]
Can you imagine?
They said there
were no survivors.
Um, 's it gotta be spinach?
Eat up.
Future Golden Knights
can't be picky.
'Sides, it's good for you.
But it tastes like
pure distilled hatred.
Do you complain
this much at the gym?
I thought you were
trying to bulk up?
No pain, no gain.
Isn't that the mantra?
Well, extend it to eating
vegetables and stop whining.
It's an acquired taste.
After all, we must enjoy life
to the fullest. See ya later!
[LIZZY sobs]
I won't rest till
every Horror's dead.
I promise.
Huh?
I will always
protect you, Lizzy.
[gasps]
Hey, Lizzy.
Have I become the kind of Golden
Knight you can be proud of?
I bet he doesn't show up.
He probably just overslept.
He'll be here.
Trust me, hon.
Sword's a man of his word.
He doesn't have it
in him to bail.
[PEDRO]
Damn it!
See, I'm the kinda' guy
who when you go for my throat
I answer by
dragging you to hell.
Nice and slow.
I... I swear I'll kill you.
Huh? Más alta, porfa.
[PEDRO]
For her. For Monica!
Mira, the pinche cabron
is talking revenge!
So sorry.
First time I heard
of this Monica.
Prob'ly some dirty puta
from the gutter, eh?
You can't be surprised
if I don't remember her.
Bastardo.
[GORDON]
That's enough, chico.
What is this?
I don't think I like
the way you look at me.
Huh?
Huh?!
Ugh! What the hell? Who's he?
Freeze, gringo!
A donde vas?
No me dejes!
[GORDON]
Calmate, chico.
Please! Don't do this!
If it's women you want,
we can work something out.
[PEDRO gasps]
[PEDRO]
A charm?
[MONICA]
Sí.
It's supposed to grant wishes.
[PEDRO]
No kidding?
What do you wish for?
Whenever it breaks,
I'm going to leave here.
This isn't the kind of place
I want to spend
the rest of my life.
You feel the same way,
don't you, Pedro?
Ah. Yeah!
Sure!
Let's leave this town together!
Getting out of here
won't be cheap, you know.
Then we'd better
start saving our money.
Okay.
We'll have to work very hard.
But yeah,
I think we have a chance!
Come on, think positive!
A chance?
There's nothing to it!
Yeah!
[sobs]
Monica!
Oh god!
[GORDON pants]
I don't know what that's about,
and I don't want to!
[SOPHIE]
Um, I, uh...
Yeah, so...
Yesterday, I-- Well I, uh...
Look, it's on me.
I shouldn't've made
that stupid comment.
Huh?! Wha? Oh...
It isn't the same kind, but...
[GINA chcukles]
You were late because
you stopped to buy chocolate?
Um, sure.
I guess so.
Wait!
It didn't come like that!
[GINA] Then what happened
to it on the way here?
[SWORD]
Just stuff!
You know!
[GINA]
Really?
I love it!
This way it's easier to share!
Have some!
After all, we must
enjoy life to the fullest!
Words of wisdom.
You're the best Sword, thanks!
[SWORD]
Hey, it's the least I could do.
[laughs]
Myaah...
Mya!
[gasps]
Huh? What is going on?
Mi-mi-mi-mi!
Myah!