How much further we have to go?
[LIZZY]
About seven hundred meters.
It's on the other side
of that wall.
Okay, hold on!
We're doin' this
the old-fashioned way!
[SOPHIE shrieks]
[LIZZY] I'm forcing a link
to the main server.
Connection's good.
We're in!
Worse ways to make
an entrance 'f you ask me.
Um...
Okay.
What is this?
[LIZZY]
The King's sovereign domain.
He sustains himself
by devouring lost souls.
This is where he feeds.
It's about to become
the hill he dies on.
Just be careful.
I'll lead Sophie
to the storage unit.
You ready?
[SOPHIE]
Huh?
Heads up!
[DARK KNIGHT laughs]
I see your attack
style is maturing.
And yet, it's all for nothing!
Hope you like what
I got on the agenda, sweetheart.
Yeah, 'fraid you won't be
getting to Sword anytime soon.
[LIZZY]
Watch out.
Both of you are logged into
the system body and soul,
which means you're vulnerable.
[SWORD]
Body and soul?
[LIZZY]
Yes.
Think of it as a
backchannel that allows you
to go full out as
a Makai Knight.
The tradeoff?
I'm no longer your gatekeeper
to the physical world.
I had to forfeit that
talent to get you here.
[SWORD] Then I'll be
damned if we waste it!
Go on.
Just take care of Sophie
She's safe.
Count on it.
[SOPHIE]
Hey, um...
Not sure how to ask you this
without sounding awkward.
Yes. I'm his little sister.
Look, I have no idea what
he's told you about me,
but not even Sword
knows the whole story.
For now, let's just focus
on saving the world, huh?
You're the only one who
can deactivate ELDO NET.
That's quite a thing.
But don't worry.
I'm here for you.
Lizzy's got your back!
[SOPHIE]
Thanks.
We're here.
The access terminal
that connects
to the main storage unit.
Deep breath.
[DARK KNIGHT]
Not as skilled shooting up close
and personal, are you?
The past still has
a hold over you.
It severely limits
your ability to focus.
[LUKE] I will not break ties
with where I come from.
I refuse.
Despite your philosophy.
That's not weakness!
[LIZZY] This might be tricky,
so prepare yourself.
[SOPHIE]
'Kay, what do I do?
[LIZZY] Only two people have
system admin privileges,
Martin Hennes,
obviously, and you.
Jump on and access
the main terminal.
Figure out the
deactivation password.
What's happening?
[SOPHIE gasps]
[SWORD]
The Hell?
[KING]
Beware.
Here you are no more than food.
Here will you eternally
sate my hunger,
as mankind has done
since time out of mind.
Embrace the darkness
and know everlasting peace.
In the void with in me,
all things become as one.
[KING] Let die the
excoriating light and succumb.
[SOPHIE]
I-I don't understand.
[LIZZY] It's the
King's security protocol.
The ancient one's
decided to show himself.
[BISHOP] Translation:
Your noble attempt is at an end.
Sorry.
Good evening, ladies.
I wonder if you'd like
to play a little game?
Oh-ho...!
You'll never
land a decisive blow.
Your edge is too dull!
You've got some nice moves.
I'll give you that.
But I'm not losing
to a fallen Alchemist!
[KING]
So predictable.
Mankind never changes.
Struggling.
Rejecting annihilation.
No matter the era.
Again and again
I crush you underfoot,
yet you scuttle back with
the tenacity of roaches.
Lizzy.
What are you doing?
Sophie!
Back away!
Now! You'll be absorbed
into the system!
[BISHOP] Some people just
don't know when to quit.
Your friend has lost
this one, my dear.
The Golden Knight is
officially extinguished.
Sophie!
[SOPHIE]
I don't believe you.
Sword doesn't have it
in him to lose!
Because he's the strongest
Makai Knight who's ever lived!
[KING]
There is no longer anyone
who can lay a hand
on this sacrosanct realm.
All obstacles have been removed.
Supernal tranquility
shall flow unobstructed.
[SWORD]
What are you, a damn thesaurus?
Why do bad guys
always monologue?
Huh? How is this possible?
[SWORD]
Clichéd reaction.
Let's just say life
is complicated.
[SWORD]
On the one hand,
it hurts like an
absolute son of a bitch.
I wouldn't go so
far as to call it ugly,
but it sure knows
how to make a face.
On the opposite
end of the spectrum,
life is beautiful.
Champagne, roses, the whole bit.
In the middle,
there's the wild card.
A little thing called hope.
That's where we come in.
[SWORD]
See.
Pain is what makes the job hard.
[SWORD]
But hope?
That's what makes
the job mean something.
[SWORD]
I'm no stranger to darkness.
I just don't give it
the last word.
'S what it means
to be a Makai Knight.
What it means
to be one who protects.
Golden Knight Garo!
[KING]
Fascinating.
Let us see how you
fare after I've destroyed
your capacity for hope!
[LUKE]
Do what you want with me.
I won't let you go.
Even if my body crumbles to ash,
you will never reach him!
Well done!
[gasps]
Wait a second.
Sophie!
We need to go!
Right!
Good bye, my King.
Come on.
Get your ass back here.
[ZARUBA]
Sword!
These are just pieces of data!
There's no end to them!
[SWORD] Then we go
straight for the source!
[SWORD]
Ugh! Damn it!
[KING]
Futile.
This world and I
are one and the same.
You cannot vanquish me.
[SWORD]
Then I guess it looks like
I have to take out
an entire world!
Zaruba!
[ZARUBA]
Ready!
Here!
Use this!
[SWORD]
Yes!
Let's do it!
[SWORD roars]
It can't be.
Garo.
Huh? Well. What's this now?
King's disappeared.
Incredible!
Sophie!
There's only one way
to save your brother!
You have to destroy
the storage unit!
I... I don't want
anyone else to die.
Help me.
Give me strength.
Whatever you've got!
This is for Sword!
Please! Help me protect him!
[girl crying]
[SOPHIE gasps]
Don't cry, Sophie.
I'm always gonna be
right here beside you.
[SOPHIE]
Martin.
[MARTIN]
Sorry.
I, uh...
I did kind of crappy job
keeping my promise.
[SOPHIE]
Don't say that!
It's not true!
You did everything you could!
At the end of the day
all of this was for me!
I know it.
I have the best
brother in the world!
You just wanted me
to smile again.
You're right.
Yeah.
That's it.
That's everything.
Well, here you go, then.
[SOPHIE gasps]
[LIZZY]
Sophie!
Are you hurt?
Talk to me, please!
Thank you, Martin.
Thank you.
Huh?
Honestly.
This is the path you've
chosen for yourself?
I wouldn't expect
you to understand.
You've done it, Sophie.
ELDO NET is no more.
Guess this is my exit.
Do me a favor if it's
not too much trouble.
Take care of him.
Sure.
Consider it done.
Thanks.
Oh, and if you can, tell the
big lug it wouldn't kill him
to eat a vegetable
every now and again.
See ya round.
[SOPHIE]
Bye, Lizzy.
Take care.
Man, I don't think
I've ever been so tired.
What d'you say we go home
an' eat till we explode?
[chuckles]
Or...
How many times
do I have to tell you?
No two-bit harlot off the
street gets a ride from me.
[SWORD]
Hmph!
Aw, c'mon!
That's now where I was goin'!