[QUEEN]
A perfect plan?
The Golden Knight
is inching his way closer.
[BISHOP]
It's no matter.
We have options.
The "princess"
needn't be an issue.
[PEDRO] I'm just gonna
come right out and say it.
I wanna take him down,
and I'm gonna need your help.
When Lizzy died, I felt
the exact same way you do.
Thing is...
There's no one left to remember
her if I let myself die.
[PEDRO gasps]
Monica!
[sobs]
[BISHOP]
Doctor Stanley, my friend!
How goes the work?
[DR. STANLEY]
Quite well.
My control simulations suggest
the fusion experiment's
objective is in sight.
Don't go too
easy on the tests, now.
We want this stage
to be an extravagant one.
[gasps]
Huh? What is going on?
Mi-mi-mi-mi!
Myah!
Um, what is that?
Ugh. Smells like a sewer.
They're legion!
A whole battalion of Horrors!
How far away
are we from El Sanvados?
Sixty-two miles
south by southwest.
Right through the center
of that mountain range.
I'll meet you there.
Take care of Sophie.
Got it.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Sophie.
I need you to do
whatever Gina says.
I've got this.
None of these uglies're
gonna lay a finger on you.
Sword, wait!
Ah, it's to be the
predictable move, I see.
[BISHOP laughs]
Should be interesting
at least, though.
Let us see how the
all-powerful Garo fares
against numbers like these.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Looks like the bad guys
are goin' all-out.
[ZARUBA]
Prudent, in their way.
They know not to
try you one-on-one.
Right!
Throttle the Golden Knight
but spare the feisty
young girl for His Majesty.
Of course. I'm sure one or
two trifling little injuries
can be overlooked
[SWORD]
A massive roving barrier.
I didn't think Horrors
could be that organized.
[ZARUBA] That's what I call
piling stink upon stink.
I know, right?
Welp, whadda say we clean house?
Let's do it!
C'mon! Turn us around!
Sword'll get himself killed!
We've got to go back!
Please!
Gina!
--[GINA] Shut up!
--[SOPHIE] Huh?
[BISHOP chuckles]
And... au 'voir.
[SWORD gasps]
He's here.
[BISHOP] Why don't you make
this easy and surrender?
We mean you no harm, I promise.
Come along quietly
and be done with it.
You seem like a
reasonable creature.
Accept that this is the end.
Garo's only mortal, after all.
Surely you don't want
your Alchemist friend there
to meet with the same fate?
[GINA]
Duck!
I didn't get him.
Rat bastard.
Should've expected as much.
Seems these unruly little
wenches prefer to play it rough.
Hold on to your ass, kid.
Did we, uh..?
'Kay.
Sophie, darling, pull on
that lever behind your seat.
[GINA]
Don't worry about trying to aim.
Just keep shooting.
Fire!
Huh?! Yes!
[pants]
We might've found your weapon.
[SOPHIE shrieks]
Gina!
[SOPHIE]
Luke!
It's Luke!
Nice shootin' there, hot stuff.
Your timing's impeccable.
I'll handle the rest of 'em.
Holy crap.
The Land of Guidance
must've set him up
with a pretty hardcore
firing range.
[SOPHIE]
Whoa.
[GINA]
Well, well.
Looks like the
barrier's defunct.
El Sanvados is
on the other side.
We're just about there.
[gasps]
G... Gina.
What do you know,
we've reached this level's boss.
Dear, oh dear.
You really should've
taken me up on my offer.
If you'd surrendered,
I wouldn't have had
to resort to such tactics.
They distilled
the power of Horrors
and infused them into a machine.
That's how they're able
to be active in daylight.
What a load of bullshit.
[gasps]
Sophie!
Sorry. That one's on me.
Should've moved quicker.
Hey, Luke.
Been a while, huh?
Oh, hey.
No rest for the weary!
Talk to me.
Zaruba.
Please tell me Sword's okay!
There is more to that
lug head than meets the eye.
So we're keeping a low profile
until this blows over.
[SOPHIE]
Are you... Are you all right?
Does it hurt?
[ZARUBA]
What exactly do you take me for?
[SOPHIE]
Sorry.
[ZARUBA]
It's all right.
I'll have them fix me up
once we get to El Dorado.
That's assuming they
have anything resembling
a repair shop in the vicinity.
[SOPHIE]
No, really.
I'm useless.
I can't do anything.
Everyone has to protect me.
Sword.
Gina.
Luke.
Even you.
And look what good it's done.
I don't...
Why? Why are they targeting me?
I'm sorry.
All that I ever wanted was
to try and find my brother.
[ZARUBA]
Don't cry.
There are fewer things more
futile than tears.
None of this is
your fault, Sophie.
You have the right to live
according to your beliefs.
And Garo exists
to protect that right.
Whether it costs injury,
or whether the battle
ultimately claims our lives,
we will always be
there to protect you.
Live, Sophie.
Never stop moving forward.
[ZARUBA]
Enough.
Get on.
I thought it curious
we broke through their
defenses so easily.
Something awful
must be lying in wait.
So what do we do?
Sword will most
certainly follow us.
We'll have to find
a way to buy some time.
Come.
Princess.
Do not resist me.
Surrender.
[ZARUBA]
Sophie.
Regardless of what happens,
remember what I said
about moving forward.
Zaruba.
Please don't.
Zaruba!
[ZARUBA]
That was rather fun, partner.
[DARK KNIGHT] A brilliant death,
if only for a Madou ring.
My respects.
[DARK KNIGHT] To think a mere
trinket could do such damage
to someone of my caliber.
The Dark Knight himself.
[SWORD]
Zaruba.
Lend me your invinceble will,
and stand beside me in eternity!
[DARK KNIGHT]
You absorbed his essence.
A clever way to
bolster your strength.
Excellent.
Let us put it to the test!
[DARK KNIGHT laughs]
A worthy nemesis.
I look forward
to our next meeting.
[DARK KNIGHT] Prepare
to die in exquisite agony
when our blades cross again.
Till we both draw
our final breath.
[SWORD]
Bastard!
[ZARUBA ]
Live, Sophie.
Never stop moving forward.
[SOPHIE sobs]