Look.
[CAROL]
Poor things.
Look at them.
So sad.
They all made their way here
to try and live the dream.
Now? What can they do?
Huddle up, brood over
the fact it didn't work out.
Not us.
Oh, no, we were chosen.
[gasps]
Wow.
El Dorado.
[BEZEL] I can never get
enough of this aroma.
Greed. Sin. Human corruption.
I can smell their
lovely scent from miles away.
[MAN E]
Take us with you!
[CAROL gasps]
His proposal was total shit.
What else could I do?
[laughter]
Yeah. No kidding. Guy's a joke.
He's lucky you didn't--
Hey! Oh. Sorry, uh...
[BEZEL]
Nice night, isn't it?
Uh. Yeah. I suppose.
[sniffs]
What is this?
Joy? Such a rancid smell.
You gentlemen reek of it.
Um... Can I help you?
[BEZEL]
You know a guy called King?
I'm here to see him.
The King?
No clue.
Sorry, man.
[BEZEL]
I see.
That's too bad.
Let me apologize.
[gasps]
I think we've found
a new look for you two.
[BEZEL]
Gotta love this city.
What a waste it'd be to let
the King hog it all for himself.
Right?
It appears we have
another troublesome guest
to contend with.
[INTERCOM] In keeping with the
Gareden Corporation's reputation
for bringing you the latest
in cutting-edge technology,
our most recent innovation will
increase the processing speed
of any device currently
available to the public.
[SHOP OWNER groans]
Look. Why you asking me?
How the hell should I know?
I never heard of him!
I'm being honest!
Please! Put me down!
I don't know any King!
[coughs]
[BEZEL]
I believe you.
Huh?
Sorry about that.
I really am.
Let me make it up to you.
Hi, Ed. My name's Carol.
Huh? You've been watching?
Yeah. Sorry.
Couldn't bring myself
to look away.
Heh. You're just that gorgeous.
[CAROL chuckles]
I'm trying to get my head
around the lay of the land.
Just got to town yesterday.
Ah! Welcome to the life!
Bet you're feelin'
pretty lucky, huh?
Yup, not just
anybody makes it here.
Right?
It certainly is breathtaking
Have you been
over to the hub, yet?
Best place in the city,
hands down.
Got that huge tower
smack in the middle.
Damned impressive.
I'll have to stop by
when I have the time.
[CAROL]
What is...?
My way of saying,
"Hey, there."
So, Big Soiree.
You should come.
Oh, well...
Thank you.
'S all part of my job.
No worries.
Totally legit.
I provide companionship.
I see.
Well good for you.
You'd be wise to take care.
Great as it is, the city's
very different at night.
The inexperienced
can be at risk.
'Specially without a guide.
You make it sound so dangerous.
Ha! Oh my!
[QUEEN]
You're calm.
[BISHOP] A perfect plan tends
to have that effect on me.
A perfect plan?
The Golden Knight is
inching his way closer.
It's no matter, trust me.
We have options.
The "princess"
needn't be an issue.
I understand you
botched her kidnapping.
I wouldn't say that.
No, as a reconnaissance effort
it was quite invaluable.
We now have more
than enough information
with which to proceed.
The King has begun
making final adjustments
to the system.
Do not allow anyone
to pester him.
[BISHOP]
Oh really?
Took him long enough
to get to didn't it?
Whatever accomplishes
the grand objective, I suppose.
[QUEEN] Precisely why
there is no room for error.
If things don't work out,
we can always blow it up.
The lab gives us
a nice precedent.
Ah.
What a magnificent bit
of destruction that was.
I remind you the King's
orders are absolute.
Don't get any ideas.
[BISHOP laughs]
Always so terrifying.
Thanks, fellas.
[gasps]
[MAN H]
S'up? This your first time here?
[CAROL]
Uh, yeah.
Awesome!
Let's get you up to the front!
Oh, well, actually.
Seriously, c'mon.
You'll have a story
to tell our grandkids.
Cool, huh?
We're practically part
of the show!
Right, party people!
Whaddya say?
Best night of yo' lives?
Hell yeah!
Okay.
We are ready
to blow the lid off!
It's almost time
for the main event
you've all been waiting for!
Lemme see you
put your hands in the air
and show some love
to our special guests.
These ladies!
[MAN H]
Congrats, babe!
I... What's going on?
You three are in
for a special treat tonight!
Oh, yeah!
You're gonna paint the town red!
Oh. Well. I, uh...
[WOMAN A shrieks]
Stop!
[CAROL]
Huh?!
[WOMAN B]
No! Please!
[MC] We gonna color the night
with yo' insides, baby!
As we rip you apart and eat you!
You're... You're kidding.
Huh?!
[MC]
Dig in.
It's feedin' time!
No!
Stay away from me!
Is that you?
Help!
Please!
These creatures.
They're trying to... Oh, god!
Sorry, hon. Can't.
[CAROL]
Huh?
Who are you?
[BEZEL]
Huh.
No King here, I see.
That's a shame.
[MC]
Why do you care?
[BEZEL] 'Cause I'm
more fit for the top slot
than some decrepit old hack
and I want him to know it.
[laughs]
You've got a sense of humor.
But you also got
in the way of our meal!
This place smells like a toilet.
That stench should be
eliminated at its source.
Anyone who lords over this shit
show of nobodies has no right
to call himself king.
Not in front of a man
with my qualifications.
[laughs]
[BISHOP] The cafeteria
in District 32 is down.
Our visitor's strength, I think,
more than speaks for itself.
You have some nerve.
Feigning ignorance.
You've known his
strength since his arrival.
True.
But I needed a proper chance
to get a lock on his methods.
Where might I ask is Knight?
I thought it'd be best for him
to handle this personally.
Well?
I believe infiltrators
are your responsibility.
Handle it yourself.
[BISHOP] Even if our friend's
primary target is His Majesty?
Damned cur.
You are such
a disgusting creature.
Coming from you,
that is a choice compliment.
Oh, dear.
Such a display.
The Man Who Would Be King.
[MC]
Here.
This is the place you want.
[BEZEL]
A barrier.
They don't trust
anyone, do they?
[BEZEL]
It's a good night to die.
The King must not be far.
Bite your tongue.
His name is not to be
uttered by the likes of you.
Now, now.
I'd wield that ring
better than he could.
Deny it all you like, but
absolute power over Horrors?
Heh, c'mon.
It's high time he
passed it down the line.
I wouldn't just
conquer some sandbox
in the middle of nowhere.
I'd take the whole continent.
Oh-ho.
Your scent is particularly
overpowering.
Adoration?
No, wait,
a fiercely loyal heart.
I like that.
Don't worry, doll.
Once you're mine,
I'll take care of you.
[QUEEN] Folly beyond
all conceivable measure.
I defend him of
my own, free will.
I am no hostage to His Majesty.
You smile, yet are not
worthy to anoint his feet.
Is that right?
Hah! But I have such
surprises in store!
You know, I actually rather
like the smell of flowers.
[BEZEL]
Huh?
[QUEEN] These are of
the carnivorous variety.
My sweet children from Makai.
Insatiable things.
Are these the claws
that dare to scratch my King?
Really?
Are these the legs that
dare trample upon his soil?
Be gone.
[QUEEN] The mouths that
dare befoul his name?
The eyes that dare
show a glint of malice?
[QUEEN] Such feeble
impudence I cannot abide.
Hideous wretch.
Shut up!
[BEZEL]
What?
Come now, you didn't honestly
think your ploy would work?
[QUEEN laughs]
[BEZEL]
You bitch.
There's no way.
It can't be possible.
[ED] What did I say
about the inexperienced?
Around here, those who
are careless get devoured.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
I'm the one who
takes care of this fair city.
Wait a second.
You're from the damn park!
Fascinating
spectacle you put on.
I admit I couldn't look away.
It's futile.
Whatever else you try to do,
you're going
to die in this city.
That's a guarantee.
You lot have only the sense
to want what's in front of you.
So very typical of a Horror.
Though as Horrors go,
you're not really my type.
[BISHOP]
What a face.
I don't think I shall ever tire
of seeing that expression.
Oh, killer entrance.
Are you done with
your so-called training?
My goodness.
Nothing interests you
but the Golden Knight.
Ah, well.
Too bad for this fellow.
As long as I breathe,
no harm shall ever come to you.
Eh. So be it.
El Dorado's true worth
is lost on cretins like him.