[CROWD crying]
[ANNE sobbing]
Sister!
Don't go! Please don't go!
[sirens blare]
[CROWD chattering]
[MAN 9A]
See anyone?
[sirens continue]
[SWORD]
Really!
Dude, why even bother
having a fridge?
Food n' water too much
of an extravagance?
Lots a' construction
in my neighborhood.
A man can't eat in peace.
That one's yours.
Time to dig in.
Look at it.
What a nightmare.
I can't let something
like this happen again.
Next time, I'll go to him.
Before he has a chance
to make a move.
I just got word from the diner.
Wish me luck.
I'm headin' out.
[SWORD]
Hurry up and bounce back, man.
[door creaks]
[door clicks]
[WAITRESS]
According to our sources,
he entered the city
from the west.
Okay.
If that's true, it makes a
strong case for our theory.
El Dorado is thought to lie
somewhere out west.
[SWORD grunts]
[WAITRESS]
Whatever it turns out to be,
the "king" he mentioned
is likely its ruler.
Bring Sophie and establish
whether or not that's the case.
If a Horror's involved,
as we suspect,
eliminate it immediately.
Why do we have to take the girl?
The Knight made evident
in his remarks
that this king is targeting her.
Needless to say:
remain vigilant.
Never let the child
out of your sight.
Be discreet.
In other words, use her as bait.
[WAITRESS]
Now, because protecting her
while battling adversaries
may prove to be difficult,
several alchemists
have been dispatched.
Your orders are to meet up
with them in San Del Dios.
[WAITRESS]
We expect the journey
to take two or three days.
It's advised you leave at once.
Beyond the rendezvous
point sits a lawless region
over which we have no control.
[SWORD]
Sounds fun.
Safe travels, Sword.
Please be careful.
[bells chime]
[footsteps]
[SWORD]
We're heading to El Dorado.
[STAFF 6A]
Hundred orders of egg drop soup!
[WORKERS]
Shi .
[STAFF 6A] Start passing
them out in Section 21!
[MALE WORKER 9A]
Shi. Hao de !
It's dangerous out west.
Been quite a while since
we had to surrender
our hold on the region.
I'm not about to defy my master.
Heh. Well, then, you
had better produce
results that will please.
Watch over the city.
Make sure Luke's okay.
I have half a mind
to leave the care
of that stubborn fool to
my granddaughter.
Meifang, huh?
Lucky. Heh.
What of Sophie?
She's joining you, I take it?
[SWORD]
Yeah.
That poor creature.
Brother's missing,
guardian's dead,
and she's being targeted
by who knows what.
There are no two ways about it;
she was born under a bad star.
[DARK KNIGHT] My master is
the King of El Dorado.
You have been summoned.
Don't worry.
I'll keep her safe.
Uh...?
[SISTER] Straighten your
back! Stand firm!
Uh?
[SWORD]
Wanna talk to 'em?
[ANNE]
Come on, guys. Wait up.
[gasps]
Let's go, Sword.
♪♪♪
I dream until tomorrow
pulls me away further away
If I relive my sorrows
I know that I could
as long as it is with you
So long to every yesterday
that proved me wrong
I sleep when the sun comes down
Let me dream
till tomorrow arrives
Sun goes down comes up
to start it over
if we choose to seize
a bright tomorrow
Sun comes up goes down
when we believe
life is better than this
Tomorrow
[yawns]
[gasps]
Well howdy, y'all!
[SWORD]
How the west was won.
[WAITRESS]
You need high octane or regular?
Strongest you've got, thank you.
[ZARUBA grunting]
So bitter.
Tried to tell you
when you ordered.
Yeah, I know.
[SWORD]
Big one's called Mount Olivie.
Left of it's the Monterey
Mountain Range.
[SOPHIE] What's all
the white stuff on top?
Snow?
[SWORD] Yep. Gives you
an idea how tall it is.
Your first time on the road?
[SOPHIE]
Yeah.
Never been outside
the city before.
No kiddin'?
[SOPHIE]
What about you?
You go to a bunch of places?
[SWORD]
Sure.
I had to travel a lot for
training back when I was young.
Climbed that sucker right there
when the snow was waist deep.
Why do you train
so much, Sword?
[SWORD] Gotta stay fit
when you tangle with Horrors.
How come?
[SWORD]
Hm?
I mean, what's the point
of doing what you do?
Why keep fighting all the time?
Sounds like a dangerous
life if you ask me.
Guess that's just
the path I chose.
[SOPHIE grunts]
[SWORD]
Brace yourself!
[SOPHIE laughs]
[gasps]
[SOPHIE laughing]
[ZARUBA]
She's weighing us down.
Hey, what do you want from me?
It's all part of the job.
Uh?
[SWORD] Coyotes, probably.
We're losin' daylight.
I wanna reach the next set
a' foot hills 'fore dark.
Hold on tight!
[gasps] Pull over!
Coyotes didn't do this.
Poor little thing took
a hunter's bullet,
then got left behind.
That's awful!
What should we do?
Not a helluva lot we can do.
'cept eat it!
Huh?!
There. That should do
the trick, I think.
Right. Let's get outta here.
[SWORD grunting]
Hop on.
Wait a sec.
[SWORD]
Eh?
Let's stay.
Just a little longer. Please.
Uh?
[ZARUBA] Don't say I
didn't try to warn you.
Aw, c'mon.
Enough a' that talk.
[SOPHIE]
Ah! Atta girl, Lucy!
I knew you could do it!
So we've given her a name?
If you two ladies
will excuse me,
we could use some more firewood.
I'll be back in a few.
Holler if you need me.
Okay!
[SOPHIE] Didn't Sword say
Lucy eats mostly soft grass?
How do you think he
knows that? Random.
Yeah. Zaruba doesn't
like to talk much.
You like it?
Wait here, 'kay? Good girl.
I'll go find some more!
[clattering]
Uh?
Uh.
This ought'a last us
for a while.
Hey, is, uh,
everything all right?
Where's, what's-her-name, Lucy?
[SOPHIE]
I should've listened.
I should've talked.
Really talked to her.
I treated her like...
[SOPHIE sobs]
Uh...
I miss her so much it hurts!
Sister! [cries]
Sadness never leaves.
And regrets are never
completely forgotten. But...
[SWORD grunts]
Despite the pain,
life goes on.
We have to move forward
as best we can.
This is good.
[SWORD] Those stars make up
the constellation, Cassiopeia.
Just under 'em there--
[SOPHIE]
Andromeda, right?
[SWORD]
Heh. Ah, very good.
You learn that at the home?
She took us to the
planetarium once.
Not long after I came to
live there, actually.
Pretty sure the whole purpose
was to cheer me up.
I was a crybaby.
[SOPHIE] Sister knew
just about everything.
Loved pointing things out.
First time in my life I'd
ever noticed the stars.
Wow.
Until then, I'd never looked up.
Never knew my world was just
a tiny part of all... this.
[SISTER]
Sophie.
What would you say if I told
you this doesn't hold a candle
to the actual night sky?
That's right. Don't worry.
I have a feeling you'll get to
see the real thing one day.
Perfect.
[SOPHIE]
Rise and shine! Time to go!
What the--?
Just a few more minutes.
Come on. You do not
want me to help.
[groans]
Okay! Read you loud and clear!
[SOPHIE laughs]
[SOPHIE]
Put your clothes on.
All right. Let's go.
The wretch dares return
empty-handed, I see.
Where is the girl you were
ordered to bring back?
I'm fairly astonished
you possess the gall
the show your face, fool.
Sacrificing poor Pawn
without a thought.
You've totally ruined
my ingenious plan.
The Golden Knight.
I assumed you traded blows?
Well? His blade.
How was it?
Perfect.
Soon, he will be here to
challenge me again.
He's coming here?
Has this news been
brought to the King?
There is no need.
Oh? Dear oh dear.
Things have taken a
rather thorny turn.
Whatever my happen,
I will not allow the king
to be put in harm's way.
Golden Knight.
I'm waiting for you.