[SISTER]
No!
Why on earth must you
frequent a restaurant
when we feed you here?
If that's not luxury,
I don't know what is!
My dear. I realize
you're doing all this
for brother Martin.
Why not be patient and let
the police do their job?
[LUKE] I prefer to take care
of this one on my own.
Why?
[SOPHIE]
I could do some research.
[LUKE]
Thanks. I owe you one.
[SWORD] I didn't do it on
my own, so you know.
Sophie's the one who found you.
If you owe anybody anything,
far as I'm concerned, it's her.
[police sirens blare]
[gasps]
Hello. Miss Melia
Wild, I presume?
So sorry. My name is Pawn.
We've spoken via email?
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for taking an
interest in our company.
Good people are hard to find.
Oh, yes. Well...
These days so are decent terms.
Uh. Not to be rude, but
headhunters rarely make
that good an impression on me.
So, then Pawn.
What do you say we
cut the chitchat
and get down to brass tacks?
Tell me more about
this "El Dorado"
that so desperately
needs my skill set.
Ah, but of course.
There's just one thing.
An unforeseen complication,
if you will.
[MELIA]
Yeah?
[PAWN]
I've let myself get hungry.
Huh?
[PAWN]
Dear, that was naughty of me.
Seems as though we'll have to
find another suitable candidate.
--[door creaks]
--Hm?
Uh. Something I can do for you?
No need to trouble yourself,
Master Knight.
We have more than enough
help on this side.
Thank you, though.
[WAITRESS]
Here y'go. Today's special.
[LUKE]
Missing persons.
Past two weeks, people
have been disappearing
one after the other.
Similar M.O.
All in their late teens,
early twenties.
Horrors have been detected
at various sites,
but... nothing definite.
One of the victims emailed
a friend, saying, quote,
"I'm being scouted
by El Dorado,"
whatever that's
supposed to mean--
[SWORD]
Gimme that!
Sword, wait!
I'm going alone!
Just-- I don't have time to
deal with you right now.
Go home.
[bells chime]
[LUKE]
I wouldn't bother.
[SOPHIE]
But...
Why can't he tell me
what El Dorado is?
How come just mentioning it
makes him act like that?
I'm sure he'll explain
the whole thing
to you himself in
his own good time.
[bells chime]
[GANG MEMBER 7A]
What do we have here?
Slow down there, buddy.
You're not tryin' to
pass through our turf
without sayin' hello,
are ya? Huh?!
You must be new around here.
Allow me to give you
a little orientation
on how we run things.
Hey.
[MALE FRIEND 7A]
Yeah. 's right.
I didn't really know what
he was talking about.
Apparently he thought
this "El Dorado"
would give him a better life?
Seemed kinda weird.
Look, I'm no expert,
but isn't El Dorado a lost
civilization or something?
The fabled city of gold.
It's part of an ancient legend
from the Andes region.
So, does that play into
why he's missing, or what?
Not quite following you.
That's what I'm trying to find
out. 'S there anything else?
Think that's about it.
Man, if I'd known
this was coming...
Hell, I'd have pressed
the guy for more details.
Can't believe detectives
are getting involved now.
Did he do something, like,
illegal or whatever?
No.
He's clean.
We're here on behalf
of a client.
[MALE FRIEND 7A]
Got'cha.
Police here are useless anyway.
[LUKE] The victims were all
single and worked from home.
Not a lot of friends
in the city.
So of course it took a while for
anyone to notice they were gone.
College student.
Programmer.
Neuroscience researcher.
Electrical engineer.
Video game vlogger.
Fairly diverse bunch.
All they seem to have in
common is the Internet,
which doesn't give
us much to go on.
This is hopeless.
It'd be easier to
track down someone
who had no online
presence whatsoever.
[LUKE] This guy's the only one
who mentioned El Dorado.
That's something.
Could be the others
weren't involved.
Could be they didn't
have anyone to talk to.
Could be they were silenced.
Either way, don't get fixated.
You'll lose sight
of the bigger picture.
'Preciate the advice, Luke.
I'll keep an open mind.
[LUKE]
What is El Dorado exactly?
A place, or some sort
of organization?
[HOMELESS MAN 1A]
Lookin' for somebody?
I gotta tell ya, folks move in
and outta here pretty damn fast.
[hiccups] Some kid
from three years ago?
Please, no one's memory goes
back that... far. [hiccups]
'Course, if we're talking
young enough,
I suppose they might've
packed her off
to one of them homes or
somethin', if she was lucky.
Most of 'em fall in with
street gangs and what not.
Wind up a statistic.
Yeah. It's a waste.
The girls start
workin' the corner
'fore they're old
enough to drive.
Hey, come on! I gave
you information!
That shit ain't free!
Come back here!
[grunts]
[ANNOUNCER 7A] Experience a
next level of virtual reality,
complete with retina
scan access!
ELDO NET is currently
looking for beta testers.
[CHAMELEON AVATAR 7A]
Huh, I noticed that guy
hasn't been posting
a lot lately.
Vhere'd he go?
[FISH AVATAR 7A]
Must've ran out of ideas.
[LION AVATAR 7A sighs]
Wait. Another one?
This is getting to be
a real problem.
[RABBIT AVATAR 7A]
Wish I could disconnect from RL.
Lol.
[SOPHIE] Has anyone been
talking about this on DM?
[FISH AVATAR 7A]
One-hundred percent sure
he's pulling a prank
for the views.
[ELEPHANT AVATAR 7A]
Hey, that reminds me.
You guys know what happened to
Team Omega all of a sudden?
[SOPHIE]
"Team Omega"?
[ELEPHANT AVATAR 7A]
You know the game, Dark Strike?
Super popular?
Well, till recently they
were in the top rank.
Now? Nothing.
[CHAMELEON AVATAR 7A] They
prob'ly just got tired of it.
[ELEPHANT AVATAR 7A]
I doubt that.
Dark Strike was
their bread and butter.
[OWL AVATAR 7A]
They're a bunch a' spammers.
Go back and read what they
posted in the chat sometime,
I'm tellin' ya. Good riddance.
Yeah. Stuff like "Get on
the El Dorado Bus."
[SOPHIE]
Sorry, what did you say?
[OWL AVATAR 7A] Some stupid
thing they were all hyped about.
"Happiness awaits in
El Dorado." Lame.
[CHAMELEON AVATAR 7A]
Sounds like they joined a cult.
[OWL AVATAR 7A]
I know, right?
[SISTER]
Where are you going?
Oh, uh, nowhere.
Just for a walk!
Yes, of course. Silly me.
Why else would you be trying
to sneak out the back?
[laughs nervously]
[sighs]
[SISTER]
Sophie, listen.
[sighs]
You can't keep throwing
caution to the wind.
You've been lucky so far,
that's it. Understand?
Sister, please. I...
I don't mean to be so--
[SISTER]
I get it, Sophie. I do.
But dear, you're still
only a child.
And as long as that's the case,
it is my duty to protect you.
Yes, ma'am.
[doorbell ringing]
Give me just a moment, please.
[SISTER gasps]
Hello. Sorry to
keep you waiting.
[PAWN] My apologies for dropping
in like this out of the blue.
See, I'm what you might
call a tour coordinator
for educational institutions.
Institutions like this.
Pawn, pleasure to meet you.
Huh?
[OFFICER 7A]
Freeze!
What do you think you're doing?
Huh. "Get on the Eldorado bus"?
Yeah. They're called Team Omega.
About two weeks ago
they stopped logging on.
It's like all of seven
of 'em vanished.
Here, take a look.
That's their main hangout.
A shop where the captain
has a part-time job.
Sort of became the unofficial
team headquarters.
People'd see 'em meet there
several times a week.
[WAITRESS]
Hm.
That's the area where Mister
Luke is focusing his search.
I should pass it on.
[bells chime]
I know it's probably not
all that helpful, but...
[SWORD]
No. This is great.
Thank you.
And, about earlier.
That wasn't cool.
I shouldn't have just walked.
You know as much about
El Dorado as I do.
I'll tell you if I find
something more concrete.
[gasps] Thank you, Sword.
[SWORD]
Now.
Go home. You've done your part.
Think you can leave the
rest up to Luke an' me?
Yes!
[LUKE]
This is the place?
[beeping]
[sirens blare]
[garage door creaking]
[ZARUBA]
There it is.
[SWORD yells]
[SWORD grunts]
[ZARUBA] Well, they did
a decent job hiding it.
A barrier made by
a Horror, no doubt.
[gasps]
[SWORD]
Still breathing.
It looks like they're
all just unconscious.
[LUKE]
It's a storage unit.
Stocking up for a rainy day.
I've heard of rationing,
but this has gotta be a first.
[LUKE] Maybe they're being
grouped together for the "bus."
You're saying these poor
bastards are beings shipped
out of town? Like to
a central nest?
[LUKE]
I'll call for backup.
Too many hostages for us
to handle ourselves.
[SWORD]
Mm.
[LUKE]
It's me.
We found the missing persons.
[LUKE]
Right. It's just the two of us.
Send Fei Long and the others.
Huh?
[LUKE]
I dunno.
Let me get a headcount.
Must be the Horror's
hunting grounds.
[ZARUBA] Just about every circle
on this map is an area
where you and Luke
have been poking around.
[SWORD]
Wait a minute.
[LUKE]
Understood. We'll stay onsite.
Hey!
The place where Sophie lives,
it's circled on the map!
[LUKE] We have an emergency.
Sword's heading--
[WAITRESS] Sorry. You guys
aren't the only ones.
We just got word seconds ago.
[WAITRESS]
Heads up,
something particularly
nasty is on the loose.
Your orders are to leave the
missing persons to Fei Long.
Sword's gonna need
all the help he can get.
[LUKE]
Copy that.
[LUKE] Damn it.
What the hell's going on?
[SISTER]
Attention, please.
I have a very important
announcement to make.
Next month, some lovely
people have arranged
to take us all on
a camping trip!
[CHILDREN gasping, chattering]
Take us camping?
Where'd we get the money
for something like that?
Questions of finance should be
of no concern to children.
A gentleman spoke
to me this afternoon.
His company specializes in fun
activities for groups like ours.
Isn't that wonderful?
I for one am thrilled
beyond words!
Sounds pretty cool.
Yeah, right? So where
are we gonna go?
It's supposed to be
absolutely marvelous.
The facilities are new,
so they aren't well known.
But, "happiness awaits,"
so I'm told.
[gasps]
[OWL AVATAR 7A] "Happiness
awaits in El Dorado."
Lame.
'Scuse me, but do you know what
this guy's company's called?
[doorbell ringing]
[SISTER]
Hold that thought.
[SOPHIE gasps]
[SISTER]
Coming.
Can't imagine who it could be.
Oh, it's you again.
[PAWN]
Sorry for coming so late.
The preparations for
your tour are complete.
Are you and the children
ready to leave?
[SISTER]
What?
Oh, um.
Sorry, this is rather more
sudden than I thought.
Not to be ungrateful, but...
...didn't you say the
trip was in two weeks?
Haste makes waste,
isn't that what they say?
I'm afraid the timetable
has changed.
[laughs] Don't delay!
Think of the children!
Won't they be delighted?
El Dorado is waiting.
[SISTER]
But, I-I...
We're not prepared to leave
on such short notice.
[PAWN] The specifics of your
situation do not matter to us.
Sadly, we no longer have
the luxury of time.
Circumstances compel us to leave
this city at once, you see.
Alas, as products you
are third-rate.
Your usefulness to El Dorado
is somewhat limited,
but you should suffice as food.
Forgive me, it's simply
that I dare not appear
empty-handed before
my glorious king.
[SOPHIE]
Get away from her!
Sophie!
Take everyone to Mr. Brooks
and have him call the police.
Explain to him what's going on.
Come with us!
You can't stay here with this
man, he... he's somethin' bad!
[SISTER]
Sophie!
Now where do you think
you're going?
Sir, I don't know who you are,
but you won't lay a
hand on my children.
Mr. Brooks! Please!
You've gotta let us in!
It's us! There's an emergency!
What in the world?
What's going on?
There's a crazy man!
He's inside the house!
Call the police!
[MR. BROOKS]
Sophie, wait!
[ANNE]
What are you doing?
Get ahold of yourself.
You've gotta say calm.
[WAITRESS]
Thank you for calling the--
Get Sword over here! Hurry!
[SISTER panting]
[PAWN laughs]
[PAWN grunting]
[SISTER yells]
[gasps]
[screams]
[SISTER groaning]
[door opens]
Put her down!
[SOPHIE grunts]
[gasps]
Getting in my way
was a mistake.
[SOPHIE gasping]
Tell me who you are.
What will you do with my Sophie?
[SISTER grunting]
[whimpers]
[SISTER groaning]
[gasping]
Go.
Now.
[SOPHIE gasping]
[DARK KNIGHT]
Sophia Hennes.
I've been looking for you.
My master is the
King of El Dorado.
You have been summoned.
[SOPHIE cries]
So it's you.
Garo, huh?
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[LUKE] At last you step out of
the shadows and reveal yourself.
[LUKE]
Dark Knight.