[ELDER]
You've completed your trial
for the Land of Guidance, I see.
[LUKE]
Yes.
I'm bound for El Dorado.
[ELDER]
Before you embark,
there is a place I'd very
much like you to visit.
A small settlement, where a
Horror has lain sealed away
for ages untold.
[LUKE]
Hm.
You don't say.
The seal's power is diminishing.
Quite soon the
Horror shall awaken.
[LUKE]
I have my own path to follow.
I'm aware, and I
understand this would be
a detour on your
journey to El Dorado.
However.
It may prove to be a
shortcut for you personally.
Ah...!
Um, is there something
I can help you with, sir?
[LUKE]
The pattern on the door.
Huh?! You're here!
[LUKE]
Sorry?
[STELLA] You do know what
that mark means, don't you?
[LUKE]
It's a bit dated,
but definitely made by
a Makai Alchemist.
Oh, I uh, yes well,
w-why don't you come in?
Yeah, yeah. Who is it, then?
Bastard!
What in the hell have you
done to my granddaughter?
It's not like that, Grandpa.
This man's a potential customer.
[sighs]
Should'a said that
'stead of letting me
stand here barkin'
at the poor guy.
I was on the verge of thrashing
him within an inch of his life!
[LUKE] The Land of
Guidance brought me here.
Oh. Well, please, come in.
So, uh...
Would it be too much for me
to ask what your name is?
[LUKE]
Luke.
[STELLA]
Mr. Luke. Cool.
I'll just come right out with
it: you're the Demon Sealer!
[LUKE]
The what?
The one foretold of in
legend who will save this land!
[LUKE]
No, I'm not.
W-What are you talking about?
Surely, you are!
[LUKE]
Nope.
Wait a second,
then how did you recognize
the mark on our door?
[LUKE]
I know things.
This "Demon Sealer"
isn't one of them.
You're kidding me.
[LUKE] So I take it you
two aren't on our side?
Well it depends.
Exactly what side is that?
[LUKE]
Forgive the intrusion.
No! Wait, please, I wanna
show you something!
Here, take a look.
This book used to belong to
my grandfather's grandfather.
[LUKE]
A Makai Knight.
What kind of knight?
So you do know
something about this!
[LUKE]
Let me guess.
This is a rendering
of your Demon Sealer.
[STELLA] "Demons lurk in
the dark places of the world,
yet there are those possessed
of the power to seal them."
According to this book,
a demon was sealed
away here a long time ago.
[ELDER]
A small settlement,
where a Horror has lain
sealed away for ages untold.
[STELLA] "When the demon stirs,
the Demon Sealer shall appear."
Here's the thing,
unpack the text a little
and it's abundantly
clear all this lines up
with the next full moon.
That's tomorrow night.
[ELDER]
The seal's power is diminishing.
Quite soon the
Horror shall awaken.
You have to admit,
someone like you just showing up
out of nowhere has got to
be more than coincidence.
[LUKE] Where precisely
is this "demon" of yours
meant to be sealed?
I'm afraid we don't know.
And believe me, we've been
turning the whole settlement
upside down looking for it.
The design on this armor's
been bothering me, too.
I mean, look at it.
Half the getup's painted black.
Do Demon Sealers...
Sorry, what'd you call them?
Makai Knights?
Is this what they wear?
'Cause really the only
thing we know for sure
is that this image resembles
a statue that used to stand
on the outskirts of town
way back in the day.
[LUKE]
Oh yeah?
It was destroyed
in an earthquake.
The only trace
of it now is the base.
It's real, though.
Grandpa saw it with his own
eyes when he was a little boy.
More of a toddler, actually,
but I can vouch
for its existence.
[LUKE]
Indeed.
Can you take me there?
Yes! Of course!
You heard the gentleman!
Let's take him sight-seeing!
Come on, now.
Wheelchair.
Get a move on!
[ALEC]
All right. Don't push.
I'm not as young as
I used to be, sweetheart. Easy.
Can I ask you
a question, Mr. Luke?
This Land of Guidance
you mentioned earlier?
What's that about?
[LUKE]
Can't say.
Is it a town? Or ruins?
Maybe some kind
of secret cavern?
Wait, I know!
It's Outer Space!
[OLD LADY A]
Stella!
Really? A stranger?
How many does this make now?
Hey! He isn't just anybody!
As a matter of fact--
We've told you time and again
these vagabonds are trouble!
Ha! And you!
Don't you have more self-respect
than to feed a young girl's
delusion, shifty-eyed, huckster?
Huh? What's a huckster?
Take it from me, young lady,
you can't trust a man just
because he's handsome.
I'll bet this Lothario
has broken more hearts
than he can be
bothered to count.
Lothario?
[LUKE]
A groundless accusation.
He, um, he says you're wrong.
So it's okay!
Trust me, there's absolutely
nothing to worry about
from this one!
What in the world are
we going to do with you?
You can't be this naïve!
I'm not naïve.
Mr. Luke's the real deal!
Grandpa agrees with me.
[ALEC]
Hey! Hey! Ahh!
Grandpa!
This is where it used to be.
[LUKE] And it looked like
the picture in your book?
[ALEC]
Yup.
Stood there for ages.
Though I have to confess:
something feels off.
[LUKE]
Meaning what?
He said the same thing
last time we were here
when I tried standing on it.
We couldn't quite figure out
what the problem was, though.
Hop over there and
try posing on the base for me
if you wouldn't mind, sir.
Seeing you do it might clear
the cobwebs and jog my memory.
You think so?
[LUKE] I don't see how
that'd make any difference.
What? For starters,
you're way taller!
[LUKE]
I refuse.
Well! You definitely look
more imposing than Stella!
[LUKE]
Please hurry.
[ALEC] He stood more
or less as you are now,
only his arm was out
holding his sword.
Well lookie there.
Stella's got someone
else along for the ride!
Where did you find this guy?
[BOY C]
Check out the look on his face!
He's so into it!
Scary!
Don't pay
attention to 'em, Mr. Luke.
You look super cool.
What'cha think?
Got anything yet?
I don't know.
Something still seems off.
[gasps]
[LUKE]
Are we done yet?
Wait! That's it! Of course!
The design.
It's not intentional.
It's just shadow!
[LUKE]
What?
[STELLA] Grandpa, you said
people used to observe
a special time for prayer,
isn't that right?
Yeah, sure. At high noon.
Which is right about now.
That means the shadows
would fall in a specific
pattern on the armor.
Would you mind facing the
opposite direction for a moment?
[ALEC]
Ah-ha!
There it is!
That makes perfect sense!
The view behind the statue
would be completely different!
Something wrong?
Not the place
I would've thought.
[LUKE]
The seal.
Amazing.
[STELLA]
Whoa!
[LUKE]
This is it.
This is where it was sealed.
[pants]
Um, are you feeling all right?
'Kay, so the demon's true form
is something called a "Horror?"
[LUKE]
Correct.
It feeds on humans by first
exploiting a person's greed
and possessing them.
Those sworn to protect mankind
from these creatures--
Are what you
called Makai Knights?
[LUKE]
Yes.
The Horror sealed here,
however, was a knight
who fell to a Horror's sway.
Really?
[LUKE] Everyday,
we must be prepared
to face the darkness head on.
When confronted with the enemy,
our hearts can
ill afford to waver.
Lest in the blink of an eye
we be utterly consumed.
Quite good.
You really mean that?
You're not just
trying to be nice?
Quit fishing.
Not to brag, but uh,
cooking is the one thing
where I'm above average.
She has quite the talent for it.
Bit of a shame, her mind
always seems to be elsewhere.
Oh. By the way, Mr. Luke,
I've been meaning to ask you
where you keep
your sword and armor.
It so happens I possess neither.
Huh? But I thought you--!
You mistake me for a knight.
Oh. But, uh, I mean,
you can still defeat it.
I'm obliged to try.
I'm the only one here.
There's no other choice.
Yeah, well, you'll do great!
You've got me!
I'll be there to help
the whole time!
That won't be necessary.
Oh-ho!
I'll have to whip up some
demon-warding supplies, won't I?
[ALEC]
Spare a moment?
All right.
[ALEC]
She's a good kid.
Always has been.
Never thinks twice
about putting a complete
and total stranger's
needs ahead of her own.
Her mother and father
travel a lot for work.
They're not around
for most of the year.
Not that she complains.
I told her an old legend
to keep her occupied, you see.
Moved on from there
to all sorts of kooky stuff.
We had fun.
Mythology.
Urban legends.
UFOs.
Cryptozoology.
You name it,
she obsessed over it.
Before long, she became our
resident expert in the occult.
Not for tea parties and
playing dress up, that one.
'Bout half a year ago I'd say,
she dug that old
book out of storage,
poured through
it cover to cover.
Got fixated on the idea
we were all in harm's way.
Started asking every traveller
who passed through town
if they were the Demon
Sealer she'd read about
and would they help us?
Struck me as good a way as any
for a lonely little girl
to pass the time.
Imagine my shock when I learn
the old legends might be true.
So you believe
the stories after all.
I do.
And I can't shake
the feeling I've involved
my poor granddaughter
in something unspeakable.
You have nothing to worry about.
I'll see to it she's
not involved.
[ALEC]
Thank you.
That puts me at ease.
What do you mean he's gone?
Why didn't you wake me?!
[ALEC]
He wanted me to tell you thanks.
I have to go!
[ALEC]
No, you don't!
Think about it!
What could you possibly--?
He left you behind,
so you wouldn't get in his way!
[STELLA]
That's insane!
He doesn't even have a sword!
Please! Whatever the man's
reasons for going alone,
we have to respect them!
Stella, you don't
have to go with--
Do you even care what'll
happen to this town?
[ALEC]
No!
All I give a damn about
is what happens to you.
But, Grandpa, you...
[ALEC]
Please.
Leave things to him.
[LUKE]
I probably only have one chance.
He's strong!
I-I didn't mean
to do that, um...
I was just gonna watch,
but then it looked like
you were in trouble, so...
[LUKE]
Get back!
I will protect you.
That's a promise!
[LUKE] I don't doubt
you were once a knight
to be reckoned with.
Did the terrible weight of your
obligations lead you astray?
[LUKE]
No.
You faltered in a
moment of weakness
and lost sight of those
you were meant to protect.
You let yourself be consumed!
You mistook your purpose.
You neglected your heart!
[LUKE]
We may fall in the line of duty,
but the hope we represent?
That takes on
a life all its own.
[LUKE]
I see it now.
I know what true strength is!
Unsung warriors.
I inherit your will!
Thank you both.
Take care of yourself.
I swear I'll never forget
you as long as I live!
Now, now, Stella darling.
Crying your eyes out's
no way to send him off.
Your story, I'll pass it on!
Mr. Luke the Mighty!
That's sweet,
but I'd rather you didn't.
Huh? Wh-What are you doing?
It's for the best that
you never come to our side.
I don't understand.
Huh?
[LUKE]
Farewell.
[STELLA gasps]
What happened?
Okay.
I get myself mixed up
in something again?
Huh?
The full moon's already passed?
Totally slipped my noticed.
You believe that?
Good god,
I hope I'm not going senile.
What about the Demon Sealer?
Did he show up?
Not that I saw.
Nothing really happened.
[STELLA sighs]
Stella?
I'm just relieved
everyone is safe.
It was just an old
superstition after all.