How sure are you?
Very. See for yourself.
Here's the thing, though.
I have to go back to
the Land of Guidance.
Yesterday's attack obliterated
by weapons inventory.
I can't be empty-handed.
I'll meet up with
you guys in El Dorado.
Oh wow.
We made it.
I s'pose they like to
keep security fairly tight.
[SWORD]
Huh.
It's a lot cleaner inside
than I thought it'd be.
This work for you?
Let me add my own touch.
So is this where
we're planning to stay?
Yep.
It's good a have a base of
operations in enemy territory.
[SOPHIE]
Whoa!
Lookit!
Everything's so shiny!
It's beautiful!
Somewhere out there,
my brother's waiting.
[LUKE] Reassure me
you know what to do here.
Find out who this King is.
It's what the Watchdog
Center ordered, right?
No problem.
I mean, how hard can it be?
Yeah, kinda wish
Gina hadn't taken a detour.
Just sayin'.
[SWORD]
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Why so somber all of a sudden?
It's bad to bottle things up.
The body doesn't like it.
Hell, 'f you need to take
a leak, the thing to do is--
[SOPHIE]
Shut up!
Why you always
gotta be such a jerk?
Could we go over
the plan again, please?
Ugh!
[SWORD]
Fits perfect.
Oh, yeah the plan!
Right! We're gonna gussy
ourselves up and explore!
[SWORD]
You gotta be kidding!
Well, hello there, pretty boy.
Wanna get an eyeful
of these boobies?
Give thanks for this bounty!
Uh...
[LUKE]
Interesting.
Everything here is made
by the GarEden Corporation.
[SWORD]
GarEden?
[LUKE]
There.
[SOPHIE]
Huh...
Oh, you don't say.
Whoa!
Something just popped up
right in front of me!
This is incredible!
[laughs]
[SOPHIE]
How is he not sad?
[SWORD]
Thank you for this bounty.
[SOPHIE] Zaruba called him...
his partner.
For most people,
sadness is part of how
they honor the dead.
That's not true for us.
[LUKE] We see our
duty through to the end.
It's how we vindicate
those who've fallen.
I don't understand.
Think about it.
What's your purpose
in coming here?
What are you talking about?
I wanna find my brother.
[LUKE]
Is that all?
Huh?
[DARK KNIGHT] My master
is the King of El Dorado.
You have been summoned.
[SWORD]
Hey!
This is where we're eating,
just so you know.
Get a move on!
They're here.
Yeah.
[SWORD]
Not just one or two either.
Should I know what
you're talking about?
[SWORD]
Horrors.
Holy crap! For real?
Wha?
I have a feeling they didn't
congregate here naturally.
Yeah. Land of Guidance
said somethin' like that.
This King guy has
the power to control them.
Might even be this
whole city's run by Horrors
under his command.
Odd that Bishop and the
others haven't made a move yet.
[LUKE] There's more to
El Dorado than meets the eye.
[SWORD]
Definitely.
[SOPHIE]
Hm.
I think it's about time we did
a little covert reconnaissance.
Leave it to me.
I'll get online and
dig up something we can use.
Who knows?
With any luck I'll point us
in the direction of my brother.
Huh?
[SWORD]
You'll find him.
No way you won't.
I concur. That's why we're here.
Well, well,
looks like your aim's not
the only thing that's improved!
Don't start.
[SWORD]
I say we ask around first.
[SOPHIE]
Sure.
But, what about Luke?
He's sorta got his
own way of doing things.
No kidding.
How 'bout I find
a network to log into
so I can do what I do best?
[SOPHIE]
Hmm?
Somethin' wrong?
No.
Not exactly.
But...
Hey, let's go
check that thing out.
[SOPHIE groans]
What's up?
Well, El Dorado has its
own proprietary network.
Basically it means the only way
to connect is through ELDO NET.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
Why not give it a try?
And, uh...
Speaking of proprietary.
Thank you for this bounty.
Pervert.
[laughs]
Now go work your magic.
Hello, ladies.
How we doin' this fine evening?
[WOMAN B]
Hey, big guy.
[SWORD]
Not interrupting anything, am I?
Okay.
Is this it?
[VOICE] You have successfully
connected to ELDO NET.
Ew! Cold!
Huh? Huh?!
This is amazing!
I can totally feel everything!
Oh wow!
I can even smell the air!
[SOPHIE]
Ouch.
Huh? It smells so good!
And tastes even better!
Wait. What? How is this a thing?
[CANDY MAN]
Hey, what are you doing?
You must be new around here.
[SOPHIE]
Um. What's...?
Sorta overwhelming
your first time, huh?
They recreate
all five of your senses!
[SEAL] Once the
beta test phase is over,
the El Dorado System
will be ready for rollout.
And available
to the entire world!
They're taking it global?
Come along, noob!
Let me introduce you
to some of my pals!
Uh. Hang on a second, please!
There's something important
I need to ask you about first!
Have you heard anything
about I don't know...
...people mysteriously
vanishing?
Maybe someone you knew,
or you've heard rumors, or...
[laughter]
Slow down!
Why you gotta turns things
dark all of a sudden?
You won't make
any friends in ELDO
if you hit 'em with that kinda
talk right out of the gate!
If a few people
disappear, so what?
[SOPHIE]
Weird attitude to have.
Okay.
[ALAN]
Hi there!
Why aren't you playing?
I...
I don't get this place.
Guess it just throws me off that
everyone here seems so happy.
They're happy
'cause they're open-minded,
ready to embrace whatever
pleasures pop up.
No matter the cost.
That's how this
wonderful city works.
You can call it
El Dorado's guiding light.
[ALAN] Why are you so
interested in missing persons?
Well, I...
You wouldn't happen to
know the Golden Knight,
now would you?
Huh?
Actually...
Uh?
They come here in droves.
And regularly,
judging from these levels.
[SOPHIE]
What are those markings about?
[SWORD] Places where we're
sure Horrors like to hang out.
'Kay, what d'they do there?
Feed.
Toy with their quarry.
That kind of stuff.
What d'you dig up?
Sophie found this.
Have a look.
[LUKE] "If you want to know
the truth of this town,
come to meet me."
Hm...
Ten to one we're
being led into a trap,
but we got no choice
'cept to take the bait.
[SOPHIE]
This is it.
I'm takin' a wild guess
that this thing is our guide.
You the one askin' for me?
Well, here I am.
[ALAN] It's good of you
to come, Golden Knight.
I've been waiting a long time.
[SWORD]
You work for GarEden?
[ALAN]
Used to.
I left.
What is it you wanna
talk to me about, exactly?
Why be all cloak
and dagger about askin'?
I didn't want those
monsters to find me.
Had to take certain precautions.
Wait, so you know about 'em?
And you're still here?
[SOPHIE]
What is this?
[ALAN]
CC footage of a "cafeteria."
[SOPHIE]
Cafeteria?
[ALAN] They're everywhere.
Monsters rule this city.
People have absolutely no idea.
The GarEden corporation
is behind it all.
[SWORD]
How's that?
[ALAN]
Communications.
Industry.
Politics.
Everything.
Top to bottom,
GarEden is calling the shots.
All to one purpose.
[SWORD]
To provide a feeding ground.
Every public figure
in the city's complicit.
The mayor, the chief of police,
even the comptroller.
Monsters, the lot of 'em!
That's one hell of a Utopia.
So, how'd you find all this out?
[ALAN] My curiosity
got the better of me.
I came across a data
server locked down
under some unusually
heavy protection.
I couldn't resist hacking
my way in and having a peek.
Wish I hadn't.
When I broke through.
You found surveillance video of
slaughterhouses like this one.
Yeah, though I regret to say
that wasn't the only thing.
Go on, we're listening.
[ALAN]
I received a message.
[ALAN] In that email, was
the ugly truth about El Dorado.
[ALAN]
And a warning.
That the corporation knew what
I'd seen and was coming for me.
If I valued my life,
I had to run.
Since then,
I've been hiding here
like an animal.
[LUKE] I'm guessing the message
is how you found out about us?
[ALAN]
Yes.
It said there was a man
who slayed these creatures:.
a Golden Knight.
Yeah, but how'd they
even know about us?
Who sent you the email?
[ALAN]
I have no idea.
All I know is he
called himself "Sword."
What?
[LUKE, SOPHIE]
Hmm?
Don't look at me!
I didn't write the damn thing!
Hang on, you're sure?
'S what it said.
Why would someone
pretend to be you in an email?
[SWORD]
Hmm...
"Whatever happens, don't
let El Dorado reach completion."
That was the last thing it said.
A keyword search in the data I
found yielded more information.
[ALAN] Namely, that there's
a secret organization
formed around a
genius programmer.
[LUKE] What happens if
El Dorado "reaches completion"?
[ALAN]
I couldn't uncover any details,
only stuff about finding
eternal happiness.
Not the first time
we've heard that.
[alarm rings]
[SOPHIE gasps]
What's that?
[ALAN]
Oh God, they've found me!
What do we do?
[SWORD]
I'll take care of these guys.
You take Sophie
and our new friend.
[SWORD]
Sorry.
We were just about to close up.
So you fellas should go
do your shopping elsewhere.
[LUKE] They have no
intention of letting us escape.
We'll have to find
a new hideout.
There's a drainage
system underground
that leads to the outside.
If we can make it that far,
there's a chance for we could...
[ALAN]
Jesus, look at me.
I'm so petrified
I can barely function.
How can I be so spineless?
From the first moment I found
out what was really going on
in this town, all I could
think to do was hide.
[SOPHIE]
That's not true.
Listen to me.
You waited for us.
Most folks wouldn't
have, but you?
No. You stuck it out.
Right.
There still might be
something I'm able to do.
Let me see your phone.
The data; I'm transferring
it all to you.
Just... Just in case
something happens.
Everything I dug up at GarEden.
Mysterious email included.
We're running out of time.
[LUKE]
Damn it.
Where the hell are they?
[SOPHIE]
H-Hello?
I'm sorry.
Are you trying to
say something to me?
[SOPHIE gasps]
Something go wrong?
Are you all right, or...?
[SOPHIE gasps]
Luke!
Enemies inbound
at ten and two o'clock!
[LUKE]
Got 'em.
Third floor, one o'clock.
Second floor, eleven o'clock!
What is happening?
Excellent work!
Look, don't worry 'bout
payin' me back, all right?
That isn't an option!
Looks like we're in the clear.
Yeah.
What's this?
[SOPHIE gasps]
Martin?
[ALAN]
You know the guy?
[SOPHIE]
Yes!
He's my brother!
Wait, just a second.
You're telling me
you're actually
Martin Hennes' little sister?
How do you know you he is?
[ALAN]
Hennes is the programmer!
The one I was telling you
about from the data search.
You can't be serious.
[ALAN] Yeah, this
is a dock for workers.
I think this ought'a get me out
of here in one piece.
Go to Twelfth Street.
There's a bike,
west of the slums.
Take it.
'S all yours.
Even comes with a barrier.
The roads won't be a problem.
[ALAN]
Thank you.
When you're in Russell City,
look for Fei Long's.
Best authentic Chinese in town.
Gal who helps run the place can
be a bit of spitfire, but hell,
it's more 'n worth puttin' up
with for those fried dumplings.
I can't begin
to thank you enough.
I'm afraid I only ever
spoke to Martin once,
so I can't really pretend
I know that much.
But I know one thing.
He did say his little sister
made him proud.
So, guess what I heard?
Somebody really came through
for us, didn't they now?
Hey!
Don't treat me like a child!
But you are a child!
How did you know
where the Horrors were?
Oh, yeah.
Some little girl
told me where to look.
Some little girl?
[SOPHIE]
Uh-huh.
Think she has something
to do with the email
supposedly written by Sword?
[SWORD]
What is going on?