[SWORD] The place where Sophie
lives, it's circled on the map!
Get Sword over here! Hurry!
Go. Now.
[SOPHIE cries]
[DARK KNIGHT]
Sophia Hennes.
I've been looking for you.
My master is the
King of El Dorado.
[DARK KNIGHT]
You have been summoned.
[police siren blares]
[siren continues]
Damn it!
[LUKE]
The Dark Knight himself.
I've been waiting a
long time for this moment!
Luke! No! Stay calm!
[SWORD growls]
We gotta get out of here.
Come with me
to Fei Long's place.
[DARK KNIGHT laughs]
Here I figured you were no more
than typical Makai
Alchemist trash.
[DARK KNIGHT]
Heh. How marvelous.
By all means, Alchemist,
entertain me.
Show me your strength.
Come.
I live to pit myself against
those who I deem worthy.
[LUKE]
You bastard.
[panting]
Stay focused and shift
your center of gravity
by repositioning your waist.
[LUKE]
Yes, sir!
[LUKE cries]
[LUKE]
You were without peer.
No one dared cross swords
with the Silver Knight!
Now look at you!
By my own hand, you will fall!
[gasps] Yes, of course.
Why, if it isn't Luke.
[LUKE gasps]
Grown quite a bit since
last time we saw each other,
haven't you, boy?
[yells]
[DARK KNIGHT]
Sadly.
You're still a child.
[DARK KNIGHT chuckles]
[LUKE grunts]
[DARK KNIGHT grunts]
[LUKE groaning]
[LUKE grunts]
[screams]
[LUKE groaning]
[LUKE]
By... my own hand...
That really all you got?
Then I have no use for you.
[SWORD]
That's as far as you go.
Let's dance.
[STAFF 6A] We have to get
the barrier set up!
Quickly, before things
escalate further!
[STAFF 6B]
Madou tools. Talismans.
Take everything.
[STAFF 6C]
Our main defensive line
will be the traffic light
in Sector Twenty-one.
Child. Please, is he or is he
not after you specifically?
[whimpers] I have no idea!
None of it makes sense!
[DARK KNIGHT]
I've been looking for you.
My master is the
King of El Dorado.
You have been summoned.
[SOPHIE]
This is my fault.
I'm the reason she...
Oh, god.
What's happening?
Why, why would a Horror...?
She didn't deserve to die!
Meifang.
Stop crying. There's no time.
Sorry. Dry those tears.
Find your words.
If you want the dead
to rest, then be strong!
[SOPHIE gasping]
We must do our best to protect
this city from the Dark Knight.
Let us begin with you.
A place of greater safety will
help you get your bearings.
Meifang. Take her down below.
[DARK KNIGHT chuckles]
[DARK KNIGHT growls]
[CROWD screaming]
[STAFF 6A]
Shifu!
The barrier will only
hold for so long.
What then?
[pinging]
[STAFF 6A]
Shifu?
[FEI LONG]
Legions of small fry are drawn
to the noise like
moths to a flame.
[FEI LONG]
Contact the diner immediately.
Have them call whoever's nearby.
We need all the help we can get.
Massive Horror termination's
on the menu tonight.
Get ready.
We are protected by
the barrier down here.
We will be fine.
Horrors can't get in easily.
There's a place up ahead
where we can rest.
Don't worry.
The area is extremely secure.
We'll get some sleep and figure
out a plan in the morning.
Our line of defense has
been broken through.
[HORROR 8A growls]
[SOPHIE screams]
The girl has been summoned.
I must obey His Majesty and
bring her to El Dorado--!
[MEIFANG grunts]
You okay? Come on!
[HORROR 8A roars]
[BOTH panting]
[MEIFANG]
Hold on tight!
[gasps]
El Dorado. What is
that all about?
Who's this king supposed to be?
Never mind.
Let's get to the shelter.
...scheduled broadcast.
Breaking news out
of Russell City.
Footage from multiple sources
confirms a massive explosion
in the heart of downtown.
We don't know the
cause at this point,
but several buildings have
sustained considerable damage.
Anyone in the area is advised...
[SWAT LEADER 8A]
Go! Go! Go!
[DARK KNIGHT]
Garo's blade.
The most powerful
sword in existence.
Exquisite!
Not a weapon for naive upstarts
or the faint of heart.
[DARK KNIGHT]
Thank you, Master.
I am honored.
It is a privilege to face such
an accomplished adversary.
Well worth the journey
from El Dorado.
[SWORD]
Who exactly is your master?
[DARK KNIGHT] If you would know,
ask with your blade.
I respond to strength.
That is why I walk this path:
the chance to fight
true warriors!
[SWORD] This is what the
Silver Knight's become?
That's just sad.
Everyone looked up to you!
Hell, I looked up to you!
You're pathetic!
[SWORD grunts]
[SWORD yells]
[DARK KNIGHT grunts]
[SWORD groaning]
[DARK KNIGHT]
"One who protects," indeed.
Arise and join me,
Golden Knight.
Duty, conviction.
What are these but chains?
Break them and taste freedom!
Claim your true power and
be a god among insects!
[SWORD]
What would be the point?
Power isn't for us,
it's for those we protect!
Toss them aside for our own
gain, and it loses all meaning!
[DARK KNIGHT]
The world profits nothing
when the weak are
allowed to thrive.
Deluded fool.
You are a slave.
Let me shatter your bonds.
[SWORD gasps]
[SWORD grunts]
[CROWD screaming]
[DARK KNIGHT]
Do you understand now?
The power you believe in
has no meaning.
[LIZZY laughs]
Hey, big brother!
[DARK KNIGHT]
So be it.
[SWORD yells]
[SWORD grunting]
[DARK KNIGHT chuckles]
Excellent!
This is who you really are!
Give me everything!
Show me the Golden
Knight's rage!
Prove yourself a force
to reckon with!
[SWORD grunting]
[SWORD]
I've had enough of you!
What in the world is going on?
[SWORD, DARK KNIGHT grunting]
[DARK KNIGHT groans]
[SWORD grunting]
[SWORD yells]
[DARK KNIGHT laughs]
[DARK KNIGHT retches]
[DARK KNIGHT] I'd forgotten
what it feels like.
What a wondrous thing--pain.
What a gift you've given me!
[SWORD yells]
[DARK KNIGHT]
We shall fight again.
I leave Sophia Hennes in your
more than capable hands.
Until next time...
Keep your blade sharp!
Police continue
their investigation
into last night's explosion,
but as yet, no official
cause has been given.
We take you now
live to the scene,
where the Russell City
Police Department...
[BOTH gasp]