[LUKE] No reason this
should be such a chore.
[SWORD]
Hey-hey!
[LUKE] You're either
phenomenally inconsiderate
or phenomenally stupid.
Which is it?
We're not supposed to get
involved with people.
[SWORD] Yeah, well,
that's not how I operate.
Can't protect somethin'
you don't make an
effort to understand.
That's something.
An ex-sprinter who can't
walk up and vanishes?
S'pose sometimes it's worth
doing things my way.
[LUKE] If you find the Horror,
I want you to lead him here.
I don't want another mess.
Zaruba!
[PRISONER A groaning]
[PRISONER A]
Owie, owie, owie!
Whaddya go and do that for?
[BOYFRIEND A chuckles]
Seriously?
Okay, that just
happened? Shall we?
[yells]
Rise and shine!
Hi, Meifang. Sorry to
keep makin' ya do this.
[MEIFANG]
I don't understand.
Why bother setting your
alarm if you have me?
I keep thinkin',
one of these days,
the damn thing'll be enough.
Force a' habit.
[STAFF A]
Zao an, Sword.
[STAFF B]
Zao .
[STAFF C]
Yeah. Zao , zao , zao .
Yadda, yadda.
One of you ever gonna take
over breakfast detail?
You're kidding, right?
Not until you can afford
to pay rent, big man.
Or settle up your tab.
You are a one-man dinner rush.
'Least you could
do is make the food
you're going to shove
in your stomach.
That's what Meifang says.
Ugh! Pretty cold-blooded
there, guys.
Our special Golden
Knight's Fried Rice.
Rarest item on the menu
made to order for you.
A man who can't
rise with the dawn
should speak with more humility.
Gotta have my
beauty sleep, right?
Don't wanna look like a
prune in my twilight years.
Since when does one
bearing the title of Garo
concern himself with looks?
When are you gonna come
outta retirement, Fei Long?
[FEI LONG sighs]
Run along and see if your boss
has any table scraps for you.
[SWORD chuckles]
[WAITRESS]
Welcome-welcome!
What a coincidence!
Did I say you could sit down?
Aw, c'mon Luke.
Thought we'd have a chat.
[bell chimes]
[WAITRESS]
Welcome-welcome!
[SOPHIE]
Hello-hello!
Ah! Sword! Hey!
On second thought,
you're tryin' to eat, so--
I'd like to have word.
It's not what it looks
like, all right?
I don't know who she is!
Hey, would'ya mind grabbing
me an orange juice?
That'd be great.
Oh. Hi.
[SWORD] I, uh, think you
may have the wrong.
Whoa! Shut up!
Is this guy a Makai
Knight, too, or what?
[SWORD]
Uh.
Full disclosure.
She's the girl from
the highway job.
Uh-huh, and why exactly is
she still hanging around?
Extenuating circumstances?
Idiot.
Sword, you're meant to
protect people like her,
not put them in greater danger.
[SWORD]
Uh.
Yeah, I know.
[LUKE]
Good.
So you have no qualms about
erasing her memory.
Easy there, tiger.
This discussion's over.
Just hear me out. She's
looking for El Dorado.
I'll never understand you.
[SOPHIE chuckles]
[WAITRESS]
Thanks for stoppin' in!
[SOPHIE]
He seemed kinda ticked off.
Trust me, it's a long story.
[SOPHIE]
I'll bet.
So you dig up any promising
leads on our case?
Not really how things like
this tend to play out.
Now, now.
You're the only one I can
depend on for information.
[WAITRESS]
Excuse me.
Not to rush, but if you happen
to know what you want.
[SWORD]
Thank you for this bounty.
T-bone. Medium rare.
T-bone, medium rare.
Jeez, Sword. All you ever
eat is hunks of meat.
Hey. Whaddaya want?
I eat for pleasure,
not nutritional value.
Enjoy your life to the
fullest, that's my motto!
[SOPHIE]
Hm.
What is it you normally enjoy
doing, then? Seeing a movie?
Now that you mention it, I
haven't been to one in a while.
Tell me where you live
and I'll tell you
where the best theaters
are near you!
Nice try, kiddo.
You afraid to let me see it
'cause it's a total dump?
Is it ghetto, Zaruba?
I'm not telling one
way or the other.
[KNIGHT]
Raise it high.
Show me the strength
of your convictions.
Ideals. Ambition.
Without might, they are
dust in the wind.
[KNIGHT]
Keep at it, Luke.
Or don't you wanna be strong?
[WOMAN A]
It's not a hoax!
People who set foot in that
place vanish into thin air.
It's all over the Internet.
[MAN A]
So it must be true.
I was gonna dump him.
Went to a movie so he
wouldn't make a scene.
I don't even remember
what was playing.
Some old piece of crap.
What was your game plan exactly?
Whisper in his ear and duck
out before the credits?
Yeah, how'd it go down?
Well, he... he disappeared.
Sounds like he dumped you.
Are you for real?
[WOMAN A]
Yes.
Son of a bitch made
off with my wallet.
You believe that shit?
[MAN B]
Uh...
[SWORD]
Uh?
[MAN A] Ha-ha! You really
had me goin' there!
[WOMAN A]
Screw you, Internet!
[MAN B]
Good one. Savage.
[bell chimes]
Oh my! Are you here by
yourself, little girl?
[SWORD]
Hm?
I thought I'd find you here.
Sorry, you can run,
but you can't hide!
Wha--? How the hell?
[WOMAN A]
Ugh. Awkward.
I don't wanna make assumptions,
but ain't she a little young?
Wow. Just when you think
you know somebody.
Wait, do you think?
Dude! That's gross!
Do I even wanna know
how you found me?
[SOPHIE] I have my ways.
Look in your pocket.
[SWORD]
Huh? Why?
Pretty cool, huh?
I snuck it on you at the diner.
A little patience, a free GPS
tracking app on my phone,
and voila !
Ha!
What the hell is wrong with you?
She's a bit more troublesome
than you expected, eh?
So this how you
stay in shape?
No wonder Horrors don't
stand a chance against you,
you're a beast!
Yeah, that's not
really how it works.
This supposed to
be you? Too cute.
Yeah.
I'm guessing you
have a younger sibling?
They must really look up to you.
Sister actually.
So how come the two of you
don't live in the same place?
She's a little too far away.
Like El Dorado?
'Fraid not.
Oh, I, uh...
Welp, you know where I live now.
Let's get you home.
I didn't mean to be rude.
Sorry for just showing up.
[SWORD]
No worries.
Hey, have you eaten?
I'll make some pot stickers.
Like a to-go order?
Yes, please! The others
would love some!
[whistles]
[chuckles]
[AUDIENCE laughing]
Daddy, wait!
[WOMAN B]
I just... I just really...
...wanted to see you.
[WAITRESS]
Thanks for waiting.
Huh. People disappearing
at a theater.
[WAITRESS]
Welcome-welcome!
What? I thought that
was an online hoax.
[SOPHIE]
Mornin', Sword!
Mind if I join you guys?
Sophie, I'm in the
middle of somethin'.
[SOPHIE]
Oh, my bad.
I prefer to take care
of this one on my own.
Why?
[LUKE] You've got enough on
your hands playing babysitter.
See ya.
Uh. Hey!
Where's he get off
callin' me a ba--?
One adult. Enjoy the show.
Sorry, sir. This is
a smoke-free theater.
It's my third time here.
[WOMAN C]
Really? Huh?
What's with the
popcorn? Is it free?
[MAN D] Did I tell you?
This place is amazing!
[LUKE] Let's hope it's not
sitting in the audience.
I need a clear shot.
[FLOORMAN A]
Hey, uh, movie's over, pal.
There's no post-credit scene.
[LUKE] Guess I need to look
at the staff schedule,
and the box office record.
I'll have to make this
a proper stakeout.
[STAFF B]
Sophie! Where's that sesame oil?
Hao de !
[STAFF A]
Sophie! I need you on dish prep!
Hao de !
[STAFF C]
Sophie!
Right! Hao de !
[MEIFANG] That tiny girl is
worth ten of you. At least.
[SWORD] You don't have
to say it like that.
Hey, Sophie! Take a five!
[chuckles] Hao de , hao de !
[MAN E]
Yeah, I know, right?
Problem is he doesn't
have the first clue.
Evidently your
friend doesn't know
what is meant by
"curiosity killed the cat."
She's a tough cookie, all right.
Poor Luke, though.
Word is he's having a hard
time on the theater job.
Not that he's told me anything.
Makai Alchemists are
a stubborn bunch.
Particularly the capable ones.
Reminds me a lot
of you, honestly.
Hogwash. When have
I been stubborn?
Um, only every
second of every day.
Isn't that movie theater the
topic of heated debate online?
Yeah, I suppose.
Seems to me it's
worth delving into
if Luke's more direct
approach isn't bearing fruit.
As the saying goes, there's no
wave where there's no wind.
[SOPHIE]
I could do some research.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SOPHIE] I need you guys'
help with a rumor
that's been making the rounds.
Couples go to this theater,
but one of 'em vanishes?
[SCHOOLGIRL AVATAR A]
Oui . I've heard of this.
It came up on a thread
about urban legends.
[DEER AVATAR A]
It's just couples who are into
that sort of thing who are
makin' a big deal out it.
[GIRAFFE AVATAR A]
The story I heard was that
people who sit next
to each other in row L
are destined to be
together forever.
[SOPHIE]
Row L?
[DEER AVATAR A]
Do you know how many theaters
with row L there are?
[RABBIT AVATAR A] Does that have
anything to do with the rumor
that seat 13 is haunted?
[DEER AVATAR A]
Again, do you know
how many "seat 13s" there are?
LOL.
[SCHOOLGIRL AVATAR A]
According to what I've read,
the disappearances all
happen at late showings.
Check out the Bizarre
Cases thread.
[SWORD grunts]
Common denominator's
a specific seat,
based on what I've found.
Specific seat?
Some of the legends
are romantic.
Most of 'em fall into the
"creepypasta" territory.
But they all talk
about row L, seat 13.
There's gotta be
something to it.
Row L. Seat 13.
[KNIGHT]
Luke.
[gasps]
[LUKE panting]
[LUKE grunts]
[KNIGHT] Harder! Treat
this like the real thing!
[LUKE]
Yes, sir!
[FEI LONG]
Sword.
I just got a call from
that woman at the diner.
Huh. No kidding?
That never happens.
[FEI LONG]
Luke has gone missing.
It's faint, but the
scent is unmistakable.
[ZARUBA]
Wait, Sword.
Yeah, where to?
[ZARUBA] Our quarry. I think
it's directly in front of us.
[SWORD]
Say what now?
[ZARUBA]
The theater itself is a Horror!
[LUKE yells]
Surrender or else!
[yells]
You dare hope to don the armor
one day with a body so frail?
[ADELAIDE]
Enough! You've made your point!
For God's sake,
he's only a child.
Come along, Luke,
you're done for today.
[LUKE]
But, Mother--
[ADELAIDE] Is very proud of
how hard her boy is working.
What do you say I make
my special lasagna
for dinner tonight?
Sounds great.
[gasps]
Not yet, though. Just one
more quick round, I swear!
[LUKE yells]
[SWORD] Looks like a perfectly
normal theater to me.
[ZARUBA] The barrier is
powerful, but unstable.
I'd have never caught on
to the Horror's presence
so quickly otherwise.
Something's caused
a fluctuation.
Luke, most likely.
[ZARUBA] There must be
a point of communication.
An opening through
which it feeds.
[SOPHIE] Common denominator's
a specific seat.
They all talk about
row L, seat 13.
There's gotta be
something to it.
[SWORD]
Say, "Ah"!
I gotcha.
[ADELAIDE]
Luke! No more!
[LUKE] But... giving up's
a sign of weakness.
There's no shame in gathering
your strength. Be patient.
Not every battle can be
won the first time out.
Remember that.
Gather my strength.
[ADELAIDE]
Yes.
Now let's go home and
get a decent night's rest.
Clear you mind.
There's no need to think
on it till tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am.
[SWORD]
Luke!
Wake up, you moron!
It's a trap! Think about it!
Your mother?
[LUKE]
Huh? What about her?
Snap out of it, she's dead!
She died right in front of you!
[HORROR A roars]
Nice goin', man.
[LUKE]
Thanks. I owe you one.
Oh, stop. It's not like I did
this for you to be in my debt.
I just like having you around.
Guess that makes me
the sentimental type.
[LUKE]
Can we not, please?
Typical.
Whoa there, cowboy.
I didn't do it on
my own, so you know.
Sophie's the one who found you.
If you owe anybody anything,
far as I'm concerned, it's her.