[KING chuckles]
Futile.
This world and I
are one and the same.
You cannot vanquish me.
[SWORD]
Then I guess it looks like
I have to take out
an entire world!
[ZARUBA]
Here, use this!
[SWORD]
Yes!
It can't be.
Garo.
I... I don't want
anyone else to die.
Help me.
Give me strength.
Whatever you've got!
Please! Help me protect him!
This is for Sword!
[SWORD] I missed my window
outta here 'cause of you.
So, now what?
[DARK KNIGHT]
As of the ancient one's demise,
my contract with
the ring is null and void.
I stand before you
a creature of agency,
a warrior answerable to no one.
I am my own master.
My very soul has existed
for this moment alone!
Come, Golden Knight,
let us settle this!
Well, damn.
You ever hear of quittin'
while you're ahead maybe?
[SWORD] This is what we
call a teachable moment.
[SWORD] Allow me to
show you real strength!
[SOPHIE]
Gina.
Luke.
Well done.
I'm proud of you, Sophie.
Thanks.
That means a lot.
Hey, where's Sword at?
I made his sister a promise.
[SWORD]
Shame you're such a jackass.
Kind of heft you've got,
we coulda faced Makai itself.
Taken out the Horror
scourge at its source.
[DARK KNIGHT]
Don't speak to me of shame.
With your unparalleled might,
you could have blazoned
your name in the stars
and taken pride of place
among the greatest
warriors of all time.
Your legend would
have endured for eternity!
[SWORD] My strength has
nothing to do with me.
It's theirs.
I fight for those who can't
take up arms for themselves.
For them.
I pit whatever I have
against the likes of you!
[DARK KNIGHT]
Then you're a fool!
Now that was a fight.
Thank you, my brother.
That was delightful.
[SOPHIE]
Say something.
What's going on?
He should be here.
Somebody tell me why
Sword hasn't come back!
Are you listening?
Luke!
Gina!
Why won't you talk to me?
[SOPHIE]
Let go of my arm!
No!
I'm not leaving without Sword!
Stop it!
He's still in there!
We can't.
[sob]
He'd go back for me if it
were the other way around!
We can't just leave him!
It's not right and you know it!
Stop!
I want to protect him!
Luke.
Please don't.
[LUKE]
I'm sorry.
Sword asked me to do this.
Forgive me, Sophie.
No!
Gina!
Don't let him!
I'm begging you!
Wait.
It's been lovely.
Goodbye.
[gunshot]
[gasps]
Gina.
[NEWSCASTER] It's been
a year since Russell City
was devastated by
a freak hurricane,
but the pace of reconstruction
continues to increase.
In other news,
official reports regarding
the internet security breach
felt by users the world over
last year have been
released to the public.
Authorities attribute the
upset to high-level hackers,
but have yet to name
a specific group.
[gasps]
[KIDS]
Mr. Brooks!
How's everybody doing?
Whoa-ho!
What's with the bag?
Oh, nothing fancy.
Just some early
Christmas presents
for you good girls and boys.
Hey, Sophie!
Get a move on.
Mr. Brooks brought us swag!
Hello?
Sorry.
Be right there.
[MR. BROOKS] Just about the
whole neighborhood pitched
in a little something
for you kids.
It's not much, of course.
Suppose I ought'a let you in
on what they told me about how
this place is gonna
be run from now on.
They've finally
reached a decision.
Awesome.
That's great news.
We're supposed to
have a sit-down tomorrow
with a representative
from the church.
I'm, uh, sorry for
keeping you all waiting
on an answer for so long.
Hey, better late
than never, right?
Things haven't been the
same here without Sister.
But, when we come together
there's nothing we can't do.
She wouldn't have wanted
it any other way.
How the neighborhood
has pitched in for us
would've made her happy.
Must've been
especially rough on you,
seeing as how you're the oldest.
I did okay.
But know what helped?
Martin watching over me.
[SOPHIE] Four years ago,
Martin died in an accident.
The Sister helped me
though the worst of it.
But now she's gone, too.
[SOPHIE] Still, I hold onto
the memories I have of them.
[sighs]
You are totally
spacing out again.
No. I'm not!
Somebody's got a
secret crush, huh?
[SOPHIE]
Gross.
[ANNE]
Nice try!
Bet I know who it is!
It's totally Andrew!
[SOPHIE] It's nothing
like that! Knock it off!
[SOPHIE] Right now,
more than anything, what I want
is to make new memories with
the people who're still here.
[ANNE]
Ugh. This sucks.
Remind me again why we couldn't
just call and have them deliver?
I mean, give me a break.
Why we gotta carry
all this crap by ourselves?
It's Christmas.
The restaurants are
busy enough as it is.
Cut 'em some slack.
Quit acting so entitled.
So, uh, what d'you think's
on the menu for us tonight?
Some beef would be awesome.
Another round of cod stew
and imma lose my mind.
Give a girl some steak!
A burger! Anything!
Am I right?
Hey. You're doing it again.
Earth to Sophie.
Yeah, this is
definitely about Andrew.
Will you stop saying that?!
Jeez.
[ANNE]
Wait up!
Anyway.
What about it?
A nice rib-eye
for the holiday season?
You with me?
[SOPHIE]
Uh... We're having cod stew.
[ANNE]
Aw, man.
[SOPHIE]
Everything I need is right here.
Loved ones watching
over me from above.
People to care for
in the here and now.
Really, what else is there?
Still, though.
Every so often...
[SOPHIE] I can't shake the
feeling I let something slip.
Something important,
just out of reach.
Sorry, Sophie.
That's my fault.
How many times
do I have to tell you
not to run in the house?
Speaking of which, I sure
hope your room is spotless.
--It will be!
--Believe it!
[SOPHIE]
Ow. Dang it.
[door opens]
[ANNE]
Huh?
What's, uh...
What's going on?
Sophie?
Something wrong?
It has to be here!
I know it does!
Come on!
[ANNE]
What're you looking for?
Let me help.
[gasps]
Uh... Well, okay then.
What is that?
Like a charm?
Sophie!
[WOMAN]
Are you all right?
[SOPHIE]
Oh, God.
What's wrong with me?
[SOPHIE]
How could I forget you?
I'm so sorry!
[SOPHIE]
Sword!
[CHIAKI]
With you in just a minute!
[SOPHIE]
Gina.
[GINA]
Uh-oh.
Not that I can honestly
say I'm surprised.
Hi, darling.
[CHIAKI]
Thanks for waiting!
There. You two take
all the time you need, okay?
'S quite a will you have.
It's saying something that not
even Luke's "rain" was enough
to wipe the slate clean.
[GINA]
Sure you wanna do this?
That amulet only
kick-started your memory.
It woke up the past.
But there'll be
a world of difference
once the past comes into focus.
Maybe you bit off more
than you can chew.
Think very carefully about
whether the question
you want to--
[SOPHIE]
Is Sword alive?
One doesn't vanquish
the Golden Knight.
At least not that easily.
He's all right.
Better than all right, actually.
Just turns out he's
not here at the moment.
[gasps]
I can't tell you how glad
I am to hear that.
[sobs]
I was so...
[SOPHIE]
Gina.
There's something else I was
hoping you could tell me.
[GINA]
Hmm?
Makai Alchemists.
How do I become one of them?
Listen.
I know you erased
my memories to protect me.
I get it.
It hurt worse than anything.
I... I could still feel them.
All the things I'd done.
My experiences.
They were...
They were there.
Part of me knew they were real.
[SOPHIE] I have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Maybe this it stupid.
Who knows?
But if there's even a chance
I could protect someone the
way you guys protected me.
Then I can honor
my brother's memory.
Martin can live through
the people I help.
One day,
I'll be strong enough.
I promise you that.
I'll be able to look
Sword in the eye.
[GINA]
You've made up your mind?
[SOPHIE]
Yes.
[CHIAKI]
Thank you for your patience!
On the house,
compliments of the boss.
Best desserts in Russell City.
Consider this an invite to
come back as much as you like.
We do love our regulars.
Still waiting on
that chili shrimp
and five-egg fried
noodles for table two!
And where's the
hell's my sticky rice?
[STAFF A]
Sorry!
It slipped my mind!
[MEIFANG]
That's why I'm yelling at you!
Idiot.
What are you doing?
Pick up the pace!
Table four won't serve itself!
Ugh.
Um. Yeah, I'm on the way there.
Aiya.
It's so peaceful lately
everyone's become a lazy cow.
Peacetime is a beautiful thing.
Be grateful for it.
Whatever.
His "one-man journey"
better not turn him soft.
[FEI LONG]
Hmph.
You, seem unusually
concerned for him.
Maybe you've taken
a liking to this man?
[MEIFANG]
Enough!
Why don't I stay and clean up?
Go home, Grandpa!
[STAFF A sighs]
Meifang is on a tear.
She's always been
easy to piss off.
But lately?
Total dragon!
You've got that right.
I see the years haven't
been exceptionally kind.
When did we last see
each other, Fei Long?
You've, got the choice
booze waiting for us,
I hope?
Yes, indeed.
Guess it's shaping up
to be a three-dog night.
Ah, look at that.
Such breathtaking debris.
Least we were
able to go all out.
In the end I'm sure
you're more than happy.
Goodness me.
I'm a free agent now.
Wherever shall I play next?
[CHIAKI]
Thanks for dropping by!
Your burgers have really
gone off, just so you know.
Tell the boss not
to skimp on quality.
Thanks for dropping by!
Sophie. Shake a leg.
'Kay.
[SOPHIE]
You better be ready, Sword.
'Cause one day soon,
we'll meet again.
[toilet flush]
Last time I test
a new menu item.
Man, they do not pay me
enough to for this crap.
Huh?
My bad.