Hell if I know
what's goin' on, man.
Like I said, it was some
kinda gold lookin' thing.
Why would I be makin'
somethin' like this up?
[CONSTRUCTION A]
Am I busy? Are you kiddin'?
You can't be that big of
a moron. 'Course I'm busy!
Huh? Over on the bridge.
Yeah. That's right. Big.
Like nothin' I ever seen before.
Ugh. You gotta do
this right now?
Hang on, it's rainin'.
[LUKE] No reason this
should be such a chore.
[CONSTRUCTION A]
Anyways... Hold up a sec.
Huh? What were we talkin' about?
Look. Sorry, uh,
I gotta go. Later.
Okay. I'm overdue
for a vacation.
Yeah. No doubt.
This is Luke's M.O.
So, you like takin'
pictures, eh?
Chillin' with mah boy?
Dumbass. You've been played.
Yeah? Well, then prove it!
Pull out your phone!
Lemme see it!
[GIRLFRIEND A] There's a
little thing call privacy!
Really?
Where do you get the balls?
Got a problem, pal?
Yo! Get lost!
[BOYFRIEND A yelps]
[GIRLFRIEND A laughs]
Dude. Pony up.
Fine. Take it, already.
I don't need this shit.
[BOY A snickers]
[BOY B]
Heh.
Ow! Oh, no. Not again.
[BOY A]
Bro!
[BOY B]
It hurts. Like, for serious.
Hey, somebody help us!
My brother's real sick!
Please, mister, if we don't get
the money for his treatment,
the doctor says he could die...
What's going on?
[bell chimes]
Ah! There he is! Hey-hey!
[LUKE] You're either
phenomenally inconsiderate
or phenomenally stupid.
Which is it?
[SWORD]
I deserve that.
Why can't it be both?
[LUKE]
Good point.
[SWORD]
No one's talkin' to you.
[SWORD grumbles]
[LUKE] We're expected
to fulfill our duties
as discretely as possible.
Yes or no?
Look, yesterday wasn't
my fault, all right?
[LUKE] Did you or did you
not leave a giant mess?
C'mon! I was takin'
care of a little girl!
That's gotta count
for somethin'!
Uh.
[ZARUBA]
Never mind. Stupid it is.
[LUKE]
There was someone with you?
Why? Had the enemy
taken a hostage?
Not exactly, no.
'S a special case.
[LUKE] We're not supposed
to get involved with people.
[sighs]
[SWORD] Yeah, well,
that's not how I operate.
Can't protect
somethin' you don't
make an effort to understand.
Am I wrong?
Not to be that guy,
but the way you work?
A little heartless, you know?
[WAITRESS] Hiya, fellas.
Hows it goin' over here?
[LUKE]
Not to be that guy,
but the way you work
only protects your ego.
I heard.
Looks like everything's
in good shape now, though.
[SOPHIE]
Yeah.
One of the sisters'll be
here any minute to get you.
Were they upset?
No, no. More relived
than anything else.
Why? Nuns that scary?
[SOPHIE]
Nah. Not usually.
Talk to me, hon. You really
don't remember anything?
The whole night's a blur?
[SOPHIE] If I have a flashback,
I'll let you know.
Sorry to push. I know
you will, Sophie.
[knocking]
Yeah?
Her guardian's come
to take the girl home.
Is she mad?
I'm sorry, but it's, um,
it's important I find somebody.
I'll be back by
dinnertime, I promise.
Truth is, with any luck,
this'll help me find out
about my brother.
[SISTER] You're aware
what will happen, yes?
If you miss dinner?
Uh! Ma'am!
Very well, go. I don't
suppose it can be helped.
[OLD MAN A] Aw. That's
awfully kind of you, miss.
Hey. Maybe...
She's not talking to you,
Grandpa. My goodness.
Thank you, Sister!
You're the best!
I'll totally be back in time
for dinner! Cross my heart!
[sighs]
[HARDY]
Huh?
You okay? Here.
Hey! Watch where the hell
you're goin', you dumbass brat!
Hardy, please.
Sorry.
My fault. I should be
the one saying I'm sorry.
You hurt at all?
No, I'm okay.
Well, that's good.
[HARDY]
Get outta here a'ready.
[SOPHIE]
But...
Aren't you in a hurry?
Just be careful.
You bet!
[SOPHIE] I'll watch where
I'm going from now on!
Couldn't help it, Enith. Sorry.
[ENITH]
I'm on graveyard tonight,
so I'll see you in the morning.
Promise me you won't
forget to eat something.
Sure, whatever.
Enith.
[ENITH]
Hm?
Stay safe.
Heh. You know I will.
Who're they kiddin'? Rehab my
ass. What a crock a' shit.
I'll never walk again.
And here my legs
are s'posed to be
some kind of national treasure.
Damn it!
Why couldn't someone else
spend the rest of his life
in a wheelchair?
Why'd it have to be me?
[HARDY] I didn't deserve
this! It's not fair!
[HORROR VOICE A] Why don't
you just stand up and run?
[HARDY]
What?
[HORROR VOICE A] Go on.
There's no reason you can't.
Who is that? Who are you?
[HORROR VOICE A]
Someone who can make
your heart's desire a reality.
Relive those glory days on
the track. Accept my offer.
[gunshot]
[CROWD cheering]
[chuckles]
[HARDY]
I'm losin' my mind.
[HORROR VOICE A] You're not
crazy. You were born to run.
I can make it happen.
No! Shut up! I'm not listenin'!
[HORROR VOICE A] You're
satisfied? That's too bad.
Piss off! Go away!
[HORROR VOICE A] Perhaps life
as a cripple suits you.
I'd give anything to
be back on my feet.
[HORROR VOICE A]
You have only to say the word.
Fine then! I accept!
Do it! Put me back
the way I was!
Make it so I can run like hell!
[IMPISH HORRORS laughing]
[HARDY screams]
[HARDY laughing]
[MAN A] Come on,
let's grab another drink.
I think you've had
more than enough.
[HARDY laughing]
[HARDY]
I can run!
I can run again!
Uh, okay, then.
Someone's got issues.
[HARDY]
It's been too long.
[WOMAN B]
Let's get out of here.
[MAN A]
Wait.
I know that guy.
Didn't he win the gold?
[chuckles]
[HARDY] Did it used to
wear me out like this?
'Cause I'm starving.
[LUKE]
He doubled back. Did he see me?
[LUKE] What the--?
What is this guy doing?
I've never felt so good!
[SWORD whistles]
Not hungry?
[WAITRESS]
Welcome-welcome! What'll it be?
'Nother round of
the same, please?
[WAITRESS]
You got it!
Uh, I didn't put
my order in yet.
There's something
special for you.
[WAITRESS]
Sorry for the wait!
Wow.
[WAITRESS] For the gentleman,
care of the house.
[LUKE]
Thought as much.
[SWORD]
I chased him last night myself.
[LUKE] Didn't take him
long to shake you.
[SWORD]
I noticed.
[LUKE] Bastard clocks in
at speeds I've never seen.
Trouble is, he doesn't follow
a discernable pattern.
[ZARUBA] Trying to understand
what's in a Horror's mind
is pointless.
He's startin' to
look like a problem.
Please. No rush.
[ENITH]
Excuse me.
Sorry. I wonder if you
could help me out.
I'm looking for someone
who disappeared last night.
Maybe you've seen him around?
[ENITH]
Uh.
Easy.
Hey, don't just brush
'er off. Girl needs help.
[LUKE grumbles]
And not only that, he
left his wheelchair behind.
All the kidnappings lately
have me fearing the worst.
See, he was sort of
famous a few years ago.
Yeah? What for?
[ENITH] Quick sprint.
He was in the Olympics.
But then...
Oh my God! Seriously?
Why would you keep that from me?
It's not a big deal.
Look, don't worry.
[ENITH]
Don't worry?
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't.
What have we been doing?
Why won't you let me in?
Baby, please. I'm sorry, okay?
Next time I'm hurt, you'll be
the first to know, I swear.
[ENITH]
Next time you're hurt?
I can't do this!
Enith.
[ONLOOKER A]
Look out!
--[thud]
--[CROWD screams]
[ONLOOKER A]
Holy--! Somebody do something!
Get it off him!
[ONLOOKER B]
We need an ambulance!
He's been hitting rehab
like a champ and all,
it's just been a long and
difficult road, y'know?
I understand.
Hey, we see him,
I'll give you a call.
I'd really appreciate
it, thank you.
[SWORD] Listen, I feel
bad even bringing this up,
but like you said, there's been
a lot of kidnappings lately.
Might not be a bad idea
to prepare for the worst.
Yeah, no. I get it.
Thanks for being real.
Sure.
[ENITH]
Well, see you 'round, I guess.
That's something.
An ex-sprinter who can't
walk, up and vanishes?
Yeah.
S'pose sometimes it's worth
doing things my way.
[LUKE] If you find the Horror,
I want you to lead him here.
Huh? Why's that?
[LUKE]
I don't want another mess.
Why's he always gotta
make it so complicated?
[ZARUBA] They say misery loves
company. Why shouldn't crazy?
Heh. Must be why
I hang on to you.
[HARDY]
Enith.
[gasps]
Hardy!
When you weren't here,
I thought somethin'
might've happened.
Don't you dare say
you were worried.
Thank God you're okay.
Huh?
[HARDY]
Yeah. I can run again.
How's that even...?
Whew! Takes a lot out of me.
Damn, I could eat a horse.
Matter fact, I could
eat just about anything.
I'm a bottomless pit.
I stuff myself to the gills,
doesn't even put a dent
in how hungry I am.
[ENITH]
Baby.
[HARDY]
I can't stand it. So hungry.
So hungry!
[HARDY laughs]
[door opens]
[HARDY chuckles]
[growls]
Zaruba!
[HARDY laughing]
[SWORD] Son of a bitch
is fast! I can't keep up!
[ZARUBA]
Should we corner him?
[SWORD]
We don't have much choice.
[HARDY laughing]
[SWORD]
Do it!
[HARDY laughs]
[HARDY laughing]
[LUKE]
Tch.
[yells]
[HARDY yells]
[ENITH crying]
Excuse me, I wonder if maybe
you could help me out.
Have either of
you seen this man?
[MAN B]
Uh-uh.
Sorry, no.
[MAN B] She looks like
she's been crying.
[WOMAN C]
Shut up. She's right there.
[MAN B]
I'm just sayin'.
[SWORD] I wonder how
she's dealin' with it.
[WAITRESS]
Okie-doke! Here we are!
[SWORD laughs]
Yes!
[WAITRESS]
Today's dessert special,
compliments of the boss.
You two make a great team.
Job well done!
Hey, Zaruba.
What was that you said
about crazy lovin' company?
[ZARUBA]
"Like attracts like."
One of those chestnuts
from the Far East.
You're an idiot.
[WAITRESS]
Such balance!
Knock it off.
Nah, you're right.
We're great together.
Still, it'd be better if he'd
just relax once in a while.
Whoa. This is good.
[WAITRESS]
Thank you very much!
Get in there. It'll
knock your socks off.
[growling]
What's the matter?
Thought you were hungry.
Well, this is fun.
Aren't they a pair?