[GINA] I take it you've
never been this far west?
These days it's basically
a demilitarized zone.
[GEORGE] The company he
worked for went bankrupt.
We pretty much lost everything.
[MATTHEW] Seems, uh,
like quite the happy place,
'least to hear them tell it.
[GINA] We can only protect
people by eliminating Horrors.
Even then, the price
they pay is high.
[MATTHEW]
Let me ride your wave of glory
all the way back
to Russell City!
[SWORD]
Fade away into the darkness!
[GINA]
In the end, no battle can help
but leave a trail of collateral
damage in its wake.
There's nothing we can do
about the pain victims
feel afterwards.
Let's move.
Is that the place
we're looking for?
[SWORD]
Probably.
I'm not clear on the details.
We're on the right track,
according to the
info I've gathered so far.
El Dorado should be dead ahead.
Hidden in these mountains,
I'm willing to bet.
The intel I have matches
up with yours for the most part.
People east of Russell City
have been traveling out
this way in droves.
"Eternal happiness
awaits you in El Dorado.
Gone will be the pain
and suffering that have
plagued your existence."
Yeah, but I mean,
what is it, exactly?
Heh. If we knew, this'd
be a walk in the park.
We could ask
the Land of Guidance.
Seems kind of risky.
You sure?
[GINA]
Yeah.
Might as well.
We're in the neighborhood.
[SWORD]
It's a secret location.
Kind of a hideout
for Alchemists.
Real mysterious.
Like the name implies,
it's where they go for help.
Question is,
will it "guide" us to El Dorado?
Sure.
Only problem being
without the right qualifications
you might get yourself
chucked off a cliff.
Huh?!
Don't be a jerk!
[SWORD]
Knock it off!
I'm trying to drive!
[GINA] We go the
rest of the way on foot.
How much further?
Seriously.
People actually live out here?
Huh?
We're almost there.
Look.
Ah!
[GINA]
Ferre Salé Dessimo.
Holy cow!
[GINA] The Makai Alchemist
village of trials.
It's so bouncy!
It's like I'm walkin'
on a sponge.
[GINA]
Woven reeds.
Whole commune's built on
floating islands of this stuff.
[GINA] Legend has it Alchemists
created this mini archipelago
as a refuge from
the never-ending fight.
Here, the old ways
persist unaltered.
Madou tools are crafted.
Obscure and
forgotten technologies
are studied in-depth.
[CHILD A]
Gina! You're back!
[CHILD B]
How long you gonna stay?
Sorry, my dears.
'Fraid I'm only passing
through on a job.
Goodness gracious,
look at all of you!
Hey! They let me on
the fishing boats now!
Isn't that great?
No kidding? That's incredible!
[CHILD C]
Miss Gina! Miss Gina!
I'm learning how
to make amulets!
[GINA]
Oooo!
I'll have to get you
to make me one next time!
[ELDER] I thought
things seemed livelier.
Makai Alchemist Gina,
I can't remember
the last time you visited.
Greetings, Elder.
[ELDER]
Rare of you to bring friends.
But a young girl? Hmm?
Huh?
Ah. Never mind.
A certain gun-toting colleague
of yours travelled here
not too long ago to
partake of the trials.
You mean Luke.
[ELDER]
Hmm?
Secluded though we are here,
persistent enough
rumors do reach us.
It would appear
El Dorado has grown
into something
of a hornet's nest.
That one's brand new.
We just rolled out
the prototype.
You can fire it from a gun.
Or, as is, use it to invoke
one honey of an explosion.
I'm a fan.
Thank you.
[GINA] What else you
got I haven't seen?
[CRAFTSMAN]
Feast your eyes on this.
Monster Gatling gun.
Specially designed
to shoot 6,000 rounds
of Alchemist ammo per second.
Not cheap, but uh,
worth every cent.
Great, throw it in.
Cash okay?
[CRAFTSMAN]
Yes, ma'am!
[ELDER] The Land of Guidance
is beyond this village,
hovering above a mountain peak.
It is sacred.
Normally only
Makai Alchemists may enter.
You friend will be an exception.
Gina asks that I permit you
and the girl to accompany her.
Are you sure?
Sophie was born
under a curious star,
thus shall her fate unfold.
In the not-so-distant future,
that child's actions will
shake the world to its core.
[SOPHIE]
Sword!
You won't believe it!
Wow! Just wow!
When Gina goes shopping,
she spends more money
than most people make
in their entire life!
She does have
extravagant tastes.
Though you gotta wonder
how many men she's made weep
collecting a fee.
What d'you mean?
You're too young to understand.
Nothing wrong with a
gal living by her wits,
is there?
Wait. Are you trying
to tell me she's--?
Uh. No!
I'm just sayin' she knows
how to break hearts.
And, she can be
a tad bit greedy.
Heads up.
Apologies.
Did you have a pleasant
chat with the elder?
[SWORD]
I suppose.
Whoa.
Those Madou tools?
What? These?
Just an accessory
that caught my eye.
It may be our duty
to eliminate Horrors,
but I still have to
take care of Gina.
No rule against spoiling
ourselves, is there?
[laughs]
[SWORD]
Some of that over here please!
[WOMAN B]
Here.
[WOMAN A]
Enjoy.
There's plenty more
that came from.
The net almost
wasn't big enough!
[laughs]
Tell us a story from
one of your missions!
[GINA laughs]
[WOMAN A] My! You've got
a healthy appetite!
[laughs]
You sure know how
to handle yourself
around a bunch of kids.
'S not that big of a deal.
I'm just used to 'em, is all.
[SOPHIE]
Used to them?
My upbringing.
Believe it or not I grew up
in an orphanage like you.
Have you finished
with the preparations?
[gasps]
Brave soul, who would
challenge the Land of Guidance,
may the path to what
you seek be clear.
[SOPHIE] What d'you think made
Gina choose this sort of life?
Huh?
I asked her about it once.
Didn't get an answer.
Thanks for the ride!
Amazing.
I had no idea a world
like this even existed.
People fighting
behind the scenes,
risking their lives
to save others.
Even the weapons
they use are a mystery.
It's just...
I'm in the middle of it now,
and I barely know anything.
I feel like an idiot.
Some things
it's better not to know.
Don't sweat it.
But you're so alone.
Huh?
[SWORD]
We know what we signed up for.
'Sides, there's a
decent enough tradeoff.
People like you get
to live a normal life.
Pretty sweet.
[gasps]
This is the Land of Guidance?
Wait for it.
The temple only appears
under a full moon.
Think of what you're
seeing as a gateway.
[GINA gasps]
[SOPHIE]
What? What's wrong?
[GINA]
That inscription.
"Those who seek guidance
must first display resolve."
Move!
Sword! Why'd--?
This trial's for Gina;
no one else.
Sorry, 's not our
place to get involved.
[roars]
[sighs]
[gasps]
Gina! Huh?!
[GINA pants]
You want resolve?
I'll show you resolve.
I'm prepared to
do whatever it takes.
Horrors must be eradicated!
They are a blight on this world!
An offense to reason!
Yet if I must be a blight.
If I must go against reason
to vanquish them, so be it!
All right!
[GINA]
Vee-nor-ma-cure-eh.
Come, O mana
of the sacred earth.
Obey my command and
return this pitiable creature...
[GINA]
...to dust!
[sighs]
[GINA]
You okay?
Oh yeah, sure.
[grunts]
Now, you're worried.
Gina!
You good?
Are you hurt?
[GINA]
Not even a scratch.
[SOPHIE]
Neat!
'S that from that monster?
[MIA]
A stone of protection.
That which reflects all magic.
Shielding from danger
those who brandish it.
Heed well this warning.
Though a warrior be
of considerable skill.
Only an iron purpose may
awaken the stone's power.
M-Mia?
[GINA]
Greetings, Land of Guidance.
It's been a while.
[SWORD] The temple guardian
is using your little friend
as a mouthpiece?
Gotta admit I didn't
see that comin.
[GINA] Yeah, he can be
surprising like that.
This is the spirit that's
guided Makai Alchemists
since time immemorial.
You, whom the
darkness known as "King"
would stop at nothing to seize.
Will you be the key
to this calamity?
[gasps]
So you've heard of the guy.
That's encouraging.
I do not claim omniscience.
Such knowledge
as I have is meager.
His name is carved
in ancient prophecy.
The eternal being.
He and the ring
he forged are everlasting.
A timeless,
inextinguishable evil.
One that evades destruction
through unequaled
guile and cunning.
Never is his power direct.
Rather, he delights
to see others dally
and drown in the
power he bestows.
The ring is the
crystallization of that power.
With it, he not only
controls darkness,
but is darkness personified.
Commanding freely those ravenous
beings known as Horrors.
Whosoever comes into possession
of the ring is changed
by the vileness within.
It renders the
heart's desire manifest.
So let me get this straight.
Our guy's been around a while,
and he has a ring lets him
get his hooks into
people like Knight.
Wait, so it's not a myth?
Something like
that really exists?
[MIA] The King has established a
seat of power and christened it
El Dorado.
The reason I cannot yet see.
I fear catastrophe
awaits all mankind.
Please, wise spirit.
Show me by what road
I might come to what we seek.
Your resolve is strong.
I see it.
Go now.
Leave here.
East of this peaceful land
sprawls a city men
call El Sanvados.
South of that, you will
find the gathering dark.
But beware the truth.
Veiled in shadow,
what you seek lies waiting.
Impenetrable even to my gaze.
So very deep does it dwell.
[MARTIN]
Sophie!
Huh? Martin, is that you?
[MARTIN]
Sophie!
Grab on to my hand!
[MARTIN]
Sophie!
[SOPHIE]
Ah! I'm here! I'm here!
[SWORD]
Sophie.
Hey.
Wake up.
What happened?
Are you okay?
I, uh...
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Mya!
Ugh! What the hell's goin' on?
Okay. Guess we're done.
We got what we came for.
Yes, we did.
Excellent work, Mia. Thanks.
Miyaahh!
Sophie.
This is yours.
Take care of it.
[SOPHIE]
But, you...!
You're the one who earned it!
The trial was just a formality.
Known my path for a while.
Heh. Ever since I was young.
Aw, don't worry.
The whole point of
this was to get a line on
where to find
El Dorado, right?
Go on.
The stone belongs to you.
Consider it a gift.
Huh?
Hey, remember what the
Land of Guidance told you.
Without an iron purpose,
that stone is nothing.
Just a pretty rock
glinting in the light.
You wanna call on its power?
You gotta dig deep.