It's kind of depressing...
when your day ends just as the
sun has begun rising, isn't it?
I know this is the fate of a bar hostess,
but it's not healthy.
Really?
I actually think it's pretty nice...
While's the sun is down
we become the stars
that light up the darkness
of the night.
Besides, Bargain Dash ice cream
tastes so good after hard work!
Otae, I really envy how easy
going you always are.
I can't take it anymore.
Some samurai named Sakamoto was
all over my butt again tonight.
Honestly, just get used to it, Oryo.
I also told you to break their fingers
whenever they try to do that.
You're actually breaking fingers?
I thought we're the stars?
You're more like a black hole!
If only the new girl, Hanako,
could be as tough as you are.
She took off from work today, too.
I wonder what's wrong.
Who knows?
It's not all that unusual
in our line of work.
It's a pretty tough job.
Isn't that Hanako?
I wonder what she's doing over there.
Hey!
What are you doing, Hanaako?
D‐Don't come any closer!
Hanako, don't!
You aren't.
I was wondering what you were doing,
taking time off work, but this...
If you want to catch crayfish,
you need to find a shallow river!
What are you talking about!
Look at this situation, would you!
I just can't take it anymore.
I've had enough.
It's over...
Goodbye!
Look out!!
That was dangerous.
You're the one that's
really dangerous!
My sister sure is late.
And after I prepared a hotpot
now that I finally got paid.
She's probably spending time with
one of her customers after work.
The hotpot is ready.
Hey, what did you put in there?
It looks really dangerous,
like an evil witch's
bubbling cauldron.
I went ahead and
threw everything
that was in the
refridgerator in here.
Hotpots taste better the larger
the variety of ingredients.
How's it taste, Kagura?
I think it tastes like
the bottom of your feet.
Hey, hey, that's not good.
You've got WMD!
That's your own feet
you're talking about.
Now what are you going
to do about this?
I suppose I could try taking
more showers.
I'm not talking about your feet!
I'm talking about the hotpot!
I'm home.
Oh no.
She's back.
‐Sis is back...
‐Do we have any
ingredients left that can
save this thing?
That's it!
‐I'll put my feet in inside it!
‐She is back.
That should fix it!.
Two negatives make
a positive, right?
‐Hm?
Kagura, what are you
putting in there?
It's Bargain‐Dash ice cream.
Big sis said she loves
Bargain‐Dash ice cream,
so she's bound to love this.
Kagura, listen, you may as well.
just be flushing that ice cream
down the toilet.
Let's clean up.
It's better if we get rid of this!
Destroy all the evidence!
Stop that.
Don't give up.
‐It's only game over when we give up!!
‐Hey, Shinpachi,
have you seen my
Bargain‐Dash?
I had it in the freezer.
This is bad.
She's already noticed that the
Bargain‐Dash ice cream is missing.
Where's the ladle?!
‐It's hot hot hot...
‐Forget it!
‐It already melted away.
‐It's burning!
How can I help you?
‐One hundred cups of
‐Bargain‐Dash, please.
Okay, sirs, you do know,
even if you collect a hundred
cups of Bargain‐Dash,
your wishes won't magically
come true.
Just bring me a hundred cups
already, baldy.
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to cheer
you up with some
Bargain‐Dash ice cream,
but I'm afraid...
I did my best to
stop them, Big sis,
but they're a really
hopeless bunch.
Well, at least we have
a hotpot going.
Hanako, dear,
help yourself to some.
Oh...
Oh wait.
You don't like hotpots?
You came here from Osaka,
didn't you?
Would you prefer Osaka
style cuisine instead?
Old Sucker?
Are you a migrant worker?
Me too.
We're alike.
Hanako...
Oh no, I'm sorry.
Ever since I came to Edo City,
I haven't experienced the kindness
of others like this.
I never knew such a kind person
like you existed here.
My dear Hanako...
Old Sucker, what's wrong with you?
Cheer up!
Have a drink!
Drinking makes everything better!
Don't let the city get the best of you!
Hanako, listen you can
tell me what's wrong.
I would like to do what every
is possible to help you out.
We both live in similar circumstances,
after all.
Otae, wow...
Really?
Are you really going
to help me out?
Sure.
If there's anything I can do.
Umm, in that case...
This is difficult to say,
but will you.
I won't lend you any money.
Of course not.
But will, will you listen to my story?
Dream catcher?
That's right.
I fell for something pretty nasty.
I came to Edo City to fulfill my
dream of becoming a dancer...
but they seized all the money
I'd saved up for my dream.
What do you mean Hanako?
I was tricked!
They took advantage
of my weakness.
Oh?
So you want to become a dancer.
So that's why you're
saving up your earnings
working as a waitress.
That's very admirable.
I never knew there were
such respectable youths
in this day and age.
Yes but, you aren't
able to achieve
your dream with just ambition.
If you could, then the
world would be filled
with pilots and baseball players
and other winners as well.
Ambition is the power
to pursue your dreams.
But you need another power
in order to reach the
unreachable dream.
We call this incredible power
a dream catcher,
have you ever heard of it?
Have you?
A dream catcher?
That's right.
Most people would say that you
either have the power
to catch dreams or you don't.
That some people are born with
it and others are born without.
But the Dream Faith shows us
how to overcome
our innate handicaps in
order to achieve our dreams
and make everyone happy.
Do you know the one
thing that people
who achieve their dreams in this
world all have in common?
Tell me, do you?
Julius Caesar, Napoleon,
the soccer player Donaldo,
and the baseball player Chichiro
were all born with this power.
And while we were not,
we have succeeded
in producing it artificially.
And here...
it is!
What is that thing?
They said that all of the people
who achieved their dreams
had a mole with a hair growing
out of it on their body.
I spent a whole lot of money
for this stick‐on mole.
But nothing at all happened...
I was completely duped.
Are you totally stupid or what?
Are you going to let that tiny
bean dictate your life?
Were you planning on
dancing on the stage
with that dirty‐looking
mole on your face?
‐A hair growing mole
‐Come on, Old Sucker!
‐on a dancer?!
‐Get up from the bottom of the pit!
So now tell me...
What else happened to you?
There, there.
You did great, old sucker.
Next time, let's try
for thirty‐seconds.
I was forced to convert to
the Dream Faith Cult.
Also, I couldn't turn down
newspaper salesmen,
so I ended up subscribing
to nine newspapers,
and I bought 20 fire
extinguishers.
Edo City is so scary!
I just can't survive this
concrete jungle, I can't do it!
You wouldn't be able to survive in a
jungle filled with nothing but sloths.
Osaka is a heart‐warming town.
Naturally, there are
bad‐tempered people,
but everyone has a
certain warm spirit
you'd never expect
from a stranger.
But everyone in Edo City is so cold.
People treat each other like strangers.
I just...
I don't think I can get by here.
If you're suffering that badly, then
shouldn't you just go back home?
After all, you can dance anywhere,
you know...
As long as you keep
depending on others,
I didn't think you'll get
very far in life
no matter where you go.
But...
If you still want to pursue your dream
of becoming a dancer
in Edo City, then I'll help you out.
The Capital has its own way
of showing compassion.
Right...
Gintoki ?
Fellow believers!
Do you have a dream?
We dream like crazy!
And are you running towards
your dreams?
We run like crazy!
Well, everyone, what a joy it is
to see you all so full of faith!
If you continue chasing
your dreams here,
you might be able to catch
those dreams pretty soon.
So today, Hanako, who dreams
of becoming a dancer,
has brought us some
new dream chasers.
Let me introduce them to you all.
Hello there, guys!
Do you all have dreams?!
‐We dream like crazy!
Otae Shimura, now tell us,
what is your dream?
My father's dojo.
I would like to rebuild it.
Hanako, dear, we all know
that your dream is to...?
To get my money back from
a phony relig...
My dream is to eat
a giant bowl of rice
that has been covered with a
whole jar of seaweed jam.
But if it comes true,
I won't have anything
else to dream about,
so I'll keep it to myself!
Is that so?
And you...
you probably just want better
eyesight or something boring.
Hey!
At least ask me!
And what is your dream?
My dream?
The thing is, I've misplaced that
a long time ago already.
Then what did you
come here to do?
Look, I just don't have what
I just don't have, okay?
How about "I want silky straight hair,
or something like that?"
Sure, I'll go with that, then.
Get out of here!
Those are the lamest dreams
I've ever heard of in my life,
so what are you after?
Are you really followers?
Maybe I still need
to be convinced.
After all, I hear that
you've got the power
to grant any dreams at all, so...
I wanted to see it with
my own eyes, of course.
Hey, Gin!
Aren't you forgetting why
we're here right now?
Just wait a second.
Before we get her money back,
shouldn't we reveal just
how phony this guy is?
Who are you guys, anyway?
We are not going to let
you make fun of Tom!
‐Get out!
How amusing.
You really want
to see my power?
This is a utopia where
your dreams can come true.
If you can train here, I'll teach
you how to gain the power...
and the ability to grant
dreams just like me.
Dream...
Catcher!
What are you doing?
You said...
your dream is to have silky
straight hair, isn't that right?
Take a look at your hair now.
Oh!
But it's impossible.
Gin's mophead is...
Is silky straight!
Your hairstyle is
totally different, too!
Really?
You're joking, right?
Hey!
Wow!
It's all silky and straight!
It doesn't stick together
or stand up!
Yahoo!
Now it won't get all tangled
on rainy days!
Before you start celebrating,
grieve over that hair style!
Now do you see?
This is the power of
the Dream Catcher!
Those who believe in the
Dream Faith can gain this power.
The power to grant
everyone's dreams.
What is the meaning of this?
There must be some
sort of trick to it.
Right, Gin?
So...
I am a believer, I am yours
to command, Master Ham.
It's not Ham, it's Tom.
Hey!
It's not like Gin to bow
down to someone.
You need to get a grip, Gin!
Hey, you!
Give us the old Gin back, now.
What are you talking about?
This is my true self.
An evil priest put a curse
on me that turned my hair
into an ugly curly mess.
Don't say that, please!
Have confidence in yourself!
You're nothing if you lose
your mop‐top head!
Young lady, your dream was
to have a bowl of rice
with a mountain of seaweed
jam on it, wasn't it?
Okay, okay.
Dream.
Catcher!
Whoa!!
It really appeared!
I am a believer and I am yours
to command, Ham Man.
What do you mean "ham man"?
I told you, it's Tom!
He's got her too!
And so easily!
Everyone, let's celebrate!
We have recruited brand new
members into our Dream Faith!
Let's all achieve our dreams
and be truly happy!
Praise the Dream Faith!
Dream...
Catcher!
You don't do it like that!
You are focusing too much
on the pronunciation.
You're not putting
any feeling into it.
Put feeling into it?
All right, then, I get it!
I think I can do it now!
Die, ugly man!
That's just a bunch
of murderous intent!
They forgotten why we came here
and fallen right into their trap.
Let's just leave those idiots.
Anyway, I'm beginning to understand
why he has so many followers.
They think they were
shown some miracle.
I wonder how he did it.
But Shinpachi, we didn't come here to
prove that he's a fraud or anything.
If you lose sight of your objective,
you'll end up just like those
idiots over there.
You're right.
We've got to get
Hanako 's money back
from that phony religious leader
and cut her a break.
No, that's not it.
We're here so we can
extort money from that
phony religious leader so that we
can rebuild our father's dojo.
What are are you saying?
I don't remember agreeing
to that objective!
Where did that plan come from?
Are you planning to use
the money stolen
from all these innocent people
for your own selfish purposes?
There's nothing wrong with taking
a little reward money, after all.
We're going to save
the rest of the money.
You're planning to take all of it!
So then, this was your plan
all along wasn't it?
Don't make me sound
like a corruption.
I intend to give Hanako's
money back to her.
Oh, wait, come to think of it,
where is Hanako?
Dream Catcher!
Seriously...
How many times are you going
to be fooled by them,
don't you ever learn?
Come on, take us to Jam's room.
‐It's Tom, Sis.
‐No, it's Tim.
I'm getting confused.
So tell me, what do you
plan to do, Otae?
We shouldn't stay here
for too long.
Let's go after the safe
in Tim Burt's room.
Tim Burt's room?
Since when did he become
a phony guru?
Breaking into his safe,
that's like stealing.
It doesn't feel right!
Hey, Hanako, exactly where
did you get those clothes from?
But if it's for the sake of
my dream, it can't be helped!
Hanako, try not to stand
out too much.
Hanako, just go back
to Osaka already.
Honestly, what fools they all are.
They can't even figure out
such a simple trick.
Are they completely blind?
Well, dreams do
make people blind.
Thanks to that,
I make quite a killing.
I can't quit being a
religious leader now.
This is all thanks to your power.
Why don't you come down from
time to time and have a drink?
Hey, you're up there, aren't you?
Owowow...
Oh, no.
Hanako, this is because
you moved around too much.
What are you three doing?
Ummm....
Owowowow.
This is going to make
me bald, definitely bald!
That hurt!
There's wig glue all over
this damn thing.
How did this guy manage to
do this in that one instant?
Hey Gin.
You look a whole lot better that way.
Hey, this is the men's bathroom.
So then he really was a fraud.
I thought you had completely
fallen for his guru act.
You thought I would really
believe this was for real?
I just wanted to investigate
and see what kind of tricks
he uses before making
my move, that's all.
M‐Me, too.
I acted like I was tricked,
so I could investigate.
I'd never being temped
by seaweed jam.
Yeah, yeah, I believe you.
It's true!
As proof, I dug up
some information on Tom.
Tom's done the exact
same demonstration
as he did with us in front
of his followers many times.
But it's only been
pathetic dreams
like curing baldness or getting
a cheap knock‐off handbag.
He's only been
granting dreams
that are very easy to
grant and quickly.
He can prepare for anything
by asking his believers what
their dreams are beforehand.
But the question is how he
was able to make my wig
and your food appear instantly
out of nowhere.
Someone so fast they can't be seen.
Impossible.
A ninja!
I saw it on TV.
But that is so cliché.
Owowowow.
This is bad.
I'm bleeding again.
I wiped my butt too hard.
Gin, Kagura!
Shinpachi, what's wrong?
You need to take a dump?
Are you about to crap
in your pants?
Bad news.
It's my sister and Hanako!
Everyone, I'm sorry to make this
unfortunate announcement,
but it appears that we have
traitors among us.
They had the gall sneak
into my room...
and they tried to steal
all of your offerings.
Do you think this is forgivable?
Never!
Die!
That's right.
Kill them!
Kill, kill, kill, kill...
Hey everyone, everyone,
open your eyes.
You're all being tricked
by this man!
Listen!
You bastard!
You threw a rock at me!
I'll remember your face!!
And I swear I'll kill you afterwards!!
Now I will leave the punishment
of these traitors...
in your hands, my dearest followers
and Dream Faith believers!
Dream Catcher holds the power
to grant wishes!
Everyone, wish intently for the
sort of punishment
you want them to receive‐Ow!
Hey, that really hurts...
And, these criminals
will get the punishment
they deserve without us lifting
our own fingers.
My eye!!
Damn it!
Dream Punishment?
We should just kill them for this!
It's been decided.
You will be punished with death.
Just try to kill us, you fraud.
If you think you can.
You just talk about dreams
and wishes,
but you don't do anything.
You're all such naive people.
Oh, Otae.
You think a mere fraudster
like you could have any
power over us at all?
How can you be so confident
at a time like this?
You have nothing to be
confident about.
Because we believe in something
that is far more powerful than you!
What could be
more powerful,
than dreams?
That would be...
our friends.
What's that?
Hey look. There's someone
on top of the roof!
Wh‐What?
Where is he?
Hey, Gin!
He's over there!
Got it!
Dream Catcher!
Unveiled!
Oh!
It's a ninja!
What's this?
Someone just fell from
the beams of the roof!
Hey!
Hattori!
What are you doing?
Get back up there right now!
Do you realize how much
I'm paying you?
I‐I can't.
S‐Something stabbed
me in the butt.
Stop fooling around,
you moron!
I picked you up off the streets
after the elite secret agent
organization fired you!
Without you, I'm just
a middle aged man.
Sorry.
But I'm quitting.
Toilet paper here is so cheap,
I feel like I'm wiping my butt
with a cheese grater.
Later!
Hey!
I‐It's a ninja...
Why does Tom have a ninja?
You still don't get it?
This is the truth behind
the Dream Catcher.
Think back.
Did he ever make a
dream come true
that wasn't simple and easy
to see or provide?
No!
He preinterviewed
all his followers and chose only
dreams that were easy
to grant in person.
He kept a ninja hidden
in the beams
and acted as if he was
performing miracles
with a speed of light...
You were all tricked by this!
Impossible.
We would never fall for such a
simple trick as that, you know!
Yeah, that's right.
I was bald, but now
I have so much hair!
Hey, this is a wig!
It's true.
Why the hell didn't you notice that
before, huh?
Well, I didn't touch it 'cause I didn't
want my new hair to fall out!
Hey, Tom, you bastard!
How dare you trick us like that!
Give us back our money!!
Where do you think you're
going, Guru?
Why don't you use your
Dream Catcher to get out of this.
‐Pray to your hairy mole for help!!
‐Pray to your hairy mole for help!
In the end, he was like us...
he was just a pathetic man who
was blinded by his own dream.
That's right.
But the only thing different,
is whether you have people
to help you out
and get you back up on your
feet when you sink.
If I ever start drowning,
you'll help me out,
won't you. Hanako?
Of course, Otae.
Next time, I'll show you Osaka's
warm hearted spirit.
D‐D‐Dream Catcher.
Please let me win big at a casino.
What are you
doing up here, Gintoki?
Hey, Gin, I want to eat
a steamed pork bun!
I don't have any.
If you want a steamed pork bun,
ask Santa for one.
You can't fool me.
Everyone knows Santa
doesn't really exist!
The next episode...