Please keep the lights on and
don't sit too close to the TV.
Why do I have to come all the way
out here on such a freezing night?
How many stores do I have to
visit to find meat buns...
Oh, I should've bought
sweet buns for myself.
I don't really like meat buns.
Oh, Man, now they're
all messed up.
all messed up...
How could you do this to me,
it's all your fault!
Look, you completely
wrecked my sleigh!
Now this year is done for!
And it is all thanks to you!
Screw you, it's your own fault!
You old fart, we agreed
that you'd get off
the sleigh whenever
we went downhill!
I should be the one
pulling the sleigh,
I was running from it
for my life!
It kept bashing against
my Achilles tendon!
Now I'm bloody!
All you have to do is outrun the speed
of the sleigh, that isn't so hard.
You're a reindeer, aren't you?!
Your dad was awesome, and he
pulled the sleigh like a real pro,
even when we were going downhill.
He was an excellent reindeer!
Yeah well, you may have
really liked my dad...
but he was always saying bad things
about you whenever he got home.
You are a liar!
Carl and I were like brothers!
He would never do that!
Seriously, he hated your guts!
His last words were, "His white beard
is actually brown"!!
Don't you dare say that out loud,
you bastard!
We can't let anyone find out I dye
my beard white every Christmas!
Well, you're the one announcing
it to the world!
Hey, come on you guys!
‐Settle down.
‐Shut up!
What are you guys doing?
Ow!
Damn it!
What the hell is your problem?!
Just cut the crap, you two.
It's the middle of the night.
People are trying
to sleep right now.
Now look, I don't know what
happened with you, but...
Well, you beat us up
is what happened...
Come on, guys,
let's have a drink.
Who the hell are you?
Drinks help facilitate communication
between people,
like a kind of like
a social lubricant.
I think Napoleon said
something like that,
but I could be wrong...
Hey buddy, get us three more bottles
and some assorted food.
The beardo will cover the check.
Yes, sir.
The Beardo will pay?
‐Are you talking about me?
‐Here.
I ought to shave this stupid beard off
already.
So tell me...
why were you two arguing?
Who are you guys anyway?
Do you guys deliver evening
mail or something?
I uh...
eh, I thought it was kinda obvious...
Well, it's against regulations
so I really can't tell you,
but I ride a sleigh and give kids
something to dream about.
You mean like Peter Pan?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sort of...
‐And my name starts with "Sa."
‐"Sa"?
Satan?
Its close!
But it has...
a far better meaning!
Hm, okay, sorry to cut into
your conversation,
but I think I have the answer.
It is pretty obvious actually.
The hint is hanging
between his legs.
What are you saying?
What kind of hint is that?
What kind of answer is
that gonna lead to?
I don't give a damn if it's
Sandwich or Santa.
That's it!
You just got it right!
Yeah, you just got it right!
So, you're a wild old man who
rides a sleigh at midnight
and sneaks into people's homes
through chimneys, right?
Well, yeah, but...
you just described
me like a burglar.
I got it!
Sorry to interrupt your
conversation again,
but I think I have the answer now.
These are the guys who ride
around in a sleigh stealing
undies from the rich
to give to the poor.
That's not what I'm doing at all!
You look like a gentleman,
but you sure
have a twisted mind, you know!
Presents!
It's all presents, okay?
I ride a sleigh and deliver presents
to all the good children.
That's my job!
But my sleigh is completely wrecked,
you see?
And now it's just...
You don't need a sleigh
to do your job do you?
I absolutely do; the sleigh,
the reindeer,
and the red outfit are my
three trademarks!
It would shatter the children's
image of me if I didn't have them!
A reindeer?
But he looks more
like a monster...
I don't really get it but...
it seems like you're in a fix,
do you need some help?
Here's my business card.
I do everything and anything,
a jack of all trades...
And I'll help you out,
if you pay me.
What?!
What can you possibly do?
Can you get us a sleigh right now?
No problem at all.
Come on, hop in.
Hop in my ass!
Someone is actually inhabiting
the thing right now!
You can actually see him?
What you're seeing is
the cardboard fairy.
He's a fairy that only people
with pure souls can see.
It's obvious you can see him too!
I mean, he's glaring right at you!
We said we needed a sleigh!
That is a cart.
It's not a cart.
It's my home!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Don't worry about the little details...
Sleigh, cart, it's all the same thing.
They even sound almost the same.
It's not a cart.
It's my home sweet home, man!
Oh, I'm sorry fairy...
Your mission is to make
children's dreams come true.
Remember what got you here
in the first place...
Remember those days...
when your eyes were still
glistening with joy,
back when you first started
this job.
What do you know
about me and my job?
Oh, besides, if you're going to worry
about your stupid image...
you ought to start by
addressing this gut, man.
Any kid who sees it will think,
"Oh, he's just like my dad,"
and be so disappointed.
It's supposed to be like that.
I'm a legend, man.
I'm an inspiration to all
those fat comedians.
Also, red isn't the right color
for you.
It makes you look fatter
than you actually are.
Ditch the outfit.
It's totally wrong.
‐No, let me go...
‐You'd look better
in something more chic.
I already told you, this is one
of my three trademarks!
No!
Stop!
Hey, if I take off my outfit,
I'll just be a regular old man.
Hey!
Now this is just...
Isn't right.
No, you both look good and chic.
Just as I thought, black makes
you look slim and cool.
It also makes me nervous
for some strange reason...
like I should go home
and lock the door.
That's because we look
like thieves!!
Nah, you're more like one of
those wild looking dads.
Just throw on a leather jacket
and it'll make you look sexy,
and you'll draw the girls like
a magnet for sure!
There's nothing sexy
about this look!
Look at me, I look like
a grave robber!
Not to mention this
homeless dude...
is wearing my outfit now!
Hey, listen up, can you
give my suit back!
But I wanna be a fashion icon!
But you're already an icon.
You don't need to wear that.
You're an icon for all the guys
on the streets!
Let's start here, alright?
This is a poor residential area,
we should help them out.
Oh, man, if we get caught in
these clothes, it's over,
we'll be immediately reported.
Why does my heart have
to beat so fast...
when I'm not even
doing anything bad...?
So, which child should we start with?
I'm not visiting spoiled kids
who ask for video games.
Let's start with the kids who just
ask for a yoyo or something.
Do you really think you're qualified to
make children's dreams come true?
Kids these days don't want
simple toys like...
I found someone, Yuri Tsukishima...
It's hard to find a kid like her these.
A‐A loving mom, that might be difficult...
Yuri...
I wonder if her mom died...
Ben, it's none of our business,
and you can't make two wishes.
Let's skip her.
How about the other kids?
Is there anyone who wished for...
something like a yoyo?
Why are you so obsessed
with yoyos?
Well, I brought lots of yoyos
because I thought they would
be popular again,
but I was wrong.
I was right about last year's Korean
pop star boom in Japan though.
What kind of presents
did you give to kids
during the Korean
pop star boom?
Oh!
Hey, heh, there might be
a yoyo boom after all.
Yoyo and wings to fly
to the future.
I want a pair of those too...
Who's next?
Who wants a yoyo?
Just forget about the yoyos!
You shut up.
Hey, I don't have anything
else but yoyos this year!
We have to find kids
who want yoyos!
Are you kidding me?
You're just an old man who
hands out yoyos to kids!
And nothing else.
All right...
let's see here...
‐Here we go!
Is this a wish list or a diary?!
How old is this kid...
Damn it!
We were being too loud!
And you're still being too loud!
And now so am I!
Let's get out of here!
Look there!
It's Yuri!
Yuri who wished for a
"yoyo and a loving mom."
And she's waiting for you guys...
She believes that you guys
are going to make
her Christmas wishes come true.
She wrote "a yoyo" next to
"a loving mom."
That means she
really wants a yoyo.
She might have some
memories of her dead mother
attached to that yoyo.
We can't do anything about her mom,
but a yoyo we can get her.
You should visit her ...
‐Yuri!
Mom, there are thieves!
Thieves outside!
Huuuuh?
Um...
Loving Mom?!
Loving Mom.
What?
Please go back to being
a loving mom!
The sun is rising, Ben.
We haven't made a single kid's
wish come true yet
but the sun is already
trying to come up, Ben...
This year's Christmas...
was the very worst.
It's our last chance, Ben.
We can't go home like this...
Let's pick a kid whose family
is so poor
that the only toys they get
are from the Dollar Store,
and then we can grant their
wish.
Then we can go home with
that child's smile in our heart...
Odd Jobs, help us, please.
I already told you that
there's no such kid
in this age where there's
practically everything they...
Hey!
Thanks for coming, Santa.
No problem, no problem at all.
You know you're very lucky to have
a child who is so low maintenance.
‐I finally feel like
‐Where is she?
I'm doing my work as
Santa.
You should really look at
yourself in the mirror...
You don't look like anything
other than a thief.
Hey, look!
Look! It seems like she fell
asleep in the living room.
What are you two doing??
Are you guys here to pull
a prank or something?
She's got a snot bubble!
What are you old farts getting
so excited about?
Hey, my turn, my turn.
Let me try this.
What are you doing here?
Where is my meat bun?!
She's half asleep!
Half‐asleep!
Shoot!
Gotta get out of here.
I've gotta feed the dog!
Let go!
Let me go!
No you let me go!
Hm, I fell asleep under the table!
Oh!
Meat buns!
Gin actually went and got
me meat buns!
Yummy!
♪O‐le, O‐le.♪
♪Samurai's samba!♪
♪O‐le!♪
♪O‐le, O‐le!♪
Kagura, dear,
that's really enough.
Do you want me to splash this
hotpot all over your face?
‐Yeah!
‐Ah, come on!
♪Funky Noodle Went to Town♪
♪Riding on a Phony... ♪
There's nothing like watching
the annual Singing Tournament
on New Year's Eve is there?
You're right.
When our dad was still alive,
we'd used to always have a blast
watching the show together.
Gin sure is late, though...
He went out to buy his comics
and hasn't come back since...
I wonder if he had an accident and lost
his memory again.
He's probably just having an
accident with some random girl.
Why don't you just let him be.
♪Funky Noodle Went to
Town Riding on a Phony.♪
♪Stuck a leather in his hat...♪
Kagura, dear, do you want
these burning hot fish cakes
shoved up your nose?
What's up, huh?
Are you here for the comics?
You here for the comics?
Eh?
Good grief.
There's only one left...
So...
what should we do?
Well, I've...
already been to seven or eight
convenience stores already.
Everyone's got time to shop
so they're already sold out.
Oh yeah? I think I've been about
to ten convenience
stores, too.
If I include those ones, I've actually
been to 15.
Well this sure is.
This sure is a pickle, Teddy really
wants to read these comics...
Oh, Teddy is my son.
He's 5 years old.
Well, my mom really wants it, too.
And she's very sick,
I wonder if she's going to
make it through the new years.
She's probably not going to...
Oh, my Teddy is going to die, too.
Teddy is going to die?
Well... I think you understand.
Sorry buddy.
Wait a minute.
What? Does Teddy really
want the comics?
Comic books these days
have really gone downhill,
I think he'll like this better.
Uh, Teddy is only five years old...
Yeah...
but Teddy might like this, uh, well.
Maybe I should buy it...
It's not for me, it's just for Teddy...
Yes, can I help you?
Hey, wait a minute!
That's not fair!
No, no, I think Teddy is really
too young to read comics.
That's definitely better for him.
He's way too young
for this if anything!
Besides, there is no
such person as Teddy.
Teddy doesn't exist in reality, idiot!
You're the idiot!
I don't have a dying mom either!
You stupid moron!
‐Here's the money!
Hey!
You're killing me!
You ought be ashamed of yourself
reading comics at your age!
Do you have Peter Pan
syndrome and never grow up?
‐No fairy will come near you!
‐Excuse me?
They're probably talking crap
about you right about now!
Look whose talking,
you pathetic comic freak!?!
Don't you have
anything better to do
than. reading comic books
on New Years?!
Excuse me...
Excuse me, but neither of you
have enough money for this...
‐What?
Yeah, it's not enough money...
You have just enough if you
combine your funds.
What do you wanna do?
So, normally, New Year's Eve is a
time to loosen up and celebrate.
But we have a duty
to defend Edo City.
So tonight let's limit
ourselves to one glass.
Just know that I'm proud of each
and every one of you...
and of your showing
restraint tonight.
Thanks to all of you, for your
hard work this year!
Cheers!
You really have no limits, do you?
They're all totally helpless...
Aw, come on!
It's New Year's!
Nothing wrong with having
a little fun once in a while.
You're having fun
every single day...
Oh, well.
I'm not going to drink tonight,
but you guys go ahead
and have a good time.
Is there anything you're
worried about that
you're not saying, you bastard?
Some of the Viper's gang is still
out there, and apparently
a bunch of the explosives have
gone missing from that warehouse.
It's like a pesky snake
that still lives on...
even after its head is cut off.
Like I said, I'll read this today,
and you can borrow it tomorrow.
What do you mean "borrow it"?
I paid for it as well, you bastard,
and let me ask..
Which part of these comics
do you read?
I bet you just read two or three
episodes, and then dump it,
right, but I read all the episodes.
I love comics more than you do.
What do you know?
I'm not satisfied with reading
only the episodes,
so I even read the comments
from the writers at the end.
I even read the lousy
editor's comments!
Hey I even read
the survey results
and then I answer all
the questionnaires
and then I send them in to
the editors every week!
That's no big deal!
I even read those sketchy
ads on the back page,
you know, those phony
looking lucky charm ads.
Sometimes I even order them.
Hey, if you don't cut it out,
the comics
are gonna tear into two,
damn it!
Let's take a timeout.
Take your hands off it for now,
and I promise
I won't run off with it.
You take your hands off it first.
Then I'll do it.
Grow up!!
Grown ups would consider
the safety
of the comic books first and foremost,
don't you think?
It'll be safe as long as you
take your hands off it.
Then let's take our hands off
it at the same time,
counting, one, two and three.
Wait a sec!
Do we take our hands off at
the "t" or the "e" of three?
At the "e."
No, after the "e."
At the moment you say "e,"
or right after you say "e"?
I'm getting so confused now...
Oh wait, let's ask that old lady
to hold it for us.
I'll bet that bent up
old lady is your spy.
You probably paid her to give
it right back to you.
If I could pay an old lady, I'd have
bought the comics myself already!
Excuse me, old lady,
but could you hold onto
this for us for a moment?
Well, I understand that you're a bit
surprised, but please?
Hey.. Are you guys going to
take your hands off it or what?
Hey, hey, cut it out.
You're still refusing to
take your hands off it?!
What are you saying?!
I'm all loose and everything.
You're the one squeezing
it too hard!
Whoaaaaahhh!
Hey!
Take your hands off it!
Gee!
You're gonna kill the old lady!
Hey old lady, that's enough!
Don't push yourself!
‐Crap!
I see...
Viper's gang got away...
And then...
What might their plan be?
Rumor is they're going to
attack the sky terminal.
Let's see...
I heard they'll attack the
sky terminal with a truck...
one full of justa
something bombs...
I can't believe they're going
to do it on New Year's Eve...
What do you think?
Do you think they'll do it?
No way.
Not a chance.
Why is that?
Barbarians who can't enjoy
a New Year's
will never accomplish anything.
Edo is a sophisticated city.
Hey, wait there!
Those comics are mine!
No way!
Those are my comics!
Is he...
a monster?
He's so acrobatic!
Sorry, brother!
I may not look it, but I actually
used to be a secret agent.
Hey! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
If you want to die, then do it
on your own!
I thought it was over for me.
I even came close to crying,
you bastard!
I'm the one who thought
it was all over!
My life flashed before
my eyes.
Hell, it's still flashing
before my eyes!
Just keep flashing for the
rest of your life, idiot!!
All right!
It's mine!
I won't let you have it!
You don't even understand
the superhero comic's
three key principles,
"Friendship," "Hard Work"
and "Victory."
You don't deserve to read it!
‐It's mine!
‐I won't let you have it!...
"Friendship, Hard Work and Victory?"
You think you can master those
just by reading comic books?
Pathetic!
You're just trying to fill the
void in your life by reading
those comic books.
You're just reading comics
to make yourself feel better.
Comics should never be
used for that purpose!
Alright...
This is the best way for men to
communicate at the end of the day.
We'll settle this just as they
do in the comic books!
I prefer love‐comedy manga
over battle manga.
But I have no choice.
Sometimes a man must fight
for his true love!
Gintoki Sakata.
Zenzo Hattori...
‐Now!
What was that?
Did you just hear a
weird noise out there?
I wonder if the cops know that
we're here in this truck.
Don't worry about it...
it's New Year's Eve and even
cops are partying tonight.
Besides, this looks like a
perfectly ordinary truck,
so no one will ever guess it's
equipped with a ton of deadly bombs.
Edo City will soon be a sea of fire.
What?
Give me back...
My comics!
Hey!
Give me back...
My comics!
"Friendship...
Hard Work...
Victory"...
I don't quite get it, but...
Those are important principles...
Who gives a shit!!
This JUMP comic book
is all mine!
Big sister, what's that gong,
gong, gong?
Is it the sound of some
high school kid...
banging his head against the
wall for not getting any dates?
No, that's not it, Kagura.
That's the sound of a businessman
who's been laid off banging his fist
against rocks, swearing revenge.
Hey, sis, what are you
teaching her, anyway?
It's all right.
You have to lie
once in a while
to give a kid something
to hope and dream of.
Well, there's no hopes
and dreams
in that revenge story
you just told her...
Kagura, listen to me, that's
the New Year's Eve bell.
They ring that bell 108 times on New
Year's Eve every year.
108 times?
That's gonna make everyone bang
their head against the wall!
The number 108 symbolizes...
the number of a person's
earthly desires.
Each time the bell is struck,
another desire is struck out
from your soul,
so you can start the
new year fresh.
Kagura, dear, your soul is already
clean because you're young...
so that mean you don't
really need to clean it,
but as soon as people
grow up,
they become more
and more greedy...
Kagura, Shinpachi,
I hope you two don't
grow up to be like that.
Because pursuing your material
desire will only ruin you.
The JUMP...
comics...
are all mine...
Looking at it up close...
it's HUMP comics.
Is that heavy snow?
The spirit of Edo City is to
enjoy every occasion!
The next episode,