Don't sit too close to the screen!
And keep your lights on!
Hi, how can I help you?
Well, you can start by
putting that away.
Aren't you on the clock?
Why are you stuffing your face
like a damn chipmunk?
Because it tastes really good, sir.
Hey, kid, do I look like a joke to you?
Hey!
You're spilling crumbs in my bag!
Look at that mess!
Hey, manager?
Somebody call the manager!
I'm the manager here today.
What's the problem?
What's got you all upset here, dude?
Two big problems that
I'm staring at!
Hey...
that guy seems awfully upset...
What'd you do to get him mad?
No idea.
He's been really cranky ever
since he got here, boss.
Hey! I'm telling you to stop
munching, damn it.
Hey!
We're very sorry, sir.
We're just filling in for today
so we don't really understand
the complicated stuff.
But I'll do my best to finish this
chocolate bar!
You don't have to do your best,
just take that damn chocolate
bar outta your mouth!
Hey!
What are you doing?
‐What are you microwaving?
‐I don't understand the complicated stuff.
But I'll do my very best! Yes, sir!
Do your very best?
You're, you're microwaving my comics!
Oh my god!
Something exploded!
Something just exploded!
Look what you've done!
My comics are probably
covered in sauce!
I don't get the complicated stuff,
but the world is a cold place these days
so I thought you could use our
heart‐warming microwave service.
More like heart‐breaking!
Hey!
Give me back my money!
This is why I said that this
was a bad idea.
My friend asked me to look
after his convenience store,
but I have some business
I gotta take care of.
Can you cover for me
for just one day?
It's just one day.
Thanks a million!
I'm sure this shop
will go out of business
by the time Hasegawa gets back.
Huh?
What are you doing, man?
Turn around now.
You took something, didn't you?
What's that?
There's no way!
Sh‐Shinpachi?
Tucker, what?
Hachibei Takaya, age sixteen.
Same age as Shinpachi, huh?
You're old enough to know
shoplifting's a crime.
Your Mom would be
ashamed of you!
And besides, what were
you planning to do
with so many bottles of hair
spray in the first place?
You'd look tight even
without all this crap...
Listen, be confident in yourself.
As if I'd use this all on my
own hair, you moptop!
Then what's it for?
Is it for your rice?
Were you planning to put it on
your rice to make it crunchy?
Tucker, man...
why'd you do this?
Look Tucker, you didn't used to be
like this when I first met you.
Shut up!
How many years do you think
it's been, Shinpachi?
I'm not the same old Tucker
you used to know anymore.
Just take me to the police station
or the magistrate or wherever.
If they wanna crucify me and put
my head up on display, fine!
Don't expect me to be grateful to you.
I'll just come back again.
Okay, then I guess I'll just
stop you again.
Sheesh, still the same
goody‐two‐shoes, eh?
Shinpachi.
Hey guys!
Leave Tucker alone!
Whenever I was being bullied
back in grade school...
you and your sister always came
to my rescue and saved me.
‐Shinpachi!
‐Heh!
You wan't some too?
Go ahead and cry loser!
Never!
I'm the son of a samurai!
The hell you think you
buttheads are doing!
Although it was usually just your
sister going Rambo on the bullies.
Brings back old memories.
I always thought that you'd be
my friend, no matter what...
Until that day you betrayed me.
Tucker, man, that was...
I don't wanna hear any
excuses from you!
Do you know how much I suffered
because of your half‐assed
attempt at being kind, huh?
Since that day, I...
Whatever.
Forget it.
Thanks to you, I was able
to toughen up a bit.
I'm in a biker gang now.
What?
Have you ever heard of the
gang the"Bulldogs"?
I don't need to rely on you or your
sister anymore, I'm strong now.
Sucker from school?
Who's that?
I forgot.
No. It's not Sucker,
it's Tucker, sis.
You really don't remember him?
No, I've left the past behind me.
I've chosen to live my life thinking
only about what's ahead of me.
But never mind that.
I brought all of you a treat for lunch.
Gintoki, Kagura,
please help yourselves.
Oh?
Yay!
Thanks big sis!
I tried out a brand
new recipe this time, so...
here you go.
Look!
Rolled omelets.
I'll go and buy some drinks for us!
No, I'll go, you stay here!
This is a convenience store.
You can get all the drinks
that you need right here.
Are you guys weeping in joy?
That's so nice.
Shinpachi, Shinpachi, come here
and have some omelet.
It's really good.
Hey, Shin...?
‐Look, Sis.
‐Hm?
If I'm remembering correctly,
then the Bulldogs are the
most violent biker gang
around here, aren't they?
They fight and steal
without any hesitation.
Oh. Listen, Shin,
why are you so concerned
about Sucker suddenly?
It's Tucker, Sis.
And it's all my fault
that Tucker changed.
I turned my back on him,
I abandoned him when he
was athis deepest point.
Huh?
Oh?
It was long ago, back when
we were in school.
Sh‐Shinpachi, what'll do I do?
I just pooped my pants.
What'll I do, Shin?
Shin, tell me...
Shinpachi, I know you're awake...
Shinpachi, Shinpachi, help me!
Friendships in school are
just like sandcastles.
One small incident,
and everything will fall apart
and get washed away.
Right after that incident,
I didn't go back to school
because of my father's debt.
But I can only imagine...
how hard Tucker's life
must have been...
especially after that
embarrassing moment.
What should I have done?
What should I have
done back then?
How could I have saved Tucker?
Honestly, there's nothing
you could've done.
Nothing at all.
No, that's not true.
Whenever your friend is crying,
a real friend cries alongside him.
Whenever your friend
is feeling worried,
a real friend always feels
worried right alongside him.
Whenever your friend
shits in his pants...
then a real friend should also
shit in his pants, Shinpachi.
True friends are able to share any
pain that the world inflicts...
no matter what, and Shin...
if your friend goes down
the wrong path in life.
Then, you must stop them,
even if it destroys your
friendship in the end.
That's what makes a true
samurai friend.
I'm very sorry, manager,
but I have some
business to take care of.
Please excuse me.
Are you sure he's gonna be alright?
There's no predicting what
kids will do these days,
so don't come crying to me
if something happens to him.
You useless idiot!
Who told you to go and
get regular hair sprays?
I told you, didn't I?
I need super hard hair spray to hold
my hair in place like this!
Right?
I‐I'm sorry, sir...
I ran into a little trouble back there.
Oh really?
You begged me to let you
to join the gang,
so I made an exception
for your sorry butt!
But look at this, you can't even run a
simple errand, can you, Sucker!
I guess we'll have to beat
some spirit into you,
to help you grow a pair.
Wh‐What's going on?
Hey, what're you doing?
Wh‐Wha‐‐?
Come on, be a man, enjoy the ride!
Huh?
‐What?
‐Huh?
Wha‐‐what's this?
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell am I, you ask?
Well, you must be an amateur gang
if you don't know who I am.
I am the Captain of the
Otsu Fan Club!
Shinpachi Shimura!
Sh‐Shinpachi.
What are you doing here?
This isn't a place for
a pretty boy like you!
Go home!
Excuse me!
Which one of you is
the boss of this gang?
Huh?
You think our boss would bother
to see a wimp like you, huh!
What's with you, kid?
What the hell do you want?
I'm here to take
Hachibei Takaya back.
From this moment on, he is
resigning from the Bulldogs gang,
and he's going to join
the Otsu Fan Club!
I came to get your permission.
Wh‐What're you saying, Shin?
What's the Otsu Fan Club?
The hell?
I Look, Tucker.
I've always been just like you, man.
Ever since the poop incident,
I've been sick of my weakness,
and have been aspiring
to become stronger.
But Tucker...
there's no shortcut
to becoming strong.
Dressing up and acting cool
might make you look strong,
but those superficial illusions
of strength will quickly wear off.
Joining a gang and hiding behind the
might of some other guy's strength.
Is that the kind of power you want?
Do you really want to be
that lame Tucker?
Listen kid!
I feel sorry for you, but this gang
ain't no after school club,
so you can't just say, "I quit."
And expect us to say, "Oh, okay.
Have a nice day!"
Well, in that case, I'll just have
to take him by force.
Hey, don't underestimate us,
you little brat!
What do you think you can
accomplish here on your own!
But he's not on his own!
Huh?
Hey Captain,
I can't be bothered working at
some convenience store anymore!
Oh!
If it's a fight you want,
it's a fight you're getting!
The Otsu Fan Club Special
Attack Squad...
the "Chihuahuas" has arrived!
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Now let's get down to business!
Hey.
Oh, no...
my hairline looks a little off today,
doesn't it?
Geez, this sucks, what if this wig falls
off while I'm on my ride?
Everything I've worked to achieve
all this time would turn to dust.
Oh...
I damaged my hair too much
when I was young with all the
perms and bleaching I did.
I guess I'll just have to glue it on
today.
Hey, Boss!
You idiot!!
Always knock when you come in, okay?
S‐Sorry!
But...
there's no door to knock on, sir?
Then go knock on heaven's door.
What do you want?
We've got big trouble, boss!
A bunch of guys just came to
fight and they're crazy strong!
Slash!
What're you idiots doing?
Boss!
I keep telling you, don't try to settle
everything with violence!
What's going on here?
What's this all about?
Hey, Boss...
It seems like something's going
on with your hair as well.
Is it really just the four of
you taking on the Bulldogs
that run the streets of Edo City?
Just who do you think you are?
Huh?
We're the, you know.
The Special Force,
the Special Attack Force.
The Attack Force of, um...
what was it called again?
Ummm.
We're the Special.
The...
Special Attack Force...
the Poodles, or something.
Yeah, something like that.
We're the Attack Poodles, that's it!
It's the Chihuahuas, guys.
At least try to remember
your own gang's name!
Oh...
that's right.
Yeeh, we're the Chihuahuas!
With a capital C and
then a bunch of Hs...
so don't mess with us!
Huh, you say "don't mess with us,"
but with a name like that...
I've never even heard
of such a gang.
Well, what do you want?
We're here to take Tucker back!
I won't let you force my friend
to steal hairspray anymore!
Tucker who?
Hey man, Did we have a
Tucker in our team?
Yes.
They mean Takaya, the
one who joined recently.
Okay then?
Where is he?
He is ver there.
Hey!
What're you doing?
Huh?
This is Sucker, then?
My mistake, dude!
Don't mess with me!
How could you make such
a mistake, Kagura?
Well, everyone's got a baguette
on their heads,
so I couldn't tell the difference.
‐Hey!
‐Hey four‐eyes,
are you Takaya's friend?
I get it.
You came here to rehabilitate
your buddy, eh?
And I like that.
You want that puppy?
Go ahead and take him.
But boss!
You can't be serious!
But, look...
you're going to do
something for me, first.
You see, we have a ceremony
that one has to go through in order
to leave the gang, you know.
But Takaya won't be able to go through
with it by the looks of it.
You guys are gonna go through
with it for him from the looks of it.
The rules are very simple.
You ride motorbikes
to the edge of town,
all the way to the freeway
that's under construction.
If you get there first,
well then, I'll let you take Takaya.
Listen up. Anything goes.
Using weapons, interfering
with the opposing team,
whatever you want.
If I were you, I'd have
one of you drive
while the other one attacks
and obstruct, huh?
But all of you have to race.
We'll have four from
our team as well.
Excuse me, sir.
We only have one scooter
and there are four of us.
Can you spare us one, dude?
Could you please?
Are you really a biker gang?
You're damn right, we are!
We're an environmentally
friendly biker gang, damn it!
I guess we have no choice.
Hey, sis, do you know how
to drive this thing?
A samurai does not concern
himself with petty details, dude.
Hey, Gin.
I really need to pee now!
Then go take a leak somewhere, dude.
That's no way to treat
a lady, you know!
This is gonna be interesting.
Okay, riders get ready!
Get ready, on your mark, get set, and...
Bulldogs!
The fools, here they come!
They have absolutely no idea
that this is a ceremony of blood
designed to punish traitors!
You're all gonna die here!
Do it!
Flatten 'em!
Heizo!
Who's gonna die, pink spikey head?
Hey, Gin, I just can't
hold it anymore.
Go ahead and pee, then.
That's the power of our
special slippery oil!
Don't ever get up!
Why you lousy...
Wh‐What?!
She just bounced on his head!
Hey, Sis, what are you doing?
You probably just killed Gin back there!
Oh my Gosh.
Hey!
I'm not going to allow
anybody to pass me!
I am the wind!
Born free like the wind!
Yahoo!
What's that?
Hey, sis!
Did you warp into another
dimension or something?
Oh, It feels so good!
If we go two miles faster,
I feel like we
could travel through time!
Come on, sis!
Time travel on your own time, okay?
Grab the handles!
And watch out!
Take that!
You're not going to pass us!
Now taste the might of the Bulldogs!
What the hell are you doing, huh?
I just need to go 2 miles faster,
so get lost!
Hey, no!
Don't!
Grab the handles!
Oh no, no, no, no, no!
Oh!
My hair!
Ah‐hah!
He's bald!
Hey, Sis, get a hold of yourself!
It's not what you think, it's just a wig!
It wasn't his real hair!
Uhh.
H‐Holy cow!
Did you see what she did?
She just pulled out all my hair,
and now I look like I'm balding!
You ARE bald, boss.
But.. but..
Look,
I heard you wanted
a new exhaust pipe...
Don't worry, boss...
Everyone's known about your hair
situation for a long time now.
It's not news to anyone in the gang,
honestly.
Oh, seriously?
Shinpachi!
Just hang in there a little longer!
Just hang on!
What the hell is this brat?
You think you're the wildest
gang in town!
But y'all ain't crap compared
to a real one!
Now go ahead and show 'em
what we got, Gin!
Who the hell is that?
Oh no!
Poor Gin!
This must be because of his drinking
problem, he's aged so quickly!
Definitely not!
You're the only problem here!
You guys would be better
off doing a standup routine
than being a bunch of thugs.
You think so?
That's pretty convincing when it
comes from you, though!
You must be killing all your crowds
with your flying wigs!
Why you‐‐!
Gintoki!
Was the girl just a decoy?
You pulled my attention away and...!
I could send you straight to hell
right now with my
Ultimate German Samurai Suplex.
Trust me, we can end this right here.
But I must respect Shinpachi's
samurai spirit, so...
you're going to race
our captain in a duel,
but you have to promise that
it will fair and square!
Shinpachi!
Go show em who's boss!
Right!
Wow, man!
What a bunch of weirdos, aren't they?
That's right!
What's the point of rescuing a
completely useless idiot like you?
Too bad for them, they're probably
all dead by now.
Yeah, nobody's ever survived
the ceremony of blood.
Or maybe they just ran away.
They're probably down
on their knees begging
for forgiveness right about now.
All together, come on!
My hair, where's my hair?
I don't have hair!
Hey loser kid, they're sure taking
their sweet old time.
I think they actually
ditched you there!
How about that!
What do you think?
They're your friends, after all.
They must have run away at
the first sight of danger.
Yup.
Birds of a feather, right?
A loser's friends are bound
to be losers, too!
Hey, look!
What's that?
There's no way, man!
Don't tell me he actually
made it this far!
Where's his bike?
Did they actually run all this way?
Not only the bike,
our bossman lost his
wig somewhere too!
Tucker...
I'm just like you, Tucker...
I hated how weak I was...
and all I ever wanted
was to be strong.
And that's why...
You idiot!
Thanks a lot for all that, ass hole.
Do you know what I had to go
through to join that gang
in the first place, huh?
I get that your'e trying to make
amends or something,
but it's way too late for that.
Yeah, yeah.
I get it, man.
Listen, I'm not forgiving you,
not now or ever!
So don't ever risk your life like
that again, do you hear me?
Tucker...
You know what...
the gang's leader started going on
about how he was all impressed
with your spirit and wanted to make
you join the gang and shit.
He was such a pain in the ass about it.
I told him I couldn't let my friend get
involved in something like this.
Okay, okay.
I hear you.
I'm never going to ask
those jerks for help again.
What's this?
Otsu was reborn as a battling diva!
You shouldn’t spread yourself too thin.
My favorite ramen shop decided to try
adding curry to their menu one day.
Within a week, the shop had to close.
The next episode...
Just bring it to me from
any warehouse sales!