Heh.
There is no way, man!
I would rather die than go
against my principles!
These Aliens just ain't shit!
Only one can survive,
the aliens?
Or the gangsters?
Aliens vs. Gangsters!
Hey, brother.
A man's back shows
everything about him.
Oh, man!
Just when we were about to
get off work!
Yeah, but I heard they found
something stuck
on the ship's chassis while
it was in flight.
Yeah, well there had better
not be alien
or something stuck to
the damn thing...
Hey, that reminds me!
Did you see
"Aliens vs. Gangsters"?
Man, it was really awesome!
I haven't seen anything in the
series since "Aliens 2."
It can't possibly be that good.
No man, you've got to see it.
This one is awesome!
There's this massive army
of aliens, right,
and they fight
a massive army
of Brother Joe
and his gangsters...
and no matter which side wins,
it spells the end of Edo City!
Why is that,
why's Edo City going to be
destroyed because of Brother Joe?
Seriously, man!
Brother Joe was even
scarier than the aliens!
Heh, is that so?
Then let's hope it's not Brother Joe
that's attached to the ship.
It's for real!
Shut up!
Keep your voices down!
I've got the absolute
worst hangover...
and my head is killing me!
Why do I have to come all the way
to Earth just to exterminate Aliens?
Seriously...
However...
I didn't come here just to work...
Are you guys mechanics?
There's a good chance
that the parasite
that was in this alien escaped
to Edo City...
So Edo City's in big trouble.
Can you call the police for me?
Just tell them that it's from
Umibozu the Exterminator.
Hello? Odd Jobs.
How can I help you?
Hello, Odd Jobs!
It's me, it's me.
Who are you?
I told you, it's me!
And I'm in seriously
big trouble.
Is that you, Gin?
That's right.
It's Gin, I'm Gin.
I just got into an accident
and hit a pregnant woman.
I'm in deep trouble.
Finish her off and
run away then.
What?
How could you say that?
That's an awful idea!
Anyway, I need money.
If you don't hurry,
I'm going to be arrested!
Seriously?
I need you to wire
ten thousand bucks
to this bank account now...
I wiped my butt too hard...
We've got to stop buying
cheap toilet paper...
Hey, there.
Did somebody just leave
from here?
Yeah.
Kagura just left.
She went rushing out in a total panic
after taking a phone call.
What's that about?
Must've been a call
from her home.
Maybe they want her to return
to her home planet.
Well, that would be great.
It would surely be a lot
quieter around here.
More importantly...
Hey, Gin, you gotta check this out.
The "It's me, it's me" scam?
It's a new brand scam
where the con artist says,
"It's me, it's me," on the phone...
without saying their name.
And then they let you assume
it's someone that you know,
and then they say
they're in trouble,
and need you to wire
money to them.
I wouldn't send money to anyone
even if they were in trouble!
Remember this, Shinpachi.
The only person who'd fall
for that would be a stupid girl
with superhuman strength.
UMIBOZU?
What is that?
Are you saying you
don't know, Okita?
I thought everybody knew.
Hey, move it and
let me see that.
Hey, don't push.
Phew!
Somebody smells!
Wash your armpits man!
Long story short, he's an alien
buster from another planet...
Umibozu the Exterminator
who hunts and eradicates
the most dangerous aliens
in the galaxy...
He's celebrated as the
strongest of all alien busters.
He has influence over authorities
all throughout the universe
despite being a mere individual...
He's a man who has
traveled the stars
and battled countless
alien monsters...
He's known as
"Umibozu the Exterminator,"
and he's a living legend.
Ohh...
So what's a legend
doing here in Edo City?
Well, it seems an alien
escaped to Edo City.
We do appreciate you
coming here to warn us...
But we'll take it from here,
and rest assured we'll take it down...
Still, I never thought I would meet
the famous Umibozu in person.
I am incredibly honored to make
your acquaintance.
Did you come to Earth to
pick out some aliens?
Why do you make it sound like
I'm going shopping?
I'm here on a private business.
I'm pursuing someone much more
troublesome than any alien.
Oh wow!
Someone who troubles
even the famous Umibozu?
It's a chick, I take it!
She's indeed female, no question.
Excuse me, Miss,
but what are you doing?!
Gin told me on the phone!
He'll be thrown behind bars
if I don't send him
"ten thousand ducks"
to his bank account!
Ten thousand ducks?
Wait, Miss, wait, Miss...
Don't you mean
"ten thousand bucks"?
And what is that you're spilling?
It's rice for luring the ducks!
Hey! Well, I'm afraid ducks
don't eat rice!
Don't bother me, four eyes!
We're sorry about
the commotion, Sir.
Now, how can I help you?
Excuse me, Sir?
What's that?
Umibozu the Exterminator?
What's such a big shot
doing here?
Hijikata, is something wrong?
No, It's nothing at all,
nothing, Chief.
We have to act quickly
or we're going to have
a major problem!
A parasitic alien...
has entered Edo City.
Alien?
These aliens just ain't shit!!
This is a land of samurai!
Hey, Hijikata, Harada,
what's going on there?
Brother Joe,
we shall avenge you!!
Brother Joe?
What happened?
Did something happen
to a man named Joe?
Brother Joe, we love you!!
Look, I have no idea
what you're saying,
but listen to me very carefully!
The parasitic alien will take over
any organism as host,
from humans to dogs and cats!
Its intelligence is very low,
but it will do anything it
can to get food
through using its host!
The quickest way to tell if someone's
been taken over by the alien...
is to look for a panda...
The parasite's host will have
dark circles around their eyes,
just like a panda...
Understand, men?
Look for a panda!
Not like, a real panda
who eats bamboo
and lays around
all day in a zoo!
But looks like a panda!
We must stop it before it harms
any civilians, so look for a panda!
Maya Sizitzy here,
I'm at the Edo City Bank,
where a robber has
barricaded himself inside.
We can see the robber's face!
What are those dark circles
around his eyes?
Lack of sleep?
It's a panda.
Testing, testing!
Listen up!
This is a message for the robber,
you are surrounded!
So come out peacefully!
We're too late.
What?
You mean that Kagura did this?
Kagura is responsible?
So it would seem.
She was tricked by the
"It's me, it's me" swindle,
and she tried to wire money,
but, of course,
she doesn't have any...
And that's what led
to this violent act.
Oh no...
What should we do?
What, what can we do?
Hey, Gin?
Oh!
‐Listen up, robber...
‐No!
Hey, what're you people doing?
I don't really think I can
beat her in a fight...
but if I don't try to stop her,
who will?
If her family were here...
they'd probably do the same.
Gi‐Gintoki!
I'm going with you!
It's too dangerous!
Kagura!
‐Never mind, you're good.
It's a monster!
Well, now...
I'm glad that it seems our Kagura
isn't the robber after all.
Yeah, you're right, Gin.
But wasn't something
attacking her in there?
That must've been, you know...
her father, of course!
That call must've been
from her father,
and so they were probably
just meeting here.
Oh, of course, so that was
just her father hugging her.
We shouldn't disturb a father
and daughter's reunion.
Wait, Gin, you're so mean!
Why won't you rescue me?
What are you doing?
Let go!
And what's that stuff all
over you?!
Is that your father's guts
or something?
I was only trying to catch
ten thousand ducks for you, Gin!
What happened to the
predator woman?
Did you settle everything?
What predator woman?
What kind of scam did you
fall for, Kagura?
What the hell is that thing?
Isn't that really your father?
That's not my dad!!
It just appeared and started
spewing all over the place.
It's still spewing all over the place!
Let go!
Let go of me!!
Bad Kagura!
Let go of us!
No way!
I'm taking both of you with me!
Oh, I found you.
Hey...
that umbrella...
I've been looking
for you, Kagura.
Papa?
Pa...
‐Papa?!
Heh.
There is no way, man!
I would rather die than go
against my principles!
I was so moved.
‐Brother Joe is the best!
Yes, it made us cry.
It was awesome.
‐These Aliens just ain't shit!
These Aliens just ain't shit!
Only one can survive...
the aliens Or the gangsters?
Aliens vs. Gangsters!
Hey, brother.
A man's back shows
everything about him..
Testing, testing.
This is a message
for the alien.
You are completely surrounded,
so just give up your
pointless resistance
and come out peacefully, alien.
Your mother from your
home planet is crying!
She said she didn't raise you
to be this kind of alien.
What kind of alien?
It doesn't matter if you're
alien or human,
anyone who makes
his mother cry is a loser.
Am I right, mother?
Say something to
your alien son.
What?
She's here?
Its mother is here?
My baby, Mommy can't look
after you anymore...
My baby, ever since
that day three years ago,
you've been dead to me.
Whoa!...
Chief!
These aliens just ain't shit!
They just ain't shit!
Hey!
This isn't an alien, though.
Hey, Chief, are you okay?
Someone's coming out now.
Ready!
Just come with me,
sweetheart!
And maybe...
I'll treat you to a
chocolate sundae!
No.
Let me go!
And don't walk so close to me!
What's the matter?
Are you embarrassed
to be with your papa?
What is it?
What part of me is embarrassing?
Tell me what it is,
and papa will fix it!
I'm pretty sure that it's
too late to fix it.
Kagura, there's absolutely
nothing that a man can't fix!
I can make amends
for any mistake!
It's impossible!
Once your follicle dies,
your hair will never grow back!
Excuse me, I'd like a
chocolate sundae, too.
No, wait a minute.
Maybe I'll have a fruit sundae,
after all.
Oh, what should I have?
What's happening?
At the sound of the gong,
the time will be...
The Umibozu?!
Umibozu the Exterminator...
is Kagura's father?!
The Umibozu?
The alien exterminator?
Did he accidentally exterminate
everything growing on his head?
Hey, mophead,
are you calling me a baldy?
I'll have you know that I'm just
follically challenged!
Umibozu is the fiercest
Alien Buster ever.
His name is known
throughout galaxy.
The wandering Umibozu.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I think I've heard of him.
The hairless sleeper.
Oh, It's the "fearless sweeper,"
you idiot,
and that's quite enough
from you!
Who is this jerk, huh?
He makes your papa mad.
So can I kill him now?
Oh, calm down, bald eagle.
Who's a Bald eagle?
Wait, like the symbol of America?
That's not bad!
Bald eagle, let me introduce you.
This hopeless four eyes
is Shinpachi.
What do you mean, hopeless?
And this guy with the
stupid mophead is Gin.
Hey, Kagura,
what's with the stupid?
So these are the guys that
I'm looking after here on Earth...
Say hi to each other.
Are you sure these two weren't
planning something illegal?
The streets are overflowing
with people
who want to misuse
the strength of the Yato clan.
What's that?
What do you mean by
"misuse" the power?
Do you mean like rubbing
your crystal head
so I can see into the future?
A father who abandoned his
daughter on planet Earth
has no right to talk like that.
I have been worried sick and
looking all over for her.
I took my eyes off her for a
second and she disappeared.
Girls at this age are very difficult.
I mean, they're as fragile
as a glass sculpture.
You're one to talk?
Well you're the one with a crystal
ball sitting on top of your neck!
Idiot!
You think you can talk big because
of your hair and all.
But, when you pass thirty,
it'll happen so quickly.
Before you know it,
‐the follicle goddess
‐Come on, stop that,
‐will abandon you too!
‐stop that you two!
The point is, I can't leave
my daughter here on Earth
with people like you.
So...
I'm taking Kagura
back home with me!
You don't get to decide that!
Kagura, dear, there's no
excuse for domestic violence!
Papa, you ignored
your family
and did whatever you
wanted all this time.
I don't want you meddling
in my life now...
Papa, I don't interfere in your life,
so don't interfere in mine!
I came to Earth on my own,
and I'll go back home on my own.
Kagura, dear...
A family is like just like
a bird's nest.
A bird can't keep on flying
around forever.
If there's no nest to go home to,
it'll eventually fall to the ground.
Papa, you're a migratory bird.
You don't need a nest,
and I'm exactly the same way.
I don't need a nest;
a wooden perch is enough.
Then what's so special about
this wooden perch?
Is there something that
you can only here?
Papa, tell me what I would gain
by going back home.
I would rather find a perch
and fly wherever I like.
Little girl!
Don't talk like you know it all.
Baldy...
You still think that
I'm a little girl, huh?
Okay?
What's going on here?
Hey, they're going to...
Kagura!
All right, carry it carefully outside.
Hijikata, what're we going to use
such a disgusting corpse for?
The Immigration officers said
to bring it to them.
Apparently, there's some VIP
who wants it, they said...
You'd think he could find
something better to collect...
Is this the kind of
monster that Umibozu
the Exterminator
always fights?
Makes me wonder which one
is the real monster.
And to think that he's that
rambo girl's father!
Not exactly the family type, is he.
There are two kinds of
men in the universe...
One is the protective type,
who seeks to protect his home
and his family at all costs...
The other is the hunter type
who leaves that home and
goes out in search of prey...
I saw hunter in
that man's eyes,
it was the eyes of a beast.
He's definitely not the type
that can stay at home...
And I'm afraid that girl must
have had a very lonely life
when she was back home...
What's that?!
What are they?
Are they humans?!
Do you think I'd really allow
my unmarried daughter
to live under the same roof
as another guy or two?
Don't you understand, Kagura,
that's how you get a
shotgun marriage!
I'm not that kind of girl, Papa!
And anyway,
isn't that why you married mama
in the first place?
That chatterbox!
I can't believe she told you that!
You've got no right to tell me
what to do, Papa!
I do!
And I won't let you make
the same mistake I did!
Leave me alone already!
That's all you've ever done
my whole life, anyway!
So I'll decide for myself
where and how
I'll live, and for now it's here!
Seems like you really like this
wooden perch you've found...
Then that's all the more reason
why you should leave it.
Have you forgotten,
the blood of the beast that runs
through our veins?
The Yato instinct that makes us
roam in search of prey?
We are beasts that can only
live on the battlefield...
Look what happens when you put
that beast in a peaceful place...
You will forget who you are...
and destroy everything
around you.
Stay here, and you'll...
end up snapping this wooden
perch in half yourself...
If you love this place, then leave it.
If you don't want to go home,
then come with me...
This isn't the place
for you, Kagura.
You and I cannot fly
freely in this sky.
No way...
I don't want to live a life
where I just give up
and refuse to change...
I'm going to grow
and change here,
I know that if I stay here,
I can change...
I'll stay with Gin and the others.
What, Gin?
That mophead guy?
What can a bum like
him do for you?
You leave me no choice...
Then I'm going to take you
home with me by force.
Oh, Gin!
Oh, Mommy!
Goodness!
What is it with you people?!
But Gin...
I...
Oh...
What do you think
you're doing?
Don't be sticking your nose
in a family matter.
That was some wild fight,
wasn't it?
Like father like daughter.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree...
Go home...
The Earth seems way too
small for you, Kagura...
This is a good opportunity.
Go home with your father...
Let's make this a good‐bye.
Huh?
But why?
Why are you saying that to me?
I'm never going back home,
I'm staying...
Staying here forever
with you and the others...
Oh, wait, don't go!
Stop it!
Think about it, Kagura...
This isn't where you belong,
and you know it.
Why, Gin...?
But why...?
You fired her?!
You fired Kagura?
Wait, does that mean she's going
home with her father?!
Gin, have you ever thought about
Kagura's feelings on this?
The next episode...