The Capital city of Edo.
Every night people
are drawn to this city
in search of pleasure and
excitement, like moths to a flame.
It was here that...
All right, Third Squad,
go around the back!
Tenth Squad, you're all
gonna follow me!
♪Oh... Samurai’s Samba!♪
In Edo City, there is a special armed
police force that serves the government.
They swiftly deal with any
rebellious elements that arise
and run rampant in the city
and with exclusionists who engage
in shady activities in the underworld.
♪At work I'm a good for nothing♪
♪Yet still I'm a human being.♪
Heave!
We've come here for an inspection!
We're the Shinsengumi!
The Shinsengumi?
What are you doing
with a television crew
if you're here for an inspection?
And what are you doing
singing karaoke at a party
while plotting to overthrow
the government?
You've got some nerve!
Arrest them!
Why you!
For the next 24 hours our camera crew
will follow the Shinsengumi
in order to bring you the true picture
of what their jobs consist of.
Give it up!
You government dog!
Up close! 24 Hours with
the Shinsengumi Armed Police!
You know there's no use
in running away.
What a pain!
Get... get away!
The likes of you will never
be able to keep us down!
Do you hear me?
You're an exclusionist but
you asssumed you had time
to get cozy with
a wench, huh?
Amazing!
What's this?
Where's Chief Kondo?
Yeah, come to think of it.
Where did he go?
Our honorable chief is a lot
more modest than we all are.
He said that he didn't want
anything to do with a TV exposé.
Wow, that's the chief for you!
He's probably having a discussion
with some government bigwig
or silently cleaning his sword
in solitude right about now.
Oh, my butt hair is
really just too thick.
There's no way any girl
would ever go out with me.
I'm no good, am I?
That's not true at all.
Butt hair is very manly,
and I think that's great.
Then let me ask you this.
‐Say, if you had a boyfriend and...
‐Hmm?
...if his rear end looked like an afro,
what would you do?
I would love him,
butt 'fro and all.
What a goddess!
She actually accepts everything!
She's just like the Buddha.
‐Huh?
‐But... but... but... but...
‐...but will you marry me?
‐Huh?
What is this?
Someone asked you
to marry him?
Are you being serious
about this, sis?
I'm being serious.‐
A customer actualy proposed
to me yesterday.
So, what did you say?
Of course, I had to politely
turn him down.
He sure surprised me though!
I can't believe how stubborn
he got about it,
even though we'd just met.
Otae, dear!
In the end,
he was so annoying.
I had to pop him in the schnoz
and make a run for it.
I... is that true?
Well, I can't imagine
what kind of person...
Otae dear!
Will you please marry me?
I'm not the kind of guy who gives up
after being told no once, or even twice!
My mother always used to tell me
that women find more happiness
in being loved than
in loving someone!
Hey, loser!
What the hell are you doing
yelling up there?
You're bothering the entire
neighborhood, idiot!
Hey, relax, officer!
I'm innocent!
I may...
I may be a thief, alright...
but I only steal hearts.
Wipe that smug grin
off your face!
That was the corniest line
I've ever heard!
Get down here right now!
Now, Otae, dear!
Won't you at least show me
your angelic face for one moment?
Oh, Otae, dear!
The Shinsengumi start
their mornings early.
They begin their preparations
very early in the morning,
so they can jump
into action at any time!
Put some spirit into it!
Anyone who skips out on morning
training will be committing harakiri!
Early morning, huh?
Early morning.
If the vice chief says it's early morning,
it's early morning.
This ain't early!
10 AM is not considered
early in the morning!
Hush you maggot!
A man with fierce determination
can make anything happen!
Whatever!
This is more fabrication
than determination.
Are you playing badminton, maggot?
Come to think of it.
I haven't seen Kondo today either.
Is he like on vacation
or something?
He isn't like you, Okita!
We're talking about the chief.
I'm sure that he's out vigorously
training alone by himself somewhere.
Oh, just what you'd expect
from Chief Kondo.
Chief Kondo really is
something else, isn't he?
I really admire him.
You sure got a really strange admirer,
don't you, sis?
Well, yeah, it really is a bother.
Okay then, dinner will be...
Eggs again?
Not eggs again!
Seriously, sis?
Don't be so judgemental about it.
Eggs are packed with nutrition.
Then let me do the cooking, please,
and you can just do
the shopping around town!
Sure.
Phew, her fried eggs?
They aren't fried eggs at all.
They're poor, innocent,
horribly abused eggs.
Oh boy!
I guess it can't be helped.
"Come with me for a load?"
‐What does that even mean?
‐Wait, sis!
Otae, dear!
‐Huh?
I may not look it,
but I'm quite the athlete.
My hobbies include both
tennis and scuba diving.
Sparkle!
Do only one at a time,
not both, you freak!
The Shinsengumi have many
different duties and responsibilities...
and directing the traffic in the great
City of Edo is also one of them.
Hey, you there, stop now!
Who allowed you to do
a U‐turn in this intersection?
Don't you dare run away!
Anyone who runs
is gonna get cut!
Now, now, Hijikata.
Come on, don't let your temper
get the better of you.
What you need to do
is just leave it to me.
I'm not leaving any...
Oh, God.
Hijikata, you always take
things to such extremes.
Don't try to pin this on me, Okita!
This is on you!
So that's the whole story, Gin.
What do you mean "thats the
whole story," you little shit?
How many minutes has it been
since the show started?
I'm the main character, so don't
you think it's problematic...
that it's taken so long
to finally get to me?
Eleven minutes, ten seconds.
This is Gin Tama, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Hey! Come on!
Right?
The show can't begin
without Gin!
Why call it Gin Tama
if I'm not on screen?
Well, it seems like the title
of today's show is
"Up close! 24 Hours with
the Shinsengumi Armed Police!"
That's what I saw, at least.
What the hell?
I haven't heard about that!
That's because you never seem
to care about the show.
At this rate, the Shinsengumi are going
to be the real stars of this anime.
Seriously?
Now that you mention it,
we haven't played
the Gin Tama opening yet!
That was a close one.
This is Gin Tama
and I'm the star of this show!
Aren't you glad that there's someone
who actually wants to marry her?
If he had a sword in his belt,
it probably means he works
for the government.
This is your meal ticket, baby!
Get hitched before he discovers
what you're really like!
What's that supposed to mean?
At first, I thought he was going to
finally give up his pursuit of me,
so I didn't give it much thought.
But then he started showing up
everywhere.
That guy is really not normal.
All right, thirty seconds left.
Hurry, hurry!
It's the home stretch!
Swallow without chewing, Kagura!
I didn't bring cash
so I'm really counting on you.
Are you two even listening?
What do you mean?
What do you want me
to do about it?
If you want me to take a job,
then show me the money.
Gin man, I haven't received
a paycheck in over two months.
So why don't you
show me the money?
Well, I would if you paid me.
Come on. If you don't find some
motivation you'll be replaced.
Stalker‐Perv, where are you at?
I'm serving you
a bowl of justice!
What did you just say,
scum bucket?
I'd like to see you try it!
He really was here.
Boy, you sure are stupid to come out
when someone calls for a stalker.
Have you decided to admit
the fact that you're a stalker?
Well aren't we all stalkers when
it comes that elusive prey love?
Listen, jerk!
I saw you getting all chummy
with Otae a moment ago.
Just what the hell
is your relationship with her?
I'm uncontrollably envious of you!
This is my fiancé.
We're actually going to
get married this upcoming fall.
Oh, really?
The truth is, we've already done
all kinds of things together.
So please forget about me
and move on.
You... you've done
all kinds of things?
Even those kinds of things?
No, nobody mentioned
those kinds of things.
No, its fine, Otae.
I don't care about
what you've done in the past.
I accept you entirely,
just the way you are.
Huh?
The same way you love me,
butt 'fro and all.
I don't love you.
Doh! Hey, you silver haired moptop!
It doesn't matter whether
you're Otae's fiancé or not!
I know that I love Otae
more than you ever could!
I challenge you to a duel!
The winner takes Otae!
Oh, I really shouldn't
have lied like that.
Yeah, it seems like it just made things
even more complicated than before.
And that guy down there,
he knows how to fight.
Look how calm he is
right before his duel.
Like he's faced certain
death many times before.
Don't worry about him.
If Gin is in any danger...
my umbrella will unleash
hell on earth, Big sis.
Try not to kill them, okay?
Hey, four eyes!
Where did he go?
Who are you calling "four eyes"?
And he said he had to go
to the can!
That's... that's awfully nonchalant
of him before a duel!
Our reporting team has received information
about an unruly drunk downtown.
We've headed to the scene!
You idiot!
The hell's wrong with drinking
during the day?
Why don't you show me where
the law that makes it illegal is?
Edo's protectors,
the righteous Shinsengumi,
have already arrived
on the scene.
Arrived on the scene.
Arrived on the...
Now they come?
They just got here?
You...!
‐You...!
‐Hey, you drunk baboon!
Don't bother trying to resist,
come with us.
What?!
You're calling me a drunk?!
I'm barely even tipsy,
you little...!
You...!
Yeah, you little...
Hey, do we have permission
to kill him, Hijikata?
No, calm down.
The cameras are rolling right now.
Stop trying to murder people
every single chance you get.
You bastard...
Am I wrong or is that
your mom's spaghetti
sliding down my leg right now?
You just signed
your death war.
Hey, everyone, hold Hijikata back!
You imbeciles, let me go!
I'm going to drag him around town
through the dirt and cut his head off!
Vice chief, calm down!
The cameras are still rolling!
Get the camera
out of my face.
What are they doing?
Apparently they're having a duel!
A duel? Wow!
You rarely see that
these days, am I right?
Hey, rice crackers
and caramel candy!
How about a soda?
Hey, is he ready yet?
He didn't run off
like a coward, did he?
Dumb ass!
What reason do I have to
run away from someone like you?
Finally!
What took you so long?
Were you taking a dump?
Don't you know that heroes
don't take dumps?
I just needed a bump.
Never heard of a
hypoglycemic hero before!
Nice sunset.
Beautiful, isn't it?
A sunset is like a sword
to a samurai.
You're pretty well spoken
for a silver haired mop top.
And you understand human language
pretty well for a gorilla, I'd say.
I... I'm not a gorilla!
I may look like one,
but I'm not a gorilla!
Whatever then.
So shall we get started or what?
Wait, do you have a weapon?
If you want to use a real sword,
I'll lend you one.
It's up to you.
This is more than good enough
for me, buddy.
Let's get this show started.
Do you think this is a game?
Well, Im so sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm not about
to determine the fate
of somebody else's life
over our duel.
It might not be
much of a substitute,
but I'll wager
my life instead.
If I wager my life
instead of Otae's,
even if you win,
Otae won't become yours,
but I'll be out
of the picture then.
You are free to go on and continue
to try to get her to love you back.
Of course, if I win, you’re gonna have to
keep your paws off her, you got that?
He's willing to face a
real blade and protect me
even if it means risking his own life
in exchange for mine?
Wait!
Stop this now!
‐What?
‐You sure are a man amongst men.
Well, I take it you're more popular
with men than with women.
Hey, kid, lend me
your wooden sword!
You're quite the man
yourself, so use that.
It's my favorite sword.
Go ahead, use it.
Gin, catch!
Win or lose today, we aren't holding
any grudges, are we?
Sure.
You got it.
Let's fight, man to man.
Let's go!
A fair...
‐Fight!
What's this?
Hold on a second!
The blade!
Wait, wait, wait,
the tip... tip is...
‐Argh!
‐...the tip is gone!
You're so naive,
more naive than the flavor
of my bottled water.
I can't believe you'd take
a weapon from your enemy!
When I went to the john,
I scored it with a deep cut so
it would split from being swung.
You bastard!
You'd really go that far?
Only a total dork like you
would put their lives on the line
for something stupid like this.
This harmlessly resolves everything,
don't you think so, buddy?
Do you call this harmless?
Hey. So wha'dya think
of my brilliant plan?
‐I've lost all faith in you!
‐You feel satisfied now, cheater?
You coward!
I can't even believe you!
Wait! What are you saying?
I defended your sister with...
I'm going home!
I never want to see
your face again!
I'm going on vacation
for a while.
Harmlessly resolves everything?
Oh well, seems like Gin
got the worst of it
trying to protect me.
What did I do to deserve
this treatment?
What a total klutz.
But I think I'm starting
to understand you.
The Shinsengumi's vice chief,
Hijikata arrives.
Quietly, he patrols the city by himself
even after a long day of work.
But what is this?
What is it that arrests his
ever searching gaze this evening?
What's all the fuss?
Well, apparently there was
some kind of duel over a woman.
A duel over a woman?
How stupid!
What idiot would bother to...
Oh, Chief Kondo.
Chief Kondo?
That's the Shinsengumi's chief.
Is that Isao Kondo?
You idiot!
Why are you filming this?
And so, thanks to the work
of the Shinsengumi,
peace in the Capital
has been upheld.
Really though?
Where's the guy that
attacked Chief Kondo?!
He may be a gorilla, but that man
is also our beloved leader!
A silver‐haired samurai?
You're that guy from…!
The next episode...