So we kicked off
the Gin Tama anime series
with two episodes full
of laughs and excitement.
This time, we'll be taking
a trip back in time
to tell the story when
Gin and I first met.
The sword of the samurai
is not something to be kept
within a sheath.
It's something that you hold
within your soul.
These days, samurai aren't
even really needed anymore.
But no matter how much
times change,
there are things that
we must never forget.
Even if the time comes when
you must give up your sword,
you must never lose the
unwavering sword held within your soul.
‐Father!
The cloudless sky of Edo City.
I wish I could've seen it
one last time.
The land of the samurai.
There was a time,
a long time ago,
when our country
was called by that name.
But the skies that
the samurai gazed upon,
are now filled with ships
from other galaxies,
and no longer filled
with dreams and clouds.
And the towns where
the samurai once walked,
are now filled with insolent
and arrogant aliens
who walk with more pride
than the samurai ever did.
This is our world today.
This is our city today.
No, you stupid idiot!
That's not the right one!
It's right there, right there!
Nowadays, even a stupid
chimpanzee could do this job!
You're human being, and you've been
working here for more than a year!
Why can't you do this, huh?
I'm sorry.
Swordsmanship is the only thing
I've ever had experience with.
You idiot!
You're still going on
about your sword?
Samurai and their swords
are all ancient history!
How long are you going to keep
acting as if you're still a samurai,
as if the samurai
were still around?
Aw, come on now.
Just leave it at that,
alright boss?
Hey, you there, kid.
Don't worry about the register,
just give me some milk.
Oh, sure thing!
Right away.
Ugh! No, Sir, you mustn't go
so easy on him.
He's an idiot.
Nah, it's just that lately whenever
I see whats left of the samurai...
I feel kind of sorry for them,
because when we got here,
the samurai were always spoiling
for a fight whenever
they got the chance.
But, now, it's as though
we've lost a very irritating friend.
It's lonely.
So I end up wanting
to mess with them a little.
Twenty years ago aliens came
to our Capital of Edo.
The Amanto, or Sky People,
took over
and led to the decline of the
samurai and our way of life.
We were stripped of everything.
They took our swords,
our status, and our honor...
and everything else.
No, it wasn't just the samurai.
Every human living in this country
has probably already...
‐Hey.
‐Huh?
A samurai?
Who do you think you are?
You think you can strap
on a wooden sword
like a samurai in the age
of the Sword Ban?
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Shut your trap.
Are you in heat right now
or something, Amanto?
Look at this here.
Look at what happened to my chocolate
parfait because of all your fussing.
All of it spilled out onto the floor!
Hey you, what do you think
you are doing?
Don't you even know
who we are, you fool?
You know what?
My doctor told me that my blood sugar
level was too high,
and now I can only eat
a parfait once a week!
This was that one time!
He was... far too barbaric
to ever be called a samurai,
but he was also too honest
and honorable...
to ever be called a thug.
Hey listen, kid,
tell your manager,
the parfait was really great.
What's going on?
Did you see what happened?
All right, all right,
everyone out of the way!
Oh! There he is!
So you're the one waving around a
wooden sword and causing a riot!
‐Wait. No, you've got it all wrong!
‐You're not going anywhere.
Hey, Yashichi,
take a look inside!
Yes, sir!
Uh‐oh! It's the ambassador
from Planet Chatoran.
This is an intergalactic incident, man.
Do you realize what you've done?
Aren't you listening?
I already told you,
it wasn't me!
The man who did it
already ran off!
Yeah, yeah, that's exactly
what the culprit would say.
Next time hide your weapon
before you try to make your excuses.
Now, I'Im taking you to
the station to file a report.
Come along.
A sword?
I just doesn't feel right.
I get all cranky if I don't have
enough sugar in me.
Hey, you!
How dare you make me take
the blame for what you did?
Everything is a complete mess
because of what you did!
What a conscientious kid to chase me
to give me my wooden sword?
Don't worry about it.
It's just something I bought
on a school trip totally on a whim.
That's not it!
I just barely managed
to get away from the police!
I keep telling them
they've got it wrong,
but nobody wants to listen
to what a samurai has to say!
In the end, even my own manager
began to say I was the murderer.
So you got fired, finally?
Well, you know a cashier
who can't use a register
is as useless as a mom
who can't make lasagna.
Yeah, yeah! Really?
So, is that how you treat
your own mother?
Oh, you're getting all worked up
just because you got fired
from a part time gig.
Don't you realize that nobody at all
hires samurai anymore?
How am I supposed
to survive from now on?
You idiot!
Why don't you quit
your whining, will you?
You four‐eyed idiot!
Don't even think that you're the only one
who's got problems in this world.
There are samurai who call cardboard boxes
on the streets their home these days!
Can't you try to be a little more
positive like they are, huh?
I doubt that you even know
what it means to be positive.
Hello.
Shinpachi?
Huh?
What are you doing here
at this time of day?
Tell me what happened
to your job.
Ack, It's my sister!
Oh, hello dear.
What are you doing
messing around out here
instead of working,
you little punk!
Do you know what kind of
financial trouble we're in this month?
Even your pitiful little paycheck
is crucial income!
We need to pay our bills!
‐Stop it!
‐I don't believe you!
This is all because of him!
I'm innocent!
Wait! Don't you dare!
I'm sorry.
I've gotta catch a rerun
of a TV show this evening.
Uhhh, I'm so sorry.
It's just that that was
my big intro scene,
so I got a little carried away.
I kinda went overboard.
I'm really sorry!
I'm really very sorry!
If "sorry" was enough, we wouldn't need
to have swords in this world.
Thanks to you, our dojo may not
be able continue to exist anymore.
It's been 20 years since
national isolation was lifted.
The Amanto began to travel
here from far off planets
and Edo City has grown
beyond recognition.
But samurai and swords,
all those who once held power here
are now perishing one by one.
The same goes for our dojo.
Because of the ban on swords,
all of our students have left.
Now the two of us are both
working part time jobs,
and the honest truth is
that we're barely scraping by.
We've been doing everything we can to
protect the dojo that our father left us,
no matter how difficult
the situation becomes.
But because of you...
it's all over, you idiot!
Calm down, sis!
Tell me something here.
Was your sister brought up
by gorillas?
Hold on, wait!
Just calm down.
I can't go around
committing sudoku,
but I do work hard
to clean up my own messes.
What is this? A business card?
Odd Jobs ‐ Gintoki Sakata.
Well, the thing is you can't be too picky
about jobs these days, right?
Because of that my business is
to do whatever I'm asked to do.
I am called Mr. "Odd Jobs" Gin.
If you've got problems, I'll solve them,
no matter what they are.
You're the one who's causing
us problems, you baboon!
‐And find me a job! And fast!
‐Alright, alright!
Calm down! Calm down!
I can't find you a job,
but I can teach you a chant that'll help you
be less nervous at job interviews.
‐No thank you!
But wait!
Hey, sis...
I just don't think it's possible to keep
running a sword fighting dojo
in this day and age.
I really can't imagine swordsmanship
ever being revived again,
and the truth is... we gain nothing
by protecting this dojo so desperately.
This isn't about profit or gain.
Does a child really need a reason to protect
the things that its parents cherished
after they are gone?
But, listen, sis!
Tell me this, what did father
ever do for us?
Greetings!
Today is the day that you're paying me
back for every last cent that you owe!
I simply can't wait any longer!
This debt is pissing me off!
Hey, so wait, you're in debt?
Seems like the two of you are leading some
pretty hairy lives for a couple of kids.
It's not even our debt.
It was our father's!
Shin, hush!
What are you blabbering about?
Hurry up and bring me
my money right now!
I need to get home to watch the rerun
of my favorite TV show tonight!
‐Wait a minute, today is...
‐Shut up, you moron!
I've been waiting for my money
since before you were even born,
and I'm starting
to go bald already!
You promised me
that you'd sell the dojo
if you couldn't pay me
back what you owe,
and I'm going to see
that you keep that promise!
Hold on, wait just a moment.
Why should I?
Haven't you had enough?
You don't need to feel obligated
to your stupid father,
the man who left you nothing
but debt when he died!
Just sell this awful dojo.
Stop it you little brat.
What do you think you're doing?!
Sis!
You little fool.
Did you think that I wouldn't hurt you
just because you're a woman?
Are you that stupid?
What?
That's quite enough of that.
Even though she was raised
by gorillas, she's still a lady.
And just who are you?
Is this dojo still in operation?
It cannot possibly
still have students!
Honestly, all of you,
listen up!
Forget about the dojo!
I have a better idea.
I'm going to make you work
to pay off your family's debt.
As you can see,
I happen to have started
a new business recently.
It's called High‐Leg Hot‐Pot Heaven.
What?!
High Leg, what...?
Why... why High Leg?!
Because I like girls
in high‐leg outfits, of course!
Look, it's a flying nightclub
where we serve hotspots.
Technically, nightclubs are prohibited
in Edo City right now,
but if it's in the sky, it'll be out of
sight from government officials,
and I can do what I want!
It'll be a literal hotpot filled to the
brim with girls in high‐leg outfits!
We'll ensnare our customers
with our sides
of rump steaks
and hamburger buns!
I've gathered so many beauties
from so many worlds,
and you'd be more than welcome.
Now, It comes down to either
selling this dojo or selling yourself.
Which will it be?
There's no way!
She'd never do
something like that.
All right, I agree.
‐I'll go with you.
‐Huh?!
Oh, my, what a devoted
daughter you are.
Wait! Hold on now!
Sis, why would you do this?!
We've done enough, haven't we?
Hey!
Hey, wait, sis!
Shinpachi, the truth is,
it's just as you were saying.
Nothing good will ever
come from this dojo,
no matter how hard
we try to save it,
only suffering.
But the truth is...
it's also painful to let go of.
Things that you can never
regain once you let go
are both painful
to keep and to discard.
And if it's going to be
painful either way...
then I would rather suffer trying to protect
what the two of us still have.
What is her problem, huh?
What a stupid sister I have!
She's always talking
about father.
And what did baldy
ever do for us?
Nothing!
He played chess with us
once in a while and that's it!
Hold on.
Your dad was bald?
Well, he was mentally bald, or...
Hey, why are you still here now?
And why are you baking something
so elaborate in my house?
What is this?
Well, I just can't go on without eating
something sweet periodically.
Then why not make something simpler
and easier and less messy!
Sweet, sweet.
Listen, shouldn't you go
after your sister?
I really don't care.
It was her decision
to leave here.
It's clear now, she really is
my father's daughter.
She's just like him.
Father was a good
natured person
who always talked about
duty and compassion.
Because of that nature, he got taken
advantage of, and he died in debt.
How could he have been
so careless?
I don't want to die with nothing but a
bunch of ideological virtues to my name.
No matter how much
times change,
there are things that
we must never forget.
Does a child really
need a reason
to protect the things
that its parents cherished,
even after they're gone?
That kind of thinking only
gets in the way nowadays.
I swear I'm going to do
better than they ever did.
Is that so?
But to me, you don't seem to be
doing very well at all, to be honest.
Samurai don't need any
complicated reasons to act.
If they have something
they want to protect,
they should draw their sword.
Tell me, kid,
do you love your sister?
"Watch the beautiful
sunset from heaven.
The first boat leaves
this afternoon at four."
This is bad!
The ship's about to leave!
Can't you go any faster
on this thing?!
Hey, its always safety first
when I'm driving,
and it'll hurt if we crash.
Now's not the time
to be saying that!
Remember, my sister is
in high‐leg hotpot danger!
Hey, you, without the helmet!
I need you to stop right there!
What do you want, officer?
If this is the feudal period, then
there are no traffic regulations yet.
I mean that's true, but it's going to hurt
if you crash, man.
I'm just telling you this
because I'm concerned.
It's okay, I'll be alright.
I'm pretty hard headed, thanks.
Hey, really?
I'm only trying to be considerate here,
and that's how you act?
It really hurts my feelings,
and it's really a big deal!
Just shut up.
Didn't I tell you
that I'm hard headed?
Ahh, that hurt!
I've got a nose bleed!
Look!
Hot Pot Heaven
is already taking off!
What are we going to do?
It's so high up!
Aaah! Sis!
He'll pay for mocking me like that!
After him!
Yes!
Hey, you little punks!
Did you really think
you can outrun the police?
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
Please allow me
to serve you tonight.
I already told you,
that's not how you do it!
You're supposed to show more
cleavage when you say that, stupid!
Unfortunately, I have never had any
cleavage at all in my entire life!
Oh, sorry.
I didn't realize you couldn't show
any even if you wanted to.
Fine then, next we'll work
on your technique!
It's time to put on your high‐leg outfit
for some hot pot heaven!
Hold on, that's a bit...
But this is how we please
our customers, honey.
Put it on or have you
lost your nerve, ah?
It's way too late to be having second
thoughts about this job, dear!
If you think I'll go easy on you just
because we're on mainstream media,
you're very mistaken!
Remember, this is for your dojo,
so buck up, little soldier!
What is that? Ah!
Hold on, hold on,
what's going on?
Hey, boss!
Whats going on?
Are you alright?
A car just...
A car just crashed into us.
Wait, this is bad!
It's a police car!
That means that the cops
are onto us!
Don't worry, guys.
It's just a rental car,
I'm not the police!
Hello, my name is Odd Jobs Gin.
Tell me right now, sis!
They haven't forced you into
that high‐leg outfit yet, have they?
Shinpachi?
What are you two imbeciles
doing in my nightclub?
We've come to get
my sister back!
You idiot!
Don't any of you understand
that it's too late?
Are you stupid?
Listen! You lot can expect your dojo
to be destroyed after all of this!
I don't care about the stupid dojo.
I want a dojo where my sister
is always happy and smiling.
If that dojo is going
to cause my sister to cry,
then the hell with the dojo!
Oh, Shin...
You idiots!
What do you think you can accomplish
with just the two of you?
Tell me that!
Hey listen, here's the plan.
I'll distract them while you two
find an escape pod
or something and get out of here.
What... what about you?
You just focus on protecting
your sister right now.
I'll protect what
I want to protect.
Just what are you
going on about, you moron?
Die!
All right!
Who's next?
Oh wow!
But his style is ridiculous.
But crazy strong!
Shinichi!
Get out of here!
It's Shinpachi, you idiot!
Shinpachi, will that man
be all right?
Why is he doing
all this for us?
I don't know,
but I know he'll be back,
because I sense it in him!
The thing that father
always talked about,
that samurai sword
in the soul.
See, he really
did come back for us!
That was really tough!
It was far tougher
than I thought!
Then try a little harder!
You didn't even last
a minute against them!
Don't be stupid!
Do you know how tough it is to make
a whole minute of anime?
Just keep looking
for an escape pod right now!
This is...
The engine room?
It's a dead end for you!
Now, it's time to finish
this game of tag.
How pathetic you are.
The samurai who once protected
the country with their swords
are now good for nothing losers
who can't even protect
a single little girl.
There's nothing at all left for
you to protect in this country.
The sky, the ground,
the Capital,
they all belong to us,
the Amanto.
The country, the sky
and ground?
I couldn't care less
about any of that.
Because I'm busy protecting the things
that are right in front of me.
I don't know how many things I've tried
and failed to protect in the past.
I don't have anything left
to lose anymore,
but if I find something laying
in the dirt in front of me...
I swear, I'm going to pick it up!
What a sappy warrior
spirit you have.
I'm tired of all of this!
Just die!
Hold on, sir!
No!
What will happen if
we hit the you know what?
We'll go crashing into the earth
along with the ship.
Oh no, I forgot all about that.
Wait, is he... is he climbing it!?
Hey, hey, hold on!
That's not okay at all!
That's the beating heart
of this ship!
What's important to my clients
is also important to me.
And if it's for the sake
of that, I'll do...
absolutely anything!
No, I don't believe it!
I don't believe that idiot!
He really did it!
What is this floating sensation?
I feel sick!
Is this thing falling?
Are we all falling?
I feel sick!
Luckily, we were over
the ocean when we fell, but...
who knows what
would have happened
if we had been over
the city when we fell.
I've never seen such
a crazy samurai before.
Yeah but...
in the end, he managed
to save us, right?
Hey, what's your problem?
Look, man, I helped you
arrest a bunch of ruffians
who were disturbing
the peace in Edo City!
You can at least let the fact that
I borrowed a police car slide!
You call it "borrowing"?
Both my car and I
are a complete wreck!
You've always been a wreck!
In fact, you actually look
better like that.
Seriously?
Which part?
‐Or are you insulting me...
‐Hey, sis, listen.
‐You should go.
‐Huh?
I can already tell that there's something
that you see in him, right?
You should go with him
and find it.
Go find your sword.
And I'll look for mine
in my own way.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything rash.
Because the truth is,
I don't want to see you crying
as a fully grown man either.
Oh, sis.
Even if there comes a time
when you must give up your sword,
you must never lose the unwavering
sword kept in your soul.
You are a terrible officer!
Admit it!
I am a hero!
Father, It's very difficult for me
to determine the nature
of this strange man's soul,
but although it's dim, I think it's
definitely glistening in darkness.
And I really think,
I'd like to stay beside him
to watch it shine for a while.
Oh no! I forgot my comic books
go on sale today!
Should I use this opportunity
to grow out of them?
No...
Men are boys at heart until
the day they die!
The next episode
Uh... I wish I could shoot a
Getsuga Tensho from my sword.