Keep the room well‐lit...
and watch from a distance!
Kaguraaaaaaaa!
Kagura!
Hey!
Wake up!
Did you just sit there and watch?
Did you bastards just sit
there and watch?
I'm asking you if you
just sat there...
and watched my daughter
bled out...
after she put her own life
on the line to save yours.
W‐W‐Wait there!
It's not like we could call a doctor
in this kind of situation, right, G?
Don't include me!
I don't know anything!
As of today have dementia!
Damn you!
Papa, please don't...
I didn't save them just
for you to kill them.
Kagura!
It's okay now!
Papa's going to take
care of you!
You don't have to worry!
Papa, I have changed,
haven't I?
My strength is no longer just
for hurting people anymore...
I have also learned how
to protect people, now.
Don't talk anymore!
I have made so many
friends here...
and all because of that...
I'm not alone anymore...
The Yato fought, and fought
and ended up
destroying themselves...
The Yato fought, and fought...
and ended up all alone...
Papa, big brother, everyone...
The ones we really have
to fight are ourselves...
Because if we don't, then we will
all end up all alone.
Papa...
Kagura!
Kaguraaaa!
Gin...
Kaguraaaaaaa!
You freaking worm!
Let her go, let her go!
Or I'll piss on you!
I'll give you that sweet
warm piss!
Don't do that!
Your you‐know‐what
will swell up!
Didn't your mother...
ever teach you that, huh?
So...
look who's decided to
show up late to the party.
You've got some nerve
to appear before me.
I just love festivities, you see.
Bonfires, brawls, and aliens
are what Edo City is
famous for, you know?
As if it is!
You're more disturbing than
the damn alien, get lost!
Shut up, because your arm
is missing,
so run your ass
to a hospital!
And you should see
a mental doctor!
It'll take a decade
to set you straight!
You should get your
bald head treated!
Although it might be a
little too late for that
burnt hilltop on your head!
Why are you still here?
Go to the hospital
to get your flathead
screwdriver installed
on your arm.
What am I gonna do with
a flathead screwdriver?
I'd rather have a torque
wrench if anything!
Who the hell goes to a hospital...
just because they lost an arm
or two in the first place!
Besides, my left arm's a prosthetic!
Have them make you a prosthetic
head while they're at it, cueball!
Fire!
We've got to stop it
right here right now!
Don't let it get into
the streets of Edo City!
Vice‐chief!
We're completely destroying
the sky terminal's facilities!
Aren't we going to get into
huge trouble for this?
Who cares?
We'll just have to say that
the alien destroyed it.
Did you hear that, viewers?
We've just witnessed a
blatant police cover‐up
of the destruction
by the Shinsengumi!
Look up there, look at that!
The alien is retreating.
We did it!
We defeated the alien foe!
No, we haven't won yet.
Wh‐What's it doing?!
The alien is gathering
around the ship!
What's happening with the alien?
What is going on over there?
Look!
There's someone...!
Right in the middle of the alien!!
There's someone shouting
in the center of the alien!
Umibozu?
That's Umibozu, the Exterminator!
‐And that guy!
‐Out of my way!
Or we're gonna piss on you!
Umibozu the Exterminator?
He's more of a monster
than the alien is...
And the bossman's keeping up
with him as well!
But we can’t shoot at the alien or
they'll be caught in the crossfire.
Those are...
the government's battleships.
It's Pops!
Old man Matsudaira is here!
The god of destruction!
Katakuriko Matsudaira!
This is very bad,
if Pops takes care of things
there'll be nothing left,
he'll take out the
entire sky terminal!
Looks like the crowds are
finally here to watch the show...
We've just about taken care
of everything here already...
I've got to hand it
to you, punk,
you're pretty good for
an Earthling.
That doesn't sound like
a compliment
when it comes from you,
but thanks, I guess...
I'm amazed you fought
this far with just one arm.
You're only using
one arm yourself!
For your own sake,
go home, or you'll die.
I'd really love to,
but the problem is...
I don't see any emergency exits.
You know, I can't figure you out...
You pushed Kagura away,
so what are you doing here?
Why do all this?
I'd like to know the same thing.
Why in the world did
I come here at all?
Are you...?
Relax...
I'm not planning on
taking such a loudmouthed
brat back home with me...
Of course, I'm not planning
on dying either.
But most importantly, I'm not
planning on letting her die here.
You really are a strange fellow,
aren't you?
I think I understand
why Kagura likes you.
But what can you do
with only one arm?
You only have one arm, too.
No.
‐Together, we've got two!
I don't like it one bit,
but I'm going to help you
until we rescue Kagura!
You can thank me
another time, dad.
I see...
Thanks for the assist!
Hey what's that?
There's something coming out...
Hey...
Hey, it's, what...
Wh‐What the hell is that?!
The nucleus...
That is the core of the
parasitic alien...
But I've never seen
a nucleus this huge!
It must have absorbed
an excessive amount
of the sky terminal's energy
and grown its way
right out of the ship...
If we smash that,
we'll be able to stop it.
Ka...
Kagura!
Whoa!
Hey!
It just swallowed her up!
This is very bad.
We can't finish it off unless
we get her out first!
If we don't, Kagura will die.
Attention!
All civilians in the vicinity
of the sky terminal!
Vacate the area immediately!
We are about to open fire
on the alien!
Vacate immediately!
What?!
What?! What's that?
Pops, wait!
A civilian child has been sucked
into the alien, wait!
Kondo...
Are you weighing the life of
a single civilian
to the same degree of Edo City?
Saving people takes more
balls than killing people,
and if you lose sight
of the bigger picture,
you're going to forfeit your
opportunity to save any lives at all.
Don't be a wussy.
But listen, Pops!
Hey Chief, look, the alien!
Damn it!
It's on the move again.
You see what I mean?
That's what happens when you
don't listen to Pops, huh?
Pops is generally right about
everything, you know?
80 percent of my body is
composed of correctness.
So on that note,
you two should go on
home!
Because you...
are in my way!
You go...
This place will soon
be a sea of flames.
You're not...
thinking of doing
this alone, right?
Turns out I'm just a
loser in the end...
They call me the strongest man
in the galaxy...
but I can't protect a damn thing...
Not even my family...
and not even my one
and only daughter....
The Yato fought, and fought...
and ended up all alone...
The ones we really have to
fight are ourselves.
Because if we don't, then we'll
all end up all alone.
This must be the price I have to
pay for running away...
I'm sorry, Kagura...
At least let me die together
with you, my child.
You know, this is why...
all little girls grow up to detest
their fathers, huh?
Look here, dad..
can't you just bring yourself
to trust your own kid?
Do you really think
she's so weak
that she could be
killed by this thing?
Listen...
give me five minutes,
delay their attack...
I'm not asking you
to believe in me...
But...
At least you can believe
in Kagura.
What are you
planning to do?
What a crazy thing to do...
What are we gonna
do now, Kondo?
Ready the Matsudaira‐Blaster!
‐But Commissioner!
‐I don't care...
‐No, it's not that...
‐just fire.
Please just...
take a look...
They didn't evacuate.
There are more of them.
What?
You dumb‐asses!
Do you see this guy
all we have over here?
If you shoot now, this Prince Caca
will also be blown to bits!
And It'll be a big diplomatic issue!
Just wait five damn minutes,
you dumb bastards!
What difference could
five minutes make?!
Seriously!
Just go make yourself
some instant noodle
while you wait for five minutes!
Why?
Why are you guys...
Well, we do owe that little
girl after all.
They won't shoot, will they?
We'll be all right, won't we?
That darn mop top!
If he was coming...
he should have at least said
so in the first place!
Well, I knew he was
coming, anyway...
I knew that he would.
I have changed...
haven't I?
My strength...
is no longer just for hurting
people anymore...
I've also learned how...
to protect people, now...
‐Kagura...
‐I'm not alone anymore.
Kagura...
Wake up...
Gi...
Gin...
Wake up...
or I'm gonna eat all your
pickled seaweed!
Commissioner...
He's really a prince!!
He's the real Prince Hata...
What's he doing down there?
Oh, is this it?
Is this the Matsudaira‐blaster button?
Yes it is, but we have to rescue
him before things escalate...
Did you just push it?
You're kidding!
Did you just push it?!
Yeah, well I have to be at my
daughter's birthday party at five.
What?!
We have to stop it!
It can't be stopped!
Hold on!
Doesn't it kinda look like
there're about to shoot us?
You're kidding, right?
I am a prince, you know!
This is very bad.
We've gotta get outta here!
That's my pickled seaweed!
Kagura!
What did you do?
Man, that kid sure has
a thing for food!
I wonder what kind of parents
she was raised by?
I'd also like to know how the hell...
you were raised to be such
a wreckless guy!
They say a man
grows up by himself
as soon as he starts growing
hair down below.
You're not wrong!
Now, I think it's about time.
Let's finish the job.
Let's do it, dad.
Who are you calling "dad"?!
Look!
The alien is...
Wait a sec, Pops!
There's no need to shoot!
Just Waaaaaaait!
A date?!
Who are you kidding?
Kuriko is still far too young.
She said she wants to celebrate her
birthday with her friends.
But I bet it's a date with
her boyfriend.
I will absolutely not allow that.
I'll do everything I can to stop it.
I'll even dance the Lambada
on top of her birthday cake.
I'm not talking about a date!
I said wait!
Can't you think of anything
other than your daughter, man?
Shut up!
And besides, I can't stop it now,
anyway.
Hurry up and get out of there!
I'm not taking responsibility
for anything
that might happen
to you down there!
Run?
Where are we supposed to go?
My glasses, my glasses,
my glasses...
Go up. GoUp!
Give me back
my pickled seaweed!
Kagura, pull yourself together.
Stop it, you're bleeding...
She's not fully conscious,
but she broke through the
nucleus in this condition
You're telling me...
this man's voice reached into the
depths of Kagura's subconscious.
Oh!
It's a pickled seaweed.
What have you done to Papa's
precious pickled seaweed!
Hey!
What're you eating?!
Spit it out!
You'll go bald!
You'll go bald
if you eat that!
What's that sound?
Confirmed.
Target has been destroyed.
Oh my dear God...
Those guys...
they must be...
How is that possible?
He blocked that attack...
With nothing but an umbrella?!
Mr. Baldy!
Looks like I got a bit fired
up myself!
Your hair is also a
bit fired up, man...
Who would have thought
I'd die saving someone else?
H‐Hey!
Mr. Baldy!
Hey!
Hey, Baldy!
Bal...
I mean, Mr. Baldy!
Baldy...
Your right side is all...
baldy!
At one point, I really thought
it was the end...
but I fought with my
exceptional kar‐atay skills,
and it really was
no match for me.
So...
What're we going to do with this
mountain of a corpse?
The sky terminal will be out of
service for a while as well.
No telling what the officials
are going to say
thanks to that damn old fart...
He was really was a monster
just like the rumors said.
I'm talking about Umibozu,
the Exterminator.
To tell the truth, I was way
more scared of him
than I was scared of the alien.
Really?
He didn't look like a monster
to me at all, Hijikata...
He just looked like
any old father,
scrambling to protect
his daughter...
A father having trouble
with his daughter,
just like any other
around here...
I hope Umibozu the Exterminator...
found what he came looking for.
Hey.
How's Kagura?
She's being treated
by the rescue team.
Her injury was pretty serious.
Shouldn't you go get treated
for your own?
I told you, my left arm is a
prosthetic to begin with.
I just need to order a new one.
I'm not talking about your arm,
but your head.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Oh, is that what you mean?
You want me to kill you?
Now, I'm missing not only my arm,
but the rest of my hair, too...
It'll grow back in time.
Arms don't grow back.
Not your arm, your hair.
I see, my hair, eh?
Listen, all you ever do
is talk about my hair.
You want me to kill you?
But you know,
both of them remind me of
an important lesson in life.
A lesson in life?
The thing is, I lost my arm
to one of my kids,
It wasn't Kagura...
I have another older kid...
He was bad to the bone,
well no...
not really bad...
let's just say he
inherited the blood
of the Yato Clan thoroughly.
He was like the embodiment
of the fight or flight response...
A long time ago,
the Yato clan
had a terrible custom
called the "Parenticides."
It was a savage practice
where a person's worth...
was determined by surpassing
their parents through death,
although these days, that practice
has mostly disappeared,
but he actually tried to
carry it out...
He tried to take the head...
of the legendary Umibozu.
Are you surprised?
That's what we Yato are like...
When it happened,
I suddenly realized,
that I wasn't trying to stop
my son who was after my head,
I was instinctively
trying to kill him.
If Kagura hadn't stopped me,
I would have murdered
my son for sure...
Even now, I can't forget
the fear in her eyes,
and after that, I couldn't
go back home...
So I ran away...
I was afraid that Kagura would
one day seek my life as well,
and I was overwhelmed with
the fear that if she ever did,
I may not be able to suppress
the monster inside of me...
I didn't have the courage
to change...
or to trust myself,
so I ran away...
leaving young Kagura and
her dying mother behind...
I was afraid of destroying
my family, but in the end,
there was nothing left of
my family anyway...
I came all this way,
because I didn't want Kagura
to go through the same suffering
that I did...
But I was about to make
the same mistake as before...
When you told me,
it hit me...
It was Kagura who
stopped me then,
and it was always Kagura
who supported me...
That's how she is, and yet
I couldn't even trust her one bit...
I thought I saw myself in Kagura.
But Kagura and I are different...
She is...
She's a lot stronger than I am.
Yes, we are very different...
And I've only just realized that...
I'm, I'm a total failure as a father...
Maybe I'm the only one
who thinks I'm her father.
Maybe she doesn't even think
of me as one at all.
‐Hm?
‐Check this out...
She was always writing
them secretly...
And since you had
no permanent address,
they were always
sent back to my place...
I secretly kept them all
in my closet
hoping I get the chance
to hand them to you.
This is the only one
I have right now.
But don't worry,
I'm not the type do anything
as intrusive as to read them...
I figure you're also not the type
to be sobbing after reading this...
‐See you later.
‐Hey!
I don't know all of the details...
but...
If you have a parent
who cares about you
what more do you need?
I wish I had one...
A family like the one you have.
You do?
Ironic, isn't it?
How only the people who
don't have something
understand how important
that thing really is...
So then...
cherish her...
Remember that always.
Let me make this clear...
I am staying at the
Odd Jobs for good...
You can think
of me as your family.
But didn't he say
that he was quitting?
Cherish her, huh?
Hey!
Are you listening, Kagura?
Due to certain circumstances,
Papa is going to cherish you
from now on...
So then, take care of yourself.
Papa!
Why?
But wait, Papa!
Dear Papa...
I haven't seen you in a while...
Are you doing well?
I'm doing fine...
Right now,
I am living in a city called Edo
with some strange people who
call themselves samurai...
They are truly strange creatures...
Even though they're usually all weak,
hopeless and pathetic,
when it really counts,
they draw out their inner strength
through the teaching
of an ideology called
"the way of the Samurai"
and become tough,
noble warriors...
We're all the same,
Yato or Samurai...
We're all fighting
against ourselves...
I think if I can stay here,
I can change...
I think I can become a person
who doesn't give in to herself...
And if I am able to change...
Papa, I want you to take me
with you on your travels...
My dream is to travel through
the universe with you...
and become the best alien buster
in the whole galaxy...
Love, Kagura.
I'll be waiting...
Kagura.
In the next episode,
now that Kagura is
gone, I'll be the heroine!