My sister, Otae works
at a hostess bar
and met a man with
a very hairy butt.
Say, if you had a boyfriend, and...
....if his rear end looked like
an afro, what would you do?
I would love him,
butt 'fro and all.
Otae dear, will you marry me?!!!
In order to thwart this self‐proclaimed
Stalker of Love
Gin declares that he's engaged to my
sister and ends up challenged to a duel.
‐Let's go!
‐A fair...
‐Fight!
Hold on a second!
The blade! Huh?
The tip is gone!
The tip is...
Gin won the duel but with a cowardly trick
that you could hardly call heroic.
Vice Chief!
Is it true that the chief
was jilted by some chick?
And then he lost her in
a duel to some weird loser
who used dirty tricks on him?
Getting shot down by the ladies
is nothing new for him,
but I can't believe
that he lost a fight!
Just who exactly is this silver haired
samurai anyway?
Pipe down, we're in
a meeting right now.
And there's no way that Kondo
would ever lose a duel.
Who is the idiot who's been
spreading such stupid rumors?
It was Captain Okita!
He was blasting it
over the loudspeaker.
I heard it from you,
Vice Chief Hijikata.
I was the idiot for telling
that idiot loud mouth.
What the hell?
You were the one who started
the rumor after all!
What's with that cocky look
on your face?
Quit messing around!
So what, then?
Are you saying
those rumors are true?
Shut the hell up!
You wanna talk about private affairs
during the meeting?
You can spill your guts, literally.
Yamazaki, you're the first batter up.
What, me?
‐But I didn't say anything.
‐I'm pretty sure I can hear you...
...speaking right now,
you maggot!
But I didn't...
Hey, what's up, guys?
This meeting's pretty lively
for a change.
Right!
Okay, everyone,
let's go out there and do
our civic duty, shall we?
What's wrong?
So then it's all right?
You'll go at it anyway,
even if I try to stop you.
Don't worry yourself
about it, Vice Chief.
We'll definitely find him
without fail!
All right, let's go, men!
‐Right!
They just don't get it.
Do those guys actually think
that they can beat
the person who defeated Kondo?
Now listen up!
It's just one opponent!
Find him no matter
what it takes!
For the honor of the Shinsengumi!
Our target is
a silver haired samurai!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're not thinking of trying
to beat me, are you?
You know what that is?
That's beyond reckless.
Its borderline arrogance,
your ego is so bloated.
You make me wanna burp.
Well, if you plan on fighting,
fight like your life is on the line.
I'll make it so that you'll never
be able to burp again.
I'm not so lame that I'll surrender
to all of your big talk,
because this fight won't be settled
with burping, but with brains.
Hey, who cares about
the burping?
Just get on with it!
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Shinpachi Shimura.
It seems like every day the trees
are turning greener and greener.
By the way, the reason
why we're scowling
at each other
like this is because...
Well, actually,
it's pretty complicated.
Hey! I’m Princess Layer!
The great space war has finally begun,
but I don't really understand
all the complicated stuff.
All I can say is, may the
horse be with you!
So, hey, you guys,
I can hear everything you guys are
thinking loud and clear, you know!
Are you pretending
to be stupid, numbskulls?
Leave us alone.
This is a part of our strategy!
And what do you mean by
"pretending" to be stupid?
They're already telling us
that this anime
is too hard for kids
to understand.
Cut the crap, or we won't just
get our budget reduced,
but we'll be cancelled!
This... Gintoki shouted from
deep within his heart.
Gintoki shouted, you say?
Why don't you stop
copying us, Gin?!
Dumb ass!
As if I'd give you the upper hand
in something like this.
That's right.
This is the one match
that we can't ever lose.
How did it turn out
like this, I wonder?
Well, just take a look at this!
It all started with
the Odd Jobs gang at home.
Gintoki, Shinpachi, and Kagura
were going about their lazy daily lives
but then came a client who shattered
the peace and quiet.
That man was none other
than the advisor
of the Kabukicho Town Council
"slash" Carpenter,
Ishida Pierre Genpachi
Saymaru.
Age 63, a Virgo.
His request was for help
with his carpentering.
However, the request happened
to have had a frightening catch to it.
He only wanted one person.
One person to do
all the work!
They reacted to the news instantly.
High level negotiations began,
voices and hands going non‐stop.
Proposals were put forth
only to be rejected immediately.
But when the dust
had finally settled,
they had decided on the best
method to choose
the one who would do
all the work.
The mother of all competitive sports.
Rock, paper, scissors!
All right, best out of one!
No objections?
If I lose,
its manual labor!
I can't afford to lose this match
no matter what!
I'll use any trick
that I can.
I simply have to win!
Here we go! Rock!
Howacha!
Hey, what're you doing, Kagura?
This is rock, paper, scissors!
There's no benefit in
showing your hand early!
The early bird
guts the worm!
Do you have any idea
how this game works at all?
All right!
If that's how you guys
want to play, so be it.
I'll play your game!
Hey! What ever happened
to rock, paper and scissors?
Come on you guys!
Ready?
Best of one!
No buts, ands or ifs!
Rock, paper, scissors... and go!
Hey, hey, hey!
You know you can't beat
your opponent by copying them.
We're just going to keep trying
unless you can be a bit more original.
In my family,
the girl wins if its a tie.
Oh, is that so?
Well we are on earth,
and in case you didn't know,
on earth we play
with earth rules!
Says the guy who's never
followed a rule in his life.
Rock, paper, scissors!
What are you jerks
trying to pull this time?
What is that?
Are you a total idiot or what?
This is a crab, obviously.
I'll admit your crab
is better than a rock.
But you still can't beat
this family of five.
Whose family
is that supposed to be?
We omitted Meg
in the Japanese version.
Did you not hear me when I said
this was rock, paper, scissors?
I guess you lose, Shinpachi.
Looking forward to
the money you bring back!
What?
Why do I lose?
You two should lose
for trying to cheat!
Don't give me that!
You know you're just jealous
of my great intellect!
Don't be a baby!
You guys are cheaters!
Come on, there are rules
in this world!
Everyone knows rules
are made to be broken.
Don't be stupid!
Fine, Gintoki wins.
Victory!
What?
That's just too bad, loser.
Don't bother coming back
until you finish.
That's right, Shinpachi,
the customer is always right.
Listen to whatever he says.
Hey wait, you've got
the wrong guy!
Quit your yapping.
The winner is blessed with
the privilege of doing this job,
and you can thank me later.
No, that's not what we... huh?
What?
‐Have a nice day.
You'll never get away,
silver haired samurai!
Show yourself!
All right, over here!
Hey, listen mister.
You know I haven't actually
agreed to this yet.
All you do is complain!
Hurry up and haul
these supplies to the site.
There he is!
The silver haired bastard!
We've got you now,
silver haired samurai!
That's...
Saliva'n and some rice...?
Seconds, please!
‐You should watch what you eat, fatty!
We found him!
The silver haired samurai
is over there!
There's no escape,
silver haired samurai!
‐This is...
‐A barber chair and a samurai?
How would you like it cut?
I think just trim it.
‐Just shave it off, baldy!
Get a move on already.
There's a mountain of work
to be done.
You just don't get it, do you?
To have a healthy work environment,
you have to inspire your employees
‐and keep them in good spirits.
‐Sure thing.
Just make sure you don't fall
and turn into a ghost.
Wear this.
What was that?
They turned the city upside down
by putting up signs
all over Edo City,
and so now everyone
and their mother
knows about Kondo losing?
Yeah, they're all really
going bananas out there.
Although they don't seem to have
anything to show for it yet.
That bunch of stupid apes.
What do they think
they're going to achieve
by telling the entire population
that our chief can be bested.
Well, what do you wanna do?
If we sit back and do nothing,
we'll just be causing trouble
for everyone
and we'll be dragging the Shinsengumi's
reputation through the mud.
Let's go, Okita.
But where are we going?
What do you mean?
Kill him?
Yeah, kill him.
Do you mean
the silver haired samurai?
Yeah, I'll have
to kill him off myself
before this mess
gets any bigger.
Vice chief, it troubles me that
every other word you say is "kill."
History teaches us that nothing good
ever comes to assassins.
This isn't an assassination.
I'll walk up to him
and strike him down.
You know, I have an idea.
If you just haul in any
old guy and dress them up
to look like
that silver haired samurai,
that should be good enough
to satisfy the troops.
How about this guy?
Here, hold this
wooden sword properly.
Hey gramps, do me a favor
and crack that idiot's skull
open with that sword.
Hijikata, sir, I know at first glance
he's not very scary,
but take off his glasses
and look!
The legend, Musashi!
That cool face
is wasted on you!
Are you really planning
to kill that guy?
The only thing we know about him
is that he's got silver hair.
He's not just any regular guy
if he's able to beat Kondo.
I'll know him
when I see him.
Yeah, it's me.
Really?
Got it.
Did they find him then?
Yamazaki found someone
who fits the samurai's description.
Hurry up, let's go!
This is the place.
Shinsengumi, put your hands up
where I can see them!
Can we help you
with something?
‐This is...
‐a really super‐poor samurai?
Oh, fits the description?
It barely sounds alike!
Get back here and
commit harakiri, Yamazaki!
‐You are done for!
‐A silver haired samurai, huh?
I wonder where in the world
he could be?
You blockhead!
Put more of your heart and soul
into that hammer, would you?
I'd probably be able to if it was your
head this nail was going into, baldy.
What was that, fur ball?
Stop blabbering on
and move your hands,
you damned silver haired mophead!
Well, we can't find him anywhere.
I still don't think
you have enough clues,
so why don't we go back?
Remember, I gotta watch my favorite
comedy show that starts at four o'clock.
When did they switch the times?
I'm pretty sure there's been
a drama rerun showing at four.
Oh, is that so?
Oh well.
But hey, that drama is supposed
to have a happy ending.
Aren't you the same
as the rest of us?
You pretend like you don't care,
but deep down you're furious.
Huh, I wonder why.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Back when we were stuck in the
countryside, filled with anger,
it was none other than Kondo
that took us in.
We were able to walk around town with
our heads held high as Shinsengumi...
like this because of that man.
We made the decision
to follow him to the end.
Isn't that right, Okita?
Now go, Sadomaru Number 3.
The target is that guy's butt.
Hey you, are you even
listening to me?
Damn it!
‐Hey, look out below, brother.
‐What?
Hey, hey, that's dangerous!
That's why I said,
look out below.
But why don't you say it
with a bit more urgency?
What's wrong with you?
Hey, shut your hole.
Like I'm supposed to listen to a stranger
coach me on dramatic delivery, ah?
It's you, that bomb suspect!
Oh yeah, I forgot that jerk
had silver hair too.
Okay, who are you again?
Oh, is that you, Johnny?
Oh my, look how grown up
you've become.
What's up? Is your pet gold fish
still alive and strong?
Hey, Gintoki, hurry up!
I need your hand up here!
Be right up!
See ya, Johnny.
Gotta get back to work.
He just left.
Whatcha gonna do, Johnny?
Who are you calling Johnny,
you idiot?
I can't believe he just forgot about me
after just three or four episodes!
Yeah, I mean, I think most people
would forget you.
Okita, please lend me
your sword.
Give me a break.
Working all day with this baldy
is going to make me start
losing my hair as well.
Sheesh! If help weren't so hard
to find these days,
I would never ask
you guys for it.
Don't screw that up, you hear?
And same to you, baldy.
First bomb disposal,
and now roof repair?
You don't have an ounce
of pride, do you?
Exactly, what kind of stunt
are you trying to pull up here?
Bomb disposal?
Hey, man, aren't you that...?
You finally remembered, eh?
Even in the Shinsengumi, there's no one
who'd do something that insane.
I couldn't believe it at first when I
heard someone had beat Kondo,
but if it's you, it might actually
be possible.
Kondo who?
You two fought over
a woman, didn't you?
Was she really all that?
Why don't you introduce me to her?
Huh? What's this?
The tip broke!
Wait, so you're friends
with that gorilla butt?
But what are you coming
after me for?
Hey, asshole,
what's the big idea?
He may be a gorilla butt...
but to us,
he's our beloved general!
We built the Shinsengumi from the ground
up with nothing but our swords.
He's my brother‐in‐arms!
I won't let anyone humiliate
the Shinsengumi
and if anyone dares
to dirty our name...
then I'll send them
straight to hell!
It's time to watch my TV!
Hey, loser!
Didn't anybody teach you
not to run around with knives?
What was that?
Hey, Gin man!
I ain't paying you if
you're going to just play around!
Shut up, baldy!
Call the police,
we got a problem!
But I am the police.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Man, this world is so messed up.
I guess you're right.
I just can't figure
this guy out.
I heard he pulled a dirty trick
against Kondo,
but he's not doing anything
like that now.
Now that I think about it,
he's not even trying to use
the sword I gave him.
Could it be...
this guy's going easy
on me even though...
I'm obviously trying
to take his life?
Damn!
Fight back!
Killing a guy one sidedly will just leave
a really bad taste in my mouth!
Draw that sword!
Well, now we're talking.
It's your life or mine!
I got him!
What?
What the...?
He dodged me?
I'm screwed!
Alright, fight's over.
Ow, ow, ow...!
Hey, baldy, I need to go
to the hospital!
Hold it!
Are you trying
to show me mercy?
Show you mercy?
If I had any of that, I'd put it
in my rice and eat it, but...
The thing about fighting
is that its only worth it
when you have
something to protect.
Just like when you were trying
to protect the Shinsengumi.
Trying to protect?
Then, what are you trying
to protect?
My way of life, man.
See ya.
What a funny guy he is.
Makes me want to try
crossing swords with him myself.
Forget it, Okita.
Even you would have
a tough time, trust me.
That man may be pointing
his blade at you,
but he's fighting something
that is much bigger
than any one of us.
For him, it's beyond winning
and losing or right and wrong.
I'm very sorry, Kondo sir.
Looks like he beat me too.
The heck is this?
Kagura, If you're gonna
pick up strays,
pick up something
at least we know the name of!
Huh? You want to keep it?
No way, no way! Daddy is
not okay with this at all!
The next episode...