So then cherish her...
Remember that always.
I see...
So that little glutton really
went back home to her planet.
Yeah...
I tried to stop her, but...
Gin said it's probably best
for her to be with her father.
Yeah, that's right.
It's much better than staying with
a drifting wanderer like Gin.
She was always noisy and
very annoying, but I think...
I'm gonna miss her
now that she's gone.
You all look so sad, don't you?
You're all so sad because
you miss me so much, huh?
I'm just going to hide
out for a while.
That way, you'll keep
believing that I'm gone
and you'll truly realize just
how important I was to you!
Anyway, I don't see the guy who
deserves to be feeling the saddest...
Where is he?
Where is that mop top...
Oh...
In the restroom...
I see now...
Gin must have gone in there so no
one can see him crying over me.
Ah!
Gee, it's all swollen!
Swollen eyes from crying
too hard?
This is terrible...
My important parts
are evidently swollen!
Seriously, this is awful!
Really?
It's probably because you've been
touching it with your filthy hands!
I'm nothing like you.
How old do you think I am?
So then, did you get a disease
from someone?
I'm not like you, either.
I don't skate on thin ice
the way you do.
That bastard!
I'm gone but all you can talk
about is your stupid crotch?
Maybe you're just imagining it?
Maybe it was just that size
to begin with.
Get back to the original topic!
No way, man.
He was more of a
modest kind of guy.
Hey, that's enough of that!
Do you remember if you peed
on a worm somewhere, huh?
They say it swells up if you do.
What are you talking about?
That's just an old wives' tale.
Come on.
Did you really...
No, no, no.
It wasn't a worm, it was
more like a worm‐like alien...
So you went and pissed
on an alien, then?
Alright, rest in peace, buddy.
My friend did that one time and
he became a shooting star.
What's that?
He became a shooting star?
What does that mean?
What's going to
happen to me?
Rather, what's going
to happen...
to the other me!
I said that's enough about
that subject already!
All they're talking about
is his crotch.
Come on!
Do they always talk about
their crotches
whenever I'm not around
or what?
Huh?
Good evening everyone!
Big sis!
Hey, Sis, what's with
the Chinese dress?
Well, it happens to be
Chinese Dress Booster Month
at the bar I work at, so everyone's
wearing these dresses to work.
What is a Chinese Dress
Booster Month, huh?
What's being boosted by that?
Well, Men's fantasies, Shin...
How do I look, Gin?
This is not good.
I don't wanna be a shooting star,
I'm still too young.
It's useless to try to speak to him
right now, and don't ask why.
Oh, you miss Kagura so much...
I'm so sorry, did I make you
remember her?
Yes, Sister!
We're back on track.
You're the best, big sis!
I think this might
cheer you up...
Have some drinks and
forget about her!
‐Oh? Big sis?
‐Wow, this is expensive sake!
‐That's not, that's not right...
‐I swiped...
‐Forget about me?
‐er got it from work.
‐Are you guys trying to forget?
‐Forgetful Wife...
Some things you just have
to forget to be able
to move on in life.
Let's rinse away the bad memories
with a glass of this, huh?
Right, Gin?
Bad memories?
Am I a bad memory?
No, I can't forget about it.
It's always hanging in
between my legs, isn't it.
Can't you think of anything
other than your crotch, man?
Well, I'm sure Kagura's doing
just fine back home.
As long as she's alive,
we'll be able to see her again.
No one's listening
to you, granny!
If you ask me, I'm very happy
that she's gone...
What did you say, pig shit?!
I've always thought
she and I were
too similar for the both of us
to be in the same show...
As if!
I'm like the cute oriental chick
from a foreign planet.
Nah.
You're not cute at all...
Meow!
I really miss her, to tell the truth...
I was starting to think of Kagura
as something like my real sister...
Because...
I've actually always wanted
a little sister.
Big sis...
When Shinpachi was little,
I used to force
him to dress up like a girl.
Our dad always scolded
me for doing that...
Right, Shinpachi?
Your father's Bleep‐bleep,
Your father's bleep‐bleep,
‐Listen to her!
‐Your father's bleep‐bleep!
‐Oh why...
‐Father's Bleep‐bleep,
Why did you have to die
and leave us alone, Dad!
You're just crying about
your father now?
Personally speaking, do you know
any good urologists around here?
Yeah that's personally
speaking all‐right.
Actually, there's a urologist
across from the grocery store...
on third Street, and I heard there's
a hot doctor working there.
Really, man?
That'll make my swelling
even worse.
Get lost, you dirty old men!
Well, maybe so.
But if I had to see a doctor,
I'd prefer it if they're hot.
But I guess you'd feel
a little embarrassed...
You idiot!
That's what's good about it, man.
Can you imagine
being examined
by a hot doc in that
kind of situation?
That's something
to look forward to!
I guess so, but listen,
if you have a stone, it'll be a
completely different story.
Stones are really nasty.
I mean, it really hurts.
The pain is out of this world.
It won't matter whether the doc is
beautiful or butt ugly.
Is that so?
But I heard you feel great
once it's finally out...
Well that's true.
It's a sign that your suffering
is finally over with...
I can't even describe
how painful it is.
It hurts so bad you can do a
somersault and win the Olympics!
So you actually experienced it?
Well I...
What the hell are you
guys talking about now?
Besides, a barbaric glutton
in a Chinese dress
in this day and age
is so last century!
I bet she was
faking everything!
She was probably sticking a finger
up her throat behind the scenes.
Hey, you're forgetting
your accent aren't you?
You were faking your
accent all along?!
Hey, Catherine,
you're way out of line!
That's no way to speak about
a dead person you know!
Have some respect at least,
would you please?
Hey!
I'm not dead!
Besides, if you ask me,
your accent is totally outdated!
I can't understand
what you're saying!
Tell her, Shin!
Your father's Bleep‐bleep,
I told you to listen!
I wonder what it's
gonna be like
to have a hot chick doctor
check this out.
Should I go, or should I not?
Please go, straight to hell!
Anyway, what about Odd Jobs?
What are you two planning
to do with just two dudes?
Do you even think you can
keep it running without her?
Huh?
It doesn't matter how many people
there are at Odd Jobs.
I used to run it all by myself
in the first place.
No no, that's not what I meant...
Actually...
A while back this girl came by
saying she wanted to join you...
I guess she must have thought
I was the boss of Odd Jobs,
and left her picture and her resume.
Huh?
She what?
I mean was the Odd Jobs
ever that famous?
I feel a little "ticklish" hearing that...
Your mean your crotch
feels ticklish, right?
This picture looks more like...
a mailorder bride ad to me.
Oh, wow, she's very pretty!
Oh, I can't see...
Ayame Sarutobi...
She's has an impressive career.
She served the Spy Agent
for a good while
and then transitioned
into an assassin.
An assassin?
Whoa!
A thief!
And a spy girl!
Just Who the hell are you?
Like the fading echo
of a Temple bell...
all things in life are temporary...
Like the flower that
blossoms and wilts...
thus marks the change of heroine.
Good evening,
Odd Jobs Sacchan is here.
Huh?
Sacchan?
Life isn't that easy.
The thing is, you can't
succeed in business
with just a bunch of dull guys...
Like Adam and Eve,
the CEO and his
beautiful secretary,
a master and his maid,
and Lady and the Trumpet...
In every circumstance, you need
to have a real heroine.
I think she's missing the point
in some of these instances...
That being said, violent little girls
are so last epoch...
and a cat‐eared middle‐aged
bonesack is totally out!
As for granny, I can't even tell if she's
a dude, or human...
Do you understand?
Things are gonna be different...
Starting today is the age of the ninja
girl four‐eyes!
Wait, Four‐eyes ninja girl?
Right, let's go with that.
It's time for three eyes ninja...
Oops, my mistake!
She's such a mess.
And thusly, to conclude...
um...
Gin, please take me...
as your bride, no, I mean...
Let me join the Odd Jobs team...
We've already got a four‐eyes
named Shinpachi, so no...
This is a team and we all need
our own distinct personality...
And your appearance expresses
your personality the most.
You don't want fans to say,
"Hey, she's just copying
Shinpachi's look,"
so maybe you can change
your hairstyle...
like to a Mohawk, or try to look
more like Choda
or Chewcocka or
R2‐D2F or something.
You have to have a stand out
look so that people can tell who
you are just from your silhouette,
and then you can come back
for another round.
He's trying to talk
like he's an editor
from some
comic book publisher.
You've got nothing to complain
about now, do you?
Are you happy now?
You can bully me all you want,
but just so you know...
I'm a masochist,
so I'm enjoying it too!
I'm a masochist and you're
a sadist, and that's enough.
What else do we need?
Uh, sorry, but I am kind of
an masochist too...
That's the DORK
that you're talking to!!
Hey, listen newcomer!
You pop up out of nowhere and
think you can be a heroine?!
This world ain't so easygoing!
Catherine, you...
I don't know who you think you are,
but I've been working here
or an eternity,
way before you
ever showed up.
I'm the new heroine
of this show!
That's definitely not how it works!
Shut up, you middle‐aged woman!
Those cat ears are completely
wasted on you!
If I had your ears,
I'd be a ninja with
glasses and cat ears.
I'd have all three elements
of the triforce of cuteness!
A middle aged woman
with cat ears.
This gap is what draws
in the fans!
Oh yeah, what fans?
That's enough,
knock it off now, you two!
How do you think Kagura
would feel if she saw
you two fighting
like this right now?
And besides...
don't you think
this Chinese dress
looks much better on me
than on Kagura?
Big sis?
Are you also trying to become
the new heroine of the show?
Why are you acting like
you're suddenly so special,
meow bow wow!
You have the least personality
of all of us, meow bow wow!
What's with the
"meow bow wow"?
Is that her new gimmick?
Is she trying to be
a dog or a cat?
Just being unique
doesn't make you a heroine.
Your face is too unique,
in an ugly way!
‐What?!
‐And as for you,
don't act so high and mighty,
just because you've known
Gin longer than me,
four‐eyes beam!
She doesn't even have
her glasses anymore.
But I've known him
the longest, Kung Fu!!
What does Kung fu have
to do with anything?
What's that?!
Listen, it's not about
how much time you spend.
It's all about the quality
of that time,
and the truth is
I've already done
a whole lot of this
and that with Gin!
Oh?
And what exactly is "a whole
lot of this and that"?
I bet they're all fragments
of your sick delusions.
You should go see
a mental doctor.
Cat woman's stronger than
ninja girls, meow bow wow!
A cat woman who's dog ugly!
What are you, kindergarteners?
Just back off, you two!
You don't love Gin
as much as I do,
and I'm the one who deserves
to be with him.
I do like him.
He ranks right next
to my nail clippers.
How far down the list is that,
meow bow wow?!
What I really love
most is myself.
So the thing is I hate losing
to anyone, and that's that.
Let me tell you something.
I don't give a shit
about that useless Gin!
I just want to be
on the show longer!
Meow bow wow!
Get lost, or take my
four‐eyes cannon!
Hey, everyone, just relax,
just calm down!
If you keep this up,
we won't be able to decide.
You should listen to the opinions
of us men.
What are you trying to decide?
Us men firmly believe...
that a girl has to be three requirements
to become a heroine...
The three are...
Good Looks.
Good figure.
Personality.
I don't have any of those!
So that being said, you can
go home now, cat ears.
Screw you.
But you two can stay.
Listen...
A heroine needs to look...
very good...
But it doesn't mean
just having a pretty face,
no, not at all...
because a face
that beats the crap
out of people with a smile...
And someone who gets
excited over things
that might cause a
kids relationship
with their parents to get awkward
are out of the question...
What I'm saying...
It's all about your
facial expressions!
You have to make
expressions the fans
expect according
to each circumstance...
Smile when you should smile...
Getting angry from
time to time.
I'm so angry now,
fume fume...
Can blossom flowers
in your background
anytime you want.
It's one day late,
but Happy Birthday!
Being able to tear
up instantly.
Oh, oh, uh...
You have to be able to
cry whenever necessary.
I'm so happy, I'm just
so overwhelmed by it ...
And therefore,
the heroine will be Otsu...
Enough of that!
You heard him.
So you go first.
Cry now.
Then...
Please use this.
You got it wrong from the start!
She's out of the question.
You try.
Cry now.
Well now, that'sway too easy.
Come on, cry!
I won't stop until I see your tears!
Um...
But, why?
But this kinda feels good...
How you like that?
Hey, Otae!
I didn't tell you to make
someone else cry!
‐I told you to cry.
‐I think I like this.
You really are a dork!
Oh, God.
Seriously, what is wrong with you all?
Hey,
you haven't given me a chance yet...
So how do I look?
Purr‐fect?
What is wrong with you all?
I'll kill you, bastard!
Oh, why don't you just
give up?
We‐well, let's leave your
"looks" for now.
What's more important
is your figure.
A heroine's gotta be, you know,
"Bang! Pow! n Boom!"
Like a juicy ripe fruit,
she must be
plump, but not fat.
From the moment
you see them,
the faces won't matter anymore.
They move up and down,
and side to side.
And your sleazy eyes keep
following those movements.
Those jiggles that a heroine,
a real heroine,
should always possess...
That's what I'm talking about
when I say figure...
An erotic hourglass figure
that's thick in parts
but tight where
it needs to be!
He's just talking to himself
at this point.
So of course, that excludes
the monster cat lady...
Now let's compare
the two of you...
Bang.
Pow...
Boooooom!
Well then, you both pass...
The last thing is...
Um?
Huh?
Was it "personality"?
Well, uh...
Both of you are totally
perfect, so...
I just can't pick a winner...
you know...
You had better
pick one, asshole!
You chumps are the ones
who started this,
four‐eyes bazooka.
Shi‐Shinpachi...
Wake up, Shinpachi.
You're the one who
suggested "personality,"
so you should be the judge of this.
A heroine?
The heroine is...
It's Otsu then.
I would say it's Otsu.
‐I'm the heroine!!!!
Come with me to the riverbank.
We'll settle this ourselves!
You asked for it!
‐Gi‐Gin, man...
‐What now?
Why can't we just ever have
nice ordinary girls around us?
I agree.
When it comes right down to it,
Kagura was the best of
them all, wasn't she?
I agree...
You guys are so pathetic.
You're the one that
told her to leave,
and you already miss her?
This is how selfish men are and why I
don't like them.
Right?
Why don't you say something?
Sorry I don't have
an hourglass figure.
All right, don't say anything.
Don't say a word.
Everyone knows that I'm the only
one who can handle you jerks...
So that means I'm the heroine.
Don't you mean a mascot?
Come inside already!
Let's have another drink.
What's this,
you're not going to eat?
Don't worry about the money.
It's on me today,
I assure you.
Don't you guys
dare eat one bite!
His face tells me
he's plotting something.
And it says he's going to ask us
to do something impossible.
No need for groundless suspicions.
Even if we really
were really hungry,
you can't buy us
off with food.
We're not that cheap...
Don't think you can sweet
talk us either, Katsura...
It's so sweet I can't talk!
This chocolate just
melts in my mouth!
Excuse me!
Can I have a refill?
I should've been
more careful...
Elizabeth was always
with me.
So I should've known
she would attract
the attention of the authorities.
So, who do you think did it?
Chintaro Toyama,
the evil magistrate.
He's a corrupt judge
who takes any bribes
to satisfy his evil desires...
Elizabeth's head will definitely
roll if I don't do something...
I'm begging you, Gintoki.
Please help me to rescue
Elizabeth from that place.
What?!
You're going to sneak into the
magistrate's office, nin nin?
Well, this idiot here, he just
won't take no for an answer.
And I thought you're a ninja,
so that means you're good
at that kind of stuff.
‐So, please.
‐What are you asking for, nin nin ?
Can you turn him
into a ninja, too?
Are you underestimating
the ninja, nin nin?
Do all ninja have to say "nin nin"
at the end of each phrase?
My name's not "nin nin."
It's Katsura.
But you can't possibly become
a ninja overnight, no way.
We girls shed blood, sweat,
and tears to become ninjas!
Don't you underestimate us, nin nin!
Manager, aren't you a man?
Then, I ask you, could you at
least come with us, Thatcher!
I'm not the iron lady!
I wanna be just like you, snatcher!
Stop calling me a snatcher,
I'm Sacchan, dumb‐ass.
I'm terribly sorry,
but I have past connections
with the government,
so I can't do anything stupid...
See, look here.
I've got a call for work...
Are you insulting us?
Stop messing with your phone
while you are with a customer!
You're awfully harsh with me.
Why are you blushing?
Why are you smiling?
You don't have connections
with the government anymore.
‐So you can help us Hey!
‐Hey! What are you doing?!
‐Hurry up and bring my damn tea!
‐Yes, sir!
I'll be right with you, nin‐nin.
I'm very sorry, but like I said,
I can't come with you.
I'm too busy with
my daytime job.
See ya!
Here's your tea, nin nin!
Here's your cake, too, and it's
on the house now!
Hey, Sacchan!
What are you doing to him?!
That's enough from you.
Now you are fired.
But...!
‐Manager!
‐I'm over here.
Oh!
My glasses...
Oh, when did that happen?
‐Hey, over here.
‐Oh?
You left your glasses here...
Oh, Sacchan, you're so careless,
aren't you?
But now that you don't have
any restraints...
Let's go.
Uh so...
Look, Sacchan...
I'm very sorry...
Ah...
I just want to be bullied
some more.
What?!
You're such a freak!
Well, I'm going to pound
into your little heads
everything that there is to
know about being a ninja...
First.
A ninja must be
like a shadow.
They do their work
so discreetly
that no one ever know
they are there...
Whatever you do,
you must be inconspicuous!
Inconspicuous?
Just look at us!
What are we, the Power Dudes?
Well, it doesn't matter, anyway,
I can't tell your faces apart.
Everyone but Gin looks
all the same to me.
We're like pebbles
on the ground?
Oh, Gin, your scarf
isn't tied right.
You're so careless,
you know.
You can't do anything
without me.
You can't tell anyone
apart period!
And you still can't recognize
anyone, come on!
Put your glasses on!
By the way,
why is my color yellow?
The leader is supposed
to wear red.
I wanna wear red.
Don't fight me on this, Cobra.
Red is my symbolic color.
So I'm the captain.
It's not very convincing, but it's
fine if I have no other choice.
As the captain,
I make the orders.
Yellow ninja, your favorite
food is curry,
so you must always
carry curry with you.
Hey, Shinpachi, can you
trade your outfit with me?
It's so white that
I'm sure I'll stain it
when I eat my curry noodles.
Who gives a crap about
curry or curry noodles!
What did you come here to do?!
Thus it happened,
we teamed up as
the Power Ninjas
to sneak into the
Magistrate's office
where Elizabeth
is being held...
But there were powerful foes
waiting for us in the path ahead!
The next episode...