The land of the samurai.
There was a time,
a long time ago
when our country
was called by that name.
With the arrival
of the "Amanto"
or Sky People
and the Sword Ban
enacted 20 years ago
the samurai class fell into decline.
In these hard times there was one man left
with the spirit of the samurai.
His name is Gintoki Sakata,
a reckless jack of all trades
with a serious sweet tooth
and a big heart.
Due to some rather
unexpected events,
I, Shinpachi Shimura and
Kagura, work here now.
The three of us working together
fight the corruption on the planet!
Is this that kind of anime?
Hey, you swine!
The huge stash of chocolate
I've been stashing away
for a special occasion
has disappeared.
I want whoever ate it to raise
your hand and confess.
Do it now and I'll only kill you
in three fourths of the way.
Three fourths of the way?
That's barely any better
than being killed all the way!
Besides, if you don't take it easy on
sugar, you really will get diabetes.
Another Amanto embassy attacked.
Serial terrorist bombing
rampage continues.
The world sure is
a very violent place.
Oh, but I'm so scared,
Daddy, Mommy!
You are the one
that's scary here.
Trying to look all innocent while
you're bleeding from your nose.
Tell me, were my chocolates tasty?
You think I got a nosebleed
from eating chocolate?
Oh, please!
Don't play dumb!
I can smell the sugar in your blood
wafting through the air!
Don't be so silly.
I just went in for a booger
a little too deep.
Too bad you missed your brain
while you were digging in there!
Have you used
a drill to do that?
What kind of nonsense
talk is that?
Just chill out already!
Oh, man, what's the ruckus?
‐What happened?
‐Did you see?
‐Are you okay?
An accident?
Moron!
What are you doing, smashing into
my storefront like that?
I hope you're prepared
to die, moron!
I'm... I'm sorry, ma'am.
I dozed off because
I didn't sleep well last night.
No problem!
I'm gonna make sure that
you close your eyes forever!
Don't, Otose!
Don't treat an injured person
like that!
Are you all right?
Ye... yeah.
This is really bad.
Hey, Kagura,
call for an ambulance.
Ambulance!
Oh, that's a pretty primitive way
of calling for an ambulance!
You're a postman, huh?
Well, your packages are now
a complete mess!
Please, please, sir.
Please, sir, deliver this package
in my place.
I think that this package is very
important and must be delivered.
If I fail to deliver it,
I might lose my job.
Please do this...
Hey!
Are you sure that
this is the place?
Yup.
An Embassy.
This is Planet Canis' Embassy!
The Canis from
he Dog Star System
were the first of the Amanto
to come to earth, weren't they?
Yeah, they're the scary ones
who fired cannons at the Edo Castle
and forced the country to open up.
This is a nasty place,
that's for sure.
‐Hey!
‐Huh?
What are you three doing
here at our Embassy?
Are you trying get ruffed up?
Uh, we were actually just asked
to deliver a package here.
Come on, Kagura,
hand it over!
Come here, little doggy.
I'll give you a treat.
What do you think
you're doing?
Oh, hey, here it is.
I didn't hear anything at all about
a package being delivered today.
Lately we've been receiving a lot of
terrorist threats to bomb this place,
and security is very tight.
Go home.
Well, it might be dog food inside.
So, why not just take it?
As if I'd eat that garbage!
My brain is not quite comprehending
what just happened,
but I think I have figured out
our next move.
‐Run away!
‐Where do you think you're going?
Shinpachi!
What do you think you're doing?
Let me go!
No way!
They're not taking me alone!
Can't you just
be cool and say,
"Just leave me,
save yourselves"?
Why don't you just leave me
and let me save myself?
Shut up! If they take me,
I'm taking you with me!
Waah! Are you fur‐real!, man?
These guys are such
a pain in the butt.
Huh?
It's time to go, Gintoki.
What? You're Cobra?
Kotaro Cobra?
My name is Katsura,
not Cobra!
Man, you jerk!
We see each other
for the first time in ages
and that's how you greet me?
Because I've told you
a thousand times
to stop calling me
by that nickname.
Anyway what exactly
are you even doing here?
How long are you going
to keep barking?
‐Save it for later, Gintoki.
‐Right.
Wait!
Come back here!
Oh, he finally exposed himself.
‐Yamazaki!
‐Sir!
Follow them and track down
their base, at any cost.
Yes, sir!
With all the Sky People
living in the world these days,
even the famed hero
of the Amanto war
is nothing more than
just another criminal.
It takes real guts to still be fighting
the Amanto in the current situation.
Hey, Okita, wake up.
How is it that you were able to
just sleep through that explosion?
Explosion?
Did you fail to stop a
terrorist attack again?
Come on, what are you doing,
Hijikata?
Are you even trying
to stop them?
Do you want me
to put you back to sleep?
They can blow up all the Amanto
in the Capital for all I care.
I'll let those fishes swim
for a bit before I'll reel them in,
line them up,
and slit their throats.
It'll be a proud moment
for the Shinsengumi.
I'm looking forward
to this fight.
Another bombing targeting the Amanto
Embassies has just been reported in.
Our reporter Maya Sizitzy
is on the scene!
Maya Sizitzy, are you there?
Maya Sizitzy!
Yes, Maya Sizitzy on the scene.
This time, the despicable bomber has
attacked a Planet Canis' Embassy.
Luckily, nobody has been
injured or killed.
Oh, it seems we've just received
word that the alleged terrorists
were caught by
a security camera.
Wow, you can see them
very clearly!
You can really see us very clearly.
What will I do?
My sister is going to kill me.
I'm on TV?
I've got to call home!
Do you think this is all
some sort of conspiracy?
How did we even
end up in this mess?
We were very lucky that Katsura
intervened in that situation.
To think he'd actually
shelter us during all this, Gintoki.
He's a friend of yours, isn't he?
Exactly, what sort of person is he?
‐Uh... a terrorist bomber.
‐Huh? What?
Stop using that terrible word,
Gintoki.
We are not terrorists,
and you know it.
What we are,
are Freedom Fighters!
Oh, so we finally
received a lead?
Yes, Yamazaki is on their trail
right now.
It's only a matter of time before
we discover their base, Kondo sir.
I see.
Excellent work, Hijikata.
It's a little too soon
to thank me.
Save it for after
we've slaughtered them all!
Yes, of course.
The Shinsengumi only give credit after
displaying distinguished military service.
The only place we, the Shinsengumi,
belong in is battle.
Hm, well, you're the chief
and I'm just following orders.
I'm counting on you, Hijikata!
Sir.
There are two malicious
looking guys at the entrance.
No doubt about it,
this must be it.
Mom, is that man
a peeping tom?
Yu, you mustn't grow up
to be like that.
Shouldn't we report him
to the police?
We must force out the Amanto
that pollute this country
and rebuild it into the land
of samurai once again.
We're eradicating the Sky People
in order to protect this country.
Foreigner expulsion?
What is that?
Foreigner Expulsion is an ideology that
sprang up during the first Amanto attacks.
It refers to the desire
to drive out any aliens.
The Amanto had been heavily pressuring
us to open our borders to them
and feeling threatened.
The samurai rose up together
and fought to drive them out of Edo City.
But confronted by the Amanto's immense
power, the government surrendered.
They abandoned the samurai and signed a
disadvantageous treaty with the Amanto.
The Amanto who now had control
over the government
proceeded to take away
the samurai's swords,
rendering them completely powerless.
Afterwards...
rumor had it the exclusionists
had been purged
and that none still existed.
Exactly right.
It seems like we've been
taken advantage of.
‐Huh?
‐Isn't that right, Mr. Postman?
Hey, Gintoki's right!
I remember those bushy eyebrows.
Hold on. Why are you here,
Mr. Bushy brows?
This is all you're doing,
isn't it, Katsura?
All these recent attacks against the
Amanto that have everyone panicking.
There was something I had
to get my hands on,
even if it meant getting them
dirty once again.
Gintoki, won't you take up
your sword alongside me
just once more in order
to rebuild this corrupt country?
Lend me the strength that made you
feared as the White Knight
just one more time.
Gintoki, won't you take up your sword
alongside me just once more
in order to rebuild
this corrupt country?
Lend me the strength that made you
feared as the White Knight
just one more time.
So this is it then.
We will not surrender.
Let's finish this battle with honor and
take our own lives as true warriors.
‐Don't be an idiot.
‐What?
Stand up.
If you've got enough time to fantasize
about your glamorous death,
why not get up and live
your life glamorously?
Let's do this, Cobra.
My name is Katsura,
not Cobra!
His silver hair was soaked
in blood, and the way
he plowed
through the battlefield,
he was like a Demon Knight.
It was he who fought with the infernal
might of the demonic lords
against the Amanto.
A god of war, feared not only by his
enemies but by his own people.
Gintoki Sakata, lend us your strength once
again to fight against the Amanto.
Gintoki, you were involved in
the Foreigner Expulsion War too?
Yes, although he disappeared
as soon as the war ended.
And I never really knew what
was going on inside your head.
I like a good fight as much
as the next guy,
but what I really hate
are sore losers.
Our war against
the Amanto is over.
How long are you going to keep
clinging to it on and on and on?
What are you,
a desperate ex?
Don't be an idiot!
And you know that girls
are always clingy.
The reason you're so unpopular is
because your heart isn't big enough
to embrace the people
as they are.
Listen to me.
If my hair wasn't a mop top
I'd definitely be popular with girls!
I think.
There you go again blaming
everything on your mop top hair.
You are so pathetic.
Who are you calling pathetic?
People use their inferiority complexes...
‐...as springboards to greatness.
‐Enough of this!
What are you two talking about?
Our fight against the Amanto
is still far from over.
And I know that deep down,
even you're still fighting.
Gintoki...
You grieve for this country and resent
the government and the Amanto
for taking the lives of all the people
who fought alongside you.
Let's cleanse the land of the Amanto
and rebuild this decaying country.
It's the only way those of us
who managed to stay alive
can honor the memory
of our dead.
Our next target in this battle
is the Sky Terminal.
We shall destroy that accursed tower
that summons the Amanto here
and annihilate the pests
that live in Edo City.
However, the tower
is well guarded.
We won't be able
to attack easily.
We need your strength,
Gintoki.
Come on, man.
I've been telling you
that I am not...
It's too late, you've already
assisted us in the bombing,
so you can't refuse.
Unless you want to be
treated as a terrorist,
you have no choice
but to come with us.
There's no need to hesitate.
Your place has always been here
with us, with the samurai.
Gintoki.
You are all under arrest!
Come quietly, you terrorist scum!
‐It's the Shinsengumi!
‐This is no good!
Run away!
Kill every single one of them!
Who... who...
who are those people?
They're the Shinsengumi,
the Armed Police.
An elite anti‐terrorist squadron assembled
to wipe out rebel elements!
Those guys are really troublesome, boss.
What should we do now?
I'm not your freakin' boss!
And you're the troublesome
one, Katsura!
Cobra, if you need a boss,
I'm your woman!
"Whether you're doing something good
or doing something bad, be the boss."
That's my motto!
Will you shut up, Kagura!
Your motto sound like something out
of those stupid self coaching books!
Hey!
Why are you running away?
Stay a little while
and let's have some fun.
Tell me this, are you really
a government official?
I'm surprised you passed
the interview.
Your pupils are dilated.
You should talk,
mop haired creep!
Because you have the eyes
of a dead fish!
It's all right, because they sparkle
during my close‐ups.
There's no way they sparkle!
You're pretty good.
There aren't many people who
can keep up with my expert moves.
Oh, that's dangerous man.
What were you gonna do
if that actually hit me?
Are you stupid?
I'm trying to kill you,
so I meant to hit you!
Hijikata, you might want to watch out.
Are you still alive, Hijikata?
Are you stupid?
You could've killed me with that!
Darn, I'm sorry I missed.
What do you mean you're sorry?
Hey, look at me!
Hey!
So, where are they?
Vice‐chief, they're in here.
Hey, come on out!
Your resistance is meaningless!
Did you grow more hair?
You are on the fifteenth floor.
There's no escaping us
from up here!
What are you doing
with that thing?
This is a time bomb.
I was going to use it
to blow up the sky terminal,
but I now have no choice
but to use it here.
I'll give you guys a little present,
and you can escape
in the confusion.
You moron! What do you think
you're doing to Katsura?
Katsura, let's stop
this nonsense already.
No matter how much blood
you get on your hands,
our dead buddies
won't come back,
nor will the world change.
Stop getting your hands dirty.
You're the one that has dirt
on his hands, Gintoki.
You've had it ever since you switched
sides as soon as we lost the war.
A warrior should always remain devoted
to defending whatever he believes in.
What's the point in sticking to some
code that someone else has laid out?
Or are you looking forward to losing more
of your precious friends again by fighting?
Because I don't want
that anymore.
If it's my life on the line,
I'll adhere to my own code.
I'll live exactly
how I want to live,
and I'll protect
what I want to protect.
Gintoki, I was fiddling with this thing
and accidentally pushed the switch.
‐What a nightmare.
‐How cliché.
Hey, come on out!
We'll fire unless you comply.
Hijikata, our favorite evening TV show
reruns are gonna be starting soon.
Oh, man, I forgot
to set my VCR.
Let's get this over with.
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
What... what are you doing?
Stop them!
If you want to stop something,
then stop this bomb, please!
Don't you all have a
bomb squad or something?
Come on, I know you do!
Look out!
He's got a bomb!
Hold on!
Hey, wait!
Shinpachi,
you once said that you were good
with machines, didn't you?
What me?
When did I ever say that?
Kagura, you take it, this all happened
because of your stupid misuse!
My misuse?
Gintoki, your mop top looks like
it would make a good fuse!
Huh?
What are we doing?
I'm a bit confused!
Eeek! What about
a hypotenuse?
Eeek! What hippopotamus?
Eeek! Just get somebody
to help us!
Oh, this is such a a mess!
‐And she makes the pass!
‐Oh, come on!
How long is this gonna last?
Enough, we need cut out
this rhyming crap!
Crap, crap!
Okay, let's stahp!
Hey, who on earth says stahp?
That's stupid! That's almost as bad
as saying black shevel!
Huh?
There's only ten seconds left!
Gin, the window, the window!
We're not going to make it!
We're so dead!
‐Gintoki, grit your teeth!
‐Huh?
‐Gin... Gintoki!
‐Bye, Gin!
See you in the next life!
If you've got enough time to fantasize
about your glamorous death...
why not get up and live
your life glamorously?
Live glamorously, is that so?
I don't know what part of that
is glamorous at all.
But then again,
I guess having a friend that never changes
no matter how much time passes
isn't so bad after all.
Run, Okita!
‐Our favorite TV show!
We made it!
All right.
We interrupt this television rerun
broadcast to bring you a special report.
Maya Sizitzy is at the scene!
Maya!
Hi, Maya Sizitzy on the scene.
Shinpachi, you're the captain
of an idol singer fan club?
That’s so stereotypical
for a four‐eyed geek.
You really have no surprises,
do you?
So, this old man is also one
of your geeky friends?
The next episode...