Echigoya, you are quite an evil rascal!
Omiya must be cursing your name
from the afterlife.
Surely you just...
You were the one who set up his murder
in the first place, Nezumiya, Sir.
I mean, after all, that was you,
wasn't it?
Really?
Is that how it went?
There you go, playing the innocent again!
To our prosperous future!
What is it?
Is someone there?
Who...
Who are you?
Like the fading echo of a temple bell,
all things in life are temporary.
The end of another day
marks the end
of another villain
and his tyranny.
Good evening.
Sacchan, the assassin has come...
Black market merchant Nezumiya...
You preyed on the weak common folk
to line your own pockets.
An act deserving of ten thousand deaths.
I, assassin Sacchan,
shall bring you to justice!
Hey, hey, hey,
I'm over here!
Now, prepare to die, Nezumiya!
What the hell did you come here for?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
But I seem to have dropped
my glasses earlier.
Would you mind helping
me locate them?
Here.
Oh, thank you so much.
Ah, now then I can see where I am...
being blind was better.
Intruder!
My plan has failed!
Retreat!
‐What?!
‐She's getting away!
Hey!
After her!
I messed up.
I have no choice.
I'll return later.
Good morning!
Oh, Shinpachi, eh?
Good morning.
You're up so early today.
You feel that way because you guys
are nothing but a bunch of slackers.
Furthermore, you lot promised that
you would pay last month's rent by today.
Relay that message to my
good‐for‐nothing tenant, please.
Uh... right.
I'm sorry.
Ah, honestly it's about
time that he got married
and started to learn a thing
or two about responsibility.
Yes, you're right.
Gin getting married?
No way that could ever happen.
Good morning everyone.
Where is everyone, Sadaharu?
They really are a bunch of slackers,
aren't they?
Okay, time to get up.
It's morning.
Hey, Gin!
Maya Sizitzy's morning Weather Alert
is about to...
What're you doing, Shinpachi?
Stay away!
Did something happen to Gin,
or what?
Ah, you're stopping me?
Does he have a straight hair now
or something?
Stop, Kagura!
Nothing but a world of filth awaits you
behind that door!
What do you want?
You're way too noisy.
Well, who is this person?
Well, you're the one
who brought her here!
Yesterday, I...
Oh, it's no use.
I can't remember anything that
happened after I went drinking.
Don't even try to play dumb
about the ninja cosplay part.
Is she a ninja?
Or did you role‐play that?
Would you just cut it out?
I wouldn't do something like that!
And if I had to choose,
I'd pick a nurse costume!
Are you telling the truth?
Shinpachi...
Men should have to mess around
while they're still young,
because if they don't
when they're older, they'll be
deceived by younger women,
or become obsessed
with weird fantasies.
That's what my Mommy told me.
Your Mommy went through a lot,
huh, Kagura?
I... I don't really
remember last night.
So tell me, did I do
anything strange?
No, nothing at all.
I see, that's really good to hear.
I thought for sure I might have done
something truly awful while I was drunk.
There is nothing "awful"
between husband and wife.
I promise I'll go along with any
of your wild desires.
‐What?
‐Now, my dear...
Look how perfectly sticky
the natto has become.
Say "aah."
That's not my mouth.
I don't think this is what they mean
by a feast for the eyes.
What do you mean,
"husband and wife"?
You will take responsibility,
won't you?
After doing what you did.
What do you mean "what I did"?
I didn't even do anything,
you said so!
What're you talking about?
We were entwined together
just like this natto.
It hurts!
Like I said, that's not your mouth!
Hey Gin, you can't change what you did.
Just accept it.
Marriage is more about knowing
each other than love.
What are you guys talking about?
Your beloved Gin's about to be taken away
by some crazy natto girl!
This is ridiculous!
You're trying to trick me because
you know I don't remember anything!
Right?
To start with, we don't even
know each other's names,
so how can we talk about marriage?
You talk as if you don't remember
but your body cannot forget.
Hey, will you stop talking like that!
And also that's not even me!
If your eyesight is that bad,
put your glasses on!
They fell off.
Here!
So, that's what happened.
Well, my name is Sacchan.
Please make me a happy wife,
my husband.
I beg you.
Likewise.
Please be good to us, too.
I like having fish over meat
for dinner, okay.
Wait!
You're too quick to accept her in!
And once again, I'm over here!
I'll lay low here for a while.
This should give me enough time
to throw off my pursuers.
Looks like she's serious
about living here, huh?
What are you going to do then, Gin?
A serious woman like her is harder to get
rid of than the stinking smell of durians.
Oh, good grief.
In times like this, all I can do is calm
myself down with something sweet.
He simply listens to whatever I say.
Men are such stupid creatures right?
All I have to do now is play the part
of the cute, obedient, young wife.
Hey, has anyone seen the pudding
that I put in the fridge?
Hey, there was some pudding
in the fridge.
Oh come on!
And I tried to hide it, too!
I guess I have no choice,
you little piggy!
What day is it today?
What is it?
Garbage day?
The expiration date on some food?
Oh my, you forgot?
It's the anniversary of when you
and I started going out!
But we just met a little while ago.
Plus, didn't your personality
just change or something?
Ta‐da!
Natto pudding for our anniversary!
Am I being punished for something?
Today, I've made a very special
combination of our two favorite things.
And now, open up.
Enough of this already!
You, after pushing yourself
on me as my wife,
you're going to harass my precious
pudding too?
The hierarchy in this
household starts with me.
And after that, it's sweets.
You understand me?
Hey!
Sweets are number two over us?
I didn't play my hand right.
Bear it.
Bear it, Sacchan.
You don't have to be shy about it.
Now eat some!
Like hell I'm eating this!
It's okay.
This is actually pretty good.
Hey, Kagura, don't eat that!
You're not going to eat it, so don't try
to create some kind of collaboration
between pudding and natto, moron!
Are you trying to be a producer?
I'll whack your head with a megaphone!
‐I can't believe how disgusting that is.
‐This is humiliating.
‐I want my sweets, not natto.
‐I was once one of the elite spy agent,
‐Who would mix the two, anyway!
‐why should I be subjected to
‐It's disgusting! I'll have nightmares!
‐this verbal abuse.
Now, listen to me.
Hey, if you can't abide by these rules,
then get out, you worthless idiot!
But what is this?
What is this feeling?
Now!
I'm going out to buy
something sweet.
Wait up!
Seriously.
How the hell did you end up like that?
Help me!
I'm trapped in natto!
Why are you following me?
And what's up with that outfit?
Don't you like my old fashioned good
housewife look?
You wanna play the typical
husband and wife game?
Then I'll play a jobless husband
who forgets to take out the trash.
That's not a typical husband!
My pursuers won't recognize me
at all in this disguise.
Now all I have to do is play the part
of the cute, obedient, young wife.
What's the matter?
Nothing at all.
Hey!
You were looking at that
woman just now, weren't you?
I want you to tell me now,
is she your type?
Absolutely not, moron!
Are you trying to make me out
to be a weirdo, or something?
What in the world are you
doing out here?
And who might you be?
Who might I be?
I should ask you who you are?
Gintoki?
You just called him "Gintoki".
It's not a big deal.
By the way, Gintoki, you said that by
today, you'd pay me the last month's...
Just a minute!
Don't talk to him as
if you're part of his family.
I'm sorry, but Gin already belongs
to me and me alone!
What's with that girl?
All I did was ask you to pay me
the money that I'm owed!
So it's alimony you want?
You already had your fun with him!
You don't deserve any money!
What on earth is that girl talking about?
You're nothing but an old flame.
‐Go drown yourself in your old memories.
‐Hey!
You really think this
is my ex‐girlfriend?
Then you must think that
I'm a weirdo among weirdos!
Listen, I'm going to kick
both of your asses!
Don't tell me
she's your mother?
Is she your mother?
Hey, if my mother were like this,
I'd get a big tattoo on my forehead
that says SHOOT ME and
put me out of my misery!
Do you want me to shoot
you right here and now?
For everything rude I've done,
please forgive me...
dearest Mother.
What is with this weird girl?
She, well you know...
she hit her head when she tripped
chasing a stray cat
that ran off with a fish.
She's a little bit of an airhead and
likes to cosplay as a random wife.
To be treated this rudely...
and in front of everyone...
Yet why, again...
do I feel this stirring
in my heart?
I want more!
I want him to torment me more!
What' in the world is wrong
with this girl?
Man!
You didn't put your foot down, so now
she really does plan on staying here,
doesn't she!
Isn't it about time that you showed her
how much a man you really are?
But I really did try to show her that.
That man has already fallen
under my spell.
Men are such stupid creatures,
but what is this occasional throbbing
of my heart I'm feeling?
I'm back everyone!
Oh?
Gin, do you think that she's...?
No don't tell me?
What?
Me?
No there's...
there's just no way.
Hello, who is it?
This is Sacchan speaking.
Hello there, Miss Assassin.
Who are you?
Nice to meet you last night.
I'm so glad to hear your voice again.
I think that I've fallen in love with the
beautiful assassin who paid me a visit.
Nezumiya?
I procured your cell phone number
from your friends
the ones who were sneaking
around my estate last night.
I'd really like to see you again.
You will come, won't you?
The stars may change, but the importance
of one's friends...
well, that never changes.
Well, I'll be waiting.
Hey.
I've made up my mind.
I'm a man, after all.
Even though I can't remember
any of it,
I can't ignore you after
what I did to you.
If you'll settle for a guy like me,
then, please marry me.
What?
Are you serious, Gintoki?
I see.
Then come with me.
Are we going to the wedding hall?
I don't have a lot of money.
Just a minute.
This is my first time,
so please be gentle!
Oh, boy.
I'd better watch out for women, too.
Shinpachi!
What's wrong?
That there!
What the...?
How long has that
hole been here?
Maybe Sacchan is an angel
who came down from the heavens.
First off, I need you to meet my father.
An introduction, huh?
Well, I've come this far,
so I might as well keep going.
But tell me, why do we have
to get there like this?
Well, I was raised in a very strict house,
so I have a curfew.
Wow, you guys sure have a nice,
big house.
Wait, what?
Is your father a scary guy?
What kind of person is he?
He's a dishonest, buck‐toothed loan shark
with hair all over his body.
What's with that?
Are you at that age when you don't want
to wash your undies in the same load?
Every girl reaches that age eventually.
But listen, try to remember, I mean,
wasn't your father your first love after all?
Hey, once we're newlyweds, I'm going to
change these bad attitude habits of yours!
I'm asserting my dominance!
Be quiet.
Who is that?
Our butler, Mr. Smith.
He's on the lookout because
I'm late coming home after curfew.
Let me go ahead and tell you.
I'm the type of guy
who's pretty restrictive.
If we get married,
I'll bind you to my rules.
Bind me...?
What is this?
Why does the sound of his words
cause my chest to tighten so...?
I want to be bound!
Bind me!
Bind me tighter!
You said that you'll...
you'll bind me, you said?
Damn straight, girl.
Staying out all night with the girlfriends
and mixers will be strictly forbidden!
Mr. Smith saw us.
Wha... What's that?
It's the assassin!
The assassin has returned!
Mr. Smith!
That's going too far!
Mr. Smith was just doing his job,
for crying out loud!
Looks like a lot are coming.
Who are they this time?
It's Mr. Smith B, Smith C,
and Smith D!
Isn't that way too many Mr. Smiths?
It's begun already.
Father is testing the groom.
I need you to fight hard
for the both of us!
Say what?
Let's go now!
Hey!
Don't leave your husband behind!
My report, sir.
The assassin woman has broken
through our security
and appears to have entered
the mansion.
Then set the traps for them!
And when you find them,
make sure you kill them!
Yes, Sir!
They're just like poor moths flying
into a flame.
They won't make it here without getting
past all the traps I've set for them.
And on the small chance they make it
we have hostages to use as leverage.
And then we will finish them off.
Your father must be really strict
for all of this.
I'm practically unemployed.
Think that's all right?
It will be fine.
As long as he can trust you
as a person,
I'm sure that....
Cliché!
‐This is so cliché, but it's coming!
‐What?
What the hell is going on
at your house?
It's a son‐in‐law test!
He's trying to see if we can
make it together
even if the path is closed off.
If the path is closed off?
But that thing is coming right at us!
Step!
And jump!
Go!
It would seems he wants to test
whether or not
you can withstand the pressure
of taking over our house.
Yeah, but I think all I was doing
was running away.
I've been expecting you.
Who's this Smith?
My ex‐boyfriend.
He's working in tandem
with my father
for the purpose
of getting in our way.
Hang on.
You're still seeing your ex‐boyfriend?
I seriously can't allow that.
I said you I'd bind you to my rules.
I know that.
He's a bit of a stalker.
Hasta la vista, baby!
Hey, ex‐boyfriend.
Men who cling on forever
without letting go...
are totally unsophisticated!
We need to hurry from here.
Okay!
What's going on here?
Who the hell are those guys
chasing us?
‐All my ex‐boyfriends.
‐Wait, what's that?
You're serious?
All of them?
‐Are you trying to make ex‐ball team?
‐This isn't good.
We need to get to father quickly
and explain the situation to him.
All right, in that case,
you go on first!
And I'll catch up later on.
But then, what about you Gin?
In this kind of situation what kind of
husband would leave his wife behind?
Geez, this is hard to run in!
I really should've worn a suit today!
Well, I'll leave it to you, then!
Give my regards to your father!
Sure are persistent bastards.
Starting right now,
I won't allow you to take...
One more step.
On second thought, there's no way
I can do this!
Mr. Ratface!
There's trouble, Mr. Ratface!
The assassin woman has bested
each of our traps,
and she appears to be
heading in this direction.
Most of the assassins
we sent after her
have already been defeated.
That woman doesn't know
when to quit, does she!
Doesn't she care what happens
to the hostages we have?
Now that it's come to this deploy
every last man to stop her!
Get rid of them!
‐Yes, Sir!
Mr. Ratface!
Their objective is clearly
to rescue the hostages.
I think we should tie
their friends to a post
and spear them to death in
order to keep them away.
Now, then, I will...
Oh my goodness, my glasses.
Hey, where the heck are
you going?
Be quiet.
It is only me, Sacchan is here.
I'll be rescuing you now,
so just play along for a while.
There she is!
It's the assassin!
Kill her!
‐Sacchan!
‐Run away!
Who is there?!
The Deadly accurate assassin!
Gin the groom has arrived!
Gin the groom!
Gintoki!
Father!
Let me have your daughter's hand
in marriage!
Gin?
Hey, Gintoki!
Can you forgive me Gin?
You see the truth is...
Nothing happened between us.
Yet you...
You still let me use you like this.
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm not even injured right there.
Are you listening to me at all?
That's enough.
Don't touch me.
You reek of natto.
If you can't even treat wounds like this,
no man will ever marry you.
You'll never be someone's wife.
See you.
Oh, and one more thing...
The next time you want my help
don't do all this roundabout stuff,
and just come over to Odd Jobs.
I wonder if Sacchan
has fallen in love.
Hard to say, isn't it?
Men really are
such stupid creatures.
Good morning!
Hey, Gin!
You're going to miss Maya Sizitzy's
morning Weather Report...
Now then, Gin, please bind me up
very tightly.
That's not what I meant.
Oh! If it isn't Kintoki!
It's me, Tatsuma Sakamoto!
What? A spaceship is
about to crash?
That's certainly terrible!
Next time...