Gin Tama
You'd better fight fair, now!
I'd better fight fair?
LAKE TOYA HEH
Come on, gimme a break!
Ah!
He's getting away!
This guy's actually running
for his life!
After him!
Ever since the Sword Ban,
nobody does this sword
fighting stuff anymore!
Gintoki Sakata.
Trademark: naturally‐wavy hair.
He has a sweet tooth
and high blood‐sugar.
and he's kind of the main
character of this show.
‐Hey! Stop!
Sorry...
but i have a TV talkshow
to watch.
Gin!
Aaaah!...
‐Gin!
‐What?
Gin, help me!
Help me, please!
Shinpachi Shimura.
Who's too straight to get along
with Gintoki.
He hopes of finding the samurai
spirit here.
Hey Shinpachi...
the program just started,
why are you being chased?
I don't know!
Nobody actually wants
to be chased!
Anyway, we should run for it!
Stop right there!
We've got you now, there's...
Gintoki!
Look, now there's no one here!
Kagura.
Member of the "Yato Clan",
the most powerful warrior race
in the universe.
She's cute but has
a sharp tongue.
Excuse me...
What is this?
Sadaharu Sadaharu, Kagura's pet.
A mysterious,
giant space creature.
Geez, would you read the room!
I think these guys are
pissed off.
Ka‐Kagura, you'd better get out
of here with us!
Hurry up, because I'll have to
walk my neighbor's hamster...
which takes one whole day to
walk around the house!
Guys, wait!
Wait for me!
Wait!
A dead end...
It's the end of the line
for you!
What are you talking about?
Truth is we purposely
let you catch us.
Yeah, you should be thankful!
What do you mean, you losers?
You should talk, you're the ones
running all over town!
Who hired you?
We know that you're the spies
who came to steal our secret!
Before we cut you down,
I'll ask you again...
Who are you and
what do you want?
You ask who we are?
All right then,
since you asked us...
We do anything from housework
to finding missing persons!
If you're ever in trouble,
just come to us!
We'll take any case and any kind
of job as long as we get paid!
‐Because we're the ones
‐known as: Odd Jobs Gin!
Odd Jobs Gin!?
You mean to say, you'll do
anything for money?
Now I see.
That's why you snuck into our
factory facility and...
There it is!
That must be it!
That's the cat
we're looking for...
Kuromi of Yamatoya!
Come on now, Kitty.
Have some pickled seaweed...
Nooo!
Hey, you damned cat!
Just Wait!
They were just looking
for a cat?
Gin Tama.
THE PLOT THUS FAR
The land of the samurai...
There was a time,
a long time ago..
when our country was called
by that name...
But with the arrival
of the "Amanto"
or sky people from outer space
and their rise to power,
they enacted sword ban
to samurais twenty years ago...
and the samurai class
fell into decline...
In such hard times,
there was one man left with
the spirit of the samurai...
His name is Gintoki Sakata.
Long story short, Kagura
and I, Shinpachi Shimura,
work at Odd Jobs Gin,
which is coincidentally run
by this very same guy.
Which reminds me,
we've been working for him
for about a year now,
but I really don't think that
he has paid us at all yet.
Guys!
Have you got balls?!
Mr. Kariya has just arrived,
sirs!
I greet you!
‐I greet you!
I can't hear you!
Once again!
‐I greet you!
That's still not enough!
Would you care to try it again?
No, sir, there's not really
enough time for that.
I see...
KARIYA, SHISHIMURA
SHIMOMOTO, PUU
Today's guest characters:
Kariya and Shishimura...
Shimomoto and Puu.
Don't try to remember
their faces,
they're definitely not regulars.
Oh, hello there, Mr. Kariya.
And thank you for coming
all this way to see us.
Dispense with the intros...
So, how are things going with
that matter we talked about?
Fine.
Everything is going very well,
Mr Kariya.
First, please take a look
at this Powerpoint.
The goal of the project.
"Ladies and gentlemen, boys and
girls, children of all ages,
all these papers aren't
telling me a thing!
Is this a presentation for the
spring anime season or what?!
Please forgive me, Mr. Kariya.
SHINSENGUMI, TOSHIRO HIJIKATA,
SOGO OKITA
The Shinsengumi.
A secret police force working
for the samurai government.
Hijikata.
Vice‐chief of Shinsengumi,
the brains...
Okita.
One of the Shinsengumi's best
swordsmen.
Yamazaki, situation report?
They're in a private meeting
in a second floor back room.
There are four of them:
one is an amanto alien,
two businessmen,
and then there's one
tough‐looking ronin...
That's just perfect...
Let's go!
Speaking of the device
we obtained
with Mr. Kariya's support...
We just finished assembling
the amanto device
at our secret factory.
All we need to do now is get it
into position.
If this project succeeds,
then all of the capital
will fall under my control.
Yes, that is exactly right,
Mr. Kariya.
This is a police raid!
It's the Shinsengumi!
‐Everyone stay still!
‐Okita! Come on!
Okay!
Freeze, Shinsengumi!
Good‐bye, Vice‐chief.
Hope you enjoy sucking on
mayonnaise in the next world.
Hey, Okita, can't you even
recognize who your enemies are?
I could kill you at any time
before killing our enemies!
No way, it was a joke.
A joke, you know?
Come on, I'm always doing that.
Do you mean to say that you're
always trying to kill me?!
Anyway, the thing is,
Hijikata.
It seems that all of our efforts
end in failure.
Well...
Not really all of our efforts.
Odd Jobs Gin.
You know, I'm really too old
to be reading comic books
like this, but oh well.
I just can't quit buying
them every week!
That's right, Gintoki.
Reading comics like that
won't fill your stomach at all,
and your blood‐sugar level
will not get lower.
I know, I know, I know, but
I'm seriously addicted to it.
I keep thinking that I won't buy
the next one,
‐but then here i am...
‐Gin, we've got a problem here.
I know.
It's a problem.
Someone my age shouldn't be
reading these.
Yeah, this onigiri's got a
problem too, it's rotten!
That's not what
I'm talking about!
Look at this!
Take a look!
A bank account statement?
You can't fool me.
You know you can't eat
a bank account statement.
We'll have nothing to eat,
get anemia and end up turning
like those blue folks in avatar
because we have no money left
and I'm feeling blue already!
Calm down, Shinpachi.
You're the little punk who
didn't get the comics,
aren't you?
The thing is, having no money
is just a chronic condition..
like a nasal infection,
know what I mean?
So get used to it!
Being poor's nothing new
and it's our destiny.
You've given up already?!
Your life is not on comic,
and being poor is not
a chronic condition.
Even bread crust would look
like a feast tomorrow for us!
What the...
Nasal infection?
It's an earthquake, moron!
The earthquake just stopped.
We're having a lot of
earthquakes lately, so it seems.
Yeah.
Like when a young boy's
heart trembles
when he has to confront
five girls
who asked him out
at the same time.
Oh, come on!
That would never happen!
Yeah but, it does happen
in comic books.
A customer?
It can't be.
It's probably a door
to door salesman.
Shinpachi, if he's from
an insurance company,
tell him everybody's
got cancer.
And if he asks for donation,
tell him the only papers
we've got are comics.
Yes!
I'm coming!
Sorry we've all got cancer...
‐You can't catch me.
‐No, I'm over here.
‐Come hurry.
‐Pass it to me.
‐Come on.
‐Oh, no.
I came here because I heard that
you guys will take any job,
no matter what.
No...
Shinpachi, what are you doing?
We gotta go pick up the hamster
in a few minutes!
I came because I heard
that this is Odd Jobs Gin.
...frigging...
What's wrong?
Was it a big mouth politician
promising employment
for 100 billion people?
In that case, you could resort
to violence and just rob the...
This is Odd Jobs Gin, right?
No way!
‐No...
‐...frigging...
...way!
Hello?
Hey, guys.
You...
no, you can't be...
Are you a client?!
Ken Kato.
Ronin.
Or a jobless samurai.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Ken Kato,
it's nice to meet you.
I've been a ronin
for a few days now.
Hey, Kagura, what do you
think is going on lately?
We've had clients two days
in row.
Probably cause it's the first
episode, typical storyline.
Here's some tea for you...
It's hot!
You're really in for it
if this is a joke!
What's that?
Now you're shocked
and getting uppity?
So what can we do for you?
Well...
The thing is...
I want to get something back
that I lost.
It is something that is very,
very important to me.
Well then, what did you lose,
what's this important thing?
Well the truth is...
I need about thirty million yen
to get it back.
Listen, Baldy!
I told you, you were in for it
if this was a joke, remember?!
What's an easy way
to earn money?
Every time I grab it, it slips
right through my fingers...
That's it!
Every time you move your hand
on the gambling machine,
we go further into the red!
But I heard that you would take
any kinds of jobs
for troubled people.
We can't even afford to pay
our rent right now!
There's no way we can take care
of someone's business!
So leave and don't come
here again!
Calm down, both of you,
calm down!..
So, now tell me, what would you
do with the money if you had it?
I've been a deadwood
my whole life,
and finally got laid off
last month..
And three weeks ago, I was
swindled out a lot of money
and I ended up
losing my house.
Then two weeks ago, my wife
and daughter left me,
and they didn't even
leave me a note.
And one week ago...
Why did you stop talking?!
Spit it out!
This really sounds like
an anime story!
Do things like this befall you
every week?!!
‐Just Finish the story!
‐Tell us what happened
to you last week right now!
Would you like...
to hear the rest of the story?
Why will he tell us the rest
of the story only
after we complete the job?
Whatever, the truth is...
I'm sure we won't be able
to complete this job.
Hey...
So now, where are we going?
Well, I'll tell you.
The point is that we get the
money as quickly as possible,
right?
Welcome.
Oh, it's just you three guys.
Otose.
Proprietor of Hostess Bar Otose
and also Gintoki's landlord.
Oh, now I see.
All you guys are such idiots.
If you could make money
that quickly,
then there would be no thieves
in the world!
Didn't you ever think
about that?
You're so dumb!
So says an ex‐thief like you!
Yeah, that's right.
Catherine...
works for Hostess Bar Otose.
She came to Earth as
a migrant worker.
Well, there might be one way
to get money...
So, what'll it be?
Donate your kidney?
Well...
I don't...
You've got two of those, so
why don't you sell one of them?
You'd sell one kidney
if you were a real man!
This isn't gonna work.
So disappointing.
You're just a big talker.
It's not going to happen
if you're not prepared to take
risks, you know that, right?
Forget it, that'll be
a crime anyway.
Hello, everyone.
What a surprise!
Ayame Sarutobi Ayame Sarutobi.
Nickname: Sachan.
An elite ninja and a former a
member of the government spy
organization directly
reporting to the Shogun.
What?
You need a way to get a lot
of money very quickly?
Hey, Sachan, why don't you put
your glasses back on?
You gotta face this way, I'm the
one talking to you right now.
And I don't care if your
character looks like mine.
What are you talking about?
I really couldn't care less
about you
or what you think about me.
There's only one I care about.
All I care about is...
you, Gin.
Didn't you hear me?
I told you it would help to put
on your back glasses!
So...
I take it that the money you
were talking about isn't
to purchase of our little
love nest, then?
What love nest are you
talking about, Sachan?
I can't even bear to think
about sitting next to you
at the diner.
Always so cold to me,
and I'm used to it.
But I don't give up so easily.
And why the natto?
The smell's spreading.
Put it away, everyone watching
the show already knows
you're extraordinary.
Oh, yeah?
Do you think that pushing me
away is going to make me happy?
‐Stop blabbering, you idiot,
‐Here we go! That's it!
‐Do something with the natto,
‐Just like that! More!
‐you natto woman!
‐More!
That's it!
Just like that!
Just keep blasting away at me!
You're really turning me on!
Just a little more!
You're turning me on!
What's this?
It stinks!
What's that smell?
Smells like natto and
a little touch of masochism.
‐Kato.
Well, well, Kato.
How's it going?
Well...
I bet that was hard on you?!
You put your seal on
a bad contract,
but you should be more careful
as to what you agree to.
That's just too bad, I mean, we
know you're hard up for money.
How did you know that?
Anyway, what have you
been doing lately?
Well, I'm trying to work hard
and buy my house back...
Buy your house back, Kato?
That'll never happen, man.
‐No it won't because...
‐Hey...
Well that's right...
Well, let us know, Kato,
when you find a house.
We'll at least send a New Year's
card when you do.
‐Call your folks!
‐Pack your bags!
Don't forget to write!
Hey, so you...
Yes?
Maybe you should rethink
your request.
Let's kill all of them, you know
I'm a professional killer.
Yes, let's kill them!
Why don't we roll them up
and throw them into
the sewer right now?!
Wait.
I'm changing my request.
But it's not going to be
an assassination.
I want...
The thing that
I really want is...
I just want..
to be stronger!
‐Okay, then we got it!
Hey, everyone.
Jack up his hit points
another hundred or so,
and avoid his life
ending up as game over.
So, now where
are you going, Gin?
I have something
that I need to take care of.
That's all I got.
Oh, so I see that
this is a blueprint...
Isao Kondo Isao Kondo.
Commander of the Shinsengumi.
Strikes fear in the hearts
of others.
By the way, Hijikata...
I have no idea what
this blueprint says...
I've been trying to explain
to you that this is a blueprint
for an amanto device, Kondo!
Oh, I see.
Some sort of device.
Yes, and someone seems to be
planning to use that device
to commit some heinous deed
here in the capital.
Oh, Hijikata.
What does "heinous deed" mean?
You haven't heard
a single word I said!
Drifting star embassy.
An embassy?
Gintoki.
"Cobra?"
My name is Katsura.
Not Cobra.
Kotaro Katsura.
Member of the exclusionist
rebels.
An activist trying to rid
the capital of amanto aliens.
Elizabeth.
What the hell is this?
Gintoki, what are you doing
here in front of the Embassy?
Well, you know...
I was just jogging, taking a
walk, something like that...
I'm not really sure, you know,
but it brought me here...
That's not a good idea.
What do you mean?
Only I heard some rumors about
something dangerous around here.
Some rumors?
Yes, Gintoki.
I've heard rumors about an
amanto who's hatching a plot
to destroy all of the capital.
But why would an amanto want
to destroy the whole capital?
I don't know...
But if it's true, we must punish
them for this evil plot...
Gintoki, I don't know
what you are going to do,
but you'd better
be very careful.
The Embassy, as you know,
is considered foreign soil.
The Embassy is
on foreign soil...
Yes, I should really be careful,
then.
Later, Cobra.
My name is Katsura, not Cobra.
You know that hat is
so out of style.
Okay!
Why don't you give it a try now?
But he can't do that!
What are you talking about?
It's incredibly easy!
Clear your mind, and you can
look like "John Cena."
Yeah, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Okay, Kato, you can start
whenever you are ready.
Okay...
Why are your eyes so bloodshot,
what happened?
Were you up all night
playing video games?
No, the game is just about
to begin.
Oh, give it a rest.
Something bad could happen
if you swing that toy
around like that.
What?
Did he actually notice
my sword cane?
Whatever, let's get on
with this,
but can you at least tell me
why you're trying to kill me?
Don't play dumb!
We already know that you've been
nosing around this place.
No, you're wrong about that.
That was Cobra.
It wasn't me.
No more discussions!
Again?
You're leaving yourself
wide open!
You think you'll become
stronger like that?!
You are such an idiot!
Oh, you're so aggressive!
I'm sorry, Kato.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
Get up!
Stand up, Kato!
Listen!
Keep your elbows close to your
body, aim to the inside corner,
and strike, strike, and strike!
Wait, Kagura!
That's a jab, not a strike.
and that won't work
for tomorrow.
It doesn't have anything
to do with swordsmanship!
Impossible.
It's temporary.
It's nothing.
It looks like
it's my turn now....
Let me make you a real man!
Tighter!
Like this then?
More!...
Much more!
Oh yes!
That's it.
Yes, so good!
How about this?!
You've got talent.
What is this training for?
What kind of talent
does it have?
As a dominatrix...
But he's a man!
Anyway, that's not the point,
Sachan!
Oh, you're very patient!
As a reward,
you can have it tighter
‐if you'd like!
‐Stop it! Just untie me now!
Hello!
Thank you so much
for everything,
but that's really enough.
I don't think that I'll ever get
any stronger, Im sorry.
It's time that I give up...
But...
So now, I'll just leave.
Kato...
Those were my very
best clothes.
My mom is going to be
really mad, you bastard!
You should worry more
about your own life
than about your clothing!
Who is Shishimura,
Gintoki's mysterious attacker?
And what heinous deed is
Kariya the sky person planning?
Did Kato really give up?
Hey people at HULU!
If you'd like to know
what happens next,
you gotta buy this show!
TO BE CONTINUED