[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Thanks to the efforts
of Lute and his friends,
peace has been restored
to Geo-Fulkright.
However, before they could
bask in their victory,
Pansy had some alarming
news to share with Navirou.
[PANSY] You see, Koapni
Village is in a lot of trouble.
I need mew to come back
with me to help save it!
What?
[PANSY]
A monster attacked.
One that's all dark
and hazy and sick.
[BOTH gasp]
Sounds like--
The Black Blight!
Navirou. We're going.
Right!
I'm coming, too.
There's a liner that goes
to the island from here.
All right, next stop,
Naubaka Island!
[DMIR]
Sorry,
but I'm afraid the liner
isn't running anymore.
[gasps] Why not?
Ships that are bound
for Naubaka Island
have been disappearing lately.
Far too many of them.
And nobody really knows why.
It could just be the rough seas,
but there's always
the possibility
it's some kind of monster.
Oh, no!
After enough ships vanished,
they stopped sending
out the liners, too.
All of the sailors are spooked.
They won't launch to
the north at all anymore.
I guess that means Ratha
will have to fly us there.
[NAVIROU yelps]
[NAVIROU] That idea
makes Navirou nervous!
[AVINIA]
Frostfang can fly, too.
I wouldn't if I were you.
Even the airships that
have headed that way
were sensing danger
and turning back around.
After all, if anything
were to happen,
there'd be no place
to land out there.
But there has to be some way
for us to get to the island.
Why, even as we speak,
that sick monster could
be wreaking havoc
on Koapni Village.
[DMIR]
Hm...
You know what?
There is one man
who might be willing
to take you guys out there.
Huh? Who's that?
A man who calls himself
the Bandit Captain.
[NAVIROU] "Bandit"? Navirou
thinks you mean "pirate."
No, for some reason he
chooses to go by "bandit."
Strange fella, that guy.
[CAPTAIN]
This is gonna be so good!
Yummy!
Uh, hey, Mr. Bandit Captain?
[CAPTAIN]
Hm? What do you want?
[BOTH gasp]
He really is a bandit!
I'm frightened!
Sorry, but we're trying
to get to Naubaka Island,
but the usual liners
aren't running,
and we heard that you might
be willing to take us there.
[CAPTAIN]
Why?
"Why"?
Well, um, because, uh,
there's a monster that's
running amok on the island
and we're going to slay it.
[CAPTAIN]
Why?
Uh, well--
Bet he's just looking
for an excuse to say no.
The villagers are
in big trouble.
We think the monster
might be Blighted.
[CAPTAIN] Isn't it forbidden for
Riders to leave their villages?
[LUTE]
Huh?
We left to stop the changes
happening around the world.
[CAPTAIN] I see. Such are
the times we live in.
Yeah, so, um--
[CAPTAIN]
All right.
[NAVIROU]
Uh?
Let's do it!
What? You'll take us there?
[CAPTAIN]
I'll bring my ship to the port!
Get ready and wait for me there!
That was awesome.
Could he actually be a good guy?
Let's not jump to
conclusions yet.
Oh, wow.
Guess that "bandit" title
isn't just for show.
Well, it sure doesn't look like
a good guy's ship to Navirou!
In fact, it seems like the kinda
boat Manelger would have.
Oh, no, that's terrifying!
This beauty is proof that
I'm an old hand at this!
I christened her the S.S. TF !
The S.S. TF ?
Don't worry, guys,
the Bandit Captain
here's made it through
more than his fair share
of monster attacks.
You'll be in good
hands with him.
Load up your cargo!
I wanna set sail before
the wind changes!
Well, the only cargo
we've got is our Monsties.
[DEBLI]
Did someone say cargo?
Well, I've got plenty and looks
like I made it just in time!
Huh? Why are you tagging alo--?
Don't you have any sympathy
for those poor,
helpless Felynes?
How can you be so heartless?
Wait. What are you
so mad at me for?
Uh. Those Felynes are
all alone out there!
With no ships traveling
to Naubaka Island,
they've gotta be running
dangerously low
on supplies by now!
Which is why I'm going
there to lend a helping hand!
I've got all kinds of great
merchandise to give 'em!
Whoa, for free?
At a discount.
So it's business!
[CAPTAIN] All right, time to
hoist those sails, Mew Crew!
[CREW]
Meow! Meow! Meow!
Set course for Naubaka
Island! Steady as she goes!
[DMIR]
Come back again sometime!
Bye for now, you guys!
Come meet up with us
once the ocean liner's up
and running again, okay?
Roger that, meow! See ya soon!
Y'know, this is my
first time on a ship.
Yeah, mine, too!
Oh, right, you both grew
up in the mountains.
This ain't my first boat.
There's always cool
stuff below deck.
Let's go explore!
[LUTE]
Ooh, sounds good!
[FIRST MATE]
But first--
If mew have time
to wander around,
then mew have time
to do some fishing.
[LUTE]
Hm? Fishing?
Yeah, you're gonna need some
fish to feed your Monsties.
And the only thing that
we've got on board is hay.
Well, then, let's fish!
Awesome! Navirou will
show you how it's done!
Now listen, when you feel
your fishing pole go bing,
that's when you're gonna go
hup, and yank it back in.
Bing, and then you hup.
Bing, and then hup.
Goes bing, and you hup.
Bing, bing, then hup.
Bing, bing, then hup, hup.
Bing, then hup. Bing,
bing, then hup, hup.
Bing, bing, then hup!
All together!
Bing, bing, then hup, hup...
Knock it off!
And anyway, shouldn't
you be fishing, too?
Those rods are too big
for Navirou's little paws.
[LUTE gasps]
I got a bite!
Then hup!
[LUTE]
Hup!
So tiny.
That's more of an
hors d'oeuvre for us
than a meal fit for a Monstie.
[DEBLI grunts]
Didja get a bing?
C'mon! C'mon! Why, you little--
[NAVIROU]
A Glutton Tuna!
[LUTE]
It's huge!
[DEBLI laughs]
How 'bout that? Maybe you
should leave the fishing to me!
All right then, I think I will.
I'll check on Frostfang
while you fish.
Okay.
[LUTE]
And hup! Ha!
So tiny.
Here you go, Frostfang.
Dinnertime.
Hey, look what I gotcha,
Ratha! Dig in!
Aw, and after I went
through all the trouble
to catch 'em for you, too!
Come on, eat up!
Aw, please, Ratha!
Check out that
incredible sunset!
It's like a great big donut
slathered with strawberry jam!
[LUTE]
Huh?
Isn't it beautiful?
Oh! Yeah!
This reminds me of all
those magical times
I spent watching the sunset
with mew back on Paupau Beach.
Huh? Oh, yeah, you don't say.
Do mew like Koapni
Village, Navirou?
Uh, yeah, sure, it's all right.
Oh, I'm so glad!
And, well, um, what
about me? I mean--
Want one?
Oh, you're so kind and
generous and just wonderful!
[NAVIROU]
Hmm...
Wee, this is awesome!
So much fun!
[laughs]
How d'ya like this?
[AVINIA]
Stop that this instant!
We didn't come here
just to goof around!
Right! Apologies!
[LUTE] Looks like you're
doin' okay. Well, g'night!
[CAPTAIN]
What is it?
Why do you call yourself
a "bandit captain"
and not a "pirate captain"?
Out here on the high seas,
pirates are ubiquitous.
That's why I'm a bandit instead.
And how did you
know about Riders?
Everywhere I go, I hear a
lotta chatter about Riders.
You people have been pretty
busy lately, haven't you?
[LUTE] Yeah, but you knew
our rules and everythi--
You should get some sleep.
It's almost time
for my shift change.
Okay.
Curious about the
Bandit Captain, eh?
He was born and raised
in the mountains.
Oh, wow, really?
As a young man,
his passion for the sea
lured him away from home
and he became a sailor.
Always says that he'll go back
once he's become the
world's best sailor,
but guess he ain't done it yet.
The mountains thing
explains the bandit name.
But how's he supposed to know
when he's become the
world's best sailor?
Captain won't be happy till
he mounts an Elder Dragon horn
as a figurehead on the bow.
[LUTE] Huh? And that'll
prove he's the world's best?
[CAPTAIN]
Hey, First Mate!
Time for shift change!
Coming, Captain!
[gasps]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
[LUTE]
Yahoo!
Let's go! Woo-hoo!
[LUTE laughing]
That's enough!
Ratha, that's enough!
[LUTE screaming]
I wanna get off! Stop, Ratha!
[yelps]
Ow, that really hurt.
Phew, it was just a dream.
[creaking]
What's happening?
[LUTE]
Captain!
This a storm? Captain!
Yeah, what?
What's going on right now?
A storm's comin'!
[CAPTAIN]
No.
It's not?
[CAPTAIN]
It might seem like a storm,
but I've never seen
a storm do this.
Well then, what is it?
[CAPTAIN]
We don't know yet.
Ships that are bound
for Naubaka Island
have been disappearing lately.
Far too many of them.
And nobody really knows why.
It could just be rough seas,
but there's always the
possibly it's a monster.
Could a monster be
causing all of this?
That seems unlikely.
There shouldn't be any
monsters around these parts.
But if there were--
[AVINIA]
Lute!
What's up? Is something wrong?
All right, crew, I want
everybody on lookout duty!
We're gonna make it to Naubaka
Island no matter what!
[CREW]
Aye aye, Captain!
[DEBLI]
Hm...
It feels so eerie.
I'm nervous.
Navirou doesn't see
anything out there.
Huh? What's wrong
with you, Lute?
[LUTE]
Uh, Captain? Are we there yet?
I thought I just
told you, not yet.
[LUTE]
It's just...
I'm feeling a little bit queasy.
[CAPTAIN] It's the weather.
Nothing I can do for you.
Hey, Lute, what's
the matter with you?
Your friend's seasick.
[NAVIROU]
Uh?!
No way! Seasick?
You mean the guy who can
fly around on his Monstie
doing upside-down hanging twists
without so much as blinking?
Yeah, well, it happens.
Please, Captain. There must
be a way to stop this.
[CAPTAIN] Not much you can
do on seas rough as these.
Please, you have
to do something!
Yeah, you're right.
There's no avoiding it.
I've got a hunch that
something's headed our way.
Oh, yeah. Navirou's
picking up on it, too.
And it's a real handful!
[NAVIROU]
Over there!
Hard to starboard, First Mate!
Aye, aye, Cap'n!
Now, strike the sail, men!
[CREW]
Aye, Captain!
Oh, no!
It's a Seregios!
It looks like that
Seregios is Blighted!
That would explain why it keeps
attacking us haphazardly.
And it must be
what's been causing
all those ships to
disappear around here.
[DEBLI] Hold on! The Seregios
is already super powerful!
If one winds up
Blighted like this,
how much more
powerful will it be?
According to this Monsterpedia
Navirou picked up
back in Gildegaran,
Seregios can launch razor-sharp
scales through the air.
Navirou says, "An eye for an
eye, and wings for wings"!
Now, before it's too late, Lute,
Ride On with Rathalos
and do your thing!
[groaning]
[NAVIROU yelps]
[NAVIROU]
Is it really that bad, Lute?
So wait, you mean Lute's
out of commission?
[CAPTAIN]
Hey! What're you doing?
[DEBLI]
Avinia!
[PANSY]
Avinia?
All right then,
Ride On! Barioth!
Let's go!
Avinia! Watch out
for flying scales!
Hang in there, Frostfang!
Okay, Lute! You've
gotta help Avinia!
Get up! Get on your
feet, Lute, right now!
C'mon, buddy,
stand up! Right now!
Uh!
Here goes. Let's Ride On!
[NAVIROU] Ah! Is it
really that bad, Lute?
[DEBLI]
Then I'll do it!
Okay, Ride On!
Rathalos!
Huh?
Bad news, you guys!
It's Rathalos!
He's seasick, too!
That's my Ratha.
He's always totally in
sync with me. Atta boy.
Are you serious? Who needs
that level of Kinship?
[roars]
Now dive!
[AVINIA]
Here goes, Frostfang!
Icicle Fang, now!
[CAPTAIN]
Where'd they go?
Did they get it?
[CAPTAIN]
What the--?
Here it comes!
Ground Cyclone!
Yeah!
Wow, that girl,
she's somethin' else!
Good news, Lute! We did it!
[LUTE groaning]
[NAVIROU] Huh? Is it
really that bad, Lute?
It's Naubaka Island! Land ho!
[DEBLI]
Whoa!
Oh, wow, so that's
Naubaka Island?
We're finally back, Navirou.
Yeah.
At last.
I can't wait to set foot
on solid ground again.
[PANSY] This is heaven for
fans of Felyne pawpads.
Uh, I mean,
it's Felyne paradise.
Naubaka Island.
We all live together in a
place called Koapni Village.
Bet I can do some real
wheelin' and dealin'!
It looks so calm and peaceful.
What kind of dangerous monster
could be lurking here?
Don't know.
But I bet we're gonna find out.
[CAPTAIN]
So long, you guys!
[LUTE] Thanks, Bandit Captain!
You leaving already?
We are!
Gotta get back to Geo-Fulkright.
Tell folks there
everything's all clear now.
They hear that, the liner
will be running in no time.
Sounds good!
All right, time to hoist
those sails, Mew Crew!
[CREW] Aye aye, Captain!
Aye aye, Captain!
[CAPTAIN] Now S.S. TF ,
set a course for Geo-Fulkright!
Let's catch as much
wind as we can.
In top form!
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Uh?
"In top form"?
But how?
[CAPTAIN laughing]
Well, say hi to Dan for me!
What the heck?
[SILVA laughing]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Seregios!
It's one sharp customer!
This wyvern bristles
with tons of spiky scales
it can spray out.
Plus, it's fast and nimble,
so it'd make one heck
of a great Monstie!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, Lute here!
We're in for a
real Felyne welcome
once we reach Koapni Village,
but there's something
weird about Navirou.
Yikes! A Yian Garuga!
Next time: "The Wolf
Raven Strikes Back"!
Ride On!