[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
After Lute met up with
Lilia in Gildegaran,
who should appear out of the
shadows but Mille and Hyoro,
Lute's estranged friends
from back home.
They had left Cheval behind
as he charged down
a dangerous path,
and were now seeking the path
that they were meant to follow.
Reunited at last,
Lute and his friends set out
for the Forest of Confusion to
find the Kinship Ore within.
There they bumped
into Genie and Stone,
two senior Hakum Riders hot on
the trail of a Blighted monster.
I never agreed with
the choice you made.
I only allowed it because
it's more important
for you to choose your own path.
But a man who can't see his own
choices through is a disgrace.
And is no Rider,
or brother, to me.
Genie.
Genie shunned Hyoro for not
staying true to his convictions,
but upon seeing
his little brother
perform admirably in battle
against the Blighted monster,
Genie had a change of heart.
[GENIE]
I was right, Hyoro.
You're not the person
I thought you were.
You're a true Rider.
Genie!
Brothers are great. I want one.
[LILIA] But in a way,
you do have a brother.
His name is Cheval.
You always say you're family.
[NARRATOR]
Lute sees himself and Cheval
reflected in the reconciled
brothers' relationship.
And so the optimistic young
Rider continues ever onward,
to restore the Kinship he
shared with his dear friend,
and to save the world
from the Black Blight.
Next stop, the
Forest of Confusion
to find that Kinship Ore.
[LUTE]
The path splits here.
Leave it to Navirou's
navigation skills!
Hmm...
This way!
So that way then, huh?
[NAVIROU yelps]
I think maybe we oughta split
up, just to be on the safe side.
All right then, we'll
go in that direction.
And if anyone finds
the Kinship Ore,
use your Field Horn to let
everybody else know.
Mille, hold on.
[MILLE]
Hm? What's up?
Don't forget what I said
earlier, about the lightning.
It'll help if you guys
get lost out there.
Yeah, I remember.
You guys be careful
and try to stay safe.
Yep! Will do!
Hey, what was that
about the lightning?
Uh, dunno. It beats me.
[LILIA] Guys, we just talked
about this at breakfast.
Weren't you listening? Honestly.
Before we left Gildegaran,
I was going through
a bunch of old texts,
and happened to find some
ancient lore about these woods.
"At the ends of the
Forest of Confusion,
beyond the lightning-wielding
phantom beast,
sleeps the Crystal of Rapport."
Lilia, be sure to tell Lute,
"If at any point you get
lost in the woods,
just keep an eye
on the lightning."
Sure, I'll tell him. But why?
[SIMONE]
You see, many years ago,
a lightning-wielding
phantom beast
was responsible
for saving my life.
Ever since, I've hoped
to thank my savior.
Show my gratitude.
You kids go on ahead.
And I'll be right behind you.
Yes, ma'am!
[LUTE]
"Keep an eye on the lightning"
sounds all well and good, but...
Gonna be hard to find
lightning to keep an eye on
on such a sunny day.
C'mon. We'll just see what
happens if we get lost.
Maybe it'll make sense then!
Yeah, good point!
Now, follow me, guys!
[PAPPAN] Oh, boy,
this forest sure is creepy.
You know, they say
that once somebody
goes into the Forest
of Confusion,
they can never find their
way back out again.
That's because there
are no maps of it,
and compasses don't work here.
If we get separated and you're
lost out there all by yourself.
[PAPPAN whimpers]
Just keep an eye out for
lightning and you'll be fine.
Really, that's it?
Is that how you were able to
find that phantom beast before?
By following the lightning?
Yes.
It was back in the days right
after I'd joined the Scriveners.
I had received reports of
an unidentified monster
that had been spotted
in the forest.
My squad and I
quickly mobilized,
but then a rainstorm
suddenly began.
I got separated from my men
and soon lost my way.
It was then that a bright light
flashed across the sky,
as though guiding me
through my exhaustion.
Using that lightning
as a signpost,
I ventured forth
into the darkness.
This place, what is it?
[SIMONE]
Looking back, I now believe
that was the lightning-wielding
phantom beast.
[SIMONE]
When I came to,
I was staring up at
an unfamiliar ceiling.
Apparently I'd been rescued
at the forest entrance,
on the verge of collapse.
After that, my squad and
I searched everywhere,
but we were never
able to find them.
Not that mysterious
white clearing,
and not my phantom
beast rescuer.
As though all of it were
nothing more than an illusion.
This world is still rich with
mysteries yet to be solved.
And as for me?
My mission is to
study this forest,
its undiscovered monsters
and untouched vegetation,
so that I may aid
future researchers.
Huh? Didn't we just
come through here?
Oh, man, are we lost?
[DEBLI] That's the Forest
of Confusion for you!
Don't you see what
happened here?!
If only you'd followed Navirou's
expert advice before,
we wouldn't have wasted
our time going around
in a giant circle!
Yeah, yeah, I was wrong.
So this time, we're gonna
follow your lead, all right.
Well, which way?
This way!
Hey, wait.
Back here? Again?
Oh, we're hopelessly lost.
Because you followed
Navirou's directions.
And that's a Navi-rule.
Wow, what a downpour!
At this rate--
A-choo! We'll catch a cold!
Come on, let's go try
to find some shelter.
Hold on. We lost Debli!
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
Oh, Debli. And after he
tells us to follow him.
Now he's run off and
gotten himself lost.
Saw that one coming.
Gotta hand it to him, he's
nothing if not dependable.
Hey! Tubbli!
[DEBLI]
"Tub" nothing!
Wait, that was him!
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Hey! Tubbli! Tub--
[DEBLI]
Stop calling me that!
It came from over there!
Are you all right, Lilia?
My bag!
It's okay, I'll go find
it once the rain stops.
Don't worry about it!
Thanks.
[groans]
[LUTE] You're not going
anywhere on that leg.
Finding shelter's gotta
be our top priority.
And afterwards, we can
go looking for Tubbli.
[DEBLI]
I told you not to call me that!
[giggling]
[LUTE]
What were you doing down there?
Found Divine Rhinos
and couldn't resist.
Always getting us
worked up over nothing!
Y'know, you can buy a whole
lotta donuts with one of these!
You chose wisely.
Navirou approves.
That was fast.
Hey, are you all right, Lute?
This is nothin'. I'm fine.
Why am I giving you a ride?
[NAVIROU chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
Look, lightning!
Sure is. That way!
Is this the right direction?
What the--?
The rain stopped.
What's going on?
Does it hurt?
Yeah, a little.
That's awful.
And with all of your Herbs lying
at the bottom of that cliff...
Ah, that reminds me.
You dropped this earlier.
Oh, now you pull that out?
Wow, you managed to grab it!
I'm so grateful, Debli!
I don't know how I
can ever thank you!
That bright smile of
yours is thanks enough!
No, no, no.
This all started 'cause you
ran off and got yourself lost.
Remember?
Well, adversity builds
teamwork, so you're welcome!
Honeslty. Layin' it on
a little thick, yeah?
[BOTH laughing]
[thunder crashes]
[LILIA, LUTE]
Huh?
[roaring]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
You must be...
What the heck is that thing?
Is it a monster?
It's not anywhere in here.
That's an unidentified
mystery monster!
I haven't seen it in any
Scrivener texts, either.
[ALL gasp]
[ALL yelp]
What is this creature?
And what's it trying to do?
'Cause it's making
Navirou dizzy!
[LUTE] Could it be
attempting to talk to us?
[DEBLI] Ha-ha. Yeah, right.
Like you can talk to a monster.
[DEBLI chuckles nervously]
[LILIA]
Maybe if it were a Monstie
you had Kinship with, but...
[LUTE]
It's just...
I can't help feeling like it's
trying to tell us something.
[DEBLI] Well, I know
what it's tellin' me.
That horn is amazing!
It'll fetch a pretty Zenny!
Now to slay it and
reap the reward.
[gasps] Debli!
[DEBLI screams]
Time to Ride On!
Rathalos!
Pull back for a sec!
Whoa, it's so strong!
Take that!
The Flash Bomb isn't working!
Yeah, well, how about this?
That Dung Bomb
didn't work, either!
Seriously, what is
this thing, anyway?
[DEBLI]
Nothing's working!
Debli!
That horn will be mine.
What admirable materialism!
Debli's greed is
nothing to be admired!
Enough! Just stop!
Careful, Lute!
Yeah, look out!
Ratha, let's do this!
Now! Sky-High Extreme!
[screams]
Oh, no! Lute!
[PAPPAN]
Look, Captain! Lightning!
I'm not so sure
that's lightning.
[MILLE]
That light...
[HYORO]
Lute and Ratha's Kinship Attack!
Why would they use that here?
We should go.
Navirou! Hey, are you okay?
Uh, where are we?
Uh.
Wait, where did everybody go?
Hey! Lilia! Hey, Tub... bli!
[gasps]
It's you.
That's the monster from before!
Hey, where are you going?
We should follow.
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
You wanna go chasing after
some mystery monster?!
Are you crazy?!
Oh, c'mon! Wait up!
There's something you
wanna tell us, right?
And that's the reason you
called us here, isn't it?
[NAVIROU screams]
Whoa, are you okay?
Navirou hears it! It's talking
directly into Navirou's head!
Navirou, are you all right?
Navirou?
And now we.. shall speak...
What the heck?
This ground... is hallowed
beyond human comprehension...
It is the wellspring of all
creation...
Binding fate to fate...
I don't understand, Navirou.
What happened to you?
Um, are you doing this?
[NAVIROU]
When fate is bound to fate...
...life moves ever onward...
to time beyond all time...
And that... is known
as eternity...
Something that we...
wish to safeguard...
To protect this Rapport...
There are things
I want to protect.
I'll guard my Kinship
till the end.
I'll keep them safe,
no matter what!
[NAVIROU] Perhaps we can
share... this sentiment...
...if we share this with you...
Whoa, a Kinship Ore!
But to us... it's known as
a Crystal of... Rapport.
[LILIA]
Lute! Stay with us!
[DEBLI]
Come on, Navirou! Wake up!
Oh, dear. What happened to them?
Captain Simone! Lute
and Navirou collapsed!
There's nothing to fear,
your friends are
simply unconscious.
Some smelling salts,
they oughta do the trick.
Oh, thank goodness!
The monster!
Wait! Where did it go?
Monster? You don't mean...
Whoa, sounds like you
know what that thing was.
Kirin, an Elder Dragon.
Also known as the
"Phantom Beast."
So that was Kirin.
Are you sure about that?
It wasn't in Navirou's
Monsterpedia ! He checked!
Yes, well, Elder Dragons
aren't like other monsters.
They're a special class
that don't really fit
into any particular ecosystem,
so your average guidebook
may not include them.
But luckily, my big one
does, and then some!
So then, you got to meet Kirin?
Lute, we saw the light
from your Kinship attack!
Where's the monster now?
It just... vanished.
[GENIE]
It vanished?
[STONE]
You mean you purified it?
No, it... It wasn't afflicted
with the Black Blight at all.
Its eyes were perfectly clear.
I hope to see it again.
Your Kinship Stone!
[LILIA] "At the ends of
the Forest of Confusion,
beyond the lightning-wielding
phantom beast...
...sleeps the Crystal
of Rapport."
So all this time, it was
guarding this Kinship Ore.
Oh, wow, your Kinship
Stone is glowing!
Whoa, is the Kinship
Ore doing that?
It's proof of the Kinship
that Lute and Kirin share.
Of that, I'm quite certain.
[SIMONE]
It seems I was mistaken.
I had wanted to survey
the Forest of Confusion
in order to confirm the
existence of phantom beasts.
I was convinced that such
advancements in knowledge
would lead this world
in a better direction.
But now, I'm thinking perhaps
there are some things
in nature that simply were
never meant to be explained.
But, Captain Simone.
This world is still
rich with mysteries.
That's right!
Captain Simone-
Simone-Simone...
Give Navirou-Navirou-Navirou...
...many, many
donuts-donuts-donuts...
...right away-away-away-away...
[SIMONE]
Let's go.
[PAPPAN]
Yes, ma'am.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Well, Lute, we're
heading home now.
Back to Hakum Village.
I guess this is
goodbye for now.
If you happen to see
Cheval out there,
tell him we're waiting
at Hakum Village.
And that we'll be
keeping it safe
until he's ready to come home.
Got it. I'll let him know.
Guess we should be
getting back to Gildegaran.
And we're off!
Adventure calls out to us!
C'mon, gang, follow
Navirou to glory!
Wait, are you sure we should
be following your lead?
You'll probably just
get us lost again.
Oh, yeah? Like you're one
to talk, huh, Tub... bli?
Debli! It's Debli!
[BOTH laughing]
We'll meet again.
For you and I are bound
together by Kinship.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU]
Our Monstie this time is: Kirin!
This elusive monster is
one of the Elder Dragons,
and you'd be super-lucky to
have this as your Monstie!
Oh, and hey, it can
command lighting
with its speedy movements.
Just like Navirou!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] There are seven
Kinship Ore in total.
And now we're off to
a legendary location
in search of the last one!
Next time: "The Deviljho
of Mt. Celion"!
Ride On!