Whoa, Ratha, slow down!
You're pulling too hard!
Stop! Ratha! I said stop!
That's too close,
Lute. Be careful!
[yells]
[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash, but enthusiastic fellow
who dreams of becoming
the world's top Monster Rider.
Lute and his friends
live in Hakum Village,
a hidden enclave of
Riders, young and old.
Earlier, Lute brought
Cheval and Lilia with him
deep into the woods to
help find a monster egg.
Lute's hope was that he and
the young creature inside
would be able to form a
deep connection, or Kinship,
at the next day's Kinship Rite.
Navirou was there, too!
[NARRATOR]
After much adventure,
including a leap
into a raging river
to escape a rampaging Arzuros,
Lute found an egg for a
Rathalos, the King of the Skies!
He then hatched it, even without
having a Kinship Stone!
Can our boy hero Lute form
Kinship with this Rathalos
and make it his Monstie?
Will Cheval and Lilia be able
to hatch their own eggs
at the Kinship Rite and
have Monsties of their own?
Our new friends are taking their
first steps to becoming Riders!
The Kinship Rite starts now!
And don't forget all
the great things
you're about to
see from Navirou!
Ow. Ow. Ow.
You'll be fine,
just walk it off.
Wow, how did Ratha get so huge?
That surprised me, too!
Ratha, you're amazing!
I can't believe how much
you've grown in one day!
And so strong!
All right now, settle down.
There's still a long road
before you're a true Rider.
Especially when it's
a monster you hatched
without a proper Kinship Stone!
Yeah, yeah. Got it, Dan.
Don't disrespect me.
It's "Got it, Dan sir!"
I can't wait to ride you, pal.
Ratha, my Monstie!
This kid's gonna be trouble.
I'm only gonna warn you once.
Even if you complete today's
Kinship Rite in top form
and become a Rider,
don't let your already big
head get the better of you
and send you running into
the Forbidden Land!
You got that?
Yeah.
What do you think happened
to Dan in the Forbidden Land?
Beats me.
All right, Ratha, you
gonna let me up there?
Yeah?
Looks like you're not yet
a real team yet. How sad.
We're just getting started!
Wow, you guys, Lute's so brave.
He's actually
touching a Rathalos!
No surprise there,
right, Stone?
Yeah, that's Lute for you.
That's not being brave,
that's just reckless.
I better not catch you
training that way, Hyoro.
Right, Brother.
I wonder what kind of Monstie
you'll hatch, Cheval?
We're gonna have such a good
time at the Kinship Rite!
Yeah, of course.
I'm home, Mom!
Oh, hi, honey. Did anything
exciting happen at practice?
Other than Lute getting
thrown around, not really.
Well, that's expected
at this stage.
Hey. Where is Lute?
He'll be here as soon as
he's done feeding Ratha.
Ah. I've got breakfast
ready for you.
And, since it's Kinship Rite
Day, I made your favorite:
Gargwa Egg Soufflé!
Sorry, Mom. But I'm
not that hungry.
The Kinship Rite, huh?
Don't worry about it, honey,
it'll all work out fine.
You know, ever since
you were a little boy,
Gargwa Soufflé always
made you feel better.
It's hot out of the oven.
I'll eat later, promise.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Cheval, I want you to meet Lute.
I expect you boys to play
nice with each other.
Hi. It's very nice
to meet you, Lute.
It's nice to meet you, Cheval.
[VLAU] Lute doesn't have
a mommy and daddy anymore,
but Chief Omna says they
were valiant Monstie Riders.
[LUTE]
Yummy!
This soufflé is great!
And it's steaming hot!
Hey, Lute.
Look, at the Kinship Rite
you're going to hatch that egg,
and you're going to become
a Rider, I'm positive.
Just relax, and
everything'll work out fine.
[chuckles]
Hey, wait. I never said
anything about being nervous.
Well, it's not exactly
hard to read your face.
I've known you forever, buddy.
You caught me,
I'm nervous about all this
because I'm not as
fearless as you are.
Listen to me, you are more
than brave enough to be a Rider.
But how can you really
be so sure of that?
Because you can be considerate
of a monster's feelings.
And plus, while you may not be
as vocal about it as I am,
deep down, I know you really
do want to become a Rider.
And that's why
I'm confident in you.
Believe in yourself, Cheval.
Your dreams are
bound to come true.
Yeah, but, Lute,
your gut's always wrong.
[LUTE yelps]
[BOTH laugh]
Oh, wow!
Your donuts are great, but this
gargwa soufflé is good too!
Navirou can't stop eating!
Navirou, come on!
Hey, that's my soufflé!
No problem, hon.
I'm always happy to
make another batch!
[BOTH chuckle]
[LOLOA] You got nothing
to worry about Lilia!
Loloa is positive
that after today
you'll be well on your
way to being a Rider!
[LILIA]
Thanks, Loloa. I appreciate it.
Although...
What's up? Lilia? Hello?
Well, once I'm a Rider,
I won't be able to leave
the village anymore,
unless I'm going on
an official quest.
Really? But why?
Yeah, so what's the problem?
Oh, Mille.
That's the way it's
always been in the past
and the way it will
be in the future.
What choice do we have?
I know that, but--
There's a huge world
outside the village
and I want the freedom to go
explore it whenever I want.
If that's what you want, you
can forget about being a Rider.
Excuse me.
[LOLOA]
What's Mille so angry about?
[LILIA]
I'm not sure.
What's gotten in to her?
It sounds like she doesn't even
want to be a Rider anymore!
I've worked so hard to beat her,
and now her second-guessing's
throwing me off!
C'mon, Hyoro. Pick up
the pace, no dawdling.
Yes, Brother.
You are aware that after today,
you'll be a Rider, too.
I shouldn't have to
keep pointing out
these obvious things to you.
I didn't ask you to
point out anything.
I was just walking.
Now what are you mumbling?
Nothing.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Greetings, candidates!
It's with great pride that
I announce the Kinship Rite
is at last upon us.
Demonstrate well what
you have learned
in your training
these many months,
and you shall earn
the title of Rider!
[KIDS]
Sir!
First, I shall bestow
upon each of you
the monster eggs
carrying your Monsties,
then I shall give you
your Kinship Stones.
Here, Cheval, as always.
Yes.
[CHIEF OMNA] Lute, since
you don't need an egg,
here's your Stone.
Yes, sir, but I mean, if you're
handing eggs out I'll--
Uh! No, never mind!
[laughs]
It seems to me you might
need to take some time
to deepen your kinship
with that Rathalos first.
What's the problem, buddy?
Feelin' a little less than?
How petty can you get?
[NAVIROU yelps]
[CHIEF OMNA]
Mille, what say you?
[MILLE]
I humbly accept.
Hyoro. Hold tightly.
Okay.
And you, Lilia,
here is a Kinship Stone
to go with your egg.
[LILIA]
Um, right. Thank you.
Now, I take it clever Lilia here
is familiar with the
rules a Rider must obey?
Yes.
Once you're a Rider,
you will no longer be
allowed to come and go
from the village as you please.
Do you know the reason
we have this rule?
To be honest, sir, I never
thought about it much.
I just always thought rules
are rules, and that's that.
But lately I've realized
the world is a big place,
full of things we
can't even imagine.
Towns nothing like
Hakum Village,
each one full of
different peoples,
including those we call Hunters.
There's just so much
to see out there!
A world to explore.
That's right, Lilia.
So now I do ask.
Why do we have
such strict rules?
Why can't Riders see the world?
Lilia.
I've never seen that
look on her face before.
Yeah.
It's not simply that Riders
cannot see or know of the world.
Dear girl,
it's about not letting the world
see or know of us Riders!
I know, but why?
[GENIE] That's something
you don't need to know
about right now, Lilia.
[CHIEF OMNA]
It's okay, Genie. Settle down.
It's only fair that
our aspiring Riders
know everything there is to know
about the life they
may be getting into.
Now please listen
close, candidates.
You all may find this
hard to believe,
having come of age
in Hakum Village,
but in the wider world,
people do not see
monsters as creatures
with which to have the
closeness of Kinship.
[LUTE]
What?
How could they even think that?
[CHIEF OMNA]
There are those in this world
who find us strange for
living alongside monsters,
even some who would fear us.
That is why we Riders spend most
of our lives in quiet seclusion.
That doesn't make any sense!
Why should we indulge
their ignorance like that?
It's just not fair!
Chief Omna, we shouldn't
have to hide!
You're right.
And that is why you're
free to live your life
however you choose.
[gasps]
Okay.
While I still don't know yet
what I want to do with my life,
I know..
...I won't be a Rider.
[gasps]
Very well.
Navirou's very surprised
that you're not
becoming a Rider, Lilia.
Oh, I know, Navirou,
but I just really wanna
see the world, that's all.
Yeah, follow your dreams, I say.
I always knew you'd
walk your own path.
That's right, Lilia.
And for the record,
Navirou had bet on that, too.
All right, you.
Yeah, Navirou, once again,
your act isn't fooling anyone.
[yelps]
All right, enough! We'll now
continue the Kinship Rite.
Hold your Stones in the air!
My name is Lute!
My name is Cheval.
My name is Mille.
My name's Hyoro.
O holy Kinship Stones,
I, Chief Omna,
call upon thee to bind together
Lute, Cheval, Mille, and Hyoro
with these slumbering creatures!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
Ah! An Aptonoeth!
Look, it's a Bulldrome!
Those are great, you guys.
What Monstie did
you get, Cheval?
I don't... know what's wrong.
Don't worry, buddy.
Ratha wasn't exactly the
quickest guy to hatch, either.
Yeah, but--
Lute didn't have
Kinship Stones then.
And Lilia was the one saying
the words of the Rite.
It would've made more sense
if that egg didn't hatch.
So with yours sitting there,
when you're doing
everything right,
tells Navirou you've
got a problem.
Don't bring that up
right now! You be nice!
Hey, Navirou always says
whatever Navirou wants to say!
If Navirou wants to eat,
Navirou... eats donuts!
So good.
[sighs]
I guess I was right to be
nervous this morning, after all.
It wasn't my fate
to become a Rider.
Great. Cheval's depressed.
This could last a while.
Well, we have to do something.
Wait, I know! I'll just fix him
one of my energy drinks!
No, no, no. That's fine.
Let's just try to cheer him up.
Okay.
Cheval! Don't give up yet!
I know you can hatch it!
Just call out to the little guy.
He's probably still sleeping!
Come on!
Give it another shot. We'll get
that monster out, I promise.
Yeah, believe in
yourself, Cheval.
Things always work out
for you in the end, right?
[LILIA]
You're one to talk!
Why're you pulling on Navirou!
All Navirou did was tell
him to believe in himself?
It sounded pretty fake
coming from you.
[screams]
I am not falling for that.
[NAVIROU] No, seriously!
It's, uh, it's that--
Look! It's something horrible!
Why's a Tigrex here?
We'll have to put the
Kinship Rite on hold
and go to the Village.
As for you Riders,
you must stop that Tigrex!
[ALL]
Sir!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Let's Ride On!
Qurupeco!
All right, Ride On!
Popo!
Let's go, Ride On!
Yian kut-ku!
Ride On!
Aptonoeth!
[heartbeat]
[gasps]
Hey, let's go!
We gotta get outta here!
That Tigrex is trouble
on two legs! Move!
He's right. Come on,
guys, let's go!
No, wait.
[heartbeat]
[CHEVAL]
Again?
Cheval, what's goin' on?
[CHIEF OMNA] My child, we must
take refuge right away.
[CHEVAL]
But just wait.
Cheval, is your egg
about to hatch?
Yeah. It's like you
said yesterday, Lute.
"This guy wants to hatch now."
Great. Then let's
finish the Rite!
Wait, what?
I'm not gonna argue
with it. Are you?
If my best friend
says it's so, it's so.
Dan and the other Riders
can take care of the Tigrex,
no problem.
I don't know, this
seems really risky.
Chief Omna, help us.
We have to finish
the Kinship Rite!
Listen to me closely, Cheval.
Reach out with your heart
to your monster egg.
Ask the unborn to
become your Monstie!
Sir!
[DAN]
Be careful!
[CHEVAL] Please, hatch for me.
I want to b e a Rider.
You can do it, Cheval, come on!
[CHEVAL]
Please, be my Monstie.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
No way!
Attaboy, Cheval!
That's it, little guy!
You're almost out. C'mon!
[ALL gasp]
And with that, a healthy
Velocidrome is born.
[LUTE]
You did it, Cheval!
This monster lives in packs
and is fiercely loyal
to his friends.
He might just be the
perfect Monstie for you!
Thank you so much
for hatching for me.
Nice to meet you, Velocidrome.
[cries]
I hope we get along.
Of course you will!
You get along with
everyone, Cheval!
That'll depend on how much love
you put in this relationship.
'Cause nothing cools
faster than passion!
Hey, would you stop trying to
rain on our parade, Navirou?
You were supposed to go
back to the village!
Yeah, but Cheval
finally hatched his--
[NOLE] I don't care. We gotta
move. Tigrex is coming!
What? Coming?
[roars]
No! We're too late!
Everybody, run!
What happened to Dan
and the Riders?!
They were attacked
and pinned down!
Are you all right, Qurupeco?
[ALL]
What?!
Don't worry, guys, they'll be
back on their feet in no time.
But until then, I'll hold
it off, so you can escape.
[NOLE]
Yah!
To safety everyone!
[ALL]
Sir!
[NAVIROU]
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Hey, come on.
[roars]
Velocidrome. Get up!
Hey!
[LUTE]
Look out!
Lute!
You all right?
Whoa, Ratha. You're gonna
let me Ride On you?
[roars]
All right! Ride On!
Ha-ha! I'm flying!
Yeah! I'm riding Ratha!
[CHEVAL, LILIA]
Wow!
What?
Ratha! Let's save our friends!
My Stone... What's this light?
So fast!
That was a Kinship Attack!
Amazing!
[LILIA]
You did it, Lute!
[CHEVAL]
That was incredible.
hat was so awesome!
You were great, Ratha!
--[LUTE laughing]
--[RATHA roaring]
A job well done, Lute.
And Ratha, too.
As expected from
Navirou's top pupil.
Hold on, "pupil"?
All you ever do is stand there
and make snarky remarks!
How dare you! Never talk
to your teacher like that!
[LUTE, CHEVAL, LILIA laughing]
[NAVIROU] Stop! Stop
laughing! It's not funny!
[GAMIGAMI]
Honestly!
When I think what could've
happened out there,
my blood runs cold!
Why is this new group of Riders
so intent on infuriating me?
Oh, and while I'm at it,
don't go around thinking
just because you pulled
off a Kinship Attack
you actually have Kinship now!
Because you don't!
Yeah.
And you! Lose that tone!
[CHIEF OMNA]
Now now, Gamigami.
All's well that ends well,
isn't that right?
[laughs]
Well, then, candidates,
it's time for the
Rite's next phase,
where you'll join together in
order to deepen your Kinship
with your monsters.
[KIDS]
Sir!
You ready, Velocidrome?
I'm glad, Cheval.
Thanks for your support
and protection.
You kept Velocidrome safe.
There's no need to
thank Navirou, Cheval.
After all, that's
what friends do!
They look out for each other!
Really?
Keep talkin', pal, you only
bring it on yourself.
Bring what now?
[DAN] Thankfully,
Nole and Lute managed
to bring down the Tigrex.
There's never been one in these
woods before, so why now?
I sense dangerous
changes underway.
Something dark and
evil is closing in.
We must remain vigilant.
[DAN]
Yes, sir.
Another perfectly
roasted dinner.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Now the part of the show
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open
for the two-screen experience.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
All right, everyone!
Time to form a Kinship
with our Monsties!
And now, the moment of new life.
Awaken!
Our Monstie this
time is: Rathalos!
The mighty beast is known as
the "King of the Skies,"
and can shoot fireballs
out of its mouth,
making it especially dangerous
when it attacks from the air!
Didn't it look super cool flying
around and fighting the Tigrex?
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
It's me, Lute!
Looks like a Hunter is
coming to Hakum Village.
He says his name is Reverto.
If you ask me, something
big's about to go down.
Next time: "Absolute Power"!
Ride On!