[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight
that's been spreading
across the world.
[NARRATOR]
Lute found a white dragon's egg,
said to be that of the legendary
Rider Redan's Monstie.
But before he could
hatch the egg,
Doctor Manelger
managed to steal it.
Now Lute is chasing
after the mad scientist
in hopes of getting
the egg back.
♪
[NAVIROU] Wow, the rebuilding
effort sure is coming along.
[LUTE] Yeah, the whole
place is buzzing!
Think they have
limited-edition donuts?
Come on, you know
we have to focus
on tracking down
Manelger right now.
[NAVIROU groans] Yeah, yeah,
but we don't even know for sure
that he's here, do we?
Besides, Navirou
hates the desert.
Too much sand in his whiskers.
Huh, well, the tip did come
from the Scriveners, so...
[LUTE]
You guys know where Manelger is?
Well, sort of.
What information we have
doesn't amount to very much.
And since the doctor is
in hiding at the moment,
he's not exactly leaving
us a lot of new clues
to investigate here.
So you're saying
you've got nothing?
No, not nothing.
We have gathered
some intelligence.
[LUTE]
Well, what is it?
This is the latest update
that we've received
from the Guild.
According to it, there have
been multiple sightings
of Dr. Manelger's airship
reported out in
the Trese Desert.
Wait, just his airship?
[LILIA]
Right now, that's all we have.
Well, if that's our only lead,
guess I'll check out
this Trese Desert.
[LILIA grunts] All right.
Looks like it's been spotted
somewhere around
Albrachs Village,
so you should start out there.
[NAVIROU]
Albrachs Village?
[LUTE]
Oh, right.
That's where we defeated the
Blighted Diablos, remember?
Okay, first we've gotta round
up some info on Manelger.
[NOLMA]
Ah, it's been too long, Lute.
I trust that you've been well?
Yep! How 'bout you, Chief?
[NOLMA] Hm. Thanks to the help
of you and the other Riders,
Albrachs Village is well on its
way to recovery. You saved us.
Couldn't've done
it without Navirou!
[LUTE, NAVIROU chuckle]
[NOLMA chuckles] I've already
spoken with the Scriveners.
This isn't just
a friendly visit.
You're here for a
reason, correct?
We're trying to
find Dr. Manelger.
The man who
mechanizes monsters?
Yes, I remember him.
The Scriveners told us that
his giant airship of horrors
has been spotted in
the vicinity recently.
I see.
Well, I can't say that I've
heard anything about it myself.
But in matters such as these,
it may be best for you to ask
some of the Hunters directly.
Where are we supposed
to find Hunters?
[NAVIROU]
Hm?
[HUNTERS chatter]
Look at that. Seems to
be a Hunter hangout.
At least one of these guys
has gotta know something
about Manelger! Let's go!
[HUNTER chatter]
[HUNTER A, VIM]
[door creaks]
Uh, Lute, why are
they staring at us?
[LILIA]
Huh...
[PAPPAN sighs] Wonder how
Lute and Navirou are.
Hope they've made it
to Albrachs by now
and are doing okay.
Yeah, me, too.
You worried about them?
Yes. We're not even really
sure if they're looking for
Dr. Manelger in the right place.
Yeah, like trying to find
a needle in a haystack.
Or a grain of sand
in the desert.
I mean, just look at these
papers we've gotta go through.
This is all the info the
Guild handed over to us.
And we're not exactly in the
people-finding business, are we?
But we have to find him.
Dr. Manelger, and of course
Cheval's team along with him.
[PAPPAN]
Oh, right, Cheval's team.
[PAPPAN sighs] Now that's a
whole other set of issues.
Oh, wow! So this is the
legendary white dragon's egg!
Is it for real?
[footsteps]
[DR. MANELGER]
Well, what do you say, my boy?
We're talking about the
legendary white dragon here.
The same monstie that Reden took
during his hard-won battle
to stop the Black Blight.
And now it can be
your Monstie, Cheval.
You expect me to believe
that old fairy tale?
Whether you believe it or not
is entirely up to you, my boy.
That's right! It's your choice!
[BOTH chuckle]
[CHEVAL grunts]
[BARKEEP A] Welcome, gentlemen.
What can I get for ya?
Ooh, what should I order?
[NAVIROU] Hm! Milk, neat,
and make it a double.
Gotta play the sophisticate in
a fine establishment like this.
And that's a Navi-rule.
You're not sophisticated
in the least.
[NAVIROU yelps]
I'll have what he's having!
Ah, fine milk.
'Scuse me, sir, have you
heard anybody talking about
a strange airship
flying around nearby?
[NAVIROU]
What's the matter, Lute?
Did that guy just straight-up
ignore my question?
[NAVIROU]
Oh, you're imagining things.
He probably just
didn't hear you.
Ya think so?
[gasps]
Excuse me, sir!
[BARKEEP gasps]
Do you know anything
about a strange airship
that might've been flying
around these parts recently?
I don't know nothin'.
But you must've heard something
working here. A rumor at least?
[HUNTER A] He ain't talkin'.
Barkeep's the tight-lipped sort.
[LUTE]
Uh?
Now you should know,
for us Hunters,
information's a close
second to weapon care
when it comes to
making a livin'.
So none of us is just
gonna go blabbin'
everything we know
to some strangers.
Maybe you could make
an exception for us?
Ya see, it's just that we--
[HUNTER A] Run along
home now, little kiddies.
This place is for Hunters!
[LUTE, NAVIROU growl]
This is gonna be so ultra-tasty!
At last my Gourmet
Steak is ready!
[NAVIROU]
That voice, it's--
Eat up. It's all
on me, of course.
[chuckles]
Whoa, Mr. Reverto!
[REVERTO]
Long time no see, Lute.
What's that kid's deal anyway?
Wait, he knows Reverto?
Hey, Master Vim,
that's the lone-wolf
hunter Reverto over there.
[VIM]
Yeah.
[He's looking as shabby and
pathetic as ever, I see.
[REVERTO] Listen up!
This here's no ordinary kid.
He's the one who
saved this village!
So how 'bout you
show a little respect
and give him some help here?
No way! Y'mean to tell
me that pipsqueak there
is the brave Rider who
slayed the Blighted Diablos?
Yup. That's what I said.
That's right!
You guys are looking at the
savior of Albrachs Village.
Sir Lute the Rider!
[HUNTERS gasp]
[VIM grunts]
A Rider.
[NAVIROU]
And then of course,
there's his brilliant mentor,
Navirou the Great!
[HUNTERS gasp]
[LUTE gasps]
Wow, you're the one who
slayed the Diablos?
You're amazin', kid!
A real hero, y'know that!
[MHUNTER B] Hey, tell us
some more about the Riders!
[LUTE]
Uh... Uh... sure!
That's right, folks, line up
to shake the hero's hand! Huh?
Hey, wait! No cuts!
[NAVIROU grunts]
Uh, hey there.
[VIM grunts]
[LUTE] Oh. That thing!
It's a Kinship Stone.
See, 'cause it's used to
form Kinship with monsters!
So this is a Kinship Stone?
Yeah, um...
[VIM]
Hm?
All right, pal, that's enough.
[VIM]
Hmph.
Are you okay, Lute?
That guy is crazy strong.
[ELKE]
Master Vim, wait for me!
[LUTE]
Sheesh, what was that about?
Beats me.
Hey, so, Mr. Reverto.
[REVERTO]
Huh?
There's something
that I'd like to ask
all the Hunters who
are here. May I?
[REVERTO]
Oh, that's right.
Hey, guys! I want everyone
to pay attention!
If any of you have seen
Doctor Manelger's airship
flying around here,
please let us know.
Wait, Manelger? The guy
who mechanizes monsters?
Oh! Hey, you know,
now that you mention it,
I did see an airship like
that a few days back,
near the Treese Salt Caves.
[BOTH]
Huh?
All right, tell us
everything you know!
[NAVIROU grunts]
Navirou's got sand in his fur!
[LUTE]
Then put on some clothes.
No can do!
Navirou believes
strongly in presenting
his true and honest
self to the world!
Sand in Navirou's eyes
and sand in his mouth!
[REVERTO]
Forget about that.
The Trese Salt Caves
where the airship
was spotted are just ahead.
Let's keep moving.
[LUTE] Hey, you really helped
us out back there, Mister.
And now you're
showing us the way?
[REVERTO] Don't mention it.
That was all you, really.
I mean, you are the hero
who saved Albrachs Village.
But you know, there is something
that's been bothering me.
[LUTE]
Really? What?
[REVERTO]
Back in that tavern--
[NAVIROU shouts]
[LUTE]
What is it?
That's-That's-That's...
the airship!
[LUTE]
It sure is!
Oh yeah, that's Manelger's
ship all right!
[REVERTO] Can't see too
well at this distance.
[LUTE]
It's landing at the Salt Caves!
[LILIA sighs]
Look! This report's
about Dr. Manelger!
[LILIA]
Huh?
You're right! And this intel
is pretty recent, too!
But wait, hold on, this doesn't
mention the Trese Desert at all.
[PAPPAN] Ooh, I found
another report in here.
Oh, wow, these are
confirmed sightings
of someone matching
Manelger's description!
From very reliable sources!
Mm? But, these don't come from
the Trese Desert, either.
What? That means...
...the info that we gave
Lute and Navirou--
It must have been bogus intel.
[LILIA] If so, then what was
it that all those people
mistook for the airship?
Good news, Master Vim.
It looks like this little
replica of an airship
is bringing them right to us.
[VIM chuckles]
[NAVIROU gasps]
[LUTE]
Navirou!
A crevasse!
[NAVIROU]
Save Navirou!
[LUTE gasps]
Don't move! I'm on my way!
[REVERTO]
Be careful!
Lute, help!
Are you okay?
Oh, Lute!
[LUTE chuckles]
As expected of
Navirou's top pupil!
[LUTE gasps]
[NAVIROU gasps]
[LUTE, NAVIROU shout]
[REVERTO]
Lute, no!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[grunts]
[LUTE]
Where am I?
[gasps]
Where's Navirou?
Navirou!
Navirou?
--[NAVIROU grunts]
--[LUTE gasps]
[groans] Oh, Navirou couldn't
possibly eat that much.
But when there are
donuts in sight,
Navirou will be sure
to eat every last bite!
And that is a Navi-rule.
[gasps]
Hey! Where'd all the donuts go?
They were right
here a second ago...!
He's all right!
[LUTE] Looks like we're at
the bottom of the crevasse.
[NAVIROU]
So it was connected to a cave!
C'mon, we've gotta look
for a way outta here
so we can find Manelger.
[buzzing]
[NAVIROU]
Uh? What's that sound?
What sound?
[NAVIROU, LUTE]
Huh?
[buzzing continues]
[LUTE gasps]
Sounds like wings flapping!
[NAVIROU gasps]
A swarm of Bnahabra!
Time to Ride On!
Velocidrome!
Ah, the fleet-footed
Velocidrome, eh?
Yes, yes, an excellent choice!
Hey, wait. Where is it?
Think maybe it's because
we're in a cave?
Perhaps your Monstie
is lost, too.
That's not good.
So what now?
Do you have to ask?
[BOTH]
Run!
[NAVIROU]
They're gaining on us!
[LUTE]
Don't talk, just run!
Oh, no, looks like
we've hit a dead end!
[LUTE gasps]
[NAVIROU] What do we do now?
There's nowhere to run!
[LUTE]
Navirou!
I'll draw their attacks while
you escape through that!
Yeah, but what about you, Lute?
I'll improvise!
[NAVIROU growls]
Navirou's not running!
He's gonna stay here and fight!
[LUTE gasps]
[NAVIROU groans]
Hey, what happened?
Why'd you stop?
Navirou's too hungry to fight.
[NAVIROU] Oh, no. While we were
talking, they surrounded us!
[BOTH grunt]
[LUTE gasps]
[LUTE grunts]
Phew, that was close.
Reverto, is that you?
Huh? You're that Hunter
from the tavern!
[ELKE]
My, my, my, mrowr!
Good thing mew're
all right, Mister Hero.
[LUTE grunts]
Thanks, sir. You saved us.
[gasps]
Lemme go!
Hey! What are you
doing to Lute?
[ELKE shouts]
Mew stay out of this.
Sure are mouthy,
mew freaky Felyne.
Just who are you, anyway?
[ELKE chuckes]
My name's Elke.
We only buttered mew up
and saved mew to get mew
to drop your guard, mrowr!
[LUTE]
Why are you doing this?
[VIM]
I'll be taking that.
[gasps]
Hey! Stop it!
[ELKE] We're just trying to
complete our quest here, mrowr.
There's no way it's a quest!
The Guild would
never order this!
Oh, did I say anything about
it being a Guild quest?
No, this is a
black-market quest!
Black-market?
What does that mean?
That means it's an illegal
quest bypassing the Guild.
It's risky, but the
rewards are better
than anything the
Guild hands out.
This one happens to be
for some fancy doctor guy,
and he's paying really well!
[NAVIROU]
It's not Dr. Manelger, is it?
[ELKE] Huh, that name
does ring a bell, mrowr.
Anyway, it's 10,000
Zenny just to fly
an airship-shaped kite
and trick the Scriveners!
Plus another hundred thousand
if we get that Kinship Stone
off of mew and bring it to him!
Manelger would really
sink that low?
All I know is we're gonna make
a fortune thanks to mew!
[VIM]
You talk too much.
[ELKE]
Huh? Sorry, Master Vim!
I just got a little
carried away, mrowr!
It's time. Form Kinship with
this legendary Monstie, Cheval!
O holy Kinship Stone,
bind the two of us together.
Now the moment of
new life. Awaken!
O dragon white,
please be my Monstie!
[CHEVAL] What is the
meaning of this Manelger?
[DR. MANELGER]
As I suspected.
This Kinship Stone
lacks sufficient power.
The power necessary to
awaken the white dragon.
Don't touch it!
You expect me to believe
that it's not strong enough?
[CHEVAL grunts]
[LUTE]
Hey, cut it out!
[LUTE grunts]
[NAVIROU]
Lute!
[NAVIROU grunts]
Why don't mew just
shut your face, mrowr!
[VIM]
Let's go.
[ELKE]
ye-aye!
[REVERTO]
Well, well.
So is this what you do,
steal from kids?
[ELKE]
Who's there?
[REVERTO] You know, you're a
downright despicable dude,
rogue hunter. For such a big
guy, you certainly act small.
[LUTE grunts]
Hey, Mister!
Don't think I'm
letting you off easy.
[VIM] Hm. A Hunter turning his
sword on another human
is forbidden.
Yeah, that's right, mrowr!
And if you violate
the Hunter's rules,
you'll be kicked
out of the Guild,
only to become a
rogue Hunter yourself!
[REVERTO] And throw in
with you lot? No, thanks.
[LUTE]
Huh? Uh, hey, Mister?
[REVERTO] A sword would be
wasted on the likes of you.
We'll settle this... with these.
Well, you were startin'
to get on my nerves.
[REVERTO, VIM grunting]
That was just an appetizer.
[grunting continues]
[gasps]
I read mew loud and clear!
[chuckles]
I'll just use this Bone Wedge,
and sneak up behind
that annoying Hunter
and smash 'im in the back!
[grunting]
You gutless coward!
Navirou's the one who you
should be up against here!
Hey, mew stay outta this!
[ELKE shouts]
[REVERTO]
Not the best time to lose focus!
Yeah, I'll be taking this back.
Mister, thanks so much!
It was nothing.
Seriously, I wanted
to punch that guy
from the moment I first saw him.
By the way, did you always have
that special lightning
move, Navirou?
Yes, well, Navirou's
a very special guy.
You wanna see it again?
Yeah, no, I'm good.
All right then,
shall we head on back now?
Sure!
[gasps]
Uh, Lute, looks like your
Velocidrome has arrived.
You're a little late.
[chirps]
Man, today was the
absolute worst, really.
Sure was. And we wasted the
whole day chasing down
a fake Manelger lead.
Well, now to take it easy.
You guys! Hey!
[LUTE]
Lilia? What's she doing here?
We know where Manelger is!
For real this time!
Hakum Village!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou tells you
about Monsties.
All right, Navirou hopes you
have your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Ahpceros!
This compact monster
lives out in the desert.
It's an herbivore like Aptonoth,
but still packs
a powerful punch!
And with its tough exterior,
this is one Monstie
who'll keep you safe
when push comes to shove!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] Looks like Dr. Manelger
has come to Hakum Village.
But I'm done letting him
do whatever he wants!
Next time: "Trouble
Returns to Hakum"!
Ride On!