[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
So how was the
Tower of Illusion?
From the look on your face,
I assume it went well.
Impressive, isn't it?
This is the suit of
armor your father wore
when he was about your age.
From my dad?
[NARRATOR]
Now wearing his father's armor,
Lute headed off to slay monsters
stricken with the Black Blight.
I will stop the Black Blight,
thanks to my Kinship with Ratha!
[NARRATOR] Lute's faith in that
Kinship gave rise to a powerful,
brand-new Kinship Attack.
Meanwhile...
Forget it! I don't believe
in any Kinship!
Rathian, I have no
more use for you!
[NARRATOR]
Cheval dismissed Rathi,
the Monstie who had been
his constant companion.
And then...
The both of you are useless.
[BOTH gasp]
You won't betray me.
I'm sure of it.
I hope you hatch soon.
[NARRATOR] With Cheval
more alone than ever,
and Lute off fighting
to end the Black Blight
using the power of Kinship,
who should sneak back onto the
scene but Dr. Manelger.
[DR. MANELGER] Sorry to keep
you waiting, Cheval, my boy!
But at last, it's ready,
my Mecha Kinship Stone!
Uh, Cheval, my boy?
[LUTE]
Hey, Navirou,
Lilia's got a lead on
a Kinship Ore for us.
Let's get to Mount
Rhyz right away.
Navirou's good to go!
Already packed and everything!
Seriously? That's
nothing but donuts!
All right, let's see.
If we're over this lake,
then I'm pretty sure Mount Rhyz
is gonna be somewhere off
to the east of us now.
Navirou's navigation
won't steer us wrong!
Okay, here goes! This Mount
Rhyz we're looking for is...
[BOTH]
It's that way!
[NAVIROU]
Oh, c'mon, Ratha!
Y'know, just once you could
follow Navirou's directions!
[ITSY-BITS]
Sir! Sir!
I think I may have figured out
where Cheval's run off to.
There's a better than good
chance he's at Mount Rhyz!
And why would he be there?
Well, according to one of
my very reliable sources,
the Scriveners think that there
may be another Kinship Ore
located somewhere
on the mountain.
So I'm thinking if it's already
been Blighted, then that would--
Then that would mean that
the local monsters
would be Blighted,
which would mean that
Cheval would undoubtedly
be making an appearance there,
sooner rather than later!
That's right! He has to!
For the moment, at least,
Cheval has devoted his
life to tracking down
and slaying Blighted monsters!
So what are we waiting for?
Let's hurry up and make our
way to Mount Rhyz, sir!
[NAVIROU]
There it is, Mount Rhyz!
So we're supposed to
find a Kinship Ore
somewhere down there?
[LUTE] Wow, this mountain
is absolutely huge.
It's gonna take days
for the two of us
to scour this place
by ourselves.
That's for sure. Too bad
the Numbers aren't here.
We could split up and search
in a fraction of the time.
Navirou wonders how those
guys are doing, anyway.
Hope they're good!
[BEATS] Yeah, totally!
We're doin' great!
Ah, what a relief to
hear you're doing fine!
That's good to kn-- Oh?
[gasps]
[BOTH]
Uh?
Whoa!
Nothing in the world burns
brighter than my spirit!
Number One.
Beats!
I am of warm heart,
but cool breath.
Number Two.
I am Cryo!
Sparkle-sparkle!
My dazzling beauty is
almost blindingly bright!
Number Three.
Fifi here!
You don't need glasses to
see I'm the brains here.
Number Four.
You can call me Spex!
Leading you onward to
a brighter tomorrow!
Number Five.
Navirou!
Always time for a nap!
Number Six!
Wook, it's me, Floof!
And all together, we are:
[ALL]
The Numbers!
Hey, long time no see, guys!
But what the heck are you
doing all the way out here?
Well, after we last saw
you on Naubaka Island,
we got to talkin' about
what we could do to help.
Yes, precisely.
Nobody should ever have
to go through what we did.
We decided that meant we
had to try and put a stop
to Dr. Manelger's
latest maniacal scheme.
Oh, great, what's he up to now?
We don't know the specifics,
but whatever he's plotting,
we do know he'd sacrifice anyone
for the sake of his research!
And from what we've heard,
he's already gone and
successfully nabbed
the legendary white dragon egg!
We've been secretly
tailing him,
which is how we've come to find
ourselves here at Mount Rhyz.
But then wight
after we got here,
we wost twack of Dr. Manelger
while I was yawning
and now we can't
find him anywhere.
Ooh, I know, maybe I can twy
to wook for him in my dweams.
Nighty-night.
Hang on a second,
did you just say you tracked
Manelger to this mountain?
Hey, that works out perfectly!
Now we can join forces and
help you guys look for Manelger
while you help us hunt
for the Kinship Ore!
Makes sense we'd wind up
in the same place eventually.
Even when we're apart,
we're still one, am I right?
That you are!
All right, then!
The Numbers are back in
business and ready for action!
Let's track down Manelger
and take back that white
dragon egg together!
Whadda ya say?
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
And we'll keep the Kinship
Ore safe while we're at it!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[LUTE]
Wait, what?
Why are we stopping to
eat all of the sudden?
We were so pumped up and ready
for action just a second ago!
But first, we eat!
And...
[NUMBERS]
...that's a Numbers rule.
[LUTE chuckles]
Aw, but, Lutie Pie,
you must be at least
a little hungry by now.
[LUTE chuckles nervously]
"Lutie Pie"?
Just "Lute" is fine.
Oh? Okay.
Here you go, this dewicious
one's just for you!
Thanks! Looks yummy!
You know, if it's too hot,
I'd be more than happy
to blow on it for you.
Uh, that's okay.
I think I'm all good.
Been so long since we've sat
down and eaten together.
Yes, but still,
we mustn't forget,
this meal is all about giving
us the energy we'll need
to stand up to Manelger.
Oh, c'mon, there's no reason
to bring that up now.
For the moment, let's
just eat up and enjoy.
[FIFI] Cryo, want me to blow on
that for you and cool it off?
Uh, no thank you, I'll pass.
After all, I'm a lot better
at it than you are.
You see?
[CHEVAL]
Pathetic.
I have no use for a Monstie
that can't slay a
Blighted monster.
Guess I'll just move
on to the next one.
[ITSY-BITS]
I'm all finished, sir!
Ah, so I see,
and what a marvelous job
you've done, Itsy-Bits.
Wow, thanks for saying
that, sir! It means a lot!
Anyway, I made these
little masterpieces
exactly like you instructed.
So we're prepared now,
and no matter who tries to come
after the white dragon egg,
they won't be able to pick out
the real one from the forgeries!
It's brilliant!
Yes, and once we locate Cheval,
we can upgrade his Kinship
Stone by combining it
with this Mecha Kinship Stone
that I so cleverly created.
And then that great white
dragon will finally be ours!
[ITSY-BITS]
Oh, look, sir! There it is!
Mount Rhyz!
But, huh, I'm not seeing any
black haze down there.
Well, that does us no good.
Cheval will only show up if
there's a Blighted monster.
It appears we're
wasting our time here.
But wait! Is that Lute
I spy with my little eye?
[ITSY-BITS]
And the Numbers, too!
Oh, no, sir!
What should we do now?
Time for a slight
change of plans.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Rub-a-dub-dub,
thanks for the grub!
[LUTE]
Ah, what a feast!
That sure hit the
spot, all right!
Now let's go find
that Kinship Ore!
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
Whoa, what the heck is that?
[NAVIROU]
Hm?
[ITSY-BITS]
Yoo-hoo, you guys!
How's it goin', everyone?
It's Manelger!
Ah, Lute, my dear boy!
We meet again!
What do you what, Manelger?
Huh?
I wasn't expecting you
to hitch your wagon
to these Felyne failures.
[ALL growl]
Whoa, whoa, there's
no need to get upset
and make those
scary faces at us!
Right, sir?
We don't want to fight
with you. But that all--
That all depends on how you
choose to respond here, Lute!
Oh, come on! That was supposed
to be my big tough-guy line!
What do you want?
Why, the good doctor here
is generously offering you
another chance to join us.
Here's an offer for you!
How about giving back that white
dragon egg you guys stole?
[OTHERS] That's right!
Give it back, you egg thieves!
Oh, but of course!
If young Lute here agrees
to cooperate with us,
then we'd be more than
happy to give back the egg.
So what do you say, my boy?
I'll never help you.
But I will get that egg back!
[DR. MANELGER] Well then,
it seems I have no choice
in the matter.
I suppose I'll just have
to use Cheval after all.
You stay away from Cheval!
Yes, well, unlike you,
my simple little friend,
that Cheval has got
what it takes up here.
What?
He's not wrong.
Sorry, but it's true.
I'm confident Cheval
will be making
that white dragon his
Monstie in no time.
With a little help from this.
[LUTE]
What's that?
[DR. MANELGER]
Oh, ho! Intrigued, are we?
This is my Mecha Kinship Stone,
or "Mechinship Stone" for short.
[ITSY-BITS] We already tried
to hatch the egg with Cheval
using his Kinship
Stone on its own,
but that wasn't enough
to do the trick.
So we came up with this.
[gasps] Wait, Cheval?
Unfortunately, the Kinship
Stones that you Riders possess,
at least on their own,
lack the necessary power to
hatch that particular egg.
Howev--
However, by installing
this Mechinship Stone,
it'll boost the power of your
regular old Kinship Stone
to incredible new
levels of awesomeness!
Which means,
with this baby here,
you can now form Kinship
with that white dragon,
and when you do,
then you can rise up
and be the next
Redan of legend!
You stole my line again,
just as I was about to say it!
That's the second time today!
[LUTE]
The next Redan?
Lute, my boy, this is your final
chance, and your last warning.
So tell me, will
you join us or not?
No, never!
Very well then.
Sounds like you won't be
budging from that position.
My, how unfortunate for you.
[BEATS]
You're the unfortunate one!
[DR. MANELGER]
Huh?
See this?
We managed to get our paws
on your white dragon egg!
Ha.
It was pretty sloppy
of you fellas
to just leave it
unattended like that.
Without this egg,
that Mechinship Stone is
just some gaudy jewelry
that's purely for decoration!
Ha! Serves you right!
Yeah, game over,
ya big meanie!
Oh, wow, awesome job, you guys!
That's Navirou's pals
for you, all right!
[ITSY-BITS laughs]
They fell for it, sir,
hook, like, and sinker!
What now?
What's that mean?
See, the real egg was
right here the whole time!
[ALL]
Huh?
So wait, you mean
this one is fake?
It's bogus? That's
no fair, you cheaters!
When carrying such
precious cargo,
it's only natural to anticipate
all manner of skullduggery
that may arise and take
every precaution necessary
to guard against it!
Ha! Looks like you're
the sloppy ones here!
[ITSY-BITS laughing]
[ITSY-BITS]
Hey, stop that! Knock it off!
[LUTE]
Got it!
Hey! Give that back!
[BEATS]
Lute! Pass it to me!
Coming right up!
Give it back!
[CRYO]
Beats! Over here!
You got it!
[CRYO]
Heads up, Fifi!
[FIFI]
Here, Spex!
[SPEX]
Take it, Floof!
[NAVIROU]
Hey, Floof! Over here!
What a catch!
Well, will you look at that?
Our stellar teamwork,
under the leadership of
yours truly, of course,
managed to get us back
the white dragon egg!
Talk about your Kinship
plays, huh, Lute?
That's right! Too bad for you!
[laughing]
Oh, what a hopelessly sloppy
bunch of fools you are!
The real egg is right here!
[ALL]
Huh?!
They've still got the
real one! Come on!
You really think we'd leave
a legendary egg wide open
and easy to snatch like that?
They must think we're dumb.
We're wasting time. Let's go.
Aye, aye, sir!
Feel free to keep that
beautifully crafted fake egg.
You can use it to play
Kinship all you like.
Oh, no! Watch out, sir!
[NAVIROU]
Way to go, Ratha!
[screams]
Oh, no!
Now there's no way for us to
know which one's the real deal!
What do we do?
With my glorious, painstakingly
accurate craftsmanship,
you'll never be able to
tell those eggs apart!
[ITSY-BITS laughs]
What are you waiting for?
Go fetch the real
one. We're leaving!
Right away, sir!
[ITSY-BITS]
Hmm...
[DR. MANELGER]
What's wrong? Hurry up!
It seems I may have made these
a little too accurate, sir,
because now even I can't
tell which one of 'em
is actually the authentic
white dragon egg!
[NUMBERS, LUTE yelp]
Uh, Lieutenant Pappan? Lilia?
A word please?
Of course.
Based on your reading
of this passage here,
you two arrived
at the conclusion
that there was a Kinship Ore
somewhere on Mount Rhyz.
That's right.
Some of it was a bit ambiguous,
but we did manage to decipher
the words "Mount Rhyz" at least.
We immediately notified Lute
so he could check it out.
Why do you ask, ma'am?
You were mistaken.
What the text actually says is,
"In the direction of the
shadow from Mount Rhyz
as the sun crosses
the meridian."
Oh, my goodness.
But that would mean that
there is no new Kinship Ore
to be found at Mount
Rhyz after all.
Rather, its shadow points toward
the location of one instead!
Oh, no! We have to
alert Lute right away!
[LUTE]
Jeez, what are we gonna do now?
[NAVIROU]
Yeah, if the guy who made 'em
can't tell the difference
between 'em, what hope is there?
[FLOOF] They weally
do wook exactwy awike.
Yep, that sure is some top-notch
replication work right there.
In fact, you might even say
that whoever made 'em
has some serious skills!
[ITSY-BITS laughs]
[ALL]
Hey, this is no laughing matter!
Um, what exactly are
you trying to do, sir?
I'm trying to stand
it on its end.
Uh, good luck with that.
Yeah, you do know
eggs can't stand up?
[NUMBERS]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
Actually, my simple friends,
if you take a close
look at an egg,
its shell is completely covered
in tiny little bumps.
And there's a position in
which you can place it
where those bumps
line up just right
with the egg's
center of gravity.
In fact, all it takes
is three such bumps
to act like a sort of tripod,
stabilizing the egg and
allowing it to stand upright.
[ALL]
Ahh...
Uh, sir, forgive me
for asking this,
but is there a reason
why you felt the need
to give those folks
a rather long-winded
science lesson just now?
In short, the egg that
can stand up vertically
must be the one that's real!
[ALL gasp]
[ITSY-BITS]
Wow, leave it to you, sir!
It just stood right up!
[NAVIROU] Yeah, but so
did both of these guys.
But how?
My eggs truly are
perfect replicas.
[LUTE]
So that science experiment
didn't get us anywhere.
Maybe if I singe 'em a
little with my flame breath,
we'll get some answers.
No, you can't do that,
you'll hard-boil them!
Or, wait, would
that just fry them?
Ah, what are we gonna do?
Y'know, this is all your fault!
There is one sure-fire
way to figure this out.
[LUTE]
Hm?
[DR. MANELGER]
Lute, my boy.
It's really quite
a simple solution.
All that you would
have to do is use
my nifty Mechinship Stone here
to power up your own
inadequate Kinship Stone,
and then try hatching all
three eggs one at a time.
Presto, the egg from which
the white dragon hatches
is clearly the genuine article!
Oh, of course!
We shoulda just tried
that from the beginning!
Right, Doc?
You heard him, Lute.
Let's get that white
dragon hatched
so we can finally figure
out which of these eggs
is the real white dragon egg!
Well, what say you, Lute?
Will you join forces with us?
Like I said before, never!
[DR. MANELGER]
But why?
I felt something special when I
first stumbled upon Ratha's egg.
Like he wanted to be born.
Even though I didn't have
my Kinship Stone yet,
Ratha still hatched for me.
So there has to be a
reason this one won't.
Besides, we can't
just force an egg
to hatch with your little toy!
Oh, poppycock!
My brilliant inventions have
made the impossible possible!
Scientific advances have
simply reached the point
where humans are
now able to control
the hatching of monster eggs!
You can't stand in
the way of progress.
So why not take advantage of
this monumental evolution?
Because real Kinship,
it can make two hearts
become one naturally.
You don't need to manipulate
it or be manipulated by it.
It's just strong emotions
binding you together!
Who needs such a capricious
form of Kinship, anyway?
With "hearts" this
and "emotions" that,
how can you ever trust in
something so unreliable,
that might change on a whim
depending on your
mood or situation?
[LUTE]
No matter how unpredictable,
and no matter how much feelings
may come to change over time,
I trust it!
And my friends. All of them!
Hey! He's got the eggs!
I've got everything
all packed up
and loaded on board
the airship, sir!
[DR. MANELGER]
Well then, let 'er rip!
[NAVIROU]
Hey! Get back here!
C'mon, Lute, after them!
Not now. Just let 'em go, okay?
It's not like
those two can hatch
the white dragon on
their own, anyway.
And honestly, we've got
enough on our plate.
There's still the Black
Blight to worry about.
[BEATS]
Don't sweat it, Number 5.
[NAVIROU]
Hm?
Just leave Manelger and
his little sidekick to us!
Yeah, we won't let him
get away with this.
You just concentrate on locating
that Kinship Ore, all right?
Meanwhile, we'll
keep our sights set
on those delinquents for you,
whatever they may be up to.
I'll twy my vewy best,
even when I feel sweepy.
You guys.
Nothing in the world burns
brighter than my spirit!
Number One.
Beats!
I am of warm heart,
but cool breath.
Number Two.
I am Cryo!
Sparkle-sparkle!
My dazzling beauty is
almost blindingly bright!
Number Three.
Fifi here!
You don't need glasses to
see I'm the brains here.
Number Four.
You can call me Spex!
Leading you onward to
a brighter tomorrow!
Number Five.
Navirou!
Always time for a nap!
Number Six!
Wook, it's me, Floof!
And all together, we are:
[ALL]
The Numbers!
Hey, wait, what about me?
If you insist.
And here's Lute, I guess!
"I guess?" What's
that supposed mean?
[ITSY-BITS]
A thousand apologies, sir.
To think, all that trouble
because I was too darn talented.
But I've finally figured
out which egg's real!
[DR. MANELGER]
Enough of this confusion.
Lose the other two!
You should know by now
I'm only interested in results.
Cheval wasn't on the mountain
and that's all there is to it.
We failed today.
Yes.
But next time, we will
find Cheval, for sure.
I have no doubt about it.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Great Baggi!
A real brainy beast,
with sharp looks, to boot!
Leading packs of Baggi
is what it does best.
It can also put
its foes to sleep
with a special liquid
before doing them in!
Wonder how that compares
to Floof's yawns.
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Our search for Kinship Ore
has brought us to new place.
Wait, is that the
same road as before?
Don't tell me we're lost!
Next time:
"Forest of Confusion"!
Ride On!