[NARRATOR]
The Felyne's name is Navirou!
He's the stalwart
companion to Lute,
a rash but
enthusiastic young boy,
who dreams of becoming the
world's top Monster Rider.
The two first met years
ago in Hakum Village,
and in the time since,
have formed a loving,
albeit strange, relationship.
As Lute has become
a full-fledged Rider,
the unusual Navirou has
never left his side,
serving as a cheerleader,
comedy partner,
and all-around right-hand man.
But most interesting
of all is that Navirou
has no memory of where he's
from, or of his early life.
Nevertheless, Navirou's overcome
obstacle after obstacle,
thanks to his playful
optimism, can-do attitude,
and plenty of donuts.
He and Lute will follow
each other anywhere,
including the deadly and
dangerous Dovan Volcano.
Unfortunately, while
searching for a Kinship Ore
in the mountain,
the duo--and Debli-- triggered
one of Doctor Manelger's traps.
Now prisoners in
the evil doctor's
subterranean laboratory,
they've discovered a group
of super-powered Felynes
calling themselves,
"The Numbers."
And at long last, Navirou's
lost memories came back.
He remembered his original
identity as "Number Five"
and learned the shocking truth
about the super
power modification
given to him by the
monster-mechanizing Manelger.
Rediscovering his past has
made Navirou determined
to take down the evil doctor
and free his old friends!
There's something
Navirou has to do first.
Settle the score with Manelger!
Okay, Lute, you're up!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Numbers, charge!
[laughing]
Hey! Head's up!
[gasps]
What's the plan?
The plan is we use this tank.
You heard him, Spex,
get ready to fire!
[SPEX]
Angle set! Locked and loaded!
You might wanna cover
your ears, big boy.
Fire!
What was that?
What was what?
[gasps]
[LUTE]
You guys, look!
It's Kinship Ore.
Well, well, I see the
Rider is still on the hunt.
What do you think? A marvelous
specimen is it not?
This Kinship Ore will
soon allow me to control
all the monsters of the world!
And on that note,
I'd like to ask you a favor.
In order to maximize
the Ore's power,
I need a Rider's Kinship
Stone, to understand
how the various connections
between them work.
Now, be a good Rider, my boy,
and let me borrow
your Stone for a bit.
In your dreams!
I'll never help you
mind-control monsters!
That's right! They form
Kinship with them!
[DR. MANELGER]
Hm. All right then.
Guess I'll have to
do this the hard way.
Not so fast.
We're the ones pointing
a cannon at you, Doctor!
Now we have the upper hand!
You don't stand a chance
against the Meownzer tank!
Your experimenting
days are done!
Give it up, Manelger!
[DR. MANELGER]
Hmm?
Sir, those are "The Numbers."
The felynes that you
experimented on long ago.
Ohh.
They were failures!
And I'm not about
to let failures
destroy a lifetime of work!
Itsy-Bits!
[ALL gasp]
Reverse, reverse!
[laughing]
[DEBLI]
Uh, guys. What is that?
It's Agnaktor, meow!
I can't believe
he mechanized it!
I do hope you enjoy being
close to the action!
Behold the culmination
of my life's research.
My greatest masterpiece!
[roars]
C'mon, guys, we can
take this thing down!
No way it's beating
the Meownzer tank!
You got that right! Let's roll!
Hey, Manelger.
Get ready for a faceful of
the Numbers fiercest fury!
Hey, what was that?
The engine just shut down.
It must've run out of juice.
What're we gonna do now?
You're up, Number Five.
Got it!
What's the hold up?
Are we gonna fight?
Give us a second!
You can do it, Navirou!
He better charge it quickly!
Number Five?
[NAVIROU grunting]
Nothing.
Huh?
[OTHERS]
What?
Well, that's Navirou for ya.
[CRYO]
Everyone just be cool!
You had it running a few
minutes ago, what's wrong?
Just do what you did
again and we'll live.
Thing is, Navirou can't
remember what he did.
You can do this, Number Five!
[laughing]
Even if it worked,
that rusted pile of bolts
wouldn't leave a scratch
on my mecha-Agnaktor!
Finish them, Itsy-Bits.
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
Boop!
There's nothing to
cry about, friends!
Sure, you're doomed, but if it
wasn't for failures like you,
I never would've perfected
the mecha-Agnaktor!
My subterranean lava laboratory!
Nice work, Lute!
Hit 'em, again!
Now's your chance, Number
Five! Start the tank!
Don't panic, though,
you gotta stay cool.
[NAVIROU]
Right. Got it!
You foolish Rider!
Fire has no effect on a monster
that lives in magma!
Attack again!
Of course, Doctor! Watch this!
[DR. MANELGER laughs]
You can't do a thing when
it's swimming in magma!
[LUTE]
Yeah? And neither can you!
Oh really, is that
what you think?
Got him!
Again!
Hurry, before it comes for us!
Attack their left;
it's a blind spot.
Ah, yes.
[screams]
[LUTE] All right, Ratha,
bank right now!
[screams]
[LUTE]
Way to go, Navirou!
Stop interfering!
A Rider should at
least understand
the scale of our research!
The Kinship Stones
and Ore are the keys
to creating a new union
between man and monster!
I don't care what you call it,
what you want is wrong!
Just think about it, boy!
If we can control monsters,
we can use them to
hunt the bad ones,
creating a peaceful world.
A world where no one will ever
get hurt by a monster again!
You're just making
them your slaves!
If you really want peace,
you'd let monsters and people
live side-by-side in harmony.
Blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
Every time I try to be nice,
you make me resort to force!
Itsy-Bits, revive the Agnaktor
and renew the attack!
Right away, Doctor!
[roars]
[ALL gasp]
Uh?
Oh, no. Look, Doctor,
something's not right!
Did you press the wrong button?
No, it's not that,
it's the Ore!
Wait, what?
No!
[ITSY-BITS gasps]
Is that...?
Great, what's happening now?
Looks like it's
the Black Blight!
And we have to stop it
before it completely
infects that Kinship Ore!
So what are we gonna do?
[ANGNAKTOR roars]
Uh-oh. Now the Blight's
spread to the Agnaktor.
But why would the Black Blight
jump from the Kinship Ore
to a monster like that?
What a fascinating development.
Seems the Kinship Ore exerts
a profound influence
on monsters.
Sir, it's getting worse!
Stop interrupting me!
--[DR. MANELGER] Oh, no!
--[ITSY-BITS] No!
[BOTH yelling]
This is my chance
to save the Ore!
Are-Are we still alive?
[DR. MANELGER]
No! My precious lab!
[ITSY-BITS] Sir, we have
to run, or we'll be next!
There's only one person
who can help us.
I'll send a message the
fastest way I know!
Now fly! Fly to our ally
and get his assistance.
[BOTH scream]
Even if he gets our note,
what makes you think he'll come?
Don't worry, Itsy-Bits.
He hates the Blight more
than anyone I've ever met!
[LUTE]
You okay, Ratha?
[roars]
[LUTE]
It's getting worse.
[NAVIROU]
Numbers to the rescue!
Locking in range and
angle of fire, meow!
[ALL screaming]
We still need to get closer
if we're gonna do
any damage to it!
It's gonna blast us!
Please, close your
eyes, everyone!
[NAVIROU]
Full power!
[NUMBERS]
Charge!
Wake up, Number Six!
You're all clear, Lute!
[LUTE]
Got it!
Sky-High Dive!
[CHIEF OMNA] "When an ebon
darkness is born upon the Earth,
it is then we seek the
coming of the One."
Isn't that from
the Redan legend?
Yes. And more follows in
the great Rider's tale.
About the "dragon white."
That's right.
"Behold!
Redan comes astride
a dragon white,
soaring gallantly
across the heavens.
The great Rider shall
pierce the ebon darkness
and thus reclaim the light."
Or so the legend goes.
[LILIA]
So if the legend is true,
and the Black Blight is
spreading again, then...
Then now is the time
for the white dragon
to return to the world.
That's right.
Only when it is born will
we possess the means
to defeat the Black Blight.
But none of this
will come to pass
if the right person
is not on hand
to hatch the dragon egg.
Cheval.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Mm.
I'm afraid your friend has
become consumed by his hatred.
Cheval...
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
So beautiful.
Wow, Lute. That was amazing.
I've never seen anyone
do that before.
And that's a Rider.
Not too shabby.
[ALL gasp]
[ALL scream]
[NAVIROU screaming]
Something must've
triggered an eruption!
You were too reckless
out there, Lute!
Don't blame me!
[ALL scream]
We're cut off!
We're fine, Number Five!
Get on Ratha and fly
out the ceiling vent!
[NAVIROU]
But what about you guys?!
[BEATS] We're gonna meet up
with the other Felynes
and escape with them!
Don't worry, we know this
place like the back of our paw!
We know every
shortcut down here!
We'll meet up again later!
Okay, we'll see you
in Geo-Fulkright!
[NAVIROU] Huh. Feels like
we're forgetting something.
[DEBLI screams]
[DEBLI] I can't believe
they forgot about me!
I don't like the heat!
I burn too easily!
You forgot about me, didn't you?
[LUTE]
No, we didn't forget, I swear.
[screams]
[LUTE]
What's wrong, Ratha?
Hey, how hard is it
to just fly straight?
Oh, no.
Ah! It's erupting!
What?
[NAVIROU screams]
Ratha, get us outta here!
What's wrong, Ratha? Come on!
I know you can do this!
[DEBLI]
I'm alive?
I'm alive.
That was a close one, Ratha.
A little too close.
Were you just gonna
let me dangle?
[LUTE]
Hey, careful climbing up here!
There's a weight limit, y'know!
[DEBLI] Jeez, now you're
calling me fat? C'mon!
[LUTE] I'm just looking
out for Ratha's back!
[DEBLI] Whatever! You
know Ratha can handle it!
[NAVIROU]
Ah! We're gonna fall!
[LUTE, DEBLI, NAVIROU scream]
That was my first
real Monstie ride.
Thanks for saving us back
there. Nice job, Ratha.
[LUTE gasps]
[LUTE]
What's wrong, Ratha?
[gasps]
[RATHA roars]
It's impossible!
The Black Blight infected Ratha!
No way.
Once a monster has been
infected with the Black Blight,
they'll go berserk and run amok,
never regaining their senses.
Lute! Use your Kinship Stone!
[LUTE]
Avinia?
Only the power of your
Kinship can purify Ratha!
Hurry, before it's too late!
The power of our Kinship.
Here goes.
Oh, man!
Calm down, Ratha.
[NAVIROU screams]
[roars]
Ratha, remember. Please
remember our Kinship!
It worked! And just in time.
Look, the Blight's
leaving Ratha's body!
[LUTE] No! Rathalos,
what's happening to you?
[NAVIROU] You think
Ratha's gonna be okay?
He'll be fine,
he's just resting.
Thank you for saving us.
But how did you know exactly
where to find us, Avinia?
I heard there was a Kinship Ore
somewhere around
the Dovan Volcano.
So I came here to find out if
it was infected with the Blight.
And I saw you guys.
That's pretty lucky! Thank you!
Sure!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Ratha?
Is the Blight coming back?
[AVINIA]
Ratha will be fine.
All this time, his
body's been fighting
to keep the Black Blight
from completely taking over.
It must've been so hard.
You mean the Blight isn't new?
[LUTE] Ratha, what's wrong?
C'mon, pull up!
Ratha's been so sick...
and I didn't notice.
Ratha being sick also explains
why he didn't come
when you called.
Ratha, don't worry,
I'm here for you now.
I won't leave till
you're all better!
[LUTE chuckles]
[LUTE]
I like petting you, too, bud.
In a way, you are
kinda Ratha's dad.
[RATHA roars]
[ALL yelp]
[yelps]
The Volcano's erupting again!
Your Rathalos has been
afflicted with the Blight.
It must be destroyed.
Cheval, no.
[LILIA]
The Book of Numbers !
Hey, it's me, Lilia of
the Royal Scriveners,
with an analysis of the
Felynes in the Numbers.
Here's who we're
covering this week.
[LILIA]
Number Four, Spex.
This bespectacled Felyne is
the brains of the Numbers
and has the traits
of the Kecha Wacha.
Number Five, our
ol' friend Navirou.
With his lightning attacks,
this chatty Felyne takes
after the monster, Zinogre.
And finally, Number Six, Floof.
This fuzzy-cutie
is like a Basarios
and can exhale sleeping gas.
The Monstie Manual
will be back next time.
I'll see you around, gang!
[LUTE]
Hey, it's me, Lute!
What are you doing, Cheval?
I thought we were like family!
Ratha isn't Blighted anymore!
Next time: "Parting Ways."
Ride On!