[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
On his first visit home
to Hakum Village in ages,
Lute unexpectedly
reunited with Cheval.
Your self-centeredness...
and your sheer arrogance...
That is what killed my mother.
[NARRATOR] The time has come
for Lute to face his past.
[horn blaring]
[VILLAGER A]
A monster's coming!
[VILLAGER B]
Everyone, get to the shrine!
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Please, take this, Chief.
If worse comes to worst and...
...I fall, I want you to
give it to my young son,
once he's ready for it.
[sighs]
[CHIEF OMNA]
It seems the time has come.
[NAVIROU] Navirou will
make you feel better!
C'mon, stay positive!
That's what you'd say if
Navirou was in your shoes!
[LUTE]
I just...
All this time, I believed
in the power of Kinship.
But now... What do I do now?
[CHIEF OMNA]
Lute, to answer that question,
you must journey to...
...the Tower of Illusion.
The Tower of Illusion?
[CHIEF OMNA]
The Tower is a place of legend.
A place that bestows great
wisdom upon only those
who can pass its trials
of mind and spirit.
And although you
will suffer greatly
throughout your time there,
I promise that if you
endure this trial,
you will find what you seek.
Find what I seek?
All right. Let's go.
I'll do the Tower's trial.
Whatever it takes to discover
the power of Kinship,
I'll do it.
Of course.
Where's the Tower
of Illusion, Chief?
It's ocean as far as I can see.
We're almost there.
We should set up camp
here for the night.
[NAVIROU whimpering]
It feels like something's
watching us.
[LUTE]
What kinda something?
An unspeakably evil
being of cosmic horror!
Giant! And hungry!
[NAVIROU whimpers]
[roaring]
[screams]
[thudding]
Oh, no.
Ah!
Lute, it's here, run!
[gasps]
[AVINIA] After all that,
he treats me like a monster?
[LUTE]
Avinia?
[AVINIA] You're the one who
asked me to come, Navirou.
[AVINIA] I was still on Naubaka
Island when I got his letter.
Navirou told me he was
beside himself with worry.
When I read that, I knew things
were bad, so I came right away.
Is that really true?
Navirou was not
"beside himself"!
No? That's what you wrote.
[NAVIROU]
Hey! You don't have to show him!
[LUTE chuckles]
Navirou, thank you.
And you, too.
What are you talking about?
Helping those in trouble
is what friends do.
You should know, you're the
one who taught me that, Lute.
Avinia.
Thank you.
[NAVIROU]
Hm-hm.
It's time, Lute.
[LUTE]
Chief Omna?
The way to the Tower
of Illusion is now open.
[gasps]
[LUTE]
I still don't see it.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Just wait.
Behold. The Tower of Illusion.
Help him. Please
guide Lute on his way.
Here we go.
Whoa, it's pitch black!
[NAVIROU squeals]
Man. It's creepier in the light!
They say that any person
with doubt in his heart
who overcomes the
Tower of Illusion
will then be led to the truth.
You know a lot about
the Tower, huh?
Yes.
Because I've been here once
before to solve my own problem.
[LUTE]
What?
[AVINIA] When the Black Blight
attacked my hometown,
I lost everything
I ever had or loved.
I was all alone.
The only thing I
felt was despair.
At that point, I decided
I'd be better off
if the Blight had taken me, too.
But in the Tower, I learned
I wasn't really alone.
I still had Frostfang
walking by my side.
All that heartache, and hope
was right there in front of me.
If I hadn't subjected myself
to the Tower of Illusion,
I never would've
overcome my despair
and remembered what's
truly important in life.
[LUTE]
Aw, it's a dead end.
Let's--
Avinia! Navi!
[yelps]
Where did this come from?
This Tower's so weird.
What's going on here?
What? Hakum Village?
[horn blaring]
Yo! Listen up, Nargacuga!
Guess what...
Navirou, what're you doing?
[gasps]
Wait, what'm I doing?
I was in the Tower
of Illusion, but now...
Hey, that's enough, Lute!
This is no time to be spouting
off random nonsense!
Go stop that Nargacuga
so we can get some of Mrs.
Vlau's soup before it runs out!
The Black Blight!
[gasps]
Wait a sec.
This is the day she--
[roars]
Look out!
All according to plan!
[NAVIROU]
Now to signal Cheval!
[horn blares]
Is this--? This isn't possible!
[LUTE] How did I end up
back at Hakum Village
at this exact moment?
[LUTE]
Did I travel through time?
That doesn't make any sense!
It's Cheval!
All right, bury it! Go!
Yes, it's totally buried! Stomp!
Let's see.
Yay, it held!
We stopped the Nargacuga!
[ALL cheer]
[LUTE] This is crazy.
Everything's exactly the same.
Oh, no!
Guys, you gotta get
away from there, now!
[ALL scream]
[LUTE]
Are you guys all right?
[CHEVAL]
Yeah.
No! It can't happen again!
I have to stop it!
This time, I will save her!
Let's Ride On!
Rathalos!
Oh, wow. Ratha.
[RATHA roars]
You feel the same way
as me, don'tcha, boy?
Let's set things right!
[LUTE] I've thought
about this for so long.
One chance. One chance to
do this day over again.
I can keep everyone safe!
Mrs. Vlau and all
of Hakum Village!
This time I'll do it!
I will save her!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[LUTE]
Mrs. Vlau!
You have to go back!
The Nargacuga's on the loose!
I forgot something important
at home! I have to save it!
[LUTE]
Wait!
Come back!
[roaring]
What if this doesn't work?
No! It has to!
Keep it up, Ratha!
We've gotta lure it away
from Cheval's house!
No! It's all happening again!
[screams]
[LUTE]
Mrs. Vlau!
[horn blaring]
[LUTE]
No!
Yo! Listen up, Nargacuga!
Yes! That's what we want!
[LUTE] What's going on?
I'm right back where I started!
Right! Now to signal
Cheval's team!
[LUTE]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU] Where're you going,
Lute? We're not done yet!
This time, I'm getting
the egg before Mrs. Vlau!
[NAVIROU] What egg?
What're you talking about?
Lute, you can't leave!
We need you to follow
through on the plan!
[LUTE]
Mrs. Vlau!
[VLAU]
Is that Lute?
Don't worry! I'll go
get the egg for you!
No, hold on!
[VLAU]
Lute, wait!
Mrs. Vlau, no!
[VLAU]
I was worried about you!
You have to go back to the
shrine before you get hurt!
[thudding]
Ratha!
[LUTE]
Take the egg and stay here.
I'll draw it away!
Lute! That's enough!
Get back here!
[LUTE]
This is gonna work.
[yells]
Yes! We're stronger than
before, we can do this!
Sky-High Dive!
All right!
[gasps]
[LUTE]
No!
[horn blaring]
[gasps]
Yo! Listen up, Nargacuga!
[LUTE]
Again? I'm back at the start.
What am I supposed to do?
[LUTE]
Better think of something fast.
I've got to keep everyone safe!
Right! Now to signal
Cheval's team!
[LUTE]
Ride On! Rathalos!
[NAVIROU]
Lute, you can't leave!
We need you to follow
through on the plan!
[LUTE]
Guys, wait! Forget the plan!
I'll take care of everything!
Are you crazy?
And disobey Dan?
Yeah, wait, what's going on?
I don't have time to
explain what's happening,
so you're just gonna have
to trust me on this one.
Okay. I trust you, Lute.
[LUTE]
Thanks!
[LUTE] I'm tired of watching
everyone I love suffer.
This time, I'll keep
everyone safe!
No one's getting hurt tonight!
[LUTE]
Ready, Ratha?
Ratha, fire!
[LUTE screams]
[LUTE]
Nothing I try works.
No matter what I do,
I can't save anyone.
I... I can't keep everyone safe.
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Are you giving up, Lute?
[LUTE]
Dad? Is that you?
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Tell me, what is Kinship?
I can't. I don't know
what it means anymore.
[LUTE'S FATHER]
All this time, I've watched you.
Your joys and your heartache.
It's your desire to share
your life with others
that keeps driving you forward,
that pushes you to reach
your fullest potential.
This drive, this emotion,
that is Kinship.
You're not alone.
You have friends who want
to share in your life.
They're waiting.
Like Ratha!
Yeah, I do want
to share my life.
With him and everyone else!
That's right. I'm not giving up!
Let's try this one more time!
[CHEVAL]
Lute!
[MILLE, HYORO]
[NAVIROU]
Lute!
[gasps]
You guys. I'm sorry.
[NAVIROU]
Sorry for what?
[LUTE]
If I was strong enough,
I could've defeated the
Nargacuga, on my own.
I convinced myself
that was true.
But what Cheval said was right.
I was just being conceited.
When did I say that?
[LUTE] I should've depended
more on you, Cheval.
I should've depended
more on all of you.
Joined forces with you!
Help me! I'm not strong
enough to do this alone!
We have to Ride
together, as one!
Our hearts are joined as one.
Let's go. Let's
face it together.
Oh, Cheval.
Right!
Hey, uh, sorry to
interrupt the romance,
but we're here, too, y'know!
That's right!
And Navirou!
I didn't forget you!
If we all work together,
I know we can run that
Nargacuga out of town
before someone gets hurt!
[RATHA roars]
'Kay, it's time for Operation:
"Lure-Nargacuga-Away-from-the
Village-As-Safely-As-Possible"!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[horn blaring]
[MILLE]
C'mon, you wanna piece of us?
[HYORO]
Yoo-hoo! Over here!
[MILLE]
Now it's mad!
It's gaining on us!
Hey, Nargacuga! Come and get me!
[LUTE]
I got this!
Well, what are you
waiting for?! Attack me!
It worked.
--Yeah, we did it!
--Hey, it's gone!
Cheval.
Now that's the
power of Kinship!
Cheval. That's right!
[GAMIGAMI]
Great job, hatchlings!
Sorry we took so long.
Hatchlings, ya say?
After today, they're
full-fledged Riders!
And in top form, no less!
That was some great
teamwork, guys!
Thanks.
Mrs. Vlau.
I, um... Well, I...
[VLAU]
Thank you, Lute.
[gasps]
Please, take care of Cheval.
You had us worried, Lute.
You were in this
really deep sleep
and we couldn't wake you up!
Do you feel okay?
Well?
Yeah, but I realized...
I always thought if
I'd been stronger,
I could've saved Mrs. Vlau.
But I was wrong.
I'm not strong.
That's why I need to
fight alongside friends.
I can't go alone, but
if we all join together,
we can protect what we love.
That's Kinship.
And I believe in its power
more than anything!
That's the spirit, buddy!
[LUTE gasps]
[NAVIROU]
Whoa!
It'll be high tide,
soon. Better move.
Hey, Chief. I dug out that
special somethin' you wanted.
Great. That's
perfect timing, Dan.
So, how was the
Tower of Illusion?
From the look on your face,
I assume it went well.
This is for you.
Just before his passing,
your father asked
that I watch over this
and give it to you
only when your skills
had reached the
appropriate level.
From my dad?
[CHIEF OMNA]
Impressive, isn't it?
This is the suit of armor
your father wore
when he was about your age.
[LUTE]
Cheval, the Kinship we share,
I'll never stop believing in it!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Barioth!
Avinia's ice cold
monster sends a chill
down enemy spines with its
huge, amber-colored tusks.
Barioth can even run
super-fast on the ice
by gripping it with the
spikes on its wings.
Talk about cool!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] There's a tempered
monster in the Babda Rainforest!
What? Kinship Attacks
won't work?
Next time: "Brachydios
the Destroyer"!
Ride On!