[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Despite growing up
together like brothers,
Lute and his best friend
Cheval parted ways.
Disenchanted and
seeking answers,
Lute underwent an introspective
trial at the Tower of Illusion,
ultimately learning what the
power of Kinship really is.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Impressive, isn't it?
This is the suit of
armor your father wore
when he was just about
your age, Lute.
From my dad?
[NARRATOR]
Lute inherited a suit of armor
from his late father, and now,
taking to heart all of the
feelings contained within it,
continues on his journey.
You got a sec?
[LUTE]
Mr. Reverto? Is something wrong?
[REVERTO]
Hm? Rathalos gear, huh?
That's right,
my dad left it for me.
I see. Well, use it with care.
Anyway, Lute, I'd like you
to help me with a Quest.
A Quest?
Yeah, we'd love to, but we're
a little busy right now,
saving the world from
the Black Blight.
Well, actually,
it just so happens
the target monster for
this particular Quest
is one that's been afflicted
with the Black Blight.
Well, in that case...
[NAVIROU]
Hmm...
Another Blighted monster?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
A real tough customer who's
tearing up the Babda Rainforest.
Well, then we should
dispatch a Rider to--
[SIMONE]
That won't be necessary.
I'm leaving this
entirely up to Reverto.
Oh, Captain Simone!
I don't mean to
question your judgment,
but if the monster is Blighted,
then won't Reverto
need the Kinship Stone?
Yes, which is why he'll
be bringing Lute.
Still, I'd like it to be Reverto
who puts this to rest.
Hey, why're you
tagging along, Popola?
Come on, can't leave Reverto
flying solo on this one.
Always gotta stick
your nose in, huh?
[LUTE]
So the Blighted monster's
s'posed to be 'round
here somewhere?
[REVERTO]
Yep.
[POPOLA] According to
the Scriveners, at least.
[gasps]
Mister, what's goin' on?
[LUTE]
Whoa, what's that?
[NAVIROU] A road? In the
middle of the jungle?
[REVERTO]
That is a monster path.
Never heard of such a thing.
It's just a path formed
by large monsters
as they pass through
the vegetation.
Well, a pretty big monster
must've made this one then,
judging by the width of it.
Yeah.
My guess is, it came through
this area a few days ago.
So in that case, wouldn't it
be a long way off by now?
Most likely.
Looks like the Black Blight's
spreading out here, too.
Ooh, that is one
funky-lookin' haze.
Hey, wait, what the
heck is that stuff?
Some kinda nectar?
No, don't!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAVIROU screams]
Watch yourselves.
That stuff was a
Brachydios slime mold.
A Brachydios?
Don't those usually
live in volcanic areas?
Why would one be out
here in the forest?
[REVERTO]
Well, on rare occasions,
a Brachydios will adapt to
live in another habitat,
but not this one.
This monster's lost.
It's originally from a volcano,
but being afflicted
with the Blight,
it probably doesn't even
know where it is anymore,
let alone how to get home.
Wait, how can you tell all that?
I didn't mention it before,
but this particular specimen
is a tempered monster that
I've been after for years.
Brachydios the Destroyer.
Brachydios the Destroyer?
A tempered monster?
[SIMONE]
Yes.
Every once in a great while,
a tremendously powerful
aberration of a monster
may crop up within a species.
So if it's
tremendously powerful,
does that mean it's immortal?
Well, obviously,
no living creature
is ever actually immortal.
But a monster at that level
would be nearly impossible
for the average
Hunter to defeat.
The Guild gives these
monsters special names,
and they always take
great care to issue
these extra-dangerous Quests
with an abundance of caution.
Because of their strength,
the Hunters have come
to respectfully refer
to these creatures as
"tempered monsters."
I see. So that's why
it had to be Reverto.
Well, yes, but also, they
have a history, those two do.
Oh, huh?
[REVERTO] The Guild named it
"Brachydios the Destroyer."
[POPOLA] All of the Hunters who
tried to slay it were defeated,
one after another.
[REVERTO]
When I first encountered it,
I was just starting out
with the Guild.
Hot-blooded as I was,
I decided to take on
a tempered monster
to make a name for myself.
Just so happened
to be that Brachy.
[REVERTO]
Wait up, Brachy. I'm still...
I faced it over and over again,
but every single time, it
wrecked me something fierce.
[REVERTO]
I haven't lost yet.
Brachy!
[REVERTO]
That day marked a turning point.
Brachy just vanished,
and there was no word
of any other Hunter
finishing it off.
I've wondered about
it ever since.
That's gotta be some monster
if it's even too much for you.
Just a regular Brachydios
is nothing to sneeze at,
but a tempered one?
That can't be good at all.
[whimpers]
You're not kidding.
I couldn't land a single blow.
And when I looked into its eyes,
I felt like... it was
saying something.
[LUTE]
Really? Like what?
[REVERTO]
"Surpass me."
Y'know, that's a pretty Rider-y
thing for you to say, Mister.
Yeah, I guess it is, but that's
what it felt like to me, anyway.
Seriously? A monster
talking to a Hunter?
Mew know that could
never happen, right?
No, I think maybe it could.
[OTHERS]
Hm?
Monsters have minds
of their own.
And if it could happen
with any Hunter,
then I think it'd
have to be you.
Yeah, maybe so.
But now there's no way
I'll ever be sure.
After all, that beast has been
stricken with the Black Blight.
It's no longer "Brachydios
the Destroyer," not anymore.
Wow, so even
super-tough monsters
can be stricken with the Blight.
All I know is,
I've gotta resolve
things with that monster.
The Captain of the Scriveners
has given me that opportunity.
Oh, you mean Simone?
That's right.
She knows all about
the connection
between the two of us,
which is the reason she
asked me to slay it.
But I only agreed
to accept the Quest
on the condition that
I could bring you along.
Was it because you needed
a Rider here with you
to purify it?
I guess. But you two can just
stand back and watch, 'kay?
This Quest is my responsibility.
Yeah, but--
It's me who has to take
down that Brachydios.
It's close.
[LUTE]
But look.
The monster path comes
to an end right here.
[gasps]
Hey! Everyone be quiet!
[NAVIROU yelps]
I can't believe we walked
straight into a trap.
So this is what a tempered
monster looks like, huh?
Brachydios the Destroyer.
Long time no see.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU, LUTE yelp]
All right!
You guys stay back there.
Are you sure?
This one is my quarry.
[yells]
It's no use!
[gasps] Oh, no!
Reverto's in trouble!
Reverto?
I told you, this fight
is between me and Brachy.
[roars]
Reverto!
Navirou can't watch!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's go!
Ooh! The new gear!
Somehow I feel stronger now!
C'mon, Ratha!
Let's show 'im what
we're capable of, boy!
Pull up!
Sky-High Dive!
Uh-oh, it's acting
kinda funny!
Careful, Lute. He's tough.
What the heck?
The Brachydios just jumped!
[gasps]
[LUTE screams]
[NAVIROU]
Lute!
C'mon, Lute, stay with us!
What now? What should
Navirou do now?
[NAVIROU screams]
[REVERTO]
Brachy, wait!
Please! Wait!
Don't leave, Brachy!
[LUTE]
Where am I?
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Lute.
[LUTE]
Who's that?
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Son.
[LUTE]
Dad?
[LUTE'S FATHER]
That armor, it suits you.
[LUTE]
Yeah!
But... I lost.
And with a Kinship
Attack, no less.
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Listen, Lute.
A Rider's Kinship Attack
can vary in strength
depending on their Kinship
with that particular monster.
You must first feel
that Kinship.
And then, put your trust in it.
[LUTE] Feel my Kinship?
And trust in it.
[LUTE'S FATHER]
Lute, Kinship never goes away.
Feel your Kinship.
[LUTE]
Dad?
Wait! Dad!
Dad, wait!
Oh, hey, look who's
finally waking up.
That was close one.
Uh, yeah, I musta just...
Were you having a dream?
I was. My dad, he...
Saved your life.
You're pretty lucky
he left you that armor.
Yeah, there's not
a scratch on mew.
But what about the Brachydios?
Beats me. Just ran
off somewhere.
I see.
Well, I guess we failed
that Quest, huh?
Between Reverto
being so outmatched
and Ratha's Sky-High Dive
not working anymore,
we didn't stand a chance.
Yeah, that's right.
You guys should go on home now.
That goes for you, too, Popola.
Reverto!
But then what're you
gonna do, Mister?
I have to finish this,
no matter what.
That's crazy!
You're letting your obsession
with that Brachydios
cloud your judgment!
Me and Brachy,
we're just the same.
You think you and Brachydios
the Destroyer are the same?
Wait, but you don't secrete
any weird exploding juices.
Pretty sure that's
not what he meant.
My mind plays tricks
on me sometimes.
Like, in the same way
that it seemed like
Brachy was speaking to me,
I've got this
overwhelming feeling
that I'm able to
talk right back.
We're past being
"Hunter" and "hunted."
Neither Hunter nor monster.
We're both simply beasts.
[LUTE]
Oh, you mean like that
"be the forest, be the beast"
thing you talked about before?
That's right.
Just feels like
everything in this world
may have started
out as one, y'know?
Oh, yeah, totally.
Navirou gets it.
Sure, sure, sure.
Turns out... Brachy was
talking to me earlier.
[REVERTO]
And now...
...now I truly believe the
intent I saw deep in its eyes.
What it was saying to
me was... "Defeat me."
Well, I believe that
you have a Kinship
with that Brachydios, Mister.
You think I have a
Kinship with Brachy?
Riders aren't the only
ones who can form Kinship.
You Hunters can form
Kinship with monsters, too.
I just know it.
So you keep on fighting to
your heart's content, okay!
Whoa, are you sure?
Yeah, but if you run into
trouble, I'm taking over!
I'll be counting on you.
Now wait just a second!
Your Sky-High Dive
isn't working right now,
so how are you gonna
fight this thing?
Yeah, that's right!
Mew should both return to
Gildegaran to regroup first!
We'll stop it with
the power of Kinship!
[NAVIROU, POPOLA]
What?!
[NAVIROU]
It left the jungle.
[REVERTO]
Well, it may be Blighted,
but with what little
mind it has left,
Brachy could still be searching
for someplace similar
to its volcanic homeland.
It's Brachydios the Destroyer.
Sorry I left you
hangin' there, Brachy.
[yells]
Reverto's so calm and collected!
Darn right! Think he'll win?
Sure feels like
this could be it!
What now?
That light's troubling!
Reverto!
All right, Brachy.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's do this!
[yells]
Hey, Lute! A little help?
Ratha! Full speed ahead!
Brachydios the Destroyer, I will
stop you and the Black Blight!
Thanks to my Kinship with Ratha!
You've got Kinship
with Navirou, too!
And with my father, as well.
All this Kinship will
be my strength!
What's that light?
Now climb!
[yells]
Ya see that?
That was an even sky-er,
higher Sky-High Dive!
Now that is what Navirou
calls a Sky Extreme!
"Two kinships shall
be joined together,
as the Hunter becomes the Rider.
When there is Kinship,
then there is light.
When there is no Kinship,
there is darkness.
And the Black Dread
born out of the darkness
will stain both heaven and
earth as blackest jet."
Hey, wait, that's from the
mural of Redan, isn't it?
Yes, and I've been thinking,
the Black Blight isn't just
the Riders' problem.
Better to say this is
a problem for Hunters,
indeed, all humans to face.
Fortunately, I'm confident
Reverto will understand that.
And that's why you
gave him this Quest.
[NAVIROU] The Black
Blight is disappearing!
Brachydios the Destroyer,
you have truly been
my finest friend.
Reverto.
Uh, Mister, were we
right to do this?
[REVERTO]
Yes.
So, Hunters can form Kinship
with monsters, too, huh?
Yep.
[REVERTO]
Thanks to you,
I think I finally get
what you meant
about how we're two
sides of the same coin.
It's up to us to stop
the Black Blight,
and stop your friend, too.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Brachydios!
It doles out ultra-effective
blows with its giant front legs,
just like a boxer!
And its exploding slime-mold
attack is a real doozy!
No wonder Reverto
was so obsessed
with this tempered monster!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Cheval sent Rathi away,
but is that really what you want
as your new Monstie, Cheval?
Next time: "The
Nargacuga Returns"!
Ride On!