[LUTE] Ratha!
What's wrong? Stop running!
What's gotten into you
all of the sudden?
Hey! Wait up for me!
[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash, but enthusiastic fellow
who dreams of becoming
the world's top Monster Rider.
For now, he's still
an apprentice Rider.
Just between us,
he hasn't even gotten the
hang of riding his Monstie.
Hey, Lute. Why is
Ratha acting so weird?
It's out of character for
him to freak out like that.
Yeah.
[NARRATOR] Lute has grown up
alongside Cheval and Lilia,
his two closest friends.
Cheval is a fellow
apprentice Rider.
While Lilia has dreams of
leaving their small village
and seeing what the
world has to offer.
[CHEVAL] It's not like him at
all. There's gotta be a reason.
I wonder what.
I've got no idea.
[BOTH chuckle]
The Kometa twins strike again!
Slow down, Ratha!
[DAN] That's enough exercise
for today! Whoa, Ratha!
[RATHA roars]
Leave it to Dan. Piece of cake.
He had a tough time actually.
You're in poor form.
What's bothering you?
Yeah, what's up, Ratha?
I've never seen you
suddenly go crazy like that.
Do you have a stomachache?
[LILIA gasps]
I think I found the problem!
[DAN, LUTE]
Huh?
[LUTE]
What the heck is that?
[LUTE] Of all the pranks...
Who would do this?
Pretty rotten sticking it in
a place he couldn't scratch.
[DAN] Even a good boy like Ratha
is bound to get annoyed by that.
Do we have any suspects?
My guess:
It's someone who craves
attention and loves jokes.
[NAVIROU humming]
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
Yes, yes.
Navirou's so spellbinding
you're lost in admiration.
Hardly.
Absolutely not.
Sorry, but no.
[NAVIROU yelps]
What other explanation is
there to gaze at Navirou?
We were wondering if you
attached this stick
man to Ratha.
Ha!
Like Navirou, comedic genius,
would use such lowbrow humor.
Without any hesitation.
No doubt in my mind.
Yeah.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Unfortunately for you,
Navirou has an air-tight ablibi
'cause he's been eating
donuts all afternoon.
No offense, but that's
a terrible alibi.
It sounds suspicious.
[LUTE]
Mh-hm.
Innocent until proven guilty.
Navirou was too engrossed
in those delectable donuts
to commit a crime!
That doesn't make
any sense, Navirou.
Forget about it.
I'm gonna use my detective
skills to find the culprit.
Come on. You need to apologize.
[DAN]
Hm?
What's the story, Genie?
I found the guilty party.
These two here
confessed to the prank.
[LILIA] Ah! None other than
the Kometas' mischief twins!
Um. I guess.
You know them as
Den-Den and Lin-Lin.
Of course!
They've heard all about
your jokes, Den-Den.
your jokes, Lin-Lin.
[BOTH laugh]
That wasn't even a joke!
[TWINS yelp]
[DAN] Whoa! Whoa!
Let's all just settle down.
I can handle these
two, thank you.
So why don't you leave
the reprimanding to me?
Yeah, okay, I guess
you're right, Dan.
You two!
The next time you do
something to Ratha,
I'm gonna get you
back twice as bad!
Believe Navirou, when it
comes payback pranks,
no one holds a candle to Lute.
Right!
Ah, jeez.
Yep.
It's hard to imagine Lute and
Navirou aren't secretly twins.
[DEN-DEN]
Hmph.
You said it!
Are their parents still
out of town buying supplies?
Yes.
That probably explains the
twin's spike in mischief.
They were acting up as
soon as their folks left,
but it's getting out of hand.
I bet those two don't even
think they did anything wrong.
[LILIA]
Probably not.
Who can blame them?
Pranks are the best.
Yeah, I know right?
When I was a kid,
I was always playing jokes
and getting yelled at,
and I never saw
anything wrong with it.
But after being
pranked like that,
I see how annoying it can be.
You know, pranking them would
make you feel a lot better.
[LUTE]
Huh?
[LUTE laughs]
Something like that?
[LUTE laughing]
What? Where'd that come from?!
Den-Den and Lin-Lin may have
had something to do with it.
Lilia.
Do you think it's possible
to mix up a potion
that would make
those two behave?
You know, like the opposite
of an Energy Drink.
Something that tastes
bitter and disappointing!
Like life itself!
Or you could just notice when
you're being scribbled on.
[NAVIROU yelps]
[DAN] Now listen up,
Den-Den and Lin-Lin.
I know you two get lonely
when your parents have to
leave town on business,
but pulling pranks on monsters
doesn't help the
situation at all.
They're not here for
creating mischief.
Riders form a Kinship with
their Monsties. Remember that.
After all, you wanna be Riders
when you grow up, don't ya?
No way!
Nope-ity nope!
What happens if you make
a monster really mad?
You think it'd share
your sense of humor?
We aren't afraid
of any monsters!
We say "Bring 'em on!"
Yeah!
Laugh it up,
but don't forget the only
monsters you've seen
are the ones we keep in stables.
Right.
Playing tricks on wild
Monsties is dangerous
and won't end well for you.
We don't care!
Yeah! So what?
Everything we're saying is going
in one ear and out the other.
We can't blame them.
They're just kids.
I bet the poor tykes are
playing jokes out of loneliness.
What do you know, dummy?
We couldn't be happier!
We're not lonely!
[LIN-LIN]
Not at all!
As a matter of fact,
we're in top form!
We're in top form!
[TWINS laughing]
[DEN-DEN] Who's in top form?
We're in top form!
Guess this'll take a bit
longer than I thought.
Well, the only thing we
can do is hope their pranks
don't get any worse.
[VLAU]
Is that so?
Typical Den-Den and Lin-Lin.
Up to their old tricks again.
It makes me so mad!
Good news.
Frustration makes Navirou hungry
and these donuts hit the spot!
Why don't you clean
off the drawing?
[NAVIROU]
Nope. Donuts are first priority.
You always cook these soufflés
so delicious, Mrs. Vlau.
[chuckles]
Thank you for the
compliment, Lilia.
Do you know how I make
all this wonderful food
for folks to enjoy?
It's because of Den-Den and
Lin-Lin's parents, the Kometas.
They leave town on
purchasing trips
and bring back supplies
for the villagers.
Now I remember!
[VLAU] There's lots
of fruits and veggies
we don't grow in Hakum Village.
Or it could be meats, spices,
pots, different medicines.
Whatever the people need,
the Kometas buy
and deliver it to us.
That's the reason we're
able to live comfortably.
Even Navirou is in awe of
how great the Kometas are.
How did such stellar parents
wind up with such sassy twins?
Those two must be lonely.
Their parents work so hard.
Lonely?
The purchasing trips
last half a month.
Den-Den and Lin-Lin
are still pretty small
for their parents to be out
of the house that long.
I guess so.
[VILLAGERS laughing, chattering]
[MOTHER A]
Yummy, isn't it?
[DAUGHTER A]
I want seconds!
[FATHER A]
It's really good, honey.
[SON A]
Tasty!
Hey, Den-Den.
When are Mama and Papa
coming back this time?
Whenever they finish
doing all the shoppin'
for the villagers, duh!
Yeah, but how long
does that take?
Five sleeps long?
Or maybe ten sleeps?
I'm not gonna bother countin'!
It's not like I'm
lonely or anything!
Then I'm not gonna
count them, either!
[DEN-DEN]
Right?
[LIN-LIN]
Right!
Hey! You guys like donuts?
Come over to my house!
Help me gobble 'em up
before Navirou eats em all!
[NAVIROU grunts]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Wow! You live all by yourself
in this house, Lute?
I'm not alone here.
I've got Ratha for company.
Oh. And that.
Navirou has a name!
They're your friends, but you
don't have a mommy or a daddy?
Yeah, of course I do!
They're right here!
[chuckles]
[TWINS]
Hm?
[LUTE] It's the same
for you and your parents!
Yours have just gone
shopping, that's all.
I know.
But sometimes I wish
Mama and Papa
wouldn't do any shoppin'
and that way they could
stay home with us forever!
Don't say that, Lin-Lin!
I'm sorry, Den-Den.
Who's thirsty for a drink?
I made them especially
for you two.
[ALL yelp]
I'm standing right here.
Why are you making
those expressions?
Um, it's just--
Wait, before you drink
that, prepare yourselves.
What I mean is--
What he means is hold
your breath first!
And whatever you do,
don't sniff it!
What's it supposed to do?
What kinda drink is it?
[LILIA chuckles]
Let's just say
I made them special
so you two would
be in a good mood.
Until your mom and dad
get back from their trip!
It won't matter 'cause we're
already in a good mood.
But we'll still try it!
Yeah!
[BOTH]
Down the hatch!
Uh-oh.
They're really chugging it.
Please don't die.
I know this taste.
Just the way Mama makes it!
[BOTH]
Scrumptious!
[ALL yelp]
There's no way!
Impossible!
They drank it and liked it!
What do you mean?
Oh! Nothing! Nothing at all!
You know what?
I always make my drinks
with ingredients
your parents bring back from
purchasing trips they go on.
I bet that's why the flavor
tastes so familiar.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
No, no, no.
[LILIA]
"No" what?
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Oh, um, nothing.
Do you know the reason our
village is so prosperous
and I'm able to mix
different kinds of drinks?
It's because your mom
and dad are kind enough
to go shopping and find us
all sorts of amazing things!
Yeah!
Mom and dad bought
me this hairpin
after they came back
from one of their trips.
And this for me!
You know what?
Whenever it got cold,
kinda like it is today,
Mama would always make us drinks
that taste exactly like
ones you gave us!
Oh, she does?
We looked forward
to it so much,
as soon as she gave the signal,
we'd run back to the house
as fast as we could.
A signal?
[BOTH]
Uh-huh!
[LIN-LIN]
"It's time for dinner you two!
Come on home as
fast as you can!"
That signal.
It's dinner time!
I wonder what we're eating!
[BOTH laughing]
[LILIA]
Oh, I understand!
[CHEVAL] Their family
has a dinner signal.
[LUTE]
That's not a bad idea.
But Papa and Mama are on
their important shoppin' trip,
so there's no dinner signal.
They said it would be a while
before they got back.
And that we should
watch the sky,
'cause when Mr. Moon
is a big 'ol circle,
they'll be coming home.
There goes their
good mood again.
They really are
lonely, aren't they?
I know! You should spend
the night here at my house!
And Ratha is here!
It'll be a blast!
The only downside is
Navirou never stops talking.
And he snores real bad.
Really, you snore?
What a weird Felyne!
Navirou is not weird!
Marvel, for Navirou
is a chosen Felyne!
But your whiskers are strange.
He's definitely a weird Felyne!
[yelps]
Look how quick they
both fell asleep.
A good meal will do wonders.
Yeah.
Are we sure they're
not unconscious?
Remember, they did chug
all of Lilia's drink.
It is a possibility.
What's that supposed to mean?
[LUTE, NAVIROU yelp]
Navirou feigns ignorance!
[laughs]
When they're like this,
they really are just a
couple of little kids.
You'd never suspect they're a
pair of notorious pranksters.
It's late. I guess we better
get some sleep ourselves.
All right, Lute.
In the morning, I'll
come by with breakfast.
Great!
[LILIA] Good luck with
those two, tonight.
I'll stop by in the morning
with a drink after I wake up.
Uh, 'kay.
Our drink-pocalypse
shall begin early, then.
[LILIA]
Did you say something, Navirou?
Not a word.
Time for Navirou
to hit the hammock.
[NAVIROU snoring]
I can't handle that snoring.
Right? How does Lute
sleep through it?
[BOTH gasp]
A big 'ol circle!
Then that means...
Mama and Papa might
be comin' home soon!
Or even better!
They already got back
and they're on their way
to the house right now!
So what are we waitin'
around here for?
You're right!
Let's go greet 'em!
The road next to Lute's house,
it leads right out
of the village!
Let's do it!
H-Hey, Den-Den.
Wh-What is it, Lin-Lin?
You know, I'm not
even scared one bit.
[chuckles nervously]
Neither am I! Not one bit!
Um, hey, Den-Den.
What's up, Lin-Lin?
We're definitely going
to run into Mama and Papa
if we take this road, right?
Definitely!
This is the only road
that leads outta town.
They have to come this way!
[NAVIROU screams]
[LUTE]
Ha, ha! You fell again.
It's gotta be one of those
kids pranking poor Navirou!
The twins! Where'd they go?
What?
Huh? You mean
Den-Den and Lin-Lin...
...vanished into thin air?
Listen! We'll find those two.
My mom's already gone to
tell Chief Omna and Dan.
[LUTE] Well, I'm not
waiting around here.
I'm going out to look for them!
Stop, Lute! You can't go alone!
Hold on!
This is a perfect opportunity
for Navirou to shine!
What?! Wait for Navirou!
[TWINS] He's not scared.
She's not scared.
We're not scared one bit!
He's not scared.
She's not scared.
We're not scared one bit!
He's not scared.
She's not scared.
We're not scared one bit.
Huh?
[growling]
[BOTH yelp]
[TWINS]
A Gypceros!
[TWINS screaming]
[NAVIROU]
Hm?
I thought I heard
screaming just now.
I heard it too.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Over there! Hm?
Which means this
is the right way.
[yelps]
Time to Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's go!
Lute! Wait!
[LILIA]
Yeah! Wait for us to catch up!
[growls]
I told you it's that way!
What does it want?
I don't know!
[LIN-LIN] Why is it
staring at us like that?
[DEN-DEN]
I said I don't know!
[TWINS whimper]
[TWINS]
Papa! Mama! Someone save us!
Den-Den! Lin-Lin! You okay?
It's Lute!
And Ratha!
There you are!
You're not hurt?
[LIN-LIN]
Lilia!
[DEN-DEN]
Cheval!
There. It'll be all right.
Yeah, you're safe now.
[LUTE] Sure. Ignore me.
Not like I saved you.
Well, maybe this will teach
you not to head into the woods
without Navirou to guide you.
That's another Navi-rule!
[TWINS crying]
[TWINS]
We were so afraid!
They're completely
ignoring you too, Navirou.
[NAVIROU yelps]
It was so scary! How come
it was chasing after us?
Gypceros are known to be
attracted to glittering objects.
Don't worry. It's gone now.
[LIN-LIN]
I wanna go home.
Great idea.
Let's go.
Everyone follow me.
I know the way out!
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
That way!
Huh?
The two of them never pointed
in the same direction before.
So are they both right?
Or are they both wrong?
I've got no idea.
Honestly, I kinda
got turned around
while I was battling
that Gypceros
and lost my sense of direction.
Well, find it!
We'll never get back
home at this rate!
I know!
[OTHERS]
Huh?
We just need to
send out a signal!
A signal?
Wow, Ratha. You're so awesome.
It's just like our
dinnertime signal!
Uh-huh!
All we can do now
is hope someone from
the village notices.
Yeah.
[thudding]
Lute! There's something
coming this way!
No kidding, genius!
What do we do? What if
it's another monster?
[LIN-LIN whines]
We'll take care of it!
Right, Ratha?
[thudding]
[BOTH scream]
Hey! It's Dan!
[DAN]
Whoa!
Ha! Found you!
What's going on? Running off
into the woods after dark!
We're sorry, Dan.
We wanted to make sure
the twins were safe.
So we just kinda took off.
[LUTE laughs]
This isn't a laughing
matter, Lute!
[LUTE yelps]
The woods are a dangerous
place at night.
It's easy to get turned around.
Follow me and
let's head back home.
Okay. Let's see...
[BOTH]
That way!
Wow, Dan. Really?
If someone points in the
same direction as Navirou,
that can't be good.
Poor form yet again.
With all these clouds, I've lost
track of the moon's position.
Which means I have no idea
how to navigate us home.
In short, we're lost.
[ALL]
Huh?!
So cold!
And Navirou misses his donuts!
[roaring]
[LILIA]
Is that--?
It's a signal!
You're right! It's showing
us the way back home!
Chief Omna must be behind this.
Your mom's dinnertime
signal is kind of famous.
Everyone in the
village knows it.
Yeah, that's right!
Because, after all, Hakum
Village is like one big family.
You said it!
So who's ready to get
outta these woods?
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
Hey!
We made it home!
[CHEVAL]
Hi, everyone!
[NAVIROU]
You missed Navirou! Admit it!
Found your way back, I see.
We had a little help.
[VLAU]
You had us so worried!
You kids!
What in the blazes
were you all thinking?
Thank your lucky stars
you're still in one piece.
It's bad enough for the kids
to venture into
the forest at night,
but, Dan, to find out you
went alone after them!
Yes. I apologize.
Now, Gamigami.
What matters is that
everyone got home safely.
All thanks to the signal, Chief!
There's a full moon out tonight.
Which means the Kometas ought
to be returning to us shortly.
Even with all these clouds,
I doubt that master buyers
Toto and Kaka Kometa
could ever lose their way.
Did you guys hear that?
Your parents never get lost!
They're master buyers!
[TWINS laugh]
Hey! Over there!
[BOTH]
We're back, Hakum Village!
Papa! Mama! Welcome home!
[BOTH laugh]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life.
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Gypceros!
It's high endurance means
it can run forever and a day!
But watch out!
This is one smart bird!
It can spit poison and create
disorienting flashes of light!
Even Monsties are suckers
for shiny objects!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Lute here!
Our village is paid a visit
by a traveling fashionista!
Powderkeg Pink,
the Pushy Peddler,
and her adorable Felyne
assistant Mocha!
Wait. What?
Next time: "Navirou in Love"!
Ride On!