[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming
the world's top Monster Rider.
And he's Navirou's top pupil!
[NARRATOR] After visiting Pawpad
Place for info on Kinship Ore,
Navirou faced
one trial after another!
And overcame them all
with his genius!
[NARRATOR]
And now a new day begins,
with a request that will
lead to a new adventure
for Lute, Navirou,
and all their friends!
[LUTE]
What?
Now Simone and the Scriveners
want us to do a Quest for them?
You're sure they want us
instead of Hunters?
Yep! In fact, it's because
you're all Riders
that Simone requested
your services--
Uh, I mean the Captain.
What is it?
There's a good chance it's
related to the Black Blight.
Where is it hitting now?
[LILIA]
It might be hard to believe,
but until just a few years ago,
this vast desert
was as lush and as green
as the forests around it.
[ALL gasp]
[LILIA] The cause seems to be
a mysterious quicksand
that's consuming
everything in its path.
As the desert spreads,
the monsters are starting
to vanish too.
So the population's thinning.
Yeah.
[CHEVAL]
And somehow, the Black Blight's
connected to this quicksand?
Possibly. The Scrivener's
believe it is,
but they're not certain yet.
So to confirm it either way,
I'd like to go with you
into the desert.
[MILLE] You sure?
It's gonna be dangerous.
If the Black Blight's
behind this quicksand,
I'll do anything to stop it.
That's right.
Yeah.
[HYORO] Have the Scriveners
found any actual evidence
that Black Blight's involved?
[ALL]
Uuh...
In the towns
on the desert's edge,
the villagers have been talking.
Rumors about black monsters
coming out of
the sands at night.
So large that they
hide the moon from view.
Black monsters.
[CHEVAL]
It has to be the Blight.
There's no doubt about it!
I agree, and that's why
I'm coming with you.
There's a camp called Oasum
that's full of refugees
who have lost
their homes to the desert.
We can stop there
to hear their stories
of the Blighted monsters.
Let's go!
[SIMONE] "I'm sure you
must have seen or heard by now.
There reports of drastic,
environmental changes
in the Desert Lands.
Based on the evidence,
we believe the Black Blight
to be responsible
for this phenomenon,
just as it was the cause of
the incident in Hakum Village.
Therefore, I am asking
for the Rider's help,
launching an independent
investigation into the matter.
I know you originally
come from a desert village,
so I thought it
important to update you.
P.S. I hear that
your current Quest
is an Desert Island
Grand Hunt-a-Thon.
I know it's not
my place to give advice,
but don't try too hard."
Uh.
[REVERTO]
In other words:
"Finish it up
and go help the kids."
[LILIA]
Okay. This should be
enough gear for
a few days in the desert.
No, you forgot the single
most important item!
What's that?
Donuts, of course!
I put Mille and Hyoro
in charge of packing
all the provisions.
They should be meeting us
back here any minute.
--[LUTE] Oh! There they are!
--[NAVIROU] Huh?
[LUTE] Well, they definitely
got a lot of something!
[NAVIROU]
Ooh!
Navirou can't handle
the mystery any longer!
Open up those bags and
give him all the donuts!
The only thing
Lilia had on the list
were standard field rations
and Well-Done Steak.
Yeah.
You're kidding. No donuts.
Navirou will die!
Huh? Donut!
That should cheer you up.
Hooray, Cheval! Navirou's
top pupil comes through!
[CHEVAL laughing]
Navirou, you're heavy.
[NAVIROU]
Don't hold back now!
Pet Navirou
as much as you'd like!
Oh good, he's back to normal.
[MILLE]
Cheval?
When I was mentioning
the Black Blight earlier,
he just didn't
seem like himself.
[LUTE] I guess. He just wants
to stop the Black Blight.
[LILIA]
Yeah.
Check, check, and check!
Everything's accounted
for and packed up.
We'll hit the road first thing
tomorrow morning, okay?
[ALL]
Mm!
The desert can be
a really unforgiving place,
so, everyone,
get plenty of rest tonight.
This is so cool, Lilia.
It's like you're a
full fledged scrivener now!
Yeah, not really.
And you look like a natural
in that uniform too!
[laughs]
I'm just an apprentice,
you guys, but thank you!
As expected from
Navirou's top pupil!
What? How many top pupils
do you have, Navirou?
[ALL laugh]
[NAVIROU] As many as there are!
And that's a Navi-rule.
[LUTE]
What part of that is a rule?
[MILLE]
That doesn't even make sense.
[HYORO]
Yeah.
[NAVIROU]
Aaah!
It could pose a real
danger to your flowerbed.
And so it goes.
If that happens,
I'll just plant more seeds.
The garden will bloom again.
[gasps]
[LILIA, MILLE]
Cheval!
[LILIA]
Hey, there you are.
I got worried when
I didn't see you at the Inn.
[CHEVAL]
Sorry.
Trouble sleeping?
Well, don't feel bad.
I can't sleep at all, either.
I'm representing the
Scriverners on this journey.
It's a big responsibility.
Ah! I'm so nervous, Cheval!
You'll be fine, Lilia.
Take deep breaths.
You've been
telling me to do that
ever since we were
little kids, Cheval.
[inhales, exhales]
[LILIA]
Yep. Still works.
C'mon, now you try it.
[CHEVAL]
Wait, why me?
[LILIA]
Why not?
[MILLE, LILIA yawn]
Hey, were you guys up late?
I was too nervous
about today to sleep.
--You, too?
--What? No, I feel fine.
According to this, we'll be
in the desert lands soon.
Oh! Then we should stop here
so I can make each
of us a Cool Drink.
Are these gonna be gross?
[CHEVAL]
I'm not sure.
But at least they'll help us
handle the desert heat.
Just gimme a second, guys.
These Cool Drinks have
a few tricky ingredients.
[ALL gasp]
I'm mixing a new combination
that I learned
from Captain Simone.
It's so tasty,
it'll knock your socks off!
[LILIA humming]
Done! Bottom's up!
[ALL]
Eeeh...
I made plenty, so don't be shy!
And remember, you guys,
restraint is hazardous
to your health!
[LUTE]
Cheval!
Let's drink ours together!
[BOTH]
One. Two.
[BOTH laughing]
Oh, well, that wasn't so--
Blaaah! It takes
a second to kick in!
Nasty!
[MILLE]
Cheval's frozen!
[HYORO]
Um, are you okay?
[laughs]
It's so delicious,
he's positively speechless!
You're so delusional!
It's a crime
you can't see the truth!
Here, Lilia,
why don't you try it!
Okay...
[slurps]
Now, watch, that gross
aftertaste will kick in--
Oh, it's even
better than I thought!
I could drink this all the time!
[LUTE, CHEVAL groan]
[LILIA]
All right, guys! You're next!
[HYORO]
Eh!
[HYORO, MILLE groan]
[LILIA]
You, too, Navirou!
Navirou's eating only donuts
for the duration of this trip!
You aren't you worried
about the desert drying you out?
Navirou has
a body of steel! Observe.
A little heat's never
slowed down this fit Felyne!
[chuckles]
[CHEVAL] Y'know, taste aside,
that Cool Drink really worked.
[HYORO]
Good thing we all gave in, huh?
[MILLE] I don't know.
My tongue is still tingling.
[LUTE] Well, if we didn't drink
it, we'd be parched and weak.
It'd be awful!
[laughs]
C'mon, buddy, no one's
gonna look down on you
if just swallow your pride
and have a Cool Drink.
Navirou would rather
wither away to nothingness
than swallow that stuff.
[NAVIROU]
An oasis!
Once again, Navirou's expert
sense of direction
has saved you all!
[LUTE]
Navirou!
That's not an oasis! Come back!
[NAVIROU]
What? Where's the water?
[LILIA]
Navi, get out!
A Barroth!
[roars]
Ride On!
Rathian!
[wailing]
Navirou, you have to
stop struggling!
He's already pretty deep
in that mud!
[MILLE grunting]
Navirou knew you'd never let
your fearless leader
drown out here!
[BOTH grunting]
Careful you guys!
Barroth has the ability
to fling mud!
Don't let it hit you!
Because that mud
will cement you in place.
[MILLE, HYORO groaning]
[LUTE]
Mille! Hyoro!
[grunting]
[MILLE, HYORO scream muffled]
[roars]
Ride On!
Rathian!
[roars]
[LUTE]
It's Cheval!
[LILIA]
It's a cleanser!
Grab on!
I owe ya one, Lilia.
[BARROTH roars]
[roars]
Cheval! This one's not Blighted!
It's just scared because
we disturbed its den!
[CHEVAL]
I will stop it!
[roars]
Cheval!
[gasps]
It's caught in the Shock Trap!
[MILLE] Now use these
Tranq Bombs to put it to sleep!
Right!
[HYORO]
All right!
Please don't celebrate until
Navirou's back on solid ground.
[KIDS]
Oh.
You're lucky we were able
to get you out of there!
Navirou can't believe
you completly forgot about him!
How cruel!
Come on Navi,
let's get that mud off.
You do realize all of this
would have been avoided
if you just had a Cool Drink
like the rest of us.
[NAVIROU sobbing]
So what, are we gonna do
with the Barroth now?
[LILIA] Well, since it
doesn't appear to be infected
with the Black Blight,
it's best if we let the Guild
decide how to handle things.
As for us, once we
get through this valley,
the road to Oasum splits in two.
According to the map,
the mountain route
is pretty treacherous.
And there are no oases
along the way.
Don't worry, Lilia.
I don't mind checking out
that route for us.
[LILIA]
But you can't go alone!
[MILLE]
Then I'll go, too.
Me too.
Aw, thanks, guys.
I'll fell a lot better
with you two coming along.
Great! And while you do that,
Lute and I will take
the route through the Valley
and hand over
the Barroth to the Guild.
[LUTE] Mmmm! This is
gonna be so ultra tasty!
--[NAVIROU] Yoink! Ha-ha!
--[LUTE] Hey!
--What a feast!
--[LUTE] Give it back!
You won't get one bite!
[NAVIROU]
Not fair!
You can't tempt Navirou
with something so tasty!
It's Navirou's!
I didn't make it for you!
[NAVIROU] We need to
settle all food scores,
right here right now!
Let Navirou eat that!
[LUTE] No way! Forget it!
You never make any sense!
[NAVIROU]
Give it to Navirou!
[CHEVAL gasping]
[CHEVAL]
Mom. Mom.
[MILLE]
Cheval? Cheval! Cheval!
Are you okay? What's wrong?
Cheval?
Bad dream.
[CHEVAL] I've been dreaming
about that night a lot lately.
And now, when I see
a Monster attack someone,
I get angry, and this rage
wells up from inside me.
At this point,
it's almost a reflex.
I don't want what happened to me
to happen to anyone else.
Maybe we should
go out of our way
to defeat monsters
who hurt people.
Well, if that feels right,
then it's probably best
if you follow your instincts.
The Nargacuga
changed things for all of us.
You're thinking about
taking a new path.
Lilia joined the Scriveners
and is tracking the Blight.
Hyoro's become braver
and stronger, in his own way.
And there's Lute, whose dreams
have only gotten bigger.
[MILLE] I'd like to
find my own path, too.
[CHEVAL]
You will find it, Mille.
I know you can.
Believe in yourself.
[MILLE]
Thank you, Cheval.
Eeeh...
For the road, buddy!
You sure?
Last night, you seemed pretty
happy it turned out so well.
Well, of course!
It tastes great, though
nothing can ever compare
to the dishes
Mrs. Vlau would make.
Thanks, Lute.
[LILIA] And here's
an Energy Drink from me.
If you feel tired
or under-the-weather,
drink this and you'll perk
right back up, good as new!
Don't drink it, it'll just
make you feel worse. Right?
[chuckles]
What? You want some, too?
Oh, no, no, no.
I couldn't take
Cheval's Energy Drink.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
It's okay!
I already mixed up a huge
pitcher of it, just for you!
Thank you for that, Navirou!
Uh, well, it's the thought
that counts I guess.
Doesn't it though?
Now, don't be shy!
I'm not shy--
what are you talking about?
[laughing]
Be careful out there, guys!
[MILLE]
You, too.
Right! Meet you in Oasum, Lute!
Yeah! I bet we
beat you guys there!
Fine, then it's a race.
Stay safe out there, kids!
Same to you, bye!
Well, we better get a-move-on!
[LILIA]
Right!
[NAVIROU]
Mm!
What the--?
No way.
It's gone.
I swear,
the Barroth was just here!
So where did it go?
[DR. MANELGER]
It's our lucky day, Itsy-Bits!
We snagged ourselves a Barroth,
without getting our hands dirty!
It's all thanks to
your genius, Dr. Manelger.
Once again, you've pulled off
your signature move:
The Ol' Switcheroo!
You, sir, are
an inspiration! Bravo!
Save some of that praise for the
victories to come, Itsy-Bits!
Stealing this Barroth
is but the first step
as we begin my larger plan
for an unprecedented
revolution with Monsters!
[laughing]
[ITSY-BITS] Doctor, look!
The ground is moving!
[DR. MANELGER] Mm? Ah, yes.
Quicksand. Quite deadly!
As long as we don't fly too
close, though, we'll be fine.
Huh? What's that?
Whoa, it is our lucky day!
First a Barroth,
and now a Diablos!
The gods smile on me.
They smile on me, I say!
A fact so important
you repeated it twice!
Itsy-Bits!
Procure the Diablos,
post-haste!
[ITSY-BITS]
But you said quicksand is deadly
if we get too close!
[DR. MANELGER] 'Tis the common
man who holds his life so dear!
[BOTH chuckle]
[ITSY-BITS]
Doctor! That's not a Diablos!
That's a Plum Daimyo Hermitaur
wearing a Diablos shell!
[DR. MANELGER, ITSY-BITS yell]
[BOTH]
Somebody, help!
Let's go! Ride On!
Rathian!
Ride On!
Bulldrome!
Aptonoth!
[DR. MANELGER, ITSY-BITS yell]
Help's on the way!
--Cheval!
--[HYORO] Mille! Look!
[HYORO]
Where's Cheval?
[CHIEF OMNA] You must never
forget the Riders' Laws.
Our humble lives unfold
only by the grace of nature.
In many ways,
we are a part of it.
Therefore, you must never
take life unnecessarily,
you must protect
and love all life.
[CHEVAL] The only thing
that will stop these tragidies
is strength. Great strength!
And an iron will!
Rathian!
Scorching Slice Attack!
[BOTH]
All right!
Oh, he's good.
Very good in fact!
I think we'll
get along just fine.
[CHEVAL] Any monster who hurts
a person must be defeated!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Barroth!
Run into one of these
in the wild
and you'll jump
outta your shoes!
It uses the mud on its body
for both offense and defense!
To top it off, that bony head
crest has major crushing power!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys! Lute here!
Well, we made it
to the camp in Oasum,
but now a conflict's brewing
between Riders and Hunters.
At this rate, we'll never
slay that Cephadrome!
Next time: "Desert Mayday"!
Ride On!