Did you find anything, Lute?
Nah, what about you?
Any sign of eggs?
[NAVIROU] Navirou's
official egg tally is...
[imitates a drum roll]
...none.
[LUTE, CHEVA groan]
[LUTE]
Don't get my hopes up like that!
[NAVIROU grunts]
[LILIA]
"Dear Simone, how have you been?
I'm happy to write that
things here at Hakum Village
are slowly getting
back to normal.
In fact, once we get the
windmill spinning again,
Cheval and Lute are
planning to go on a voyage."
Hitting the road's great,
but without Monsties?
That's a mighty
big gamble, boys.
Even with the battle-tested
Navirou around,
it's better to be
safe than sorry!
And that's a Navi-rule.
Hold on, you're
coming with us?
[NAVIROU yelps]
[coughs]
Navirou knows that
you'll need his skills
and is happy to lend a paw,
provided that you extend
the invitation first.
[coughs]
He's right, Lute,
we'll need help.
[LUTE]
Not to worry, Cheval.
I'll find a new Monstie,
I know it!
How do I know, you ask?
[imitates a drum roll]
I don't know!
[CHEVAL, NAVIROU groan]
[LUTE]
But I do!
Even with nothing backing
me up I know I will!
I can feel it in my gut and
I never bet against that!
[LUTE] And I know I'll
see you again, Ratha.
[LILIA]
That's it!
Guys, look! I can combine
this into all kinds of things!
[LILIA chuckles]
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
We thought you found an egg!
Oh, no, but since
you're empty-handed,
can you help carry stuff?
You've got a lotta nerve trying
to make Navirou your servant!
Navirou will never!
It's your loss,
because if you help me,
I'll pay you with a plate
of mouth-watering,
Royal Honey donuts.
Go help her, Lute!
Then give Navirou the donuts.
Do it yourself!
This guy...
Lute, wait!
What's wrong?
[CHEVAL]
Shh!
[thumping]
Gypceros. Let's get
out of here, now.
We can't just leave behind
all that Royal Honey!
We don't have a choice. C'mon!
Hey, what about what
Navirou wants?!
A mouth-watering,
Royal Honey donut!
[roars]
[ALL screaming]
Another fine mess
you've gotten us into.
How is this my fault?
Whoa!
Guys! Hey, I found an egg!
[LUTE]
O holy Kinship Stone,
bind me together with
this slumbering creature!
Now! The moment of new life!
Awaken!
Wow! It's a Velocidrome!
They're so fast! It'll be
perfect to have on your journey.
Nice to meet you.
My name's Lute.
[LUTE laughing]
[DAN] The stables
are all fixed, Chief.
So then, they'll
be ready as well.
Yes, I had thought the kids
still needed more time.
But they sure have
proven themselves.
Unfortunately, suffering
changes children,
whether we like it or not.
The days of our ancient laws
protecting this village
may be behind us.
Like the young riders,
we, too, must find the courage
to step into a changing world.
We will, Chief.
Dan, it's time I talk
with the children.
Right!
Tomorrow we will hold
the Purification Rite.
[ALL gasp]
Purification Rite?
This is the big one.
It's where Apprentice Riders
become full-fledged Riders.
From tomorrow onward,
its up to each of you
to forge your own path
of your own free will.
And so I ask once again,
as full-fledged Riders,
what is your path?
I know my path:
Become the best Rider!
That's why I'm gonna leave Hakum
Village and travel the world,
forming Kinship with as
many Monsties as I can.
And with each one,
I'll get stronger!
Lute, you are aware
of what it means
to leave Hakum Village, yes?
The dangers you must face?
[LUTE]
Yes, sir!
He won't be alone.
I'm going, too, to help
stop the Black Blight.
I'll find all the Kinship Ore
and purify every one.
I'm going, too.
[HYORO]
Huh?
Well then, what of Hyoro?
Uhh, I think I...
I don't know.
I'm sorry, guys.
Don't apologize.
That's quite all right.
We must keep our
laws and traditions.
However, we can't let ourselves
be chained to the past, either.
Since you have found
your own answers
and wish to move
forward in your lives,
it's not my place to stop you.
I permit your journeys.
[ALL]
Sir!
I'll be so lonely
if Lute leaves!
[NARIKI cries]
[DEN-DEN]
Well, I'm not gonna cry!
[LIN-LIN]
Yeah, we don't get lonely!
[LOLOA]
Lilia! Are you going, too?
Yeah, I was gonna leave town
once the windmill's up
and running again.
Don't think I'm abandoning our
home. I'm trying to save it.
I promise I'll find a way
to stop the Black Blight!
But you're not a Rider,
you don't have a Monstie.
It's so dangerous.
Don't worry.
After all, I'm traveling
with the best weapon ever:
My knowledge!
Here, I want you to have this.
Loloa hates it!
You're a stupid big sister!
Loloa hates you, too!
Loloa!
[LILIA]
Chief.
Lilia, my dear,
may I speak with
you for a moment?
[LILIA]
What? I can leave with them?
While you may not
have become a Rider,
you're still a child
of this village.
Allow me to wish you
a good journey.
Wow! Thank you, Chief!
Hey, Loloa!
I was just looking for you--
Hey, what's wrong?
Loloa's sister is leaving
to travel the world
and stop the Black Blight!
Aw, you don't have
to cry, Loloa.
'Fact, I know
something you can do
that'll take your mind off this.
Are all you guys
really heading out
right after the
Purification Rite?
[LUTE]
Yep!
But, Cheval, it hasn't
even been that long
since you lost your dear mother.
Are you sure you've
thought this all through?
Mom wouldn't like me
just moping around.
She'd want me to go
make a difference.
That's what I'll do.
I'm putting everything I've
got into this journey.
[GAMIGAMI]
Now listen up!
These young Riders are leaving
to help secure a future
for Hakum Village.
So before they go, let's show
'em how much we care!
[VILLAGER A, VILLAGER
B] Yeah, let's do it!
We'll keep the village going!
If things get too rough,
you can come home anytime.
We'll do our best to keep the
village safe while you're gone.
So focus on your journey ahead.
This town will do
just fine without them.
C'mon! Let's get back
to the afternoon work!
[VILLAGERS shouting]
All right, what's
with the frowny face?
[LUTE chuckles]
I know you're being dramatic.
Oh, Lute. Navirou's sad 'cause
of what you forgot to ask.
[LUTE]
Hm...?
Oh!
Go on!
I shoulda asked permission
before eating the donuts
that you stashed under the bed.
More important than that!
[LUTE]
Hm... Oh!
Yes! Go on!
You're sad 'cause I also ate
the ones under your pillow.
Sorry!
It's like... sometimes
I get so hungry...
It's not like you to stay
this quiet, Navirou.
Did you eat something
you weren't supposed to?
This has nothing
to do with food!
It's about you not getting
other people's feelings!
Hmph!
Wait, what?
[CHEVAL]
You okay?
[HYORO]
Cheval.
How'd you work up
the nerve to decide?
It's just so scary out there.
People might target us just
'cause we're Riders.
And there might be
monsters scarier
than anything we've
seen around here.
I'm just so... I'm completely
terrified, Cheval!
How can you not be?
I'm scared, too.
But I feel helpless here.
I'm going so that I can
become a stronger person.
And with that strength,
I'll be able to keep
Hakum Village safe.
Cheval.
[CHEVAL] I'm going so that
I can become a stronger person.
And with that strength,
I'll be able to keep
Hakum Village safe.
[GENIE] Aren't you done
cleaning the stables?
Genie.
Don't forget to change
out all the bedding.
Big brother, can we...?
Did you notice how
worn down these are?
Here, look. You have
to polish them.
Okay.
[GENIE] We won't see
each other for a long time.
I want you to watch
everything I do.
Genie.
Tomorrow morning,
I'm gonna drill you
on all the Rider skills
I know, so listen close.
It's gonna be an all-nighter.
Yes!
Ride On!
Rathian!
[DAN] The Purification
Rite won't be here.
We'll go to the
Waterfall of Trials.
Are your hearts ready for this?
[ALL]
Yes!
That's just what I like to hear!
All right! Now who's
in top form, huh?!
[ALL]
We're in top form!
So I guess you're coming, too?
That's right.
I'm gonna see the Royal
Scriveners in Gildegaran.
Oh, so we won't be together
for the whole journey.
Sounds like you're
gonna miss her.
What? That's not true!
You got a lotta nerve to be
spreading gossip like that
before we do a Sacred Rite.
Hmph!
[HYORO]
Cheval!
Thanks for yesterday.
Of course. I'm glad
you decided to come.
Are you still sulking
about whatever it was?
[NAVIROU]
Hmph!
More silent treatment?
Well, you're the one who's
got something to say Lute,
not Navirou!
What am I supposed to say?
Why don't you ask yourself?
Hmph!
I am so lost.
[LUTE]
Wow.
I'm glad to see that
you all made it.
The time is now at hand to
begin the Purification Rite.
[ALL]
Yes, Chief!
[chanting]
[chanting continues]
Ha!
Your Kinship Stones
have been purified
and their power increased.
The light now emanating from
them will serve as a beacon
to illuminate your
paths in this world.
[CHIEF OMNA]
All right,
since that takes care
of Kinship Stones,
we can move on
with the ceremony.
I will now give each
of you something
to mark your new status
as full-fledged Riders.
Please accept it
with great care.
First, Lute.
Yes, Chief!
It feels like it
was only yesterday
when you came into our
village and into my life.
Your innocence and enthusiasm
was a bigger breath of fresh air
than the Hakum Gale itself.
I expect to see great things
from you as a Rider.
Yes, sir!
Now, Mille.
Yes!
You are a Rider with
great conviction,
who works twice as hard as most.
But please, make sure
your conviction
never robs you of your freedom.
Always remember
to open your heart
and trust your friends
when they offer advice.
[gasps]
Thanks!
Hyoro!
[HYORO]
Sir!
[CHIEF OMNA]
You have a firm backbone
and gladly put
your friends first.
This inner warmth, much
like the rays of the sun,
is a light that shines on all
those who are close to you.
Never lose faith in yourself.
Sir!
[CHIEF OMNA]
Cheval.
Yes, Chief!
So much tragedy has
happened to you,
and yet you have endured
it with a maturity
far beyond your years.
Your courage has
been an inspiration
and has helped us honor the past
while looking to the future.
Cheval, since you were a boy,
you have shown great kindness.
You can easily sense
the pain in others.
Of your many strengths,
this empathy impresses me most.
You must always keep
it in your heart.
Yes.
Heavy, aren't they?
Know these swords are yours.
However, only draw them
to defend yourself,
a friend, or your Kinship.
The swords' weight represents
the weight of the Kinship
that binds you together.
And, Lilia.
Yes, sir!
Your knowledge,
bravery, and honesty
are great assets for
yourself and others.
You secure not just a future for
our Village, but a bright one!
We all await your return
with much anticipation
and excitement.
Thank you!
[CHIEF OMNA]
It is my firm belief
that each of the
paths you follow
will overflow with
brilliance and joy!
Now it is time to depart!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ALL gasping]
[VILLAGERS shouting]
[LUTE]
Huh?
You'll need this out there.
Thanks, pal.
Don't let Navirou see you cry.
The time you and
Navirou spent together
was always full of
smiles and laughter.
That doesn't change even when
it's time to say goodbye,
and that's a Navi-rule.
Aw, thanks, Navirou.
From the first day we met,
you've been the
funniest little weirdo.
As long as I live,
I'll never forget you.
[NAVIROU] Fare thee well, Lute.
Go forth in good health!
Navirou?
Uh, wait, hold on!
Why are you walking
back to the village?
Because Navirou was seeing
you off with a smile, obviously.
[LUTE] Seeing me off?
I thought you were coming too!
[NAVIROU]
What?
You mean you don't wanna
leave Navirou behind?
Well, I mean, it's more like--
I've just gotten used
to you tagging along.
So you're finally
brave enough to admit
you can't live without Navirou.
But why couldn't you
say that before?
I didn't say that!
[NAVIROU] Well, if you're
an emotional mess,
Navirou has no choice
but to accept your invite!
So glad you got that out.
Great, but I never said that.
All this time, that's what
you wanted me to ask you?
[BOTH laugh]
All right, let's get going!
Everyone, follow Navirou!
Stay safe!
Stay smart!
Go get 'em, guys.
[BOTH]
Right!
Uh. No, wait!
Something wrong Lilia?
[LILIA]
Where's my sister?
I didn't think
she'd still be mad.
Loloa hates you, too!
I can't believe she's not
here to say goodbye to me.
[LOLOA]
Lilia, wait!
Loloa!
--[clattering]
--[CHILDREN scream]
[CHILDREN groaning]
What were you guys doing?
[ALL chuckle]
[LOLOA]
We were getting this for you.
[LILIA]
Royal Honey?
Oh, Loloa, thank you,
but that was so dangerous.
What if you got hurt?
I know, but I couldn't forget
how badly you wanted it.
So to show how much
we appreciate you,
we got it as a
going-away present.
Thank you!
Loloa didn't mean it when
she said she hated you.
She loves you more than anything
else in the whole world!
And I love my little sister
more than anything else
in the whole wide world!
Here you go, Lute!
A goodbye gift!
A box lunch me and the
other kids put together!
[LUTE]
Seriously?
My favorite stuff! Awesome!
We made one for
you too, Cheval.
Aw, thanks a lot, Nariki.
We'll be cheering
for you, Hyoro!
[LIN-LIN]
Take care, Mille!
Watch over the village.
Next year, I'll be
a Rider like you!
So until you get back, I'll be
spending all my time training
and helping to keep
the people safe.
You're leaving the
village in good hands!
[TWINS]
That's right!
Thanks, guys.
Thanks for everything!
[crack]
[LUTE]
Well! Let's dig in!
What? You're eating
your lunch now?
That's our Lute for ya!
Always expect the unexpected!
This place won't be
the same without him!
The new Riders really know
how to make an exit, don't they?
[DAN laughs]
They're in top form!
All right then, your next
stop will be Gildegaran!
If you get yourselves
into trouble,
seek out the Wyverian that
lives in the Arctic Ridge.
I'm certain he'll be
able to help you.
[LUTE]
The world is waiting for us!
Yeah!
Who's in top form?
[OTHERS]
We're in top form!
[CHIEF OMNA]
The Kinship they share
will usher in a new
era for us all.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Velocidrome!
Thanks to the crest on its
head, you can't miss it.
This clever beast leads the
Velociprey with great skill.
Navirou just hopes it can
put its smarts to work
taking care of his buddy, Lute.
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
We've started our journey,
and it looks like we're
meeting a mysterious beauty
on the Arctic Ridge.
As long as that Khezu
doesn't attack us first!
Ah! Do something, Navirou!
Next time: "Avinia's Secret."
Ride On!