[NARRATOR] This is Lute,
a young monster Rider!
He and his friends have just
defeated a Blighted Diablos
and purified a Kinship Ore.
But though Cheval,
Hyoro, and Mille
have come all
this way with Lute,
they've broken off to
follow their own path.
The Scriveners just gave
me the good news.
Thanks to you, the Kinship
Ore at Albrachs Village
is pure once again.
Most impressive work.
You Riders don't disappoint.
Well done!
[LILIA] We all worked
together, Guild Master.
I would assume so,
which is why I've
called you Riders here
for some important news.
But it seems like some
of you are missing.
Yeah, Cheval and the others...
...they decided to...
Instead of returning
to Gildegaran,
they're still fighting
the Black Blight.
[GUILD MASTER]
Hm. I see.
Ahoy, there, Cheval!
Cheval, my boy!
Have you given any more thought
to my offer of a partnership?
Join with us, and you
can help save the world!
We've no use for either of you.
No need to be so cold-hearted,
my young friend.
My young friend.
He said it twice
'cause he's sincere!
Leave me alone.
You're making the wrong decision
by turning us down, my boy.
[GUILD MASTER] Have you ever
heard the name "Redan"?
The great Rider, yeah.
[GUILD MASTER]
Good, good.
But have you ever heard
the stories of his Monstie?
No. Although, we have
heard about his Palico.
According to the Redan legend:
"The great Rider soars
gallantly across the heavens
astride a dragon white."
So it seems to me that
this "dragon white"
must've been the monster Redan
used to seal the Blight away.
A "dragon white"?
That's right.
And since you have
made it your mission
to stop the Blight
as well, Lute,
it stands to reason you'll need
the same Monstie Redan rode.
Do you know the kind of
species it was, sir?
I have no clue.
[ALL yelp]
Of course he has no idea.
[GUILD MASTER] And with that,
I've told you Riders all I know.
You're looking for a dragon,
well, a big, white monster,
more or less.
Yeah, no surprise there.
Hm. A monster that looks
like a white dragon.
That's pretty vague.
I'll go do some research
at the Scriveners guild.
Great, thanks!
[LILIA]
See ya!
Let's try to find some
clues on our own, too.
What? Do you have a
lead or something?
Well, not yet,
but we might be able to
get one by asking Hunters
if they've ever heard
of a "dragon white."
We'll start with Reverto!
[DEBLI]
Hey-Hey!
Lute, what's goin' on, my man?
Hey, Tub... bli?
It's Debli! It hasn't
been that long, has it?
Anyway, I heard you just
finished a whopper of a Quest!
What did you do?
How much did you make?
You bet your thick hide we did!
Thanks to Navirou,
it was a huge win!
Sounds great! I wanna
hear all about it!
Here's the scene.
Blighted monsters surrounded
Hunter and Rider alike.
The brave Navirou
arrives in a flash!
Sorry, Debli, but we gotta go.
Not fair!
Are you starting another Quest?
Lemme come along!
It's not a Quest.
We're just asking Hunters
if they've ever heard
of this one monster.
Oh, is that so?
Well, maybe the time is right
to introduce you to my teacher.
You have a teacher?
Who taught you to be shady?
Aw, c'mon, I'm not shady!
And on that note...
Hey! Come back and hear me out!
He's no normal teacher, he's a
descendant of a legendary hero!
What?
A legendary hero, huh?
What's his name?
Oh, I don't know
the hero's name,
but I do know my
teacher's Nedan!
[BOTH]
Nedan, huh?
[NEDAN snoring]
[DEBLI]
Hey-Hey! Teacher!
This is my buddy, Lute.
[NEDAN]
Huh?
Lute, I'd like you to
meet my teacher, Nedan!
Hey, teach, do you mind if Lute
asks you a question or two?
Depends on the question
this Rider has for me.
What? How could you
tell I'm a Rider?
Well, son, your eyes
gave ya square-away
before you even said a word!
A whisperin' wind, they are.
Wait, what?
You can read people that way?
Look into Navirou's eyes next
and tell him what you
can see about him!
[NEDAN]
Hm...
In those big blues, I see...
Glitterin' stars
upon an inky sky!
Great constellations
showin' Riders the way!
Oh, wow!
Navirou's navigational
skills are heaven-sent!
Are you descended from
a hero named Redan?
[NEDAN]
Redan?
Yeah. Yeah, old
ancestor of mine.
[LUTE]
The legendary hero?
[NEDAN] Yep. Uh-huh.
Saved the world that one did.
[LUTE] By sealing away
the Black Blight, yes!
[NEDAN]
Sealed it away. Totally sealed!
[LUTE] So, then what do you
know about Kinship Ore?
Now, wait a sec. You've
heard about Kinship Ore?
Yeah.
We're traveling the world,
finding and purifying
all the Kinship Ore
tainted by the Black Blight.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Kinship Ore's gotta be
as clean as crystal,
or else it don't "Kinship."
My dear ancestor could've
never saved the world
without them rocks.
[BOTH]
Uh?
His story's been handed
down for generations.
Oh, wow, sir!
You really do know
a lot about this.
Have you heard of
a "dragon white"?
[NEDAN]
Hm?
A dragon white?
Legend says Redan could
only stop the Black Blight
with one as his Monstie.
That means I need
one as my Monstie.
But I need to find a
white dragon egg, first.
[NEDAN]
So that's your deal, huh?
The egg of a dragon white
sounds simple enough, I guess.
But do you even know what
kinda Monster that is?
[NAVIROU] Not even Navirou
could figure it out!
That's why we came to you!
You're in luck,
'cause I've seen one!
You have?
[NEDAN] It was back when I was
a wet-behind-the-ears greenhorn
to the whole Huntin' game.
You see, the older Hunters
had taken me along
on a very arduous Quest.
[door opens]
[SIMONE]
Lilia.
The Guild Master wants us to
look into something for him.
The name of a monster
that till now
has only appeared in legend
as "the dragon white."
[LILIA]
What a coincidence,
that's exactly what
I was researching!
I'm afraid you won't find
any mention of it in here.
That's why I'm forming
a field research team.
Its only goal will be
to gather information
on the white dragon.
I'll be captain of this team.
With Pappan as my lieutenant.
And I've made a special request
for you to join as well.
What? Really?
I'll be working with
you on this mission?
You better go get ready now.
We leave tomorrow.
Right!
And then, the white dragon
flew high into the air.
Higher and higher,
till it was outta sight.
That was not the end
of the peril, however,
as the long trek back to
Gildegaran was even scarier
than the great white beast!
But that's a story
for another time.
--C'mon, tell us now!
--Whoa, that's amazing!
So then, do you know where I can
find a white dragon egg, sir?
Yeah, let me think on that one.
A while back, I did hear
of a promising spot
that's not too far.
Now, let's think about what
an old-fashioned egg hunt
will set ya back in
the Zenny department.
Lotta supplies.
The hunt'll cost
ya 10,000 Zenny.
You like the sight of that?
Ten what?! Think about
all the donuts that'd buy!
All right, fine!
You're gonna pay?
[NEDAN] Hm. In advance,
if you don't mind.
Now hold on there, Lute.
It's custom to only
pay a deposit up front
and the remainder upon
completion of said task!
Do they give you Quest rewards
before or after you're done?
Uh. Good point.
[NEDAN]
Hm.
Son, I apologize.
Your friend is right.
That there's one good Rider's
Palico you got by your side.
What? Well, Navirou
wouldn't go that far.
[NEDAN]
I'll take 5,000 as a deposit.
Fine! You strike a
hard bargain, sir!
[LUTE]
Here ya go!
[NEDAN] Let's meet here.
Tomorrow morning.
[LUTE]
Got it!
[NAVIROU]
See ya, tomorrow!
Scorching Slice!
[BOTH gasp]
Wow, the Blight had a major
effect on that Tigrex.
He was on a rampage.
Yeah. I've never seen
one so violent.
That's why the only option
left is to defeat them.
C'mon. There're plenty
more out there.
Shouldn't we maybe take
a break, Cheval?
Aren't you hungry?
There's still daylight
left. Let's go.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
[NEDAN snoring]
[DEBLI]
Teacher! We're all ready!
Wake up!
[LUTE] Mister Nedan,
did you remember the spot
where the egg is?
Yup. It all came back.
That's great!
Yeah, I feel good
about this spot.
But the hard part's gonna
be gettin' over there
in the first place.
Don't worry about us,
we can handle it!
[NEDAN]
Hmm...
Well, let's go!
[NAVIROU]
Whoa, what's that thing?
Never seen a Huntin'
Horn, have ya?
She's a beauty.
Can't wait to take this
here Phenomenal Phlute
out for a swing once more!
You're so amazing!
Eh. I don't know
about "amazing."
Don't doubt my greatness, boy!
You have no idea how
many Zamtrios I defeated
just to get my
hands on this baby.
Years later and I still
wake up in horror
thinkin' about
their big fat bodies
and those freezing attacks!
Brr. So cold!
--See, I told ya! He's great!
--Wow, you really are great!
[NEDAN]
Hmm.
What do ya see out there, sir?
Is it a monster?
Say, could one of
ya go poke around
in that grass over yonder?
[LUTE, DEBLI, NAVIROU]
Huh?
[DEBLI]
Whoa! Herbs!
[LUTE]
Antidote Herbs!
[NAVIROU]
And Felyne?
Awesome!
That's right!
And there'll be even more
items for us up ahead!
We'll fill our pockets!
[NAVIROU]
Ooh! Here's some more!
[LUTE]
Yeah! Nulberries!
[NEDAN] One of you check
out that thicket, too.
[DEBLI] Uh, but, Teacher,
I can't carry anymore!
[NEDAN] Well, we finally made
it to the white dragon's lair!
Now ya just gotta crawl on in,
find its nest, and grab an egg!
In there, huh?
Hold on, Lute!
What for?
It's great that we found
the dragon's lair,
but shouldn't we assume that
the dragon is there, too?
Navirou doesn't
wanna be eaten today!
Don't be scared.
Mr. Nedan's with us.
Ayup!
That's a Rider's Palico
if ever I heard one.
You're Navirou, that right?
Huh?
When you're egg-huntin'
around big monsters,
you can never be too careful.
You're doin' the right thing
tryin' to keep your Rider friend
all cautious-like and safe.
Aw!
Yeah, Navirou is a super guy.
For you.
A small token of Navirou's
gratitude for your appreciation.
[NEDAN]
Ooh! Thank you much.
At this time of day,
the white dragon will be out and
about huntin' for its own grub.
And with this wind blowin'
something fierce,
I doubt it's back soon.
Let's go!
Best teacher ever!
[NEDAN]
Hm...
Hey. Someone check behind that
rock 'fore we go any further.
[DEBLI] We're stuffed! We don't
have room for more items, sir!
[LUTE]
Yeah, let's just get the egg.
[NEDAN]
This ain't about items!
A Nerscylla!
[DEBLI screaming]
Time to Ride On!
Rathalos!
What?
[NAVIROU] Too much distance
between him and the cave!
Teacher!
I'm-a-comin'!
Ah! Oh, yeah!
Sometime today!
Easy for you to say, Debli!
You're not the one who's gotta
warm up his Huntin' Horn!
Oh, man!
Ratha, you're here!
Are you done yet?!
Hang on! I'm almost ready!
Make it snappy!
Now, Ratha! Fire!
Yeah!
Aw, and just like that,
it's all over.
I was just about to
make my big move, too.
Can we stay here and rest a bit?
That's the most
Navirou's ever run.
You are one powerful
boy, if I do say so.
As quick as lightning you were!
[LUTE]
Huh? Ha-ha. Thanks.
You should be able to find that
egg on your own, no problem.
I'll double back to the mouth of
the cave and stand guard for us.
Never know when we might
run into another Nerscylla,
or if the white dragon
is gonna come home.
[LUTE] Are you sure
you'll be okay alone?
Aw, you don't have to
worry about me, son.
I'll be fine.
My teacher's so cool!
Yeah! He really is so cool!
You'll know the dragon egg
as soon as you see it.
It's as white as snow
on a moonlit night.
I'm positive it's right
up ahead. Well, bye!
[NEDAN]
Good luck, fellers!
Whoa.
Is that it?
[NAVIROU]
It's white, all right.
[LUTE]
We found it!
The fabled egg of
the dragon white.
Let's get this bad boy hatched!
Here goes!
O holy Kinship Stone.
Please bind me together with
this slumbering creature.
Awaken!
[ALL gasp]
[NAVIROU]
What?
[LUTE]
A Khezu?
[DEBLI]
Did we get the wrong egg?
[NAVIROU] It's painted
white! We've been had!
No! How could my
teacher do this to us?
Your teacher is not a great
man, he's just a con artist!
Navirou wishes he'd never
given that trickster his donut!
Navirou wants it back!
[LUTE]
Stop right there!
How dare you try to con us!
What? Ya already hatched it?
How'd ya do that?
[NAVIROU]
Don't underestimate Riders!
[LUTE]
This is a Khezu egg!
Sorry, but there just ain't
white dragons around here.
And if there are,
you certainly ain't gonna find
'em on one little day trip.
[LUTE]
What?
[NAVIROU] So you thought
you could pass off
a random Khezu egg?
[NEDAN] Hey, findin' that
wasn't easy, either!
[NAVIROU] And then you literally
just painted it white?
[NEDAN] Well, yeah, it had
to look the part, right?
[NAVIROU] Then, before we even
left on this wild dragon chase,
you hid it in a
Nerscylla's cave?
Sure looked and felt
like the kinda place
where a white dragon
might live, didn't it?
And all the items we
found on our way up here
were planted by you ahead
of time, weren't they?
Oh, no, I didn't
work that hard.
I saw them on my
way home last night
and thought I'd point 'em out.
Well, now you've
confessed everything!
Master detective Navirou
will never be fooled again!
You're the bad guy here.
Give us our money back!
Yeah, but your money is...
...gone.
What?!
Gone where?
It all went into
expenses for today.
Since when does a Khezu
egg cost 5,000 Zenny?
[NEDAN] A guy I owed money to
had taken this baby from me.
Cost me the 5,000
to get it back.
But you'll get your money back.
Now that I got the
ol' Huntin' Horn,
I can do all sorts of work.
You just watch me!
Why should we believe that?
Navirou will never
forgive himself
for trusting 5,000 Zenny
to this donut thief!
Wait, Mister Nedan.
What makes you so sure
there aren't any white
dragons in this area?
[NEDAN]
Hmm...
"The Rider soars gallantly
across the heavens
astride a dragon white."
What? The Guild Master
said the same thing.
[NEDAN]
Not surprised.
That tale's been handed
down for generations.
But since no one seems to know
what Monster a
"dragon white" is,
stands to reason folks have
never really seen one!
So then if it is real,
and if it is still alive,
I'm betting it probably lives
way, way far away from everyone.
[LUTE] Mister, are you really
descended from Redan?
[NEDAN] I wouldn't know all
this stuff if I wasn't!
If you're one of
his descendants,
why are you a
shifty junk dealer?
Well, look,
sure, I'm a descendant
of the legendary Redan,
but that don't mean
I get an inheritance,
'specially not if
I'm no Rider myself!
I live my life. So what's
wrong with that?
When you put it that way,
it doesn't seem so bad.
I'll pay ya back because
I never lose sight of a debt.
Now what?
I guess I don't know.
[NEDAN] The answer is to start
your journey, my young friends!
Away to those far-off lands
in search of the
fabled "dragon white."
Is that really what
the legend says?
Nah. I just made
that up on the spot.
[NAVIROU yelps]
The lies have to stop!
[LUTE] Let's forget about
the white dragon for now
and head to the Dovan Volcano.
[NAVIROU]
Dovan Volcano?
Don't tell me you
forgot about that.
Lilia said there's
supposed to be
a Kinship Ore
there, remember?
Yeah, Navirou blanked.
Who can keep track of
all these place names?
We've still got all the Herbs
we found on this trip.
We can leave right now.
And with those, we don't need
Lilia's gross drinks, either.
[LUTE]
See ya 'round, Mr. Nedan.
[NAVIROU] He'll be keeping
the Khezu as his new Monstie.
We'll let you off with
just that for today.
Sounds good!
[LUTE]
Ready, Ratha?
[RATHA roars]
Take care, boys!
Now we know how Debli
learned to be Debli.
Y'know, I've been thinking.
That old guy had to go
out and get a Khezu egg,
then he had to plant it
in a Nerscylla's cave,
and he pulled it all
off by himself!
Yeah. He actually is
pretty tough, huh?
Eh, whatever! Next stop:
Dovan Volcano!
[NAVIROU]
Yahoo!
[DEBLI]
Hey! Wait for me!
Come back for Debli!
Yeah! And gimme back
the Herbs I found!
Aww.
Eh, oh, well.
[NEDAN]
Time to get back to work.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Zamtrios!
Also known as "Monster Sharks,"
these amphibians are at home
on land or in the water!
They have the power to encase
their whole bodies in ice armor
and can blow themselves
up like a huge balloon
to crush their enemies!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys, Lute here!
We finally made it to
the Dovan Volcano!
Navirou, what's going on?
This is so weird! Why're
you all electrified now?
Next Time:
"Dovan Volcano Memories."
Ride On!