[LUTE'S FATHER] I have to
stop it, no matter what!
[roaring]
[LUTE'S FATHER yells]
[LUTE crying]
Oh, Lute.
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
This is all your fault!
No, it's your fault!
No, your fault!
[roaring]
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
You were the one who was all
like, "It's an egg! An egg!"
[NAVIROU] So? Don't take
it out of the nest!
And you're the one who's
always going on about eggs!
[roars]
[BOTH screaming]
What just happened?
It's your fault, Navirou!
No, it's your fault, Lute!
Your fault, your
fault, your fault!
No, no, no, your fault!
[BOTH growling]
I wish those guys
would stop arguing
with each other for a second
so they could at least
thank us for rescuing them.
[BOTH] That was in no
way my fault at all!
They're two of
a kind, all right.
Yeah, they make quite a pair.
[BOTH]
Huh?
What does that mean?!
[NAVIROU]
Egg, where are you?
I feel it.
There's an egg around
here somewhere!
Oh, come on.
You say that every day,
but you still haven't
found a single one yet.
Yeah, that's true,
but it's not like you've
been right either, Navirou.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Hey, Lute, you do know
you don't have to worry about
finding an egg on your own.
You can just get one from
Chief Omna at tomorrow's Rite,
like everybody else.
There's no need to go to
extremes searching like this.
Well, yeah, I know, but...
I just.... I wanna be the
one to find it by myself.
I mean, it's the first...
...the first Monstie Egg I'll
form Kinship with as a Rider!
We know.
You've been saying that
for a while now.
Well, I guess we can
look a little longer.
Thanks, guys.
[DAN] How's everybody
doing this beautiful day?
Now then, being a
Rider is all about
the Kinship with your monster.
You'll begin by forming Kinship
with a companion monster
who will eventually
become your Monstie.
And the first step
in that process
is hatching a monster egg.
To do that, you're
gonna need this.
It's a Kinship Stone.
A Rider only receives one
of these precious stones
during the course of
his or her lifetime.
So after Chief Omna
gives you yours tomorrow,
be sure to keep it on you
at all times, is that clear?
[ALL]
Sir!
Sorry to interrupt,
Dan sir, but--
Yes? What's wrong?
Well, this isn't all of
the Rider candidates
who will be in tomorrow's Rite.
[DAN]
Huh?
Oh, no, not him again.
[LUTE]
Hey, egg! I know you're here!
"I feel it. There's an egg
around here somewhere!"
That's what you
always say, correct?
But then it never
turns out to be true!
Oh, it's here, all right!
And we're getting really
close now, I can feel it!
--[grunting]
--[stomach growling]
I'm so hungry.
Hey, are you really
picking up on an egg
or are we just on a
stroll in the woods?
No, I really am!
But I'm really hungry, too.
[stomach growls]
Oh, it's no use. I'm running
out of energy now. Ah!
That's not good.
We didn't bring anything
to eat with us.
Ugh, fine, hold on a sec.
I'll be right back.
Oh, please no.
Bet she's gonna make me eat
something disgusting again.
Wonder what it'll be today.
There we go!
Nitroshrooms! We'll be
all set with these!
[LUTE]
Great, she found Nitroshrooms.
[CHEVAL] What could she
possibly have up her sleeve?
Ah! Nitroshrooms?
That must mean she's
making the, uh, you know,
that thing that she makes.
The, uh...
How can you just stand there
chowing down on a donut
when I'm over here starving?
Oh, come on, you know
Navirou's special donuts
are for Navirou only!
But...
If you happen to stumble across
anything delicious out here,
Navirou gets half of it.
And... those are the rules!
Listen, you--
[LILIA]
Hey, Lute!
Look I found a beehive too!
[LILIA laughs]
What's she gonna make
me eat this time?
No idea.
Well, when you combine
a Nitroshroom with honey,
you get, you know, uh,
that thing that's like, um...
Voilà! Here you go.
A nice Energy Drink!
You first, Cheval!
[CHEVAL yelps]
What's wrong? You afraid?
No, it's not that,
it's just I--
You're supposed
to become a Rider,
but how are you gonna do that
when you're such a scaredy-cat?
That is enough, Lute!
You drink it!
You are still hungry,
aren't you?
Oh, yeah, that's right!
You're the one who's
hungry here, not me!
Good point.
Heh. All right then.
I guess I've gotten used to
Lilia's crazy
concoctions by now.
That's it, I'm just gonna
chug this whole thing down!
Go on and drink it already!
It'll perk you right up!
All right, all right,
I got it. Here goes.
Are you okay?
He certainly doesn't look okay,
that much is for sure.
Huh.
It's like...
...I'm gonna burst!
[yells]
Well, that's Nitroshrooms.
Always immediate results.
And some might say excessive!
[CHEVAL chuckles]
Yeah! Let's go get some eggs!
Oh, I had some honey left over,
so let me know if
you want any more!
It's close. I can sense
the presence of an egg.
In that case, just let
Navirou be your guide!
The egg... is right this way!
So that way then.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Is there something
wrong, Cheval?
It's just, I don't
think we should be
venturing in any
farther than this.
We're headed towards
the Forbidden Land,
which is, ya know,
kinda forbidden.
I'm positive there's an egg
up ahead. I just know it.
Trust me.
But... that'd be
breaking a village rule.
And I bet we're
already in hot water
with Dan and the
others right now.
Not to mention, Mom's gotta
be worried sick about us.
Uhh. Well, yeah, I guess you
do have a pretty good point.
Those guys sure are
taking their time.
Usually by now
they'd have given up
and come home with their
tail between their legs.
You don't think
there's any chance
they would've been
foolish enough
to set foot in the
Forbidden Land, do you?
Well, well, Navirou
smells something!
Make no mistake. That's the
smell of a monster egg!
I do smell something here.
Maybe, but this is Navirou
we're talking about.
No way it's really an egg.
Hey, guys, is it just me,
or does it smell a lot less eggy
and a lot more monstery?
[CHEVAL yelps]
[LUTE]
Hm?
[LUTE, CHEVAL scream]
Cheval! Behind you!
What? Where?
Calm down Cheval,
everything's all right.
Lute was teasing.
There's nothing there.
Phew. Jeez.
Now c'mon, let's go.
We're gonna track down that
egg and become Riders!
This is no time to stand
around shaking in our boots!
[CHEVAL]
Guess you're right.
[screams]
[laughs]
Oh, yeah, like I'm really
gonna fall for that
right after I pranked you.
No. No. Look. Look.
It's-- It's a--
[ALL]
Huh...?
[roars]
Er, uh, isn't that
a, uh, you know,
an Aka-- Ao-- Aka-- Ao-- Aka--
It's an Arzuros.
[ALL screaming]
[LUTE]
Which way?
Go right!
[LUTE]
Left it is!
[ALL screaming]
Run faster!
Hold up!
--Wow!
--Whoa!
Oh, no!
--[ALL scream]
--[ARZUROS roars]
What do we do now?
This wouldn't've happened
if you'd followed Navirou!
Sorry, Navirou!
[roars]
I'm jumping!
Follow me!
[NAVIROU screams]
[roars]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[DAN] All right, I'm going to
look for Lute and the others.
Genie and Stone, I want
you to hold down the fort.
[BOTH]
Sir.
Oh, man. I can't
believe they did this.
And with the Kinship
Rite tomorrow, too.
Yeah, I know.
It just seems like those kids
don't even want to be Riders.
Sure, they do!
That's the reason they
went looking for eggs!
In fact, Loloa wanted
to go, too, but--
All right, you guys.
Back to studying.
[OTHERS]
Okay.
A week ago, I saw some
pitch-black grass in the woods.
It worries me.
[NAVIROU groaning]
Hey, where are we?
I think we must still be inside
the Forbidden Land's forest.
Great, so you mean
on top of everything,
we're even deeper into
the Forbidden Land now?
[LUTE]
Uh.
Huh? What's that?
Something sparkly!
Pretty!
Hold on, where has Navirou
seen that light before?
So familiar.
I see. Lute and his
friends, you say?
That's right. They should've
been back hours ago.
I'm afraid they may have gone
into the Forbidden Land.
Huh.
Dan, are you aware of the
disturbance in the woods
that's been reported recently?
I am. Stone mentioned something.
He said he saw
black grass there.
Ah, yes. It's a
bad omen, indeed.
You just try and be
careful out there, Dan.
[LILIA] So this junk is
what we saw shimmering?
What is this thing?
And how is it so ugly?
You know, it kinda looks
like you, Navirou.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Well, whatever it is,
it's gotta be pretty old.
And look at that mural.
What's it mean?
[LUTE yelping]
Oh, come on, how many
times do you think
we're gonna fall for that one?
No! Over there! It's an egg!
An egg? Really?
Nuh-uh, nuh-uh, nuh-uh!
No way! It can't be!
[LUTE] That's an egg,
all right! I'm sure of it!
You see? An egg!
And, uh, what part of that is
supposed to be an egg, exactly?
I don't know, Navirou.
I mean, yeah, it's
all covered in moss,
but it sure looks
like an egg to me.
[CHEVAL]
Hm.
But it's way too old to still
be alive, don't ya think?
Uh-uh. It's alive.
I can feel it.
Ha. Here he goes again with
his "I can feel it" business.
Meanwhile, your feelings
haven't been right
about a single thing yet.
Lilia, you got any idea
how we hatch this thing?
Hatch an egg?
Well, I'm pretty sure we need
the Kinship Rite to do that.
And that would require
a Kinship Stone.
A Kinship Stone.
That's a problem.
We haven't gotten our
Kinship Stones yet.
But by this time
tomorrow, we will have.
Come on, Lute, can't hatching
this egg wait just one more day?
I mean, it's just that...
I feel like this guy
wants to hatch now.
[BOTH gasp]
Let's do it, guys!
But how? You heard
what she said.
I don't know, but Lilia
the All-Knowing must, right?
Don't be silly!
Yeah, but you do
know, don't you?
How you're supposed to
perform the Kinship Rite?
Yeah, of course I do.
I thought only a Rider
with a Kinship Stone
would be capable
of hatching an egg?
Well, then we just need to
become Riders, don't we?
And how exactly are we
supposed to become Riders?
[LILIA] Okay. Hold up
your Kinship Stones.
But these are just
plain old rocks.
Hey, quiet down!
This ceremony is sacred!
Oh, all right. So
we're playing pretend.
Okay, now comes the part
where you address the egg.
Introduce yourself.
Okay, my name is Lute.
O holy Kinship Stone,
please wouldst thou
bind together Lute
with this slumbering creature.
And now for the
moment of new life.
Awaken!
[LUTE]
What?
It didn't work?
I don't get it. I said all the
words right and everything!
[LUTE] Yeah, and I was really
going along with it, too.
Oh well.
Looks like you do need a
real Kinship Stone after all.
I guess we should head
back to the village.
Yeah.
But you wait,
'cause I am definitely
gonna hatch this thing
at the Kinship Rite tomorrow!
Just hang in there
till then, all right!
After that, you get
to be my Monstie!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
The egg is hatching!
It's-- It's being born!
Oh, wow! That's a...
a Flame Wyvern!
Rathalos, King of the Skies!
But what does this mean?
Oh, boy! Navirou always
knew you could do it, Lute!
Navirou always believed in you!
Oh, you did? Really?
[NAVIROU]
That's the truth!
[laughs] You know what?
Right now, I don't even care!
[LUTE]
You hatched for me.
I'm grateful.
Hold on.
He may've hatched,
but you still don't have
Kinship with him yet.
Be careful.
Oh, don't worry, it's fine.
He's my Monstie after all!
Isn't that right, Ratha?
Ratha? But that's a Rathalos.
No, this guy is my Rathalos.
And his name's Ratha!
[LILIA , CHEVAL laugh]
[screams]
Jeez, Navirou,
do you ever give up?
Yeah, you're not fooling
anybody, you know.
No, no! For real! It's back!
It's back! This isn't a joke!
[NAVIROU screams]
Ya see?
Stay back! This is
just a hatchling!
[yells]
Uh-oh.
[roars]
Look out!
Ratha!
Whoa!
[roars]
[DAN]
You all right?
Where'd you come from?
Lemme guess, you've got
a beehive on you.
No wonder you guys have
an Arzuros on your tail
carrying that around!
Gimme!
You're our hero!
[DAN]
Don't give me that nonsense!
[screams]
Hey, hold on a second.
What's with this Rathalos?
[GAMIGAMI]
Honestly!
You kids may've
gotten lucky this time,
but confronting an Arzuros
without a weapon or a Monstie
might just be the
most reckless thing
I've ever heard of
in my entire life!
Not to mention the fact
that you ventured
into the Forbidden Land!
I mean, what were you
even doing there anyway?
I know you were behind this,
weren't you, Lute? Admit it!
I thought there might
be an egg there.
Foolish boy!
Why do you always do
things like this?
[DAN] Gotta say,
I'm a little surprised.
Whoever heard of hatching an
egg without a Kinship Stone?
It is remarkable.
Perhaps this miracle
justifies and excuses
their little transgression.
You're too easy
on the boy, Chief.
For goodness' sake,
these children barely
made it back here at all!
I completely agree. I was
worried sick about you.
So don't think you can
escape my punishment.
Cheval, Lute, and Lilia,
none of you will be getting
any dessert tonight.
Aw, but, Mom.
You really mean that?
But we love the
desserts you make!
They're all so
incredibly delicious!
I'm sorry, but I was
really worried this time.
Sorry, Mom.
Yeah, sorry, Mrs. Vlau.
I'm sorry.
You guys better think long
and hard about what you did.
You, too, Navi.
There will be no donuts
for you tonight.
[screams]
Say it ain't so!
[ALL laughing]
All right, everybody, remember,
tomorrow is our
great Kinship Rite.
I think that we should
all get some rest now.
Oh, hey, Chief,
is it okay if I take this
little fella home with me?
[CHIEF OMNA]
Hmm.
I doubt he'd leave
your side anyway.
[CHIEF OMNA] "When an ebon
darkness is born upon the Earth,
it is then that we seek
the coming of the One.
See, he comes astride
a dragon white."
[LUTE]
Hey, Lute here!
Now that I've formed
Kinship with Ratha,
I'm finally gonna be an
honest-to-goodness Rider!
Whoa, what's that?
A Tigrex attack?
Next time: "A Monstie Is Born!"
Ride On!