[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming
the world's top Monster Rider.
Lute and his fellow Riders
Cheval, Mille, and Hyoro
worked together to
defeat a Nargacuga,
who had been afflicted
with the Black Blight.
Afterwards, under the
guidance of Chief Omna,
these brave youngsters
embarked upon an adventure
to purify the world's
Kinship Ore.
Along the way, Lute and Navirou
stumbled upon Avinia,
a Rider who had fled
from another village
with her Barioth
Monstie, Frostfang.
The experience left all
three encouraged to discover
that they're not alone in their
mission to stop the Black Blight
and save the world.
And now, the band of Riders
finally arrives at
their destination!
Expect big things from Navirou!
[ALL]
Whoa.
[MILLE]
So this is Gildegaran.
[LUTE]
It's so big!
Wow, just get a load of
all these people here!
Everyone's so fashionable!
Man, this place is nothing
like Hakum Village.
Well, of course it isn't.
This city is Hunter central!
Hm. Navirou feels
an intense gaze.
Is that a Felyne there?
What weird whiskers.
Weird face, too.
He's weird all over.
[NAVIROU] Heh, seems everyone's
fascinated by ol' Navirou.
[NAVIROU laughs]
[LUTE]
C'mon, Navirou! We're leaving!
Wait up guys! Hey!
[chuckles]
Now there's some easy marks.
Excuse me, do you know
where I might be able
to find the Royal Scriveners?
The Scriveners?
[HUNTER B]
Hmm...
Oh, you may wanna
try the Hunter's Guild.
Uh, the Hunter's Guild?
[LUTE] Lilia isn't wasting
any time looking for Simone.
She must really wanna see her.
Yeah, well, I don't
get what's so great
about the Scriveners anyway.
Uh, hey, so have any
of you guys noticed
that we all look
completely different
from everybody else here?
Huh, you think so?
I guess maybe a little.
[NAVIROU] Yeah, Navirou was just
noticing how lame you guys look.
[DEBLI]
Hey, country bumpkins!
Must be your first time
here, am I right?
Well, not to worry,
I can show you around!
What do you want?
I'm the hottest Hunter in town!
You can call me Debli,
or for short, D.B.L!
Debli!
[ALL]
"Tubby"?
No, not Tubby! Debli! Debli!
Ha. Just walk away.
Navirou's gut says you should.
Listen here, you--!
Don't mind him.
This guy's gut hasn't
been right once.
Ha! You seem like a fella
who knows what's what.
So where're you
fine folks from?
Oh, we're from a small
town called Hakum Vill--
Watch it, Lute!
You know we have
to keep the whole
"you-guys-being-Riders"
thing a secret.
Oh, yeah, right.
C'mon, let's get moving!
Ow, stop! Lilia,
that really hurts!
[DEBLI]
Hey! Wait! Come back here!
Dang.
Don't think that I'm just gonna
give up that easily, you rubes!
So then, what do we do now?
To eat a donut or a soufflé,
that is the question, is it not?
Well, I'd like to
find the Scriveners.
I wanna find an inn
and get situated.
Uh...
'Kay.
I'll go with Lilia to
track down the Scriveners.
Hyoro and Mille can
try to find an inn.
[HYORO]
Okay.
[MILLE]
Sure.
[LUTE]
What about you, Cheval?
Uh. I guess I'll--
[BOY A laughing]
[MOM A]
Slow down!
You're gonna fall and
hurt yourself again!
[BOY A]
I'm fine, Mom!
I'll go look for an inn
with Hyoro and Mille.
I'm not big on crowded places.
Now just a minute!
First we need to get either
donuts or a soufflé!
Okay, so let's all meet
back here at noon then.
Sounds good!
Wait for Navirou!
[LUTE]
Wow!
Just look at all the
stuff they have here!
What the heck kind of
creature is that?
Is it a Felyne?
If it is, it's a weird one!
Oh, that is way beyond weird!
Don't let those jerks
get to you, Navi.
Yeah, that's right.
You're just you, Navirou!
Always the center of attention
wherever Navirou goes.
It's not easy being
a chosen one.
[laughs]
Nothing gets to Navi, huh?
Yeah, he can get
by no matter what.
[GENTOR]
Hey!
So it is you.
The outsiders who've
been causing a ruckus
throughout the town.
Well, there has been a little
fuss surrounding Navi, but--
What with being such an
awe-inspiring specimen and all.
And what are you, exactly?
Navirou, one of the chosen
Felyne, at your service.
I see. And where are
you travelers from?
Oh, we're from a small
town called Hakum--
I told you not to tell
anyone about that!
Oh, right, sorry.
Heh. Tangle with us and you're
gonna get burned, buddy.
So what you're saying is
that this little oddball
is a Felyne,
and you people can't say
where precisely it is
that you come from!
Pretty much.
Well, I don't know if that's
quite how I'd put it, but yeah.
Ah, yes, yes, so I see.
I understand it all
perfectly now.
Take them away!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[LUTE, NAVIROU scream]
But, sir, I promise you,
we're not shady or anything!
Navirou's face may be,
but that's all!
[yelps]
You can plead your case
back at the station.
[GUILD MASTER]
What's all this?
I apologize for the
sudden interruption,
Captain Gentor,
but would you mind
leaving these three
for me to deal with?
Huh? He looks kinda familiar.
Yeah, right?
Sir!
Understood, Master, sir!
[LUTE, NAVIROU, LILIA]
Whoa, "Master"?
Indeed!
This personage here hails from
the Hunter's Guild headquarters.
He is the Guild Master!
[ALL gasp]
That's right, and my old
friend Omna has told me
all about you little
adventurers.
Wait. You're saying that
you know Chief Omna?
Oh, yes.
Let me formally welcome
you to Gildegaran,
home of the Hunter's Guild.
So there you have it.
Omna and I grew up together, as
close as if we'd been brothers.
Wow, really?
Sounds a lot like you
and Cheval, actually.
Guess so.
Heh. Feels like I know you.
You must be...
Ah, yes, Lilia the All-Knowing.
You want to be a Scrivener.
Right!
[GUILD MASTER]
And you must be Lute.
I hear you hatched a Rathalos
without using a Kinship Stone.
Sure did!
[GUILD MASTER]
And you're Navirou!
That's right!
[GUILD MASTER] Your talent is,
well, it hasn't been mentioned.
[yelps]
Oh, of course, Lilia's
a master at combining.
Isn't that right?
Yep.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Oh, no, no, no.
What?
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
It's nothing. Never mind.
I've heard about it.
The Energy Drinks that you make
and how extremely
bitter they are.
Bitter as life itself!
That's right. So bitter!
Amazing! You really
do know everything!
Yes, Omna speaks very
highly of you all,
and in extensive detail.
In fact, from the way
he boasts about you,
I would say he practically
sees you as his own children.
Really? He does?
But going back, Energy Drinks
as bitter as life itself?
What does that even mean?
Jeez, let it go, Lilia. We were
having a real moment there.
Both sides of the
Hunter-Rider divide
could afford to understand
one another better.
Oh, yeah, that's for sure.
We've never left
the village before,
so there's a lot about Hunters
that we don't get at all.
Back home, we were
always under the belief
that everybody
grew up to be Riders,
forming Kinship with monsters.
But that just isn't
the case, is it?
Well, you see, in some
ways, it is in fact true,
while in other ways, it isn't.
[ALL]
Huh?
Hunters have to work hard, too.
They perfect their skills daily,
and make their living by
taking on hunting orders,
or as we call them, Quests.
Quests, huh?
Meanwhile, we here provide
support to aid in their hunting,
like sending Hunters
to base camp
and preparing
essential hunting tools
for them to use on their Quests.
Huh?
Oh, yes! I've got
a tremendous idea!
While you're here,
why don't I have you go on a
Quest just like the Hunters do?
It'll be a great
learning experience.
Yeah, that sounds like fun!
Just be careful, Lute.
You can't let anyone find out
that you're a Rider, remember.
This again? Why such secrecy?
[gasps]
Uh, I-I totally wasn't
eavesdropping on you
from behind that
sculpture just now!
[LUTE, LILIA, NAVIROU]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[ELDEST DAUGHTER]
Oh my goodness,
what are we going
to do with you?
Our sincerest apologies.
We'll have a word
with her later.
So, um, were all three of
you eavesdropping?
[ELDEST DAUGHTER]
Oh, dear.
[ELDEST DAUGHTER chuckles]
Today's your lucky day, ladies,
because you get to meet the
chosen Felyne, Navirou,
or for short, N.V.R.
Navirou!
He sure picked that up fast.
Of all the things to pick up.
[NAVIROU]
And you are?
Oh, my. Where are our manners?
I'm so sorry, we're three
sisters who work here
at the Hunter's Guild
headquarters.
If there's anything you
don't understand, just ask!
Yes, whatever you may
need, we'll do our best.
In other words, they'll
support you while you're here
and cater to your every need.
[LUTE gasps]
Wow, this city truly is the
most fantastic place ever!
So come on, you've gotta tell us
what it's like bending
monsters to your will.
What? We can't bend
monsters to our will.
But that's what you do.
You're a Rider.
No way.
They aren't nearly
obedient enough
for us to try to force
them to do anything.
You'd have to have really strong
Kinship with them for that.
Whoa, really?
My goodness.
Could you tell us
any more about it?
[bell tolls]
Ah, Sounds like it's
lunchtime already.
Now that you mention
it, I am hungry.
Here's a chance to experience
the Hunter lifestyle.
You should go out and
eat a nice lunch in town.
Yes, sir!
But first, we have to
meet up with our friends
who came with us
from the village.
Please, take this list
of great restaurants.
How very thoughtful of you!
Or wait, could it be that you're
in love with... Navirou?
[ALL chuckling]
[NAVIROU] Navirou's sorry for--
Navirou's just sorry.
And in the meantime,
I'll get in touch with the
Scriveners for you, Lilia.
Thank you very much, sir!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys!
[LILIA]
Did you find an inn yet?
About that.
We got a little lost.
The big city's a lot more
confusing than our village!
[laughs]
Sounds like you could've used
Navirou's navigation
skills after all!
That wouldn't've helped.
No way.
Not quite.
Not at all.
Nada.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Anyway, come on,
let's go grab some lunch.
We've got a list of good
places to check out!
[LILIA] Wow! Just look at
all this scrumptious food!
I've never seen
such beautiful cakes.
What kind of veggie is that?
Wow, I have no idea!
[squeals]
[NAVIROU] Such a dazzling
display of delectable donuts.
What a glorious
time to be alive!
So who's eating what?
Want a soufflé, Cheval?
Nah, nothing sweet for me.
Oh.
Then how about
some meat instead?
We'll have a contest to
see who can eat the most!
Oh, yeah, meat sounds good!
All right, let's eat!
Ride On!
Rathian!
[NAVIROU screaming]
[GUILD MASTER]
All right then,
I'll go ahead and take Lilia
to see the Scriveners now.
The rest of you can
head off to the inn.
Thank you so much for
everything you've done!
Oh, and say hi to Simone for us.
So is she never gonna
come back again, ever?
[LUTE chuckles]
It's not like I care!
Fear not, Mille!
For the two of you are
bound by a deep Kinship.
You may be apart, but your
hearts will never let go!
Oh, that was good!
Yes, that was very good.
And very irritating.
Well, setting all
that aside for now,
we're still friends,
first and foremost.
I'm so excited! I finally
get to see the Red Swan!
Red Swan? And what is that?
Another name for Captain Simone.
She's my role model.
I wanna be just
like her someday.
[sighs]
Oh, Captain Simone.
Lilia!
Captain Simone!
I'm so glad you made it. Here.
Oh, Lilia, I'm thrilled
to see you again, truly.
Oh, yes, so am I!
Woohoo! Woohoo!
What a fine example
of a lieutenant.
He must be incredibly loyal.
[MILLE]
I don't see any inn.
But the map says it should
be around here somewhere.
Maybe it's over there?
[LUTE]
Huh?
[DEBLI laughs]
Well, fancy running into
you fine folks here!
[LUTE]
This guy? Again?
[HYORO]
It's, uh, De-De--
Tub-something!
No, no, I'm not Tub-anything!
I'm Debli, dang it!
Or, for short, D--!
Give it a rest, will you?
But I--
Uh, so what are you
doing here, anyway?
You're in our way, so move.
You sure about that?
The Forest of Confusion's that
way. It's dark even in daylight!
Plus it's crawling
with monsters!
[MILLE]
Yeah, and?
[CHEVAL]
Is there a problem?
Uh! I mean.
You should be prepared in case
you meet a monster out there!
Lucky for you guys,
I'm willing to sell you some of
my Debli-brand Hunter supplies!
No, thanks.
We don't need any.
That stuff's garbage.
[DEBLI]
No, it's not!
It's all very useful equipment
to have on a hunt!
[LUTE] Then we
definitely don't need it.
We're not going on a hunt.
[chuckles]
Well, then, I can't
be held responsible
if some black
monster attacks you!
Wait, a black monster?
Yup, that's right.
Rumor has it a
creepy black monster's
been showing up in
the forest lately.
[gong sounds]
What's that?
That's it!
What's "it"? What do you mean?
That alarm we're
hearing right now
means that a monster's
been spotted.
It sounds like it's coming
from the Forest of Confusion,
so that's where it must be!
Forest of Confusion.
Let's go.
[DEBLI]
Hey, don't blame me!
I tried to warn you.
Monsters are trouble.
[LUTE]
Which way back to our Monsties?
[NAVIROU]
Right! To the right!
[MILLE]
Straight ahead it is!
--[LUTE, CHEVAL, HYORO] Got it!
--[NAVIROU] Hey!
[LUTE]
There they are!
Hey, wait. Where'd mine go?
[roaring]
What?
So Blighted monsters
have started showing up
near the city now, too, really?
Yes.
I'm afraid the situation is
just as dire as you reported.
At least, the Hunters were
able to slay them right away,
so there was no damage, but...
That means the Black Blight
is starting to spread.
Seems that way.
For right now, we're
operating under the belief
that the most effective way
for us to stop the Blight
is to purify the Kinship Ore.
You demonstrated
that quite clearly.
Oh, that wasn't me.
It was my Rider friends.
They were the ones
courageous enough
to stand up to that
Blighted Nargacuga.
Still, they're your friends.
Yeah, well, I guess they are.
In any event, if we're
serious about preventing
any more of these monsters
from being Blighted,
then we can't merely
slay the Blighted beasts.
We also need to purify
the Kinship Ore.
You'll hear no objection
out of me, Captain Simone.
You have the full support
of the Hunter's Guild.
Thank you, sir.
[LUTE]
There it is.
[HYORO]
It's definitely Blighted.
We've gotta beat it.
Ride On!
Rathian!
All right, Ride On!
Velocidrome!
[LUTE]
Time to stop this!
You got it! Let's get
it on our level!
Yes!
Now! Charge!
[LUTE]
All right!
Whoa. What are these people?
They're awesome!
[gasps]
That's bad!
Amazing!
Riders. They must be the
ones I've heard about.
[LUTE]
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
[gasps]
What do I mean? Uh, you just--
Wow, Cheval! You were amazing!
Yeah, but it was almost
like that wasn't you at all.
It was just that--
if I hadn't've--
I thought that someone
would get hurt.
[DEBLI]
Hey! Ha-ha!
Oh, whoa! You guys are
like crazy powerful!
Where'd you come from?
Well, you were
pretty good, I guess,
but you, my friend,
were somethin' else!
You're like a real
top-of-the-line Hunter!
[CHEVAL]
Huh?
You really think so?
[DEBLI] Totally! You've
got a lotta potential!
Hey, look,
Cheval's cheering up.
[CHEVAL, DEBLI laughing]
Oh, man, am I beat!
We never did find
that inn, though.
[LILIA]
Hey, welcome back, guys!
Long time no see, eh?
Oh, wow! You're
already a Scrivener?
Well, uh, actually,
I'm still an apprentice.
Regardless, Lilia
is one of us now.
Oh, thank you, Simone.
I mean, Captain.
Good for you, Lilia!
The uniform looks good on you.
Aw, thanks, guys!
Oh!
I heard you did an amazing
job out there, Cheval.
Stopping that Kecha Wacha.
Yeah, well...
I just... wanna be stronger.
Strong enough to stop any
monster who's been Blighted.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Kecha Wacha!
That's one fancy-looking face!
The Kecha Wacha hops
around in the treetops,
using its tricky movements
to toy with its prey!
The mucus it shoots from
its nose is bad news, too!
It'd make a fine
Monstie, though!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
First we wind up crashing at
ace Hunter Reverto's place,
and then I've gotta do a
Guild Quest all on my own?
Next time: "Nerscylla Blitz!"
Ride On!