[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a Quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Along the way, Lute and
Navirou came across Debli
selling imitation
Kinship Stones,
and together, they ventured into
the mine where he'd found them.
Alas, awaiting them there were
the monster-mechanizing
Dr. Manelger and his loyal
assistant Itsy-Bits.
Soon, they learned that
in addition to monsters,
Manelger had been
modifying Felynes as well.
With the help of
some old friends,
Navirou regained the
memories that he had lost
and recalled that once,
he too had been modifed.
Lute and the others
had finally managed
to escape the dastardly duo,
when they noticed that
Ratha was acting strangely.
At that moment, Avinia appeared
and told them that Ratha
had been stricken
with the Black Blight.
Still, Lute maintained
faith in their Kinship.
Just then, who should swoop
in out of nowhere but--
Your Rathalos has been
afflicted with the Blight.
It must be destroyed!
Cheval, no.
[NAVIROU]
Is that really Cheval?
He is standing on Rathi, but--
[DEBLI]
Yeah, what's with all
the Azure Rathalos
gear he's wearing?
How'd he get his hands on that?
Don't tell us you've joined
forces with Manelger!
I joined forces with no one.
Wow, he even sounds tougher.
I'm not the boy I used to be.
Cheval...
Lute. Hand over that Rathalos.
Don't try to resist,
or I'll have to hurt you.
Is that how it is? You mean it?
Blighted monsters
must be defeated.
Every one of them.
Ratha is gonna be fine!
I'll get him back to
normal in no time.
No use.
There's only one way to stop the
Blight, and that's to slay him.
Well, I'll stop it!
I speak now as a Rider
who slayed an Azure
Rathalos for this armor.
I've seen a lot since that day.
The day I decided to
walk a different path.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[CHEVAL]
It was horrible.
So much more of the
world had been stricken
with the Black Blight than
I ever could've imagined.
[CHEVAL]
I saw Hunters fight desperately
to slay the Blighted monsters.
[CHEVAL]
To keep the people safe.
That's when it hit me.
[CHEVAL]
All this time,
what have we been
doing with ourselves?
[MILLE]
Cheval.
[HYORO] But Riders... we're
the only ones who can Ride On.
It's what we do.
[CHEVAL] And yet we
couldn't protect them.
Not Hakum Village.
And not my mom.
[CHEVAL] Ever since then, I'd
been wondering why that was.
[CHEVAL]
Then I understood.
Merely protecting
people isn't enough.
[MILLE] That's right.
We have to slay the monsters!
[HYORO]
Yeah. Let's wipe 'em out.
[CHEVAL]
Since that realization,
we've taken on Quests
like the Hunters do,
slaying Blighted monsters.
[yells]
[CHEVAL] We're just as
strong as any Hunters.
That's what we learned...
when we slayed this Rathalos.
[roars]
[CHEVAL] Well, that's an Azure
Rathalos for you. And yet--
[yells]
Stay strong, Rathian!
I can't afford to
lose this battle!
So let's go!
Time to unleash
the Scorching Slice!
We're not just some
monster keepers anymore!
We're the chosen ones.
We'll save the world by
slaying Blighted monsters.
[CHEVAL] This equipment
is proof of our might,
and how far we've come.
Wow, it sounds like they
really did go through a lot.
The look in their
eyes is different.
Yeah, but we're Riders!
Cheval, Mille, and Hyoro, too.
All of us are Riders!
Oh, we're Riders, all right.
But the Rider I've become
is nothing like the ones
you're thinking about.
[gasps]
It's the same.
Riders are all people who
form Kinship with Monsties!
And that's enough to
keep everyone safe?
What if Ratha--?
That Rathalos there.
What if it ran amok
and attacked a village?
That's right, Lute.
What would you do then?
Could you stop him?
Stop and protect!
Protect it, you mean.
And the villagers!
Both of them!
It's pointless for us
to keep talking.
Raise your sword, Lute.
The days of us joining
hands are over.
This is the end.
Whoa!
Oh, this ain't good!
I won't part ways with you.
We're family, Cheval!
[AVINIA]
This precious sword I'm holding
has been handed down in
my village for generations.
But it's rusty now, thanks to
the Black Blight's influence.
It'll never be like it once was.
As my village will
never be the same again.
But still, my Kinship
with Frostfang,
it's managed to imbue within
this sword the tiniest light.
[BOTH gasp]
[AVINIA]
Back when I lost my village,
I took this sword as a reminder,
so I wouldn't forget
my resentment.
But these days, I carry
it as a warning.
About what?
We humans can be
foolish sometimes.
[AVINIA] There had been
outbreaks of the Black Blight
here and there for so long,
yet we ignored the changes.
The Black Blight spread because
we cared only about ourselves,
and paid no attention
to our surroundings.
True enough,
but back in my town,
everyone's working together
as hard as they can
to put our lives back to normal.
Of course.
In times like these,
humans also help one another.
And the Kinship
with our Monsties--
If you have that Kinship,
then I believe the Black
Blight can be halted,
even in those Blighted monsters,
who are far more powerful than
we humans could ever be.
You get it, don't you, Lute?
I do. I know I can
stop Ratha's Blight.
Navirou believes in you!
Then use your strength
and prove it.
Let's see if you can stop us.
To inspire you, I'll deal
that beast its final blow.
Cheval, stop!
[yells]
Oh, Lute!
This just got really real!
Hold it right there!
Lilia filled us in.
Enough of this nonsense!
Why are you two at
each others' throats?
You're supposed to be friends.
I'm sorry, Stone, but--
Big brother.
This isn't the time
for infighting!
But Ratha's been infected
with the Black Blight, Genie!
[gasps]
Seriously?
What if he attacks
someone, huh? Then what?
You don't understand anything
that's going on here!
What happened to us,
the tragedy of Hakum Village,
must never happen again.
[CHEVAL]
And this one...
This one must be slain!
[LUTE yells]
[DEBLI gasps]
Lute, no!
You haven't changed.
It's just like every other time
you've lost your temper.
I have changed Lute.
Do it, Rathian.
[CHEVAL]
Get him out of here.
[LUTE yells]
Whoa, Lute! Uh, Lute,
are you okay there?
There's no way he's okay!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[RATHA cries]
So you've still got
enough strength to move.
The power of their Kinship...
Well, in that case,
let's do this.
We should join them.
You're right.
Now Ride On!
Rathian!
Rathalos!
[LUTE]
Ratha!
Do you really think you can win
with your Rathalos in
such a weakened state?
I don't care about
winning or losing!
I believe strongly in
my Kinship with Ratha!
And, Cheval, in my
Kinship with you!
Demolition Dash!
Then Demolition Dash it is!
That's some pretty weak
Kinship you've got
with your Monoblos
there, little brother.
Maybe, but I can see
through your every move!
Stone, I won't go easy.
[STONE]
Stop this, Mille!
I've changed, Stone. You'll see!
[STONE]
So be it.
Magma Surge!
Mille, please.
I'm not done yet!
Time to Rock Smash!
[roars]
They're so strong!
Holy donuts!
Team Cheval is kicking
some major butt!
Why are you admiring
them, Debli?!
What? No way! I am not!
No matter how much
you've changed,
you're still Cheval!
You can never get back
what you've lost!
And all these Blighted monsters
will never be restored
to the way they once were!
Even our Kinship
can't reach them!
They can only be
slain! Right now!
[BOTH yelp]
See, Lute! I'm not
like you anymore!
Rathi! You don't really wanna
be doing this, right? Right?
Cheval's making you do it
against your will, right?
Isn't that right? Blink
twice for "yes"! Hm?
Out of my way.
[screams]
Lute and Ratha's
Kinship is solid!
Navirou believes in it 100%!
So do I!
Yeah, me, too!
Besides, I don't
wanna see you two
fighting each other anymore!
Wow, guys.
Cheval, I swear, I won't quit
till we see eye-to-eye!
Because our Kinship
can never be broken!
[CHEVAL]
We'll see about that.
Scorching Slice!
[roars]
Ratha, no!
Now do you understand, Lute?
It's not the same
Rathalos it used to be!
Ratha.
It's all right, Ratha!
Just calm down!
I'm right here with you!
Don't be afraid!
Our Kinship can never be broken!
It's the light of Kinship.
[RATHA roars]
Yeah, come on, Ratha!
Let's Sky-High Dive!
Blow them away, Rathian!
Scorching Slice!
[LUTE yells]
My goal is to purify
the Black Blight.
And I know that I can
purify the monsters, too!
Oh, thank goodness.
Ratha's back!
What a relief.
Yeah!
Navirou is so unbelievably
moved by all of this right now!
His overjoyed heart can't
stop sweating tears!
It can't be.
Has he really managed
to subdue the Blight?
Is it true?
Yes.
The black haze is gone now!
Yeah.
Cheval!
Only the power of Kinship
can drive away the
Black Blight for good!
That's right. There's no
greater power than Kinship.
Don't you remember, Cheval?!
We all raised Ratha
together, as friends!
I'll let it slide now.
But there's no next time!
I won't give up. Our
Kinship is still unbroken!
I just--
I'm only trying to make up
for not protecting
the village before.
We're not done!
[LUTE] You worked hard out
there, Ratha. Thank you.
You get some rest now.
I'd never seen such
sad eyes before.
[NAVIROU]
Cheval's, you mean?
No. His Monstie's.
The Rathian's.
Yeah.
[gasps]
Sorry. I, uh...
It's okay. We'll tell Chief
Omna what happened today.
We're gonna head back
to the village now.
We'll be apart,
but still connected.
That goes for Cheval, too.
Right.
[NAVIROU]
Navirou's gotta say...
Phew! Been a long
couple of days!
Hey, you two, take a load off!
I'll go rustle us
up an inn, okay?
And some donuts, too!
[LUTE]
Actually, I am hungry.
Let's grab a bite!
[FIFI]
Ah, we've been waiting for you!
[LUTE]
Hm?
We wanted to thank
you for your help.
[NAVIROU] Oh, look!
It's Navirou's old friends!
And donuts!
Whenever you're in a pinch,
we'll be there to help you out!
And that's the Numbers' Kinship!
[NUMBERS]
Mh-hm!
[ALL]
Yeah!
And with that said,
donuts ahoy!
Om, nom, nom, nom, nom!
Bet Cheval feels the
same way about you!
I have no idea
what you're saying!
[ALL laughing]
Hey.
Whoa, Mister!
[REVERTO]
We're goin' on a Quest, kid.
Huh? A Quest?
Like now? Right now?
Stat? You mean A.S.A.P?
It involves one of that mad
scientist's mecha-monsters.
A mecha-monster.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties!
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Gravios!
Its solid, stable stance makes
it a perfect fit for Stone!
It can even wade into lava
thanks to its super-thick shell!
And that Magma Surge Kinship
Attack sure packed a punch!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, Lute here!
Rumor has it they show up
deep in the Dovan Volcano.
And who might "they"
be? That's right, ghosts!
Next time: "Be the
Forest, Be the Beast"!
Ride On!