The outside world.
[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming the
world's top Monster Rider.
Along with his friends, Lute is
leaving Hakum Village behind
and venturing out into
the great wide world.
Ratha has to be out there.
He has to be; I'm sure of it!
Yeah, along with some tasty
donuts we've never tried before!
[BOTH]
Let's go find 'em!
First we have to
go to Gildegaran,
where Captain Simone is.
Let's head out!
[wheezing]
Hey, Hyoro, are you all right?
I think so...
It's easy to get lost
around here, so stay close.
[LILIA] They say that
in the Sea of Trees,
if you get lost, you'll lose
all sense of direction
and never find your
way out again.
[squeals]
Okay, no matter what,
I'm gonna stay right with you.
Oh, come on.
Jeez, Hyoro, you're
always slowing us down.
So, Mille, even after
all this walking,
we still have a long,
long way to go, right?
Yeah, of course we do.
It's a journey.
Then that means, we have
to camp out here at night?
Yeah, of course we do.
It's a journey.
And camping means that
we have to sleep outside,
isn't that right?
Yes, of course we do. Why are
you asking all this now?
Well, I... I've never been
outside Hakum Village before.
And there's no telling
what we might encounter.
Yeah, that's right,
which is the whole reason
why Chief Omna gave us
these things, remember?
Uh, sure I do, but--
[LUTE] Besides, it'll be
fun camping together!
Sleeping under the stars.
Right, Cheval?
[CHEVAL]
Yeah.
Lute's got a point.
A journey should be enjoyed.
Uh-huh!
The outside world
is one of freedom,
with no rules to tie us down!
Which means that we can eat
as many donuts as we want,
whenever we want!
Ah! No fair!
You're eating again?
Slow down. We have a ways to go.
You shouldn't eat
them all at once.
Whenever someone asks
why Navirou eats donuts,
he always answers,
"Because the donuts are there!"
And that's a Navi-rule.
[stomach growls]
Uh. Guess I must be getting
kinda hungry myself.
Oh, thank goodness!
I didn't wanna say anything,
but I've been starving
this whole time!
Gosh, you guys are too much.
But I guess a short break--
[LUTE, HYORO]
All right! Let's chow down!
Yum!
Well-Done Steak is great!
Ahh... I'm completely stuffed!
That oughta get us through
the rest of the day.
Huh? Wait, but how much longer
do we still have to walk today?
Until the sun goes
down, of course.
[HYORO groans]
I knew it.
But look, the Arctic
Ridge is right up ahead.
It won't be easy.
We have to be prepared.
[LILIA chuckles]
Luckily, I've been saving
a special drink I mixed up,
just for this occasion.
You see? It's a
batch of Hot Drink!
[LILIA] One sip of this will
warm your body right up!
You won't even feel the cold!
Here, go on, drink!
What do we do?
I don't think I can drink it.
Who's up first?
Draw numbers?
Guess it's the only way.
Uh, what's going on guys?
We're about to take our lives
into our own hands here!
[ALL]
Ready, go!
Aww!
Oh, fine. This is how
I live my life--boldly!
[LUTE screams]
Great. Now you guys.
[ALL]
Uh... Okay.
[ALL yelp]
Uh, yeah. Navirou's gonna pass.
Hey, wait. I think it's working.
I feel warmer now.
Whoa, you're right!
It's amazing!
That's our Lilia!
Although, wouldn't it be more
amazing if it tasted better?
[chuckles]
We'll stay nice and toasty
in the frigid Arctic Ridge,
even if there's a
blizzard up there.
The only thing left is to make
sure we have enough food to eat.
Yeah, well, that's the
part that has me worried.
Some way, somehow,
we really are
going to need to find
food supplies somewhere.
I know, let's look
here in the forest,
before we go up
to the Arctic Ridge.
[CHEVAL]
Good thinking.
[LILIA] Okay, when the sun
is directly overhead,
we'll all meet back here.
Try to gather as
much as you can.
Also, it's really easy to
get lost in these woods,
so be sure not to stray too far.
[OTHERS]
Got it!
You think that's enough?
[LILIA]
Oh! I might be able to use these
Herbs in my combinations.
[MILLE]
Incredible!
Hyoro, look, all of these
trees are full of fruit, too!
[HYORO] But I-I can't--
I can't carry any more.
[HYORO yelps]
Wow!
There are all kinds of fruits
I've never even seen before!
It's just like I thought it
would be outside the village!
[stomach grumbles]
Oh, man, wonder if
any of these trees
have donuts growing on 'em.
Wha--?!
A donut tree! Donuts!
Hey, wait!
[CHEVAL] What's taking
Lute and Navirou so long?
[MILLE]
We just started our journey.
How can he already be lost?
Oh, for goodness sake,
this always happens when
those two go off together.
Well then, maybe we
shouldn't go any farther
and just rest here tonight?
No, I think I'm gonna go
look around a little more.
Yeah, me, too.
Count me in.
--[screeching]
--[rustling]
[screams]
[HYORO]
Wait for me! I'm coming, too!
These aren't donuts.
They're just plain old fruit.
What a world. Where, oh,
where are Navirou's donuts?
[LUTE chuckles]
[LUTE] What can I say?
You already ate 'em all.
Come on, let's go back.
Uh. Wait, so which
way did we come from?
Stand back. This calls for
Navirou's navigation skills.
This way!
Which means... we go this way.
Hey, wait, Lute, why
are you going that way?
Because your sense of direction
is always totally wrong.
It's more reliable to go
the exact opposite way.
What?!
You mean you don't trust
Navirou's navigation?!
[screaming]
Hey, where you going, Navirou?
What's a big rock doing here?
[screams]
The rock started rolling!
[LUTE] That's not a rock,
it's a Konchu!
Run!
Yeah, well, what the heck is
a Konchu doing here, huh?
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
That was all your
fault, Navirou.
Hey, was not!
Navirou didn't put that
Konchu there, so--! So cold!
Huh? Hey, so where are we?
Don't tell me we ran all the
way to the Arctic Ridge.
And what was that?
Oh, it's probably just
some thunder.
But never mind that, let's
head back to the others. Uh?
[sneezes]
[NAVIROU]
Oh, no, not another Konchu!
[LUTE] It's snowballing!
And it's headed right for us!
[BOTH scream]
Let's get outta here!
[BOTH screaming]
We searched everywhere and
still couldn't find 'em.
[MILLE] And now it looks
like the weather's
taking a turn for the worse.
This is bad.
What should we do now, Cheval?
It's getting pretty late and
it's gonna be dark soon.
Let's stay put till
they come back.
We'll set up camp here tonight.
[NAVIROU screams]
The snowball just keeps
getting bigger and bigger!
There! Head for that cave!
Whew, that was too close.
It's so cold!
What's wrong? Wait, didn't
you drink your Hot Drink?
Oh, yeah,
Navirou'll drink it now.
--[whistling]
--[BOTH] Huh?
It's coming from in there.
[NAVIROU]
Wait, Lute, you'd better not.
Navirou's got a bad
feeling about this.
[yelps]
Hey, don't stop short like that!
Navirou needs a
little more warning!
Whoa, it's a girl!
What's wrong with her?
[NAVIROU]
Lute, check out that pendant!
Kinship Ore!
That girl's a Rider!
[BOTH scream]
[roars]
[NAVIROU] That monster must've
been the one who injured her!
Lute, it's too dangerous!
[roars]
We should run!
I can't. I gotta help her!
Frostfang, it's okay.
Hey, look. It's calmed down now.
Huh.
[NAVIROU]
Now it's backing away.
[NAVIROU screams]
You all right? Hey, miss!
She's hurt pretty bad and
her body feels awfully cold.
She needs help.
Well, that should take care of
the first aid for her injury.
And don't forget the Hot Drink.
Navirou purposefully saved it
for an emergency
just like this one.
Nice of him, eh?
Leave it to you, huh.
Drink some of this, it'll help.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Uh! She's waking up!
Ride On!
Rathian!
[NAVIROU screaming]
Hey!
Who are you?
[groans]
Careful now.
Don't strain yourself.
It's okay, we're not
gonna bite you.
[NAVIROU]
Mh-hm.
[GIRL gasps]
You're a Rider, aren't you?
I never imagined I would
run into another Rider.
I mean, outside of the village.
Well, you're the first
I've come across.
I see.
That's why Frostfang
let his guard down.
Frostfang? You mean
that monster there?
[GIRL] Yes. This is Frostfang,
my Barioth Monstie.
Barioth?
Oh? So that's a Barioth, huh?
I've never seen one.
Anyway, what's a
Rider doing out here
all alone in the Arctic Ridge?
I mean, really, who knows what
could've happened to you?
Oh, please.
It's not like I asked
anybody to save me.
[BOTH gasp]
I've got Frostfang. We would've
worked something out.
Really, don't overdo it.
Your wounds haven't
fully healed yet.
I don't have time.
I'm looking for somebody.
Oh, who?
I have no reason
to tell you that.
Frostfang, I'll be right back.
Listen to me, you
really shouldn't--
Hey, wait!
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
Hold on, don't go, Lute!
So cold!
Ah, still some left.
Bitter!
[NAVIROU chuckles]
Navirou is going, too!
Navirou's going! Okay?
So no eating Navirou!
You got that?
Hey, wait for Navirou!
Listen, you shouldn't
be walking on that leg.
I get that you're in a hurry,
but at least wait until
it's had time to heal.
[NAVIROU]
Don't strain yourself so much.
The best thing you could
do right now is rest.
[sighs]
Stubborn, aren't you?
[GIRL] Listen, this is
none of your business.
So please stop following me.
Sorry about that,
but we were goin'
this way anyway.
So see, we're not following you.
That's right. Total coincidence.
I see. Suit yourselves then.
Ha. We were planning to
suit ourselves anyway.
Right?
[NAVIROU]
Mh-hm!
Uh, you know,
if you push yourself too
hard when you're hurt,
it's only gonna make your injury
that much worse in the long run.
Say, it's getting
a little late now!
That Hot Drink will
start to wear off soon!
Oh, yeah!
It'll be a lot colder then,
and we'll be hungry.
Hey, you think she can hear us?!
You think she can hear us?!
[GIRL]
Look.
There's nothing I
can do about you
going in the same
direction as me,
but could you please at
least try to keep it down?
Oh, so you can hear us.
In that case,
are you hungry, too?
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Uh?
[gasps]
You see? I told
you so, didn't I?
You shouldn't be up
on that leg yet.
[roaring]
It's-It's back again. The Khezu.
What Khezu?
[GIRL] It was the
Khezu that injured me.
You two should get
out of here now!
We're not gonna leave you.
Hop on.
I'll carry you. Hop on.
Are you sure?
[roaring]
[NAVIROU screaming]
Come on, hurry! Let's go!
He keeps getting closer, Lute!
Gotta go faster!
Wow, it's gotten
really dark already.
[LILIA]
Yeah.
Do you think that
they're all right?
I don't know,
but I hope that Navirou
remembered to eat.
Well, I can tell you
that's one thing
we never need to worry about.
Yeah, guess you're right.
They'll be fine.
It's Lute after all.
Before too long,
he'll come, want food,
and act like nothing happened.
[LILIA chuckles]
You're probably right.
Navirou really doesn't wanna
become an appetizer for a Khezu!
[NAVIROU screams]
It's the bottom of the valley!
[NAVIROU, LUTE scream]
Look, it's not
chasing us anymore!
Hey, you all right?
Not good. We need to
let her rest somewhere.
Lute, look! There's
a light there!
[LUTE]
Let's go check it out!
Hello?
Pardon the intrusion.
It looks like nobody's home.
Ah, now that's... toasty.
Finally, we can get some rest.
[stomach growls]
So hungry.
[NAVIROU sighs]
Well, that was pretty rough
out there, wasn't it?
Thinkin' about the others?
They must be so worried
about us right now.
I mean, we went through
the Purification Rite
and all set out together, but...
[BOTH gasp]
Are you okay?
[gasps]
Where are we?
You just won't learn, will you?
If you sit up too quickly
with an injury like that,
it's gonna hurt.
I know that.
What's this?
[LUTE]
A hot springs inn.
You guys brought me
all the way here?
Yep! All thanks to
Navirou's navigation.
And we did it while running
away from that Khezu.
With you there, on my back.
[gasps]
I can't tell you how
grateful I am for that.
Good. That's great!
Because I was worried you'd say,
"It's not like I asked
anybody to save me."
You know, like you did earlier.
Oh, right, my name's Lute.
And this guy is--
Name's Navirou!
Lute and Navirou.
I'm Avinia.
Avinia, huh?
[HYORO] I hope those
guys are doing okay.
[MILLE]
All right.
Well-Done Steak is ready!
Oh, yummy! Looks so tasty!
[LUTE] So, Avinia,
you said it was the Khezu
who did that to
your leg earlier?
[AVINIA]
That's right.
I came to the Arctic
Ridge with Frostfang
trying to find someone.
But then, along the way, we
were attacked by that Khezu.
Frostfang protected me.
And Frostfang is that Barioth
we met back in the cave, right?
[AVINIA]
Yes.
My beloved Frostfang
is the only family
that I have in this world.
Family.
[AVINIA]
Frostfang and I...
...understand each other
like no one else can.
And we respect each other
more than anyone else.
If you really are that
attuned to each other,
then you must know when
Frosty is hungry, for example.
Did you say, "Frosty"?
That's right. Yeah, Frosty.
Well, yeah.
[AVINIA chuckles]
Aw, that sounds really nice.
Frosty sure is one lucky
monster, you know.
Navirou wishes
more than anything
that he could have such a
powerful Kinship with somebody.
Someone who'd feed him donuts
whenever he got hungry.
Right? Eh, Lute?
Uh, hey there, Lute?
Are you listening?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, sure.
[AVINIA]
If you're a Rider,
then you must have
a Monstie, too, right?
Yeah, a Velocidrome right now.
[AVINIA]
Right now?
But forget about me.
Even with Frostfang,
why did you-why did you leave
your village by yourself?
[NAVIROU]
Uh-huh. That's right.
It's too dangerous to go alone.
Well, I... I had no choice.
I mean... I don't have a...
...a village anymore.
[gasps]
You have no village?
[banging]
Someone's coming.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Lagombi!
Aw, just look at
those cute ears!
Thanks to its thick
hide and fur,
it's at home in cold places
like the Arctic Ridge,
without even having to swallow
any of Lilia's
bitter Hot Drinks!
Man, is Navirou jealous!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
I thought we might
finally catch a breather
at the hot springs inn,
but someone suspicious
is about to show up
with a suspicious request.
Actually, this is way
past suspicious!
Next time:
"Meet the Riddlemaster"!
Ride On!