[LUTE panting]
[LUTE yells]
C'mon, Lute, run faster!
I would if I didn't
have to carry you!
Don't worry, pal!
Navirou will take good
care of your egg!
It doesn't sound
like he's buying it!
Plan B! Navirou will
distract it with items!
[screams]
[NAVIROU]
Navirou threw his donuts, too!
[BOTH gasp]
[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming the
world's top Monster Rider.
Lute and his friends have
finally arrived in Gildegaran,
home to the Hunter's Guild.
Small town boy in the city!
[NARRATOR]
The kids have mostly managed
to keep thier Rider
status a secret,
as they gather information
on the Kinship Ore
affected by the Black Blight.
Wow, y' know, you kinda
remind me of Ratha!
Oh, lucky day!
There's a Rider right
here in Gildegaran!
This is the chance we've
been waiting for, Doctor!
[chuckles]
[LUTE]
I'm beat.
Good night, Navirou.
When you can sleep, sleep.
That's a Navi-rule.
[knocking]
He's still sleeping?
What?! We have a Quest!
Jerk! I'm waking him up!
Don't bother.
When he's like this,
not even a Field Horn blast
right in the ear will wake him.
[MILLE] Well, good for Lute,
but we can't wait all day.
[CHEVAL]
We'll go without him.
[HYORO] That'll work.
After all, we still have Rathi.
[MILLE]
That's true.
[LUTE screams]
You were supposed to wake
me up for the Quest!
Navirou forgot. Sorry.
You can't just
shrug this one off!
Now they're on a Quest and
we've got nothing to do!
[INNKEEPER]
Excuse me, sirs.
If you'll be staying
one more night,
would you please settle
your bill in advance?
Oh. Sure.
Go ahead, pay him, Navirou.
[LUTE]
Huh?
[INNKEEPER]
Oh?
[NAVIROU]
Can't.
[LUTE]
Owie.
Ah, we'll be fine, Lute!
What did you do with it?
I know that Chief
Omna give us enough
to afford a month's
worth of lodging!
Yes, that is correct.
And it's gone?
Navirou will explain.
He was in charge of the funds.
And yes, he took the
responsibility seriously.
So seriously that he spent it
on something of great value.
Something more important
than a mere bed to sleep in.
Something essential to
our very well-being!
Navirou couldn't resist this
town's variety of donuts.
How could you spend
everything we had on donuts?
'Cause that's a Navi---
So where are we supposed
to stay tonight?
We cant even afford
to buy real food!
[NAVIROU] Fear not!
Navirou has connections.
What are you talking about?
You'll see.
You try to sit down
and have a nice meal.
What're they doing here?
Mew met in Hakum
Village, remember?
Yeah, I know. So what?
So they'll be staying
with us for a while.
And this place is
nice and cheap, too!
We have a spare room, Reverto.
This will let us take in
a little extra income.
It's purr-fect.
I gotta say,
I'm kinda impressed you
really did have a connection.
All part of Navirou's
Felyne Network.
Other than me, I didn't
think you had friends.
Hey! Don't say such
depressing things, Lute!
Navirou may have
spent our Zenny,
but he still got us
a place to live!
[REVERTO] I never said
you could live here!
Aw, man.
Mew have no choice
but to let them stay.
With the way mew laze around,
the bills are piling up!
We can't even afford to
buy a loaf of bread!
If mew wanna earn even more,
mew could go down
to the jungle river
and hunt the swarms of Altaroth.
[REVERTO]
Altaroth, huh?
Nope.
And this is why we're
renting out the spare room.
Fine, they can stay.
Listen, son!
I'm no babysitter, so you
take care of yourself.
Your business is your business,
not mine! Got that?
You listen!
I'm no baby. I can handle my own
business just fine, all right?
Good, then we're both
on the same page.
Clean the spare room
and it's all yours.
However! My room's off-limits
to everyone but me!
If I find out you or your
little friend went in there,
there's gonna be trouble.
[POPOLA]
Here's mewr room.
[groans]
[POPOLA]
If mew wanna stay in it,
all mew gotta do is clean it.
And if mew don't like it,
mew're more than welcome
to sleep on the street.
So now we're chore boys?
How convenient for them.
[NAVIROU]
Well, go get 'em, big guy!
[LUTE]
Oh, no!
It worked!
All right! Quest complete!
[BOTH sigh]
[REVERTO]
Oh!
This place actually
looks livable!
Hey, good news.
I talked to the Guild and
they said come on over.
Wait, for what?
Because If mew don't get to
work, mew don't get to eat.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[ELDEST DAUGHER]
Reverto gave us some details.
But we're still thinking of
the right Quest for you.
What? I didn't know I was
allowed to do a Quest alone.
You are. Although, it
depends upon the Quest.
Excuse me!
Is it true that
you're staying at
the diabolical, lone-wolf,
expert-Hunter Reverto's place
What? How did you know that?
Our Felyne friend
Popola said so.
For a loner like Reverto
to let you stay there,
that must mean you two are
pretty special in your right.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Hm?
Oh! Here's a good one for you!
A Mushroom-gathering Quest!
All you have to do is go out and
find us ten Primo Mushrooms.
Wait, hold on.
Mushroom-gathering?
You underestimate us.
[chuckles]
Mushroom-gathering is an
honorable and worthy Quest.
Everything has a deeper
meaning, you know.
What?
Whether big or small,
every Quest has
something to offer.
[GUILD MASTER] Young man,
it is only by gaining experience
that you're able
to gain knowledge.
Likewise, the more
experience you gain,
you will find it
progressively easier
to win the trust of others.
All that from Mushrooms, huh?
[GUILD MASTER]
With this knowledge, trust,
and experiance, you will
have the opportunity
to take on more
difficult Quests.
All right! I'm in!
Good!
First they tell us to clean,
now we're told to Quest.
They've no respect for
Navirou and his pupil.
Speaking of, why aren't
you mad about this, Lute?
Because when I told Reverto
I could handle my own business,
I meant it.
Besides, it's just a
Mushroom-gathering Quest.
No big deal.
[NAVIROU] Great. We can
only afford cheap supplies.
Navirou hates being broke.
Oh, and whose fault
might that be?
A thousand pardons,
oh, good sir!
Honestly!
What's that, boy?
Financial difficulties?
It's never fun being in the city
when all you've got are big
dreams and empty pockets!
Yes, yes, nothing takes
the fun out of shopping
quite like being poor.
Being poor really takes
the fun out of it.
It's so bad I just
repeated it twice, I did.
What the--?
[NAVIROU]
Lute is a magnet for weirdos.
Now Dr. Manelger can tell
that you're a
promising young fellow
who's just down on his luck,
so I'll be happy to give
you a couple Zenny.
No! No!
That way you can buy
better supplies.
[LUTE]
Let's go, Navirou!
[ITSY-BITS]
Huh?
I almost had him!
That is one street-wise kid.
That Felyne looked
familiar, though.
Didn't he use to be in
the Numbers, Doctor?
The Numbers, you say?
My boy, I think you're right.
But for now, let's focus on
getting our hands on a Rider.
Yes, Doctor. I'm sure
there're others we can find.
[DR. MANELGER]
Mh-hm!
Oh, man!
I always just assumed
people who sweet talk you
and offer you things
were stories
that grown-ups tell
to teach a lesson,
but those nut jobs are real!
Wow, I mean, who knew?
Got that right.
Navirou doesn't know why,
but he was frozen with fear.
[DEBLI]
Whoa!
Ow! You tripped me!
And you broke my arm!
I might have to tell the
police about what you did!
Either way, you're gonna have
to pay for my lengthy recovery!
[NAVIROU]
It's that Debli guy.
[LUTE]
What are you doing?
Oh, man, it's just you? Dang it.
Navirou can smell a
hustle from a mile away!
Listen, Felyne, I don't
go to where you work
and make fun of
whatever it is you do!
It ain't cheap
livin' in this town,
so I do what I gotta
do to get by!
Why don't you
just go on a Quest?
Navirou and his pupil are
just about to start a Quest.
A Quest, huh? Whoa.
Okay, count me in!
[LUTE]
Huh?
Debli will be your guide.
From the desert, to the jungle,
to the frozen plains
of the Arctic Ridge,
I got maps for this whole
region in my noggin!
Best decision of your life!
And since we know each other,
I'll even give you a discount!
You seriously wanna charge us?
Primo Mushrooms, got it!
Just watch me; I know
exactly where to find 'em.
Wow.
I mean, Mushrooms always grow
in damp places, am I right?
So we need to check under
rotting trees and stuff.
There's one right down-- Ah!
Sticky! Get it off me!
Get it off! Help!
[LUTE]
You okay?
[DEBLI]
Yeah.
There they are.
[LUTE]
Whoa! Mushrooms!
[NAVIROU] Navirou didn't
wanna make Debli look bad,
but he found this
spot a while ago.
[LUTE]
Wow, these look great!
And there's a ton of 'em!
Navirou's got his paws full!
I told you I knew this area!
Uh... there's your lunch.
I'll just leave now.
Goodbye, fellas. I'm sorry.
[screaming]
[LUTE]
Debli?
[NAVIROU]
Um, what is that?
[DEBLI] Guys, help!
I-It's the Nerscylla!
Ride On!
Rathian!
Come on! Don't just sit
there, cut me down!
Don't let Debli become
a Nerscylla's dinner!
Debli, you were gonna run away
and let that monster
eat us, weren't you?
[DEVLI]
What? How did you know?
Oh, Navirou knows.
C'mon, Navirou, I'm sorry!
Well, I mean, I guess we
can't just leave him there.
Let's go cut him down.
Nah, Navirou's good.
I don't care! Just save me!
All right! Ride On!
Yian Kut-Ku!
Oh, yeah! It's Monstie time!
C'mon, Yian Kut-Ku,
we can do this!
[LUTE] It's off-balance!
Hit it with your Breath Attack!
Nice work! Let's rush it!
Hey! Be careful!
[LUTE yelping]
[LUTE]
Whoa, calm down!
Oh, no, now I'm stuck!
Navirou, help!
Help us!
Don't worry!
Navirou will save you by
finding someone who will!
[LUTE]
What?!
[DEBLI] We'll be in its stomach
by the time you're back!
[BOTH]
He ran away?
Navirou doesn't abandon friends.
Navirou's just choosing to
make a courageous retreat!
And that's a Navi-rule.
[screams]
This is what you
deserve for trying
to ditch your best
friend, Navirou!
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Nerscylla, sir.
Those two are way
tastier than me!
No, wait!
Yeah, Debli's got more
meat on his bones
than Navirou and Lute combined!
And you know
nothing tastes sweeter
than a big tubby guy's belly!
[DEBLI]
Don't call me tubby!
Well, I mean--
[LUTE screams]
[ALL]
It's climbing up!
[REVERTO]
Hey!
Thought you were pickin'
Mushrooms. What happened?
What? Mr. Reverto?
Wait, the Reverto? For real?
The diabolical, lone-wolf,
expert-Hunter is gonna save me?
[REVERTO] I'm not surprised
you ended up like this.
Mushrooms around here
grow along monster paths.
When you find one, you're
guaranteed to find the other.
You see, for a Hunter, we're not
just gathering Mushrooms.
We're looking at the
environment they grow in,
searching for patterns.
Like how and when the
monsters are moving.
[NAVIROU] Sure, that's great!
Now cut us down!
Yeah, I guess I should, huh?
[NAVIROU]
What about Navirou?
Mr. Reverto, you forgot about
Navirou! Hey! Save Navirou!
Okay, Lute. I think you
can handle it from here.
All right, pal, let's
show 'em what we can do!
What?
What, is this snack time?
It ate Konchu and burped
them out as fireballs!
We'll give that move
the tasteful name:
"Fireball Expulsion!"
Hey, that's awesome!
So that's the Rider's
Kinship Attack, huh?
Wow, that's cool.
Well, technically,
it's hot, but who cares?
[REVERTO] Well, after a hard day
of avoiding a Nerscylla's mouth,
must feel nice to be the
ones doing the eating.
[BOTH]
Got that right!
Don't I get any meat?
You didn't do
anything to earn it.
Come on!
He's just kidding. Have at it.
Thanks, Brother Reverto!
You're the coolest!
Don't call me that.
[NAVIROU sighs]
Navirou's full!
Well, bully for you.
I didn't get a single piece.
Hey, uh, Brother Reverto, sir?
[REVERTO]
Hm?
Um. It would be an honor
to get your autograph.
What? Autograph?
I mean, I guess I could.
Okay, your name?
Yeah, well, uh, there's no
need to trouble with that.
Come on, Debli, be honest.
You're selling it.
How did you know?
Uh.
Well, you sure know how
to ruin a guy's night.
But the part about you being
the coolest was totally true!
[rustling]
[REVERTO screaming]
What's that?
Bugs! Big bugs! Go away!
Get away from me!
No, get away! Get away from me!
Is it gone? Tell me
when it's gone.
Say what?
Wow, who knew that
Reverto is afraid of bugs.
[REVERTO]
Oh, no! It's on me!
I'm itching everywhere! No! No!
I wonder if he realizes
that waving a torch around
is only gonna attract
more of them.
Brother Reverto isn't
the man I thought he was.
[REVERTO] It's in my hair!
My glorious hair!
Hey, it's Lute!
So are you all
checked out of the inn?
Yeah, about that--
It's more accurate to say
that we got chucked out.
Which was all your fault!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Anyway, we ended up renting
a room at Reverto's place.
[HYORO] The Hunter who came
through Hakum Village?
Oh, yeah! Guys, how did
things go on today's Quest?
I'm proud to say we just
defeated a Gypceros.
How 'bout yours?
I'm actually reporting in now.
Mine was gathering
Primo Mushrooms.
Wait, that's all?
We did happen to defeat
a Nerscylla as well.
Yeah, I mean it wasn't all me.
Reverto helped a lot.
I can't believe you
defeated a Nerscylla.
Well, sounds like it's easier
when a pro-Hunter's there
to do the dirty work.
Navirou will have you know that
Lute got in the final blow!
Wow!
[LUTE]
Hm?
Why you so quiet, pal?
Just thinking about
our next Quest
and how I have to
get ready for it.
There's no time to
rest in the big city!
See ya soon. Good luck!
Yep! Same to you!
That's weird.
Something's going on
with Cheval, Lute.
Ya think so?
[laughs]
You slayed a Nerscylla
on a Mushroom Quest.
I had a feeling you were
a skilled young man,
but your bravery exceeds
all expectations.
Your actions today may
have just opened up
an entirely different
path for your future.
What do you mean?
[GUILD MASTER]
With its promises of adventure,
fortune, and glory,
the lure of the outside world
has long beckoned Riders
right into this very
city of Gildegaran.
Many like yourself have
stood in that spot.
Each one bursting
with excitement
for what his future might hold.
Wow, really?
Yes, but eventually they left
as quickly as they'd arrived.
Huh?
[GUILD MASTER]
It's no great secret.
Riders just couldn't
get used to this place.
People who hunt monsters
and people who ride them
are cut from different cloth.
That sounds so familiar.
Like something Chief Omna said.
And that is why, many years ago,
Riders and Hunters decided
it would be best
to go their separate
paths in this world.
That way, both could
fulfill their callings,
without ever being in
conflict with the other.
Riders preferred seclusion and
settled in distant villages
that put them close to nature.
Meanwhile, the Hunters
constructed great cities,
within which their
Guilds were born.
Separate they have remained,
and continue to do
so to this day.
That means we have
a real opportunity.
You know what I mean?
Both sides can learn
from each other.
Yes, you've got it!
That's exactly right, my boy.
But I warn you. This task
will not be an easy one.
You Riders commune with monsters
and form Kinship with them.
This is an arrangement we
Hunters find hard to comprehend,
let alone support.
Your first step then, must be to
dispel their skepticism of you.
Right, I want people to
learn more about Riders,
and I wanna learn about Hunters!
When the Hunters of this guild
see how you can be
of help to our city,
surely their view
of you will change.
Make yourself known to Hunters,
and Riders will become
known in return.
Thank you, sir. I will.
But beyond that advice,
I've no more.
Whether you can make an
honest go of it in this city
rests entirely on you.
I wish you luck.
I know I can!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: The Nerscylla!
It's a spidery type of monster
that freezes its prey with webs,
then attacks with
its claws and teeth!
And if that's not scary enough,
the Nerscylla also
has a special attack
that can put you to sleep!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
While exploring the forest,
we discovered a whole
village of Felynes!
Huh? Some of these
Felynes are weird.
Almost as weird as Navirou.
Next time: "The Legend
of Pawpad Place"!
Ride On!