[screaming]
Did you hear that?
Yeah, we better look.
Let's go, boys!
[LUTE]
Wake up.
We'll lure him the whole way!
Do you wanna wear all
the most glamorous styles?
[WOMEN, GIRLS]
We do! Ms. Pink!
[VLAU, LILIA'S MOTHER]
Over here!
[MS. PINK] Do you wanna look
like beautiful, modern women?
Who is that?
That's Powderkeg Pink,
the pushy peddler!
Powderkeg is a weird first name.
That's not her real name,
that's just what Lute calls her.
She goes town-to-town
selling her wares.
Her and Chief Omna go way back.
She's a little kooky, though.
A little?
Powderkeg's got more energy
than a stick of dynamite!
[MS. PINK]
Who's calling me Powderkeg?
[ALL]
Huh?
You can make fun of my face,
but never my personality, Lute!
Uhh!
Although, if you buy something,
you can say whatever you like!
[WOMEN, GIRLS shouting]
Look at them flocking
to her mindlessly.
Stay back! This scene
can get dangerous!
I see you're getting rich
off our village again.
When I think of how much
you secretly scrimped
and saved for this day,
Chief Omna, I wanna cry.
Now, back to making stacks
of Zenny off your ladies.
Oh, please try to be
gentle on us, Ms. Pink.
I don't like that color on you.
Try on this shade
of red instead.
Makes your face look thinner.
You need this dress,
no question.
Accentuate your curves, girl.
Don't hide behind
all that fabric,
you just end up looking fat!
You need to class it up!
More glamour in your wardrobe
will keep your
husband's eye on you!
Such wisdom.
Ms. Pink's makeover advice is
always right on the money.
Loloa is in awe!
'Scuse me, Ms. Pink?
Don't worry, kid,
I'll do you next.
Thank you!
Oh, wow, Mille,
you look so adorable!
Spare me your flattery, Lilia.
Hey, that looks great on you.
Thanks, Cheval.
[MS. PINK]
Well, Lute,
your fashion sense
remains as boring as ever.
It's high time you get
a Ms. Pink makeover!
[LUTE] What? Hey, I don't wanna
wear some "fancy lad" outfit!
[MS. PINK] I'm just making
you stand out a little more!
Now stay still!
[chuckles]
[ALL laughing]
Cheval, you're already
quite the looker.
You don't need any help
in that department.
This hat's the cherry
on your sundae!
If I were a hundred
years younger,
I might try to steal
a smooch from you!
Y'know, I used to be quite
the looker myself, lover boy.
[LILIA]
Is that really you, Ms. Pink?
Other than the hair,
you'd have no idea.
Father Time is a
cruel man, indeed.
And what kind of
exciting makeover
should I give your
avant-garde Felyne friend?
Let's see.
[squeals]
[MS. PINK]
Hmm.
[gasps]
No exciting makeover needed.
You're fine as you are!
[yelps]
Navirou chooses to take
that as a compliment,
meaning it's impossible to
improve upon perfection,
but he knows the right
clothes can help.
Shall we say, better emphasize
those perfect qualities
for the discriminating female.
I've never seen one
like mew before!
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
May I please pet mew, sir?
Uh, yeah, okay then.
Wow. He's softer than he looks!
Will mew please try this on?
It's from Mocha's
very own design.
[NAVIROU]
Uh.
Are you sure?
[MOCHA]
Hope it looks good.
Mocha threw it together
from some extra fabric.
There! Done!
Thank you so much!
You have Navirou's
gratitude, lovely lady.
[giggles]
Nice to meet mew. I'm Mocha.
Name's Navirou!
So why are we still here?
Feel free to put
these kids to work.
They're not the smartest,
but they're good muscle.
Well, thank mew!
It's always nice
having extra bodies
helping Ms. Pink's business.
Mocha, do you have a good time
traveling around with Ms. Pink?
Yeah, Mocha loves fashion!
Life on the road can be hard,
but it's an adventure, too!
And Ms. Pink's a great boss,
as long as you get used
to her sharp tongue.
Mocha!
Make up as many of these as
you can in this color combo!
[MOCHA]
Yes, ma'am!
[giggles]
[MOCHA chuckles]
She's gorgeous.
She's polite and
she can even sew!
It sounds like Navirou's
got a little crush!
Wha--?
It's pretty obvious, Navirou.
[NAVIROU yelps]
This is no mere crush.
It's a love written
in the heavens
between the golden
shooting star of Navirou
and the silver star of Mocha!
Silver star? So she's like
second place in your heart?
I guess first place is a donut.
You're not listening to Navirou!
It was something with
outer space, right?
This has nothing to do
with outer space!
Love, you fool!
Wait, love who? Like Cheval?
Forget it.
Navirou can't explain to a
boy with no life experience
what happens when
hearts start burning
in the red-hot furnace
of true passion!
I don't get it.
Why don't you get to
know her first, Navirou?
This isn't some ordinary
hollow love, Lilia.
It's a miraculous true love
here in a tiny corner
of this wide world!
[KIDS]
Huh?
Maybe you're just too
young to understand.
Excuse Navirou.
He's such a weirdo.
Navirou would look
great in this.
But being weird's
part of his charm.
[TWINS laughing]
You two! Either buy
something or get lost!
[BOTH]
Um, I'll take this one.
Great choice, guys.
All right, you've really
got a knack for this!
Here. You kids really
worked hard today.
As payment, have some clothes.
[NAVIROU]
Ooh!
Well that's a bit
mean to the kids,
making the handsomest fella
here even more handsome
instead of paying them!
Thank you so much, Ms. Pink.
I hear you're not
becoming a Rider, Lilia.
If you're ever looking for
work, stop by my place.
I meant what I said about
you being a good salesgirl.
[LILIA chuckles]
Right!
Huh?
[gasps]
[NAVIROU]
Mocha?
Hi, Navirou. I was just
tidying up for the day.
Oh, is it hard work, Mocha?
Eh. It's fine.
I enjoy it, so it's
not that bad.
The real hard part is spending
so much time on the road.
I miss being home, mew know?
Your home, huh?
You mean like the place where
you were born and grew up?
Back home is where all
of my loved ones are.
Your loved ones?
Thanks for all your
help, Navirou.
Working with mew helped
turn a regular old day
into a purrfect one.
Navirou's entire life has been
building to this moment in time.
[MS. PINK]
Okay, folks, I'm movin' on,
but that doesn't
give you permission
to forget all my style advice!
[WOMEN, GIRLS]
We won't!
Make sure you start
saving plenty of Zenny
for the next time I'm in town.
[WOMEN, GIRLS]
Right!
Goodbye, Ms. Pink.
I'm always sorry to see you go.
We've had some trouble
lately, though. Monsties.
Nole here will escort
you through the worst
of the mountain passes.
We're coming along,
too, Ms. Pink!
Uh! What? Don't
drag me into this!
Mocha.
Thanks for all your
help, Navirou.
Working with mew helped
turn a regular old day
into a purrfect one.
Saying goodbye to mew is the
hardest thing Mocha's ever done.
Mocha's heart is
beating so fast.
Mocha doesn't know
how to explain
all the feelings she's feeling.
She just knows it could
cause mew too much trouble.
Just thinking about
being away from you
makes Navirou's chest feel
like it's been ripped in half!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Oh, Navirou. I was actually
just coming over to get you.
Powderkeg Pink is
leaving right now.
And here's your share.
Mrs. Vlau made them for
Pink's big send-off.
[LUTE gasps]
What's wrong, pal?
You always want a donut.
It's all yours, Lute.
Are you sure? Lucky!
You got a fever or something?
An Important announcement.
Navirou's in love with Mocha
and leaving Hakum Village.
What?
This is goodbye, Lute!
[gasps]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
What? You can't just
leave us, Navirou.
Navirou's stayed here too long.
You see, Lilia, Navirou's
a loner, a rebel.
He crosses the world,
going wherever adventure
and romance take him.
It's time for you to go back
to how things used to be.
Are you sure?
Yes. Navirou knows it's tough.
The feeling of "Navi-loss"
can be crushing.
But look, a meeting always
leads to a parting.
That's just life, kids.
Finally, let Navirou say this.
You were a loyal friend to him.
Please, do not turn our
parting into a tearful one.
See Navirou off with a smile!
Navirou will never
forget any of you.
I can't believe he's
really leaving us.
I always assumed that little
guy would be around forever.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Genie. Stone.
I'm proud to announce that
today you will become Riders!
Now then, let's begin
the Kinship Rite.
Huh?
[LUTE]
Hey!
Quiet down back there.
Oh, right.
[yelps]
[chanting]
[CHIEF OMNA chanting]
Hey! I haven't
stopped chanting yet!
That egg's jumping around
like it means business!
Now that's what I call top form!
[KIDS gasp]
If the egg's moving up there,
that is a good sign!
So cool!
Hey, Lute! Don't stand there!
Go save our Monstie egg!
[LUTE]
Right! Hey!
Gotcha!
It's getting away! Stop it!
Hey, wait! Ugh!
Huh?
[NAVIROU]
Who are you? State your name!
Wha--? Who am I? Who are you?
You ruined our ceremony!
It wasn't on purpose!
Navirou was
peacefully passing by
when he happened to see the egg.
"Happened to see"?
We're in the middle of
doing a sacred Rite!
You're a thief, and
a bad one! Get out!
And you're rude!
And that's why Navirou's
not going anywhere!
[stomach growling]
Oh, wow, are you
hungry little guy?
Bah!
Even the wisest are no match
for an empty stomach!
Pity Navirou.
Well, whatever.
Here, have a snack!
You're a good kid,
you know that?
It's settled then! Navirou's
sticking around for a while!
What? Are you sure?
Wait, why are you staying?
Delicious!
What manner of glorious
foodstuff is this?
Huh? It's a donut.
Donut!
As of today, you and
Navirou are besties.
So then, take Navirou
to the field
where these donuts
are harvested!
They're not harvested.
They're a pastry.
Mrs. Vlau bakes them in an oven.
[laughs]
You're a weirdo, you know that?
Navirou is no weirdo.
Navirou's Navirou!
Navirou? Even your
name's kinda weird.
[laughs]
This'll be fun!
You sure do like to eat a lot.
When was the last
time you ate?
Navirou hasn't had a bite
since he crossed the ocean.
The ocean? You've come
from a distant land?
Yeah! From an island.
Island?
So when you're not traveling
the world, that's your home?
Whaddaya mean "home"?
You know, the place
where you were born.
Birthplace, huh?
Navirou doesn't
have one of those.
What are you saying, then?
You were never born?
So are you like a ghost?
Who're you calling a ghost?!
No ghost has ever had
a face this handsome.
Handsome face? Where is it?
Right here! It's Navirou's face.
Wait, what did you
mean by saying
you don't have a birthplace?
Oh, that, um, Navirou
can't quite remember it.
To be frank, not
sharing personal info's
kind of Navi-rule.
Anyway, back to the issue
at hand: These donuts.
Navirou will eat every last one.
He's been completely shamless
since the day we first met him.
Are you gonna be okay?
You and Navi have
always been so close.
Of course. We're only going
back to how things used to be.
Maybe so.
I don't know where his
journey takes him next.
I just hope he gets his
fill of donuts there.
Oh, Navi, are you sure
you want to leave?
Navirou means what he says.
That's a Navi-rule.
If you're ever hungry for
a donut, come back anytime.
Mrs. Vlau!
Hey! It's time to head out!
With that, Navirou's off
to be with his woman!
Goodbye, friends. Love awaits!
[VILLAGERS shouting]
I'll miss ya, buddy!
[CHEVAL, LILIA]
Huh? What's up with Lute?
Say "hi" to Mocha for me!
[laughs]
[NAVIROU]
Top form, Navirou!
You and Mocha are all
aboard the love train,
racing headlong toward
your destination:
A town called "Happiness"!
[gasps] That was odd.
Navirou told Lute to see
him off with a smile,
but he never expected him
to look that happy about it.
Shed a tear, Lute!
It's goodbye forever.
[CHEVAL]
Navirou?
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
There's still time to
go back, if you want to.
The Navi-rules forbid
doubling back.
Navirou will only look forward.
[LUTE]
That's a weird cloud.
I can't believe
he's really gone.
I guess this means I get
all of Mrs. Vlau's donuts
for myself now.
Lucky!
[laughs]
What's wrong, pal?
You always want a donut.
It's all yours, Lute.
Salty.
[NOLE]
Watch out!
Whoa! Ride On!
Velocidrome!
What's going on?
Dan, I think our friends
might be in trouble!
All right, then
let's get moving!
Now that's some
good flying, Lute!
As expected from
Navirou's top pupil!
Stop calling me your pupil!
We won't last long!
Use Navirou's secret plan!
All right, I'm in!
Wait, Lute! You know what
Navi's secret plan is?
No idea.
But we're outta time,
and I trust Navirou!
Aww! Come on, guys.
Run Navirou Operation G!
What's that?
Operation what now?
Just tell us what
you want done!
Operation G means put
some oomph into it!
Your big plan's to try harder?!
[NOLE]
Lute!
All you, push now! We'll
launch it to safer ground!
How impossibly rash.
Navirou's in top form!
[laughs]
So you came back.
I see. That means...
[NAVIROU yells]
Navirou can't even look
you in the eyes, Lute.
Navirou is still angry with you
over your cold-hearted goodbye!
Cold-hearted?
And that big stupid grin
is what Navirou's mad about!
It's like you're dead inside!
But you specifically told me
to see you off with a smile.
That is true, but come on.
Navirou didn't mean it.
He thought he'd
never see you again!
Show you care.
All right now, men don't cry.
So why are you crying?
I'm not crying, you're crying.
Now we're both crying!
To be honest, Navirou doesn't
wanna leave you, Lute.
But a man follows through
with his decisions.
And Navirou's decided to
take his heart to Mocha.
Look, I wanted to make
sure that our goodbye
was a happy one, Navirou.
So why don't you just let the
goodbye stay happy already?
Mocha, I hate to tell you and
Navirou how to love each other.
But maybe give him
a few more days
to tie up loose ends with us.
Navi and Lute were so close.
What? Hold on.
Love who now?
Mocha has no feelings of love
toward Navirou whatsoever.
Mocha has a boyfriend
waiting for her back home.
[gasps]
Maybe Mocha gave off
mixed signals?
Whenever Mocha yawns,
her eyes water,
so purrhaps he thought she
was emotional over him?
Mocha, if Navirou learned that
you don't share his feelings,
he'd be devastated.
Will you...?
Will you do me a favor?
[MOCHA]
hm?
Thanks for the escort, gang!
Take care, Cheval!
All right, time for
Navirou and Mocha
to get on the "romance express."
[MOCHA]
Wait, hold on, Navirou!
What? What's wrong, love?
Mocha admits she has
romantic feelings for mew,
but she doesn't want
to get in the way
of your friendship with Lute.
It's rough, but Mocha
thinks we should cancel
our love train
to happiness town.
Oh, Navirou. Goodbye.
[screams]
Navirou?
[LUTE]
Navirou, wait!
Thanks for doing that, Mocha.
That poor little guy.
Yeah well that's a man for you.
Hakum Village sure
is a lively place.
[MS. PINK laughs]
I hope that it never changes.
Come on, Mocha!
There are many more
villages we have to visit!
Yes, Ms. Pink!
What a marvelous moment!
I'm literally
marveling right now!
I can tell you're excited
'cause you're
repeating yourself.
We can operate on monsters
whenever we like!
Marvelous!
I can't wait to see
what research samples
we get our hands on here.
Hey, c'mon, cheer up, buddy.
You'll see her again someday.
But Navirou wants her now!
You sure are an
ugly crier, Navirou.
[NAVIROU] Navirou is
handsome at all times!
Aw, don't cry, Navi.
Have one of my Energy Drinks.
[CHEVAL]
Mm...
Might have the opposite effect.
Knock-knock. Time for
a donut delivery!
[NAVIROU]
They're all for Navirou!
Well, that perked him right up.
Gut over heart.
That's his stance.
[LUTE]
Hm?
What's Navirou's dance?
Óle! See what you
made Navirou do?
[LUTE, CHEVAL laugh]
Your home, huh?
Back home is where all
of my loved ones are.
[LUTE laughing]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now, it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life.
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Bulldrome!
They sure have huge
tusks, don't they?
A regular Bullfango can't
hold a candle to these giants!
They're so strong and fearless,
they charge headlong
into their prey!
Even other Monsties tremble
at the Bulldrome's power!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys, Lute here!
Up to now, Dan's just
been our trainer,
the guy always harpin' on us
to improve our
Kinship with Monsties.
But what's this?
Dan has a secret?
Next time:
"Dan and Silva's Zeal"!
Ride On!