Guys, look!
[roars]
Diablos?
And it is infected
with the Black Blight!
[NARRATOR]
These young folks are Riders
who form Kinship with monsters.
They fought as hard as they
could to stop a Blighted monster
who's running amok
in the desert.
All right!
[NARRATOR]
But the Blighted Diablos
attacked the young Riders
without mercy.
[yells]
Aw, man. You okay?
Lute, hit him one more time!
Are you ready? Basarios?
It's gone!
Where'd it go?
[yells]
[LILIA, CHEVAL]
Lute, no!
[ALL yell]
[ALL screaming]
[LILIA groans]
Lilia!
Are you okay?
It's my leg.
[NARRATOR] And despite all
of the Riders' best efforts,
Lilia was injured.
[LILIA whimpering]
[LUTE]
Are you all right, Lilia?
[LILIA]
Hey, what's wrong, guys?
What do you mean?
We've been worried sick
about you, that's what.
[LILIA]
Worried?
Well, yeah, you were
moaning in your sleep
all through the night.
Really, I was?
Does your leg still hurt?
I'm okay.
I was having a bad dream.
The Blighted Diablos
attacked me and then...
You'll be fine, Lilia!
Don't worry,
we'll keep you safe!
No, Lute.
It's not as simple as that.
[LUTE] Yeah, it is! With all
our Kinship power combined,
I know we can do it!
Rest easy now.
If push comes to shove,
Navirou will protect you!
[laughing]
Wha--?
Thanks, Navi, that's sweet!
And I'm sorry if
I had you guys worried.
I'm feeling much better now.
That's great.
It doesn't change the fact
that that Blighted Diablos
is still running wild out there.
[SHOPKEEPER A]
You like?
[BOYS laughing]
[CROWD cheering, clapping]
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Aah!
Look at all those people!
Oh yeah, it's festival time!
Time to make some bank!
It's you!
[NAVIROU]
What're you doing here?
I'm here to make money!
You can't enjoy a festival
without having some
Zenny in your pocket!
Hey, um. What's your
name again? Tub-something?
[grunting]
You still can't get it right?
Jeez, come on,
I'm the hottest Hunter around!
It's D! B! L!
That's Debli!
Oh yeah, right. Debli!
Hey, wait a second.
Didn't you say you were
going to become a Rider?
Ack! Well, I can do
just about anything!
Now then,
time to head into town!
You should tag along if
you want some spending money!
[CHEVAL] Going to the
festival's not in our plans.
We have to get back
there to defeat that Diablos.
Lilia, you should stay here
until your leg's healed.
Yeah. But you guys
are gonna need to
stock up on supplies if you're
going back to the desert.
Why don't you
take today to rest up?
She's not wrong.
You can't do too much good in
a fight on an empty stomach!
Need some donuts
to get back in the game!
They only sell these limited
editions at festivals.
Cheval.
All right.
Here you go, Lilia. We mixed it
just like you told us.
Aw, thanks, Mille!
Drinking this oughta have me
feeling better in a jiffy.
Uh! It's so... bitter!
We followed your
directions to the letter.
Are you sure?
Guess I have to do every step
myself, even the combining.
This should taste a lot better.
[MILLE, HYORO]
Uh...
[knocking]
Hey, long time no see!
Lieutenant Pappan,
at your service!
I have a special delivery for
Lilia from Captain Simone!
She's been so worried about you.
Well, bye now!
"Dear Lilia, I'll be
singing for you tonight
in hopes that you'll
be feeling better soon."
Aw, Captain Simone!
The Scriveners are singing
in the town square later today.
And there's gonna be
a shadow play, too!
Really? Sounds like
it could be fun.
Why don't we stop by
and check it out for a bit?
We always had
a good time together
at Hakum Village's festivals.
Yeah, and I'm gonna
rake in the dough!
Oh, yeah? Well, Navirou's
gonna rake in the donuts!
You could buy even more
with the kinda money I bring in!
Seriously?!
--[DEBLI] You're comin' right?
--[LUTE] Uh. No, I--
[NAVIROU]
There'll be donuts for days!
[DEBLI] And money for miles!
Come on, let's go!
We're gonna make more money
than we know what to do with!
Cheval?
[NAVIROU chanting]
Donuts! Donuts!
Yikes, I've gotta go
get my shop up and running!
Come by anytime if you feel
like joining me! Bye!
[ALL sigh]
Boy, is he amped up.
Hey, wait.
What happened to the others?
[indistinguishable chatter]
[MILLE]
Cheval?
Where are you going?
[CHEVAL] Sorry, it was just hard
for me to be in that room.
But Lilia's better now, right?
So, we should be gearing up
and heading back to the desert.
To do what needs to be done.
--You're right.
--Yeah.
[CHEVAL]
How is it, I wonder?
How did Lute and I come
to see things so differently?
[MILLE]
For what it's worth,
I don't think
you're wrong, Cheval.
[HYORO]
Me, either.
[DEBLI]
Funny, I heard that Riders
were bound together
with deep Kinship,
but it looks like that
doesn't apply to you guys.
So are you sure
you're okay with that?
I mean, us Hunters prefer
to take on monsters as a team,
but whatever works for you.
[DAN]
I see.
So Cheval was extra eager
to return to the desert. huh?
Yeah, and then
he just took off.
That Blighted Diablos
is nothing to be trifled with.
This is when we Riders need
to stick together the most.
That's right.
If only I had been stronger,
I coulda saved Mrs. Vlau.
And Ratha.
If only I had been better
at Riding On, then maybe...
Maybe...
[GAMIGAMI]
Here, have some warm honey.
Sweet and delicious.
Once bound,
Kinship can never be broken.
That's what Kinship's all about.
Lilia! Are you okay
moving around?
Hm! Yeah!
I had that Energy Drink.
That's right,
she chugged down
that whole bitter-as-
life-itself concoction.
[LILIA] Come on,
let's check out the festival!
Navirou's going! So he can
make money with Debli!
Gotta stock up on donuts
to take into the desert!
But Cheval and them--
[LILIA]
Yeah, so let's go!
We'll catch up with them there.
Enjoy it together!
Oh, right.
Where are they?
You know, I seem to remember
the same thing happening
when you guys were little.
We'd be at a festival,
and you and Cheval
would get into a fight
over something
and then you'd let go
of each other's hand.
In the end,
you'd both wind up lost.
This is just like that.
You're both just a little lost
right now, that's all.
You'll be holding hands
again in no time.
--Uh, Cheval.
--Where are you going, Cheval?
[CHEVAL]
I don't know.
Let's just--Let's just get
all of the supplies we need.
It's time to get going.
--All right.
--Yeah.
Hey, look, it's Captain Simone!
♪ Listen close as I sing
you a timeless tale. ♪
♪ An old story
that still abides. ♪
♪ Man and beast have been
at war for ages now. ♪
♪ Unending will
these battles be. ♪
♪ Wielding swords proudly. ♪
♪ Fearless show of fangs. ♪
♪ All those live sacrificed
now serve to remind. ♪
♪ We must sing,
while we have breath. ♪
[CROWD cheering, clapping]
That reminds me of how you
and Cheval would hold hands,
when you two would make up
after one of your fights.
Oh, yeah.
[SIMONE continues singing]
This way we'll never
tear 'em apart again!
Perfect!
[BOTH laughing]
Yeah, you're right.
You guys'll be fine.
I know you can work it out!
Yeah!
[SIMONE continues sining]
Cheval! You remember
this, right?
What?
How we would fight, but make up.
And then be even better
friends because of it!
You've always been
family to me, Cheval!
I feel the same way about you.
Okay, then!
And yet, why isn't
this moving me
the same way it did
when we were kids?
Cheval.
[SIMONE]
♪ ...while we have breath ♪
You're my family, Lute.
[SIMONE]
♪ ...while we have breath ♪
You were.
Ride On!
Rathian!
[NAVIROU yelps]
[PEOPLE gasping, laughing]
Hey, do you think that memories
ever just fade away for good?
Like fireworks do.
I dream about Mom all the time.
And wonder why
I wasn't able to save her.
It's like you said
back then, Lute.
If only I had been stronger.
It's not your fault, Lute.
I know you didn't
do anything wrong.
I truly believed that.
And yet, all these thoughts
just started bubbling up,
I can't hold them back.
I'm going to the desert.
[LUTE] Gamigami said
that once it's bound,
a Kinship can never be broken.
But I--
Oh, Lute.
I shouldn't have let him go.
I should've gone after him.
I'm gonna find Cheval!
I'll come, too!
[SIMONE]
Lilia!
Are you all right?
Oh, Captain Simone!
I was so worried about you.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm feeling much better now.
I've decided
I'm going to investigate
the attack on Hakum Village
so I can understand
the Black Blight
and prevent it
from spreading any further!
[Well then, I'll help you.
If it's what my prize
Scrivener wants.
Oh, Captain Simone.
[SIMONE] Where are all
your friends from back home?
Oh, man! We haven't
sold a fricken thing!
"We're gonna make more money
than we know what to do with.
You'll be swimming in donuts."
So what happened?
It's all your fault!
Yeah, that ugly-looking
mug of yours
is bad for business, buddy!
You're one to talk!
Oh, shut up, Weird-whiskers!
Can it, Tub...
Uh...
[NAVIROU, quietly]
...bli.
Hey, quit messing
with my name like that!
[LUTE]
Hey!
[panting]
Hey, Tub...
--...bli.
--Quit messing with my name!
Have you seen
Cheval and the others?
Uh. Can't say I have.
Why, what's goin' on?
[LUTE]
I need to find him.
Oh, come on now.
The two of you are over!
[gasps]
Sorry, but it can't
always be like it was
when you guys were kids.
That's just what
becoming a man is all about!
[LUTE]
Not true.
What you said just isn't true!
Cheval and I are family!
A Kinship bound can never
be broken! Never!
Really, is that so?
[grunts]
Wait, he was going to
stock up on supplies, right?
So, if I were you,
I'd try looking for him
somewhere over by the docks.
Got it! Thanks, Tub--!
[DEBLI] I told you,
stop messing with my name!
[LILIA]
Navi! And Tub...
[panting]
--...bli!
--Oh, come on!
[LUTE]
That's right.
Kinship can never be broken.
No matter what!
Hey, Cheval!
--[HUNTER A] A monster!
--[HUNTER B] Here in town?
[HUNTER C]
And it's a Rathalos, no less!
[HUNTER B]
A Rathalos?
[LUTE]
[REVERTO]
Hey!
[LUTE]
Mister!
Hey there, Lute.
Lotta stuff went down
in the desert.
Oh, yeah.
--[RATHALOS roars]
--[HUNTERS gasping]
[REVERTO] A Rathalos?
Huh, what's that doing here?
Hey, what the--?
Well, oddness abounds.
[RATHALOS growling]
[gasps]
[LUTE]
Ratha, what's wrong?
C'mon, pull up!
Ratha?
Hang in there! Ratha! Ratha!
[LUTE]
Ratha! Ratha!
Ratha!
[HUNTERS yell]
--[HUNTER A] Now!
--[HUNTER B] Keep it surrounded!
[HUNTER C]
Don't let it get away!
[roars]
--[HUNTER C] Watch out!
--[HUNTER D] This one's quick!
No, stop! Don't do it!
That's my Monstie!
[REVERTO]
You're gonna have to show 'em.
The Kinship between you.
You won't be able
to stop them otherwise.
[RATHA growls]
[gasps]
Hey, kid!
Ratha! It's me! It's Lute!
You can tell, right, Ratha?
[growls]
[roars]
Is that... a Rathalos?
Is it?
[gasps]
Whoa, is that?
Ratha!
[roaring]
That's right, it's me!
It's Lute, Ratha!
Is that really him?
I guess so.
Ratha! Ratha!
[RATHA growls]
Oh, wow, it really was Ratha!
Well, Navirou
could tell right away!
Ratha. Oh, Ratha!
[gasps]
[HUNTER A]
Hey! Watch out, kid!
[HUNTER B]
Step aside!
[REVERTO]
Lute!
Now fly!
[LUTE]
Ah!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's go!
[laughing]
Oh, Ratha. I'm so happy
you're still alive!
Oh, Ratha!
[RATHA roars]
A Kinship bound
can never be broken.
It really can't!
Hey, Lute and Ratha!
Aren't you guys forgetting
a certain very important
Navirou here?
Go, Lute.
So this is the famed Kinship
between Rider and Monstie.
Hey, Lute!
Hey, guys!
I thought we might
find you out here.
Cheval, I just--
[CHEVAL]
We're the same. You and me.
No family. Home to return to.
--Only our Monsties--
--[LUTE] No!
You do have family.
I'm your family!
Then let's take down
that Diablos together!
With these Blighted monsters,
it's our only choice.
Well, uh...
[REVERTO] I heard about the
Blighted Diablos mid-Quest.
My village was
the one it attacked.
Your village?
That's right. My hometown.
♪
[LILIA]
Be careful out there.
I'll do everything
to learn about the Blight.
So we can stop it.
Good. And thank you.
Don't overdo it now.
Same to you.
And as for you, Reverto.
Please try to keep your cool.
No promises.
My village is toast, after all.
Good luck, to every one of you.
All right, let's move out!
[whistle blows]
♪
This is just terrible.
Mister.
Where is it?
Where's the Diablos?
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out, too,
while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: One-Eyed Rathalos!
At long last, he returned!
His eye may have been injured
in the Nargacuga fight,
but you know,
it's just not an adventure
without Ratha there!
Way to go, Lute!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
Well, we made it
to Albrachs Village
and finally found a Kinship Ore.
But standing between us
and that Ore is a monster.
C'mon, Cheval!
Next time: "Diabolical Diablos,
Horned Wyvern."
Ride On!