[NARRATOR] Navirou reunited
with his old girlfriend, Pansy,
and the whole gang set off for
her home on Naubaka Island.
She is not Navirou's
girlfriend! It is a gray area!
[NARRATOR] But ships had
stopped sailing to the island,
and the kids were stuck on land.
Luckily, a man stepped
forward to help:
The "Bandit Captain," Silva!
All looked well as they set
sail for Naubaka Island
but then, the weather turned
and a Blighted
Seregios attacked!
After a hard-fought victory,
Lute, Navirou, and friends
finally arrived safely
on the island.
Except Ratha's still a little
green from getting seasick.
Wow! Look at all those Felynes!
[FELYNES] Meow-loha,
welcome to Koapani Village
on Naubaka Island!
[ALL]
Meow-loha!
[LUTE] Hey, why are you
lookin' so bummed out?
I thought you'd be excited
we made it here.
Despite his otherwise
illustrious career,
there are may be one
or two rough patches
Navirou doesn't wish to revisit.
What rough patches?
Yeah, you leave behind a crazy
ex-girlfriend or somethin'?
Wait, a girlfriend?
With your face?
[CHIEF MALLERIE] Navirou!
You finally came back to me!
[yelps]
Navirou!
That old lady is
Navirou's ex-girlfriend?
You're back!
Chief Mallerie!
That's the Chief?
I'd like you all to meet the
Chieftess of Koapni Village.
Navirou's ex-girlfriend
is the chief?
No-No!
Nothing romantic
has ever happened
between Navirou
and Chief Mallerie!
Navirou, I'm so
glad you're back.
And Pansy, too.
I spent many-a-sleepless night
worrying where you two might be.
We searched everywhere we
could possibly think of!
I'm so sorry for putting
mew through that.
Um, well, Chief.
Navirou's passing through.
He can't stay.
You can't have come all this
way only to make me sad again.
Just this morning
I saw a good omen.
A stem was floating
upright in my tea,
and sure enough, you're here!
All that time away and you two
are finally where you belong.
I don't think I've ever been
happier than I am right now.
[NAVIROU]
Sorry, Granny.
And even after Navirou vanished
without saying a word.
An adventurer can search
the whole of creation
and never find a Felyne as
special as you, Navirou.
Wherever your travels take you,
I will always keep
you in my heart.
Oh, Granny!
[whistle blows]
[ALL]
Ahoy!
Look! The Numbers are
visiting, too! Hey!
That looks great!
Oh, man. I'm flat broke.
[DEBLI] Don't you
worry there, buddy boy!
As soon as I rake in
the dough, I'll treat ya!
Wanna Felyne snack?
Then I'm your man!
Today's special is top-grade
sprigs of fresh Felvine!
Sir, I challenge
you to taste this
and say it's not the
finest you've ever had!
It's so shiny,
it's almost glowing!
That's how you know he's telling
the truth about its quality.
So gorgeous! But it
must be so pricy.
Well, ma'am you're in luck,
'cause I'm selling them for
the bargain-basement price...
...of only 1,000 Zenny each!
[NUMBERS]
Ooh!
[SPEX]
Yes! One please!
[DEBLI]
Thank you, thank you.
Get in line for the finest
Felvine! C'mon, folks!
[FELYNES yelling]
Whoa. Wait!
[ALL laughing]
[NAVIROU]
Hm?
Are those guys old
friends of yours, too?
Nah!
Navirou's oldest friend
will always be the donut!
Also, since we're here,
Granny's Poi Palloi Pickles!
Corduroy pickles?
Poi Palloi Pickles!
[CHIEF MALLERIE chuckles]
My Poi Palloi Pickles
are so popular
they were even featured
in the Meowchelin Guide
for Naubaka Island fine dining.
Oh, wow!
Navirou's happy to report
they're still the best in town!
What? Just the best in town?
And to think, all this time
I thought my pickles
were the best in the world!
No! You're right.
The best in the world!
Heck, the best in the galaxy!
Not just that!
Best in the universe!
[CHIEF MALLERIE laughs]
Flattery might work with
friends, but not me.
Speaking of friends,
where are they?
Oh, Debli and Avinia?
They're enjoying all the
pleasures of the village.
[DEBLI sighs]
This is
nuzzling nirvana.
[sighs]
Now I'm in pawpad paradise!
Huh?
Nothing in the world burns
brighter than my spirit!
Number One!
Beats!
I'm of warm heart,
but cool breath.
Number Two!
I am Cryo!
Sparkle-sparkle!
My dazzling beauty is
almost blindingly bright!
Number Three!
Fifi here!
You don't need glasses to
see that I'm the brains here.
Number Four!
You can call me Spex!
Always time for a nap!
Number Six!
Look, it's me, Floof!
And all together, we are:
[ALL]
The Numbers!
[FELYNES cheering]
[FELYNE A] These big city
Felynes are so glamorous!
[LUTE laughs]
[LUTE] Well, if they're not
here, that's more for us!
They're missing out on some
of the best grub so far!
[BOTH]
Hey!
Don't fight, boys.
There's plenty more
where that came--
Dearie me.
It's completely empty!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Navirou's favorite
non-donut food.
I'm sorry.
Vegetables have just gotten
so hard to come by these days.
And without veggies,
Granny can't make any
of her Poi Palloi Pickles.
I'll get the veggies for ya!
That's right, and
Navirou will help!
That's kind of you, boys,
but I'm afraid it's not
as easy you think.
It seems the woodland farm
fields have been destroyed by...
...that awful Black Blight.
It got your crops?
[CHIEF MALLERIE]
Throughout our history,
the Blight's always
been a disaster
that comes about naturally,
only to recede in
much the same fashion.
But for whatever reason,
this time the Blight
is not going away.
Well, Lute. Let's roll!
Right! We'll stop it!
We can't live in a world
without Poi Palloi Pickles!
Donut down!
And here I thought someone
dropped trash in the road.
Nope! It's just mew.
So gross. It tastes weird.
It's purrfect for
a weirdo like mew.
[TIGER, SCREWTAIL laughing]
[NAVIROU] Say what
you want about Navirou.
Just don't talk bad
about his donuts!
Oh, no, watch out, Tiger!
Donut-lover's gonna zap us!
[grunts]
If mew try that
freaky trick on us,
we'll literally kick
mewr tail outta town!
Ha!
The thrill of the wider
world calls to Navirou!
He's a busy Felyne!
He doesn't have time to waste
purring with the likes of you!
No fighting! Everyone,
just be nice to each other!
We're just looking
out for mew, Pansy!
If mew do anything
to hurt her, Navirou,
we'll make sure mewr never
able to eat another donut again!
Yeah, that's right!
Jeez, what's with those guys?
I mean, sure you
have a weird face,
weird whiskers too, and
a creepy love of donuts,
but you shouldn't be
bullied for that.
[NAVIROU yelps]
And you're certainly
not the type of Felyne
who'd ever hurt anyone.
True, Navirou is quite complex.
You can't expect those small
brains to understand him.
Besides, it's not like this is
Navirou's home
town or anything.
He doesn't care what they think.
Wait, now where're you going?
[NAVIROU]
Back to the village
to buy some of their specialty
Felyne sugar donuts.
Go on without Navirou, Lute!
That's weird.
Up to now, I had figured this
is where Navirou was from.
I remember when I found
him washed up on the shore.
It was a warm day
and the Anesfreesia had
just begun to bloom.
[gasps]
Oh, no! Please still be alive!
Hi, there. What's your name?
My name? It's, uh--
[PANSY]
He didn't remember anything.
Neither his name,
nor where'd he come from.
In that moment,
there was no Navirou.
There was only a
mysterious Felyne
carried in on the
waves to our island.
I took him in, and in time,
his body recovered.
But his emotions, like his
memories, remained missing.
Hey, there! Do mew wanna
go on a walk with me?
I call this place
my secret garden.
Whenever I'm feeling depressed,
or I just need some time to
think, I come here to relax.
I find that the view and
smell of the blooming flowers
always lifts my spirits!
[laughing]
[PANSY giggles]
Your smile is purr-ecious!
[gasps]
Navirou.
[PANSY]
Huh?
Navirou's name is
Navirou! Yahoo!
[NAVIROU laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[PANSY] That afternoon,
Navirou remembered his name
and his smile.
And although the rest of his
memories never came back,
his fun-loving ways soon made
him the life of Koapni Village.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
It sounds like you saved
Navirou's life, Pansy.
If anything,
Navirou saved mine.
[roars]
[screams]
Pansy!
[gasps]
[PANSY] His power not only
saved me from that monster,
it was the most beautiful
sparkle I'd ever seen.
But Tiger and Screwtail
didn't see it that way.
They thought Navirou
was trying to hurt me.
Mew get away from her!
[TIGER yelps]
I'll save mew, Tiger!
[SCREWTAIL yells]
I wanted to clear up
the misunderstanding,
but then one day, when
I went to get Navirou,
he had just disappeared.
So that's what happened.
I know he wasn't born here,
but everyone in the
village loves Navirou
and wants him to feel at home.
Except Tiger and Screwtail.
[gasps]
Gotta tell the others!
Funny meeting mew again.
[TIGER]
Where do mew think mew're goin'?
Pansy may've
stopped me, earlier
but this time, I'm definitely
gonna get my payback.
Navirou doesn't have
time for this right now.
Mew hurt Pansy,
now I'll hurt mew!
Ugh! You've got it all wrong!
Navirou wasn't hurting her,
he was saving her
from that monster!
I'm not talking about what
mew did with the monster.
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
That day... when mew
left the village,
she went after mew!
When she saw mew were
gone, she was devastated.
She couldn't understand
how mew could leave
without saying goodbye.
I swore never to let her go
through that pain again.
Think hard about mewr
plans this time.
If mew're leaving again,
mew have to make sure
that mew tell her first.
But if mew're staying
on this island,
mew better prove to the Village
that mew're someone
we can trust.
[NAVIROU]
Uh...
Let's go, Screwtail!
Show us what you got!
[LUTE gasps]
[PANSY gasps]
I have to see how
far it's spread.
Pansy, wait!
Lute! Look at what Navirou
found in the sand!
The Blight's at the beach, too?
[PANSY screams]
Pansy!
[roars]
Navirou, that
monster's Blighted!
Hold on, Pansy!
Ride On!
Yian Kut-Ku!
[roaring]
It got Pansy!
Fluffy, wuffy.
Tubli!
My name is Debli! Debli!
[NAVIROU]
Pansy, we're here!
Navirou!
re you scared?
Lute, how could you forget?
These two Monsties
are natural enemies!
You rest, and I'll
take it from here.
Ride On!
Let's go, Tigrex!
[roars]
[MONSTERS roaring]
[gasps]
Hey, Lute! Give it some room!
[LUTE]
Okay!
The tail is it's weak spot!
But be careful, the
spikes are poisonous!
Got it!
Attack it the next time
it uses its breath!
Rock Smash attack!
Pansy!
Navirou.
You're safe, Pansy.
Navirou's here.
Hm?
[NAVIROU]
Hey! You leave her alone!
[NAVIROU screams]
Mew did it! Mew're my hero.
Thank mew. That's twice
mew've saved my life.
How'll I ever repay mew?
No, Pansy, Navirou
should be thanking you.
He'll always owe you for
finding him on that beach.
Navirou.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
Hey, why're you
riding Great Poogie?
Oh, right, about that.
Ride On!
Barioth!
I think your Monstie is sick.
It must be this weather.
Frost Fang is used to
a much colder climate.
Just leave this to me!
Ride On!
Great Poogie!
[POOGIE]
Poogie, poogie, poogie...
Hey! Come back!
So much for leaving this to him.
[laughs]
And that's why it's important
we Riders stick together!
Right?
Hey, c'mon, you guys.
Back me up here.
[AVINIA]
It's infected with the Blight.
[LUTE]
It's not just this monster.
Pansy and I found
the Blight inland
and Navirou saw it at the shore.
What now?
The ore.
There must be Kinship Ore
somewhere around here.
And if the Black Blight's
already taken it over,
like I think it has, we're
gonna have to purify it!
Tiger.
[NAVIROU]
Uh?
It looks like we
had mew all wrong.
Sorry 'bout that.
And I'm sorry I stole
your precious donut.
Okay, thanks?
Misunderstanding or not,
I acted like a jerk,
and that was wrong.
Go on, hit me.
Um, I don't really
feel like being hit.
But you can call me any names
you want and I'll take it.
Please accept these
tokens of friendship.
[TIGER, SCREWTAIL gasp]
After all, you fellas were only
looking out for Pansy, right?
Well, obviously, Navirou
cares about her, too!
That means we're all
on the same side!
Navirou. You're
such a good guy.
And after all the cruddy
things we said and did.
You're not good, you're great!
Okay, bring it in!
[TIGER, SCREWTAIL]
Oh, Navirou!
[TIGER, SCREWTAIL crying]
[TIGER]
We're so sorry.
[NAVIROU] Pansy, remember
the first time we came here?
The Anesfreesia were blooming
just like they are now.
Feels like only yesterday.
So, um, there's something
I've wanted to ask mew.
Navirou, can you
think about maybe...
....staying this time?
Uh?
Mew don't want to?
No, It's not like that at all.
It's just complicated.
But everyone in the
village would be so happy
if mew stayed with us.
We could live here
together, Navirou.
[NAVIROU]
Pansy.
Here's the thing.
[CHIEF MALLERIE]
Bad news, everyone!
It's an emergency!
Granny, what's wrong?
Someone has stolen Granny's
precious pickle weight!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Yian Garuga!
You can't miss this bird wyvern
thanks to its black shell,
poisonous tail, and long mane.
It's so hot tempered, it'll keep
attacking even when hurt!
This is one Monstie
you can count on!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys, Lute here!
Someone has stolen the
Poi Palloli pickle weight
and Koapni Village
is in a frenzy.
But don't worry, we're on the
case, right? Detective Navirou?
Next time: "Rainbow
Beach Blockade!"
Ride On!