[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Having learned about
a Kinship Ore
located in the
Forest of Confusion,
Lute followed lightning
strikes to the den of Kirin,
an Elder Dragon.
However, Lute discovered
that the Kinship Ore there
was untainted by
the Black Blight.
The Kirin had kept it safe.
After conveying its intentions
to Lute through Navirou,
the beast disappeared
into the forest.
Huh? What is it Lilia?
We've seen murals
of Redan before.
Yeah? Well, I haven't.
So what does it say?
"An ebon donut was
burned upon the edges,
a donut white came
forth undercooked."
You really only care
about one thing.
"In the beginning
was the Awakening.
When an ebon darkness
is born upon the Earth,
a dragon white will come forth
at the base of a great tree."
[NAVIROU]
Oh, yeah! That!
"Two Kinships, joined.
Bound together. The Hunter
becomes the Rider.
When there is Kinship,
there is light.
When there is no Kinship,
there is darkness.
The Black Dread,
born of the darkness
will stain the earth
as blackest jet."
Come to think of it,
we never did find out
what that Black Dread
thing was about.
That's right, though
you gotta figure
it's probably something
both black and dreadful.
I wonder if this tablet
could be showing us
where to find all
of the Kinship Ore.
Huh?
[SIMONE]
The Kinship Ore?
[LILIA]
That's right.
It looks like each
sectioned-off block here
is showing the location
of another Kinship Ore.
Ah, yes, I see it now.
Let's compare them
against the old maps
we have back at the
Scriveners' office.
Okay, so if this
thing is divided up
into seven segments,
do you think that means
there are seven
Kinship Ore in total?
How many have we found so far?
The Forest of Confusion, and,
um... Where else have we been?
Why don't we head
back and check?
All right. Lieutenant Pappan?
Ma'am?
I'd like for you to go
join up with our detachment.
Aye, roger that!
What detachment?
They're searching for
Dr. Manelger's whereabouts.
Look there! It's Cheval!
Cheval, my boy!
[DR. MANELGER] We've been
searching all over for you!
Gathering intel from
Hunters and Felynes alike,
and here, at long last,
we've finally found you!
What do you want?
Oh, come on, cheer up!
My Mecha Kinship Stone
is fully operational now!
So, Cheval, you've been rather
reckless on your Quest
to find a mighty Monstie
that you can make your own.
But that all ends today!
Your search is over!
Why, with this Mechinship Stone,
that legendary white dragon
will be yours in no time!
And you're telling the truth?
Oh-ho, you bet I am!
Now, if you just hand over
that Kinship Stone of yours.
What, mine?
Yes, indeed!
I've just gotta pop this
Mechinship Stone onto it
and then we'll be
all set to begin.
That white dragon will
be putty in your hands!
Well? Well? Well?
[chuckles]
Now, let's get these
forged together.
Aye-aye, sir, right away!
[DR. MANELGER] You seem
awfully tired there, my boy.
You should go on and get
yourself some rest, now.
It'll do you good.
[SIMONE] The mural of
Redan tells us that there are
a total of seven Kinship Ore.
There are seven!
Now so far, we've
found six of them.
The Forbidden Land
in Hakum Village.
Albrachs Village.
The Dovan Volcano.
Naubaka Island.
The Purespring
in Hakum Village.
And the Forest of
Confusion makes six.
That means there's still
one Kinship Ore left.
Well, where do you
think it could be?
A place of legend, it seems.
Huh? What does that mean?
It's in the Ruins of Zalam,
located within Mount Celion.
The Ruins of Zalam?
Where is this Mount
Celion anyway?
Even a world-traveler like
Navirou's never heard of it!
[SIMONE]
Right here.
Whoa, that's even beyond
the Darj Snowfields!
After comparing
the mural of Redan
with some of our ancient maps,
I'm confident the location
of the seventh Kinship Ore
corresponds to the
Ruins of Zalam.
So that's where we'll
find the final Kinshp Ore.
But what kinda place is it?
What're we getting
ourselves into?
Well, the Ruins of Zalam
appear only in the literature.
No one alive today
has ever seen them.
After suffering some
sort of disaster,
it was sealed away behind
an impenetrable gate.
This is known as
the Gate of Zalam.
According to the texts,
the seal can only be broken by
"Redan, astride a dragon white."
Wait, does that mean we won't be
able to open the gate ourselves?
I'm not sure.
But if "Redan" here
simply refers
to a Rider with a Kinship Stone,
then it may still be possible.
There's only one way
for us to find out.
You should know, it definitely
won't be an easy trip.
There are a lot of very tough
monsters up on Mount Celion.
Most Hunters won't
go anywhere near it!
Would Fate tell Navirou
to venture off
to such a dangerous place?
There's no way!
If that were the case, Navirou
would have to defy Fate itself!
We can leave you here
if you don't wanna come.
[NAVIROU yelps]
No, no, if you're going,
then Navirou's going, too.
I've gotta go. This is
the last Kinship Ore.
And that Kirin...
I bet it wants me to go.
Then we'd better start
gathering supplies.
We're running severely
low on donuts!
I'll handle drink preparations!
Why don't you let
somebody else handle that?
I'll arrange for some
Hunters to escort us.
We can use the help.
We'll set out as
soon as we're ready.
[NAVIROU] That's a hundred
Guild donuts in all!
Throw in some extras?
[VENDOR A grumbles]
[DEBLI] You can't just
ask her for handouts!
Try this: "You're so beautiful.
I'll be seeing you again!"
[giggles]
[BOTH]
Thank you!
[LUTE]
Hey! We're leaving!
All right, we've got
plenty of donuts!
[LUTE] From Gildegaran
through Perennial Pass
to the Darj Snowfields.
It's the reverse of the
route we took before.
That was back when
we were all together.
Yeah.
So where are these
Hunter bodyguards
who're s'posed to
be escorting us?
We're meeting up with them
at a little inn on
the Darj Snowfields.
Oh, yeah, with the hot springs!
I wonder how the
Riddlemaster's doing.
Right, I remember him.
That Wyverian guy.
That was rough, having to
answer all his weird riddles.
[LUTE] Hey, by the way,
why are you even here?
"Why," you ask me?
'Cause I think there's
money to be made!
[NAVIROU]
Of course.
[RIDDLEMASTER]
I'm the one monster
that's always hangin' around.
What am I?
What are you? I don't know!
A Khezu?
Correct you are!
Good t' see y'all again.
Y'all come on in now
an' set a spell.
Cold, cold! The snowfields
are a brutal place for a Felyne.
You could always
wear something.
No way! Oh, so cold!
[LILIA] That's just Navi's
little hang-up, I guess.
Do you by chance know
if there are any Hunters
waiting for us here?
Oh, is that who you
folks're lookin' for?
Reckon you'll find
'em in the hot spring.
[NAVIROU
Hot spring?!
That's right,
there's a hot spring!
We can all warm up in there!
[LUTE sighs]
So nice.
Nice and toasty.
Hey, no swimming!
Where are your manners?
Navirou's not swimming.
He's just giving
his mind and body
over to the flow of the water.
[yelps]
That's what you get!
[REVERTO]
Hey, watch it!
[NAVIROU screams]
Sorry about my friend, sir.
Got here faster than I expected.
Whoa, Mr. Reverto?
The lone-wolf Hunter!
Are you our escort
for this journey?
Me and one other Hunter.
And if the Scriveners
asked for that ace,
you know we're in for
one heck of a Quest.
[LUTE] So our other
bodyguard is Fahali?
Yeah, she outranks Reverto.
Mount Celion? Really?
But as I understand it, the
trail that goes up Mount Celion
has been lost for ages now.
Thanks to the Scriveners,
that ancient path has
now been uncovered.
So when do we leave?
You'll accept the Quest then?
Well, if I said no to danger,
what kind of Hunter would I be?
Can't wait to see what sorta
monsters they have up there.
I thank you both in advance.
Captain Simone, wait! Captain!
Lieutenant Pappan?
[PAPPAN] Oh, thank goodness
I finally caught up with you.
What's wrong?
It's Dr. Manelger, ma'am.
We went to go investigate
his research lab,
but the place was abandoned.
However, we did find a map,
and there was an "X"
marking Mount Celion.
It looks like Manelger's
got his sights
set on Mount Celion, too!
That means he must be searching
for the final Kinship Ore,
just like us.
Then we have to hurry!
Right. Lieutenant
Pappan, listen.
I want you to stay
behind and stand watch.
Keep an eye out for
Manelger, right?
Yes, ma'am. I got it!
[LILIA]
Here you go, Energy Drinks!
These'll give you a boost!
Uh, did you make these?
They're from the Scriveners.
That's a relief.
But I guess I did help
make a bunch for them
in the first place, so...
[OTHERS scream]
There it is.
That old familiar flavor.
[DEBLI]
Oh, why me?
And now for some Hot Mists so
we can all keep the cold at bay!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Eek! There's no path up here!
I don't think anyone
ever makes it this far.
What could Dr. Manelger possibly
want with the Ruins of Zalam?
Just making creepy
mecha monsters
must not be cutting
it for him anymore.
Now he's stealing
white dragon eggs,
and trying to recruit Cheval.
He's gotta have
something up his sleeve,
but what the heck is it?
I wonder if Cheval's
with him now.
Since he seems to be
such an important part
of Doctor Manelger's
plans, he probably is.
Yeah, you're right.
That's it.
This isn't a route you just
happen to stumble across,
that's for sure.
Ah! We're so high up!
It's a long way down.
Be careful.
We're finally on Mount Celion.
[LILIA] Then those must
be the Ruins of Zalam.
So that's where we're going?
Can't Ratha just fly us
all over there real quick?
[ALL yelp]
It's freezing!
Even with that Hot Mist on us!
The harsh winds
whipping around up there
will be much more
biting, I'm afraid.
We'll have to go
ahead on foot.
I'll take point
and lead the way.
Then guess I'm
bringin' up the rear.
[roaring]
That's a Brachydios!
Mount Celion for ya.
Tough monsters up here.
Come on. This way.
Baggi! And they saw us!
That was awesome, Mister!
Yeah, yeah, just watch.
Navirou will scare off
the next batch of Baggi.
Really? You, Navi?
They might think you're
a snack and pounce.
[NAVIROU yelps]
Well, we can't just
sneak past this one.
You guys make a run for it!
Fahali!
C'mon, let's go!
She can take care of herself.
[gasps]
More Baggi.
All right, now it's
Navirou's turn to step up
and chase 'em away!
Nu-uh, I'm gonna do it!
Oh, please. Reverto's got this.
[roar]
What the--?
Ah! What is that?!
That's a... Deviljho!
[screams]
Let's see, Monsterpedia says...
Here it is!
"The Deviljho is an
extremely violent predator
that can hunt nearby
monsters into extinction.
Also known as
'Violent Wyvern'"?
You guys keep going, all right?
[LUTE] Really? Are you gonna
be okay here by yourself?
Leave this to me!
[DEBLI] Yeah! Reverto's
got this under control!
He's slain one of these before!
[REVERTO]
Actually, I haven't!
[NAVIROU]
What?! You haven't?
Mister!
I've got your back!
[LILIA]
Captain Simone!
It's in your hands now.
I believe fully in
the power of Kinship!
Only you Riders
can stop the Blight.
Good luck, Lilia.
Yes, ma'am!
[REVERTO]
Get outta here, Lute!
[LUTE]
Okay!
Bring it.
[LUTE]
So it's up there?
The Gate of Zalam's that way.
[roar]
Oh, man! Don't tell me
there's another monster!
Ah! Navirou's tingly!
Navirou felt like this
once before when... Uh?
It's a Zinogre!
Worse! A Stygian Zinogre!
And it looks like it's Blighted!
Uh-oh.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
Here comes its Dragon Tackle!
Great, what now?
[LUTE yells]
[LILIA]
Lute!
Don't worry, I got this one!
Ride On!
Great Poogie!
[POOGIE]
Poogie-poogie-poogie-poogie.
[DEBLI]
Uh. What?
[POOGIE]
Poogie!
Let's go!
Now! Sky-High Extreme!
You okay there, Ratha?
Got a little rough, huh?
[DR. MANELGER,
ITSY-BITS yelling]
Manelger!
[DR. MANELGER, ITSY-BITS]
Help! Help!
[NAVIROU] Guess the winds
are really bad up there.
[LILIA] They're heading right
for the Gate of Zalam!
[LUTE]
Then we'd better hurry!
Ha, a crash landing!
It serves 'em right!
But I don't see any sign
of Dr. Manelger.
[gasps]
[ITSY-BITS] So is this
the Gate of Zalam, sir?
Yes, and the final Kinship
Ore should be hiding
just beyond those
enormous doors.
[LUTE]
Wait!
It's no use, you
can't go any farther!
Aha! It's the
white dragon egg!
Give it back! There's no
point in you two having it!
What good's it to you?
[chuckles] You'll
see soon enough.
Ahem, that's your cue
to enter, my boy!
Oh, Cheval.
Cheval!
What are you going
to do with that egg?
I'm making it my Monstie.
And then I'll stop
the Black Blight.
I'm putting an end
to all of this!
But only Redan can make
a white dragon his Monstie!
That's what the legend says!
I'll prove to you all that my
way is ultimately the right way!
Whoa, hold on, is that...?
The fruit of my labor and
genius, a Mecha Kinship Stone!
Wait, a Mecha Kinship Stone?
Is that different from this
artificial Kinship Stone?
Well, either way,
it's still just a fake!
This is a Kinship Stone
above all others!
You just watch me, Lute.
As long as I have this
enhanced Kinship Stone...
Stop it, Cheval!
Manelger is just using you!
You have to realize that!
I will be the next Redan!
Look, the white dragon
is responding!
I am the one the white
dragon has chosen!
What's that?
Hey.
Do you think...?
[LILIA] This is the
dragon white of legend.
It's huge!
How's it this big when
it's only just hatched?
[DR. MANELGER laughing]
Redan is reborn!
At long last, Cheval
is become Redan!
[DR. MANELGER laughing]
[LUTE]
Cheval! Wait!
[NAVIROU screaming]
Please, Cheval, no!
I'm going!
Help me out, Ratha!
[DEBLI]
Huh?
Hey! Don't leave us here!
I said, "Don't leave us!"
I'm coming, Cheval.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Versa Pietru!
The monster from the legend
of Redan has finally arrived,
and who knew it would
awaken looking like that?
Hey, Lute, you're really gonna
have to stop Cheval now!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] At long last, the
white dragon has awoken.
But, Cheval, wait!
I don't wanna fight you!
Next time: "The Legendary
White Dragon Is Born"!
Ride On!