[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
By using the power of Dr.
Manelger's Mecha Kinship Stone,
Cheval has hatched the
legendary white dragon egg!
I will be the next Redan!
Look, the white
dragon is responding!
I am the one the white
dragon has chosen!
[NARRATOR] At long last,
the fabled "dragon white"
has been reborn!
But has Cheval truly assumed
the legacy of Redan?
[LUTE]
Cheval! Wait!
Please, Cheval, no!
I'm going!
Help me out, Ratha!
I'm coming, Cheval.
You heard that, right?
I did.
The white dragon of
legend is reborn.
So what do we do now?
Put our trust in the
children. All we can do.
Sounds good.
Besides, we got a monster of
our own we're dealin' with here.
Where's Cheval and
the white dragon?
Navirou knows. He's got this!
[BOTH]
They're that way!
[DEBLI]
Hey, c'mon, Lilia, wait, up!
Shouldn't the Rider be the
one setting the pace here?
Debli, you're gonna
get left behind!
Eh, who cares? I'll just
stay back, like always.
No, wait! Debli's
not giving up yet!
[yells]
Nothing.
We lost their trail.
[LILIA]
Lute!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[LUTE]
Lilia!
[DEBLI]
Check out my full-tilt dash!
[DEBLI yells]
Normally, Navirou would
say something witty here,
but these are not
exactly normal times.
Navirou bites his tongue.
Maybe next time, pal.
Blah-blah! No one
asked for your opinion.
Lute, I wanna come with
you to look for Cheval.
No, things are only gonna get
more dangerous from here.
Lilia, the best thing for
you to do would be--
[LILIA]
I'm not staying back anymore!
All this time I've been
searching for him.
The old Cheval.
[LILIA]
I need to see him.
I think he can still
be reasoned with.
We'll be okay.
If I can just talk to him,
I know he'll understand.
You're right.
Come with us, Lilia.
I'm glad you agree, Lute.
Let's split up!
We gotta find him before
he gets the Kinship Ore!
I'm ready! Debli'll find
him, just you watch!
All right, guys,
let's find Cheval.
We'll go search the
outskirts of the ruins!
Okay, Lute! C'mon!
Huh? Oh, yeah, right!
And I was so pumped up.
[LILIA]
Cheval! Hello!
[DEBLI] This is hard.
Cheval and Lute get to fly!
Meanwhile, we're stuck down
here, trudgin' in the snow.
Uh?
[DEBLI gasps]
Hey, Lilia, come here.
I think I found something.
This is big.
Can you make out
that inscription?
[LILIA]
It says: "The Ore-born Blight
is become the Black Dread,
thwarting the workings of all."
[DEBLI]
And what does that mean?
It means a monster
that had been Blighted
by the Zalam Kinship
Ore transformed
into the Black Dread,
and turned Zalam Village
into these desolate ruins.
What? No way.
So this whole place...
Lilia, look!
[LILIA]
Cheval!
[DEBLI] And Manelger
and his little lackey!
[whistle]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Lilia's whistle! They
must've found something!
Yeah! Take us down, Ratha!
There he is.
Cheval!
Now hold on a
minute there, Lute!
You know we can't let you just
waltz right up to
Cheval like that.
[DR. MANELGER] I hate to
be the bearer of bad news,
but the boy you once called
your "friend" is gone forever!
Cheval is now the reborn Redan!
He will become the hero
you've always wanted to be,
all thanks to the Kinship
Stone that I created!
You wish!
I'm going to talk to Cheval,
so you two better move
before you get hurt!
Cheval! Are you crazy?!
How could you ever give your
Kinship Stone to Manelger?!
[CHEVAL]
That's irrelevant, Lute.
Now that the white dragon has
responded to me, and only me,
it means I'm the one who
will finally put an end
to the Black Blight.
We're not equals anymore,
it's not even close.
Don't do it. You can't win!
I have to try.
Lute, don't!
That's not some normal monster,
it's the white dragon!
Let's Ride On!
Rathalos!
I'll show you the power
of the white dragon.
Go!
[CHEVAL] Behold! This is
the white dragon's might!
White Breath!
Uh, you better have a Plan B!
There's no way you can
go toe-to-toe with him!
[CHEVAL] I have a power
that's only bestowed upon
the chosen ones!
The Blight will be defeated
at last. It is my destiny!
The next one's for real. Now!
Watch out!
[gasps]
[LUTE screams]
[CHEVAL] This power coursing
through me, it's incredible.
It's like nothing I've
ever felt before!
It's him. The power is Redan!
The person I've become
is capable of anything!
Destroy.
Lute, get out of there!
Hey, Ratha. Are you okay?
Thanks for saving me again.
[CHEVAL]
It's over, Lute.
I don't care how close
you are to that Monster.
You two don't stand a chance.
No one does.
Now finish them off!
Finish them! Now!
[CHEVAL yelps]
Sir, what's wrong
with the dragon?
Look there! His Kinship Stone!
[gasps]
[ITSY-BITS]
What happened?
Oh, man, what the
heck is going on now?
No, it's happening.
What the--?
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Doctor, it's cracking!
It's like the white dragon
is hatching all over again!
This is bad.
What happened?
A minute ago that dragon was
shimmering white, but look now!
It's all... It's become
totally black!
Oh, no. Is the white
dragon the Black Dread?
I'm not sure. What now?
If it is the Black Dread,
then my handiwork is
responsible for resurrecting
the world's most dangerous
force into the present.
If you hadn't used
the Mechinship Stone
to force the white
dragon to hatch,
none of this would be happening!
Because of you, they formed
the wrong kind of Kinship!
But we were connected by
a Kinship bond, I felt it!
No! Cheval, hold on!
Cheval, get outta there!
[CHEVAL]
Rathi?
[CHEVAL screams]
--No!
--Wha--?
What the heck was that?
Cheval! Cheval, no!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU, LUTE yelp]
[LUTE]
Cheval!
We're here!
I have to save him!
[NAVIROU]
Navirou's in!
Lute, wait!
We're coming to help, too!
[DR. MANELGER]
Well, let's go.
What? You wanna go down there
and look for Cheval, too?
Oh, no, the boy's already
served his purpose.
Right now, the only
thing that matters to me
is what's flying away.
[LUTE]
Cheval!
Cheval, where are you?
Hey! Cheval, you okay?
Where are you? Cheval!
[DEBLI] We're worried about
ya, pal, give us a sign!
[gasps]
[CHEVAL]
Rathi.
Oh, no.
Rathi!
I don't believe in
Kinship anymore!
Rathian, I have no
more use for you!
Rathi. You came back.
[CHEVAL] Well, I'm ending
it here. All of it.
Don't follow me!
[CHEVAL]
Rathi... Why? Why'd you do it?
Oh, Rathi. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Rathi.
Rathi! You're alive!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
[BOTH gasp]
[LUTE]
Cheval?
You're all right!
Despite everything,
she came back.
Even though I cast her aside.
Even though I tried
to sever the bond.
The Kinship between us.
But thank goodness a Kinship
bound can never be broken.
You always used to say that
to me, Lute. You remember?
Of course.
What do you think, Rathi?
Way back, when I first found
Rathi's egg, I was so excited.
I couldn't believe my luck.
And I... Well, I wanted to
surprise the whole gang with it.
So I hid the egg in my house.
Cheval, honey. Are you sure
that's a real Rathian egg?
Yep! I'm positive!
Well, if Lute calls his
Rathalos, "Ratha,"
then you should call
your Rathian, "Rathi."
[CHEVAL] Rathi's egg.
It's why my mom...
[CHEVAL] All you were trying
to do was protect my mom.
Weren't you, Lute?
But we still lost
her that night.
And all this time,
I blamed it on you.
That's why...
I wanted it so bad.
[CHEVAL]
The power...
Because with more power,
I-I'd be able to...
[LUTE] I know. You'd be
able to keep everyone safe.
We all worked hard to
protect Hakum that night.
I can't believe what I've
turned myself into since then.
[LUTE]
Well, I'm happy!
You two are safe and sound!
Oh, Lute.
Rathi. Thank you so much.
Oh, Cheval.
You're finally back.
I can see you again.
[DEBLI]
You guys, I love a happy ending.
Why're you crying?!
You barely know him!
Shut up! We're all crying!
It's an emotional reunion!
Wrong! Navirou is not crying!
Navirou would never
cry in public!
And that's a Navi-rule.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Cheval, I want you to meet Lute.
I expect you boys to play
nice with each other.
Hi. It's very nice
to meet you, Lute.
It's nice to meet you, Cheval.
I mean, you do
know pretty much
everything there is
to know about me!
Oh, yeah, well,
I think that you know
everything about me, Lute.
That's right!
So do you, Cheval!
Uh, Lute?
It makes sense 'cause
we're always together.
And because you
and I are family!
You don't have to say
that. Not ever, Lute.
Because that goes
without saying!
Itsy, look at that!
It's absorbing energy to make
itself even more powerful!
I know you enjoy the
spectacle, Doctor,
but it's not wise for us
to stay here any longer!
I have a bad feeling
about what comes next!
Uh?
Uh, guys. What's that?
It's the Black Blight!
And it looks like it's
spreading fast, too!
We have to stop it!
Let's Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU]
And Navirou!
No, Lute, it's too
dangerous now!
There's no choice!
[LILIA]
But!
Uh! Hey, wait!
[NAVIROU]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Is it just Navirou, or does
it look way stronger now?
I will stop it!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Deviljho!
It's massive jaws are
constantly snapping up prey!
That's why they call it
"Violent Wyvern"!
Navirou's certain you won't find
a more dangerous
monster than this one,
'cause that's the end of
the Monstie Manual !
Navirou hopes you managed
to find all those Monsties!
[LUTE] Even the White
Dragon's been taken over
by the Black Blight!
The whole world's at stake!
Let's go, Ratha!
Next time: "This Is It:
The Black Dread"!
Ride On!