[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Different opinions
about monsters
drove Lute and Cheval apart,
and led to Cheval attacking
his former best friend.
The boys mounted their Monsties
and were ready to settle
things once and for all,
but neither Ratha nor Rathi
could bring themselves
to attack the other.
Disenchanted and
seeking answers,
Lute underwent an introspective
trial at the Tower of Illusion.
Meanwhile, Cheval returned to
his friends Mille and Hyoro,
unaware that Dr. Manelger
was once again
trying to get his help.
[distant roar]
[HYORO]
Hey. Wait, a second.
Why do you have a
Velocidrome now, Cheval?
Didn't you leave with Rathi?
What happened to her?
She's gone.
I don't want a Monstie
that I can't use.
[DR. MANELGER]
Cheval!
Cheval, I'm back!
Cheval! Cheval,
my boy! I'm back!
He's so excited to see you,
he said it twice!
It's Manelger.
He's bad news.
[DR. MANELGER]
Cheval, my boy! Come with me!
I have something to show you!
[HYORO gasps]
Whoa! Hey, look!
Isn't that the white
dragon egg?
Yeah, that's the same one
Cheval couldn't get to hatch.
[MILLE]
Huh?
[DR. MANELGER]
Cheval, my boy!
Right this way, my boy!
You'll be interested to
learn I recently obtained
a shard of Kinship Ore!
From this fragment,
I intend to craft my very
own Kinship Stone.
And once it's ready,
you can use it to form Kinship
with the white dragon!
It's the culmination
of his life's research!
How long will the stone take?
If I'm being honest...
If you're being honest?
If he's being honest.
I don't know when!
You don't?!
Of course I don't know!
I'm doing something no
man's ever done before!
But I will get it done,
that much I promise you!
Just watch. I promise you,
I will get it done!
He means it so much
that he even said it twice!
But it is possible, right?
Yes!
And once this new Kinship
Stone is complete,
it will be yours to have!
Do you understand?
My dear boy, you will
be the first person
to ride a white dragon
in a thousand years!
I see.
But, Cheval.
You actually trust this guy?
Are you two ready?
Huh?
For what? Why?
Let's go.
What?
Go where?
We're not gonna
stay here and wait,
we're gonna do what Riders do.
[HYORO]
Uhh...
Good!
We don't really have enough room
for you kids to stick
around anyway,
so do whatever you like
in the meantime.
Let's slay some
Blighted monsters.
But where should
we start looking?
I guess we could try
the Hunters Guild first.
They might even give us a Quest.
We're not going
back to the Guild.
I know another place
than can help.
See any Blighted monsters?
And who are you?
Have you seen Blighted
monsters, yes or no?
You're talking awfully big
for a kid playing dress-up.
[FAHALI]
He's not just some kid.
[HUNTER A]
Hm? Fahali!
He and his friends are Riders.
[HUNTERS]
Hm?
What? She's kidding, right?
[FAHALI]
Nope.
They're some of the Riders
who saved Albrachs Village.
[HUNTER A] You kids were
part of that group?
You celebrating another
successful Quest?
Yeah, and it was
a dangerous one.
This is the best way to recover.
But enough about me, are
you gonna answer the kids?
Oh, right, what did he want?
Blighted monsters.
Anyway, yeah, we've been
hearing stories, lately,
about a real nasty one
that lives on the outskirts
of the desert.
And you're positive
it's Blighted?
[HUNTER A] Haven't seen it,
so we couldn't tell ya.
But we have heard
it's a Black Diablos.
Is a Black Diablos
supposed to be stronger
than a regular Diablos?
[HUNTER B]
Sure seems that way,
considering no one's
brought her down yet.
[CHEVAL]
I see.
[MILLE]
Hey, wait up!
[HYORO]
Cheval!
The other Rider we met was a
lot friendlier than that group.
Well, I guess Riders
come in many stripes.
Hey, bartender! Why
don'tcha keep them comin'?
[HYORO] Cheval, what are
we doing in the forest?
Yeah, last I checked,
Diablos is a desert monster.
And Diablos are
also very strong.
I need a Monstie that can
stand up to their power.
[HYORO]
Whoa! A Royal Ludroth?
You can find all kinds of
monsters in a forest this thick.
[roaring]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, no!
Nargacuga!
Hyoro! Mille! We're
gonna take it down!
What?
But it's not infected
with the Blight!
[CHEVAL]
Let's drive it out.
But, Cheval.
[CHEVAL]
You'll do it...
...'cause you're on my team.
--Now, Ride On!
--Ride On!
Monoblos!
Tigrex, go!
Charge!
[HYORO]
Right!
[MILLE yelps]
[MILLE]
C'mon, Tigrex, shake it off!
[HYORO]
Double strike attack!
Breaking Crush!
All right!
Hey, Cheval, we drove it away!
What now?
[CHEVAL]
Found you.
You're perfect.
What kind of egg is this?
O holy Kinship Stone,
bind me together with
this slumbering creature!
[CHEVAL]
And now, the moment of new life!
Awaken!
[BOTH gasp]
[HYORO]
A Nargacuga?
Hold on, are you--?
[CHEVAL] That's right.
I'm making it my new Monstie.
Cheval, you can't do this.
A Nargacuga killed your--
[yelps]
Cheval, are you
sure about this?
[CHEVAL]
I need its speed.
[MILLE] But can you really form
Kinship with a Nargacuga?
[CHEVAL] We're going to
slay the Black Diablos.
[HYORO]
Ugh... I'm so hot!
Well, duh, Hyoro. That's
what happens in a desert.
[HYORO]
Hey. There're people up there.
Oh... The people turned out
to just be a cactus patch.
It should be close by.
Yeah, good thinking.
Diablos eat these cacti.
It's gonna be a tough battle.
How are we doing on items?
Good. We're fully stocked
up on potions and tools.
All right, tomorrow we
bring down the Diablos.
[CHEVAL]
This is for you, Mom.
[gasps]
Oh, man. I thought the heat
was bad, but now a sand storm?
[MILLE]
Cheval, we're getting nowhere.
Let's pack it in for the day.
[CHEVAL]
Don't be weak. This is nothing!
[HUNTER B screams]
[HUNTER B]
Run! Don't look back!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Is that--?
[MILLE] I think those
are the same Hunters
we met in Albrachs Village.
[HUNTER A]
I thought we saw you!
[HUNTER B] If you're here
for the Black Diablos,
forget about it!
[HUNTER A] That's no ordinary
monster, she's a demon!
A rabid, violent, demon!
So she has been Blighted, then!
[roaring]
[HUNTERS gasp]
[HUNTER B]
Get outta the desert!
So what now?
[MILLE]
I don't know.
[CHEVAL]
Do you even have to ask? C'mon!
[BOTH gasp]
Do you really think it's
wise to go after a monster
that not even two
Hunters can handle?
[CHEVAL]
Those Hunters are weak.
Hyoro, Mille. We can do this!
[MILLE, HYORO]
Right.
[MILLE]
Wait!
Let's spread out!
There it is! The Black Diablos!
And it's definitely Blighted!
All right, let's Ride On!
Nargacuga!
Steady. This fight's
all about your speed.
[CHEVAL]
Dodge!
[MILLE gasps]
[MILLE]
Oh, wow.
[MILLE screams]
Now's our chance, Nargacuga!
Hyoro! Mille!
Now, Ride On!
Monoblos!
Let's Ride On!
Now, Tigrex!
You two, distract the Diablos!
[BOTH gasp]
Go! Make me an opening!
[MILLE]
Tigrex. Stone Toss!
Oh, no.
Killer Fang!
[CHEVAL]
What are you guys doing?
Get back in the fight!
[CHEVAL]
Now! Do it now!
Demolition Dash!
Tigrex, Rock Smash!
[MILLE]
How's that?
[MILLE yells]
[screaming]
Time for the Dark Thrash!
It worked.
We did it.
[MILLE]
How ya holdin' up, Tigrex?
[HYORO]
Monoblos, I'm so proud of you.
[CHEVAL]
You two were sloppy.
You were slow on
your follow-through.
You're no better than
a couple of Gargwa!
How rude!
Hey, we did our best
out there, Cheval.
Whoa. What's that?
Well, it can't be
the Blighted Diablos.
It's still lying right
where we left it!
[HYORO]
Oh, no! Another one?!
[MILLE]
There're two?
Wait, hold on.
Look, Cheval, this other
Diablos hasn't been Blighted!
That means we don't
have to slay it!
You're right. There's no
point in starting a fight.
Let's just leave it
alone and run away.
[CHEVAL]
Run?
It is Blighted!
[MILLE]
What? No, it isn't!
But Blighted or not, we
should still get outta here
before it sees us.
Go! Nargacuga!
What's wrong?
Why're you backing down?
Attack, Nargacuga, attack!
Hyoro, Mille! Go! Now!
Cheval.
I swear, it's not Blighted!
Mille's right, Cheval.
Can't we just get out of here?
Because sooner or later this
monster will be Blighted!
We can stop that
before it happens!
Do it! Attack!
[CHEVAL]
Get up, Nargacuga!
Dark Thrash!
[roar]
Coward! We have to finish it
off before it can escape.
[CHEVAL]
What are you doing?
Get up!
You haven't done
enough to be tired!
After it, you lazy beast!
Hyoro! Mille!
It's no use, Cheval.
It can't move!
[CHEVAL]
Get up!
C'mon, it's getting away!
Follow it, Nargacuga!
You failed me!
You're even more
useless than Rathian!
I don't need you, anymore.
So just get out of here.
[HYORO]
How could you say that?
[MILLE]
That poor Monstie.
Same goes for you!
Whaddaya mean?
The both of you are useless.
[BOTH gasp]
Well, I'm going to bed.
I mean it. I've had it
up to here with Cheval!
[HYORO] I'm not even
sure he likes us anymore.
It's pretty obvious
that he doesn't!
We're not friends to him.
We're pawns to order around!
Yeah. Right.
I also don't like him saying
that we're useless,
or that we're like Gargwa.
And using us as
decoys was real low.
I know. It's just not right.
I'm done. Do whatever
you want, Cheval.
[HYORO] I can't believe
all this time, I thought...
I really thought that
he was our friend.
[MILLE]
So did I.
[CHEVAL]
Mille? Hyoro?
Mille! Hyoro!
Anyone? Where are you?
[CHEVAL]
Where did you go?!
Get me a measurement
on that spectrum, Itsy-Bits.
Yes, sir!
[CHEVAL]
It's still not ready?
Cheval! You've actually come
back at the perfect time!
[ITSY-BITS]
But why'd you come back alone?
[DR. MANELGER]
Well, that is odd.
Where are your confederates?
They were both useless,
so I got rid of them.
Well, Cheval, my boy,
you'll be happy to know
that I have no need for
those Riders, anyway.
[ITSY-BITS] Wait till you see
what we've come up with!
[DR. MANELGER]
Okay! Boost the power output!
[ITSY-BITS]
Right!
[DR. MANELGER]
Ah! Too high, too high!
[ITSY-BITS]
Sorry, Doctor!
You won't betray me.
I'm sure of it.
I hope you hatch soon.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Royal Ludroth!
That big mane is used for more
than just looking fabulous!
It's where Ludroth stores
water for its attacks,
or so it can survive on land.
That's why, no matter
what environment it's in,
people call it,
"The Water Beast!"
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] There's a Kinship
Ore on Mount Rhyz?
Well, then we better find
it before Dr. Manelger!
Next time: "Numbers, Assemble."
Ride On!