[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Monster Hunter Stories ,
a Tigrex attacked Hakum
Village in the middle
of the apprentice
Riders' Kinship Rite!
At the last minute,
Lute and Ratha swooped in,
capturing the Tigrex.
Lute and his friends left
home for the first time,
hiking up into the mountains
to return the wayward beast.
But more trouble soon arose,
and the kids got their first
look at a real Hunter in action!
Our young Riders were left
with much to think about
as they returned home.
Navirou can't wait to
see what'll happen next!
[CHIEF OMNA] With the threat of
the Tigrex now safely behind us,
we can resume the Kinship Rite.
[KIDS]
Sir!
You will venture outside the
village, this time into a cave,
and swear an oath at
the Waterfall of Trials.
I know each of you wishes to
be a certain type of Rider,
and in saying this oath
that wish will be impressed
upon your hearts.
But as its name implies, the
Waterfall cannot be reached
without first overcoming
many a trial.
It is not the bond between
you and your Monstie
that matters here, but
the bond between each other.
Cooperation is key!
[KIDS]
Sir!
Top form! I like
that spirit, Riders!
And trust me, you'll need
it all in that cave.
[laughs]
You'll also need courage and
wisdom with your cooperation.
Good luck, my young Riders.
What's up, Cheval?
This feels weird without Lilia.
Yeah, you're right.
I haven't seen her all day.
I know she doesn't
wanna be a Rider now,
but I thought she still wanted
to see the Kinship Rite.
I guess she changed her mind.
[DAN] All right, Riders,
this is as far as I go.
When it comes to finding the
waterfall, you're on your own!
[HYORO] Wait, we have to get
through that cave alone?
[DAN]
Well, yeah.
The point of the
Waterfall of Trials
is you figure them
out as a group.
If it goes well,
the experience will strengthen
your bonds as friends.
I mean, if you can't maintain
Kinship with your friends,
you probably won't be someone
who has Kinship with a monster.
Ahh, I don't know about this.
We don't even have a map.
What if we get lost
in their forever?
[MILLE]
Don't be such a baby!
Plenty of other kids
have done this before!
[HYORO]
Hey.
There's nothin' to
worry about, buddy.
We got this in the bag!
Yeah, and Navirou's directions
will be a huge help.
Can you think of one time when
his directions have been right?
We'd have better luck
in there blindfolded.
Ya see?
Hey! Don't be mean to Navirou!
Just for that, Navirou
will find the Falls first
and prove once and for all
Navirou has the best
sense of direction!
Nerve of those guys.
Well, guess it's our turn!
I'll be waiting out
here the whole time.
So if anything happens,
I can run right in.
Deepening your Kinship
isn't only for Monsties.
The bonds you have with your
friends are just as important!
[LOLOA]
Hey.
If you're so worried they'll
get into trouble in that cave,
you should just go with them!
But I'm not going to
be a Rider anymore.
I'm not supposed to take
part in the Kinship Rite.
But Loloa was certain her big
sister was going to be a Rider.
[DAN yawning]
Now's my chance!
No, you can't go!
It's too dangerous!
Not true!
I brought a map of the
entire cave system with me.
I'll be fine. You can
go home, Loloa.
Wait, sis!
[HYORO yelps]
[MILLE] Jeez, Hyoro! Do you
have to make so much noise?
Sorry.
Really, there's no point in
being scared during the day.
It's night when
you should worry.
Don't you know this cave is
full of nocturnal monsters?
Drag your feet enough and
the sun will go down
while we're still in here.
Before you know it,
the whole cave will be full
of glowing eyes and
glistening, white fangs!
All right, let's go!
[MILLE]
Much better!
Nice job, Mille.
As expected.
[NAVIROU]
Mh-hm.
Not bad at all.
[KIDS gasp]
What're you doing here?
I thought you'd be
way ahead of us.
"Navirou has the best
sense of direction!"
Isn't that what you said?
But you forgot the part
where Navirou feels bad
and comes back to
keep you company.
You should thank him.
It sounds like it was
you who needed company.
So not true, Cheval!
Navirou is just
fine being alone!
Yeah, sure.
Hey, get back here!
You can't leave Navirou behind!
[LUTE]
Which way?
Navirou smells victory this way!
Well, c'mon!
Follow Navirou to glory!
[NAVIROU screams]
[LUTE laughs]
So where's all that glory
you were talkin' about?
If Navirou says we go left,
then we go right.
It doesn't seem smart
to pick so quickly.
Of course it's smart.
If we're wrong,
we just come back.
Second-guessing is the
real problem. Let's go!
That's enough, Mille. I'm done.
I don't belong out here.
I'm going home.
Besides, we all know I was never
gonna make it as a Rider.
You're being too
hard on yourself.
Hyoro, you've got what it takes
to be a Rider and then some.
You're the only one of us
who hatched a Bulldrome egg.
Hpmh.
If you wanna go home,
you should just go home.
You're obviously not going
to put forth the effort,
so why are you even here?
I mean, let's be honest:
You only started
doing any of this
because your brother
Genie made you, right?
Oh, yeah? Well,
what about your reason?
You're only here because
of your rivalry with Lilia!
You're so obsessed with her.
When she decided not to be
a Rider, you got depressed!
Oh, Mille.
How dare you say that to me!
You don't know anything!
Hey, wait!
Well, Hyoro.
Apologizing to her's
now your first trial.
I know, it's a hard one.
Who does that guy think he is?
Like I really care
what Lilia does.
That's right, pal. I've got
my own future to worry about!
[buzzing]
[gasps]
Bnahabra!
[LUTE]
Mille!
Get rid of your torch!
Bnahabra are attracted to light!
[MILLE]
Hyoro!
[LUTE]
Watch out!
Come on, come on.
You want this? Let's go!
Lute, wait!
[NAVIROU]
Great, he took the bait!
You know how to
capture him, right?
Nope!
What?!
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
Oh, man.
It's a smoke bomb.
Lute, get down!
[sighs]
Honestly.
Hey, Mille?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
said those awful things.
And I'm sorry for
throwing my torch at you.
I didn't mean to.
It's all right.
Here's your Kinship Stone.
I appreciate it.
Thanks, Hyoro.
It's nice to see that
under your hard exterior,
you have a soft side.
Hey! Shut up!
You had to get in the
last word, didn't you?!
What? But I--
It's a dead end.
Come on!
No! You can't give up now, guys.
There's a clue right
there in front of you!
You have to look up!
[gasps]
I did the right thing saving
them from that Bnahabra,
but this is a part that they
must pass on their own.
I'm not a Rider.
I can only watch.
The only thing I can think is
maybe we should've gone
the other way at that fork.
Hold on.
If you're blaming me for our
current situation, just do it!
No, I'm not trying
to blame you at all.
I don't think arguing is
helping us get anywhere, guys.
Flashbugs?
We don't go through
the wall, we go up it!
Nice, Cheval!
Amazing.
All right!
[CHEVAL] We're getting
closer to that waterfall!
Let's go!
[NAVIROU]
C'mon, everyone!
Navirou leads the way!
[NAVIROU yells]
[NAVIROU screams]
[NAVIROU]
Navirou meant to do that.
[KIDS sigh]
I'll climb it first.
What?
I'm good at rock climbing.
[HYORO]
Wow, Cheval really is good.
[MILLE]
He's so fast.
Ready?
We'll get to those
Falls in no time.
Ah, man! I hate this!
Just take it slow and
don't look down, guys.
That's right!
Navirou wants no complaining.
Take it slow and up you go!
I've just about had it with you.
So, uh, you think this is it?
This sure looks like the
Sacred Spring, all right.
I wanna be a Rider who
always helps those in trouble!
I want to be a Rider who
never runs from a challenge,
no matter how dangerous
that challenge may be.
My desire is to form a deep
Kinship with my Monstie.
I hope to become the
world's best Rider.
No, wait. I will be!
[ALL chuckle]
So pretty.
You did great, guys. Congrats.
[SIMONE]
Knock-knock.
Excuse me.
[SIMONE]
Fear not. We mean you no harm.
The Scriveners. What're you
doing all the way up here?
[LOLOA screams]
[LOLOA]
Help!
Loloa! Oh, no!
[LOLOA whimpering]
--[LILIA] Loloa!
--Save me!
I'm coming! Close your eyes now!
Lilia!
[LILIA]
Dan, you're here!
You two keep moving!
[LILIA]
Right!
[DAN]
And you all, this way!
Loloa!
Big Sis!
[LILIA]
An Iodrome!
Move!
[LOLOA]
I'm scared!
Now go!
Captain! I'll hold off
this monster for you!
[PAPPAN]
On second thought, run!
[SIMONE sighs]
Don't worry. I'll handle this.
[LILIA] She's beautiful.
Like a graceful bird.
Mistress Red Swan.
Well, are you all right?
Any injuries?
Thank you so much, Miss--
There's no need to thank me.
Here, drink this antidote.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Where am I?
[LUTE]
She's awake!
You're in the Chief's house.
You were brought here
after collapsing
at the Waterfall of Trials.
Are you okay?
Any aches or pains, dear?
[LILIA]
Uh, no.
Thank goodness.
For a while, you had
us pretty scared.
Your prompt treatment
worked, I see. Good.
In worst-case scenarios,
if no antidote is used,
the Iodrome's poison
can be quite deadly.
[LOLOA]
Loloa's so sorry!
You only got sprayed
because Loloa followed you
into the caves and was--
Don't apologize!
What?
If you hadn't gotten in
trouble with those monsters,
I wouldn't have gotten a chance
to meet Mistress Red Swan!
Are we sure she's okay?
I've heard Iodrome poison can
do some nasty stuff to you.
Navirou definitely knew that.
[LILIA] Guys, I'm fine!
Now where is Mistress Red Swan?
Huh? Red Swan?
You mean the lady who saved you?
[SIMONE]
I've never met anyone
who's exchanged Kinship
with a monster before.
Do you mind if I sketch you?
Uh, yeah! I'm in top form!
Lilia, I thought you
wanted to thank her.
I do, it's just--
What happened?
You were so excited.
Now that I see her
again, I'm nervous.
[NAVIROU] You miss 100% of
the shots you don't take.
And I'm taking this
lovely lady's heart
with my own two paws.
That's Navirou!
So what's with that cape?
What's he doing?
He looks ridiculous.
A warning.
Fall for Navirou and
you'll only get burned.
[SIMONE] Wow, I've never seen
a Felyne like this before.
Your facial symmetry
is practically divine!
And your tail, too.
Everything about you!
Unique from head to toe.
Marvelous!
So Navirou has stolen your
heart, just as he expected to.
Heh.
You may now pet.
Navirou always wins.
Whether it's on a quest,
or in the pursuit of romance.
I think he's only
getting weirder.
Yeah.
Rathalos, King of the Skies!
I've never actually seen
one in person before!
It's beautiful!
Careful, ma'am!
Ratha gets bitey around
people he doesn't know.
I'll be fine.
Hello, my name is Simone.
I'm captain of the
Royal Scriveners.
It's an honor to meet you.
Wow, Ratha is being good.
What's your secret, ma'am?
Oh, I didn't do
anything special.
I've merely expressed
my own feelings to it.
Expressed your feelings?
The joy, surprise, and thrill
that comes with meeting it here.
I look deep into its eyes with
those feelings in my heart.
And in turn, they get
through to its own heart.
Humans and monsters are both
living things, after all.
Sharing honest feelings can work
just like a common language.
Hard to believe it's
been 30 long years
since the last Chief Scrivener
graced our little village
with his presence.
This really takes me back.
Chief Omna, we're here looking
for environmental changes,
vegetation that's turning black,
monsters running amok
where they shouldn't be.
Have you seen
anything like that?
Yes, and I assume because
you've been sent to our village,
these changes pose
a grave danger to us.
We can't afford to sit
back and do nothing.
It could up-end the
balance of nature!
I'm talking about entire
species of monster
suddenly going extinct!
What do you think
they're talking about?
I dunno, but it
looks pretty heated.
Uh, Lilia?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, or not.
Hi. I'm fine.
Sorry, I spaced out.
Ah-ha. And what are
you Riders doing here?
You look like you're
feeling well, Lilia.
Yes! And, um--
She has something for
you, Miss Simone.
A thank you gift.
[LILIA]
It's an energy drink.
Making you one was the
best way I could think of
to say thank you.
Oh.
Did she say energy drink?
Look out!
Navirou will
protect you, Simone!
Wow. Not the usual kind
of energy drink I've seen.
Her recipe really gets ya goin'!
It's a pity I couldn't try it.
[yells]
Oh, Lilia dear,
will you be our guide
when Pappan and I investigate
the woods tomorrow?
Yeah! Of course I'll help you!
[LILIA] This area we're going
through now is Mosswine country.
You'll find lots of Blue
Mushrooms all over.
You really know
your surroundings.
I like reading about different
kinds of plants and monsters.
I find that having a
passion for something
is the strongest
force in the world.
There's one thing I
don't understand, though.
If most of the children in
your village become Riders,
why aren't you taking
that step, too?
Do you have a different dream?
Sorta. I guess.
It's okay.
You only need to focus
on being yourself, Lilia.
That's what counts.
Yes, ma'am!
[PAPPAN gasps]
Captain, look.
That matches Reverto's report.
[LILIA]
Madam Simone, this looks like--
[SIMONE]
No!
I need you to step back now!
That goes for you boys, too!
Right.
C'mon, Lilia.
Okay.
They're so cool!
I know, right?
And they're not the only ones.
The outside world is full
of people like this,
who do things we
can only dream of!
I'm glad you came
out here with us.
Thanks to your help,
our investigation
made good progress.
Simone, is it all right if
I ask you a personal question?
Of course!
What made you decide to join the
Scriveners in the first place?
I often ask myself
the same thing.
Indeed. There's no easy answer.
Believe me, I've traveled
the world trying to settle
on the right one.
In the meantime,
I'll keep filling my
fountain of knowledge.
That's the best part
of life on the road.
The paths our lives take open up
when we least expect them to.
All we can really do
then is hone our minds
and wait for the big moment!
Um, I think--
[PAPPAN] Captain Simone!
We're all set for departure!
Okay! I'll be right there!
Someday we'll met
again. I promise.
Yes, ma'am!
[ALL]
Bye, Captain Simone!
Oh, no. It's too late.
Lilia. What's wrong?
I know...
Now I know how to answer
her, but she's gone!
Hey, it'll be okay, Lilia.
In fact, there's still time!
If you wanna tell her, let's go!
How? She's already so far away.
Don't worry. Leave it to me!
[LILIA]
Captain Simone! Simone!
I did it! I found
the road to take.
The dream for my future life!
I wanna grow up to become just
like you, Simone!
I'll study hard. I'll travel
across the whole world!
And make sure my
fountain is always filled
to the brim with knowledge!
Great!
I'm so glad to hear it,
Lilia! Good luck!
I'm proud of you, Lilia.
Thanks to you both.
Lute and Ratha!
[roars]
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life.
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Iodrome!
This particular one is the alpha
of a poison-spitting
Ioprey pack!
You can tell he's in charge
due to the big red
crest on his head!
Remember when he spit on Lilia?
His poison had her
in real trouble!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, Lute here!
Hakum Village is holding a huge
festival for all the new Riders.
It's the most fun you can have
when you're not riding Ratha!
Next time:
"Off to the Monstie Races!"
Ride On!