[DAN] We've gone over
it every which way
and I think you all
finally grasp the basics
of the relationship between
a Rider and their Monstie.
All right then! Does anyone
have any questions?
I think we got it.
[LILIA]
I do!
Could you briefly
discuss the guidelines
regarding split-second decisions
one needs to consider
when riding a Monstie?
And provide some
real world examples?
Oh, well, great question.
Uhh...
Tell ya what, let's set
that aside for now.
Next up! We begin our
adventure training!
Now we're talking!
[GAMIGAMI]
You gotta be kiddin'!
This is an absolute disgrace!
He's right!
We've got a whopping
four apprentice Riders
this time around!
We have to!
A banner year, if I've seen one!
Hold on, gentlemen.
While it's true I have
been considering it,
to pull it off, we would
need the entire village
to help with the preparations.
We have to make a
strong appeal to them.
Appeal, nothing!
Of course, they'll help!
Get loud! Who's in top form?
[KIDS]
We're in top form!
One more time, with feeling!
Like you're being chased
by a wild Tigrex!
[KIDS]
We're in top form!
[DAN]
I don't believe you!
Embarrassing.
[KIDS]
We're in top form!
Repetition won't
hone their skills.
It's important to
learn the basics.
I can't believe we're
still doing the basics.
We're Riders after all.
[KIDS]
We're in top form!
Hey, Lute! Take this seriously!
I figured our training could use
a little real world application.
You don't even know the
fundamentals of "Ride On."
You're the furthest
behind out of the group.
Huh?
The furthest behind?
But we're all doing
the same drills.
Now, now, Genie, calm down.
I mean, Lute is kind
of a special case.
That's no excuse.
Going easy on him is the
worst thing we can do.
Special or not, he trains
the same as everyone else.
[NAVIROU]
Whoa! What's this?
Lute, treated like an
incompetent kid? How true.
Everyone knows he'd
be completely lost
without the guidance and
knowledge of the great Navirou.
You mean he'd be completely
lost with you guiding him.
Wait, I guess that means
he's hopeless no matter what.
[horn blaring]
[GAMIGAMI]
Listen up.
We're bringing back
the Monstie Race!
That's right.
As of this moment--
As of this moment,
we need all of you to do your
part to get ready for the race!
People making decorations!
An obstacle course!
And food stands!
We'll split into groups.
Who's with us?
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[CHIEF OMNA] Someone give
me something to do too!
[horn blares]
Attention, young Riders.
The Monstie Race has returned!
Okay. What exactly
is a Monstie Race?
[UNCLE HORNBLOWER]
An event for apprentice Riders.
What? The four of us?
You and your Monsties
will compete in a marathon.
Our first one in over ten years.
Speaking of first, I wonder
which one of you will win.
The race is in two days!
So, if you want to win,
you better get started
with your training!
Woohoo!
[horn blares]
One question. Who's that?
A villager?
That's Uncle Hornblower.
He never speaks. Only smiles.
I think he confused the two.
Wow, I've never heard
Uncle Hornblower
talk that much before.
Some people are just like that.
Whether it's a fight,
flood, or festival,
they thrive off it and
make it a big show.
Reminds me of you!
[HYORO]
Hey, Genie.
What kind of race is this?
I've never been in one.
But you get a chance,
so aim for the top, Hyoro.
[DAN]
Here's the rundown.
The Monstie Race features
apprentice Riders
atop their monsters.
Together you'll be
competing as a single unit,
navigating a course the
villagers have prepared for you.
Finally, the Rider who
comes in first place
is awarded a secret prize.
Does anyone have any questions?
What place were you in
when you raced, Dan?
[DAN]
Uhh...
Tell ya what, let's just
set that aside for now.
Ah! One more thing.
Each of you will be paired
with a senior Rider
to serve as your coach!
Hyoro gets Genie.
My brother, huh?
[DAN]
Mille and Nole.
[MILLE groans]
[DAN]
Cheval's with Stone.
And you're with me, Lute!
So training for the race
begins tomorrow.
Until then, you're dismissed!
[CHIEF OMNA]
This can be a straightaway.
The best method to
test who's fastest.
[GAMIGAMI] Let's put a trap over
here. A pit or climbing wall.
[DAN] We should accommodate
each Monsties' abilities.
We should make the finish
a straightaway to test speed.
What about what I think?!
[LUTE] Wow! They're
already setting things up!
The air is teeming
with excitement.
Then again, adults have nothing
better to amuse themselves with.
How sad.
[CHEVAL]
You too, Mom?
Seems like everyone
is helping out.
Just with the food.
I'll be selling snacks
during the race.
Please, please!
Tell me you're making your world
famous donuts for Navirou!
Well of course.
[NAVIROU]
Yeah!
The whole village is
looking forward to this.
And I've got my eye
on first prize!
I'm not about to lose either!
No way!
Just do your best, you two.
[BOTH]
Right!
[GENIE]
Here's the deal.
Bulldrome is heavy,
but build momentum
and it'll gain speed.
Be sure to watch out if
the course gets technical.
You can guide it left or
right to avoid anything
that'll slow you down.
'Kay.
Velocidrome is quick.
If you make good use
of its jump ability,
you'll be able to clear
any obstacle with ease.
Got it.
[NOLE] Aptonoeth is slow,
but it has decent stamina.
So if it maintains its pace,
I guess there's a possibility
you two could win the race.
Um, probably.
What do you mean, "probably"?
Could you be anymore hopeless?
I want special training
to make sure I win, okay?
Got it.
[laughs]
This race is in the bag.
Don't get over confident.
How can I not?
Ratha is a Rathalos!
When's he's flying,
we're unstoppable!
When he's flying?
Now, listen here, you've
gotta learn how to ride him
before you can fly.
Yeah! Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's show 'em what you've got!
[LUTE] Hey, hey! Whoa!
Focus! Focus! Um.
Okay, never mind on the
walking. Who needs it?
All right. Let's take
to the skies, Ratha!
[screaming]
[LUTE]
Not good.
[LUTE screams]
Yeowch!
Ow, ow, ow...
[DAN]
It could use a little work.
The point of the Monstie Race
is to demonstrate the Kinship
between Rider and monster.
A first place finish shows
your bond is strong.
If you wanna prove that
you're the real deal,
winning is how you do it.
C'mon, Ratha, I'm begging you!
We gotta win first place!
[BOTH]
Huh?
A pit in the middle
of the village?
[LUTE gasps]
[LUTE]
And a mud wall over there.
They aren't kidding around.
I wonder if Velocidrome will
jump when the time comes.
Can I get Ratha to
even fly for me?
Navirou's famished.
What a day. Been waiting long?
How about "not at all"?
What've you been up to anyway?
Rehearsal.
[CHEVAL]
Rehearsal?
Along with Lilia.
[LUTE]
For what?
You have to wait and
find out tomorrow.
Besides telling you would
break a sacred Navi-rule.
Time to dig in!
Even the vegetation
is changing.
Has evil really spread this far?
And the distribution of monsters
has changed significantly.
It's happening so fast, we'll
have to redraw the maps.
[roaring]
That's abnormal.
[REVERTO] There shouldn't
be any Diablos out this far.
[thudding]
Guess it's gone.
Man, these days I never
know what we'll find
waiting for us
around the corner.
[POPOLA]
Meow! Reverto!
Meowr dinner, it's burning up!
[REVERTO yelping]
[NAVIROU]
The big day is upon us at last
and you couldn't ask
for better weather!
The apprentice Rider's
Monstie Race has returned
after ten long years!
You may recognize this face!
Providing play-by-play is the
darling of Hakum Village,
trendsetter for today's youth,
master foodie reporter,
the great--
I'm Navirou's
co-commentator, Lilia!
In addition, joining us is a
panel of guest commentators.
But they don't matter, so none
of them get introductions.
[ALL yelp]
Unfair!
The village is wild
with excitement.
The race hasn't started
and people are shouting.
Now let's take a moment
to thank our sponsors!
Get your kabobs! Fresh
kabobs. Take your pick!
Mosswine or King Turkey!
Everything's hot!
Including me.
They could at least let me
sell somethin' frozen.
Well, if that's how
it's gonna be...
Kabobs! Fresh piping-hot
kabobs over here!
Would you care for a soufflé?
We also have donuts
if you prefer.
Drinks for sale!
Right over here!
All kinds of drinks!
Lilia!
Before Navirou spoils the race
with his spot-on prediction,
give us your error-laden guess!
Well, Monstie-wise,
Velocidrome is fearless
and well-suited for
this type of playing field.
But the real question is whether
Cheval shares that mentality
as a Rider.
Manners win you friends,
but this is a competition, baby!
If you're in it to win it, you
gotta show some guts!
If Ratha flies, they'll be
the team to watch out for.
But let's be honest,
everyone knows Lute won't
get him in the air.
He'll probably end up
digging his own grave
is more like it.
Now what do our guest
commentators think?
Top three finishers!
Cheval, Hyoro, then Mille.
Hyoro, then Cheval and Mille.
Mille in first, Cheval, Hyoro.
And Lute is nowhere
to be found, as expected!
[VILLAGER A]
C'mon! You can do it!
I think everyone's more excited
about this than we are.
It's a really big deal for them.
That's right! And I'm gonna win!
Ha-ha. I think I have to pee.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Uh, ahem!
Attention!
The apprentice Rider's Monstie
Race will begin momentarily!
The winner of this race will
receive a spectacular prize.
It's gonna be mine!
In your dreams!
t the sound of the sonic bomb--
[UNCLE HORNBLOWER]
Enough talking! Ready, set, go!
[horn blares]
The race just started!
But we don't even
have our Monsties.
You have to run to the stables.
That's the first
leg of the course.
[KIDS]
What?!
We have to outrun each other
before the race even starts?
Will someone please
let me do something?!
Now for an overview
of the course
our Riders will face today.
First, our competitors will
race through the village.
Will they be able
to make it past
the elaborate obstacles
we've left waiting for them?
[screams]
[whines]
Don't give up,
Cheval! Hang in there!
[VILLAGER A]
Could I get three soufflés?
Three soufflés?
Sure, thing! Coming right up.
[LUTE yells]
What do we have here?
Lute has taken the lead
to everyone's shock!
Looks like he's headed straight
for the Monstie stable
where the real race can begin!
Time to Ride On!
C'mon, Ratha! Let's get moving!
[NAVIROU]
Oh, no!
Lute can only watch as
his lead rapidly vanishes
and the other racers
close the gap!
Let's Ride On!
Go, Bulldrome!
Ready? Ride On!
Aptonoeth!
Ride On!
Velocidrome!
Let's go!
And Cheval has taken the lead!
Hyoro in second,
followed by Mille.
It's anyone's race
at this point!
Except for Lute, who's
still stuck in the stable!
We're gonna wind up dead last!
Come on! Work with me,
Ratha! What's the deal?
Run, Ratha!
[LUTE] Oh, no! Wait up!
Slow down, Ratha!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU]
All Riders are out of the stable
and onto the second leg of
the race towards Mt. Dacapo,
known for its beautiful autumn
colors and exotic mushrooms
that grow near its peak,
and nowhere else!
Whoever finds one and brings it
back first will be the winner!
Smells like a matsutake,
tastes like a shimeji!
Like an Exciteshroom
too dangerous to eat!
Cooking tip! Exciteshrooms
make for great ingredients.
[VILLAGER B]
One Mosswine kabob, please!
[VILLAGER C]
Three for me!
Agh! I can't take this heat!
And I'm running out of layers!
Get your kabobs, right here!
Boiling hot, sweltering kabobs!
[CHEVAL]
Huh?
C'mon, Velocidrome!
[LUTE]
Wait for me!
[MILLE]
He's catching up!
Come on, Aptonoeth!
Run that way!
Over here!
[GENIE]
This way!
[MILLE yells]
Well, seems it's going with
the Monstie's strengths.
Good.
Navirou, former food critic
and world traveler,
proudly presents:
The Grand Foodie Stroll
and Sampler Tour.
Stay close and watch
a master palate at work!
Here we have
Lala's kabob booth.
One King Turkey to go.
Thank you!
Well? Pretty tasty, huh?
Meh. I can't complain.
Huh?
Are you gonna pay for that?!
[NAVIROU]
You're welcome!
Next up, we have
this beverage stand!
Don't mind if I do! Ha-ha!
You're not supposed to
drink it that fast!
[screams]
It's my latest creation!
One-part Hot Drink, one-part
Cold Drink. Whaddaya think?
Silly girl! You should
never mix your drinks!
[CHEVAL]
No mushrooms. Where are they?
None over here either.
Let's check higher up.
Close to the peak.
Find anything, Aptonoeth?
Huh?
[MILLE gasps]
We did actually did it!
Let's head back
and win this race!
[gasps]
Hey!
I guess you caught up.
Looks like none of us have
found those rare mushrooms yet.
It just seems really strange.
You'd think we'd find
at least one of them.
Hey, you guys, do you smell
something kinda weird?
[LUTE]
Whoa! Over there!
A ton of unique mushrooms!
Oh, and that thing.
[HYORO]
What the--? It's a monster!
[LUTE]
Hold up!
You gotta quit eating
all these mushrooms.
We need 'em!
[screams]
[BOTH coughing]
[CHEVAL]
That must be a Congalala!
[HYORO] I've never seen
one of those before!
[LUTE] It reeks! My nose
will never work the same!
There's no way we can leave
this thing near the village.
It's a walking health hazard!
Forget about the race,
we gotta drive this thing off!
What?
But how?
[roars]
[LUTE]
Here it comes!
Hyoro!
Split up!
Hyoro?
That Congalala has
nothing to do with me.
[LUTE]
Hey! Hyoro!
That guy.
[CHEVAL]
Velocidrome!
[LUTE]
Why, you!
Don't, Lute! It's too risky!
[LUTE screams]
[CHEVAL]
Lute!
Jump attack!
Lute! Speak to me! Are you okay?
[LUTE groans]
[LUTE]
What about the mushrooms?
Yeah. There's still some left.
[LUTE] Then take one
and go ahead without me.
No way!
Don't worry. I'll be okay.
Plus, the race is
still going on!
Go show 'em the Kinship you
have with your Monstie!
I understand. I'll send help.
I'm not goin' anywhere.
Hey, Ratha. How ya feelin'?
[LUTE coughs]
It's just Deodorant.
Should cure most of the stench.
Wow, you're right!
I never expected a
Congalala to show up.
Sorry I didn't get here sooner.
But you boys handled
yourselves well.
Uh. Um, thanks.
It's too bad about
the race though.
I'm gonna head back down.
[LUTE]
Listen, Ratha.
I haven't given up
on this race yet.
There's still a
chance we can win.
You're a Rathalos, the one they
call the King of the Skies.
I'm asking you to fly for me.
[RATHA roars]
[LUTE]
What is it?
Hey! Wait up for me!
[LUTE screaming]
[horn blaring]
[gasps]
[NAVIROU] Three outta four
contestants are in sight!
In first is Mille!
Followed by Hyoro!
No! Wait! Hyoro has
taken the lead!
Cheval is closing
in from behind!
And Lute is nowhere to be seen!
No! Wait. Look up in
the sky! There he is!
Lute and Ratha are flying
right in! Unbelievable!
I wouldn't call that flying.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say they were falling!
[LUTE screaming]
Pull his head up to steer him!
[LALA]
Kabobs! Kabobs here.
[LALA, LUTE screaming]
[NAVIROU]
Right on the nose!
Where's the finish?
[LALA] You'll want to hurry
and go that way.
C'mon let's go, Ratha!
Velocidrome?
Oh, that's right!
The Congalala wore you out.
[NAVIROU] Velocidrome
has had a malfunction!
It's down to two teams
vying for the top spot!
You can do this, Ratha!
Come on, Bulldrome!
[NAVIROU] Looks like Bulldrome
has finally run outta juice!
And team Lute and Ratha
are the first racers
to cross the finish line!
No one coulda predicted
that! What a race!
The comeback story
of the century!
I knew the kid had it in him.
I knew before you.
So did Navirou! Honestly!
Yeah. Yeah.
[HYORO]
Second place.
Genie!
You should be ashamed running
away from Lute and Cheval.
Riders treasure all
forms of Kinship.
That goes for both Monsties
as well their friends.
Think about what you've done.
Genie. I thought you wanted...
You were just trying to win
the race for your brother.
It's all right. You didn't do
anything wrong, Hyoro.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Congratulations, Lute!
You're the winner of the Race!
All right! So what do I get?
Ahem! Gamigami.
Bring forth the prize!
I'd love to,
but you were in charge of
preparing the award, Chief.
Well, you were the one that
kept asking for something to do.
Don't tell me...
There's no prize?
You get the honor
of being chief for a day!
I don't wanna!
Chief for a day?
You've gotta be kidding me!
You saw a Congalala?
On Mt. Dacapo?
That's right.
[DAN]
But why?
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual .
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life.
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Congalala!
This monster's got a
bottomless pit for a stomach!
Mushrooms happen to
be its favorite food
and its Breath Attack changes
depending on the type it eats.
Navirou doesn't stand a chance
against its powerful farts!
Keep your distance!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, Lute here!
Cheval's itching to get his
hands on a rare you know what!
You guessed it!
A great glorious glittering
golden egg, obviously!
Next time:
"Quest for the Golden Egg."
Ride On!