[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming the
world's top Monster Rider.
Due to the effects
of the Black Blight,
a Nargacuga running amok
has left Lute's once-peaceful
hometown of Hakum Village
in terrible shape.
Still, these brave
young Riders push on,
pursuing the crazed
Nargacuga without any fear.
[yells]
And without any
grown-ups knowing!
[LUTE]
The Nargacuga!
[roars]
'Kay, Cheval, I'm gonna
draw its attention.
You've got this!
After all, Navirou will be with
you every step of the way!
[LUTE] Good, 'cause I'm counting
on you to have my back!
[NAVIROU]
Sure thing, Lute!
Navirou stays still as a stone.
And that is a Navi-rule.
Now Ride On!
Rathian!
[BOTH]
Ride On!
--Bulldrome!
--Aptonoth!
Let's go, Rathi!
[RATHI roars]
[MILLE]
Don't let it get away!
Come on!
It disappeared!
[NAVIROU]
Where'd that Nargacuga go?
'Kay, here we go.
Hey, guys, cover your ears!
I found you!
Rathi, now!
Ram it!
Okay!
How do you like this?
[gasps]
What the--?
If only our Monsties
were fully healed!
I'm sorry, Dan,
I understand how you feel,
but right now, our best option
is to wait for the Hunter.
Yeah, I know that.
I really do, but still...
[CHIEF OMNA] With a Nargacuga
driven mad by the Black Blight,
I'm afraid we have no other
choice but to put it down.
Sadly, he's right.
A Blighted monster will never
again return to the way it was.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Hmm.
This situation calls for more
than just sitting around
waiting for that Hunter.
Although, what is
there for us to do?
Huh, I guess we really aren't
spring chickens anymore.
Dan.
[DAN]
Yes?
It would appear that the
apprentice Riders' Monsties
are nowhere to
be seen right now.
[DAN]
No, that can't be.
Don't tell me--!
Poor Ratha. He's in
pretty rough shape.
[LUTE]
Take care of him.
I'm trusting you.
Look after Ratha while I'm gone.
I won't let you down!
You're gonna be in top
form really soon, Ratha.
Uh, are you all right?
That's probably what
Lute would say to him.
You really do know everything.
Nah, Lute's just
that predictable.
[DAN]
So then tell me,
where is that predictable
little chucklehead right now?
[LILIA]
Um, well, you see, he's, uh...
[CHIEF OMNA]
He's left again, hasn't he?
Gone off to look
for the Nargacuga?
And he took Hyoro, Mille,
and Cheval with him, too, right?
Honestly, and this time, their
lives are in serious danger.
Something isn't right.
[roars]
[CHEVAL]
But still.
Hyah!
What?
It vanished again!
Aptonoth, where is it?
[MILLE]
Over there?
But it's not.
[thud]
[HYORO yelps]
Hyoro!
They're spikes!
It's shooting spikes at us!
Yeah, but from where?
I still can't see it!
I don't know.
Okay. This calls for
some Navirou action!
[screams]
Navirou sees it!
The tail, the tail!
Nice job!
All right, watch out
for the spikes
when you see its tail, guys!
I got it!
Ugh!
Quit hiding and just
show yourself already!
We may not be able
to see anything,
but I know that you're
watching all of us!
[MILLE]
There!
[roars]
Just gotta make out its shape.
Use your breath, Rathi!
Incredible.
Those guys are so in sync.
Well, of course, they're
inseparable. So it makes sense.
Now show us what
you've got, Aptonoth.
You're good to keep
going, right, Bulldrome?
Rathi!
Mille, behind you!
[MILLE gasps]
[HYORO]
Mille!
Oh, no! C'mon, Rathi!
[yelps]
[CHEVAL]
Rathi, what's wrong?
Rathi!
[LUTE]
Over here!
[NAVIROU yells]
[BOTH] Hey, you, over
here! Nyah, nyah, nyah!
[BOTH scream]
You ready?
Oh, yeah!
Come on! This way!
Your "this way" can wait!
I guess we're just
not strong enough.
No! We have to do something!
No matter what,
I will defeat it.
Right here, by my own hand!
Rathi, lend me your strength.
[roars]
That's it! Over here!
Lute, no.
'Kay, Cheval, I'm gonna
draw its attention.
Lute!
[chuckles]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Cheval!
[roars]
[LUTE]
Whoa!
[gasps]
If I fall, I'm a goner!
[HYORO]
We're still here!
[LUTE]
Mille!
Are you guys all right?
Don't worry about us!
Okay, one more!
Amazing.
The Kinship between
Cheval and Rathi...
I can't believe
she just hatched!
Oh, yeah! Way to go, Cheval!
I know you can stop it!
[CHEVAL yelling]
That did it!
You did great, Rathi!
We got it--
Even that wasn't enough?
Cheval.
[LUTE]
Darn it!
There's nothing left!
[CHEVAL] I-I'm going
to defeat this thing.
I have no choice
but to defeat it!
[CHEVAL]
Lute?
Come at me!
I'm gonna take the hit!
[ALL gasp]
[LUTE]
Ratha!
Wow, you came for me!
Whoa!
Ratha gave Lute a Ride On
without even being asked!
Thanks, Ratha!
'Kay, let's do this, Ratha!
Man, Lute really is incredible.
[NAVIROU]
That he is.
'Course, so are you.
Like Lute said, you're really,
really tremendous.
He must've been pretty serious
with the two "really"s and all!
And plus, Navirou here was
on his back when he said it,
so you know it's true!
C'mon, Lute.
[roars]
Let's end this! Ratha!
Go! Sky-High Dive!
[laughs]
You see that?
The awesome power of
the Sky-High Dive,
a Kinship Attack
named by yours truly!
Gotta love that name. For sure.
[CHEVAL gasps]
Where did he go?
Say what?
[BOTH gasp]
[CHEVAL]
Lute!
[LUTE] Ratha, what's wrong?
C'mon, pull up!
Ratha?
Hang in there! Ratha!
Ratha! Ratha--
[LUTE]
Ratha!
But why would--?
[CHEVAL]
Lute!
[LUTE]
Ratha! Ratha!
[NAVIROU]
Hey, guys!
Check it out!
[HYORO] The dark miasma,
it's disappearing!
Looks like the Kinship Stones
sucked out all of the Blight.
And that's not all.
Look over there.
Uh, Lute? Cheval?
[ALL gasp]
[LUTE]
Uh?
[NAVIROU]
Ahh!
[DAN]
Hey!
[ALL gasp]
[LUTE]
It's Dan!
What you did was
incredibly reckless, kids!
Hi, guys!
Lilia!
[NAVIROU]
And the chief, too!
Chief Omna, sir, you see
the thing is, sir, that, uh--
You can explain later.
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
[CHIEF OMNA]
So it really was that.
That was what, Chief Omna?
[CHIEF OMNA]
The Kinship Ore.
Kinship...
...Ore? What do you mean?
[NAVIROU]
Oh, yeah! That's what it is!
Navirou remembers
now! Kinship Ore!
That's why he said it
looked familiar before!
[CHIEF OMNA] The Black Blight
has existed in this world
from time immemorial
as something that comes
and goes like the wind.
[HYORO]
Like the wind.
[CHIEF OMNA] But somehow, this
time, it wasn't going anywhere.
And now it's clear
that's because
it got to the Kinship Ore.
So the Ore was infected?
That's correct.
The same Black Blight that our
Rider ancestor once confronted.
[gasps]
[CHIEF OMNA]
It tells of an age
when the Earth was
engulfed in darkness
and of one particular
Rider who appeared
and managed to save
the entire world.
[LUTE] And this Rider
you're talking about?
[CHIEF OMNA]
Redan.
Redan!
But wait, if this is the
same as it was with Redan,
the world will--
The world will what?
What will happen to the world?
It may again be engulfed in
darkness, just as it once was.
[MILLE]
You mean...?
[CHIEF OMNA]
That's right.
I'm afraid that what
happened to our village
may happen all across the world.
[ALL gasp]
[HYORO grunts]
Hey, what are you
hitting me for?
'Cause this thing is just
way too big to cope with!
[HYORO gasps]
But, Chief Omna, how will
this lead to the world
winding up in total darkness?
Well, given what we've
seen here already,
it wouldn't be a
surprising outcome
if all of the world's Kinship
Ore were infected
with the Black Blight.
That means Kinship Ore is
found all around the world?
[CHIEF OMNA]
We must investigate
and find out whether these
Ore have been affected.
And if they have been
tainted in some manner,
well then, we'll just have
to do something about it.
We are Riders, after all,
which means we have
the power to purify.
Whoa, as Riders,
we can do that?
The Kinship Ore all
around the world...
[CHIEF OMNA]
I have a strong feeling.
If something evil is indeed
attempting to swallow
this world up,
it may be due to the evil that
lies in humankind's hearts,
the wrath of heaven
and Earth combined.
As Dan said earlier,
you children behaved quite
recklessly coming out here.
However, what you have
valiantly confronted
was not just a
Blighted Nargacuga.
It was in fact the
Black Blight itself.
The Black Blight itself?
What does that mean?
[CHIEF OMNA]
Don't you see?
You youngsters saved more
than just Hakum Village.
You also rescued the monsters,
including this Nargacuga.
In fact, you've saved
all living things.
Which is unquestionably
something a Rider would do.
So chin up now, Lute.
[LUTE gasps]
Oh, yeah. I guess that's right!
We saved everyone.
The four of us!
Ratha...
Yep, yep, yep! The four of us!
Uh? Uhh...
One, two, three, four.
Hey, Lute! Include Navirou
in your count, too!
Navirou helped a lot!
[DAN]
All right,
now let's all head back to
the village in top form!
[KIDS]
Yes, sir!
[LILIA]
Hm?
Hey, c'mon, Lilia!
Uh, but they're--
Just c'mon.
Can we go back after all this?
Well, I for one am planning
to run back there. Ha!
You've got spirit, Lute.
So do you, Cheval!
Uh, Lute?
It makes sense, 'cause
we're always together.
And because you
and I are family!
[CHEVAL]
Lute.
You don't have to say
that, not ever, Lute.
Because that goes
without saying!
[LUTE]
Yeah!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Aptonoth!
These gentle herbivores
raise their young in herds,
so they're twice as
cautious as any human.
Did you notice how
Mille's Aptonoth
was the first to pick up
on that Nargacuga?
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
It's finally time for us
to leave Hakum Village
and venture into
the outside world.
I'm super excited to
see what's out there!
Okay, everybody, we're off!
Next time: "The Journey Begins"!
Ride On!