[NARRATOR]
These young folks are Riders,
who form Kinship with Monsties.
A Blighted Diablos has
attacked Albrachs Village,
home of their Hunter
friend, Reverto.
Now they've come to see the
devastation with their own eyes.
This is just terrible.
Mister.
Where is it?
Where's the Diablos?
What about the people?
I heard the Hunter's Guild
took them all in as refugees.
Good, they're safe.
Yeah, I hope, but...
So this is the Black Blight.
[NARRATOR]
Will they ever be able to stop
this rampaging beast?
All right, let's go find it.
Yeah!
I'll look for tracks!
Better if we split up.
Right!
Mister?
Go with him, boys.
He's got that ol'
Hunter's intuition.
[NAVIROU] Like Navirou's
sense of direction.
[REVERTO]
Hey, Lute!
We'll start up there!
This tree was practically
the source of all life here.
[REVERTO] For centuries, the
people of Alrbachs Village
drew vitality from this tree,
and flourished in its shade.
But now it's dead and dry.
Just like the village around it.
Hey, mister, is it true?
There's a glowing
stone here, right?
Yeah, that's right. There's
one in the forest up ahead.
How'd you know that, Lute?
Chief Nolma told us about it.
There's a light!
Despite everything,
the stone is still glowing,
but the question is, how bright?
I saw it first!
Kinship Ore!
So they really do have one.
So "Kinship Ore"'s
what Riders call it?
[HAYORO]
Mh-hm.
It's full of black splotches.
It's not the same as
the last time I saw it.
Did it used to
glow more brightly?
It was so bright,
it'd hurt your eyes.
It's clouding over like the
other Kinship Ore we saw.
[MILLE, HYORO]
Yeah.
Reverto?
Oh, Chief Nolma!
[CHIEF NOLMA]
It's good to have you back.
This is--
[LUTE]
Uh.
We met the children
at the camp in Oasum.
I know they're just kids,
but these are great Riders, sir.
Navirou is a great Navirou!
Indeed. We saw their skills
on display in the desert.
We have no quarrel
with the Rider's actions.
But the fact is, monsters
are the bounty of the land,
not to be used as tools.
We're not just using them!
Navirou will have you know
that they form Kinship!
How dare you
disrespect his pupils.
We're nothing like
those weirdoes
and their mechanized Barroth,
so just back off, all right?
They're good kids, Chief,
and they're Riders we can trust.
Reverto, I wish I could
trust you blindly on this,
but I need to know why you're
so willing to back them up.
I've seen them in action.
That's the reason.
It seems like such a leap.
These are Riders, huh.
Give 'em a chance, all right?
I guarantee these kids
will earn your trust.
[rumbling]
[LUTE]
What the--?
[HYORO screams]
Here it comes! Scatter!
[NAVIROU screams]
[NAVIROU
Lute! Run.
[BOTH scream]
[roars]
The Diablos is back!
It's got some real blood-lust!
[DAN]
Heads up down there!
Let's draw it away!
Follow me!
Why are you trembling?
I'm just excited to fight.
That's good. Then let's go.
Hold on, Genie. Before you go,
there's something I need to say!
Oh, yeah?
I'm a full Rider now,
same as you are!
I'm not just some burden!
Cheval knows. He respects me.
Blighted monsters
have to be defeated!
You're a Rider.
Don't forget that, Mille.
Yeah! Of course
we're still Riders!
It's not like I'm running
off to join the Scriveners.
But we are slaying that monster!
That's what a
Hunter would say.
All right, let's Ride On!
Rathian!
Ride On!
Bulldrome!
Aptonoth!
Careful, pal.
Now, Ride On!
Rathalos!
Ratha, you have no idea
how much I missed you!
Now let's stop the Blight
and bring this village back!
[RATHA roars]
It's strong.
[STONE]
I'm going in!
Uh!
Cheval?
[CHEVAL yells]
[roars]
Now it's my turn.
We're coming, Cheval!
No, wait!
You're being too reckless!
[BOTH yell]
Hyoro! Mille!
Guys, get up!
[BOTH]
Genie!
[gasps]
It's coming!
My leg!
That's enough!
[LUTE]
Great work, Ratha!
Don't let it get away!
All right, Ratha!
Kinship Attack--
Scorching Slice!
He did it!
Oh, wow!
[DAN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Run!
Ratha, Sky-High Dive now!
[gasps]
Yes!
Now that's top form! Nice, Lute!
Navirou's top pupil's done
it again! Yeah, Lute!
[BOTH gasp]
That's nice work, Little Rider.
What? "Little"?
[laughs]
Well, let's go purify
that Kinship Ore!
Once they use Kinship Stones
to bring back the
Ore's true light,
this whole mess
will be behind us.
Oh, my.
It's finally glowing
bright again!
All this is the Riders?
That's right, or rather,
the purifying power
of the Kinship Stones
each Rider carries.
We did it, Cheval!
Cheval?
[REVERTO]
You really hate them, don't you?
That's right.
I wont allow it.
I'll destroy any monster
infected with the Black Blight.
All of them!
Poor kid. The only thing
in him now is hatred.
This is what his grief over
his mother has turned into.
[CHIEF NOLMA]
Now I understand.
I've seen your power.
This purification
was only possible
because your hearts can form a
genuine Kinship with monsters.
I thank you. All of Albrachs
Village thanks you.
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[BOTH yelp]
Ratha, how's your eye feeling?
I missed you.
Thanks for comin' back.
[DAN]
There you are, Lute.
[LUTE]
What's up, Dan?
We're gonna head back
to Hakum Village, now.
Would you like to come with us?
I think I'll stay out here
and keep purifying Kinship Ore.
Me and Ratha.
Okay. So then, it's
goodbye for now, Lute.
Don't do anything too dangerous.
I won't.
I worry about the
changes in Cheval.
You grew up together,
closer than brothers.
Keep an eye on him.
Right.
I guess my brother's
thrown in with Cheval, too.
It's hard, but I won't stop
him from making that choice.
I just hope they remember.
We walk apart, but we
come from the same place.
We're all Riders.
Yeah!
Yeah, take care of your friends.
Huh? Wait, that's all?
--That's right.
--What?
You never pass up the chance
to give crazy old-man advice!
[DAN laughs]
Gotta point!
This is how Gamigami
says he likes you.
You fool!
What makes you think I don't
have a problem with this boy?!
He's an arrogant greenhorn!
Though, he did stop the Diablos.
Bye, guys!
Tell everyone to have
donuts ready for Navirou
when he finally comes home!
Those are some
good senior Riders.
Oh, yeah!
So, Hyoro, are you okay not
saying goodbye to your brother?
Yeah.
You good, Cheval?
[CHEVAL]
I'm good.
[MILLE]
Same.
[CHEVAL]
Then we should go, too.
Hey! Over here!
We figured it out!
It's Lilia?
[LUTE]
What?
Hold on, you discovered where
there's another Kinship Ore?
[LILIA]
Mm.
With the help of Captain
Simone, of course.
So where is it?
Dovan Volcano.
And where is that?
Way over there.
Reverto, you been there?
Yeah.
Great!
Then let's go see if that
Ore's turning black, too!
Even if it is bad news,
Navirou will have his
number one pupil purify it
before it causes any trouble.
Captain Simone says
there's no doubt.
We must purify the Kinship Ore.
They're the source
of the Black Blight
and the only way
to stop its spread.
The Scriviner sure are
on top of this one.
Cheval, this is just
the beginning, I promise!
I'm gonna track down every
last Kinship Ore out there.
Glad to hear it.
But still, I'll keep
finding Blighted monsters
and destroy them.
Even as we speak,
they could be rampaging
through another
peaceful village.
[LILIA] Cheval, you're
not going with Lute?
I'll leave the
purification to him.
It's hard for me to be
around Lute right now.
[LUTE gasps]
[yelps]
[LUTE]
Cheval...
Cheval, listen. And you.
A while back, my mom told
me something important.
She said that 12 years ago,
the village that Lute was
born in was attacked
by a Blighted monster.
What? She told you
something about my village?
[LILIA]
Mhm.
Your old village was right
next to Hakum Village,
so when the Blighted
monster attacked,
we sent many Riders
over to help.
One of those Riders
was Cheval's father.
My father?
During that awful night,
your father and Lute's
became close friends.
They sealed their bond...
...with a firm and
mighty handshake.
From then on,
they worked as a team
to stop the Blighted monster
and protect their villages.
Our dads did that?
And I'd be willing to bet...
...that this is
exactly what they did.
[LILIA]
A Kinship handshake.
A Kinship handshake?
[LILIA] The Kinship between you
started 12 long years ago.
it was formed by your
fathers and their actions.
A bond that's firm and forever.
[NAVIROU]
Mm!
You see then?
You guys can't fight
and go your own way.
It's written in the stars
that you two join together
and face the Black Blight!
Yeah. Cheval, let's
keep this bond going.
So that's what happened...
My dad... was
protecting you, Lute.
He was protecting you.
And then he died.
But, uh, Cheval, Lute's mom
and dad are both gone too.
[CHEVAL]
I know that!
I know that we're
the same, Lute.
Our families are gone;
no home to return to.
So why...? Why does your hand
feel like a stranger's in mine?
[CHEVAL] Why don't I feel
any of the weight of Kinship?
Cheval, no.
Don't do this.
I... can't be your
friend anymore.
This is it. This is where
we go our separate ways.
It's all we can do,
because we'll never be
able to stop the Blight
doing things your way, Lute.
I'm stopping the Blight my way,
the only way I know how.
Sorry, Lute, but I'm
going with Cheval.
So am I.
And then there were four.
Cheval, Hyoro, Mille... gone.
I wouldn't have
brought up that story
if I'd known this would happen.
Don't beat yourself up, Lilia.
He was probably already
looking for an excuse to leave.
How are you holding up?
[LUTE] I want... I want
to be with Cheval.
There, there.
You'll meet up again!
After all, you still
want the same thing:
To stop the spread
of the Black Blight!
Mm! Navirou is wise!
[LUTE]
How could he leave?
I thought we were...
I thought we were family.
C'mon. Eat up.
These provisions are from
Chief Nolma and Fahali.
They're very gratful
to all of the Riders.
They'll never forget it.
I know!
He's got his own way
to stop the Blight.
[LUTE] I don't like it, but I
won't stand in his way.
Because...
One day, this'll be over
and things'll go back
to how they were.
I feel the same way!
Yeah!
[NAVIROU]
Oh, yeah. It'll happen.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, that's my Well-Done Steak!
Ratha, there may not've
been a Kinship Rite
that made me and
Cheval best friends.
But it still felt like
something bigger bound us.
That feeling, that's why
you remembered me, right?
Why you're back?
He'll understand one day.
The Kinship we share
can never be broken.
[DR. MANELGER,
ITSY-BITS yelling]
Hello! Your name is
Cheval, correct?
Behold, Dr. Manelger!
And his assistant, Itsy-Bits!
[DR. MANELGER]
We hereby extend an invitation
for you to work with us!
That's a little sudden,
don'tcha think?
Once in my company,
I guarantee you'll
become even stronger.
Stopping the Blight
will be easy.
Let's go, Cheval. These
guys give me the creeps.
No thanks.
We'll be doing things
our way from now on.
[DR. MANELGER]
You're passing up the best
and only chance you'll
get to stop the Blight.
Join with me, boy,
and save the whole world!
The world!
This is all so important,
he said it twice!
And I'll tell you
this a second time--
we have our way of doing this,
and it doesn't include you.
[DR. MANELGER] Hmm.
An unfortunate decision.
[CHEVAL] The Black Blight will
be stopped... by my hand.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Diablos!
The tyrant of the desert is
known for its raw power.
Diablos burrow through
the sand to sneak up
and attack prey
with two huge horns!
It's terrifying!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys, Lute here!
Sounds like Debli's
old teacher Nedan
knows quite a bit
about the Redan legend.
I wonder if he's got any
clues that might help us. Hmm.
Next time: "The
Mysterious White Dragon."
Ride On!