[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash, but enthusiastic fellow
who dreams of becoming
the world's top Monster Rider.
Lute and his friends,
Cheval, Mille, and Hyoro,
spend their days training
in the isolated Hakum Village.
Lute has a Monstie
named Rathalos,
with whom he's formed Kinship,
but the pair still
have a ways to go
before they're on the same page.
Will Lute ever make it
as a full-fledged Rider?
Hyoro, pick up the pace!
[HYORO]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR]
Genie is Hyoro's big brother,
and already a talented Rider.
You're too slow! Come on!
[NARRATOR]
Hyoro is still a junior Rider,
struggling to meet his
brother's high expectations.
Hyoro's nice,
but he might be the most
timid person Navirou knows.
It's 'cause his big bro's
always on his case.
[BOTH gasp]
[GENIE]
What're you doing, Hyoro?
You keep signaling late.
This is exactly what
I'm warning you about
when I tell you to do it
quickly and clearly.
Come on, Genie, I barely
bumped into the obstacle.
No excuse!
What if you got caught in
a Monster's hot breath?
You'd get more than
just a scratch.
[HYORO]
You're right, Genie.
[LUTE yells]
[LUTE]
Onward, Ratha!
[LUTE] Hey, wait!
Slow down. Ratha, listen!
--Right! Right! Right! Right!
--Left! Left! Left! Left! Left!
[LUTE, NAVIROU scream]
Lute, no!
Are you guys both
still in one piece?
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
We're fine, Stone.
It's all your fault
I'm soaking wet.
It's all your fault for
messing up the directions.
No way, it's your
fault, Navirou!
Navirou will never
take the blame!
But it's your fault!
It's all your fault!
Your fault!
Admit it, it's your fault!
No, you admit it!
[LUTE] I'll pull those
whiskers off your face!
You wouldn't dare!
The whiskers are Navirou's
handsomest feature!
[RATHA growls]
[BOTH yelp]
[CHEVAL, HYORO]
Oh no!
Are you okay?
Oh. Ratha's breath
got me all dry.
Navirou's whiskers are set.
[RATHA roars]
Nice work, Ratha!
[LUTE, NAVIROU laugh]
[NAVIROU]
Wanna give it a try, Cheval?
[CHEVAL]
Uh, maybe next time.
Hyoro.
A Rider and his Monstie
can't be friends.
Do you understand?
[HYORO]
Huh?
'Kay, Big Brother.
[DAN]
All right now, listen up.
There are certain rules
that every Rider must obey.
The most important one being
that we live our lives
here in Hakum Village,
so our existence is never
revealed to normal society.
Okay, but why is it so
bad if they know us?
Well, Cheval.
Many people not from around
here find it strange,
or even scary, that
an experienced Rider
is able to emotionally
bond with a monster
and form Kinship with it.
You don't have
permission to eat that.
[DAN clears throat]
[grumbles]
Monsters are nature.
Since we live in harmony with
nature, the same goes for them.
I guess when you put it
that way it makes sense.
[DAN]
Our windmills for example.
Those big vanes only turn thanks
to the power of the Hakum Gale,
the wind that blows
down the mountain.
Just as a windmill uses the
wind, Riders use monsters.
The moral here is that if you
live in peace with nature,
it'll provide you with
everything you need and can--
Stop goofing off
and pay attention!
[BOTH scream]
Yeah. Yeah. Nature and stuff.
We got it.
Now see here, you two!
[GENIE
Hey, Dan.
[DAN]
Hm?
I know what Lute's problem is.
He learns more by doing
than by listening.
How 'bout a mock battle?
Yeah, you might be
onto somethin' there.
What's a mock battle?
[GENIE] A practice fight,
but with real Monsties.
All right, that sounds
fun! Let's go do it!
Now this is my
kinda lesson!
Fine. But you need a partner
to have a practice fight.
[HYORO]
Uhh...
Who, me?
Perfect choice! Let's do this!
Uh, yeah, let's do it.
Right. I'll lay out
the ground rules.
Whoever is the first
to pop the balloon
on his opponent's
Monstie is the winner.
Oh, and direct attacks
on the other Rider
are strictly prohibited!
Got that?
[BOTH]
Yeah!
Oh. I almost forgot that
flying is banned, too.
What?
Okay.
[laughs]
You don't have anything
to worry about, Lute!
And why might that be?
'Cause when it comes
to popping balloons,
these whiskers are
lethal weapons!
Ow, ow! That hurts! Cut it out!
Wheresoever you and Ratha goeth,
there goeth Navirou!
And that is another Navi-rule.
Just sit back and leave
this all to Navirou!
No, you just leave me alone!
[GENIE]
Hyoro.
Even though it's a mock
battle, I expect you to win.
[HYORO] If I win, maybe
he'll finally go easier on me.
C'mon, Lute, I know you can win!
Yeah! I'm gonna try!
Well, ready?
Mock fight. Begin!
All right! Ratha, dodge left!
No, right! Dodge right!
[LUTE]
Left, left, left!
[NAVIROU]
Right, right, right!
They're running.
But Bulldrome's a faster
Monstie than Ratha!
Go!
Ratha, they're coming up
right behind us! Circle right!
No, go left!
[LUTE] Ratha isn't
listening to either of us!
Oh, that's bad.
You're running off course!
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
[DAN] What am I gonna
do with that kid?
[HYORO gasps]
All right, we're catching up!
Time to pop that balloon!
[BOTH gasp]
Uh, I warned him about flying.
[LUTE]
What're you doing, Ratha?! Stop!
Go back down!
Hm?
Huh?
The wind.
[LUTE]
Hey, pull up, pull up!
Watch out!
[LUTE, NAVIROU screaming]
[LILIA]
The windmill!
[MILLE]
Wow, look at 'em go.
[DAN] It's always gotta be
somethin' with those two.
[LUTE] Then this huge gust
came up outta nowhere!
It blew us straight up!
Then threw us to the side!
Like we were just a leaf!
Well, yes, and the windmill
wasn't the only part of the
village to see damage.
Given the strength of that gust,
I'd say it's a miracle
no one was hurt.
We can all breathe
easy for that.
[LUTE chuckles]
[CHIEF OMNA]
However.
Getting the village back
on its feet won't be easy.
Windmill Vanes are quite
precious and hard to replace.
Don't worry, Chief,
we won't rest until we re-attach
the one that blew off.
Genie?
Yes, sir!
I'm putting you in charge
of repairing this windmill.
Take these children and
do whatever it takes.
It's all up to you now, Genie.
Thank you, Chief.
Good luck! We're all
counting on you, Lute!
Oh no you don't.
You're helping with this.
[LUTE] Now that I think about
it, that gust was pretty weird.
Have you guys ever heard of the
Hakum Gale being that strong?
That was definitely the
strongest I've ever felt it.
It was blowing roofs off houses.
Seems like everything's
off-kilter lately, doesn't it?
Hey, what are you workin' on?
I'm calculating where
that windmill vane landed.
Huh?
[LILIA] Given the vane's weight
and this area's terrain,
and then factoring in
the speed, duration,
and direction of
the wind gust...
...it's right over there!
[LUTE, CHEVAL]
Wow!
[NAVIROU]
Not so fast.
This expedition is
the perfect time
to show off the
skills of Navirou,
the natural-born navigator!
That's it!
Navirou's whiskers say
the vane is over there!
[LUTE]
Great. We're goin' this way.
[LILIA]
I hope we find it fast.
[NAVIROU yelps]
[CHEVAL] Wonder how things
are going with Hyoro's group.
[NAVIROU]
Hey!
I don't see any sign
of that vane.
[STONE]
Me neither.
Do you know why this
happened, Hyoro?
Because the Hakum Gale
broke the blade?
That's the obvious answer,
but not the only one.
We're here because you
couldn't defeat Lute
when you had the chance.
You're too timid,
and now we're stuck
hunting for windmill parts.
The day you become a real
Rider is a long way off.
[BOTH laughing]
[GENIE] Ooh! I see bad guys!
What're we gonna do?
Circle around. Get 'em
from the right, Genie!
Yes, sir!
[HYORO]
Kinship Press!
Kinship Kick!
Now for the breath.
[GENIE]
Ha! Kinship Breath!
All right! Genie, we won!
Nice job!
Keep it up and you're sure to
make a great Rider someday!
[HYORO]
Mh-hm.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna be the number
one Rider in the world!
[GENIE]
Nope, that's wrong.
What?
You're just gonna have to settle
for being the second best.
Because your big brother Genie
is always gonna be number one!
Okay!
I'm happy to be second best
if my brother's first!
We're gonna be the two
best Riders around!
[BOTH laughing]
I wish. Why can't
I do any better?
Based on my calculations,
that windmill vane
should've been right here.
Keep looking, guys.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah! There it is!
[LUTE]
Whoa! How did we miss that?
I'm so great! My calculations
were spot-on!
Nuh-uh. Navirou's the great
one! Navirou found it!
I beg your pardon!
Let's use Ratha.
Do you think it'll fit?
All set! Now don't
drop it, Ratha!
Fly it all the way back
to the village!
Well, let's get moving.
Hold on a second!
[CHEVAL, NAVIROU]
Huh?
I smell a Monstie egg.
[CHEVAL, NAVIROU]
What?
It's this way!
Lute, no!
But there's an egg here.
I'm sure of it!
Our sole priority right now
is bringing back that vane!
Yeah, but--
[ALL gasp]
[roars]
A Rathian!
What's it doing down here?
We gotta go.
'Kay, Ride On!
Velocidrome!
You guys, run!
I'll slow it down!
Cheval.
Okay. Don't be crazy!
I'll be fine!
Oh, no!
[yelling]
Are you all right, Cheval?
Yeah, I'm fine!
Go run back to the others!
[CHEVAL]
Got it!
Oh, wow.
That explains why
the Rathian was here.
You made it back!
Are you okay, bud?
You had us worried.
I'm sorry 'bout that.
And the Rathian?
Genie and Stone
swooped in to help me.
They're leading it
back into the woods.
Awesome! Then we'll start
fixing the windmill!
Wait, you guys--
[LUTE] Now, let's see how
this thing connects.
[LILIA] We'll need all
the other materials too!
[VLAU]
Cheval?
Are you up here?
Oh, well.
I could swear I heard
him come inside.
He must've gone
right back out. Hm?
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
[VLAU]
Lunchtime! C'mon, eat up!
[KIDS chattering]
[LUTE] Whoa! Garlic rice
and Amno Meatballs!
This'll re-charge us!
A donut lunch for Navirou?
Mrs. Vlau is the best.
And she brought
big portions, too!
Everyone gets seconds!
Huh?
Hey! Hyoro!
Come over and eat with us!
Oh, thank you!
Got that right!
After all, we're the ones
getting this windmill
up and running.
We're kinda why it needs
fixing in the first place.
So, Cheval and Lute,
you guys are pretty close.
That's because we
grew up together.
I bet it wasn't easy for
you growing up with Genie.
[CHEVAL]
Hmm.
Is he as hard on you now
as he was back then?
Yeah, but I don't mind.
It's how Genie shows he
cares and looks out for me.
Oh, okay.
That said.
Since I started training
to be a Rider,
I don't think I've seen
Genie smile even once.
[HYORO]
There!
[GENIE]
Hyoro!
Tie it nice and tight so
it doesn't come un-done!
[HYORO]
'Kay!
Oh, man, he can be so useless.
Hey, Genie.
Well, don't you think you're a
little too hard on your brother?
I just get so irritated
watching him.
Heh. You can be
irritating, too, y'know?
Hard to be friends with.
What?!
But friends should look past
flaws. Especially brothers.
All that's left is to
hoist up the vane
and re-attach it to the axle.
Hey! That's enough for now!
It's break time!
[ALL]
'Kay!
All right! You ready to go?
What?
[BOTH sigh]
How come you're not
in the bath, Navirou?
[NAVIROU] Because unlike you
walking dirt clods,
Navirou exists in a state
of permanent cleanliness.
Ah. There's nothing better
than a good, hot soak
in the middle of the afternoon.
We should've done this after
we finished the windmill.
Hey, c'mon, now. Breaks
are important, too, Genie.
[NOLE, LUTE, HYORO, CHEVAL sigh]
All right!
Time to teach you boys the
real art of Hakum Bathing.
Now listen up!
[ALL]
The real art of Hakum Bathing?
[chuckles]
♪ Bless the mighty
Hakum Gales, ♪
♪ for the gifts they bring
to this sacred land. ♪
♪ The winds bring life
to our fields and trees, ♪
♪ each one so green
with beauty!♪
♪ The wind tells us
it's time for fun, ♪
♪ and so to the
harvest everyone! ♪
♪ All as one to fields
we've sown, ♪
♪ to reap the bounty
we have grown. ♪
♪ Bless the mighty
Hakum Gales, ♪
♪ for the gifts they bring
to this sacred land. ♪
♪ The winds bring life
to our fields and trees, ♪
♪ each one so green
with beauty! ♪
All right, now let's
hear it, fellas.
[OTHERS] ♪ Bless the
mighty Hakum Gales, ♪
♪ for the gifts they bring
to this sacred land. ♪
♪ The winds bring life... ♪
Genie, I don't hear you
singing along with the others.
[GENIE grunts, chuckles]
♪ Bless the mighty
Hakum Gales, ♪
♪ for the gifts they bring
to this sacred land. ♪
[ALL] ♪ The winds bring life
to our fields and trees, ♪
♪ each one so green
with beauty! ♪
Being a boy sure is easy.
With a simple mind, all you
need are simple pleasures.
What's wrong with having fun?
Well, nothing.
Girls are able to have just
as much fun as boys are!
What're you talking about?
[MILLE]
Nothing! Forget it.
[GENIE] Well, I hope you're
all nice and refreshed
after that generous,
midday spa visit.
[OTHERS]
Yes!
Then let's finish this
job before it gets dark!
[BOYS]
Yeah!
It seems like they
really bonded, huh?
Like I said, boys
have simple minds.
Stay there until
we bolt it in place!
'Kay!
[gasps]
[screams]
Ratha, hold on!
[BOTH grunt]
[MILLE]
What? Oh, no!
Uh-oh! Bulldrome, dash!
Hyoro!
[LUTE]
Ratha!
You can do it!
[screams]
I'm coming! Hold on tight!
Whoa, Lute! Genie!
[sighs]
[HYORO]
Good job, Bulldrome.
You all right?
Hey, when you're training to
become the world's best Rider,
a day like today is
a piece of cake.
I see.
Wonder how serious you
really are about that.
Teach me!
I want you to teach me
everything you know
about Monsties!
How to ride! How to fly them!
I wanna be an even better
Rider than you, Genie!
[gasps]
[LUTE] Hyoro sure is lucky
to have you as his teacher.
You should know, I'm not
a big pushover like Dan is.
Right!
[chuckles]
Hyoro, you made the right
decision back there.
Well done.
[HYORO]
Huh?!
But you--
Thanks for that, Genie.
You're very lucky to have
all these great friends.
[ALL chuckle]
[DAN]
So you think this is why
the Hakum Gale
changed direction.
Unfortunately, it's gotten to
the point where it's doing
a whole lot more than
just changing direction.
I'm afraid there's no
doubt about it, Dan,
we have a disaster on our hands.
We must keep a close watch
on this, at all times.
[DAN]
Yes, sir.
Cheval, honey. Are you sure
that's a real Rathian egg?
Yep! I'm positive!
Well, if Lute calls
his Rathalos "Ratha,"
then you should call
your Rathian "Rathi."
Rathi.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life.
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Yian kut-ku!
You can't miss these guys,
thanks to their big
jaws and big ears.
They're very fast,
but those ears do make them
sensitive to loud noises.
Nobody around here rides a
Yian kut-ku better than Genie!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
I hope you've noticed by now,
but things just keep getting
stranger in the woods!
Thankfully, we're about
to find out why!
Next time: "Before the Storm"!
Ride On!