[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
Disenchanted and
seeking answers,
Lute underwent an introspective
trial at the Tower of Illusion,
ultimately learning what the
power of Kinship really is.
Meanwhile, Cheval had
learned a different lesson.
He tossed aside
his Monstie, Rathi,
and then turned his back on his
loyal friends Hyoro and Mille.
Alone and embittered,
it looked like Cheval
had finally given in and joined
forces with Dr. Manelger.
[DR. MANELGER] Sorry to keep
you waiting, Cheval, my boy!
But at last it's ready,
my Mecha Kinship Stone!
[NARRATOR] But no! Cheval had
vanished without a trace!
[LUTE]
You sure about this, Navirou?
I think we took a wrong turn,
because this doesn't look like
where we're supposed
to meet Lilia.
Never doubt Navirou's
navigational skills.
[LUTE]
Are you kidding?
I've doubted it every
day since we met!
Wait.
Why'd you stop?
[grunts]
Come on, pal. What's going on?
Ever since we got here,
I've had this weird feeling
that someone's following me.
No, everyone's eyes
are on Navirou.
Such is the fate of
the world famous!
[NAVIROU laughing]
[LUTE]
Really?
You're saying
there's not actually
a Kinship Ore on Mount Rhyz?
Sorry, we got it wrong.
It turns out that
the Kinship Ore
lies somewhere in the
shadow of Mount Rhyz.
So we have to search in
the Mountain's shadow.
Which means...
Means what?
Well, it means we better
get on the road!
--[NAVIROU yelps]
--[LILIA chuckles]
[gasps]
What's wrong? Are you okay?
[LUTE]
Actually, no, I'm not.
All afternoon I haven't been
able to shake the feeling
that I'm being followed.
What? By whom?
Fans who want
Navirou's autograph.
It's hard getting
around when you're
the greatest
adventurer on Earth.
[chuckles nervously]
Is there any chance it's Cheval?
No. Cheval, well,
he's on his own path.
Yeah, okay.
[NAVIROU]
Ooh, it's so good!
Big city donuts are different,
but no less delicious!
[stomach growls]
[NAVIROU]
Wait!
Navirou senses a donut danger!
[LUTE]
Right?
See, I told you:
Someone's following us!
These donuts are
Navirou's property!
Only Navirou touches
them and no one else!
I don't see anyone.
[stomach growls]
[NAVIROU]
Over there! Hi-yah!
[BOTH gasp]
[LUTE]
Hyoro?
[LILIA]
Mille!
How long has it been since you
guys had something to eat?
[HYORO]
Two days.
And is that when
you last saw Cheval?
Yeah. Can't believe what
he said to us. Jerk.
I still can't believe he
got rid of Rathi like that.
I don't understand him anymore,
he's totally different.
Do you think he's joined
forces with Dr. Manelger?
Doubtful.
I think he's probably
just out there
fighting the Black
Blight on his own.
Probably.
So now that you've
left him, what's next?
[MILLE]
We don't know.
What do you think we should do?
Well, why not go back
home and rest up?
It's been a while since
you were there, right?
They'd all be so
happy to see you!
I'm not so sure.
[HYORO] It's more like
they'd be "disgusted."
After what we did to my
brother and everyone else...
Demolition Dash!
That's some pretty weak Kinship
you've got with your Monoblos
there, little brother!
Maybe, but I can see
through your every move!
[GENIE gasps]
It's time to Rock Smash!
We were mean to you, too.
Please forgive us.
Oh, it's fine, guys.
Don't apologize.
Here we are,
back to hanging out
and eating donuts like
the old days, right, Lute?
Right!
That reminds me, give Hyoro
and Mille some more donuts.
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
Take it!
It's chocolate.
Uh, thank you.
But really, we are sorry.
But why would you try to steal
Navirou's donuts like that?
That's not what we were doing.
[LUTE, LILIA chuckle]
Well, I assume that
you were following us
for some other reason, then?
[BOTH]
Yeah.
There's no way we can
get through to Cheval.
Lute's the only one
who can do it.
[HYORO]
It's like...
...the Blight's making the world
more dangerous every day.
And 'cause Cheval was
trying to protect people
from Blighted monsters,
we wanted to be
right there with him.
But the way he's going
about it now is all wrong.
Do you think Cheval and I
are really that different?
You've both made it your mission
to stop the Black Blight,
just not in the same manner.
Navirou thinks
the big difference
is that one of you
wants to protect
while the other
wants to destroy.
[gasps]
Navi, you're as poetic
as you are brilliant.
[laughs]
Navirou just loves that praise!
Keep it up. More-more-more!
Hyoro and I, we just didn't
know how to reach him.
So sad.
Mille. Hyoro.
I was just telling Lute that the
Scriveners have figured out
the location of a
new Kinship Ore.
Wanna come find it with us?
[BOTH gasp]
Supposedly, there've
also been sightings
of Blighted Monsters
in that area's forest.
So there's a chance we could
run into Cheval there, too.
Yeah, that's a good point.
And if we do find
that Kinship Ore
and it turns out to be
infected with the Blight,
we're gonna need your
help purifying it.
[LUTE]
Yeah!
Whaddaya say?
Let's do it.
We're in.
[NAVIROU] Well, if you're
all coming, then we better..
...go stock up on donuts!
How many donuts do you need?
All right, Navirou Team,
let's find that Ore!
[LILIA] First we've got to find
the Forest of Confusion
and the Ruins of Redan.
[MILLE]
Forest of what now?
[NAVIROU]
Hey, wait for Navirou!
According to the Guild,
the Forest of Confusion,
like the Ruins of Redan,
is off-limits for studying.
So we don't really know much
about it, or even where it is.
Piece-a-cake! Leave the Forest
of Confusion-finding to Navirou!
I'd rather take our chances
with her old map.
[NAVIROU yelps]
[POOGIE]
Poogie-Poogie-Poogie...
[DEBLI]
Hey!
[ALL]
Huh?
Slow down, Poogie! Slow down!
Whoa. It's Tub... bli.
[DEBLI]
My name is Debli! Debli!
And he's gone.
Are you just joking, or did
you really forget about me?
Y'know what, I guess
we kinda did.
[NAVIROU]
Yep.
Hey!
Debli, what're you
doin' out here, anyway?
Ha! Glad you asked!
I'm here to face the Black
Blight with you, of course!
Only now as, "New Rider Debli"!
"New Rider"? And what is that?
It's not quite a real
Rider, like you guys.
But in some ways,
it's even more impressive
than being a real Rider!
The whole thing smells fishy.
I'll say.
[DEBLI]
Hey, wait.
Lute, what are these two
doing back with you?
We patched things up and now
we're going on an adventure.
Well, since I'm
friends with you,
that makes me friends
with them now.
Wait, when were we
ever friends with you?
I'm still a higher
rank than you, pal!
Wait, where's that Cheval guy?
We don't really know.
[DEBLI]
Rider against Rider, huh?
I guess.
But all of us standing
here are friends.
Yeah, that's right.
And with New Rider Debli,
you have a friend who
always has your back!
You guessed it! I'm comin'
on your adventure!
[ALL chuckle]
Navirou senses fear in you.
Just so you know,
these adventures can
get pretty dangerous.
I'm so ready for this,
I'll drag you guys
along with me!
I've even mastered
everything there is to know
about monster Riding!
Let's go, Great Poogie!
[DEBLI yells]
[DEBLI]
Hey! Come back!
C'mon we talked about
this! Great Poogie!
He hasn't mastered
Riding at all.
I'd say it's more like
Poogie's taking him for a ride.
Well, this adventure
will be a delight.
Yeah!
I'm glad that we can be
together again guys.
It means a lot.
You haven't changed one bit.
Still spouting out sappy
feelings with a straight face.
Cheval. One day soon,
you'll be back with us, too.
[gasps]
[LUTE]
A Nerscylla?
And it's Blighted!
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU, LUTE yelp]
It's definitely
not a good sign
when a Blighted monster shows
up right outside a city.
Blighted monster attacks
have become more common
in every place
we've been, lately.
[HYORO]
It's like they're taking over.
All these monsters are
just a symptom of how far
the Black Blight has spread.
If that Nerscylla and other
monsters nearby have the Blight,
then the Kinship Ore we're
after could be infected, too.
We'll stop it!
Let's go!
Ride On!
Great Poogie, charge!
Hey, wait, the
monster's that way!
Turn around, Poogie!
Don't do this to
me again! Obey...
How exactly does he
think that's helping?
Time to Ride On!
Rathalos, now!
Okay.
Ratha, let's show our
friends down there
how the Kinship we all share
is our greatest strength!
[roars]
Ratha! Use your breath!
Now! Sky High Extreme!
Oh, wow. Leave it to Navirou's
top pupil to put on a show!
I'll say.
[BOTH]
Wow.
Hey, so, Lute, your
Kinship Attack's amazing.
I hope I learn how to pull off
one as strong as that someday.
So where did you and Ratha learn
such a powerful new Attack?
Navirou's teaching is
the key to the attack,
and only a small amount of
Lute's effort, to be polite.
Whaddaya mean "small amount"?
But still, it'll
definitely surprise Cheval.
If both Lute and
Cheval were with us,
well, we could stand up to
any threat we come across.
Oh, Cheval. What
happened to you?
Deep down, you're
pretty worried, huh?
If you wanna talk to Navirou
about what you're feeling,
he's happy to listen.
Cheval's our friend
no matter what happens!
And I bet in his heart,
Cheval still feels
the exact same way.
I hope you're right, Lilia.
Yeah.
[DEBLI]
Hey!
Hold up-hold up-hold up!
I'm getting real fed up with
you guys leaving me behind!
I thought we were friends!
We're not leaving, you
keep riding away from us!
Because the Great Poogie
here won't obey my orders!
[POOGIE]
Poogie.
[DEBLI screams]
[LILIA]
Careful, Debli!
You don't wanna
accidentally end up
in the Forest of Confusion!
What? Is that bad?
You could be lost
in there forever.
[squeals]
Turn around! Ah!
No, stop! Sto--!
Ow!
Lute, what in the
world is Debli doing?
I guess he's playing
with Great Poogie.
[NAVIROU]
You need more training, kid!
Anyone else got a weird
feeling out here?
It's sure-as-heck not like any
forest I've ever hiked through.
So are we officially in the
Forest of Confusion now?
Well, according to the map,
it should be right around
here somewhere.
How are we gonna find it
when we've been walking
in circles all this time?
Yeah, look. See the
mark on the tree?
That's where Great Poogie and
I crashed into it earlier.
No way.
I could swear we were
walking straight ahead.
We got lost.
Technically,
we're not really lost
if we keep coming back to
the same place, right?
Well, I guess.
The point is, we're in the
Forest of Confusion now.
Even with Navirou's expert
navigational skills,
he still has no idea
where the ore is.
Well, that's that.
But wait, if we've found the
forest, then that means...
...the Ore's close, right?
Yeah, it should be.
Whoa, what's that?
[MILLE]
Damage from the Black Blight.
[LILIA]
That confirms it then.
The Kinship Ore in this forest
is becoming infected
with the Black Blight.
We'd better go find it,
before it's too late.
But we still don't know where
in the forest to start looking.
[LUTE]
Hm.
[NAVIROU]
Hm...
--That way!
[LILIA]
Well, then that means it's...
...definitely the
opposite direction.
Oh, yeah.
[HYORO]
Huh.
How about we try to follow
all that smudgy stuff
on the trees back to its source?
Wait, Navirou doesn't
think it's that simple.
How can we tell the difference
between the direction
it's coming from
versus the direction
it's going to?
Any ideas?
What direction did
we just come from?
Uh, well...
How are we ever gonna
find the Kinship Ore
if we don't even know that?
[shrieking]
[ALL gasp]
A monster!
[squeals]
Hyoro?
Big brother!
And Stone?
Mille! Lute. And Lilia, too!
Don't forget Navirou! Ha!
And me!
Oh, I forgot that you guys
have never met... Tubbli.
My name is Debli!
Hyoro.
How in the world did
you end up here?
I could ask you the same thing.
We heard reports of a
Blighted monster around here,
so we came to check it out.
Why're you back on Lute's team?
Uh, well...
I thought you and Mille
were with Cheval.
Oh, Genie, we're so sorry.
Going with Cheval
was a big mistake.
We thought we'd be helping
to stop the Blight,
but it turns out we were wrong.
So if you're here,
then where's Cheval?
We have no clue. We left him.
Genie. I'm sorry.
I never agreed with
the choice you made.
I only allowed it because
it's more important for you
to choose your own path.
But a man who can't see his own
choices through is a disgrace.
And is no Rider,
or brother, to me.
Genie.
That's going a little far.
Genie!
He's still a Rider, and he's
still your little brother!
He and Mille didn't
leave Cheval on a whim.
They thought long and hard
before coming to us.
Let's go.
We can at least follow through
on the commitments we made.
As Riders.
[STONE]
Hey. Wait up!
[roaring]
[HYORO]
The Nerscylla!
[NAVIROU]
It's back!
[BOTH yelp]
Lilia!
Tub... bli.
That's not my name!
Now get us down!
What's wrong?
[GENIE, STONE gasp]
A Nerscylla!
Ride On!
Monoblos!
Genie! Don't get hit by
its webs! They're dangerous!
I don't need Rider
tips from you!
Oh, no!
[GENIE]
Calm down, Monoblos!
[HYORO]
Genie!
Ride On!
Monoblos!
Hyoro.
Genie!
[GENIE] Don't worry about me.
Get Lilia and Debli!
[HYORO]
Come on!
Here goes.
I will stop it!
Hey, why aren't
you helping, Lute?
Help them? Oh, they'll be fine.
You see that, Genie?
That looks like the
face of a Rider to me.
In fact, looks like yours.
Hyoro's not your little brother,
anymore. He's an equal.
All right. Demolition Dash!
I did it.
Hyoro!
[HYORO]
Genie?
[GENIE]
I was right, Hyoro.
You're not the person
I thought you were.
You're a true Rider.
Genie!
Brothers are great. I want one.
[LILIA] But in a way,
you do have a brother.
His name is Cheval.
You always say you're family.
[MILLE]
Lute. Please.
Let's go find Cheval
and bring him back.
I'm sick and tired of feeling
all broken up inside.
Yeah. We'll find
him. Count on it.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Great Poogie!
This Monstie gives off
a courageous air
that other Poogies lack,
what with that rakish eyebrow
scar and flashy purple scarf!
A powerful figure,
even when taking Debli
for a wild ride!
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Wait, what?
A phantom monster is in
the Forest of Confusion?
Next time: "A Mystical
Meeting with Kirin"!
Ride On!