[NARRATOR]
These youngsters are Riders,
on a quest to track down
blackened Kinship Ore
and stop the Black Blight that's
been spreading across the world.
That mission was
brought close to home
when Manelger's scheming caused
Hakum Village's Kinship Ore
to be taken over by the Blight.
In the fallout,
Lute barely managed to
slay a Blighted Tigrex
and defend Hakum Village,
when suddenly, Cheval appeared.
[LUTE]
Cheval!
[CHEVAL] If there are no more
Blighted monsters here,
then our business is done.
[gasps]
Cheval!
[NAVIROU] Now you wait
just a minute, mister!
That is, if you don't mind.
Oh, right!
Donuts! Do ya want some donuts?
They're super delicious!
So tasty and so sweet.
Here, take 'em all!
Three-for-none!
That's the best deal
Navirou can offer!
[CHEVAL]
Come on, let's go.
[CHIEF OMNA] Ah, it's been
a while, eh, Cheval?
It's so good of you
to rush back home
to aid your village
in its hour of need.
I'm not here because
this is my hometown.
We slay Blighted monsters no
matter where they spring up.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Yes, that reminds me, Cheval.
Your mother's flowers are in
fine bloom again this year.
So beautiful.
You've come at the perfect time.
I'm not the boy I was back then.
That may be, but you're
still Vlau's son.
[CHEVAL]
Rathian!
Oh, poor Cheval.
Really? Cheval was here, huh?
Yeah.
He coulda at least said
hi to the rest of us.
Coming back here, that's
gotta be emotional for him.
Yeah.
Navirou tried to tempt him
into staying with donuts,
but it didn't work.
Oh, Navi.
I don't know what to do.
[LUTE gasps]
About Cheval and Mille...
And Hyoro...
What else can we do
to get through to them?
I've lost him. My own brother.
It's like he doesn't want to
hear anything I have to say now.
[GENIE]
No. He was always like that.
Guess I just thought that's
how younger brothers are.
[CHIEF OMNA]
Genie.
Instead of thinking
about what we can't do,
focus on what we can.
We'll protect our village.
Be ready to welcome them home
with a smile, and that's all.
Yeah, you're right, as usual.
This place will always
be their hometown!
That's right.
They can come back any time
and have a place to stay.
A place to stay.
Our hometown.
Yeah, of course. I'm sure
they'll come back soon.
When they do, oh, we'll just
talk and talk for hours.
There are so many things
that I wanna say to Cheval.
Like "I'm sorry"!
Navirou can't breathe!
[DAN]
Hey, Lute.
Eat up. It's tasty!
Oh! I know!
You must be exhausted, Lute.
I'll whip up some Energy Drinks.
[OTHERS grunt]
[screams]
What's that?
Navirous's expressing
what we're all thinking.
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh, you know, it's just...
We're all totally stuffed.
That's it, yeah.
Really?
[BOTH grunt]
[DAN]
Mh-hm.
But what about Lute?
--Hey, Lute! Just nod, Lute!
--He barely touched his food.
Lilia, sometimes a man just
wants to be left alone.
You understand.
I see.
Guess an Energy Drink...
wouldn't be so bad.
What are you doing?!
You're not thinking
straight right now!
I know how you're
feeling, but still!
Pull yourself together, Lute!
Don't do anything drastic!
[LILIA] Hey, I dont get it.
What are you all talking about?
[DAN, GENIE, STONE chattering]
[roar]
Whoa, look!
Let's go!
Hey, Cheval,
the soufflés are ready.
Go and get Lute, all right?
[gasps]
[CHEVAL]
Why?
[LOLOA]
Cheval!
Wow, it's really you!
We missed you so much,
but thank goodness
you came back to us!
Welcome home, Cheval!
Boy, am I glad to see you!
[CHEVAL] Hate to break it
to you, but I'm not staying.
No, you can't leave again!
Everybody in the village
wants to see you!
Including Lute!
He's been staring at
these flowers all day
'cause he misses you!
I have to go.
[LOLOA]
No, no, no!
Please don't abandon us, Cheval!
[CHEVAL]
You kids take care.
Hold on just a second!
Wait there!
Loloa will be right back!
Take these!
It's something that
Mrs. Vlau taught Loloa.
[LOLOA wailing]
Loloa's favorite dolly broke
and Loloa can't play
with it anymore!
This is the worst thing
that's ever happened!
So do you wanna know a secret?
[VLAU]
You see,
when you pick a flower,
you may be inclined to feel
a bit bad for pulling it up,
but a plucked flower can
serve a greater purpose
than those left in the ground.
Really, in what way?
[VLAU] Well, they can
warm a person's heart.
[LOLOA]
They can?
Sure, the flowers are able
to take root once again,
living on forever within
the heart they've warmed.
Likewise, your dolly,
although it's been broken,
will live on inside
of your heart, Loloa.
So whenever you're
feeling sad or lonely,
or if you see somebody else
who's down in the dumps,
gather up a nice bouquet
of flowers and give it away.
Whether you give
or receive them,
the flowers are sure
to warm your heart.
Okay, I get it!
[LOLOA]
You looked so sad.
That's why I picked
these for you.
I hope they cheer you up.
But, Cheval...
Why's this happening?
Why do you have to leave us?
[LOLOA]
We'll be waiting here for you!
As long as it takes!
Cheval, we'll wait for you!
Just come back! Please, Cheval!
Loloa will pick flowers
for you every day!
Which means that... your
heart will always be warm.
[NARIKI] And then,
Cheval just turned around
and walked away for good.
Loloa and I both begged and
begged for him to stay here.
We asked him not
to go, but still...
Ah, that's a good boy, Nariki.
Thank you for filling
us in on all of this.
Yeah, good job. And thanks
for bringing Loloa here.
[DAN]
Hey, kid.
Uh, yes, sir?
It's nice to hear that Cheval
visited his mom's garden.
Shows he still cares.
Wouldn't you agree, Lute?
[LUTE]
Nariki.
Uh-huh?
Thanks for tellin' us!
[NAVIROU]
Hey, wait! Lute, where ya goin'?
Uh, Lute?
Even if you're not all
together at the moment,
your paths will eventually
merge and become one.
For the roads that we Riders
travel are all interconnected.
Come on, Lute, give it a rest.
The sky's fit to busting
with stars already.
Sure, Navirou's eyes won't
open... but he sees 'em.
Navirou sees everything.
If you're tired, just go to bed.
Navirou can't sleep! Not when
his top pupil is suffering!
No, Navirou's here
to prop him up!
[NAVIROU snoring]
Hey, Ratha, thanks for flying
as fast as you could.
Really thought we were
gonna catch up to him.
I coulda sworn he was still
nearby. I could just feel it.
Hope you know... he went
to see your garden.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Vlau.
I'm sorry I wasn't
strong enough.
If I had been...
I could've saved you.
I mean, I'm more than
strong enough now.
[screams]
Ugh. Dang it. Dang it!
[CHEVAL]
Don't flatter yourself!
[LUTE gasps]
Ride On!
Rathalos!
[NAVIROU yelps]
Don't fool yourself.
Even if you'd had the
strength you have today,
I doubt you would've
kept my mom safe.
Because your way doesn't
work and never will.
Not when you cling
to your belief
in this "power of
Kinship" nonsense.
[CHEVAL]
What don't you get?
How can you say
something like that?
That you would've kept her safe?
Your gut? Is it your
gut telling you that?
Same as it ever was.
Doing whatever you wanted.
Just following your gut.
[CHEVAL] Y'know, I always
envied you for that,
your carefree attitude.
And I... I hated you for it.
But then it dawned on me.
Thinking back to that day,
the day when you first
stumbled upon Ratha's egg...
You led us into the
Forbidden Land, carefree,
without any concern
for the risks.
And what's worse, you put
Lilia in real danger.
You were ignorant of the
whole Kinship Rite process,
but you didn't let that stop you
from pressuring
Lilia into helping.
Just thinking about it makes
me furious all over again.
I'm mad at myself, too,
for not stopping you.
But you just kept ambling along,
never bothering to find
out how I might feel.
And then, when the Nargacuga
attacked the village,
it was the same thing.
The adults warned
us apprentice Riders
not to do anything reckless.
But you...
If you hadn't raced in to try
and stop that Nargacuga...
...then to this day,
you'd still be acting cocky,
claiming you could've
kept the village safe.
[gasps]
Tell me I'm wrong.
It's true, but...
I did it...
...because I thought I
could save the village...
...and I thought that
I could save your mom.
[CHEVAL] I knew it.
You haven't changed a bit.
Not since we were kids.
Always playing the hero,
thinking you could
save everyone.
If only you were stronger.
Even worse... is how you
naïvely just keep insisting
that you've somehow cured
your Blighted Rathalos.
What if it runs amok
again? What then?
Ratha--
Once the blackness has tainted
them, there is no going back.
It's better if you
just accept that.
Better than being betrayed
by someone you trust.
That's for sure.
Cheval.
[CHEVAL]
Listen to me, Lute.
Today I prove that you
still aren't strong enough
to get the job done!
Now!
Come on!
Look, Cheval, just slow down.
I don't want to fight you.
I can't fight you.
[CHEVAL] All right, then let me
tell you what I really think.
[CHEVAL]
Frankly...
Your self-centeredness...
and your sheer arrogance...
That is what killed my mother.
Now, Lute, Ride On.
I'll show you that
despite what you think,
you don't always get your way.
But I can't.
I said Ride On!
I can't!
Oh, yeah? Well, how about now?
[CHEVAL]
Get up! Get up and fight me!
No way. I don't wanna make
Ratha and Rathi face off.
Not this again! Ugh!
Cheval, I still believe
wholeheartedly
in my Kinship with you,
and with Ratha.
Just shut up!
[LUTE] All that stuff
you said, it hit me hard.
I was wrong.
So please...
"So please hit me!"
Right, Lute?
That what you were saying.
Navirou knows all!
I told you, you can't
always get your way, Lute!
Now Ride On!
Rathian!
Ride On, Lute! Do it!
Ratha.
Are... you sure?
Then Ride On!
Rathalos!
Let's go, Rathian!
Nice work!
Okay, Rathian, one more time!
Let's show him that Kinship
holds no power whatsoever!
Go!
[CHEVAL]
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Just finish him!
End this once and for all! Now!
Cheval.
[LILIA]
Lute! Cheval!
Rathian! I order you
to finish him!
[LILIA]
Cheval!
All this time, I thought that
I knew how you must be feeling,
but I had no clue.
And the same goes
for Lute, I'm sure.
But your Kinship should--
[CHEVAL]
Forget it!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHEVAL]
I'm sick of this!
Rathian, I'm sick of you, too!
Cheval, no!
[roars]
I don't believe in any Kinship!
Rathian, I have no
more use for you!
[CHIEF OMNA]
Ah, but, Cheval.
Don't you remember
how Vlau kept her safe?
[gasps]
[CHEVAL] Well, I'm ending
it here. All of it.
[CHEVAL]
Don't follow me!
[RATHI cries]
What could I do? What else
should I have done?
There's nothing anyone can do.
He's found his own path.
[LILIA]
But...
Chief Omna, weren't
you telling us earlier
how all of the Riders' paths
will eventually become one?
Tell me, Lute, as a Rider,
what do you believe in
more than anything?
The power of Kinship.
Ah, but do you know
what kind of power Kinship is?
Just as I thought, you still
have much to learn, my dear boy.
You can start at the sacred
place: The Tower of Illusion.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
And now, it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie this
time is: Great Jaggi!
The alpha leader
of a Jaggi herd
can be a real doozy when
teamed up with their underlings.
These monsters expertly
use combo attacks
with the right power, speed,
and technique for any job.
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE] We're on our way
to a mysterious place
to learn more about the
power of Kinship and--
Whoa, time's been turned back?
Next time: "Tested at
the Tower of Illusion"!
Ride On!