[NARRATOR]
This young boy's name is Lute,
a rash but enthusiastic fellow,
who dreams of becoming the
world's top Monster Rider.
After getting separated
from his friends,
Lute found the
injured girl, Avinia.
But now, having brought
her to a hot springs inn,
a mysterious force is
suddenly drawing near!
Don't worry about a thing, Lute!
Your mentor Navirou is
ready to lead from behind!
Oh, great!
[BOTH]
It's here!
Well, howdy-do, fellas?
[LUTE, NAVIROU scream]
[LUTE]
Who are you?
Uh, hello. So you're the
innkeeper, right? Or something?
The girl hurt her leg.
Do you mind if we stay
here until she's better?
Fine, but ya gotta
answer a riddle.
What?
I give you a riddle,
you give me an answer,
and if it's right,
you get to stay.
Really, that's it?
All right! I'll solve any
riddle you've got. Hit me!
Okay, here we go!
I got pointy ears
and a big ol' potbelly.
Tell me, boy, who am I?
It has pointy ears...
And a big potbelly...
Uhh... Well...
Maybe...
That's that. Your time's up.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
What?!
[NAVIROU] Not fair! You gotta
give us more than that!
Hold on. I know it.
The answer's you, right?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[LUTE]
He has pointy ears.
[NAVIROU]
And a big potbelly.
[AVINIA]
It's not so much a riddle
as it is him
introducing himself.
That's right!
The answer to the riddle is me!
What kinda answer is that?!
I'm the Riddlemaster,
and since you're stayin'
in my hot springs,
I promise there'll be
plenty more to come!
We'll still pay
you for our stay.
We're sorry for
intruding like we did.
Well, ain't no need, missy.
Wow, thanks!
The Riddlemaster's heart
is just as big as his belly!
Yep, yep, yep.
Although, at first, you do
come across a little odd.
Oh, you two still pay.
--Uh?! That's not fair!
--We do?
It is too fair 'cause neither
of you solved the riddle.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Well, yeah, but so?
I can let ya stay the night,
but come dawn, you
gotta start working off
your room and board.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Aw, come on.
Rested and ready!
Hey! There you are, Cheval!
Lilia! Good morning.
[LILIA]
What are you doing?
Oh. I'm just--
Well, I had a hard
time sleeping,
so I've just been
studying the map.
[LILIA]
Good.
I'm starting to worry about
Lute and Navi. Still not back.
[CHEVAL]
Yeah.
[LILIA] It was a little rude for
them to run off like that.
I mean, they can't expect us
to just camp here forever
waiting for them.
[CHEVAL]
You're right.
They can catch up with us.
We're headed to the same place.
Heck, knowing Lute, he might
already be at Gildegaran.
Good point. Okay.
I'll wake up Mille and
Hyoro and we'll get going.
All right.
[LUTE, NAVIROU scream]
Wake up! The work
day's a-startin!
[LUTE] How'd we even
get into this mess?
You couldn't answer the
easiest riddle ever, that's how.
If it was so easy, then why
couldn't you solve it?
It's your fault!
No, this is all your fault!
No, your fault!
[LUTE]
Your fault! End of story!
Once you're done scrubbin',
I want you working
on the hallway,
front doors, and toilet.
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
What?! All that stuff?!
[RIDDLEMASTER]
Well, sure!
That's the price you pay for
squattin' in a fella's inn
and not solvin' the
easiest riddle ever.
That jerk! I hate this
stupid Riddlemaster!
[stomach growls]
[BOTH groan]
Navirou's hungry, Lute.
Me too.
[AVINIA] Come to my room!
I have plenty of food there!
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
Avinia, is that you?
Of course.
The Riddlemaster prepared an
enormous breakfast for me
that I'll never be able
to finish on my own.
Why don't we eat it together?
[BOTH]
Wow, free breakfast!
Avinia, saves the day!
Hey, look! It finally
started snowing!
Yeah, but wait...
Should the ground
be so slippery?
When did we start
walking on ice?
Something's wrong, guys.
The road isn't supposed
to be frozen like this.
We must've taken a wrong
turn along the way.
All right. Well, let's all
just be extra careful.
Nice knowin' ya, Hyoro.
I'll be fine.
Look how careful I am--
[HYORO yelping]
Hyoro!
[HUNTER A]
Are you okay?
[HYORO]
Huh?
Are you okay?
You okay?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Sorry I spilled your fish.
Hey, don't worry about it.
It's my fault for being slow
to clean up my fishing hole.
You're a fisherman?
Actually, no. I'm a Hunter.
A Hunter!
What's a Hunter doing
fishing up here?
My kids and I like to do it.
We catch ancient fish to use
for my hunting equipment.
Oh, wow, I didn't know
there were so many resources
you could get from them.
We're sorry if we interrupted
your family activity.
It's fine.
We should move.
This area gets dangerous fast
when the Lagombi comes out.
[ALL]
Wait, a Lagombi?
Follow me. There's a safer
area I can take you kids to.
Yeah? Thanks, Mister!
Of course!
[ALL chuckle]
Well, let's go!
[ALL]
Okay!
[ALL chuckle]
Oh, man! These
riceballs are delicious!
Everything is so tasty!
Whoa! Avinia's smiling!
Yeah, I think it's the first
time you've smiled since we met.
What? That's not
true. I do smile.
[BOTH chuckle]
[RIDDLEMASTER] Boys!
Got some guests that need help!
[BOTH]
'Kay!
[LUTE]
Here ya go!
Thanks, kid!
Yeah, thank you.
Whoa! Where'd you get
all the battle scars?
[HUNTER B]
Mm?
Oh, those? I was hunting
at Heaven's Mount.
A Seregios swooped down and
slashed me outta nowhere!
[HUNTER C] Injuries come with
the job when you're on a Quest.
You see these two?
I was wading through
the Flooded Forest
when I ran into a
Gobul's back spikes.
Got this big one from the
Gobul's cousin, the Nibelsnarf,
when he jumped me in the desert.
And finally, this is from when
I got a little too close
to a Gravios' breath.
It's crazy you've fought so
many different monsters.
Well, that's our job.
We Hunters hunt
what we're paid to
and the scars are souvenirs
we keep from each journey.
Interesting.
Yep, and over in Gildegaran,
you'll meet some of the most
skilled Hunters in the world!
Wait, Gildegaran?
That's exactly where I'm headed
once I pay off my debt!
[HUNTER B chuckles]
Don't quit your job. You ain't
ready for that journey.
What?
Hey, why not?
It's 'cause in
order to get there,
you have to first go through
the cave of a Khezu.
A Khezu?
[BOTH]
Wait, that thing?
So you've already had
a run in with it, huh?
Yeah, Khezu's a monster who'll
scare you outta your boots.
But wait! I have to get to
Gildegaran no matter what!
Is there another way?
You could ask the Wyverian
from the Arctic Ridge.
You know the Wyverian?
If you ever get
yourselves into trouble,
seek out the Wyverian who
lives in the Arctic Ridge.
[HUNTER B] Never seen
or met the guy myself,
but supposedly,
he's tall and fit
and has a way of makin'
ladies weak in the knees.
Basically, the kind of
guy they call a hunk.
Seek out the Wyverian?
The word on the street
is the guy's a total hunk.
Ha. Probably looks
a lot like Navirou.
Avinia, is something wrong?
The Wyverian's actually who
I've been looking for, too.
[BOTH]
What?
For real?
So you're on a hunk hunt?
My hope is that
if I can find him,
the Wyverian will be
able to re-awaken
Frostfang's lost powers.
[LUTE]
How did he lose them?
He went into some kind of shock
after fighting a rabid monster.
A monster that I now understand
was infected with
the Black Blight.
You've seen The
Black Blight too?
Yes, my whole village was
completely devastated
by Blighted monsters.
So if I could just
find the Wyverian,
I can heal Frostfang.
And if he has his powers back,
we'll have our
Kinship Attack again.
And we can stop the Black Blight
from doing any more damage.
[LUTE]
It's just like us.
We left our village
for the wider world
so we could stop
the Black Blight,
and that's why I'm trying to
become the best Rider ever!
Sounds like you've
got big plans.
Come on!
There are way more
important things to do
than cleaning up around here.
Let's go find the Wyverian
of the Arctic Ridge!
Yeah, let's find that hunk!
[AVINIA]
I'm coming, too.
But isn't your leg still hurt?
I feel fine now.
That hot spring helped me
more than I thought.
So let's go!
[BOTH]
Mh!
[LUTE]
Looks like we're all clear.
Now!
[LUTE, NAVIROU scream]
I reckon y'all tryin' to leave.
Riddlemaster, I'm sorry,
but we've gotta find the
Wyverian from the Arctic Ridge
before we run outta time!
Fine, but if you wanna leave,
ya gots to solve
my riddles first.
Didn't you just hear me?
We don't have time to solve
any more of your riddles!
I get that, but
what if I told you
I happen to know
this Wyverian feller?
[ALL gasp]
You know him?
The hunk second only to Navirou?
That's right, boys, I sure do.
And he's a
right-honest gentleman.
[LUTE] Well, that's great!
Can you take us to him?
Of course, I'm happy to.
Once you solve my riddles.
Ugh. C'mon, really?
There's no other choice,
Lute. We have to play.
Fine, guess we're stuck.
All right, pal, we'll answer
any riddle you've got!
Yeah! And in record time!
Navirou goes hard!
And that's a Navi-Rule.
Ride On!
Rathian!
[HUNTER A sighs]
The rest of the way
should be an easy hike.
You'll be fine!
We appreciate
everything you've done.
You saved our whole journey.
We won't forget your
help, Mister Hunter.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I almost forgot!
There's a hot springs
inn up ahead.
If I were you,
I'd stop and rest a bit.
Then go on to Gildegaran
at full-strength.
All right. Thanks again.
Oh, and if you do stop,
do you mind giving this
to the innkeeper for me?
[CHEVAL]
What is it?
That innkeeper and I go
back quite a long ways.
This box will be your
letter of introduction.
Thank you very much.
Congalala?
[RIDDLEMASTER]
Mh-hm!
You got another one right!
That's 20 in a row we got right!
Really!
Riddlemaster, isn't that enough?
No way, boy.
Not fair!
We answered your riddles,
tell us where the Wyverian is!
Yeah, what he said!
Or maybe you don't even really
know how to find the Wyverian
and you've just been lying
to us this whole time!
I ain't lyin'! I do know!
Liar!
You're only pretending to know
so you can have fun asking
us your dumb riddles!
[RIDDLEMASTER]
Don't be mean to me.
[NAVIROU]
Uh.
[LUTE] Way to crush
his spirit, Navirou.
I don't think the big
guy's ever felt smaller.
[AVINIA]
It's so pitiful somehow.
[NAVIROU]
Um, Navirou's sorry, you know.
Oh, yeah?
Are you sorry enough to solve
another one of my riddles?
Sure, whatever you want, sir.
But after this, will
you please, finally,
take us to meet the Wyverian?
Yup. I promise.
I'm warnin' ya though, this
one's a real head-scratcher.
Riddle number 2-1.
Now, the Wyverian
from the Arctic Ridge
can never get enough of me!
So who am I?
The Wyverian can't
get enough of it?
I have no idea.
This one barely
counts as a riddle.
[RIDDLEMASTER chuckles]
It's a toughie, all right,
but if y'all can't
figure this one out,
then y'all're goin'
nowhere fast!
Ah!
Lute, think!
I knew y'all'd
never get this 'un.
Aw, man! And it's the
last riddle, too!
[CHEVAL]
Lute!
[LUTE]
Whoa! Cheval!
[NAVIROU]
And the others!
Hey, Lute! Where've you been?
We've been worried
sick about you two!
I'm sorry, guys.
Well, all that matters
is we're back together.
That's right.
[LUTE]
Oh!
Avinia these are the
friends I told you about
and don't worry,
they're all Riders like me.
Nice to meet you.
Get this: She's a Rider, too!
You are? That's so great!
My name's Lilia.
Hello, I'm Mille.
I'm Hyoro!
And I'm Cheval. It's a pleasure.
Same to you.
I knew we'd meet back up
again after we got separated.
I was sure of it!
[NAVIROU]
Of course!
Navirou's navigational
skills never fail him!
[laughs]
Oh! Hold on.
A Hunter who helped us told me
to give this to the innkeeper.
Yeah, okay, he's that
big guy over there.
Uh, not so fast
I think ya forgot you were
smack dab in the middle
of answering one
of my riddles!
[LUTE]
Oh, yeah! The riddle thing.
[LILIA]
A riddle?
[CHEVAL]
Uh.
This is a gift from a Hunter
we met on the Arctic Ridge.
Well, this is it!
The right answer!
Hot Spring Dumplings!
[ALL]
Hot Spring Dumplings?
Those are just balls of moss!
Hits the spot! Deelicious.
Now this here is a hot spring
dumpling done just right!
Ball-a-steamed moss!
[laughs]
Well, great!
I'm glad you got what
you were looking for,
but what about us?
Yeah, what he said!
We've played your games
and you still won't take us
to meet our Wyverian hunk!
'Cause the Wyverian's
already here.
[gasps]
Wait, what?
[RIDDLEMASTER] The Wyverian
you all been lookin' for...
...is the Riddlemaster!
[ALL]
What?
Wait, hold on!
The Wyverian is tall.
And young!
And a total hunk!
Well, look at my skin.
The hot springs help make
it all smooth and clear.
So handsome!
And while I may not be a human,
I'm clearly a tall hunk
of somethin', right?
[ALL]
Uhh...
If you are the Wyverian,
then I need your help.
Please, give my dear
Frostfang his powers back.
Yep, I know all about
your situation, so--
Do you mind bringin' your
Monstie over here for me?
[ALL gasp]
All right, let's kick this off!
Now you riddle me this, kiddos,
what's big and loud
and needs to awaken?
The answer is: This 'un here!
What the heck is that?
He's doing his Frost Breath!
His special move!
[RIDDLEMASTER] Well, Miss,
looks like your Monstie
finally woke up!
Frostfang!
Oh, thank goodness. You're back
I don't know how I'll
ever repay you.
Thanks, Mister Wyverian!
Aw, you don't owe me nothin'
for anything now, Missy.
And Riddlemaster's
just fine with me.
Thanks again, Riddlemaster.
[RIDDLEMASTER chuckles]
Next time, we'll
do more riddles!
[LUTE]
You can count on that!
--[LUTE] Bye!
--[AVINIA] Goodbye!
Toodles!
[CHEVAL]
What a crazy couple of days.
[LILIA] And you were
injured, right, Avinia?
I was, but the
important thing is
you guys showed up and now
Frostfang's powers are back.
Good things happen when
you've got Navirou guiding you.
Yeah, I'd say the real help
came from that Hunter's
box of steamed moss.
This is it.
The Khezu's cave.
Ooh, Navirou doesn't
like these places!
Just put one foot in
front of the other,
and we'll make it
outta here alive.
Make sure to be careful.
The Khezu's known to
sneak up on its prey.
Nice knowing you, Hyoro.
Yeah, I get it. Okay.
[yelps]
[MILLE] Calm down.
It's just a drop of water.
[HYORO chuckles nervously]
Oh, right.
Uh. But why's it so sticky?
Hm?
[NAVIROU]
Huh?
[BOTH scream]
It's here!
Guys, look up!
[ALL scream]
The Khezu's really here!
Run!
Avinia! What are you doing?
Ride On! Barioth!
Avinia!
Whoa!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAVIROU]
Frostfang!
[LUTE]
Look at 'em go!
Ground Cyclone Attack!
Wow, those two have a
strong Kinship Attack!
Avinia! Awesome!
Nice work.
Go on! You're almost
there, guys.
Thank you.
But what are you going
to do now, Avinia?
We'll continue the
journey we've been on.
That means that just like you,
we'll try to stop
the Black Blight
and make sure it never
hurts anyone again.
That's great! Then I know
we'll see you soon!
I'm sure.
Until then, I'm glad we met,
Lute. Thanks to all of you!
You bet!
Avinia, it's not a "goodbye,"
it's a "see ya soon."
Thank you. Take care
of yourselves, you guys.
[LUTE]
And thank you, Frostfang!
[chuckles]
[LILIA]
It's so warm out here!
[HYORO] From winter to spring
in just a couple steps.
[MILLE]
Look at these cherry blossoms!
Guys we finally made it!
That's Gildegaran up ahead!
Yeah.
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
teaches you about Monsties.
Now then, Navirou hopes you have
your Media Trigger Smart
Phone app open for this.
And get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form a
Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU]
Our Monstie this time is: Khezu!
This creepy, pale beast
generates its own
electricity for attacks.
Khezu live in caves,
where they use thier prodigious
proboscis to sniff out prey.
Getting shocked
while riding one?
Navirou says, "No thanks!"
Navirou can't wait to see what
monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey! Lute here!
Well, we finally made it to
Gildegaran, and it's great!
Not only is it a magnet for
Hunters from all over the world,
it's got tons of
delicious food to eat!
Next time:
"Welcome to Gildegaran"!
Ride On!