Lute's out there.
He and others are on a Quest,
investigating the Black Blight.
This whole area is quicksand.
Then it's true.
Everything's just as
Chief Omna suspected,
this growing desert is the
result of a nearby Kinship Ore.
[exhales]
Oh yeah. Took me
a while, but I made it.
And the kids are still
somewhere out there, huh?
Well, what are you waiting for,
ya big lunk? Start looking!
[ALL sigh]
[BARROTH roaring]
[roars]
Why didn't I do it?
I shoulda beat it
when I had the chance!
But that Barroth
was just being controlled
by that scientist guy!
Either way,
it's a danger to people!
Rathi! It's time
to deal the final blow!
[RATHI roars]
Stay back! I'll handle it!
[BARROTH roaring]
Well, the boy
has that Flying Wyvern
obeying his every command!
Splendid!
Let's finish it off!
[LUTE]
Cheval!
That's enough!
Leave that monster alone!
It isn't Blighted!
No, Lute. You'll never
protect anyone
if you think like that.
Let's go, Rathi!
Scorching Slice!
O-ho! The more I see,
the more I like.
I do think this Cheval boy
shares our vision!
[ITSY-BITS]
O-ho!
It couldn't move
with that controller on it.
But if it got
in the wrong hands,
it could do a lot of damage.
[DAN]
Hey!
[LUTE, CHEVAL]
Why is Dan here?
And Genie, too?
Hey! Long time no see!
You in top form?
Oh, yeah, the sweltering
heat brings out our best.
Oh, shut up.
It's good to see you again, Dan,
but why'd you'd come
all the way out here?
We'd been hearing
rumors of more monsters
stricken with the Black Blight,
so Chief Omna sent us
to help where ever we could.
If a neighbor's in danger,
Hakum Village will always
be there to help.
So, of course, we made the trek
as soon as possible.
Gamigami only came
'cause he thinks
Tropical Berries
grow around here.
Um, well yes, but no.
I mean, yes,
I'm here for the berries.
Who wouldn't be?
They're delicious!
But I'm also here
to help the villages
--and so on and so forth.
--Hey, you two. What's wrong?
What?
You've lost your playful spark!
Did something happen?
No, things are fine.
Yeah, fine, Lute and I
are just doing
what we both feel is right.
We've heard rumors that you guys
have taken on some Quests.
No! Uh. Yeah.
And how many Monsties
do you have now?
Um, I-I still
only have my Bulldrome.
[sighs]
So, despite your
recent journeys,
you still have a long way to go
before you're an expert Rider.
[HYORO sobs, sighs]
Well, I still only
have my Aptonoth.
You don't know how hard
we've been working out here.
How dare you
question our progress!
You can't talk--
Come on, kids. I wanna see
a friendly reunion.
I agree! It's time
for a celebration!
But to do it right, we need
some Tropical Berries.
This is the second time
you've mentioned
those berries, Gamigami.
What's the deal?
Yes, well, they're very--
I'm sorry to interrupt!
I think we should head back.
I'm worried the sand will
bury our whole camp site.
Ah! Navirou doesn't want
his donuts to get sandy!
That sweet glaze!
[ALL laughing]
[NAVIROU]
Don't laugh at Navirou's fears!
To think,
controlling the Monsters
and making them
fight each other. Well then.
I'd say it's almost
as impressive as
what those young Riders
are capable of.
Taking down a Blighted
Cephadrome is no easy task.
And we couldn't do
a thing to help.
Ha! We could've
taken it down ourselves,
without incident.
We just gave them
this little victory
to be friendly.
What really matters is that
the quicksand has stopped,
and we get to cross it
off our "to-do" list!
[laughing]
What in the blazes?
I don't get it.
Why is it still here?
[GENTOR]
Hmm, I don't understand.
We let you slay
the Blighted Cephadrome,
but nothing has changed.
Why is the quicksand
still out there?
It just means that there
must be another cause for it.
Yes true, but what
could that cause be?
We're not sure,
but we have an idea.
[GENTOR]
Hm?
Chief Nolma,
have you ever encountered
a glowing stone around here?
[gasps]
The bluntness of
your question surprises me,
but yes, we do
have a sacred stone
that we hide from outsiders
like yourselves.
Chief Nolma!
We're in a crisis!
And without help from other
villagers, even Riders,
we will be overcome
by this menace!
Yes, Chief.
[NOLMA] Surely, it is
this spirit of cooperation
against a common threat
that has brought you
all here from
your own distant land.
That's right, Chief,
and that glowing
stone your village
has is what Riders
call "Kinship Ore."
If you'll allow us,
we need to see
if the Black Blight has infected
yours, before it's too late.
Ya see, back in our village,
we found out the only way
to stop the advance
of the Black Blight was to
purify our own Kinship Ore.
Purify it?
And I assume this ritual
requires a Rider's powers?
You are correct, Chief Nolma.
[sighs]
I understand.
If that is what must be done,
you have my permission.
Thank you, Chief Nolma.
Well, glad we figured that out.
Have a nice day folks!
I will find them!
No matter what it takes,
those berries will be mine.
Hey, Gamigami?
Is this that berry thing again?
Oh, yeah.
All right, listen up.
If you find even a single berry,
you run over
and tell me right away!
[KIDS]
Huh?
From what I hear,
Tropical Berries taste best
fresh off the vine!
[LUTE, NAVIROU]
What you hear?
Have you ever actually
eaten these berries before?
Not yet, I saw some once
though, when I was a kid.
What? Then how do
you know they taste good?
'Cause they have to!
Now you listen and listen good:
Tropical Berries
are a precious fruit
that only grows in the shadows
of large plants and rocks.
You'll find the vines clinging
to cliff faces and in valleys,
the round fruits
glistening like red jewels!
And their scent! It's so sweet,
you'll quicken your step
the second it hits your nose!
As for their actual taste,
it's better than
three donuts combined!
[NAVIROU]
Three donuts?
No! It's more like five
donuts of deliciousness!
[NAVIROU]
You're--You're serious?
Say no more!
Navirou will lead the way!
Berries, ho!
If Navirou's going that way,
then we should go
in the opposite direction.
Oh, right. I almost
forgot about Navi's
terrible sense of direction!
That really takes me back.
Yeah, doesn't it?
Ha! Right, Cheval?
Hm? Oh, yeah, sure.
But seriously guys,
don't let your guard down yet.
Out here, a Blighted monster
could show up at any time.
[NAVIROU]
Whoa! Whoa!
The berries are here!
What? Ooh! All right!
Wait.
I'm afraid that right there
is a Mockberry Cactus!
That's a fruit
that doesn't mess around!
As soon as you pick 'em,
they grow spines.
--[NAVIROU yelps]
--[GAMIGAMI] Yep.
If you're unfortunate
enough to get pricked,
you swell up in blinding pain!
[NAVIROU]
Owww!
Ow-wee, ow-wee, ow-wee, ow-wee!
It's difficult
for novice enthusiasts
to tell the difference
between the two types.
Uh, did we pack medicine?
--What's he doing over there?
--This is so boring.
Is that--?
It's quicksand!
That's not the only thing!
There's something under it!
A monster, you think?
The bigger question is
what kind of monster.
Yeah, I wonder...
A Daimyo Hermitaur,
or Cephadrome again?
Let's go, guys!
Cheval, wait.
The sun is already setting.
Whatever that is, we should
face it in the daylight.
Let's find a secure spot
for a camp site.
I saw a rock formation
back there that'll be perfect.
All right, let's move out!
[KIDS]
Right!
[LUTE]
Roger that!
Ride On!
Rathian!
[fire crackling]
[sighs] Even after looking
the whole day, still no berries.
There, there. Navirou will
sniff them out tomorrow!
We still don't have
a good guess
of what monster we saw
under that quicksand.
What do guys think?
[BOTH]
No matter what monster it is...
I'll save it!
I'll fight it!
You serious?
If it's been Blighted,
we'll have no choice!
I mean, yeah, I know.
I'm with you on that, but--
All right!
Cheval, that's not what I'm--
[DAN]
Boys, that's enough!
What I'm hearing
is you're both hungry.
You stay right here.
Perfectly roasted!
Even my grilling's in top form!
Eat up! And don't
forget to share.
[laughs]
Listen up you two!
Quarrels are all
part of being young.
But we're fine.
We're not really fighting.
Coming up as Riders together
makes you the very
closest of friends,
but also the fiercest rivals.
It's okay if you butt heads,
so long as you remember
at the end of the day,
you're both still Riders
and you share the same goal
of stopping the Black Blight!
Kinship binds us to Monsties
as well as each other!
You understand?
--Yes, sir.
And if you do have
a problem with each other,
get it out in the open.
The best friends are
the most honest ones!
Don't forget to eat, boys!
It's so cold.
[LUTE]
It's freezing.
You'd never believe this place
is a furnace during the day.
The desert's
always cold at night.
[exhales]
[CHEVAL]
I like the clear skies out here.
It makes the moon
and the stars seem so close.
Oh, wow!
I think I can touch 'em!
But you can't
touch them. It's impossible.
Hey, you don't
know that for sure.
I bet if I jump hard enough,
I can grab the moon.
Hi-yah!
[hollers]
You never change, Lute.
Oh, come on.
Y'know, you used
to goof around, too!
[BOTH gasp]
The Black Blight!
Guys, look!
Ride On!
Qurupeco!
Let's Ride On!
Yian Kut-Ku!
Now Ride On!
Popo!
We'll go stop the monster.
You stay back here.
Protect Lilia!
Got it!
[DAN]
Let's go!
[GENIE, STONE]
Sir!
I say we start
this fight off with a bang!
[roars]
--[NAVIROU screaming]
--Diablos?
And it's infected
with the Black Blight!
Why'd it have to be a Diablos?
[roars]
[ALL yelling]
Find a way to get its attention,
then draw it away
from the group!
[BOTH]
Right!
[roaring]
Watch out!
[STONE groans]
Stone!
It's quicksand!
[GENIE groans]
[DAN yells]
You all right?
I'll live.
--[distant groaning]
--Yian Kut-Ku!
This is bad!
Time to Ride On!
Basarios!
Laser Ambush, now!
Did it work?
All right!
[DIABLOS growls, roars]
[yells]
Aw, man. You okay?
Lute, hit him one more time!
Are you ready? Basarios?
It's gone!
Where'd it go? Ah!
[LILIA, CHEVAL]
Lute, no!
[ALL yell]
[ALL screaming]
[gasping]
[LILIA groans]
Lilia!
Are you okay?
My leg.
Over here, hurry up!
[roars]
I'll never hold back again.
They all must be destroyed!
[GAMIGAMI]
Cheval.
Right now your only mission
is to take care of Lilia,
you understand me?
Yes, sir.
Here I come!
Hold tight, guys,
I'll distract it!
[ALL]
Right!
All right, see if this works.
Hit it with the call!
[blares]
[BARROTH roars]
[HYORO, CHEVAL gasp]
It's a Barroth!
Yes! Now's our
chance to fall back!
[roars]
[BOTH roaring]
Genie, Stone,
take good care of Lilia.
All right, we'll hurry
back to Gildegaran.
[DAN] Agreed.
We'll follow close behind.
Understood.
'Kay, let's pack our
stuff and get on the road.
[KIDS]
Right.
Remember what
I told you earlier.
You two can butt heads
all you want,
but at the end of the day,
that fighting won't outweigh
the fact that
you're on the same team.
Yeah, but we're
not fighting, right?
What's wrong, Cheval?
You okay?
Monsters kill people.
Like my mom.
[gasps]
[CHEVAL]
These tragedies happen
because Lute puts monsters
ahead of people!
Like Lilia getting hurt.
Or our village getting attacked.
And my mother dying.
[NAVIROU screaming]
Now what?
Is it another Diablos attack?
They're here!
Hold on! What?
[NAVIROU, GAMIGAMI]
We found the Tropical Berries!
[GAMIGAMI]
Mmm! Gorgeous!
Ah! I've waited my whole life
to taste this moment!
Down the hatch!
[BOTH]
Mmmm! So good!
[GAMIGAMI]
Makes me glad to be alive!
[NAVIROU] It really is as good
as five--no, a dozen donuts!
[ALL]
These are delicious!
Well, of course they are!
Didn't you listen?
Lucky for us, morning's when
they're at their best tasting!
Cheval! Get over here
and join in the fun!
No, thanks. I'm good.
[GAMIGAMI]
Here.
Who knows how long
we'll be tromping around
on this desert Quest.
Before we get on
each other's nerves,
it's best to do
something as a group--
like eating the same thing!
Or you'll never
get the better of him.
C'mon, you want
more people to get hurt?
These are good. Thank you.
What, you thought
they were pretending
these are the best berries ever?
Go on, have more!
[CHEVAL]
Okay!
[GAMIGAMI laughing]
[LUTE]
Yummy!
[NAVIROU]
Monstie Manual !
Here comes the part
where Navirou
tells you about Monsties.
All right, Navirou
hopes you have
your Media Trigger
Smart Phone app open.
Better get your eggs out,
too, while you're at it!
Now it's time to form
a Kinship with our Monsties!
The moment of new life!
Awaken!
[NAVIROU] Our Monstie
this time is: Basarios!
This monster's body
is rock hard!
In fact, when it
digs in and stays still,
it even looks like a rock!
And the heat rays
it shoots from its mouth
send other monsters running!
Navirou can't wait to see
what monster hatches next time!
[LUTE]
Hey, guys! Lute here!
Well, we're all
back in Gildegaran,
safe and sound
and enjoying a festival.
But guess who we ran into?
My Rathalos, Ratha!
Next time:
"Sky Wyvern, Land Wyvern."
Ride On!