[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
To find out if
Yua's accusation
that I'm the
General was true...
I went to the
same hospital
I used to go to in
elementary school.
But... I didn't
learn anything new
'cause I was too
scared to ask...
I wanted to do something
about it so I investigated
the image the
General sent me
and did a little research...
Turns out a local
band predicted
the second New Gen crime...
The lead singer's
name is FES...
After listening
to her song,
there's no doubt in my mind,
she must've
known something.
After that I was told
another New Gen incident
had already taken place...
And the dying message left at
the scene of the crime...?
I know it all
too well.
It's the same phrase I
often whisper in my mind.
Hey, did you see those pictures
from the Vampire killer?
Yeah, I did!
Did you see the message?
"Those eyes,
whose are they?"
Hey, pretty lady!
What's up...?
Wanna play whose
eyes are those?
You're an idiot.
Ah, come on, baby.
Get set... Go!
Those eyes,
whose are they? !
-I won!
-Oh, man!
Whose eyes are those?
It's not me...!
It just can't be me!
You.
Do you see it?
Answer me.
I want you to tell
me if you can see it!
Please... What the
hell are you doing? !
So I was right all along.
Don't hurt me...
I'm sorry...
I didn't see anything...
I swear!
Liar... I know you did...
I know 'cause you were
staring at it just now.
No... Please I
really didn't...!
I didn't see-!
I'll make you
tell me the truth.
Well now... How's that...?
Is it good...?
Do you like it?
What's wrong...?
Don't like it?
Oh no!
Fess up...
Tell the truth...
You see it, don't you?
What...? Was
that a delusion?
That's right...
You should be scared...
I am pointing a
di-sword at you.
Di-sword...? What's that?
It's true...
You've been gathered,
just like me ...
Tell me, have you
witnessed an error yet...?
Let me know if you do.
I'm Sena Aoi and
I'm a third year...
I'll be at the
train station.
It's those eyes...
Whose are they, my man?
Just kidding...
Isn't it nuts how
popular that saying is?
Hey...! You remember FES
from that Phantasm concert
we went to, right?
Those eyes,
whose are they?
Well guess what
I found out...
There's this girl,
Ayase Kishimoto.
She hardly ever
comes to class,
but she's one of the hottest
chicks I've ever seen.
This Ayase girl's really
FES, the lead singer.
Man, how awesome
is that, huh? !
To think a super
hot rock star's
actually a student
at our school...!
I suppose it's
my destiny
to make her fall
in love with me.
Well, speak of the devil.
You're about to see
a master at work...
Here's a lesson . I sure
hope you're taking notes.
Ayase. Hi there,
I'm Daisuke...
Nice to meet you.
You know...
I was at a Phantasm concert
just the other night...
And your voice...? It
was just incredible.
I swear, it blew me away.
By the way.
I'm thinking about
starting my own band,
and I was wondering if you
might want to get together
sometime to give me
a few pointers...
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh no...! She
looked at me again!
Sorry, I already
have someone I like.
Ooh, really...? It isn't
me by any chance, is it?
He's right there.
Who, him?
I, uh...
You came to my
concert, didn't you?
I felt it at first glance.
You are the one I'm
destined to be with.
I know it... You...
and I.
We will get married.
What...? Married?
What's wrong?
Uh... I don't, uh-
I don't know.
That must've
been a delusion.
Hurry up.
You must find it...
If you can find your
sword you will be saved.
Damn.
I thought she was into me.
Sword?
Finally, I got the new edition
of the Seira action figure...!
I'd better get home
as quickly as I can
to give her a
thorough inspection.
Do you have a minute?
Here's my identification
in case you're curious.
The police?
You haven't heard
anything about
what the kids are calling
"New Generation
Madness", have you?
Uh... Sort of.
Right...
Then I'm assuming you've
heard of the so-called
'staking' incident,
is that correct?
See, me and my partner here,
we're looking
for a witness...
Ah... I forgot...
Could you tell
me your name?
I see...
What's the matter? You're not
gonna answer us?
Uh... Um, Takumi... Nishijo.
So your full name's
Takumi Nishijo?
That looks like a Suimei
uniform you got on...
What year are you?
Two.
Huh? What's that...?
I couldn't hear
you... Say it again.
Uh... second year, yeah.
Ah... I see, you're a junior.
So... Mr. ishijo...
Can you please tell
me where you were
and what you were doing
on the 29th of September...
Between six and ten p.m.?
Does he want my alibi...?
Wait, does this
mean I'm a suspect?
Listen, kid... Don't worry,
we don't think you had
anything to do with this.
Look, I didn't do it.
Oh...?
What exactly
didn't you do?
I saw it!
I saw it happen!
The staking...! I
saw the killer, too...!
She had blood all
over her hands...!
Stakes pierced through his body.
It was horrible...
She saw me.
She's a wicked devil...!
She's not human...
Not... at... all...
A demon...
And she'll murder us all!
Her mind...
She has the power to
see into the future!
And she's got
everybody fooled.
She goes to school with
me and she's in my class.
Help! Please protect me!
A demon... This is
really good info...
It'll give us
something to go on.
And... I... promise,
it's the truth.
Oh, you don't have to
tell me. I get it...
It's valuable intel...
We need to get back to
headquarters immediately
and see if we
have any leads.
Wait, is this some kinda joke?
Uh... right, sir... Sure.
Now... Mr. ishijo...
I need your contact information
so we can stay in touch.
Wait, what for?
Well, we have to
protect you, don't we...?
Unless of course you wanna
handle that demon on your own.
Oh... okay.
Well... Thank you
for your time...
And don't worry,
there's no reason for
you to be afraid...
The police will
keep you safe.
Take care!
Finally.
I have been waiting
for this for so long!
Oh, they got the
skirt just right!
Oh, this is amazing!
This is the best
version by far!
You pervert... Geez!
Sorry...
Didn't mean to
scare you...
I knocked on the
door, you know.
Please don't hurt me...!
I'm so sorry I tattled
on you to those cops!
The cops?
Yes... That's why you
came here, isn't it...?
'Cause I talked to them...
I... told them about the
staking and everything else!
That again...?
Taku... You said Blood
Tune's Post Awakened version
came out today...
I came over to see
Seira, that's all.
Listen, we need to talk...
Taku has been acting
really strange
and avoiding me lately.
Hey... don't do that.
Takki... You be nice to Rimi,
she's one of your
best friends...
Silly boy.
Give me back my Seira...
Don't you touch my wife!
Oh, my love...
You're safe.
Um, hey Taku?
What the hell...?
Having a romantic comedy
moment with that demon girl
isn't my idea
of a good time!
Sorry...
I think we got a
bit carried away...
I should probably go home.
Taku... Are you coming
to school tomorrow?
I sure hope you
decide to go...
I get lonely
when you don't.
Will she be watching me...?
Is she planning on keeping
tabs on me every day
to make sure I don't do
anything she doesn't like?
General.
This doctor...
I've got to get him
to remember me...
If he can help me...
Maybe I'll finally
get some answers.
Well... Have a
seat, young man.
Wait, I... Um...
Where's my normal doctor?
Dr. akashina's no
longer with us.
Well, where is he?
He recently collapsed
due to stress
and needed time off.
He's been at
home ever since.
It's a trick.
Part of the demon
girl's master plan!
I'm alone...
Why isn't there
anybody on my side?
Why doesn't anyone care,
why won't someone help me...?
How come these terrible things
always have to happen to me?
I don't care who...
I just need someone to
reach out a helping hand.
Hurry up...
You must find it...
If you can find your
sword, you will be saved.
Sword... A sword...!
I have got to
get my sword!
It doesn't look like it's
a weapon from an anime...
If I just type in sword,
I don't get anything...
Just a bunch of gaming
walk through sites...
This is gonna
take forever...
I need something to
narrow the search.
You should be scared...
I am pointing a
di-sword at you.
The di-sword!
That's what she called it!
Yay!
"Di-swords, or 'dark
swords' were mysterious
weapons created in
Ancient Europe...
According to the legend,
these swords were crafted
by an infamous Devil King
who used them to arm an
infantry of ferocious
Black Knights."...
King Gladiale?
"The energy of
these swords derives
from the negative
emotions of human beings.
Allegedly, the di-swords
grew too powerful
and began to eat
away at the hearts
of the Black Knights
who wielded them...
However, unlike the majority
of holy or demonic weapons,
a di-sword cannot be seen
with the naked eye."
Crazy.
What is this, some
sort of a myth...?
Look at the
picture on here,
it's so plain looking.
That Sena girl's sword didn't
look anything like this.
"I bought one of these.
Apparently it's
called a di-sword.
It's a sketchy
part of Shibuya
but it's well
worth the trip.
Go to Town Vanguard and
buy one for yourself.
"Wow, you can buy a di-sword.
Hey, I don't think that
Town Vanguard place
is too far from here...
If you really need it,
you should go buy one!
Take your time
and look around.
Is that it?
I don't know about this,
what if it's a fake...?
Yeah, maybe I
shouldn't buy it...
Come on... Look
at this thing,
it's a big piece of junk...
But maybe when it
recognizes me as its master,
it'll transform
into something magical
and show me its true power.
I think I've been watching
way too much anime...
Ah... What should I do?
Ten thousand cash and
you get something extra.
And by the way...?
That is the last one.
Come on in!
Last one.
All right...!It's the last
one, must be my lucky day.
How can that Sena girl carry
around a di-sword all the time?
People were looking
at me like I'm an idiot.
Someone's here...!
No, what if it's
the demon girl? !
Taku?
What are you doing?
It's you.
You scared me.
Here you go.
Geez... You're a nerd,
you know that?
What is that?
Some kind of anime toy?
Hey, how's the phone...?!
You like it...?
You know you could
at least call home
and let us know
you're alive...!
Oh, do you have some tea?
I'd like some of
the hot kind...
Oh, wow... What is that thing?
Ooh, what a
pretty bracelet!
Did you buy this, too?
It came with the sword.
It's cool...
Hey, let me
have this, okay?
-Huh?
-Why not...?
Would it kill you to
give me something...?
Come on, give
me a present!
-Oh fine.
-Really...? ...
Yay!
What do you
think, Taku...?
How's it look?
I really like this, so no matter
what you say, it's mine...!
As a matter of fact, this
might be the first time
you've given me a present,
so how about that? !
You're finished with your
business here, right...?
Go home.
I really don't appreciate
your attitude...
Besides, what
about the oranges...?
And I do recall asking
you for some tea!
Make tea at home.
Suit yourself! . . . !
If I'm in the way,
then I'll leave!
I hate your guts...! I
hope you choke to death
on orange peels,
you stupid jerk!
You deserved that!
It's broken, my only hope!
Yo... Taku...
What's up, takin' a break
from otaku life...?
Hey, what's wrong...?
You in power
nap mode already?
Leave him alone!
The devil girl.
Taku needs some
peace and quiet...
Just look at
how tired he is.
It's from playing too
many video games...
Maybe you shouldn't
be so easy on him.
You're the enemy of all
women, you know that...?
And I'm never nice to
idiotic people like you...!
There, it's time
for school to start...
The teacher's coming.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay... Folks, we have a
transfer student starting today.
It's her first day...
Everyone say hi.
Well... It looks like
she's nervous...
Students, this is
Kozue, she's new here...
Be nice to her now, okay?
Go on... Take your seat.
He's just like me.
I'm so glad we're
in the same class.
Wait a sec.
Was she just
talking to me?
Hey, uh... Taku.
What did she say to you?
Damn it! She's a machine,
she's never gonna give up!
I'm sorry I'm curious...
When that transfer
student walked by you,
I swore I heard her
whisper something...
But I didn't hear
what though...
Do you two know each
other from somewhere?
I always assumed you weren't
interested in real women,
only in anime girls...
But maybe you are
interested after all.
Well if that's the case...
You're not by any chance
interested in... me maybe?
I just can't figure
this girl out...
Is she trying to murder me
or does she wanna
make me her boyfriend?
I'll stop
talking to her...
If I don't, I'm
gonna go insane!
Wait... Taku!
I've had enough...
I can't take this...
And the di-sword I
bought turned out
to be completely useless!
I can't go to the
hospital anymore...
I can't even go
to my own school.
Yua's at the
internet café...
And every time I get
online there's the General.
I shouldn't go outside,
I should stay in
my base forever.
Where'd they go,
what happened?
No way.
No... It can't be real!
This is a dream!
An illusion!
There's no way this
could be reality...!
Sure, I wanted to live
a quiet peaceful life
where people
didn't bother me...!
But that doesn't mean I
want to be completely alone
in a world with
nobody else in it!
Somebody's here...
I'm not alone,
somebody else is here!
Who are you?
I've been waiting a long time.
But... I just...
I... Where did...
I don't understand, why
are we alone...?
The streets are empty.
Where'd the people
go...? Tell me...
What is this about...?
Why is this happening?
I suppose I could give
you that information...
But tell me, did you
receive my message?
Message...?
Who are you?
Those eyes,. whose
are they? Right?
The time is here...
Awaken. Now...!
If you don't, many
people are going to die.
Wait... Who in
the hell are you?
You know...
You call me the General.
The General...?
This guy is
really the General?
Don't forget.
Be strong...
No matter what,
you can't give up.
Taku
What?
Hey.
Taku, Can you
walk...? Get up.
No... Stay away!
Hey... everything will be
fine, just come with me.
You... You were the one...!
You showed me that delusion,
didn't you, you devil...!
You did it...!
You... You took
over my mind, demon...
To destroy me...! To
leave me for dead!
I am gonna kill
you... demon...!
I'll go back to my base
and get my di-sword ...
I don't care if
it is broken!
Just stop it...!
It's too dangerous
to stay here...
The light.
It already turned red.
She wasn't trying to
kill me after all...?
But why is she helping me?
If I continue to feel this
kind of warmth in my heart
for her...
If she keeps staring
at me so sweetly...
My thoughts...
My thoughts will
begin to waver...
I'll start to trust her.
Taku... Please, I want
you to come with me...
Okay?
Thank goodness!
I'm really sorry.
But wow, you scared
me back there...!
I saw you lying
down on the ground
right in the middle of
the intersection...!
And if that light
hadn't been green,
who knows what would
have happened to you?
Bye.
Wait... Should I
walk you home...?
Since you're not
feeling well?
You sure?
Um. Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
[Music]
Those eyes, whose are they?