[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
Rimi finally confided
the truth to me.
I'm not supposed to exist,
I'm a being created by the
delusions of a gigalomaniac,
the real Takumi Nishijo.
Rimi...
She knows a lot
of things I don't.
Something else is happening
in a place I can't see.
I hope Nanami's okay
after being kidnapped?
In the end...
I'm nothing but a
delusive existence...
So I decided not
to care anymore.
But then...
I had company...
The General appeared
before me again.
Tell me...
Tell me who you are.
I am you, Takumi.
You're the one
who created me...
I'm your delusion,
aren't I...?
You've been watching
me this whole time...
From the very start,
haven't you?
If this continues,
the world will end...
The mind of
everyone on earth
will be controlled
by Noah II.
But I don't care...
None of this has
anything to do with me...
I'm begging you...
Please erase me...
I don't wanna deal with
this, just kill me!
This whole thing
is my fault...
Because I envisioned
IR2 in my delusion...
I created you because
my body's weak
and I lost my ability
to move freely...
You're here to do all
the things I can't.
This isn't my problem...
It's not my fight!
Rimi...
She was captured trying
to rescue your sister.
Don't you see...?
Rimi has been trying
to save my life.
It's all for me.
Look at the sky...
It's so blue...
Why is that?
It makes me want to cry.
Because you wished for it.
But I didn't wish for it.
Maybe it was me...
It's amazing this is
your mental landscape...
But it's also mine
at the same time.
What does that mean?
Are you another "me"?
No.
Well then who are you...?
There's never been anything
but darkness...
But then you came...
And the darkness
vanished...
And then the
sky appeared...
The big blue sky.
Our delusions matched
up and synchronized.
Oh.
Before now, I'd never seen
anything as beautiful as this...
My world was
always black...
An empty dark void.
What about the real sky?
Don't you think you'd
like to see it some day?
Where is that sky...?
Do you know?
As long as you wish
for it, it's anywhere.
But how do I wish for it?
Light is nothing
more than waves...
Electromagnetic waves...
Humans perceive
these oscillations
as different colors...
First pick out a color...
then send it to
your dead spot...
If you can...
you'll be able to create the
color of the world you desire.
Yes?
I came back
here to see you.
Did you get to see
the real sky yet?
Rimi...
Why did she get
so close to me?
She was monitoring
your actions...
Watching over you.
She kept close
tabs on anyone
who tried to approach you...
Everything she did was to
prevent your awakening.
Because once that happens,
my life on this
earth will be over.
I didn't want Rimi
to get involved...
but she sure
is a nosy girl.
Who's responsible...?
Who kidnapped the girls?
The man in charge
of Project Noah...
The one behind it all...
Genichi Norose.
Wait, I know him...
Yeah, from Nozomi.
And this isn't the first
time he's held Rimi captive.
Of course that
didn't stop her.
Please don't...
There's no need for
you to go this far.
There is...
After all you've done,
let me help...
Also...
I don't want Taku
mixed up in this thing.
He's weak...
He's not confident,
he's hopelessly pitiful...
He's the type of guy
that normal girls
wouldn't think twice about
or even give the
time of day...
Even so...
In my heart I
had feelings...
feelings of joy...
like all I wanted was to
spend more time with him.
Well... I'm sure
he enjoyed it too.
I sure hope so.
Well then...
I've got to get going.
Rimi, don't!
I'm telling you,
I'll be fine...
You don't need to
worry about a thing...
I'll settle this,
I'm going to take care
of everything, Takumi...
Bye.
Rimi really is
nosy, isn't she?
How about I stay
with you then?
I shut myself in home base
and went out of my way
not to talk to anybody...
It's like the minute I
was born into this world
I was already dead...
But Rimi...
She was always there,
right by my side.
She comforted my mind
when I trembled,
overcome with fear...
She supported me...
She encouraged me...
She was kind and taught
me human warmth
even though I'm
just a delusion...
She could've easily
let me die...
But she protected me.
I remember every
detail so clearly...
All of Rimi's
little gestures.
Her soft breath...
The sparkle of her eyes...
Her sweet voice...
And her tender warmth.
I see...
I've always been
in love with her.
Even if everything
else was a delusion...
If it was all fake...
My feelings for her and
the love that I felt...
It was real.
It's time you
saved the world.
You don't understand,
I'm not a hero.
I am truly sorry for pushing
this onto you so unfairly...
But you doing this
is our only option!
Don't you know it's stupid
to apologize to yourself?
When people have a chance
to realize their mistakes,
they can do
things over...
So... because you
and I are one...
I hate you for what
you've done to me.
That's funny,
because I envy you.
I'm not doing this to be
your second chance, okay?
The only reason I'm
doing this is for me.
To discover my purpose!
I'll figure out why I'm
here on my own terms!
What is that?
I finally found my light...
my di-sword.
I'm going to end
this thing...
Once and for all.
Go, Taku.
Find the porters who
are causing this riot
and destroy the machines
they're carrying...
Without their equipment,
the people will relax...
Their biorhythms
will settle down.
Porters?
They serve as terminal
units for Noah II...
You've already
seen hints of them.
Wait, I've seen them?
My company is calling
them porters...
To put it another way,
you might think of them
as a mind control team.
I see...
Have I been reading
his thoughts
all along without knowing it?
Read the porters' minds...
You must hurry.
Divine light save us...
Divine light save us.
Divine light save us?
Divine light save us...
Where are they?
He's right there!
What...? Oh no!
Take this!
The divine light save us.
There's one more...
But where?
Wait, she's from
the hospital.
Show these people.
Expose her for the
monster she is.
What do you mean,
what has she done?
No, Hazuki ...
Please you can
still let me go...
Don't do this.
The divine light
will save you.
Salvation's here.
Hazuki...
What are you going to do?
No please don't do this...
Please don't...
These are your
memories, not mine.
You're behind everything,
you're the New Gen criminal!
That's not all.
Tell me why...
Why'd you brutally murder
all those people...?
Tell me, Grim.
Hello, Knight Heart.
Everything I did was
for one purpose,
to awaken your
gigalomaniac powers.
What did you just say?
Don't you see,
Knight Heart...?
These were direct orders from
the great founder of our sect.
Your founder?
Wait, that stake, it's...
May the divine light
save you, my friend.
The Third Melt...!
It's already happening.
According to the
Meteorological Agency,
the earthquake that struck
Shibuya yesterday
was comparable in size to the
Great Kanto Earthquake...
a 7.8 in magnitude.
So far only 233 deaths
have been reported,
but according to authorities
the final death toll may
ultimately surpass 30,000.
Ayase...
Let's hurry, we should
get somewhere safe.
No way...
King Gladiale has
already awoken...
We have to meet up with
the other Black Knights
as soon as possible.
Yeah, but...
Who's that?
Huh? Hey wait, that's Takumi's
younger sister Nanami.
Takumi's what?
Hey, Yua...
Rimi's in trouble, we
have to do something!
Rimi is another one of
the seven Black Knights.
What...? She is...? Really?
Please just listen...
I don't want you getting
any closer to him...
I don't want
Taku to awaken!
Have you forgotten
you're one too...?
All the Knights
must join together.
I can manage this situation
on my own, thank you.
Your feelings are very
inspiring, truly they are...
But you must understand,
this is not what the
Great Will desires...
It's not what I
desire either.
I cannot let you shoulder
everything by yourself.
She's one of us.
So where is Rimi right now?
Hey are you okay...?
Hang in there.
Thank you.
Everyone who can
move, lend a hand!
Right!
This is the power
of Noah II...?
General
General!
You have got to get
it together, General.
It is the Great Will
Leading us to pleasure
I know that voice.
Will you come?
Follow
And love will flow.
Takumi.
Ayase!
There are two more here...
Your sister's one.
Nanami...?
All right.
Your di-sword...! Finally!
This rubble is nothing...
There's a lot of it,
but each piece is small...
It's not heavy...
I can save all
three of them!
Nanami!
Taku.
Thank goodness.
Nanami.
You came.
You're okay.
You're such a good
brother, Taku...
Thank you.
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but I'm not actually
your real brother.
What?
How are ya, Taku? !
Hey, you've been skipping
meals again, mister...!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
You have to eat!
Sorry, Nanami.
What's the
matter with you?
Listen... Something happened,
and I have to hide...
so you can't...
come here anymore,
do you understand?
No I don't,
what do you mean?
Go, Nanami.
I forgot...
How could that happen?
I can't take this...
I know all I ever did was
nag you about stuff...
But I never once
wanted to forget...
I'm sorry...
Please believe me, I swear,
I never wanted to
forget you, Takumi
Go on...
He and I are one
and the same...
Follow him...
He's your brother now.
Taku?
Hey wait!
Listen...
Maybe you and I aren't
really related after all...
And I know I
always give you crap
'cause you're
an anime nerd...
But still...
No matter what happens,
you're my brother!
Thank you so much, Nanami.
Taku.
Well, well, it looks like
you've finally awakened.
But now will you be able to make
it all the way here to me...?
The hard part
is yet to come.
Help me.
Rimi's in big trouble,
she needs our help.
I know...
And I'm going to
rescue her right now...
Take good care of him.
I, uh... Takumi.
Huh?
I know that I've said a lot of
really terrible things to you...
I'm so sorry.
You remember the Seira
figurines at my place...?
I want you to have them.
They're yours.
You... are going to
defeat King Gladiale?
If you mean Noah II,
then yeah...
That's the plan.
Then I'm coming with you.
And me, too!
What's this?
-Takumi.
-Taku.
Stand back... You
leave this one to me!
If this is enough to
repent for my sins!
Quick! Get Gladiale!
On my way!
I can't walk any more.
Hey what's wrong?
At last, I finally found you.
For the past six months
I've been dreaming
of this day...
I've wondered how I would
settle things with you.
Thank you.
Why would you thank me?
Because however you
settle things...
it will be the ultimate
atonement for all my sins...
I deserve this.
In that case,
let's get right to it.
Just one question...
How could you do something
so terrible to them?
I mean they were
your own family.
Trying to explain away
what happened makes no sense...
And besides, nothing
I can say to you
will change
what I did, Sena.
Your way of running
away again, huh?
Coward...
That's all you are.
You still expect something.
Everything's an electronic
device, including people...
You're the one who said
that, Sena, not me.
Sena... Stay strong,
they're attacking your mind.
The things you feel
about me are nothing...
Just another
electronic signal.
Sena!
Uh-oh, looks like
I missed that one...
But still if you
consider the distance,
it's actually not that
terrible of a shot.
Why would he protect me...?
After all this.
These words,
they're meaningless...
But you're too
honest, Sena...
And that's why
I adore you...
I love you the way you are...
Don't say that.
Oh well, it doesn't really
matter, does it...?
After all, I suppose
two dead Hatanos
are better than one,
am I right?
Don't stand in my way!
My sister...
This can't be...
When I saw my mother and
sister in that state,
I didn't just feel sadness...
Even more than the
shock and horror
of seeing her hurt so much,
I felt sick
to my stomach...
I've always felt
guilty about that...
And I think by
hating my father
I avoided ever having
to deal with the pain.
I just...
I...
Who are you?
Are you a person...?
Who are you, girl?
Who am I...?
Are you a person?
Who are you?
You're Kozzy, that's who!
That's right, I'm Kozzy...
I am Kozzy!
Takumi!
Thank goodness,
you're okay...
I heard your cries
for help in my mind...
I wasn't sure I was gonna be
able to make it here in time.
Well, this is a
lucky break, huh?
Mamoru Suwa...
I can see it, I know
what this man has done.
Mister Nishijo...
The higher ups
have ordered me
to capture you on
sight, my friend.
You murdered him...
You shot your own
partner, didn't you?
If I were you I'd
watch my mouth
and learn some
manners, kid...
You're talking to
a police officer.
I'll say whatever
I want...
There's no reason
to be polite to you.
You think it's all right to
talk down to me like that...?
You pansy!
Look out!
That stake, it's...
How about I recreate
the staking for you,
does that sound like fun?
See I'm just a
regular human being...
but thanks to Noah II,
I've gained power
as great as yours.
It's the Noah II terminal
inside his backpack.
If I could just get to it.
As long as I have
this mechanism,
Noah II's power will be
with me wherever I go.
As long as he has
that mechanism,
Noah II's power will be
with him wherever he goes.
I can become an
artificial gigalomaniac.
He'll be able to be an
You're like an
insect specimen
held in place with a pin.
But this next
one will end you.
It'll kill me!
There's no divine
light waiting for you
at the end of the tunnel!
The one who'll be
killed by this is...
This isn't the
end of my story...
It's just the start.
But wait...
How...? What's this?
I linked our delusions...
You made the rules, then I
flipped them on their head.
You distorted my delusion.
How in the hell
did you do that?
-I switched them up.
-You switched them up.
And I don't need
any salvation!
Kozzy, are you okay?
Yeah but what just
happened here?
I don't understand?!
Kozzy... Hey you're
talking out loud!
Goodness...
Wow, I am, no kidding...!
Hey, Sena, listen to this,
I can talk again...
Damn it...
Do you think you made
up for your sins?
Just 'cause you
protected me?
No way.
I don't care...
I'll never forgive you.
Poor thing...
She can't stop
the tears...
I guess all she really wanted
was to be with her father.
Why'd you have to go?
You could've tried to live
and repent for your sins...
Why'd you leave me here alone
to deal with this by myself...?
Damn it... Come back.
Sena.
Please, Takumi...
Do it...
You must destroy Noah II.
I will...
But this is my burden.
I have to do it
for my own reasons.
Takumi.
Wait for me, Rimi...
Don't lose hope,
I'm coming for you.
[Music]
Those eyes...
...whose are they?