[Music]
You know...
I don't have
much time left...
I was born with
this disease...
I first showed symptoms
when I was ten years old
and I stopped
maturing normally...
And then I started
to age rapidly.
Why don't you just
heal yourself
with your gigalomaniac power?
Unfortunately, the
more I use that power,
the more severe my
disease becomes.
As a result, I
can't heal myself...
It's the one thing
my power can't touch.
No matter how
hard I try...
Nothing will change it.
What about after you die,
what will happen to me?
Even though you and I
are the same person,
regardless of anything
that happens to me,
once you were real-booted you
became a separate human being.
Even if I die...
you will continue
to live on.
What if I disappear,
will you be saved then?
It's useless...
That's just prolonging
the inevitable...
My life on this
earth is over...
You need to destroy
Noah II, Takumi...
Use your power...
without a single
regard for my life.
I don't need you
to tell me that...
I'm not nice enough to
hold back on your account.
I'm happy you
finally awakened.
I will leave
the rest to you.
So that's it...?
You dump this on me?!
I'm a little tired...
Let me sleep.
I know who I am...
And I know what my
purpose is in this life...
Rimi, I will save her.
Amazing...
I never dreamed Noah II
would be so powerful.
It will play a vital role
in restoring our city...
The Meiwa Party's approval
ratings will rise
and we will flourish.
And we couldn't have done any
of this without you, Chairman.
May the divine
light save you.
Let us welcome the dawn
of the Church of Natural Divine
Light and the Meiwa Party
as we work together to
achieve all our goals.
We've put an enormous
amount of money
into Project Noah.
Let us hope it bears fruit.
Yes, of course
gentlemen...
You were expecting
an equivalent return
on your investment.
But regardless of elections
or gaining followers,
at the end of the day,
every person in this country
is under my influence.
What did you just say?
Have you forgotten
who you work for?
I'm assuming full control
of this project now...
Because, you see, our goals
are a little different.
Mine aren't nearly
as vulgar...
Everything that I do is
for a much nobler purpose.
What, are you
betraying us now?!
You think you'll become
some sort of god?
I don't think I'll
become a god...
Don't you see, gentlemen...?
I already am a god.
That's enough!
Yes I think this
should do the trick.
You've been blinded by
greed, but that ends now.
You monster.
I don't think so.
You're the monster.
Noah II's power is mine...
It appears evil men like
you wouldn't understand that.
You use tricks to avoid
getting your hands dirty...
But you're still
responsible...
Don't you see?
You're the evil one.
Tell me, why haven't you asked
Takumi Nishijo for help yet?
Taku's got nothing
to do with this.
Did you know that
he's already awakened?
No way.
I imagine he'll make his
way through the trials
and arrive here soon.
And after I retrieve
his code sample,
Noah II will be one step
closer to perfection...
Then I'll achieve power
on the level of the gods!
Taku.
Rimi
Takki.
Seira?
I'm over here.
Seira!
You're so mean,
leaving me behind.
How could you?
I'm sorry.
Oh, Takki, I'm so lonely.
Seira.
Hey, Takki, will you
come play with me?
Let's do something that
feels really good...
Okay, Takki?
I miss you, Takki!
What is this,
another delusion?
What's wrong, you
don't like it?
Is this what I wished for?
Well, of course it is,
you silly boy.
I'm sorry, but
I can't do this.
I have to go save Rimi.
Huh?
Why don't you just
forget about her?!
Don't you wanna play
with me anymore?!
Takki!
Seira, no!
There's too many!
I got this!
Cocytus!
Nice work.
Thanks, Ayase.
Let's hurry.
We should get him
somewhere safe.
I know, why don't we
take him to Taku's place?
Good call...
That should be safe...
Hey, what happened?
Takumi.
He's telling us he
isn't our top priority.
Let's find Takumi
and destroy Noah II.
He might need our help.
Is that what he wants,
for us to take down Noah II?
Hey, guys!
Hey, Kozue...
You're really talking.
I can't believe
I'm crying...
It's ridiculous.
No, it's not, Sena...
Every single time
a person sheds a tear,
they move on to the
next stage of life.
We cross one river
of sadness...
and another river waits
just on the other side...
It never ends...
But because of
that vicious cycle,
we're strong.
After Takumi saved
me that day...
I realized that truth.
But wait a second...
Where is Takumi?
He's gone to
destroy Noah II.
-He went that way.
-Taku.
We're going to follow
them there, Sena...
Will you come?
Sena?
I will...
But it's the same for
me as it was for him...
I'm doing this for myself.
The Black Knights...
United at last.
Man, I got dumped.
Rimi!
Oh no.
No...
Taku...
Why'd you come?
Why...? To save you.
But why...?
You're a fool...
Taku... What if something
happens to you?
I told you to wait
for me at your place,
why didn't you listen...?
Why...? Tell me.
Because... I love you...
I have always
loved you, Rimi.
Taku... Taku!
You should be commended
for your bravery.
You bastard.
However, you have made
one fatal mistake here...
You didn't think this
thing through clearly
because your actions are
based purely on emotions.
Do you really
think it's evil
to sacrifice smaller
things for the greater good?
Personally I don't think so...
If nothing changes,
mankind will be destroyed.
And do you know
what will cause it?
It truly is an
ugly emotion...
Each man thinking
only of himself...
In the end it only results
in conflict and destruction.
It's greed, the strongest
of all weaknesses.
I came into existence
at a very young age,
so I've had the benefit of
seeing the potential danger
for several decades...
And then one day
I realized...
in order for the world
to be a better place
changing the social
structure of a society
won't get the job done...
It's the human heart
that needs changing.
The human soul
must be reborn.
With Noah II, we can erase
all negative emotions
from mankind and purify
the whole world...
We'll cleanse their
hearts once and for all...
War will be no more.
And human beings all
across the world
will finally live
in eternal peace...
I suppose you won't be
looked down on as
an outcast anymore either.
Maybe you're right...
Maybe everything
you say is true...
It could be...
I don't know...
But still.
You're just satisfying
your own greed!
-It really is a shame.
-Rimi!
In order for Noah II to
achieve its full potential
I need to extract the
final code sample from you.
Taku.
-No!
-Taku...
Do it, destroy it now!
What the hell happened?
I just put my sword
right through that thing!
Again?
I meant to turn around...
No I did turn around...
But it's like it
never happened.
What's going on?
What do you think?
You've just experienced
Noah II's self defense function.
It's quite
impressive actually.
The system interferes
with the minds of anyone
who tries to harm it.
Nobody can get
close to Noah II.
Nobody except me,
of course!
Oh no, he broke my sword!
How about I erase your
existence for you?
No!
Don't do it...
Leave him be.
Rimi...
She's trying to save
my life again...
I came here to rescue her.
I'm so pathetic.
Taku... Stop it.
No...!
Taku!
Why...?
Why am I doing this...?
I don't get it,
why am I making her cry?
Because in the end,
this is all you ever really
wanted from her, isn't it?
That can't be true...
No I love Rimi,
I'd never do that!
But you're going to die
soon anyway, right...?
What's the harm in
having a little fun?
This is my delusion,
isn't it...?
My weak mind is
trying to distract me
and push me towards
a different path.
My mind...
My mind is under attack...
Be strong, I can't let my
delusions get the best of me!
But Rimi pities you,
remember...?
She'll let you do anything
you want to now.
-Leave me alone!
-You are so pathetic.
Huh?
The stake.
It's driving into my body.
Do you wanna
hear something...?
The most interesting
characteristic
of this type of torture
is that it takes three
full days to die.
But while you're writhing
in horrible pain,
I'll be gathering
code samples from you
that will ensure the
success of Noah II.
This is a delusion...
It's a delusional attack...
If I endure it,
the whole thing will
end and I'll wake up.
The stake...
I can feel it pushing
past my organs...
And digging deeper into me...
I have to save Rimi...
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
School at Suimei Academy
has been suspended
ever since that big
earthquake happened...
But today we're back.
I've had a change of heart.
I've decided to take
this opportunity
to quit my shut-in lifestyle
and take school more seriously.
Of course, my wounds haven't
completely healed yet.
Taku!
Rimi.
Ten-hut...!
Good morning, Taku
I'm so happy you and I can walk
to school together again,
-aren't you?
-Yeah.
You okay?
Oh yeah, I'm fine.
Taku.
It's a bit early for that,
don't you think?
Nanami, cut that out.
You're gonna give
me a heart attack!
Good morning, Nana.
You two seem like you're
getting pretty close, huh...?
In fact, I'd say you're
closer than close...
Anyone else feel hot?
Good morning, Takumi.
How are you...?
Guess what...?
Yesterday was great.
I had so much fun.
Yesterday?
I displayed my new Seira
doll in my room right away...
I hope you'll
come and see it.
You'll come over,
won't you?
I hope you will.
Please will you?
Well, well...
Good morning, Takumi.
Hey... Ayase?
My band has a concert
coming up pretty soon...
-Please come.
-Can we go?
I'm inviting Takumi.
-Hi, Taku!
-Kozzy?
Good morning, everyone!
Hey, Takumi...
I've been dying
to tell you this.
Uh, what's up?
I've loved you forever...
-I'm yours.
-Huh?
What?
What did you say?
You heard what I said.
Hey!
What's the matter?
You got a problem
with that, pink hair?
I most certainly do!
He's mine.
Wow this is like heaven...
I hope this
goes on forever.
Oh no... Was I just hiding
inside my own delusion?
Huh...? Who did
he just shoot?
Rimi!
Rimi! I... I couldn't protect
you, I'm so worthless.
There's no point in
going on anymore.
Taku...
Taku!
Huh?
-Taku... You're awake!
-Rimi!
So you're back from your
little daydream I see...
I have to admit that was
pretty clever actually,
I never imagined you would
give yourself another delusion
right in the middle
of my attack!
Rimi, run!
I won't!
Just go.
I have to save Rimi,
I don't have a choice.
No!
I can save her...
I can...
Huh...? What's
happening to me?
What sort of state
am I in right now?
In the end, human beings
only have the ability
to see a clear
picture of themselves
when they are looking
through another person's eyes...
And you are a
delusive existence.
You're real,
not a delusion.
Who's there?
Just look.
It's them.
We're here.
It's time.
Hold on.
We have to let
Cocytus assimilate
with the spiking GE rates.
But that's impossible,
there's no river of
lamentation here,
there's no way it will work.
There's the Shibuya River.
The Shibuya River?
It's right underneath
the city...
Several rivers flow together
to form the Shibuya.
And also...
Shibuya is a valley,
so it won't be too difficult
to gather up GE Rate
energy will it?
That's right.
With this, we will finally
defeat the evil King Gladiale.
Let's go.
I was too weak to
do it myself...
But thanks to
your actions...
everyone's finally
working together.
You're giving me
too much credit,
I'm not special...
Besides I was created
by a delusion, remember?
Even if you are
a delusion...
your creation
was inevitable...
Every person is born
with a purpose...
All beings that
exist are the same...
Besides...
everyone's had their
eyes on you, right...?
This is it.
Your time has
come at last.
My time?
You... are me.
I am...
I'm you.
You're my big brother.
You are Takumi.
You're Takumi Nishijo.
You're my friend Takumi.
You are Takumi.
You're Taku.
They're right, I am me...
Even if I'm a delusion,
I'm here right now...
In this moment I exist
'cause I'm Takumi Nishijo.
-I am!
-Taku!
The fear that
closes in on me
is an illusion
inside my heart.
If I can follow the mystery
it will lead me
towards pleasure.
I know that...
It's FES's song.
You did it, you
beat the delusion...
I give you my
final power...
Now finish this.
Please don't cry...
Please.
I'll destroy you
once and for all,
you delusive monster!
It's true, I certainly
am a monster...
But I wished for it...
In order to save Rimi...
And to destroy
Noah II for good...
This is my delusion.
Let's finish this.
I thought that
I had him cornered,
but now he has
the upper hand...
I can't let this happen,
I will not allow it!
Huh?
I shut down my
sense of pain.
So you can take
any shape you want,
because you've abandoned
your physical form,
is that what you've
done, you freak?
And it's all thanks to the
delusion you placed on me.
Because of you I couldn't
maintain my human form
so I absorbed the delusion
and then made it my own.
You can't make any more
delusions without a brain,
can you?
Physically attacking
him with my di-sword
isn't working...
and he absorbed the delusional
attack to erase his existence.
Takumi Nishijo isn't like
a human being anymore,
he's something else...
His existence is
too distorted...
He's a monster.
He's too powerful.
I should command Noah II
to attack him with a
legion of antiparticles
fueled by GE Rate power.
Even a monster like him
will turn to negative
matter and self- destruct
if you bombard it
with antiparticles.
Yes that's true.
He read my thoughts!
Although I'm betting
you can't read my thoughts
right now, can you?
I never knew this
place existed.
This is the river on the
lowest level of Shibuya,
it will serve
as Cocytus...
We'll use its
holy power...
And we'll combine it
with the GE Rate power
of the entire city!
Today is a day of reckoning
for all these sinners...
Anyone who ignores morality
doesn't deserve to live.
That's right, Sena...
Get those bastards!
-Hey, watch your mouth.
-Sorry!
Come on... Let's go!
Merge our
delusions into one!
Cocytus!
Everyone's thoughts
and feelings,
they're all trained on me.
Hmph... That's
not even possible!
Don't you know what you see
doesn't represent everything?
It's time...
The dark snake which swallows
up all evil will defeat you...
And Noah II...
King Gladiale will
meet his end today!
Even if you do defeat me,
no one will be able to get
close to that machine...
Noah II will operate
until the end of eternity!
It's an artificial
manmade god
that will control humanity
till the end of its existence!
What about you...?
You can touch it!
You are the key
to stopping it!
Have you forgotten that
little tricks like this
don't work on me?
I might be the enemy of
humanity by doing this.
But I don't want
your endless utopia,
or your blissful peace...
Your future without war...
I'll put a stop to it
right here, right now.
You hear about it in
legends all the time...
Even the gods
have a weakness...
Their love for women
overcomes them...
And I am the same way.
That's why I'll sacrifice
the happiness of all mankind
for the girl I love.
No way!
This dark serpent's body
was made with masses
of powerful antiparticles...
It'll cause anything that
comes in contact with it
to self-destruct...
It's a righteous, destructive,
all consuming monster!
Taku!
I refuse to believe it...
I will not accept it...
A real god wouldn't build
happiness on someone's pain...
What sort of a
life is that?
A piercing gaze falls from
the sky like rays of light.
An angel...?
Kill me...
Please...
If you don't,
the real me will...
I can't do it...
I can't do
something like that.
I love you even with
your weaknesses...
You're cowardly...
You're not strong...
But you fought with
everything inside of you,
just to come here
and rescue me...
Rimi.
I want to spend more
time with you...
I don't want
to lose you...
All I want is for
you to live...
I want us to share
our lives together.
But I'm not real, I'm
nothing but a monster.
I'm the same as you...
It's all right.
Yeah but...
is it okay for me to live?
Yes, if that's
what you wish for.
Then it's okay to live.
Takumi...
Did he pass on?
Rimi...
I have always loved you.
Light is nothing
more than waves...
They're actually
electromagnetic waves...
Humans perceive
these oscillations
as different colors.
Taku... Those words.
Wow.
First pick out a color
and then try sending it
straight to your dead spot...
Then you'll be able to
create the color of the world.
Just make a wish.
[Music]