[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
Sena, Kozzy and
I teamed up
and went after the
Nozomi Group,
a powerful company that is
trying to recreate the ability
of the gigalomaniacs
and use it for
evil purposes.
However, company president
Genichi Norose
was immediately
on to our plan.
He used the power of
Noah II's prototype
to make Sena and
Kozzy suffer...
He also tried his
best to kill me.
Suddenly a miracle
happened...
Ayase showed up and
came to our rescue.
But the Norose we fought
so hard to beat...
It was a delusion.
I'm so sorry, I hope you
haven't been waiting too long.
I'm Ban, Shibuya Police.
Your name's Yua
Kusunoki, right?
Yes.
You're related to
Mia Kusunoki...
The young girl who died in
the first New Gen crime,
known commonly as
the "Group Dive"...
You two were twin
sisters, correct?
Well to bring you
up to speed...
Yua here has been
investigating
the New Gen incidents
all on her own...
She's trying to find out what
happened to her sister...
That must've been really
difficult for her.
That's not all. She's narrowed
it down to one suspect.
It's Takumi Nishijo.
That's interesting...
Very much so.
So what exactly led
you to this conclusion?
Just give me one sec.
I gotta take this call.
Yeah, this is
Ban, what's up?
It's number six...!
The sixth New Gen incident
was just reported!
What was that?
The sixth case?!
No,. it can't be...
Hey what's wrong?
Each of the three victims'
bodies were severed,
all of them cut in half
at the waist...
Their upper and
lower bodies were...
all sewn up
and then stitched back together
again with fishing line...
There were wounds
on their bodies
resembling the letters
"D," "Q" and "N."
So gruesome.
I know these guys!
What do you mean?
Well, they, uh-They picked a
fight with me a while back.
It's the General...
He's provoking me
again, I know it!
Hey don't worry.
I'm sure it's just
a coincidence.
Plus...
I am so hungry
I can't think...
You wanna go grab
a bite to eat...?
I know an awesome place
that's super cheap.
Just give me a break...!
This whole thing is
driving me insane!
You got it...
You're in charge of
the crime scene...
I'd come, but I think
I'm onto a very important
lead right now.
Roger.
You may end up
opening Pandora's box
if you're not careful,
Detective.
Your temperature's at
a hundred degrees...
That's high but
not dangerous.
My head is hurting...
It's bad.
Oh my... Again?
Well that's a side effect
of the medication...
Just try not to
think about it
and it'll go away soon.
I know these symptoms...
I've had them before.
No matter what happens...
I'm ready for
anything that comes...
Because...
I've endured the
divine punishment.
Hi-ya!
I can't wrap my
head around it,
why is the General
targeting me?
"Those eyes,
whose are they?"...
That's the phrase
I always say.
I even wrote an essay about
it in elementary school...
What exactly did I write?
You lose, you silly boy!
This is it but it
doesn't make any sense.
IR2, huh?
I know this equation,
it's the same one the
General posted online...
Oh no...
What if he's secretly
reading my mind?
The General...
Is it him?
Nanami...
Of course.
Taku.
Yeah, what do you want?
Please... Help me.
Prank-calling me...
She's so annoying.
Yua, have you heard anything
about students at your school
performing magic tricks,
or supernatural feats?
For example, have you
ever seen anybody
pull a big sword
out of thin air?
How do you know about her?
Do you know her name?
Yes, Ayase Kishimoto.
I saw her do it...
It was incredible,
she pulled a sword
out of nowhere.
I saw the exact same thing
done by another
girl named Sena.
Huh?
Several reports have been
submitted by concerned citizens
who have seen this girl carrying
a sword all over the city.
Yes, but... that's not all...
I saw Ayase split in two.
Just like that,
there were two of her!
I've already confirmed
that Ayase and Sena
have separately made contact
with Takumi Nishijo
in the past few days.
Takumi.
I may not be able
to explain it,
but everywhere that boy goes,
strange and mysterious things
seem to be right behind him.
Oh, by the way, Yua...
Those little charmy things
hanging from your bag...
Those are the
Hoppy the Frog dolls
that are so popular with
all the kids, aren't they?
Oh yeah.
I think I'd like one.
Would you mind
picking one up for me?
Of course,
I'd be happy to.
What the hell's
Hoppy the Frog?
It's a teenager thing,
a few specialty shops
in town sell them... Duh.
On Fridays kids line up
all the way around the block
to get one.
On Fridays, huh?
Yep, every Friday
new designs come out.
People look forward
to it all week long.
You thinking
the same thing?
Hoppy the Frog sales
aren't the only thing
spiking on the weekend.
Let's check this thing out.
Taku...
Hey, Taku!
Where the heck
is Ayase's room?
I've got no clue.
This is the
outpatient ward...
In-patients
are over there.
What are you,
a tour guide...?
You sure know a lot
about this place.
Well at least somebody
knows what's going on...
You invited us to come,
you should at
least know the way.
Actually, I only
invited Taku...
You just decided
to crash the party.
Did I really?
Well, I'm going
to the bathroom,
you guys go on ahead,
I'll catch up with you later.
Cool.
Where do you
think she went?
Hell, I don't know.
The "Gladiale Saga"?
It looks like a
fantasy novel.
If I'm going to make
Ayase fall in love with me,
I'm probably gonna have to
read this book, aren't I?
I guess Ayase's well
enough to walk then.
By the way,
do you think
Rimi's gonna be able
to find this room?
Huh?
Rimi's not exactly the
smartest person I've ever met,
so I highly doubt it
occurred to her to stop
and ask somebody
for assistance.
We should go find her.
Hey wait a second.
That thing I heard
about you and Ayase
sleeping together was
just a rumor, right?
I mean, you look so lonely
when Rimi's not by your side.
Well... I'll check downstairs.
Then I'll go up.
Why do I feel this way,
like I shouldn't be here?
What is this place?
Oh no...
No!
The General...
He's reading my
thoughts again...!
I wanna go home!
May the divine
light save you...
light defend you...
May the divine
light protect you...
light cleanse you.
Oh wow...
Takumi is a full-blown
anime nerd, isn't he?
Takumi Nishijo
is not normal.
What if somebody is giving
him artificial support...?
What will we do?
Cool...
"Those eyes,
whose are they?"...
I guess Takumi really is the
"Whose eyes" guy after all.
I knew it was
him all along!
No way.
"Ir2"?
Well, what's that?
Are you okay?
What in the
world was that?
Hey, Taku.
You don't look so good...
But I guess you
never really do, huh?
I found Rimi and Ayase.
Look right down there.
What was that
all about...?
Do those two hold
some kind of grudge?
Anyway...
Let's pretend we
didn't see that.
Yeah.
Yo, Ayase!
Just thought you'd
like to know,
you look hot in your PJs...
Right, Taku?
How do you feel...?
You sure do look a
whole lot better.
Hey...! Ayase...
Do you like books...?
I'm reading one that's
called the Gladiale Saga...
Takumi... You do realize
you're one of the
Seven Knights of Gladiale.
You have a great
wickedness inside of you...
That's what makes you
an ideal Black Knight...
It's why you've
been chosen...
All the pain and suffering
you're experiencing
is divine punishment...
The Great Will of the
Universe is testing you.
Once you have overcome it,
you will be free again,
and the di- sword
will be summoned.
Trust me...
I know it.
It will appear
before you...
A great black serpent...
It will swallow
up all destruction
and take down the
evil King Gladiale...
This is the
path you are on.
Together we will
destroy the King...
We must.
Well... To be honest,
I have no idea
what's going on...
She's all yours, pal...
Good luck!
Daisuke, leaving me all
alone isn't gonna help.
You created it,
didn't you?
You made the flowerbed.
You gotta understand,
I'm not a gigalomaniac...
I don't think.
Gigalo... what?
You don't know what a
gigalomaniac is...?
That girl Sena
told me about it.
Oh, that girl,
I know her...
She is a Knight
of Gladiale too,
just like you and I are.
Listen to me,
I am not a knight...
I'm not...
I don't have a di-sword...
I've got nothing.
It's your divine
punishment...
Once you overcome it,
your sword will be revealed.
Punishment?
Your suffering...
The explosion of
emotional burdens
burying themselves deep
inside your mind...
In other words...
Psychological torture.
I experienced it...
The drops of water
fell into my eyes
in precisely
five-second intervals.
It went on like that...
for two weeks without
a moment's rest.
The instant before my
mind was about to break...
I could hear the voice
of the Great Will.
And I was finally
able to summon it.
That was divine
punishment...
In order to get the power
to defeat the demon,
you have to purify your own,
and cleanse it from within.
What are you saying...?
That I have to keep
on suffering...?
I don't want to do this...
Please, I just want
to be left alone!
It's all a revelation.
We're running
out of time,
the Seven Knights should've
already gathered in this city...
The moment has come,
they must awaken!
If we don't do
something quickly,
the world will fall to
ruin by Gladiale's hand.
I'm sorry, guys...
I didn't know where
the hospital room was,
so I got lost
wandering around.
So... Did you
get to see Ayase?
Yeah, but I don't really
care about Ayase anymore.
She's way too
crazy for me...
Plus I don't like
fantasy novels.
Did something happen?
Oh yeah...
You could say that.
Another prank call?
Hey, Nanami, cut it out!
Taku...
Where am I?
Please help me...
I wanna go home!
Nana...
This place is dead...
Guess there aren't a lot of
customers before the weekend.
Yeah...
It's 'cause it's the
middle of the week.
From Friday to Sunday it's
pretty crowded in here.
Um... In other words...
it's not usually very
busy until the weekend
when a new Hoppy
gets released.
So it only happens
on the weekends, eh?
Oh... look!
What's wrong?
That must be the new
Floppy the Frog
that goes on sale tomorrow.
Uh... Actually,
it's Hoppy the Frog.
Well, well, looky there...
The Shinko Corporation.
I'm worried
about Nanami...
What if it wasn't a prank?
What's the matter, Taku?
You're acting a
little weird...
Is everything okay?
I'm just a little bit
worried about my sister.
I think I should go
home and check on her.
Oh... So you're going home?
Yeah... Would you
come with me please...
I really don't wanna
go there alone.
Sena?
Are you the one who
drew this picture?
Answer me!
What in the world is
she doing with that?
I asked you a question!
Yeah, I did, so what?
Takumi, run, now!
Prepare yourself!
Look out!
Why is Sena attacking me?
Wait, what did I do wrong?
Rimi.
Move!
Stop it... Stop it!
What the hell is this?!
Rimi is one of us.
She's a gigalomaniac, too!
Stop it, you
leave him alone!
But don't you realize what
this idiot created...?
He's responsible for
the IR2 equation!
Yes, I know.
Then move.
If you cause
him to awaken,
things won't
get any better.
I'll kill him before that.
You won't be able to.
Sena.
It's you.
I finally found you.
I didn't know
what else to do...
I had no other alternative
but to offer your
mother as a sacrifice,
can't you understand that?
Shut up.
Because of your mother,
we were able to achieve
unparalleled results...
Her death was useful
in our experiments.
Shut the hell up!
At last...
I've finally avenged her.
Sena.
No, stop it...!
Please let go of me!
It's okay.
No... Let go...
I don't want this.
But this is the delusion
that you wished for.
Sena!
I'm sorry for causing
you all this pain...
But you left me
no other option.
Did Rimi just
do that to her?
It's over now, right...?
You'll leave her be,
won't you, Rimi?
If you're a big
meanie head to Sena
and try to cause
her any more pain,
I promise I'll never
ever forgive you.
It's all over
now, I swear.
I really didn't
want to hurt her,
that was never
my intention...
If she promises to
keep away from Taku,
then I'll leave her alone.
That's not gonna work...
It's just not possible...
I mean, the three
of us are friends.
We do stuff together
all the time, right?
Right...?
Tell her how
it is, Takumi.
Because of what you've done,
my family is ruined!
Whadda you mean,
your family?
The formula you created,
it has potential to
destroy the world...
It's the most
dangerous equation
that has ever
been conceived...
And it's the cause
of all the chaos
that's assaulting our city!
Equation?
Don't say any more.
Just drop it.
But what do you mean?
Hey is this it...?
The formula?
That's just a drawing,
it's nothing!
F U N to the tenth
power times I N T
to the fortieth power
equals... I R two.
The moment you
created this equation
the world split in two...
You destroyed everything!
This equation is the principal
mathematical component
behind the functionality
of Noah II.
The formula is
incorporated
into the core of
the system...
Remarkably, we discovered it in
the most unusual of places.
A young child scribbled
it while drawing...
Yes, "IR two"...
Thanks to this
simple equation,
Noah II's mechanism was
taken to the next level,
its hardware achieving
what you might call
god-like ability.
Now all we have to do
is continue to gather
gigalomaniac code samples
for Noah II's software,
and the program will begin to
operate at full capacity...
just like that.
How many samples
have you gathered?
Where do we stand?
I have already
secured samples
from five different people.
Then things are
right on track.
But remember this,
the more samples
we can get...
the more powerful the
Noah II will become...
With your permission,
there is one gigalomaniac
boy in particular
whose sample I am
planning on collecting.
That's fine,
so long as it does not
cause a delay in our plans.
How long until Noah
II's fully operational?
Before we move on,
I must conduct one
final experiment...
I will initiate
the third melt.
Wait, the third melt?
I believe it will be
on the level of the
Great Kanto Earthquake.
The Kanto Earthquake,
are you serious?
That was the greatest
natural disaster
this country has seen.
After the third melt
successfully achieves
its result,
Noah II will have
attained near perfection
in its final form...
The world's possibilities
will be in our hands.
IR2...
The formula that
creates silent weapons.
But what are the
silent weapons?
Mind reading...
Visual projection...
Sensory control...
With this...
gigalomaniacs will never
be special beings again...
This power will be
available to anyone
to use indiscriminately.
And it is all thanks
to the Noah II machine
derived from
your equation.
The Noah II.
We saw it!
What's worse...
People will never
know about this...
Norose and those corrupt
bastards will monopolize it
before people
ever realize.
But that's got
nothing to do with me!
Look I'm not to
blame for this,
I didn't hurt anybody!
If I don't even remember
writing the stupid thing
then how can
it be my fault?
None of this
really matters.
The important thing
is the person
who came up with the
"Those eyes" phrase.
And that's you, Takumi,
you made it up...!
See, the old man knew exactly
what he was talking about!
What's that...?
What old man are
you talking about?
Well, let's see.
He was the person who
originally told me
how important
di-swords were.
I remember him 'cause he
was the first one in town
to speak to me.
Why didn't you tell me
about this sooner, Kozue?!
I'm sorry!
How was I
supposed to know?
It's true...
He's really in this city.
I'll finally get
my revenge...
Finally...
I will kill him!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I lied.
I don't even know
who you are anymore.
Taku...
I think of myself
as your friend,
I don't want to lose you...
Please just trust me.
Rimi.
Can I trust her after all
the lies and deceit...?
If I ask her if
she's on my side
do I run the risk of
losing her forever...?
No.
You saved me...
Thank you for
the protection.
You're welcome.
Stop...!
Hold on.
Are you really
going home...?
Please don't do that...
Things there will never
be the same again.
I don't want you
to have to hurt.
Let's go back...
We'll go back to
your secret hideout
and play games...
As long as you want,
I'll stay right by your
side, Taku, I swear.
We can walk to school together
and gossip with Daisuke
about all the things
that are happening.
You don't get it...
It's Nanami,
I've got to see her.
She's not there...
She's gone.
Taku... It hurts me
to see you sad...
Please don't go.
Stop being so mysterious!
Look, if there's a reason I
shouldn't go home, tell me...!
Don't make me guess,
I'm so sick and tired
of all this speaking
in riddles bullshit!
Taku.
This is the right street.
Where is it...?
Where's my house?
Don't you get it, Taku...?
There's no home in this
world for you to go to.
[Music]
Those eyes...
Whose are they?