[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
The day that a strange
earthquake struck,
Ayase jumped off the
roof of the school.
Apparently, I created a
delusion of a flowerbed
that saved her life
by breaking her fall.
After that, rumors started
flying about me and Ayase...
I quickly became the target
of all the jerks in my class.
Then suddenly a mysterious voice
began to echo in my head...
The voice belonged
to Kozue Orihara,
aka "Kozzy"...
Turns out she's a
friend of Sena's.
Sena explained that she and
Kozzy are gigalomaniacs,
or special people
with a unique ability
to turn delusions
into reality
through a process
called real-booting...
She also told me that
there are bad people
who want to recreate this
power artificially
and use it for evil.
Takumi...
Thank you.
Huh?
What?
What the hell is this?
Some kind of trick?
Who exactly is this girl?
Have I seen her before?
It doesn't look like the
tape has been edited...
It looks real.
Better be careful...
I think I just
saw something
I wasn't supposed to see.
I didn't get to
see Rimi today...
It seems like she's been absent
ever since the earthquake...
Hope everything's okay.
Kozzy.
Taku...
Sena is calling for you.
She is...?
Oh no-
Our only option is
to destroy the
Nozomi Corporation
once and for all.
Are we really going
to attack them?
Don't worry, the three of
us will combine our power
and give those bad
guys a smackdown!
I think I'll pass...
After all, I don't
even have a di-sword.
Hey... Crying won't make
me change my mind--
Look... Takumi's making
the new girl cry.
Well, well. First
FES, now her.
Look at you, Mr. Popular!
Nice work.
I'm not coming
with you, okay?
It's about time.
-Sena.
-Don't get the wrong idea.
The only reason you're
coming is 'cause
Kozue insisted all three
of us go together.
I'd be just fine
without you.
Well that was
nice of her...
But I'm not going.
Taku, please!
Well I don't intend to force
you to come along with us.
But I will give
you one warning:...
Nozomi Technology is
trying to collect samples
from gigalomaniacs...
and they don't care what
destruction they cause
in the process, so you
should be careful.
The fact that you're a
gigalomaniac means that
at some point they will be
coming after you too.
But of course, there's
a possibility
that they're targeting
you already.
You think they're
coming for me?
If you want to know the
truth, then come with us.
Sena, wait!
Oh no...
What if the General
has something to do
with the Nozomi Corporation?
Taku?
Sena is right...
If there's something
that you need to know,
you should come with us and
see it with your own eyes.
With my own eyes, huh?
Yes... With your
very own eyes...
It's time to be brave.
Be brave?
The Gigalomaniac Trio's
off to take out
the bad guys once
and for all!
What sort of a
graph is this?
It shows patterns of GE rates in
Shibuya over the last year...
Now maybe it's
my imagination,
but I get the feeling
they're being controlled
by some outside force.
Do you really think something
like that could happen?
Well... It all seems
pretty unnatural to me...
There's too many
fluctuations
and according to
my research...
GE rates are only spiking
on the weekends,
which seems like an
extremely unusual pattern
if you ask me.
For example...
Do you see
these two areas?
The GE measurements
are enormous.
Compared to the rest of the
graph, the one on the right
looks like the biggest
jump of the year.
Never mind the year.
That one's the largest spike
in the last few decades.
What are the dates?
The one in the middle
was three months ago.
Do you remember
that earthquake?
It wasn't huge but it
did cause some damage.
That's right, it was only
three on the scale,
but somehow eight
people still died.
The big one happened
on the same day
as the most recent quake.
Uh-huh.
Did you know that
a large outbreak
of electromagnetic pulses
occurred on that day?
Yeah, apparently computers
all over Shibuya broke down.
They say that the
electromagnetic waves
were a result of
the earthquake,
but what if the
opposite were true...?
What if the earthquake
was a direct result
of the waves?
This is just conjecture...
But I believe that both
of these earthquakes
might possibly have
been man-made...
Think about it, neither
of them were normal.
The first one killed
eight people even though
it was only a three
on the scale.
This one was a five,
and it killed just
over one hundred.
You're saying that too
many people are dying?
And don't forget,
there were rumors
that the sky turned white.
Now that you mention
it, it does seem like
everybody stopped
reporting that story
all of a sudden.
It's possible somebody
was putting pressure
on the media outlets.
You're kidding, right?
The Meiwa Party.
Yeah, that would
be my first guess.
Whoa... Are you serious?
Then we should probably
look into businesses
with strong political
ties to the party?
I'm way ahead
of you, Banny.
Momo, my girl,
you're the best... So-
I couldn't
find a thing.
Oh come on now...
There's no leads at all?
I'm sorry, Miss Momo,
but are you sure
you're not wrong
about all this?
Well either someone's
done a good job
covering their tracks...
or I'm wrong this time.
I guess we'll have to attack
this from another angle.
Yeah but where
do we start, sir?
Do you have anything
specific in mind?
Somebody's gotta be
benefitting from GE rates
spiking on the weekends...
That specific
enough for you?
Our only objective is
to destroy Noah II.
But, how can we destroy it
if we don't know where it is?
I put the screws to some
people and found out...
Noah II's in an underground
research facility.
You put the
screws to them?
Hey... We can't just walk
through the front door!
Don't worry, Taku,
everything's peachy keen,
just follow us!
"Peachy keen"...?
Yeah I bet.
Oh no.
Hello, sirs.
They're just gonna let
us walk in like that?
Don't worry, they
can't see us.
What do you mean?
To them, we look like some
company executives in suits.
To protect our identity,
I created particles
with my di-sword...
then sent them to the dead
spots of everyone inside.
Is it really
that easy to do?
Sure is.
Being a gigalomaniac
is pretty cool, huh?
Just remember, don't
let your guard down.
Please... Let's stop...
I hate to say this...
I don't want to...
But I'm afraid Takumi
Nishijo needs to be erased.
And why is that?
'Cause he's way
too dangerous...
So just tell me...
Do you want it done?
No... Not yet...
There are many things I
need him to do for me.
Tell me...
I've always
wanted to know,
do you remember
your dreams?
-Yes.
-Really...?
I forget mine,
I can't ever remember them.
There are some
people who can,
and others who cannot.
The ones who remember...
They must be romantics.
Sometimes I have dreams
that seem like
they'll never end.
I used to be like that...
Or at least I
feel like I was...
But that's just an
illusion, right?
A dream in my heart.
Please, you need to wake
up from your dream...
If you don't...
I'm afraid that someday you'll
be erased by Takumi Nishijo!
That's all right with me...
Sooner or later this
dream will have to end.
Will there be anything
left in this world...?
After the dream is over?
Looks like Noah II's
not in here either.
-This is odd.
-Huh?
Where's all the staff,
why aren't they down here?
Well, I don't know, maybe
they all went home early.
Stay on your toes.
Look... there.
Noah II.
Well, well,
I trust you found what
you were looking for?
It's the President
of the Nozomi Group.
Genichi Norose!
Welcome, my young
gigalomaniac friends,
to the future!
Oh no...! He knows
that it's us!
Are we being ambushed?
Miss Kishimoto...
It's time to take
your temperature!
Miss Kishimoto?
You see, I've received
quite a few reports
that a young girl has
been going around
defeating my porters with
a single sword.
Immediately I knew
it had to be you...
Sena Hatano.
Hatano...? I
don't understand,
I thought that Sena's
last name was Aoi...
Those two seem to know
each other though.
Oh I'm so scared...
Barbaric activities such
as fighting with swords...
That's never really
been my specialty.
A di-sword...! Is he
a gigalomaniac, too?
I've never seen a combat
game like this one.
So, did you find
your father yet? !
You shut your mouth!
She's predicting
every move I make...
How? !
He's coming at
you from the side!
This time he's gonna
try to fake you out
and then strike when
you leap towards him.
Stand up.
So the little one's
reading my mind
and communicating
it to you.
After all this is done,
I'm going to make you
Noah II's next sample.
Please don't make
me kill you,
you might actually
prove useful here.
What the hell is that?
He real-booted mirrors
to confuse her...
Kozue!
Who are you?
Are you a person?
Who are you...?
Kozzy, what's wrong?
As a little girl,
she was harassed
by a group of stalkers.
A group of stalkers?
Every day, masses of
strangers would scream at her,
"Who are you?" ,
showing her mirrors, forcing
her to look at herself...
Eventually, she
became so terrified
that she lost her identity.
And because of her fear,
she lost the ability to speak.
Don't you say
another word!
Don't go yet, I haven't
given you my present!
No, go away.
Please just stay
away from me!
I don't understand,
Sena's afraid of dogs?
You know something,
Miss Hatano?
You haven't
changed one bit.
Stop it! No, please don't...
Just leave me alone!
Sena.
There is nothing for
you to be afraid of...
You will always
be Kozue...
No matter what people
say, you're still you.
Well... Visually projecting
your image onto your blazer,
that's quite a trick
you just pulled.
You've finally learned
how to use your power.
Yes.
I had to so that I
could destroy you.
Those chains.
You've given me some
fun toys to play with.
What?
Sena!
You leave Sena alone!
Sena.
How can she keep
on fighting
when she's in that condition?
Why?
Sensory control.
Visual projection...
Mind reading...
We've collected more
than enough data
from this subject.
Mr. atano...
As a researcher and
someone who gave his wife
to our experiment in
accordance with the creeds
of the Church of
the Divine Light,
you must be quite satisfied
with our results.
Dad, what's wrong with
Mom? Is she okay...?
I don't understand what's
happening here...?
What is that? What
is she holding?
Don't worry, Mommy's
perfectly fine.
She's only dreaming.
Dreaming?
In her mind, your mother's
living a normal everyday life...
But the moment of her awakening
has finally come now.
Please don't do this...
Please sir, just let
her stay like this.
What could it hurt...?
I'm begging you.
Please don't!
Oh no, my little baby...
What happened to
my little baby? !
No way...
That can't be my
little sister...!
What the hell did
you do to her? !
Sena Hatano is a
valuable sample...
Everyone give her the
red-carpet treatment.
Sweetie, I'm so sorry...
Please forgive me.
Damn you...! Damn you both!
What just happened...?
That wasn't a normal delusion.
Wait, what is this...?
Huh? Sena, are you okay? !
I was the one who ordered
your whole family
to meet a tragic end...
But they were part of
something very significant.
It was an invaluable
scientific experiment.
I'll kill you!
All your code samples have
already been extracted...
To be completely honest...
you're of absolutely
no use to me!
What is it this time?
Ah, this must be
your handiwork.
All right, backup is here!
Cocytus flows.
If I remember all
this correctly,
Cocytus is a river on the
lowest level of hell
in Greek Mythology...
And all the sinners there-
-will freeze forever!
Sena... I don't get it,
how come we're not
ice blocks too?
She doesn't want us to
be, so her delusion didn't
involve us being frozen.
You saved us...
Thank you.
But how in the world
did you find us?
I was led here by the
power of the Great Will...
My mission was to rescue
my fellow Black Knights.
We have to work together
to stop the resurrection
of the devil king...
To put an end to...
an end to... Glad-
Hey, what's
wrong, are you okay?
Her wounds haven't
healed yet.
She pushed it
way too hard.
This girl's got guts!
It's all because of you...
You saved us...
-Thank you.
-Norose!
You don't know when
to give up, do you?
This ends right now!
I'll crush you!
Wait. Hey, you
two cut it out.
What the heck
are you doing?
You're on the same side!
Even though they're going
after each other,
in their minds they think
they're fighting me.
Wait, what do you mean?
Because of your
delusion they believe
they're fighting you...
What did you do?
Did you send particles
into their dead spots
to confuse them?
That's absolutely right...
And I took it further...
To give it a little flavor
I made it so they can't
see anything besides me,
and the very sight of it
fills them with a burning
rage they can't control.
So what now...?
Your friends are
in grave danger.
I shouldn't
have come here.
I should've just stayed
home and watched anime
and played video games.
I hope your plan isn't
to stand there
and watch your friends
murder each other.
This is a delusion...
Wake up...!
Come on wake up from it
like you always do!
I hate to disappoint,
but that's not the way
this is going to go...
I didn't prepare a "this
is all just a bad dream"
ending for you.
It's impossible.
I don't have the sword
or the courage
to fight that monster.
I can't do it! I can't!
I guess it's probably
time to end this thing.
No please!
Help me. Sena!
Kozzy, please! I'm
begging you, save me!
Please don't do this...
My, my.
-Sena!
-Hear me now...
The blade of this di-sword
will take revenge on you
and that man...!
Now prepare to die!
This can't be...
How can she see me...?
He must have sent
antiparticles
into each of
their dead spots
to cancel out my particles...
thereby putting an
end to the delusion.
Here I come!
Bam, boom,...
crash!
Hey we did it! We
destroyed Noah II!
What the hell
did he just do?
Takumi Nishijo...
Even though you
don't know it,
the moment of your awakening
draws nearer every day.
I don't get it,
what just happened?
What happened is, the
Gigalomaniac Trio plus one...
just kicked some
serious butt!
Yeah, we did it!
Where are you?
Congratulations, you destroyed
the Noah II prototype...
You think I'd let you
near the real thing?
It was a prototype? !
And the person you fought
so hard to defeat
was nothing more
than a copy of me
made by the prototype.
No way.
Of course, the
machine's defective.
The real me is
much stronger
than the fake
version it produced.
-Trust me.
-Hold on...
What do you mean, are
you saying that you're
stronger than that? !
Don't worry, you'll
find out soon enough.
Take care of
yourselves, my friends.
I can't believe this!
That bastard was just
playing games with us
the whole time!
Sena.
Hey she doesn't
look so good...
We'd better get her to
a hospital immediately.
You're right, let's go.
Rimi...
She's absent again.
Taku... Morning!
Hi!
Thank goodness...
I'm so glad she came!
Whoa, Taku...
What's wrong with you...?!
Did something happen?
Are you crying?
I know, you're crying
because you're so happy
you got to see me again!
I know you too well.
Oh I'm just kidding.
Hiya, Taku.
Whoa, gloomy.
Somebody's depressed, huh?
Oh, don't worry, buddy,
I know that's just
the way you are...
You can't help yourself.
What's up?
You're awfully cheery for
so early in the morning.
What's so awful about it?
Well...
How about
"unbelievably" then?
Taku, I don't get it.
How come she's
such a weirdo?
Well I don't know.
I guess it's
like they say...
The more things change...
What's that
supposed to mean?
It has been a
remarkable journey,
so much time has passed
since this project
was first conceived.
Now, then.
I'll admit, never in
my wildest dreams
did I imagine that you
were a gigalomaniac.
In order for this to work,
I need more samples from
you gigalomaniacs...
Or to be a bit
more specific,
I am going to need a code
sample of your NA synapses...
They're the part of your
brain that gives orders
to the rest of your body
and tells it what to do.
Those samples are the equivalent
of a processor to Noah II.
Without it, the machine's
virtually worthless.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
That's excellent.
The day the world will be
reborn is drawing near.
[Music]
Those eyes, whose are they?