[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
With Rimi's help
and support,
I continued to search
for my di-sword,
but I didn't even
know where to begin.
The fifth New Gen
incident occurred...
This one called
'Brainless.'...
And as if the General
was provoking me,
Dr. Takashina,
my old psychiatrist,
was the victim.
Plus...
I also found
out that Ayase
had once been hospitalized
for severe psychological
problems...
"If I find my sword,
I'll be saved."...
But can I really
trust her...?
Can I believe
anything she says?
The moment I
thought that...
a strange and powerful
earthquake struck Shibuya.
What in the hell
just happened?
Huh?
One p.m.?
I was unconscious for
more than an hour? !
No way... It's impossible.
Did I lose all my data,
including my gaming progress...?
Oh no.
What's the point
of going on now? !
Let me repeat this...
Today just before noon,
a five point magnitude
earthquake occurred with
Shibuya at its epicenter...
The casualties numbered
over two hundred.
But authorities have
yet to comment on
what happened immediately
after the quake...
A strange white light.
For unknown reasons,
a glow suddenly
illuminated the sky
and was accompanied by
unusually violent shockwaves.
Thank God...
It's not all gone.
The server kept a backup
copy of my save data!
But I don't understand.
What in the
world was that?
It felt like my whole
body was boiling,
melting from within...
That wasn't a
normal earthquake.
The General...? He could
be the one behind this!
I'll destroy you.
A... A delusion?
Rimi.
Oh, Rimi... I
need you by my side.
You're connected to a
messaging service...
At the tone, please
leave a message,
Voicemail...? No.
That's right...
it's a school day!
What's happening?
She was sick, right?
Yeah, and apparently,
when everybody
found out about it,
it made her even worse!
Taku!
Aw man... This is bad...
Look there.
Ayase?
This delicate world
is overflowing
with malicious delusions.
I closed my eyes and
covered up my ears...
But nothing helped...
It was always there,
right by my side.
I wanted peace...
And I longed to go to the place
where the Great Will resides.
So I ripped my
heart into pieces...
and embraced the chaos...
I yearned to
be a vessel...
for the pain.
But Gladiale is
becoming stronger
with every single
day that passes...
And the time is
already here...
But where are they?
I can't find them...!
Is the legend of the
Black Knights true?
I've poured out my
heart through music...
But if that's
not enough...
Fine...
Hear me, Great Will.
Take me now...
I freely give you my soul!
We were not aware that
there would be triple digit
casualties in
the Second Melt.
What exactly went wrong?
Was there some sort of
flaw in the software?
No, the casualties were
within our estimates,
within mine anyway.
Then why didn't someone
notify us of this beforehand?
There are certain
preliminary arrangements
that must be made in order
to control information.
Don't forget who's
in charge here,
I will not be at the
mercy of your whims,
do you understand me? !
Now, gentlemen...
Very soon, you won't have
to worry about
upsetting your constituents
or campaigning for votes
or covering up your tracks
because of some scandal...
A new day's upon us...
And we will change
this world forever.
Mind your tongue!
Just remember, your job
is to follow orders
and make sure things run
according to plan...
If you do what
we tell you to,
there won't be any problems.
We're the ones calling
the shots here.
Understood.
Now then, let's
hear your report
on the progress of the
second-generation machine.
The Noah II, of course.
Hey... It was you.
You real-booted
that flowerbed...
Because of that,
her life was saved.
Huh? What are you saying?
Don't play dumb
with me...!
So are you connected with
the Church of Natural
Divine Light?
And where did you learn
that power from...?
Who taught you...? Tell me!
I don't... I don't
know what you mean!
So you're really not
involved with them?
You're telling me the
truth, aren't you?
What are you
talking about?
What's the Church
of Divine Light?
I'm sorry...
Forget I even
mentioned it.
No, wait!
So... What's this "power"...?
Tell me, did I really make
that flowerbed appear?
You wished for it and
then it came true.
It is possible to convert
delusions to reality.
Objects that aren't real get
mixed in with what we see...
In other words,
you can make people believe
these errors exist.
Yeah... but...
if they only think
they're there...
then they're...
really just figments
of their imagination?
The world can be explained
with three numbers:
Zero, one and negative one...
It's everything...
Our entire existence.
Di-swords are used as
accelerated gateways
to creating those
negative-ones...
But somehow, you accomplished
this without a di-sword...
How lucky to be able to
believe everything you see...
I envy that.
Wow... Sena really does
know something after all.
Let's move!
Ayase... Why?
What a waste of time...
In the end I didn't
even get to see Rimi.
Rimi!
-Nanami.
-Hey, Taku,
you'll never
believe this...
Something incredible
happened at school today!
This girl jumped
right off the roof
and landed in a flowerbed...
It was really terrible.
Oh the poor thing, I hope
she'll be all right...
I'm totally worried.
Yeah right, I'm
sure you are.
The earthquake was
pretty amazing, too...!
My head was pounding.
It was the worst pain
I've ever felt...
Wonder why it hurt so bad?
Her too?
It's probably
just the quake...
But something's
not right today...
The city feels weird.
It's not because of me...
It's not because of me!
Takumi's pretty
popular, huh?
I didn't see
that one coming.
Hey Takumi...
It's not nice to make
girls cry, you know?
Did you use FES up
and toss her aside?
Takki, you naughty boy.
This is the worst...
Those damn jerks are never
gonna leave me alone...
Rimi... Where is she?
Daisuke.
What's wrong?
Stop it...
Please, I'm not even
worth looking at!
Oh I think you're
worth it...
You're worth a lot...!
You were the one
who saved the girl
who tried to
commit suicide.
Without you she'd be dead.
You see? You
should always try
and look on the bright
side of life, Takumi,
that way you won't
be so depressed.
That voice...
It feels like it's resonating
directly inside my head...
A delusion.
Hey mister, I'm
not a delusion.
Kozzy is real...
I'm right here!
Who the hell
is "Kozzy"...?!
Where is "here"? !
You're totally wrong to
think you have no worth...
It's just not true...
Not one little bit...
You know what...?
They're the ones...
The people in class who
say mean things about you
are the ones who
are worthless.
Trust - Please
just stop it!
It's true...
I've completely lost my
mind, I've gone insane.
Rimi...
Help me...
It's like I'm
completely worthless...
Useless.
Hey that hurt...
You... come with
me for a second.
What's wrong...? You
done already, kid?
What should we do now?
I don't know, I guess
we should rough him up
a little more...
That is what the man
said he wanted after all.
Well, I'll tell
you this much,
he must really
hate this guy,
paying us money to kick
his ass like this.
All right, let's get
to it, gentlemen!
I want to kill them...
Every last one of
these bastards...
I want their blood.
I want to watch
them all die!
What's that transfer
student doing here?
What the hell is this...?!
Did I...
I don't understand this,
what happened here?
Did I blackout back there?
How long was
I unconscious?
For about five minutes.
Again?
Whose voice is that...?
Oh no-
It can't be, that's
impossible...
Telepathy isn't real, how
is this happening to me?
How can I convince
you to believe me?
If you can hear me...
then tell me your
measurements.
Takumi, that's gross,
you are such a pervert.
That's true.
Okay... What's your birthday?
I was born on the
thirteenth of November...
See? Huh...?
No way... It's real.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you
from the very beginning,
but you wouldn't
listen!
It's really you, Kozue?
Call me Kozzy.
Kozzy, huh?
Come on... We should
probably get out of here!
How can she speak
to me with her mind?
I didn't even know things
like this were possible.
I guess it's a little
creepy, isn't it?
Do you think I'm a weirdo?
Honestly I don't mind...
Compared to the crazy people
I've been running into lately,
you seem pretty normal.
Crazy?
Oh yeah...
You do talk
kind of funny...
But I don't mind.
Oh thank you, that makes me
so happy I could just cry!
But wait a sec...
You said those
people were crazy.
How so?
Well.
One of the girls
looks really scary
and all she does is babble on
about incomprehensible stuff
like brain waves...
She also carries
around a huge sword.
What kind of sword
is it...? A di-sword?
Yeah it is...
Wait... Hold on!
How do you know
about di-swords? !
'Cause I've got
one, silly boy!
Wow... A di-sword.
This is it!
Pretty cool, huh...?
I use my di-sword to
go after bad guys!
Bad guys, huh?
If you wanna
hear my opinion,
I don't think people like
that deserve to live!
It was you...
You were the one who took
them out, weren't you?
They're barely human.
Nothing more than a
bunch of cockroaches.
She's not malicious, she's
just so matter of fact...
It's like it's a regular
occurrence for her.
Yay! Sena's here!
Sena?
Kozue.
So you're friends
with Sena, huh...?
Uh, don't tell her I
said she was nuts.
I'm new to Tokyo and
when I got here,
Sena was the first
real friend I made.
She's the best!
Kozue...
What are you
doing with him?
Oh! Taku and I are
in class together!
Calling me "Taku" already?
And that's not all...!
He can see my di-sword
too, can't you?
Yes I'm aware...
He's also a gigalomaniac
just like we are.
Gigalo-... What was that?
A "gigalomaniac"...
It's a person who can
see di-swords...!
Apparently, you're one too!
I'm a gigalomaniac?
Hey, Sena, you're on your
way to buy popsicles
at the corner store,
aren't you?
Uh... well, yeah, but...
Awesome...!
That's perfect,
we can all go there together!
My company's made
great strides
with the second-generation
Noah II...
It is now possible to show
people artificial images
in their minds.
Is it something
like a hologram?
Or perhaps a collective
hallucination?
It's much closer to
a hallucination...
but there is one major
difference of course.
The artificial images have a
tangible sense of presence
and therefore are perceived
as being part of reality.
What's this?
Did something happen?
I don't understand,
what's causing these
people to panic?
They're panicking
because they can see it.
See what...? What is it?
A runaway excavator.
A runaway excavator...?
Created by Noah II?
The artificial images
created by Noah II
were converted to
optical nerve impulses
and radiated as
electromagnetic waves.
They pass through the skin
and penetrate the skull
where they are caught by
dopamine receptors
inside the brain.
The final process is
pushing the images
to unused portions
of the mind.
This is the mechanism for
creating something
from nothing within human
vision and perception.
So in effect,
it now rivals
the abilities of the
gigalomaniacs?
Yes that's the
whole point...
Basically, the Noah II is
an artificial gigalomaniac
over which we have
complete control.
What about the
coverage area?
How accurately can you focus
the output of these waves?
We are not interested
in indiscriminately
brainwashing everybody.
There's no need
to worry...
I've prepared variable
factors for that very reason.
Who are these ruffians?
What do they have to
do with all of this?
My company is calling
them porters...
Put another way, you
might think of them
as a mind control team,
assisting in
managing targets...
Each porter has a mechanism
in their backpack
designed to be a transceiver for
images created by Noah II.
When any of these units
receives a signal,
they automatically broadcast it
to their surrounding area.
I see, so they're
mobile terminals.
If that's the case then
there would be virtually
no limit to their
effective range, correct?
And, with an
army of porters,
limited use becomes
a nonissue as well.
Well...? Tell me...
Why are you with this guy?
Takumi was in trouble,
bad guys were after him
and he needed help.
So I stepped in and
delivered some justice!
Your di-sword,
did you use it?
You bet I did...
Take that...! Bam...!
And that...!
I told you not to do anything
stupid, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean the popsicle.
Just be more careful.
Huh? Thank you.
I still don't
understand exactly
what happened with those
guys back there...?
Did Kozzy save me...?
Or was it... me?
Listen... Sena
knows everything.
Just ask her...!
She was the first one to tell
me about the di-sword...
And also real
bolting...!
Or was it... real bot...?
Real boom?
It's real-boot.
Yeah, that's it!
What's real-boot?
If a di-sword isn't
real-booted,
then technically no one should
be able to see it...
But Sena could...! Oh I
was so excited about it...
I asked her why and she said
we're both gigalomaniacs.
So... what is a gigalomaniac?
Whoa... What is that? !
It's a monster excavator!
No this can't be real-
It's one of their experiments!
Oh no!
You... Stay right there!
Huh?
Gigalomaniacs are those with
the power to interfere-
To disrupt the
flow of the Dirac Sea.
The Dirac Sea...?
Wait a second,
I think I've read
about that online...
It's an
unobservable vacuum
filled with negative
energy, right?
The essential function of
a di-sword is to serve
as a shortcut to real-booting
something into existence!
When you widen the gap
between the di-sword
and the vacuum of
negative energy,
according to the hole theory
of the Dirac equation,
formations occur...
A particle and
an antiparticle.
These particles...
They're the
delusional errors
created by gigalomaniacs...
To make the error a
part of reality,
all you have to do is
transmit that information
to a dead spot in
someone's mind.
There it's converted to
an electrical signal...
and it's jointly acknowledged
by those in the vicinity...
In other words...
the error becomes real.
These two young girls,
are we sure they're
gigalomaniacs?
It would appear so.
Well, well, well.
I don't understand...
Who are they
fighting against?
What does the popsicle in
your hand look like...?
Describe it.
Well... It's just a...
It's an ordinary
blue popsicle.
But is it part
of reality...?
How can you prove that
it actually exists?
Huh?
You accept that
what you're seeing
and holding is a
blue popsicle...
But only 'cause your
brain recognizes it.
What if it were possible
for your brain to lie to you,
or trick you into seeing
something that isn't there...?
Consider the possibility
that your brain is creating
a delusion of a popsicle
that only you
believe exists.
But I don't understand,
then how can you ever know
if something's
real or not?
If more than one
individual sees
what you're holding
in your hand
and confirms it is
indeed a blue popsicle,
it becomes a part of the
collective awareness
and you know
that it exists.
This is how you
create your reality...
To make a delusion
into reality,
you simply need to run
this process in reverse.
So in other words, if you
were to create a delusion,
then use the particles
form the di-sword
to force other
people to see it,
it would enter the
collective awareness
and become a part
of reality?
I am so confused...!
Only thing I
know for sure
is that normal people
can't see this sword.
No, Kozzy, don't!
Don't worry, they
don't feel a thing! See?
Oh I see...
The sword doesn't
have physical matter.
Bingo, Takumi...!
My di-sword isn't real,
it's just my delusion!
Right now, that sword's
nothing more
than an imagined
error Kozue created...
Since there's no
shared awareness
with the people
around her,
the sword doesn't exist.
But if I real-boot it,
then everybody would be
able to see it, right, Sena?
I think I understand...
Real-booting is the
process of sending
the particle to a dead spot
inside a person's mind,
-isn't it?
-You got it...
And when that
happens, you can
"wham", "bam", "pow" like I did!
But wait...
Is it possible I might
have that power too?
Don't worry, you'll get
your sword. I know it!
Yeah, but how?
Well... Now that
you mention it,
I'm not exactly sure
how that works.
When there's a big
spike in biorhythms...
excessive amounts
of dopamine
are secreted inside the neurons
of the mesolimbic pathway...
and your di-sword appears.
It could happen when
you're in grave danger...
or angry...
or happy or sad...
Everyone's different...
The more dopamine
involved...
the easier it
is to observe.
See, I told you
Sena was brilliant!
When I'm in grave
danger, huh?
It's too dangerous to
let those girls run free.
We have to stop them.
If we don't do
something immediately,
they could become
a real problem.
Gentlemen, relax...
Leave that issue to me,
just like you did
with the samples.
Well, you have
three codes already
and you still haven't
reached the target yet...
What exactly is
the issue here,
how many more will we need?
It'll be impossible
to reach those numbers
without code samples from at
least five more subjects.
My people are already
working on it.
Then we leave
everything to you...
Move forward with the plan
and keep us informed
of your progress.
May the divine
light prevail...
It is important that we
all be extremely cautious
from here on out.
Of course... I'll
be very careful...
Everything we do is
for the sake of our
unified ideals, is it not?
With every day
that passes,
their experiments get
more out of control.
So that thing they're
making is almost finished?
We're going to carry
out our plan soon.
Yes, sir!
I don't get it, what
are they talking about?
Your name... What is it?
Uh... My name's
Takumi Nishijo.
Listen up...
You real-booted without a
di-sword, Takumi Nishijo...
Until you, no one's been
able to do that before...
Which means you're
not normal...
And I wouldn't
be surprised
if they're
targeting you too.
But... Tell me... Why?
There are people who
are trying to use
the power of the
gigalomaniacs for evil.
Yes... But who?
Nozomi Technology.
Are you talking about
the Nozomi Group?
Yes...
They're very powerful...
They have many branches
that carry out
business licensed by
the government...
They're doing research
and development for
sinister reasons.
They plan to use a device
called the Noah II
to artificially create the
power of gigalomaniacs
and ultimately to
alter reality.
Remember the earthquake
from the other day?
It was caused by a
Noah II experiment.
Uh, Kozzy...?
Are you sure she's not
having a delusion?
No it's true...! And Sena
and I are going to stop them...
We'll take down
the Nozomi Group
and teach them a lesson!
Our only option
is to destroy the
Nozomi Corporation
once and for all.
I've got a great idea!
What if Taku
comes with us?
No I shouldn't-
Sure you should!
Now we're the
gigalomaniac trio!
-Hold on.
-Ooh...!
We should go take a
picture together to celebrate!
Perfect... Let's go!
Takumi... You
stand in the middle!
But I don't want to-
Come on, get in
there, guys. Hurry, go!
I don't do this stuff-
I know, it's my first
time, too. I'm so excited!
Okay! Say cheese!
[Music]
Those eyes... Whose are they?