[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo...
I recently discovered that
the mysterious formula
I doodled on the
back of an essay
I wrote in elementary school
is the exact same one
the General sent to me
while we were
chatting online.
Then on the way home from
visiting Ayase in the hospital,
Sena attacked me...
Apparently the
Nozomi Corporation
developed the technology
which led to Noah II
based on the formula
in my doodle...
Sena took out her rage
and frustration on me
because she lost her mother
and sister in those experiments.
And again...
I was saved by Rimi.
It turns out she's
a gigalomaniac, too.
I was worried about Nanami,
so I tried to go to my parents'
place to check on her.
But...
my home was nowhere
to be found.
Taku... Listen...
Your house has
never been here...
You just assumed it was...
Don't you see...?
Your memories are
nothing more
than your mind
tricking you.
But I... I...
Look I remember
growing up here...
I... I remember everything...
I don't understand this.
Taku... Your memories
are fabricated.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you're not real.
You shouldn't exist.
She's been lying
all along...
I thought I
could trust her.
It was you...
Yes... You were
behind the staking!
Taku... That was fake.
If our delusions
get too strong...
sometimes they'll mix...
They'll synchronize
with the delusions
of other gigalomaniacs.
At that time...
three synchronized
delusions
were happening
simultaneously...
Mine first...
Then yours...
Then the New Gen criminal.
You liar!
This isn't happening...
It's fake...
Another delusion...
Now I just have
to wake up!
You can't have any
more delusions.
If you keep this up...
Then I'll be forced
to erase you.
Erase...? Erase me...?
You really are the
New Gen criminal.
I'm not even real,
and you're gonna kill me...?
I don't understand...
What am I?
Taku...
You're only an
imagined person,
simply a gigalomaniac's
delusion.
You were born a little
over a year ago today.
No way... 'cause...
if that's true and
I'm that young,
then shouldn't
I be a toddler?
Since the time
you came to be,
you've always been you.
Then who created me,
whose delusion am I?
The real Takumi Nishijo.
I didn't want you to have
to deal with any of this...
I didn't want you to come
in the first place...
But now...
You've come this far...
Maybe it's better you know
the truth about who you are.
But wait,
if I'm a delusion...
then Nanami and my
parents are too!
This is seriously
messed up...
I was really hoping
that you were going to
be on my side, Rimi...
But I guess you've betrayed
me too, haven't you?
I know...
It's true...
I've been hiding lots
of things from you...
Sorry...
I'll understand if
you hate me forever.
I don't believe you...
I don't care if
you apologize...
I don't trust you.
Rimi's kindness...
Her warmth all but
saved my soul...
She taught me the
meaning of friendship...
But now...
That warmth feels like
it's an entire world away.
I have to leave soon.
Where do you have to go?
I'm going to hunt down
Nanami's kidnapper...
I have to bring an
end to all of this.
'Cause at this rate I won't
be able to protect you either.
What do you mean?
So Nanami has been kidnapped?
I'll be back, just wait
for me at your place...
Then we'll talk...
We'll gossip and have
all sorts of fun...
Taku... Will you
promise me one thing...?
Please don't have any
more delusions, okay...?
Your power is a lot stronger
than you think it is...
Each time you have
another delusion...
it shaves life
off the real you,
and shortens his time.
I don't get it...
No wait... Don't go.
See you later...
I gotta run...
Ten-hut!
Rimi.
How cute...
What is it called?
Well, her name is
Weepy the Frog.
Oh hello...
Miss Weepy.
So... Momo...
Tell me where we stand...
Any leads on Shinko?
Well, it looks like your
hunch hit the mark, Banny Boy.
The parent company
of Shinko Limited
is Nozomi Technology.
I don't...
Nozomi what?
And why am I
not surprised?
Five years ago,
they merged by acquisition
into the Nozomi
Corporation...
Ever since, they've put
out a lot of products,
most of which have
been big hits.
It seems their change in
marketing strategy worked...
Basically what
they do is...
They crank out a new product
every weekend, am I right?
Yep.
How does this
relate to GE rates?
There's no way to deny
there's a connection...
All the evidence
points that way.
Since the merger
five years ago,
weekend GE Rates have
gone nowhere but up.
And that's not the only
interesting piece of
information about Shinko...
I went through all of
their documentation
from the very beginning...
and I think I hooked
us a big fish here.
Just how big?
Kozo Inohana.
He's the leader of
the Meiwa Party.
Things are starting
to connect...
The thing with
the Professor,
not to mention
the earthquake...
We've got the Meiwa Party
exerting pressure
on the media outlets...
And stopping all reporting
concerning GE rates.
Um... Excuse me...
But I'm starting
to get scared here.
A public phone?
Hello?
Who's this?
Sir, I'm so sorry...
I screwed up.
What happened?
Suwa... Tell me
what's going on!
I'm... at AH Tokyo
General Hospital.
What? The hospital?
What the hell
happened to you?
You there...? Suwa!
What's wrong?
Is everything okay?
Don't know...
But I'll tell
you this much,
somebody who doesn't like
what we've been up to
is making a move here.
Stay put and keep
your head down...
You got it?
Hey... Wait...!
Banny!
I wasn't created by
someone's delusion.
I know it...!
I'm real,
I'm Takumi Nishijo!
Hello?
Uh... Hey... Daisuke
Hey, Taku...! How are
things with you and Rimi...?
You owe me big time for leaving
you two alone by the way!
Daisuke knows me, that
means I must be real...
There's no need to worry,
I'm not a delusion.
You wanna hear
something funny?
The other day, my
girlfriend was asking me
how come you and I became such
good friends all of a sudden.
I sort of remember meeting
you through Rimi...
but for some reason I can't
remember any of the details,
it's all a little
bit hazy to me.
No...! Shut up,
don't say any more!
So what's up...?
When exactly did you
and I become friends?
I can't find anybody
who can prove to me
that I really do exist.
Well then...
I've got to get going.
I'm telling you,
I'll be fine...
you don't need to
worry about a thing...
I'll settle this.
I'm going to take care
of everything, Takumi...
Goodbye.
Detective!
I'm so glad you're here...
I just saw a suspicious
looking man go up on the roof.
Stay here.
The person that Detective Ban
is investigating,
I'm sure he's the one
who killed Mia...
I just have this feeling.
Mia?
Wait, am I seeing a ghost?
No, she's real.
Come on, Grim,
just say something.
Anything... Grim.
May the divine
light save you.
What's he saying?
Kill me...
I want you to kill me!
Somebody please...
just kill me...!
Rimi!
Taku...! Open the door...!
Let me in, Taku!
Wait a sec...
-That voice...
-Open up, dummy!
Nanami?
Wow, so you're alive.
She's acting
totally different
than the Nanami
on the phone...
Oh, I get it...
This Nanami must
be a delusion.
Hey, what's wrong, Taku...?
You seem upset.
Oh, shut up!
You know what...?
I don't appreciate you
talking to me like that!
What do you care?
You're not even real.
Not real...?
Taku... What's wrong?
You're not acting
like yourself at all.
I get it. You must
be hungry, huh...?
You want me to cook you
up something delicious?
Nanami, I need your help.
Just kill me...
Please, I want
you to kill me.
Huh?
Was I imagining things?
I know that laugh...
It's Mia!
Mia... It's you...
But how?
Do you really
think I'm Mia...?
Do you believe
that you're Yua?
What do you mean?
What if it's the
opposite, huh?
What if you're Mia and Yua
was the one who died...?
What if you were the
one who killed her?
No... What are you saying?
You hated your sister
because your parents
loved her more...
So you hired a killer
over the internet.
What's more...
to cover your tracks and
make it look like a suicide,
you made four
strangers jump.
So you became
the other sister.
And then you
pretended to grieve
and shed tears over your twin
sister's death, didn't you?
No... that can't be...!
-I am Yua!
-Yeah?
Can anyone prove that?
Me.
You saying it's true
doesn't mean anything to
anyone else, does it?
There's no way I'm Mia,
it's impossible!
Think about all those things
you've been investigating...
Multiple personalities...
sleepwalking...
memory forging...
and also delusions.
I don't understand
anymore...
I don't know what I am!
Who I am!
Well, whoever you are,
you'll suffer the
same fate that I did.
In the beginning we were
joined together as one person...
We're simply returning.
With one step, I am you...
With one step,
you will become me.
Our fates are intertwined.
Because we are one person.
Sir, you came.
Suwa?
I'm glad you did.
What happened,
are you okay?
I'm just fine.
Suwa.
Well...
I should be congratulated
for my first shot.
Tell me why.
Because you got a
hold of information
you didn't need to know,
you were too clever
for your own good, sir.
I'm a detective.
Yes, but so am I.
But... you and
I were partners...
How could you go and
betray me like this?
Because honestly, sir,
you've always irritated
the hell out of me...
And now... it's
time for payback...
I have specific orders
to eliminate anything
that stands in my way.
Suwa...!
Please don't make
this mistake...!
Don't be a puppet
for these men,
you have to be in
control of your own mind!
May the divine
light save you, sir.
What are you doing...?
Don't you try to
run away from this.
You must feel
the pain I felt!
-But Mia...
-You're wrong...
Remember I'm Yua.
No, that's not true.
It is, you're Mia.
No, I don't understand.
Who are you?
I'm everything that
you wished for...
And you are everything
that I wished for.
Please...
For once in your life,
listen to what I have to say...
I have been patient with
you this whole time!
She'll kill me.
You see...?
The same face.
No one can tell who's
Mia and who's Yua,
'cause we're the same!
No way.
Hold on...
What's this...?
Tell me, what did
you just do to me?
Mia... I see...
It all makes sense now...
I finally understand,
I know why I put
so much effort
into investigating
your murder.
I was afraid of you...
And I always have been...
I thought you died
as a way to spite me.
I wanted to make
myself feel better
by proving once
and for all
that your death
wasn't my fault
and that I had
nothing to do with it.
No!
My sister...
has been dead
for two months...
So who are you?
What the...?
What's happening?
Don't tell me this brat's
a gigalomaniac...!
To hell with this!
Who's there?
Ayase...?
Wha...?
The power of the Great
Will kept me close by...
That's why I remained
here at the hospital...
It was leading me to you.
You see... You're one of the
seven Black Knights of Gladiale.
The Black Knights...?
What's that?
Come on... Just
hurry up and kill me.
Oh please, why don't
you give it a rest
with the lame jokes, Taku.
That's not like Nanami...
The real Nanami
would get angry
and lecture me
for being stupid.
I meant to tell you...
I feel really bad 'cause I
lost the bracelet you gave me.
I'm so sorry...
It's the first present you
ever gave me, you remember...?
I really did love
that bracelet...
And I don't know
how I lost it...
Taku... You hear
what I said?
I just...
Why do you always act
like this, Taku...?
You know it
wouldn't kill you
to show me some
brotherly dependability
every once in a while.
I'm... I'm just a delusion,
I'm not even real!
Sometimes... I just
wish you would pamper me
and treat me with a
little more kindness.
Hey, I'm kinda
sad now, so...
I want you to hold me
for a little bit...
Will you please?
Just for once let me have
it my way, okay...?
Just give me a hug...
Come on... Please?
It's okay...
There's no need
to be afraid.
Noah II...
It's already working.
It's all thanks to you.
Hello there, Rimi...
It's been a while,
hasn't it?
Nanami!
Of course you
must know this...
But you being here
is a big problem.
You let Nana go!
She doesn't have anything
to do with this!
Nanami!
Rimi.
My right hand...
It hurts...
It hurts bad.
Nana!
Hey uh... Rimi...
You haven't seen my bracelet
anywhere have you...?
I can't find it...
I've looked everywhere.
A bracelet?
Oh yeah... That's right...
Don't you worry...
I know exactly
where it is...
Let's just get
out of here
and we'll go get
it together.
My... My hand hurts bad...
Rimi...
How do you and I
know each other...?
I can't remember.
I feel like I should know
you but there's nothing...
-It's blank.
-Nanami.
Rimi tell me... did you
steal my bracelet?!
Why?! That's so mean.
What exactly are
you showing her?
Did you take it, Rimi?
Don't lie to me!
Of course I didn't.
Why did you take
it from me...?
Give it back...
Please just give
it back to me!
It's okay! Calm down...
It's precious to me,
you know...?
It was a present
from my brother...
I don't want anyone else
to have it but me...!
Give it to me...
Give it to me!
Give it back!
No way... A di-sword!
Please, give it back...
I want it...
If you don't...
I won't forgive you...
I swear!
Nana...
I can't believe you're
a gigalomaniac too!
You can cry... but I
still can't do anything...
Don't you get it,
I'm just a delusion...
I'm not real.
It's impossible, you're
real, I know it...!
I remember everything from
when we were little kids,
don't you, Taku?
You may not be
very dependable...
But regardless,
you're my brother
and we've been together
since the beginning!
That's it...
Nanami is right...
I remember when we were little
kids growing up together...
I have memories
of our childhood!
Nanami.
My sister...
She's the only hope I
have left in this world.
Nobody else can rescue
me from this nightmare.
Nanami...
Help me...
Please help me.
Taku.
If Nanami's warmth is real,
I can prove to myself
that I actually do exist!
Please hug me...
Will you?
If this is the only way
I'll be able to save Nanami...
If this is the only
way to save myself!
Nanami...
Save me.
Oh, Taku!
You did cruel things to Nana
just like you did to me!
Don't worry she wasn't
near as much effort as you.
You see it's not
like before,
now we have set procedures
for awakening our specimen...
Of course it goes
without saying,
none of those protocols will
work on Takumi Nishijo...
There's nothing
more difficult
than dealing with an irregular
monster, is there?
He's not a monster,
don't call him that!
Yes of course I'm sorry...
How... about a freak
born from nothingness?
I'm taking her
back with me.
Please be my guest...
We're already finished.
So... I'm dying to
know something...
You're both extremely
valuable to Takumi Nishijo...
but if he had to choose,
which one of you
is more important?
I remember this...
The dark...
It brings back memories
of when it first began.
I woke up and I
was imprisoned,
being used as a test subject
in some sort of experiment...
I knew nothing of
myself before then...
My consciousness came into
being in that waking moment...
or at least it seemed so.
Maybe the personality that
existed in this body before me,
erased herself inside
her own delusion.
To escape the
terrible pain.
Who really knows...?
And maybe there had been
different personalities
before her?
Who am I?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Hmph.
Grim said to come.
I don't care...
I don't care about
any of this anymore!
It's just like Grim
said it would be...
A party...
A big party!
It hurts...
Please help me!
-Seira!
-Takki...
You silly...
If I stay here,
someone will kill me...
Erase me.
Listen... You can't die yet.
Are you responsible
for this...?
Did you do it?
It's begun...
They're on the move.
"They"?
The ones behind it all...
The ones who caused
this chaos...
Don't you understand?
You're the only one
who can stop them!
A gunshot?
What's happening?
Why are they
acting this way?
It's Shibuya's GE rates...
People's biorhythms are
spiking out of control...
The people here are under
an invisible attack,
they don't even realize
it's happening.
The silent weapon...
Noah II's already
operational...
The primary goal
is indiscriminate human
experimentation...
You see...?
You're the only one who
can stop it, Takumi...
You are our only hope.
It was you?
Of course...
I've always been watching.
[Music]
Those eyes...
Whose are they?