A piercing gaze
falls from the sky
like rays of light.
Don't look...
Not at me.
I'm so sorry.
An angel...?
It's me and her...
We are the only two people
who exist in this world...
If we were to look into
each other's eyes forever,
what would I see...?
Would my world be confined
to what was
reflected in hers?
And what would she see...?
Would her world
be confined to
what was reflected in mine?
I am everything to her...
She is everything to me...
forever.
[Music]
Takki...!
Come on, wake up...!
Takki!
Seira baby!
Hey... this is exactly
the way she woke people up
in the second episode
of "Blood Tune"...
I'm in heaven!
Hurry up or you'll
be late to school.
Get a move-on, mister!
Hey!
It won't hurt anything if I
miss the first class today.
Oh boy...
You might be the laziest
person I have ever met.
Making a chart
outlining the maximum
number of days you can miss,
and still receive the minimum
number of credits required.
You should be ashamed
of yourself Takki.
Those eyes,
whose are they?
No way!
Yes!
Guess what he did next?
Whatever, they probably
think I'm disgusting.
But I don't care...
3D girls are the
ones who are gross.
Yo! Well, well, look who
decided to come to school today.
Hey Daisuke,
what's up, man?
As usual, you look
down in the dumps.
Stay up too late
playing video games?
Not to brag, but yesterday
I bagged my third girl
in this class...
A few more to go
and my collection of the
hottest chicks in school
will be complete.
Yeah right.
Yeah... I wouldn't expect
a shut-in like you
to understand...
Hey, I don't suppose
you've heard anything
about the "New Gen"
crimes, have you?
No... What's the "New Gen?"
It's what they're calling
all the weird stuff
that's been happening lately.
Get a load of this!
In a report, the eyewitness
said the criminal is a girl,
and a bona fide hotty!
Man, if she's as
hot as they say,
she can perpetrate
a crime on me...!
-I'm in love!
-Cool.
Yeah, yeah, I know
it's super cool.
Hey... You wanna come to
the scene of the murder
with me today...?
Maybe we'll get lucky and
bump into that sexy killer.
You know what they say?
People always return to
the scene of the crime.
No thanks.
Good talk.
Yes...! I did it!
Wow, Takki,
you're the best!
There's just no
denying it, is there?
I'm unbeatable
in this world.
That's why they call
me the Knight Heart,
I'm the best there is!
It's from Grim?
Your levels are
getting too easy.
How 'bout a challenge?
Reality, huh? Lame...
You know I don't care about
the three dimensional world.
The New Gen.
What's that?
"You're slipping,
Knight Heart...
Stick around and maybe
you'll learn something...
See ya"?
Look, Takki, there's
a link there.
There is now a common name
for the two incidents
that have happened during
recent months here in Shibuya...
First named the "Wrath
of the New Generation",
it's now called
the "New Gen."
The first case was about a group
of five high school students
who committed suicide by
jumping off a tall building...
People call this
the "Group Dive."
The second case
involved a male corpse
later found to have a
fetus stuffed inside it...
This is called the
"Pregnant Man."
My goodness, what is this?
Taku...! What gives?
Open up...!
It's Nanami.
Come on, let me in...!
Stupid brother...
You'll get it if you
don't open this door...!
Come on, let me in!
So you're still alive!
Ugh! It stinks in here...
Why's your bedroom always
such a disgusting mess...?
Didn't I tell you
to clean up...?
Don't you ever listen?
Well... Since you don't
have a girlfriend
who is willing to
do it for you...
and since I'm such
an amazing sibling,
I've decided I'm
going to help you.
No thanks.
What do you mean?
Look... This is my room...
I don't want you in here
messing everything up.
You jerk!
How can you be so mean to
your little sister,
who came all this way just to
make sure you're okay...?!
It's not fair,
why was I cursed with such
a hateful big brother
who causes me nothing
but trouble!
I don't know.
Ah... I am dying of thirst...
Let me take a sip.
You could've at least
used a cup, you know?
I am using one.
Oh, okay then.
Hey... Will you please leave?
Aren't you done
annoying me yet?
No actually I'm not...
I am going to help you
purchase a new cell phone.
It's Dad's idea...
That way we can
always be in touch.
You should get the
same model as me!
I can even get us matching
charms, how cool is that?
Gross, the person who
designed that should be shot.
You don't know
Hoppy the Frog...?
He's so hot right now.
High school girl
fashion trends,
there is no way he'll
ever understand that.
Whatever...
Let's go get
you a phone...
And just so you know, we're
not getting the same models
so we can match...
We're doing it
because Daddy says
we can get a
family discount.
-No, I don't want it!
-Why not?
Dad's paying for it, it's not
like you have to do anything.
I don't need one.
Sometimes I just
can't stand you...!
Goodbye!
Geez.
You could at least walk
me to the bus station!
Don't feel like it.
This neighborhood has been
dangerous lately, you know?
You don't say.
No way...
You don't even care what
happens to your own sister?
Jackass, jackass!
I hope that serial killer
chops you up into little pieces!
Finally some
peace and quiet.
Those eyes...
whose are they?
The General?
An image link?
Now, where did he come
from out of the blue?
A virus...?
There's no way I'm
gonna fall for that.
Better luck next time.
What's with this guy?
I won't click your link.
"Not a virus."
Huh, is that so...?
Don't be so cryptic then.
Where are you from?
"Shibuya. "Me too.
Strange happenings
lately, huh?
"There's more to come."
A formula?
Wait, what is this...?
Who is this General person,
some sort of
doomsday nutcase?
What's the deal
with this link?
You're saying that
if I click on it
things will get interesting.
"Give it a try."
Oh no, what is this?
Nanami smash!
Sorry.
Excuse me!
Hey, throw it over here!
Sure...
Here it comes!
Oh.
Uh, one more time.
Here it comes!
Geez, that girl
was terrible.
I've never seen
anyone that bad!
She must be
rich or spoiled.
Thanks to that General guy,
I can't relax at home...
I'll just hang out here for a
little bit in my usual spot.
Good times.
Huh?
That's the same
one Nanami has.
Why would you want three?
Researching New Gen?
And just when everything
was starting to look up.
What's that...?
I am in Shibuya, right...?
Least I think.
What's this?
That's the image...
From the General's link.
Hello...
I've been waiting
for you, Taku.
Hello...
I've been waiting
for you, Taku.
What...?
How does that
girl know my name?
What the hell was that?
What is happening to me?
She saw my face...
She looked at me and
called me by my name...
What should I do?
Hey, it's okay, Takki.
I'm sure it was just
one of your delusions.
But... But that stake?
I don't see anything.
Huh...?You're kidding.
Now no more negative
delusions, mister.
Think positive, okay...?
Don't I love you most
when you're happy?
You're right Seira...
It must've been
a delusion!
What was I thinking?
Happy thoughts
from now on!
Now I can see the shape
of a cross here...
dark gray needles form...
the image for me...
Washing o'er us
while you're near.
Cleansing our sin...
Our prayers
are with you...
holy one.
Those eyes...
whose are they?
Who is that?
Someone's watching me?
Damn it, why is
she following me?
Maybe it's the demon
girl from yesterday?
Has she come
here to kill me?
Hey... Hope you're
having a good morning.
Did I do something to make
her hold a grudge against me?
No, that's impossible...
No one pays
attention to me,
I might as well
be invisible.
I don't know, maybe
I was overreacting
with the whole being
followed thing?
I was right, she's been stalking
me since this morning...
She must be working
with that devil girl!
Stop it, no!
Was that a delusion?
Either way, I better
get outta here.
That was so not awesome.
Excuse me, but are
you gonna be okay?
Do you need me to take you
to the hospital or something?
Who are you...?
Why are you following me?
Please... Tell me
what you want from me!
I, um... well,
you see I wanted to...
Well, my name is...
Yua Kusunoki and I just...
Well... The truth is...
after I saw you
this morning
I couldn't get you
out of my mind.
I see...
She's trying
to seduce me...
I won't fall for it.
Uh... Listen...
You're bothering me...
So... please stop
following me around.
I'm so sorry.
Wait, is she being
sincere...?
Just... Just please
leave me alone...
You sure you don't
need a doctor?
Look, I'm fine!
At least let me
walk you home...
After all, it's my fault you got
hurt in the first place...
Let me help,
it's no biggie.
Um, what part of
town do you live in?
Uh... In Shinsen.
Shinsen?
Oh crap...
Why did I just
tell her that...?
What am I expecting
out of this?
I swear, my brother's
so mean to me sometimes!
And what pisses me off
even more is his obsession
with those stupid
little dolls!
So your brother's one
of those guys, huh?
Only interested
in anime chicks?
Ugh, boys like that
are totally weird.
The weirdest!
But you know what?
More women than
you'd expect
actually go for those
types of guys...
I have a friend like
that and she thinks,
"Oh I can change them,
I'm gonna save them
all from themselves!"
Hey! Maybe Takumi
can find a girl
to rescue him from
his otaku ways!
What...? My brother?
Sure, why not?
I... I think I can take
it from here, thanks.
Wow, this is it?
This is such a
cool place to live.
I could get
used to this...
It's awesome.
It's got a real
outlaw vibe to it,
living life on the
edge and all that.
I won't be fooled...
I will never let a 3D
girl get the best of me!
Feeling any better?
Yeah, I guess.
She's so gentle
and considerate...
No...!I won't
be tricked...
I will not be fooled!
Oh! That's Seira
from Blood Tune...
I love her.
Wait... Do you
know Blood Tune?
Yeah, I watch
it every week,
it's my favorite
TV show by far!
Oh, wow.
So you're a fan
of Seira, too?
I think she's awesome,
definitely the coolest
heroine out there.
Are... Are you
really an anime nerd?
Oh... nothing.
Hey, do you mind if I
take a look at these?
Um...
I'm really sorry if I'm
being too pushy here...
I guess I should
probably go home now.
No, go ahead and look.
Are you sure...?
Oh thank you so much!
That's the very first version
of the Seira action figure.
They've released a bunch
of different editions
since the game
came out...
That one's definitely
my favorite.
Wow.
Did you see that
shelf right there?
Cool, you have so many!
That's awesome!
Actually, I have every
Seira figurine ever made...
I've been waiting for them to
release the newest version...
But it's probably gonna
be pretty expensive.
You mean the
Awakened version
from the big scene
in Episode Twelve?
Wow, I'm really
impressed...
You sound like
a super fan.
Yeah I guess I am...!
I can't stop watching
that episode.
It gets better every time.
I think the reason
it's so awesome
is 'cause the acting
and animation director
is the same...
He's easily one of the best
directors in the business,
so the high quality
is to be expected.
Wow, you really do know a
lot about this kind of stuff,
don't you?
You should pay attention
to the writers and directors
who work
on those shows.
Oh I will now, thanks for
teaching me something new.
Hey, uh...
I don't mean to
be too forward.
But would you
tell me your name?
Yeah... I'm Takumi Nishijo.
It's nice to meet
you, Takumi...
What year are you?
Oh... uh... second.
Hey, I'm in third year...
I guess that means I'm
older than you are, huh?
Oh no... I'm falling for it,
I think she's
getting to me...
Is Yua like the serene,
gentle older girl?
So Takumi...
I have a small
favor to ask of you.
A favor?
I want you...
I've wanted you
for a long time...
I've always had my
eye on you, Takumi...
What's the matter? Don't you
wanna get to know me better?
Why is she wearing
Seira's bikini?
Ow...
I'm sorry,
I'm such a klutz.
I hope I didn't break
any of your CDs.
I'll clean it
up right away.
Uh. That's okay.
Oh no, it's nothing,
don't pay attention to me.
Please... try not to
touch the figurines, okay?
Uh, okay...
But...
That wasn't it-
I... don't mean
to alarm you,
but it's a fan
fiction mag...
There's some pretty
racy stuff in here...
I'm sorry, I wasn't expecting
to see something like that.
Don't look
through my things.
I'm sorry!
So like I was
saying before...
I have a favor to ask.
I really wanna go
to an anime store.
Would you please
come with me?
Huh?
As much as I love it,
I've never been before,
but I've always wanted to
see what one was like...
Uh, this is kind of a
bold move on my part
since I barely know you...
I'm sorry.
This has got
to be a trap...
Things like this
don't happen!
This is like some
farfetched plot
out of an erotic
fantasy game.
Well... Let's forget about it,
I don't want to put you
on the spot or anything...
It was good enough
just to be able to have
a nice long chat with you
This is an act,
I have to reject her.
I've gotta tell
her like a man!
You gotta be kidding!
She's crying?!
Now I'm just lost,
what the hell
is she up to?
Please, there's no
need to force it...
Anyway it's not
really fair for me
to drag you along for
my own selfish reasons.
I'll go.
Wait, are you serious?
Oh...
This is wonderful...!
Thank you!
That look on your
face won't fool me!
I'm so sorry if I overstayed
my welcome tonight...
You really should
go see a doctor
if you're not feeling
better tomorrow...
Bye-bye.
Don't worry, Seira,
you'll always be
my number one girl.
I'll be waiting for your
Awakened version to come out!
And in other news...
Another dead body was discovered
in an alley in Shibuya
late yesterday evening...
A man was left to die
after being pinned to a
wall with metal stakes.
This is the latest in a
series of brutal murders
commonly known as
the New Gen crimes.
The police department
is launching a
full-scale investigation
in order to put a stop to
this horrific chain of events.
Good morning!
Morning.
Morning!
No. There's no way.
It's really her.
Hey there... Taku!
[Music]
Those eyes...
whose are they?