[Music]
I'm Takumi Nishijo.
Yua confronted me at
the internet cafe...
She told me
that I had DID,
or multiple
personality disorder,
and that a different
aspect of my personality
was the murderer.
I tried to run, but it
wasn't just Yua chasing me.
Police officers were
hot on my trail too...
That's when Ayase
came to my rescue.
Apparently she was
a suspect too...
'Cause her song
predicted the staking...
Together, Ayase and I
ran from the police...
Once we had lost them,
she showed me
something incredible.
She pulled a real di-sword
out of empty space.
Then, inexplicably,
another Ayase appeared
right in front of me...
It was a version of her
from a delusion I had before.
Delusions becoming real...
When I got back
to home base,
I saw an online video of
the first New Gen incident,
known as the "Group Dive"...
I heard a familiar sound
and I knew who shot
the footage...
It was the General.
We now know that the phrase
"Those eyes, whose are they?"
the famous dying message
from the Vampire incident,
was spoken by a
member of the Group Dive...
What this means is that
all four incidents
might have been the work of a
single criminal mastermind...
Police know where the
video was posted...
It happened at a
local internet café...
Although they can't be
certain who's responsible,
authorities say
their investigation
is generating
some good leads.
It doesn't
make any sense.
Why would the General bother
uploading that video...?
Is he trying to provoke me?
The time is here...
Awaken...! Now...!
If you don't, many
people are going to die.
Be strong.
No matter what...
You can't give up.
Yeah right...
That's basically a threat.
"You can give up and
run away if you want,
but if you do,
I'm going to kill you."...
I have to find my
di-sword, and fast...!
Di-sword?
But I still don't know,
how the hell am I
supposed to get one?
You are the only
one who can find it,
you must do it alone.
This is too much, I
didn't even get a hint!
And what about Rimi?
I can't figure her out...
Is she on my side?
It's called
visual rebuilding.
Individuals who have been
blind since birth
are given the ability
of seeing again.
It's achieved with
the use of a device
similar to a video camera.
What if you reverse that?
You might possibly
be able to change
what you're thinking
into electronic signals,
send your thoughts to a
video recording device,
and convert that
information into data.
For example, if you
sent a mental image
of what person A is thinking
to a hard disc recorder
and turned it into
a video recording,
and then somehow
transmitted that information
to person B's brain,
that would mean that
person A's mental delusion
would become
person B's reality...
Your thoughts...
become part of the world.
Maybe that's the answer
I've been looking for,
maybe that's how
I'll get my di-sword.
Somebody, please, help me.
You're okay...
Don't worry about a thing.
Everything's all right,
because I'm on your side.
I'm so scared...
I'm afraid to be alone...
I don't know what to do.
All right... How 'bout
I stay with you then?
Sure, it's impossible for
me to be with you 24/7
but still...
We can meet up in the
morning if you'd like to...
And on the way to school we
can gossip about everybody...
Of course we can always sit
with each other at lunchtime...
We can walk home
after class too...
And every once in a while
it might be fun to
go shopping together
at the anime store...
I'll be there
when you need me.
If you think that
will help you...
then I'd be
happy to do it...
'Cause honestly...
I had been hoping
I could help!
It's almost like
we'd be lovers.
What do you think, Taku?
But... well, how come?
Why would you go
out of your way
and sacrifice so
much just for me?
Well I...
Ten-hut!
'Cause you're my best friend
and it's my responsibility...!
No more asking sad
questions like 'Why?'...
You got it?
Let's go home.
It's all right...
The coast is clear.
I hope you don't
mind me asking...
But what exactly happened?
An old man in
a wheelchair?
Are you sure that's
what you saw?
I'm absolutely sure...
You didn't see
anyone like that?
No...
I don't think so.
You remembered the intersection
being empty, right...?
But it was crowded...
Just like it usually is.
Down with these demons!
Everything happened
really fast...
Plus there were so
many people there,
I might not have noticed
someone in a wheelchair...
But I'm pretty sure
I didn't see him.
I'm really sorry.
I wish I could
help you out.
At the very least,
I'm certain it wasn't
another delusion...
The General is real
and I saw him...
But maybe my
delusion was Shibuya
being completely deserted.
Hey, what's wrong?
Destroy these demons!
Taku?
What is it?
Drive back the demons!
What kind of
protest is this?
Destroy these demons!
Taku, what's the
matter with you?
Drive back the demons!
Destroy these demons!
Demons?
Drive back the demons!
Delicious!
You're into Phantasm too?
Everyone's talking about
'em these days, aren't they?
She said it was possible
to make a video out of
something that's in my mind...
But how?
Taku, what exactly
are you doing, huh?
Oh come on,
this is no fun.
-Tell me what you're up to?
-Here.
Lemme see.
"Equipment and methods
for monitoring nerve
impulses remotely...
Technology for converting
them and reproducing them
as images and audio data."
That's it. It's exactly what
I've been looking for!
I don't understand,
what's the big deal?
Um, well...
Put simply, this is a
patent for new technology...
It records footage
of people's thoughts.
In other words, you can
use a special device
to look in on the
sound and images
a person is thinking
in their subconscious,
without them ever
knowing about it.
"Secret footage of other
people's thoughts"...?
Is something like
that possible?
After I saw that...
it just hit me.
The power to make a
delusion reality...?
To make someone's
thoughts come to life...?
No, no...
Even if there is some sort
of scientific system
which makes it possible to
convert thoughts into images,
to think I might have
supernatural powers is insane!
But what if it's not.
What if that's the only
way to get a di-sword...?
What if I have to unleash a
special power from within me?
Is it as easy as that?
I just have to picture
a sword in my mind...?
Will it appear in my hand?
Stop it!
Um, I, uh...
Taku... About that sword...
Huh?
Just forget it...
Please throw it away.
But why...? What for?
'Cause... You're not
a little kid anymore!
Huh?
Sure, I can understand how
men love that kind of toy
regardless of
how old they are,
but can you imagine
what someone would think
if they saw you swinging that
thing around all by yourself?
Think what they'd say?
Man, that scared me.
I don't get it,
are they popular?
Just wondering...
Seems like an unusual
thing for someone to buy.
Well, this is just an
imitation actually
but real ones are out there.
Real ones?
Oh yeah, I know people
who have them...
I saw their di-swords...
Two girls actually, they
both go to school with us.
No, I'm serious...
These things exist,
they're not toys!
You know it's against the
law to carry swords, right?
Who are these girls...?
And how do you know them?
She smells nice.
Well, they're not your
girlfriends, are they?
Okay, that makes me
feel a little better.
I can't believe it...!
I don't know what to say.
How am I supposed
to respond to this?
But... I'm still curious,
who are they?
Well, I don't know, I...
Is something the matter?
Is... Is this a delusion?
Um...
-Taku.
-Uh, yes?
I'm thirsty...
Not to be a bother,
but do you have anything
to drink, by chance?
Uh, yeah...
There's soda.
Ooh... Fresh squeezed
juice would be nice...
I'll be right back.
See you soon!
No way...! Rimi, you're
an exhibitionist?!
What's that?
Geez, Taku, you scared me.
What was that all about?!
You were acting
really strange.
First you started
mumbling to yourself,
then out of nowhere you
started screaming...
What's wrong?
Uh, I'm fine,
it's nothing.
Weird, there's
not even any soda.
Huh?
I'm thirsty. I think
I'll go buy something...
Be back in a minute.
Sure.
I guess that means the erotic
Rimi wasn't real after all,
just another delusion...
But still.
The erotic Rimi.
Both of the Ayases.
What exactly was it
that made both of them
feel so real to me...?
And how was I able
to reproduce them?
What is this
"new info", huh?
Again?
Hold on!
The internet café has already
given this event a name?
"Brainless".
What's this?
The victim's a psychiatrist?
"On the streets of Shibuya,
just before dawn
on the 23rd...
a psychiatrist from AH Tokyo
General Hospital was killed.
"I can't believe this.
It's Dr. Takashina...!
Dr. Takashina was murdered?!
This is aimed at me...
The General is clearly
trying to provoke me,
I know it!
Help me!
Somebody save me!
Help me, please!
No...! No!
No...! No...! No!
Help me...! Help me!
Oh please... Save me...
Rimi... Rimi!
No... She's gone!
Where is she?!
Where did she go...?
Rimi save me...
Don't leave me alone like this,
please, I'm begging you!
Taku.
I'm back now.
Rimi.
You're back.
I'm right here.
Don't worry...
There's no reason
for you to be afraid.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
Right now...
she's the only thing keeping
my spirit from breaking.
If it weren't for her I'd
go completely insane...
I want to hold onto
these hands forever.
Hey... Who the hell are you?
I'll ask the
questions here.
You're not one of us...
Get lost!
Where's Hatano?
Hatano...?
Sorry I don't
know that guy...
and I wouldn't tell you anything
even if I did know him.
Hey, what's your problem?
I'm so sorry...
It just slipped
right out of my hand.
Now hold on...
I swear to you,
I wasn't lying,
I don't know who that
person is, I promise!
Oh, don't worry,
I believe you.
But whether you
know him or not...
I'll destroy
it regardless.
Nozomi.
The power to make my
thoughts reality...
What if I've had that
ability my entire life...?
That day I wasn't able to
go on the field trip...
What if everything that
happened back then was reality
reflecting my imagination?
If that's the
case, then I...
Morning...!
I came to get you!
Why do you keep spacing
out like that...?
I told you yesterday that I
was gonna come and get you...
What did you think?
I was gonna stand up my
favorite person in the world?
Not a chance...!
Ten-hut, Taku...!
I'm not the type of person
who goes back on her word!
You know...
I've been wondering
why winter skies are
so grey and faded...
I bet it's because
the cold weather
makes everyone depressed,
so fewer people wish
for blue skies...
Do you think?
It's strange,
but I feel like I've had this
conversation with Rimi before.
So even if it's freezing,
let's keep our spirits up.
Takumi.
I hope the cops
haven't bothered you.
You must find
your sword...
You don't have any other
choice but to do so.
Give me a hint please...
I just need a
little guidance.
How'd you manage
to get yours?
It was there before
I ever realized it.
I didn't know what
had happened at first.
Once I changed my
perspective, I understood.
It's possible that your
mind is already ready
and willing to see it...
but you are too
afraid to look.
Yeah, but...
I've been looking
everywhere...
and I'm not afraid...
I swear I'm ready for this.
Hey, Taku!
Tell me... How'd you
pull that off...?
What gives? I didn't realize
you two were close...
That's the first time I've
ever seen her talk to anyone...
It's time to fess up...!
What did you do to make
her fall for you...?!
Come on man,
I'm not kidding!
Stop it!
Why don't you just relax?
You're bothering Taku!
Actually, he's the
one bothering me!
So... Time to spill
the beans, my friend...
What exactly did
you do, Taku?
Tell me!
I wish they
wouldn't look at me.
You know, I never thought
you would be so popular.
What?
Oh come on, you haven't
noticed yet...?
Weren't you hanging out with a
pretty third year with glasses
or was that just
my imagination?
Well, she was...
Yeah... You already told me...
She was really mean to
you or something, right...?
Oh yeah and today you were
chatting with that Ayase girl.
And then there's
Kozue, too...
She said something to you
on her first day of
school, didn't she...?
And don't forget.
Now you're going home
with me, Mr. Popular!
See?
It's true, I have
noticed that lately.
My time's finally come!
Speaking of which.
What exactly were you
talking about...?
I mean this morning
with Ayase...
I would like to know.
It's probably not
my place to ask
but still I'm
sort of curious.
Because...
When you were
talking to her
you looked deep
in thought...
Like something was
really bothering you...
I was a little worried.
We were just chatting...
About the di-swords
and stuff...
She's got one, I
hoped she might help.
Oh yeah?
It's the real thing.
Well, that's
highly illegal!
But she...
I'm telling you,
that one's only a toy
that just looks real...
A toy, a toy,
a toy, a toy!
I'm not sure...
But it's possible
I have the ability
to turn my thoughts
into reality...
And I think that's why
the General is after me.
Are you talking about that
thing you looked up online...?
Taku, do you have
one of those?
That's not what I mean...
I think I might be
able to affect reality
without the help
of a machine.
You're teasing me,
you big weirdo!
Ha...! I get it, you're
just mimicking an anime
you've been
watching, aren't you?
It happened to me
when I was young...
An accident when I was
in elementary school.
Don't overthink it...
It's just another one
of your silly delusions.
Try not to dwell on
it anymore, okay?
No one's there...
You're fine.
Hey... Momo, my girl!
Banny Boy!
What brings you here?
You got any good stuff
on the New Gen incident?
Ah, you brought
food, I see...
You know me too well.
There's been another
New Gen crime, right?
So what's the plan...?
Are your people busy
pursuing the GE rate angle?
Yeah, that's right,
the GE rates...
Pretty amazing stuff...
I owe you big time for
turning me onto this lead.
That's it?
That's it...
No... Actually, I'm
investigating this thing
all on my own.
Have you lost
your mind...?
Banny Boy... going at this alone
can be extremely dangerous!
Or did you forget what
happened to Professor Ota
after he gave that televised
lecture on GE rates?
-Is that what you're after?
-Yeah.
He was the victim in
the staking, wasn't he?
I'll be fine,
don't worry about me...
I tried to
persuade the bosses
to jump on board
with this GE angle
but they think that
I'm a crazy person.
So... Is it really possible
to use biorhythms as weapons
of mass destruction...?
The truth is I can't
wrap my head around it...
If you think about it,
the whole thing does sound a
little bit nutty, doesn't it?
Look, it's exactly
like I told you before.
You're police,
you know what it's like
when there's a full moon...
The biorhythm
curves all spike...
Well what if something
caused biorhythms
to jump even higher?
The people would get all
excitable, wouldn't they?
And that's not all.
Shibuya is a very
special place...
The math is simple.
The higher the GE rate,
the higher the biorhythm
curve will be...
The rate is sixty-eight
hundred times
greater than the rate
of a full moon...
That's not exactly an
insignificant jump.
What's causing
it to happen now?
Here's what Professor Ota
said before he was killed...
That about six months ago
there was an unexpected
increase in the GE Rates,
which is usually impossible,
unless there is a sudden
geological change
in the surrounding area.
-Change?
-Right...
At the crossing in
front of the station,
you'd need energy on the
level of a volcanic eruption
in order to match it.
A volcano...?
There's a force like that,
in the middle of the city?
That's insane!
That's exactly the point,
our GE rates are off
the charts right now.
And when the professor tried
to tell the public about this,
the New Gen killer
murdered him?
The day before he
was murdered...
the program he was
scheduled to appear
on went off the air...
No explanation...
Never showed.
Are you sure?
I got the info
from a friend
who works for the station.
Hard to imagine a
television network
being pressured that way...
Who's got pull like that?
I don't know
any specifics.
But government, religion,
and business...
Those are definitely people
who aren't afraid to get
their noses dirty...
Banny Boy...
You could lose
your job, you know?
If I can catch
the New Gen perp
and put a stop to all this,
then that's fine by me.
Come look at this.
"Meiwa Party"?
Momo...
Give me a break here.
If I was making an
educated guess
I probably woulda said
opposition party...
This is the last thing
I would've thought.
If this blows up, it'll
shake the whole country.
No...
This can't be true.
Hey, Takki, what's wrong?
-Look at this.
-Huh?
Whoa, they're going
crazy over it!
"Phantasm...
FES's real name is Ayase...
She was previously
hospitalized
due to psychiatric problems."
"AHM...
Arkheart Medical Group...
It's a longstanding
specialized medical facility
which only treats
serious mental cases."
Ayase's been there, too?
Hurry up...
You must find it...
If you can find your
sword you will be saved.
I wonder if I can really
believe the things she says.
Damn... Stupid
phone scared me.
That's exactly why
I didn't want one.
Well, pick it up.
It's probably
just Nanami...
Hello. What?
Who is this?
The General...?
Seira baby,
what should I do?
Should I answer?
You can ignore him,
you know...
Just hang up.
Oh, yeah...
I could definitely
just hang up, huh?
What's that?
Takki.
Taku.
Hello?
Yes, and who is
this exactly...?
Oh... I'm fine...
No, everything's
okay, it's just...
I'm sorry, say that again?
But that can't
be possible...!
Because...
Because actually
I'm the one who...
Get away from the windows!
Yes...
She's my sister...
Oh, okay...
Okay, thank you very much.
[Music]
Those eyes...
Whose are they?