[Music]
Hi, my name is
Takumi Nishijo...
I'm a second year...
I'm seventeen years old...
Basically, I am what you
might call an otaku...
Right now, in
Shibuya where I live,
a mysterious string of events
known as the "New Gen"
has been terrorizing
our city.
I never had any interest in
the 3D world until recently.
Ever since a guy
called "The General"
showed me that image
predicting a New Gen Crime,
I haven't been able to
get it out of my mind.
Especially now.
Because I saw it happen
with my own eyes,
it was exactly like it
was in the picture.
Also... a girl I
go to high school
with might be the murderer.
What's worse...?
She's sitting right
next to me in class.
Oh... oh no-
The demon girl.
What's the
matter with you?
No... What are
you doing here?
What do you want from me?!
Oh... Help me...
Don't murder me...!
Please, I'm begging you!
Ten-hut...!
Stand up and get it together.
You're babbling like a
crazy person, you weirdo!
Hey, what's wrong...?
Come on.
No way!
I saw it...
I saw you...
You murdered that person.
Thanks a lot...
I don't know why you are
being so mean to me...
-What did I do?
-Wait...
You're going to
kill me, too...
Aren't you?
Well I certainly
never thought
I would be accused of
murdering somebody...
I don't like it.
Spare me.
Don't kill me.
Now stop...
I am utterly
offended Taku.
Taku.
Hey... How do you
know my name...?
Do you... know me?
Are you kidding...?
How long have
we been friends?
We're friends?
What are you up to?
Is this some kind
of a joke...?
I know I'm not the
smartest girl in class
and my grades aren't
spectacular...
But it hurts my feelings
when you make fun of me...
You should be ashamed!
Hey, who are you,
devil girl?!
I see, so you don't
even recognize
your own classmates anymore,
is that it...?
You jerk...!
I guess there's not
much hope for you...
After all, you barely
show up for school so...
You don't know it...
You actually
forgot my name.
You didn't, did you?
You know it, right?
You ought to
know it, Taku.
It's... Rimi.
That's absolutely right!
Rimi...
Rimi Sakihata!
I'm really glad you
remembered me...
Wow, what a relief.
I don't understand.
How do I know what this
girl's name is...?
How?
Guys! What's up?
Hey...! Good
morning, Daisuke!
As usual, you're like a
couple of peas in a pod...
You should just date
and get it over with.
You're not gonna
believe this...
Taku was so mean
to me just now...
Oh man...
That's weird...
Daisuke acted like me and the
demon girl being together
is a normal thing...
That doesn't
make any sense!
Jeez dude.
You miss a couple
of days of school
and you forget about
your closest friends...?
I would be one thing...
But you two've been
in the same class
since your first
year of school.
What...? We've known
each other that long?
Hello, we just hung out
together a few days ago...
See?
No... No way.
You know, someone as nerdy as
you should be thankful...
You are lucky you
have friends at all,
Mr. omputer Geek.
Hey now that
was a low blow.
Yeah, but it's true!
That girl...
I swear I've never seen
her before in my life.
At least I think...?
Just stop talking
to yourself.
You're having more of
those scary delusions,
aren't you, Takki?
Seira... You don't understand...
The demon girl is real,
she isn't a delusion.
Oh yes she is...
-Just trust me, okay?
-Yeah... But...
You're such a
worrywart, Takki...
Just relax, she'll be
gone before you know it...
Why don't you forget about
it and play your game?
Yeah... You're right...
I just need to forget
about the stupid 3D world.
You know it's true...
I'm like a god
at this game,
no one even comes
close to me.
That's the spirit!
Taku.
Don't even think
about running away...
I'll find you
wherever you go.
It is time...
Don't be scared...
Let it happen.
Guess that was
another delusion...
-What a relief.
-Taku...
It's really not safe to
leave your door unlocked.
Especially with all the
weird things happening lately.
Is this a delusion, too?
Every time I
come over here,
your Seira collection
has grown.
Ow... Nope...
Reality.
Oh... Looky here...
Hey, that's the pre-awakened
figurine, isn't it?
That post-awakened version
has got to be coming out any
day now, don't you think?
How... How do you know that?
Well duh...
You told me a couple
days ago, silly.
That's not possible...
Hey... Hold on...
What are you doing here?!
Well, you didn't seem like
yourself at school today,
so I came over
to check on you.
You really
don't look good.
I know... I'll cook
you a nutritious meal.
That'll perk you up!
Please go home.
-What?
-Just leave me alone!
Inspector, let's
hear your report.
Inspector...
Inspector Ban, are
you paying attention?
Hey... Boss...
You're up now,
they're calling you.
Yeah... Sorry about that...
My partner here
will do the report.
But... I'm not prepared!
Improvise.
I apologize.
I wasn't aware I was
doing this presentation.
Moving on then...
We have footage of a suspicious
man near the incident.
Here it is now.
This was recorded by
private security cameras
located approximately
50 meters
from the scene
of the crime...
As I'm sure most of you
gentlemen are aware,
according to the statements
given by nearby residents,
several different witnesses
heard a distinct hammering
sound in the distance
between nine o'clock
and nine-thirty pm.
At 9:34 our mysterious
man runs by.
In other words...
he's fleeing the scene,
right after the
murder occurred.
Based on the crime
lab's analysis...
we're pretty sure
he's a young man...
Probably somewhere between
fifteen and twenty years old...
And there's more.
We were able to match his
clothes to Suimei Academy,
a private school
located nearby...
I'd like you gentlemen to
pay special attention
to what's in his right hand.
And what exactly
is this young man
holding in his right hand...?
A metal stake.
A stake that just so
happened to be the only weapon
used in this
particular murder.
Meaning this kid is most
likely our perp, correct...?
We even have him running
from the scene of the crime!
Yeah, it looks
that way to me.
Figures...
Stealing the best part
for yourself, huh?
Yep, he's finally
given himself away...
Best thing we can do is
catch the son of a bitch
and get him to
sign a confession.
Don't think about it...
Don't think about it.
The demon girl
isn't real...
Seira, my lover, please
lend me your strength.
No way... The demon girl.
Takumi, you there...?
I'm sorry to bother you,
can I come in?
Hey that voice is...
Yua?
We... have our appointment...
You did remember, right?
Huh?
You said you'd take
me to the anime store
to help me reserve a
Seira action figure.
Oh yeah...
I totally forgot about it
because of the demon girl.
Hey, I hope it's okay
I dropped by your place
and picked you up.
Uh... It's no big deal.
Well...
Sorry for asking you to
do something like this
when we barely
know each other.
It's fine.
This is awful...
I think I'm
gonna be sick...
I'll hurry up and
get this over with,
then get back to base.
Taku?
Hey!
Hey who's the pretty girl?
Is she your girlfriend?
No, of course she's
not my girlfriend...
I'm just taking her
to the anime store
so she can reserve
an action figure.
Oh, so she's into
dolls, too...
That makes sense,
there's no way he could
get a girl like her.
Hey there, my name's
Yua Kusunoki,
I'm a friend of Takumi's.
Hi...! I'm his
sister, Nanami!
I'm so sorry for dragging
your brother along with me...
I needed help.
Oh, it's no problem...
He's a disgusting slob,
but by all means,
please take care of him.
Ow!
Now you listen up.
This girl is way out
of your league...
I think you're lucky
she'll even be seen in public
with somebody like you,
so don't screw
it up, okay?
Oh... Gosh I'm starting to
get a little bit nervous...
Promise me you won't
go home by yourself
and leave me here all alone.
I won't.
I'm sorry...
Not only did you
take me to the store,
but then I made you carry
all my stuff, too.
Oh no... it's nothing.
Oh I almost
forgot to ask you,
do you have a cell
phone by chance?
Well I guess we can't
keep in touch then.
Uh... in touch?
But wait...
You have a computer back
at your place, don't you...?
Maybe we should exchange
email addresses?
What for?
Uh... Well, uh...
When the action
figure's ready...
I'm going to have to come back
here and pick it up, right?
I really don't think
I have the courage
to go back to that
place by myself.
To tell you the truth...
I'd like to get to
know you better...
If that's okay
with you, I mean.
You've got mail...
You silly boy.
Yua...
Man, she's fast.
Good evening...
This is Yua...
I couldn't resist
so I emailed you...
I'm sorry for making you
come along with me today.
I really did have
an amazing time...
Maybe it's 'cause I've
never been to a store
like that before.
Or maybe it's because I got
to spend the day with you...
Taku.
Hey, what time do you think
you'll be going to school
tomorrow morning...?
Uh, you're probably wondering
why I want to know that, huh...?
It's no big deal, I just
wanted to say hi to you...
At the very least,
I hope we're lucky enough
to bump into each
other at some point...
Well, good night.
Have sweet dreams.
I'll write again soon.
Are you going to reply?
Huh...? Yeah right...!
I'm not writing her back...
2D girls are the
only ones for me!
I'll just delete this.
You bad boy!
Stop, that tickles.
Hey, who are
you looking for?
I can help you out.
Thank you very much...
I'm trying to find Takumi.
Taku...?
Well, he's absent today.
Oh I see.
-So you're a friend of Taku's?
-Yes.
Ah I'm surprised...
He never mentioned he had such
a beautiful friend before.
We just met actually,
we don't know each
other that well,
but yesterday Takumi and
I went to the anime store
and he helped me
pick out some things.
Wow, so you two went out?
So... What else did you do?
Huh...?
Well nothing really,
just shopping.
Oh, I see...
Then everything's fine...
I'm sorry for asking
such weird questions.
No... It's fine.
I don't care what
anyone else says...
That demon girl's
a delusion...
Seira... She's the
only one I can believe.
Takumi, wait up!
I saw you from behind,
at least I thought
it might be you,
so I started
calling your name.
I ran as fast as I
could to catch you...
I sure hope you're having
an excellent morning.
She won't give up,
will she...?
What is she
expecting from me?
Ah, I love you...!
Hold me!
Oh boy...
Oh boy!
Oh boy.
What are you saying?
Hey... Did you get that
email I sent you...?
Did you have a chance
to read it yet?
Yeah.
That's great...
You didn't reply
so I was kinda worried you
hadn't gotten it yet.
Oh.
Um...
So I went to your
classroom yesterday
to say good morning...
They said you
were absent...
I thought maybe you'd
caught a bad cold
or something like that...
I was worried about you.
Well I hardly ever
go to school...
People think I'm a hermit.
Well that's too bad...
But hey, I'm glad I
ran into you today.
Just don't let those kids
at school get to you...
I don't care what
they say, Takumi,
you are not a hermit.
I... I'm sorry...
I should probably
keep my mouth shut.
Um... No...
Please... I'm used to it.
Well, I think
you're amazing...
Because despite all of the
people who make fun of you,
occasionally you still
try and go to school.
But... But I...
I'm not anything...
Just a nerd.
So you like anime
and computer games,
that doesn't mean
you're a nerd.
I like you just
the way you are.
What...?
What's her deal...?
Why is she saying this...?
Why is this girl
being so nice to me?
More importantly, why does
she make me feel so good?
Oh no! The tardy bell!
I'd better go, Takumi.
If I don't hurry,
I'll be late!
Bye-bye!
Um... Do you have time
after... class...?
Are you busy?
Huh?
Well, uh, I
wanted to ask you,
I mean if you
don't have plans,
do you want to meet
up after school?
I thought you and I could
walk home together
or something fun
like that...
I'll wait for you in the
courtyard after school, okay?
See you later.
It's definitely
not a delusion...
Oh boy.
You're kidding me...
Wow.
Yua.
She really came...
She waited here
just for me.
I know she won't
betray me...
A person like her,
she might even be
able to save me.
Hey, you scared me.
You really came,
I was so worried you
wouldn't show up.
Uh, whaddaya think...?
You wanna walk
home together?
Uh... Yeah.
There's nothing special
about this place...
It's beautiful
and peaceful...
So why do I suddenly
feel like crying?
Hey, is everything
all right?
Oh... Yeah.
Those little frogs?
I remember seeing
those somewhere.
The internet cafe...
Wait a sec...
Was she the one next door?
Do you like those?
Hoppy the Frog...
They're super
popular right now.
You can take one
if you'd like...
I have plenty.
That's weird...
It won't come off.
New Gen research...
Printouts.
Why?
Hey, what's that?
Say something...
Why won't she answer?
I can't believe that
I trusted her...
I started to believe
that she was on my side,
that she was really
a friend to me.
In the end, there's no
way someone like Yua
would ever like
someone like me...
She only got close to me
because she wants something.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Don't move.
You stay right here...
I'm sorry I had
to trick you...
But you're no better...
You're hiding something,
too, aren't you...?
Tell me the truth.
She had this whole
thing planned out...
from the beginning...
Everything she told me,
every nice thing she said,
it was all lies!
Shit... Shit...!
I can't believe
I fell for it!
How could I have
been so gullible?!
Originally, I had planned to
do some more investigating...
but you found me out
so that's that...
There's something I need
to talk to you about...
And you're going
to listen to me.
You're going to tell
me what I want to know.
Do you understand, Takumi?
I will ask.
And you will answer.
'Cause if you don't...
You recognize this,
don't you...?
You've seen it?
Of course you have...
And don't try to
tell me otherwise
because I know the truth.
It would be odd
if you didn't.
You know it, don't you?
Don't you, Takumi?
After all, I found
it in your room.
On your floor,
under your bed...
Tossed on the ground...
It was you...
You left it there...
Did you throw it away...?
Hoping no one
would find it...?
Well someone did!
This weapon is
exactly the same
as the one used in the third
New Gen case, isn't it...?
It's the same.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me it's
the same one...
Say it...
The same one used to pin
that poor man to the wall!
Oh no...
This girl really believes
I'm the New Gen murderer!
She thinks she's a cop...
The teenage detective
on the case, huh?
You're wrong.
I'm sorry...
I don't mean
you any harm...
All I wanted was
to confront you
and find out if you knew
anything relevant...
I'm really sorry, I didn't
plan on being so direct.
Also... There's one more
thing I need to confirm.
Are you a clairvoyant, can
you predict the future?
Huh?
I'm assuming you
have that power...
Otherwise there's
no explanation
for the image on
your computer.
But... But that's...
Why would you have a picture
of the New Gen's third case
stored on the hard drive
of your computer?
And how did you get
that picture one day
before the actual
event occurred?
I... I don't know!
Some guy called the
General sent me a link
when we were chatting
online and I clicked on it!
Wait a second...
It's you...
You're the General...
Are you trying to set
me up or something?
Please... Don't do this!
I found this image stored on
a hard drive in a computer
in room thirty-seven
at the internet café.
Wait, room
thirty-seven...?
That's the room
I always go to.
Just look...
This is a record
of all your chats.
I noticed something
strange in there...
The time stamps of Knight
Heart and the General's chat
don't line up at all.
That's the list of your
entries as Knight Heart...
The time stamp says you posted
on September 9th at three am...
Then two days passed...
And you went to the
internet café...
at seven o'clock.
At the same time
the General posted.
What...?
What are you saying?
You were putting
on a one-man show.
But I... I don't...
Don't you get it?
You own both profiles.
Stop it...
Let me be!
It's you, Takumi...
You're the General.
It's not real...
This isn't happening...
I wasn't meant to be born
into a world like this...
I've never belonged here.
[Music]
Those eyes.
Whose are they?