[NARRATOR]
This world is overflowing with
a power known as Fantasia.
Those who wield this power
can become either heroes
or villains.
Here, terrifying monsters
fall from the sky.
Is this divine retribution?
Demonic malice?
Or a symptom
of Mother Nature’s wrath?
The one thing known for certain
is that these monsters,
called The Nemesis,
leave disaster in their wake.
They are terrifying to behold
and can kill
with the lightest touch.
Those few humans who cross
their paths and survive
are forever cursed.
But along with their curses,
they receive power.
The power to stand against
The Nemesis.
Now, these tainted humans fight.
And at times, they can be
even more fearsome
than the nemeses themselves.
They’re known as sorcerers.
This is the story of a boy
who strives to become a great
sorcerer and save the world.
[NARRATOR]
“True Courage.”
Seth is a young sorcerer,
staying near the village
of Pompo Hills.
He was training hard, hoping to
be accepted by the townspeople,
and by Alma,
the sorcerer who raised him,
when a fearsome Nemesis
appeared in the village.
While protecting
his friend Tommy,
Seth risked life and limb.
Just as all seemed lost,
he was saved by an
unfamiliar group of Sorcerers.
Whoa, they must be-- I guess
you guys are sorcerers, too?
Yeah! What gave it away?
The brooms, maybe?
Perhaps we should talk once
we’ve dealt with that big guy.
You're up, boys!
Right, Boss!
They made it stop moving.
Way to go.
I believe that’ll hold it
for a good while.
[SETH]
‘Preciate it.
Who are you guys?
We’re a team of wandering
Nemesis Hunters,
as proud as we are brave.
As for our name:
You can call us...
[ALL]
The Bravery Quartet!
We rehearsed this, Jiji.
You’re s’posed to turn
to the right!
How many times do I have
to tell you
first impressions
are everything, you numbskull?
-Ya gotta calm down, boss!
-Yeah, he’s right!
The seal won’t last long,
remember?
Ahem.
People of the village,
hear me well!
You’re safe now.
My associates and I have come
to protect you
from this foul Nemesis!
So, you guys are gonna save us?
Sure.
Just do exactly as we say
and no one has to get hurt.
Or at least none of you
will end up dead, probably.
We men of the Bravery Quartet
have arrived to save the day!
I’ve never met another
sorcerer before.
Aside from Alma, that is.
Hey, so, listen.
I’d like to fight with you guys.
Please let me help!
Oh, would you now?
I know I got a little
careless earlier,
but I’m a full-fledged sorcerer,
so I’m sure I can help you out!
I’ve been training
really hard lately
to prepare myself
to take down my first Nemesis.
If you give me a chance
to put my training to work,
I swear I won’t
let you down!
Hmm...
A full-fledged sorcerer, eh?
You seem to be
on the young side.
But I like your style!
Ya know what,
you’ve impressed me already!
The bravitude you showed
by squaring off
with that Nemesis by yourself,
has earned you my respect!
[laughs]
Bravitude?
I think it must’ve been
the will of God
that our path’s should’ve
crossed in this place.
I’ll accept your assistance.
Let’s work as potters!
Hey boss? I think you
mean “partners.” That right?
Yeah, “partners,”
that’s what I said!
At any rate, I like the cut
of your jib, kid.
So what say we handle
this together?
We’re partners now?
So that means it’s cool
if I help you guys fight?
[MAN 1]
Hey, wait a second.
That kid can’t be trusted!
What he said!
That twerp has brought us
nothing but trouble.
Yeah, the punk’s bound to do
more harm than good.
Get out of here,
you snot-nosed brat!
[MAN 1]
Beat it kid!
[MAN 2]
You infected scum!
[DON BOSSMAN] Let’s not bandy
about such words, good people.
You might hurt my feelings.
As you can see, the youngster
and I are birds of a feather.
Which means if he’s ‘infected,’
then so am I.
We may have just met,
but I have faith in this kid.
Well, no point in dawdling
around out here!
That seal won’t keep it down
for much longer.
Won’t you fight it?
[DON BOSSMAN] First we need
to get you people out of here.
But, our families are still
in their homes.
Papa.
Mama.
Don’t you worry about them!
We of the Bravery Quartet
will ensure that all civilians
are evacuated safely!
But while we’re doing that,
we’ll need someone to act
as a decoy
to hold the beast’s attention.
Well kid?
Feeling up to it?
Yeah, for sure!
But why should I stop
at just being a decoy?
I’ll take that thing down!
That’s what I like to hear,
knock yourself out!
But make sure you don’t act
too rootless, okay?
‘Ey boss.
You’re doing it again.
Not rootless. “Reckless.”
Yeah! Exactly as I said!
You know,
it’s good be brave ‘n all,
but run when the time
is right, kay?
You can’t brute force your way
through everything, kid.
You gotta keep your wits
about you
if you wanna survive
this crazy world.
But since you’re
a full-fledged sorcerer,
I’m sure you already know that.
Right.
Yeah.
I think I get it.
[SETH]
Hey, look!
That seal’s starting to fade!
[DON BOSSMAN]
Indeed, you’re right!
We’d better be off!
Best of luck, kid.
We’ve put our faith in you.
Thanks!
Uh...
-Hey Seth?
-Tommy.
Your father’s still workin’ down
at the bank, isn’t he?
Come with me,
I’ll take you to go warn him.
But I wanted to talk to Seth.
All right!
Relying on equipment wasn’t
getting me anywhere before.
This time.
I’ll come at you
with my own magic!
Titan Punch!
What the heck is
with this thing?
It goes from hard to soft
just like that.
Oh, crap!
[screaming]
Why is everything trying
to trample me lately?
Come on!
It’s close!
This thing is gonna flatten me!
How'd you like that?
You look like an idiot!
If attacking from the front
won’t work.
then what about this?
Titan Punch!
I’m barely even slowing
the thing down.
Now what am I supposed to do?
Look kid, to survive
in this world,
you need your wits about ya.
Yeah, he’s right.
Come on.
Just think.
I’ve got it!
[TOMMY]
Papa!
Hey, Tommy!
A Nemesis is here,
we have to escape!
Are you serious?
Well, sir.
We should gather key documents
and evacuate.
Yes, good call.
[heavy door opens]
[DON BOSSMAN]
Well, well.
This is awkward.
[TOMMY'S FATHER]
Um...who are you guys?
[MAN]
It’s the Bravery Quartet.
Thought you’d
all be gone by now.
Or haven’t you heard
there’s a Nemesis in town?
Here we go!
[heavy footsteps]
[SETH]
Hey Squishy!
You look lost.
That’s right, I’m up here!
Come and get me!
Nice!
Whoa, you’re really fast.
But I think this’ll work.
Ha! Wrapped like
a pig in a blanket!
You like that?
Wonder if I’ll hear you land
when I roll you off the island!
[groans]
Oh, please.
Don’t you try and play
on my sympathies now.
Listen, what’s
your problem anyway?
Why’d you come attack
this poor town?
Say something already!
[NEMESIS groans]
Nu-uh.
Don’t you grunt at me.
Look here.
You pretty much destroyed
the whole place!
[gasps]
I guess that made it angry.
[shouts]
This cannot be good!
Well,
that’s certainly one way
to waste somebody’s day.
How much of an airhead
do you have to be to mistake
a cow for a Nemesis?
I should’ve expected it,
but I didn’t realize people
as thick as Seth
are actually out here.
Plus I went in my full gear.
This stuff is heavy as a--
What’s this feeling?
This eerie sensation,
tell me it’s not what I think.
No. Damn.
It must be.
Don’t do anything rash, Seth.
Just wait for me!
[NEMESIS groaning]
If that blast had
hit me directly,
I’d have been toasted alive.
Well,
Alma told me
they were strong,
and that they were
able to use Fantasia
to create something pretty
similar to magic, but...
this is way crazier
than I imagined.
-[TOMMY screams]
-Huh?
Tommy!
How could you?
Simmer down.
It’s the brat’s own fault
for steppin’ out of line.
I mean, really.
We only had to do this
‘cause you didn’t evacuate.
Why, you bunch
of rotten scoundrels!
You were planning to take
advantage of the chaos
from the beginning!
You’re not brave at all, you’re
nothing but thieving bandits!
[FEMALE BANK EMPLOYEE]
We should’ve known better
than to put our lives in the
hands of a bunch of Sorcerers!
You’re in no position
to be hurling insults, lady.
And also, we really did try
to help you escape the Nemesis.
We bought plenty of time
for you idiots,
but you just had
to drag your feet.
Never meant for this little runt
to get involved,
but them’s the breaks I guess.
I’m sorry it had to be this way,
but we all play
the hand we get dealt.
Take a look at this haul,
we made a killing off of
these losers!
We’re all gonna be rich, Boss!
I’m so delighted
I can’t stop laughing!
Tell me this is not
what it looks like.
Ah, well if it isn’t our
bravadocious little decoy boy.
I’m pleasantly surprised
to see you made it.
You played an instrumental
role in this.
-Huh?
-I doubt we would’ve been able
to make out with half
as much money
if you hadn’t volunteered to
keep the Nemesis at bay for us!
It seems we’re in your debt!
So, that punk was in
on the plan?
I knew I was right
not to trust him!
That must mean
he and the old hag
have been casing out the place!
I bet you he only
befriended Tommy
because he knew that his dad
works here at the bank!
No way!
You guys, I thought you said
you were Nemesis hunters,
not filthy robbers!
Hah. That’s rich, kid.
Guess you could say
that’s just our cover story.
In actuality,
we’re treasure hunters.
There’s always a lot of loot
waitin’ to be bagged up
whenever a monster
attacks a town.
It’s the money
that we come to save.
How could you--.
I can’t believe you tricked us!
I thought you said you had faith
in me, was that just a lie?
[laughing]
You swallowed that right up!
Talk about naive.
“We’ve put our faith in you.”
I could tell right away that
you were one of those screw-up
nobodies who’d be desperate
for a pat on the head.
But I’m a full-fledged sorcerer,
so I’m sure I can help you guys.
I’ve been training really
hard lately
to take out my first Nemesis.
Come on!
Let me put my training to work,
I won’t let you down!
After all, you were kind enough
to tell me as much yourself.
-[DON BOSSMAN laughing]
-But why?
Why would you do this?
I thought it was the duty
of all sorcerers
to fight against evil
and keep people safe!
[sighs]
Listen, kid.
One of these days you need
to realize
that these people will hate you
whether you’re good
to them or not.
They treat us like a bunch
of plague rats,
and hold us to blame
for all their troubles.
Whatever they see us touch,
they wash after.
There’s only one time that
they don’t run us out of town.
When they want us
to fight for them!
And whenever we’re
dumb enough to do it,
they hand us over
to the Inquisition as a reward.
If you hadn’t been here,
that Nemesis wouldn’t have come!
How dare you get my little boy
involved in this?
-I’ll have your heads!
-See what I mean?
You just took the beating
of a lifetime
in order to protect this town.
You did your best
to keep them safe,
and all they do now
is threaten you.
They’re not the least
bit grateful.
Don’t tell me you honestly
believe that regular humans
would want to coexist
with people like us, kid.
I guarantee that as far
as they’re concerned,
we’re no better than the beast
that trashed their town.
You can either
take my words to heart
or you can work yourself
to death
for people who hate you.
This is no world for heroes.
The fools who try end up
persecuted and betrayed.
You’ve seen enough
to know I’m right.
Haven’t you?
Take it from me.
If you wanna survive,
you gotta be smart about
the choices you make.
And nothing’s smarter
than making sure
ya got plenty of money to burn.
Boss!
I think it’s about time
we got outta here.
There’s no tellin’ when
that Nemesis will show up
and tear this place apart.
Ah, right you are.
Farewell, my young bird
of a feather.
A parting gift.
Can’t have people saying the
Bravery Quartet
doesn’t repay its own kind.
[laughing]
[BOTH]
He punched the boss!
Disgusting.
You guys are pathetic!
Why, you little punk!
I’ll show you exactly...
what kind of
sorcerer-- I wanna become,
and it’s nothing
like you losers!
[SETH shouts]
No, Seth!
Good grief.
That magic’s more terrifying
every time I see it.
I know I’ve said
this before, but,
if you weren’t such a moron,
you might’ve been
the boss, Jiji.
[JIJI]
Mm.
Serves the brat right.
So, what do we do now?
Should we finish ‘im off, boss?
No.
He should learn his mistake
soon enough.
The world’ll wear him down,
and he’ll see I was right.
Like it or not, we’re still
birds of a feather.
We’ll all be hated the same.
I am nothing like you,
criminals.
[sighs]
-[NEMESIS groans]
-Uh?
Great!
The Nemesis must’ve found us
thanks to Jiji’s magic blast.
Time for us to move, boys.
Giddy-up.
Hey, wait!
You can’t just
leave us here tied up!
We’ll all be killed
by the nemesis.
At least let us go!
[DON BOSSMAN]
Shut up!
This is it, normies!
Maybe we’ll meet again
in the afterlife.
No, please!
And as for you,
if you’ve got the strength to
crawl, then you better start.
No sense in you dying here.
Leave these people for dead
and get out while you can.
Untie us, please!
I don’t wanna die today!
Please, just save my son!
-Tommy!
-[WOMAN] We’re done for!
[screams]
There’s no escaping now!
It’s not fair,
I’m too young to die!
[SETH]
It’s gonna be okay.
Trust me.
You’re safe, Tommy.
I’m not gonna leave you here.
Like it or not, we’re still
birds of a feather.
We’ll all be hated the same.
I’m nothing like those four.
I’m going to become
an amazing sorcerer.
Courageous and with the power,
to protect everyone!
[BRAVERY QUARTET B]
That was a strong blast. Wow.
I hate to say it, but everyone
in that bank is toast now.
Hmph. That stupid kid
shoulda run.
[BRAVERY QUARTET B]
Boss! There!
-Look at him!
-Huh? Oh!
[SETH shouting]
[DON BOSSMAN]
No.
It can’t be.
This is impossible!
I thought he could barely
even wield fantasia!
Just what is with this kid?
[NARRATOR] The Bravery Quartet
turned out to be villains
who were deceiving
the villagers.
Now, Seth is conflicted.
What is right?
And what should
he do moving forward?
If the Nemesis ceased to exist,
would all the fighting end, too?
As Seth makes a rash decision,
Alma can’t help
but be concerned.
Just how are these sorcerer’s
histories intertwined?
Next time on Radiant:
“The Day of Departure.”