[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
Seth arrived at Artemis,
the so-called
Sorcerers Paradise.
While searching for
the sorcerer Yaga,
he met a strange old man.
Around the same time,
the Inquisition arrived,
intending to arrest Seth
and his friends.
But the day was saved by the
floating city’s military might,
and Master Lord Majesty’s
political influence.
Witnessing this renewed
Seth’s determination,
and at last, the old sorcerer
revealed his true identity.
Yes, the strange old man
was Yaga all along.
Ah! Talk about
a beautiful morning!
Don’t you agree?
Gudule?
Gertrude?
[MELIE giggles]
I feel like this is gonna be
a really wonderful day!
[MISTER BOOBRIE snoring]
[SETH]
Head’s up, Melie!
-[SETH] Ahh!
-[MELIE screams]
No, Gudule!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[SETH grunts]
Sorry for dropping in
so suddenly.
I need you to help me
learn magic, sound good?
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
“Drops of Friendship.”
[MELIE] So, where is
all this coming from?
Why do you need me to help you?
Mostly cause of what Yaga said.
[YAGA] So tell me.
Who the heck are you?
You said you know
Alma somehow, right?
I’m Seth!
And Alma taught me
everything I know.
She told me to come out here
and look for you.
Here! She wrote you a letter.
Hmm...
[SETH] Okay, you’re one
of the strongest sorcerers
around here, yeah?
I was hoping you could
help me find Radiant.
Hm.
What a waste of time.
-Ow, ow. No, no, no, no, no, no.
-Oh no! Careful.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What’d you go
and do that for?
Alma wrote that to tell you
how great I am!
I don’t care if Alma
thinks you piss rainbows, kid.
If you can’t demonstrate
your strength,
then I have nothing
to teach you.
So if my help
is what you’re after,
then I suggest you prove
you’re worth my time.
Sure.
I can do that.
I’ll show you
my most powerful move.
Titan... Punch!
[crash]
Oh yeah, you’re impressed.
Ahh!
Stupid fool!
All you did was gather Fantasia
in your fist and punch with it!
That doesn’t even
qualify as a spell!
Wait, really?!
If you’re not even
competent enough
to master a basic offensive
spell like Meteor Drops,
then you have no business
searching for Radiant.
Come back to me
once you’re stronger, boy!
[SETH]
So, yeah.
That’s why I could use
your help.
Oh. That does make sense.
Anyway, I need you to teach me
some of those awesome
attack spells of yours.
[SETH] I saw you use
a whole bunch of them
on the day we first met.
-You remember?
-Yeah...
that may be true, but--
Would you mind teaching me
how I can do the same thing?
[MELIE]
Mm...
Look, Seth,
it makes me happy to know
that you have faith in me.
It means a lot.
More than you would think.
But I can’t help you!
I’m really sorry.
[MELIE]
I used those spells after
my personality
switched, remember?
As I am now, I’m terrible
at offensive magic.
I can barely use it at all.
[SETH]
You’re kidding.
I’m still pretty good
at defensive spells,
but that’s it.
[SETH sighs]
Oh! Maybe, you could
help me get better
-at gathering Fantasia then!
-[MELIE] Huh?
I guess I could try.
Yeah. Okay!
So when the Fantasia
goes like “fwooo!”
You hold it and kinda
go like “schwoop!”
See?
I’m really not following.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Come on!
Don’t look at me like that,
Mister Boobrie.
you’re hurting my feelings.
I did my best, didn’t I?
I’m sorry I couldn’t
help you out, Seth.
[laughs]
Nah, don’t sweat it.
I’m sorry for buggin’
ya so early.
I’ll just go and practice
on my own.
[BOTH sigh]
-[MELIE] Hey! Wait a second!
-[SETH] Mm... hmm?
I can’t help much,
but I do know someone who can!
[MELIE]
He should be around here.
Yeah! There he is!
[SETH]
Huh? Isn't that...?
Although this rose pales
compared to your beauty,
I hope that you’ll accept it
as a token of my undying love.
All right, Doc, game face.
-It’s time you made your move.
-[MELIE] What’s up, Doc?
[DOC]
Ahh!
For you! Take it! Please!
Wow, it’s so pretty!
[DOC]
Huh?
Wait, Melie?
And Seth’s with you, too?
You got me a flower?
Aw, that’s so sweet of you, Doc.
What?
Why would I get a rose for you?
This is obviously
for my beloved--
[WOMAN]
Welcome to Kettle Coffee!
-Good Morning!
-[DOC strains]
Nice to see you, Doc.
Oh, and you brought Melie too!
Yeah, uh, how are ya, Melba?
It is a good morning, I mean
just look at this weather!
Yeah, what Doc just said!
How’s life, Melba?
Well, every day’s
a new adventure.
Say, I don’t think
I’ve met your friend yet.
Hi there, my name’s Melba.
What’s up, I’m Seth!
I’ma be a famous hunter
before long.
Oh!
[chuckles]
Well, I’m not much
for fighting Nemeses myself.
I just serve up drinks.
But it’s nice to meet you.
Yeah, right back at’cha!
Seth here is new to town,
he only just registered
as a citizen.
[MELBA]
That’s great!
This is a wonderful place
for young sorcerers.
Please feel free to visit us
at the café anytime!
-[SETH] Sure!
-[DOC] My beloved Miss Melba
looks as beautiful as ever!
Her big brown eyes
are like the cocoa
beans that grow
in paradise itself!
[PAPA]
Take this!
Get lost!
How dare you leer
at my little girl like that?
Papa, be nice!
Hm? Well, that’s
a beautiful flower.
-[PAPA grunts]
-[DOC screams]
-[MELBA] Please, Papa!
-Hold on.
The puppet’s her dad?
Sure is!
His name is Mister Melba Papa.
He’s a wonderful cook
and a doting father
who loves his little girl
more than anything in the world!
[BOTH panting]
That’s enough.
Really, you’re gonna scare away
all of our customers!
Hah! Any bloodsucking insect
that thinks he can steal
my daughter away
should be exterminated!
[DOC]
Wait, insect?
The man doesn’t even
consider me a human being.
So cruel.
[sighs]
I’m sorry, Doc.
When Papa gets worked up like
this, there’s no stopping him.
I wouldn’t worry
too much about him.
He’s used to this sorta thing.
[DOC cries]
And I thought today
was gonna be my day.
[chuckles]
Tell you what,
as a token of apology
and a gesture of friendship,
we’ll treat you all to one of
our best dishes, on the house.
Thank you!
Sounds great!
[groans, burps]
[SETH sighs]
That really hit the spot, Melba!
Thank you for treating us.
[MELIE] Yeah, I haven’t had
a meal that tasty in a while.
[MELBA]
I’m glad you liked it.
Make sure to let people know.
So, Seth,
you said you came here
from Pompo Hills.
Looking to get
your curse removed, I’ll bet.
-[SETH] Nope!
-[MELBA] Huh?
I wanna find out
where Radiant is,
so I can destroy it.
[MELBA]
What’s Radiant?
[MELIE] It’s apparently where
the Nemesis come from.
-[MELBA] Oh! You don’t say!
-[DOC] Hmph.
Of course a kid like him
would believe in fairy tales.
Talk about a stupid
waste of time.
-[MELBA] That’s amazing, Seth!
-Huh?!
And really brave of you.
I bet most people
would be too scared
to go to a place like that.
That’s true, but not me!
[DOC grumbling]
We just ate.
Are you still hungry?
That chair can’t
actually taste good.
It tastes like wood!
[SETH] Thing is, before I
can get to Radiant,
I need to learn
some new offensive magic.
[MELIE]
I really wanted to help him,
but I don’t know
that much myself.
So, we’re in a rut.
[MELBA]
Oh, I see. Rough.
[SETH] But then Melie suggested
that I get you to help me, Doc!
[DOC spews, coughs]
And what makes
you think I can help?
[SETH] Well, you’re
a researcher, so you know...
-[DOC] Huh?!
-[MELIE] I figured you’d’ve
learned a lot about
magic from your studies.
[SETH] Yeah, so I’ll be
counting on you!
[DOC] I can’t believe you had
the nerve to show up here,
let alone ask me to take time
from my day just to help you.
I could make a list of crap
you’ve done to me
that’s longer than you are tall,
you little menace!
-[SETH] Uh...
-[DOC] The debt you've saddled
me with gives me stomachaches
so bad I can't even sleep
at night! I just stay up
belching and crying and--
[MELBA] That’s just wonderful!
Huh?
Not only have you uncovered
the secrets of sorcery,
you’re also generous enough
to share your wisdom freely.
It’s like you’re
one of the great sages
they talk about in legends.
-[DOC grumbling]
-I respect that.
[DOC]
Ugh...
Yeah! That’s just how I do.
I mean, It’s my civic duty.
When you’ve got as much
worldly wisdom as I have,
you must save future generations
from their own ignorance!
Offensive magic, eh? Rest easy.
Once I finish teaching you,
you’ll be slinging spells you
never even realized existed.
[chuckles]
[SETH]
Whoa, really?
[MELBA]
I’m excited for you, Seth.
-She digs it.
-[MELBA] I’ll have to lend you
my own support as well.
I’ll brew you a cup
of my special herbal tea!
Huh?
Enjoy! I hope you like it!
Oh wow! Cool!
I didn’t know tea
could come in that color!
-Neither did I!
-[DOC] Don’t do it, kid,
if you drink it, then she’ll
make the rest of us
-drink it too,
-Down the hatch!
my stomach can’t
take it, ahh!
[gulping]
[coughing]
That’s certainly something.
I’ve never tasted
that combination of flavors.
-[PAPA] Hmm-hmm.
-'Course you haven’t.
It’s my very own
experimental blend.
The secret ingredient
for this batch is roast beef.
What the--?
Well, Doc? Like it as much
as the last blend?
Yup. Sure do.
You’ve outdone yourself
yet again.
[DOC screams]
So gross!
It taste’s like
a demon’s toilet water
mixed with cockroach tears.
If not for this,
she’d be a real angel!
[giggles]
Nothing gives an energy boost
quite like meat does.
-[MELBA] Here!
-[DOC cries]
Now don’t you worry,
there’s plenty more
where that came from.
Drink up! And put your best
foot forward, okay?
[nervously laughing]
This herbal tea of yours
is just incredible.
I wish I could sit back
and drink it all day long!
[nervously chuckles]
But Seth here says he wants
to start his training
as soon as possible,
so I’m afraid we have to run.
-[MELIE and SETH] Huh?
-But your tea.
Seth! What are you sitting
around here for, kid?
Come on, we gotta go!
Boy, it's really
a shame, though!
Another time, okay?
You keep that tea ready for me.
I love it more than anything!
-[DOC crying]
-Get lost.
And we’ll be keeping the change.
[MELIE]
Seth! Wait for me, will you?
They sure are in a hurry.
[DOC sighs]
I can’t believe I actually
agreed to help you learn magic.
What a pain the neck.
Good luck!
You try your best, okay?
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[DOC sighs]
[SETH] Well, Doc, let’s get
started already!
Come on!
Hey! Listen here!
I’m gonna help you
out this one time.
I told Melba I would,
and I keep my word.
That said! I’m not touchin’
any Fantasia myself,
and I’m not about
to spar with you.
The most I’ll be able
to do for you
is maybe read out loud
from some grimoires.
That sounds good to me!
For starters,
how ‘bout you teach me
what I gotta to do
to cast Meteor Drops?
[sighs]
-[MELIE giggles]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Let’s see.
Meteor Drops, Meteor Drops.
It’s around here
somewhere... ah!
Okay. Here it is.
So... first, you close
your eyes.
Then, take a deep breath,
nice and slow.
[DOC]
Next, release that breath
as if you’re expelling
all impurities from your body.
Once that’s done,
and you’re left empty,
open your consciousness
to the outside world,
and expand your senses.
You should feel Fantasia
all around you,
pressing against your body,
like a warm breeze.
Gather the Fantasia
in your magic tool.
Guess that’s
your gloves... yeah.
Gather it all in your gloves,
and clearly visualize the form
of the magic you want to create.
Focus your entire
being on this image.
[SETH] Visualize the form
of the magic.
Once the image
is formed in your mind,
shout the name of the spell.
Well, here goes nothing.
Meteor Drops!
[fart]
-[Doc] Uh...
-Aw, man!
What the heck was that?
Why didn’t it work?
I did it just like you told me!
-Come on!
-[DOC] I don’t know!
I gave you the instructions
straight out of this grimoire.
'Kay!
Let's try this again!
Meteor Drops!
Just drop already,
ya dumb meteors!
[SETH]
Meteor Drops!
[SETH with an accent]
Ya can’t brute force your way
through everything, kid.
Ahhh!
[shouts]
This time I’ve got it.
Meteor Drops!
[DOC screams]
[DOC]
I’ll be back.
-You killed Doc!
-I killed Doc!
[SETH]
Get over it.
I said I was sorry,
so stop your grumbling.
You shut up!
I don’t care what you say,
I’m never gonna help you again,
and that’s final!
But Doc,
if you won’t help him
then there’ll be nobody left
to teach him magic.
Sounds like a “him”
problem to me.
-[DOC grumbling]
-[MELIE whimpers]
[MELIE] Oh no.
Doc seems really upset.
If Seth can’t train, then
he’ll never find Radiant.
And I can’t help at all!
The heck’s my problem?
No matter how hard I try,
I can’t seem to do magic right.
Heh. I say, you just
don’t have the talent.
That’s so mean!
If you wanna know
what your problem is,
I can tell you right now.
-[SETH] Oh--
-[DOC] Huh?
In fact, I’ll pound
the answer into you
to make sure
you never forget it!
[DOC and SETH]
She flipped her switch again!
Here goes.
Meteor Drops!
-[SETH] Ahh!
-[PATRONS scream]
[SETH]
Wahh!
If I knew that crazy Melie
ate here,
I never would’ve come!
Run away!
Somebody save us!
Look, Papa, seems like
they’re having some fun.
Huh?
Look out, Melba!
Run for your life!
Uh...
[DOC screams]
[DOC]
Sometimes love hurts.
Doc, no!
I need to get
the heck outta here.
[SETH grunting, panting]
Get back here!
How cute!
It’s like they’re playing tag!
I’m gonna bill that Doc guy
for every last thing
that girl broke.
[explosions]
Melie! This isn’t funny!
So stop messing around!
I’m dead serious, Seth!
I suggest you start
fighting back!
No way am I gonna do that.
I don’t wanna hurt you!
You say that like
you think it’d be easy!
Oh crap, oh crap, oh crap!
[SETH screams]
Ow!
It’s almost like she’s
actually tryin’ to kill me.
Pathetic.
How’s a brat with no backbone
like you expect
to become a warrior?
You make me sick.
This isn’t the place
for a sparring match, Melie!
Whatever, stop with the whining.
Here comes round two!
[cracking]
Oh no! Wait!
Blow away!
Uh...
Melie no!
Ti--!
[MELIE]
Huh?
She’s too far away!
No choice then.
[SETH]
Come on, Fantasia.
I need you to work
with me, this time!
Meteor Drops!
[SETH]
Melie!
-Uh...
-[SETH squeezes]
I did it! I really did it!
You saw, didn’t you?
Well, of course you did.
So cool!
I just cast Meteor Drops
for the first time!
[SETH chuckles]
I really did it!
And it’s all thanks
to you and Doc!
Uh, am I--?
Oh. Hey, Melie.
Looks like you’re back
to normal again.
Huh...
Hm...
[MELIE screams]
This is horrible.
I hope you’re okay.
[SETH]
Oh, I’m fine.
I managed to dodge
most of your spells.
[gasps]
Oh my gosh, I’m so sorry!
If you hate me now and want me
to stay away, I get it.
I’d never hate you over
something silly like that.
Huh?
In fact, I should
be thanking you!
After all,
if you hadn’t pushed me,
I wouldn’t’ve been able
to use Meteor Drops!
Really?
Seth, do you mean it?
Because as long as I was able
to be helpful to you,
I’ll be happy.
-Yeah!
-[MELIE giggles]
Oh. So, um...
you kinda sent Doc flying.
-We should prob’ly find him.
-[MELIE] Ahh!
[DOC]
Hey!
Help me!
Someone get me down!
[cries]
[SETH]
Meteor Drops!
See that? What’cha think?
Well...
you could stand to gather
more Fantasia,
but I’ve seen worse.
[chuckles]
Way to go, me!
Now, I’m ready
to take on Radiant!
-[whack]
-Ow!
Ow! What was that for?
You really don’t understand
a thing, do you?
That blasted Alma dumped
a complete rookie on me.
-Huh?
-Listen well.
Radiant is
a forbidden territory.
[YAGA] Many of the world’s
most notable sorcerers
have tried long
and hard to locate it.
And not a single one of them has
ever come close to that goal.
How would a feckless punk
like you stand a chance
where they failed?
I’m not saying it’s impossible.
Just that if you wanna do it,
you have to train hard,
and become
a first-rate sorcerer.
Luckily for you,
I happen to know a sorcerer who
can bring you to their level.
[SETH gasps]
Yaga!
Please take me on as your pupil!
I just might,
but before that...
Uh...
Cauldron. Crash!
Eeee...
-No way!
-[DOC
-Exactly as I thought.
-What was that for?!
You said your name
was Seth, right?
Uh, yeah. Did you forget?
You’re going to have to learn
a lot more control,
especially considering
those frail hands of yours.
I warn you now,
my training is both strict
and demanding.
Uh...
Right!
[sighs]
Wow, what a beautiful morning!
Don’t you agree?
Gudule.
Gertrude!
[MELIE giggles]
I feel like this is gonna be
a really wonderful day!
[SETH]
Watch out Melie!
Not again!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE screams]
-Oh no!
Gudule, your head!
Melie.
Sorry for dropping in like this.
The thing is, I need you
to let me live in your house.
-Huh?
-I’m sorry.
I was staying in the park
and that was fine for me.
But Doc tells me
I can’t even sleep there.
Well, not for free.
You’re a real piece
of work, kid!
You just keep runnin’ up
my debt don’t’cha?
Between café repairs
and street repairs,
and walkway fees and now this,
it’s pilin’ up so much
I can’t even afford to go
to Kettle Coffee anymore!
[SETH]
Oops. My bad...
If you get that it’s your fault,
then hurry up,
and find a place to live!
-Yeah
-Oh.
So what do you say?
Please let me stay here!
I suppose.
I do have a spare room
that I’m not using
for anything else really.
So...
You could use it if you want.
-You’re serious?
-Totally! Why not?
I mean, I always
have a lot of fun
when you’re around,
so let’s do it!
The idea of having my own
roommate is kind of exciting.
[giggles]
So move on in!
Thanks, Melie,
you’re a lifesaver.
-I’m glad we’ll be roomies!
-Thank you!
-I feel exactly the same, Seth.
-So... hey,
I’ve been wondering
since I last flew in here...
[MELIE]
Hm?
What’s the deal with
that doll lookin’ thing?
[MELIE]
Oh! That’s uh--
Well it’s a he, and he’s um...
you know. I guess
you could say...
he’s my friend.
[SETH]
Wait. What?
-Does he talk to you?
-[MELIE] Kinda?
[NARRATOR] Danger stalks
the streets of Artemis.
One seemingly
peaceful afternoon,
Doc is taken away
by a mysterious creature.
To save Doc,
Seth and Melie venture
deep into the sewers.
There, in the darkness,
they encounter a fearsome beast
that the Titan Punch
cannot harm.
Next time on Radiant,
“The Beast of the
Underground Water System”