[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who
can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
Doc, Seth, and Melie
went to Rumble Town,
accepting a job request
for Nemesis Hunters.
Discovering Nemeses
in its oddly deserted streets,
they gave chase.
But Seth was stopped by Grimm,
a mysterious sorcerer
wrapped in bandages.
Thanks to Melie's help,
they emerged unscathed.
But the damage caused
by their fight
attracted Inquisition attention.
[whistle blowing]
[INQUISITION SOLDIER 1]
Leave no stone unturned!
[INQUISITION SOLDIER 2]
Where could those sorcerers
have run off to?
Did you look down that street?
[INQUISITION SOLDIER 3]
Not yet.
[SOLDIER 2] Then come on!
Let's get moving!
[SOLDIER 1] They must be
around here! Get a move on!
[SETH]
Think they're gone?
[MELIE]
I don't hear them but--
[DOC]
I say it's worth the risk.
[ALL]
So stinky!
Damn you!
Why'd you have to go
and make such a ruckus
as soon as we got to town, huh?
Like I told you!
I was chasing
a bunch of Nemeses
when that bandaged guy
attacked me out of nowhere!
Did you conveniently
forget the part
where you destroyed
a whole building
while you was fightin' him?
Yeah...
and all the lil' monsters
got away too.
How many were there?
[SETH]
Dunno.
I'd guess around fifteen?
[DOC]
That many? No way!
How the heck can we
capture ‘em all at once?
Then again, if we do manage
to pull it off,
it'll do more
than repay our debt.
I'll be filthy rich!
And Melba's pops'll have to
acknowledge me as a fine suitor.
[DOC and MELIE sigh, laughing]
Hey, what's the hold up?
We've got Nemeses to hunt,
let's get a move on.
Not so fast.
Before we do anything else,
we need to talk to the client
who sent the letter.
-Hey.
-Huh?
Could we discuss this
outside the dumpster?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[NARRATOR] “The Shadow
Lurking in the City.”
[machinery pounding]
Damn these sorcerers.
Instead of facing my forces
openly, they hide like rats.
It seems I've no choice
but to head out there myself.
First, I'll find out
where that scum is hiding.
Then I'll mop it up by hand.
[grunts]
Err?
[slurping]
Ahh, Konrad,
how've you been?
Dragunov?!
Well, given the fine furnishings
you have in your castle,
and the well-aged wine
you've stocked,
I don't actually need to ask
to see that you're doing well.
[door slams shut]
Tell me, Captain Dragunov,
what business do you have
in my town?
[DRAGUNOV]
Straight to the point, eh?
We've known each other for ages.
Don't you care to ask
how I've been?
Konrad, you wound me!
That's “Captain Marbourg”
to you!
You look even beefier
than I remember.
Konnyboy.
It's Captain Marbourg!
I'm quite impressed that you
can balance your duties
with a 12-hour-a-day
workout plan.
I don't work out
12 hours a day!
That isn't what
you said in your journal.
What? Hey!
How dare you read that?!
And get your damn boots
off my table!
[DRAGUNOV laughs]
That sounds more like
the Konrad I know.
[huffs]
We're both captains now,
which means that you can no
longer treat me as an inferior.
It's time you addressed me
with the respect I'm due.
Rumble Town is under my command.
These soldiers answer to me
and no one else.
Fine, point taken.
Here, you take a seat
and I'll shut my big mouth.
I say, you take a seat and
I'll shut my big mou-ou-oh.
[KONRAD grunts, grumbles]
[KONRAD grunts again]
Actually,
you just sit and be quiet.
Tell me what you're doing here.
I wasn't informed that
you were coming this way.
[slurping]
Hey!
Answer the damn question,
would you?
Thought I was s'posed
to keep my mouth shut.
Fine! I give you permission to
tell me what you're doing here!
I'm after a group of sorcerers
that I believe
are somewhere nearby.
Ah, I'm hunting them myself.
They caused an explosion
on 12th Street,
and fled to the slums
where they're now hiding.
Don't you worry, Captain,
I'll have those filthy infected
in chains before the day's end.
[DRAGUNOV]
About that,
could you leave them be
for now?
[gasps]
I give the orders here!
And if you don't like it,
then I'll rip your eyeballs out
through your nostrils!
But I'm not the source
of this order.
It's from above.
[KONRAD exhales]
The Commander?
Try about two levels higher up.
You mean General Torque?
But why?!
I can't tell you that.
Suppose you'll just have
to wait and see.
Arrgh!
But there are sorcerers
skulking about my city!
I can't be expected to stand by
and do nothing!
Are you throwing a tantrum?
You're the one
who's throwing a tantrum!
Now stop trying to
boss me around!
You look about fit to explode.
You're the one who looks like
he's about to explode!
Just have a glass of your wine
and relax.
You have a glass of my wine
and relax!
I'll go out and tell your troops
to stand down for you,
how's that sound?
I can tell my troops
to stand down myself!
[KONRAD grumbles]
[panting angrily]
I've had it up to here
with your mind games, Dragunov!
[humming]
[DOC]
This should be the place.
-[DOC clears his throat]
-[knocking on door]
[DOC]
Anyone home?
What the hell do you want?
[DOC] We're looking for
the Zeda family.
Wrong address.
[ALL gasp]
[pounding on door]
You've got the wrong place,
so leave already!
Huh?
You people are the ones
who called us here!
So if you don't want your house
blown to bits,
you'll let us in right now!
[MR. ZEDA]
All right, fine!
I'm sorry about
my husband's behavior,
but thank you so much
for coming to Rumble Town
to fulfill our request.
[TAJ'S SIBLINGS laughing]
You stink!
That's a lively bunch of little
rascals you've got yourselves.
[MR. ZEDA grumbles]
[DOC chuckles awkwardly]
Listen dear, these sorcerers
traveled all the way
from Artemis to help us,
so the least we can do
is be polite.
[MR. ZEDA]
Hmph.
I really am so sorry.
[awkwardly laughs]
In the letter you sent,
you mentioned that your son
came across a Nemesis
in town, correct?
Yes.
It was our eldest son Taj.
A demon-- no.
No, a Nemesis, as you call them,
attacked him in the street.
Hold on, are you sayin' that he
came into contact with one?
-[MRS. ZEDA] Yes.
-[BOTH gasp]
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize--
I don't know anything
about a Nemesis.
[DOC]
Uh, who's this?
[MRS. ZEDA]
That's our eldest son, Taj.
[ALL]
You mean he's still alive?
Well, of course I am.
Don't go killing me off yet.
You don't know how lucky you are
to have touched a Nemesis
and lived to tell about it.
Like I said, I don't know
anything about a Neme--
A-choo!
Well then what do you
have to say about that?
You clearly have a curse.
No, it's just a cold.
Hate to break it to ya,
but that's a curse for sure.
-No, it's just a cold!
-[DOC whimpers]
-[TAJ sneezes]
-[MR. ZEDA groans]
[DOC]
Wha--? Get outta here!
You complained about
the Nemesis,
but the Inquisition
don't believe you?
I'm pretty sure we said
all this in the letter.
-I remember that...
-[SETH drooling]
but I thought it was
some kinda mistake.
I can't believe they'd ignore a
Nemesis right under their noses.
[TAJ'S YOUNGER SISTER]
We've told them over and over,
but they won't
even look into it.
[DOC]
Hmm. Well that's a problem.
We need to get the Inquisition
to see our side of things.
Without their permission,
we won't even be able
to stay on the island.
Let alone use magic
on a Nemesis in public.
Forget it.
The Inquisition will not lift a
finger to help migrants like us.
Migrants?
[MRS. ZEDA] Rumble Town
is known far and wide
as a good place to find jobs.
Thanks to the factories,
people have migrated here
to seek work for many decades.
We came here over 20 years ago
for just that reason.
But the locals--
those whose families
have been here for generations--
well, they never thought
too highly of people like us.
So if you were to go and tell
them that our son's infected,
they would not be kind.
I told you, I'm fine!
I just have a cold, let it go!
That's right, Taj.
It's nothing but a cold.
And that's the whole story.
Sorry to waste your time,
but I would like you to leave.
Now.
I know how you feel,
but if we don't do something--
[MR. ZEDA]
Hmph!
[ALL sigh]
[SETH sighs]
Not to worry.
Permission or not,
we'll destroy that thing.
No, we won't!
We're gonna capture it,
remember?
Was that the plan?
Yeah, maybe try
listening for once.
Eh, doesn't matter.
There are Nemeses in town.
We know because
we saw them ourselves.
And we can't just ignore that.
-[TAJ] Hey. You serious?
-[SETH] Huh?
You're really gonna try
and help us out?
Yeah!
We're not leavin'
till the Nemeses do.
Well in that case,
I can point you in
the right direction, at least.
♪
Hey, Taj!
This bread your mom made
for us is fantastic!
[TAJ]
Meh.
[DOC panting]
[SOLDIER 4]
Move it! Clear the way!
Anyone suspicious
will be arrested!
What's their problem?
That's how they always act.
Let's go.
[DOC]
By the way, Taj.
Can you tell us anything about
what the Nemesis looked like?
[TAJ grunts]
Just that it was huge.
[MELIE]
So how many were there?
[TAJ]
I only saw one.
[SETH]
And it was really big, huh?
[MELIE]
It sounds to me like the one
Taj ran into must've been
the Source Nemesis.
And what does that mean?
Not all Nemeses come down
by themselves.
Some bring allies.
The smaller ones that we were
tracking last night
are called Echo Nemeses.
They're a good bit
smaller and weaker,
and unlike
the Source Nemesis,
they aren't able to
infect people with curses.
I guess they're kind of
like scouts.
Echoes.
-[TAJ] It was over there.
-[SETH] Hm?
That's where
the Nemesis attacked.
[SETH]
Near that building?
It was dark when it happened,
so I couldn't see all that much.
But its eyes were enormous,
and they glowed.
Thanks, you can go back.
If it's still around,
we'll deal with it.
I'm gettin' kinda dizzy.
Well.
Try to hang in there, okay?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[groans]
Ever since we got here,
I been smelling somethin' awful.
We must be in the right place.
[SETH grunting]
This building's pretty huge.
I bet a Nemesis could
live in here for sure!
Whoa.
It's a Feather Tree!
This one's enormous.
It isn't the first one
you've encountered then?
It's not.
Back in the day, Alma took me
to see a couple of 'em.
[SETH] She said they grow
wherever a Nemesis dwells.
This is the biggest one
I've ever seen, though.
[DOC] That's a pretty
crazy amount of feathers, too.
[MELIE]
Yeah.
The Source Nemesis must have
been holed up in here
for a good while.
[DOC] Which is odd, since
they're typically nomadic types.
I've never heard of
a feather tree
getting anywhere near this big.
[rumbling]
[SETH]
What the--?
[MELIE] Pretty sure
it's an earthquake!
-[rumbling]
-[bell ringing]
[CITIZENS worried chatter]
[SOLDIER 5]
Come on! Keep it movin'!
Hurry up! Before the ground
falls out from under you!
Hey, twerp!
Didn't you look
at the day's clock map?
The shelter's back
on 5th Street.
[SOLDIER 6] 15 years behind bars
to any non-compliants!
Head to Gate 12,
on the double!
What's the deal?
Why are they making
everyone evacuate?
I don't think this is just
some random earthquake.
Wait, I know!
All these years of mining
deep into the ground
have made the island unstable.
So when the place
gets out of balance,
they have to move the residents
around to prevent a collapse.
Gotcha.
And that would explain
where everyone was
when we first got to town.
[DOC]
Yeah.
And I bet that clock tower's
givin' people their orders.
All right, we'd better move too!
-[MELIE] Right!
-[SETH] No, wait.
[DOC and MELIE gasp]
Didn't you hear what I just
said, this area is dangerous.
The first place we went
was evacuated,
and that's where
we found the echoes.
Wait a sec, do you think
the Nemeses are waiting
until everyone leaves
to come out?
Can't say for sure.
But still, there's a chance
they'll show up again.
There's also a chance
we'll be crushed by the rubble.
Not if we keep watch
from the sky, there isn't!
[ALL breathe nervously]
[bell ringing]
[CITIZENS indistinct chatter]
[MR. ZEDA] We cannot get
separated again, all right?
Yessir.
Huh?
[DOC groaning]
[gasps]
[SETH]
Bingo! See 'em?
[MELIE] It looks like
there are more than 15.
[DOC] No way we can handle
all these things on our own.
[SETH]
They're coming this way.
Can't we do something
about those three at least?
[MELIE]
Yeah, if we corner them somehow.
[SETH]
Hmm...
Titan... Punch!
Kid's off his rocker.
Hey, Seth, can you hear me?
You okay?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[SETH lightly grunting]
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha! We just put these
echoes down for the count!
[continues laughing]
[SETH]
Huh!
Meteor... Drops!
[gasp]
[SETH grunts, groans]
It got him!
Land right there.
[MELIE]
Seth! Are you hurt?!
[SETH]
I'm fine.
[DOC] It looks like you scraped
up your face pretty good.
[SETH] Forget that,
deal with the echoes!
Don't let them get away!
If you hold them in place for
a few moments, I can trap them.
I'm on it!
[SETH grunts]
Whaddaya think, Melie?
Will this work?
Yes!
[gasps]
Why's that glowing?
You probably wanna get out
of the circle now!
Oh, okay!
Here I go!
Gravem Carserem!
-[SETH grunts]
-[MELIE gasps]
We actually pulled it off!
Yeah!
We bagged ourselves
one, two, three!
We caught three Nemeses alive!
We can make a fortune
off these things!
And when Melba finds out...
Wow, you really caught
three of them, you're so brave!
That's right,
we just turned ‘em in.
It was no big deal though,
at least not for a natural
born hunter like myself.
Ah! Then I want to
marry you three times!
And buy three houses!
And bring up
three beautiful babies!
-[MELBA sighs lovingly]
-[DOC chuckles]
You and your pretty schemes.
Whoa, buy me a drink first,
dollface.
Or just bring me one
from the shop, ha-ha.
Ahh, if we really
get rich after this,
I know what I wanna do.
Everybody!
There's lots of food!
So eat your hearts out!
I want all my friends
to have a great time!
[ALL]
Yay!
[chuckles]
Yeah, of course you can
have seconds, Gertrude,
you are one of my many
dear friends, after all.
[SETH]
Nice!
After this, we can
pay off our debt!
Yeah!
And I can start to eat somethin'
aside from wild plants!
Let's get these echoes
captured for real
so we can have a party
every single day!
Huh? I thought that part
was already done.
No, we still need to seal them
inside of those magical
scrolls I brought.
It's not the easiest
spell to do,
so I'll really need to focus.
[DOC] There's no chance of them
gettin' away, is there?
[MELIE]
Thanks to my binding spell,
they should feel too heavy
to run anywhere.
Plus, they're all connected
so I don't think one of them
would leave the others
even if it could.
Go Melie! You're a genius,
ya know that?
Who, me?
I wanna hear three cheers
for Melie, the hero!
[thud]
[ALL gasp, whimper]
-[SETH screams]
-[MELIE] Another one!
Four, five, six, and seven!
We caught seven live Nemeses!
-[SETH and MELIE] Yahoo!
-[DOC cheers]
[DOC]
Seven weddings!
Seven babies!
Seven houses!
[explosion]
[ALL scream]
Not my parties and my friends!
You ruined my wedding!
You murdered my family!
Hey!
You're the guy!
The sorcerer who attacked me!
We meet again.
Unfortunate.
You are not the ones
Grimm was seeking.
[SETH] Yeah, well we didn't
wanna see you either!
Get lost already!
First a quick look.
Veneficium Revelare.
-[ALL gasp]
-[GRIMM] Hm...
Your goal was to
capture them alive?
What was it that woman
entrusted you with?
Like I said, I'm not
telling you anything!
Now square up and fight!
I'm'a kick your butt
into orbit!
Apologies.
But Grimm has no time to waste
on the three of you.
What?! You're running again?!
After him, go grab him
with your chain, Melie.
Right!
Farewell.
[SETH]
Come back here!
Aw, crap!
He got away so easy!
[MELIE]
It's okay!
I was able to put a mark on him,
so he won't get
the drop on us again.
-[SETH] Awesome!
-[DOC] All right!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
This journey has been
both long and unpleasant.
Forgive Grimm for that.
But it's all over now.
You can finally rest.
[ZOMBIES muffled grunting]
Gentlemen.
Please, treat your new guests
just as gently
as Grimm once treated you.
[NARRATOR]
When Konrad of the Inquisition
fills the citizens
of Rumble Town with fear,
they riot in the streets,
calling for the expulsion
of all immigrants.
Needless to say, this is
exactly as Konrad had planned.
The people grow violent.
Can Seth bring an end
to the chaos to come?
Next time, on "Radiant,"
“Overture of Turbulence.”