[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[machinery pounding]
[SETH sighs]
What the heck is that
bandaged weirdo's deal?
Yeah, it was pretty mean of him
to swoop in right
as we were about
to catch those echoes.
[DOC]
He might be the person to blame
for all the recent
disappearances in Rumble Town.
There've been disappearances?
I remember.
Mrs. Zeda mentioned them
in the letter she sent out.
That's right.
At first I figured the Nemesis
was behind it,
but now I'm not so sure.
[groans in pain]
It sounds like you're
still feeling
a little bit under the weather.
[DOC] I bit off more than
I could chew with this trip.
I'm sorry, but I think
I'd better head back to Artemis.
Huh?
But we haven't finished
the job here!
[DOC scoffs]
[DOC] As if a coward like me
could help you beat a Nemesis.
I'm gonna shove off tomorrow.
Just leave me be
in the meantime, okay?
No way this can really be
what you want.
Sure it can, and it is.
[BOTH groan, disappointed]
[MISTER BOOBRIE snores]
[SETH]
Doc.
Hey, Doc.
[DOC]
Mm? Wha--
[DOC clears throat]
Whaddaya want?
[SETH] If you're really gonna
leave tomorrow,
then first, let me ask you this.
Here's the thing.
When we were capturing
those echoes.
I got close,
and I noticed a weird
marking on one of their tails.
-[DOC] Mm?
-Can you guess what it was?
Uh...
[DOC]
All right.
So every Nemesis has some
kinda mark like you described
somewhere on it.
I've studied 'em for years,
and I've still got no clue
what they mean.
They take all shapes and sizes.
All I can tell you for sure:
is that if that mark is glowing,
it means the Nemesis is being
controlled by a sorcerer.
[SETH] Whoa, people actually
control them?
Yeah, they're widely seen
as enemies of humanity.
These sorcerers are known
as "Domitors."
Domitors, huh?
[flute playing]
[running footsteps]
[flute continues playing]
[WOMAN gasps]
Welcome back.
We lost so many
little ones today.
I'm so sorry.
But after 15 years,
we've finally reached the end.
It'll all be over soon.
Okay?
All of it will end.
[NARRATOR]
"Overture of Turbulence"
[ROOKIE yawns]
[ROOKIE] Just how long are we
supposed to stay on standby for?
[VICE]
I don't know.
Sit tight.
We're to wait for further
instructions.
Have faith.
I'm certain the Captain
has a plan.
[ROOKIE sighs]
I just mostly miss
the captain's cooking.
[VICE] Your demeanor's taken
quite the shift, Rookie.
Huh?
Not sure what you mean,
but anyway.
I hear that
Captain Konrad de Marbourg
is in charge in Rumble Town,
and uses some
pretty shady methods.
Our captain knows, right?
[VICE]
He's heard the rumors.
That said.
Captain Dragunov's always been
one to draw his own conclusions.
If he decides action is needed,
we'll be ready.
[ROOKIE]
Yes, sir.
[TOWN CRIER]
Hear this, good citizens!
There was a terrible incident
last night
in which the theater's
roof caved in!
[CROWD gasps]
Paragon of stoicism
though he is,
even our own Captain Konrad
is enraged!
And who has provoked him?
Who has blatantly attacked us?
It's the unwashed immigrants
we welcomed to our town,
only to watch them spit
on our way of life!
Even now, they conspire
with foul sorcerers!
In a sinister scheme
to overthrow Rumble Town,
and take it for themselves!
Right under our noses.
I bet they're the ones behind
all of the disappearances too!
-[bell dinging]
-[BOTH CITIZENS] Huh?
[TOWN CRIER]
But that isn't all!
There are also rumors that
Captain Dragunov himself
has been sent here to glean
what he may with his Lynx eye!
All evidence points to an
impending large-scale
terrorist attack,
perpetrated by
an immigrant-sorcerer alliance!
[WOMAN]
How terrifying.
[MAN] What if they
cause a repeat of what happened
15 years ago?
[TOWN CRIER]
Remember!
It's been a mere 15 years
since District 13 caved in!
It is only through
our collective vigilance
that we can prevent
a repeat of that tragedy!
We must never allow it
to happen again!
-[CROWD murmuring]
-[MAN A] He's right!
We need to clamp down
on those immigrants!
[MAN B]
What the hell?
Is taking our jobs
not enough for them?!
[MAN C]
I say let's run them out!
Let's take back Rumble Town!
-[CROWD] Yeah!
-[KONRAD chuckles]
[KONRAD] Seems all is
proceeding smoothly.
-[DRAGUNOV slowly claps]
-[KONRAD] Hm?
Impressive.
You certainly know
how to work up a mob.
[KONRAD]
I don't know what you mean.
There's no need to play dumb.
This was clearly your doing.
You're riling up the townsfolk
so they'll hunt down
the sorcerers
and immigrants for you.
This civil strife
is your kindling.
Soon, you'll need but a spark
to set it aflame.
And recreate the tragedy
of District 13.
Just what are you implying?
The sorcerers are just
a pretense, right?
Seems to me, it's the immigrants
who are really in your way.
That's right.
They've already
ruined their homelands,
and now they want to do
the same here!
For every normal person you pass
in the slums,
you get a dozen foreigners.
Argh!
I shall act as this town's
defensive wall,
by protecting it
from every threat.
And the insidious danger
posed by these foreigners
is the greatest threat
we now face.
I'm sure your mother's
very proud.
Enlighten me a bit further,
Konrad.
Do you think you're a king?
What?
Stop with your taunts.
Exactly whose side are you on,
Captain Dragunov?
It's my sworn duty
as an Inquisitor
to protect the people
at all costs,
and that's what
I intend to do.
So when you speak
of protecting "the people"
you mean the ones
who aren't immigrants.
Right?
Obviously!
Ugh, immigrants shouldn't
be protected any more
than the infected are.
[DRAGUNOV] This town is
under your jurisdiction.
So I won't interfere.
However...
I'll ask you one last question.
You aren't so preoccupied
with immigrants
that you're letting a Nemesis
roam the town freely, are you?
[KONRAD nervously grunts]
Because if you were,
then I would feel compelled to
ask whose side it is you're on.
Would a defender of the people
let a monster
stalk their streets?
[KONRAD laughing]
Don't be ridiculous.
You have no proof
of this theory.
No sir.
I don't.
Please forgive me.
I almost forgot to tell you
something quite important.
[KONRAD]
Mm?
[DRAGUNOV]
You should expect General Torque
and his Thaumaturges
to arrive in town by tomorrow.
What's the general want here?
What's he after?
[DRAGUNOV] They're coming for
the same reason I did.
It's the horned sorcerer
I've been pursuing.
General Torque is gravely
concerned about the danger
he could pose.
I'm sure that when the General
sees what you've been up to,
he'll reward your efforts.
That is, if you've been
doing your job.
Have you?
[hurried footsteps,
metal jingling]
[KONRAD]
This is bad.
The last thing I need now
is a suspicious Dragunov
nosing about.
[DRAGUNOV]
You aren't letting a Nemesis
roam the town freely,
are you?
"Roam freely"?
[chuckles]
[laughing maniacally]
Certainly not.
[huffing, breathing heavily]
But...the man is perceptive.
Also, with General Torque
and the Thaumaturges
arriving tomorrow,
it may prove difficult to keep
this secret any longer.
[fist clenching]
Even if I have to use
a bit of force,
just as I did 15 years ago.
I need to advance my plan
to its final stages.
[creaking]
And the sorcerers hiding in town
are just what I need
to turn this tension
-into chaos.
-[thudding]
Now, the hunt can truly begin.
[SETH]
Hey, Doc.
-Doc, wait up!
-[DOC groans]
Look, uh,
are you really gonna take off?
-Because--
-Yeah, you better believe I am.
That crazy bandage guy's here.
And if you saw right,
there's also a
Domitor-controlled
Nemesis roamin' around.
I gave this adventurin' thing
my best shot.
But I'm done takin' on jobs
that involve Nemeses.
This stuff's
too dangerous for me.
I understand that, but maybe
you should stay here
until you're feeling better.
[DOC]
Even if I were immortal,
it wouldn't be enough
to keep me alive in this town.
I'm going home.
You're just gonna leave
all these defenseless people
to suffer?!
[DOC grunts]
[SETH]
Well, I'm not going with you!
[DOC]
That's fine!
Have it your way!
But...
don't forget what I said.
There's something off
about the Inquisitors here.
It's as though
they're deliberately
ignoring the Nemeses.
You might catch the monsters,
but good luck
bringing them to Artemis
so you can get paid for it.
[MELIE]
Yeah, but...
You're right, and that's why
we can't ignore this!
More of these people
could end up like Taj or worse,
and no one else cares enough
to protect them.
We're the only hope they have!
[DOC sighs]
Someday you're gonna
have to see reality.
I can't help.
That's that.
Don't blame me if you
get in over your head
and wind up dead.
Didn't think he'd really leave.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
So what do we do now, Seth,
where do we go from here?
That's a good question.
[MELIE groans]
This day has gotten off to
a pretty rough start,
hasn't it?
[SETH stomach rumbling]
Agreed, we haven't
even had breakfast.
Then why don't we go back
to Taj's house,
and see if they might be willing
to share some food?
[SETH]
Yeah, good idea!
We're their only hope,
so they have to feed us!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chattering]
-[MELIE] I hope they have meat!
[wood creaking]
-[SETH grunts]
-[MELIE whimpers]
[SETH]
Whoa!
What the heck happened here?!
Taj! Mr. and Mrs. Zeda,
it's me, Seth.
If any of you can hear me,
then say something!
It looks like everyone's gone.
And whatever happened here,
it was violent.
[MAN]
Excuse me, but uh...
You should prob'ly keep
your distance from that house.
Why, do you know
what happened here?
The family that lived
at this address
has been taken
to the authorities.
On suspicion of harboring
an infected.
-[MELIE gasps]
-You're kidding me.
As of today, the Inquisition
has been rounding up immigrants
from all over the place,
and accusing them
of colluding with sorcerers.
Word is, they were plotting
some terrorist attack.
[MELIE]
What?! Oh, no...
Taj!
[MELIE whimpers]
Oh, yeah.
Right behind you!
[CROWD murmuring, indistinctly]
And now...
Konrad de Marbourg
will show you all
the grandest drama any of you
will see in your lifetimes.
What do you think
Konrad'll have to say?
I heard he found out the truth
behind that terror
incident at the theater.
Look.
There's the captain now!
[CROWD mummers excitedly]
[KONRAD]
Good Citizens.
I'm sure that you've felt
concerned, even afraid,
since the extremist attack
on our theatre.
However,
I've uncovered an even more
frightening truth
that I must share with you.
This was but the first stage
of a large-scale terrorist plot,
conceived of and carried out
by an alliance
of immigrants and sorcerers!
[CROWD gasps]
[WOMAN] They have
to be stopped! But how?
There is but one way
to keep the events of 15 years
ago from happening again.
And that's by taking
drastic measures.
Your countrymen.
Your families!
Your homes, and your very lives
are all in danger.
These outsiders have come,
not to live beside us,
but to take all that
we've built for themselves!
How far will we let them
push us?
When will enough be enough?
[MAN A]
No! We're gonna fight back!
[MAN B]
We won't let them do it!
We'll stop them!
[WOMAN]
Please help us, Captain Konrad!
Obviously.
As Rumble Town's defensive wall,
I shall protect my people!
However!
Preserving the balance
of this town is no easy task.
Therefore, I must ask each
of you to lend me your aid.
I'm not following.
[KONRAD]
We have been too tolerant,
too accepting
of their differences.
And we've been blind.
Blind to their savage customs.
To the truth that violence
is rooted in their culture.
To the threat
of their sheer numbers.
Let us stand as one,
to protect our beautiful town,
and our way of life, together!
[MAN A]
Yeah! Go!
Hunt down the infected
and the immigrants!
[MAN B] We gotta
kill them before they kill us!
[MAN C]
Let's show 'em that we won't
take this lying down!
[MAN D]
Wait, how can we tell
which immigrants
are responsible?
[WOMAN] We can't
sort out the one or two
good ones from all the bad.
There's no time!
The lady has it right!
There's too much at stake
for us to compromise!
Don't waste your pity
on the enemy.
Either they're one of us,
or they're against us!
Show these bloodthirsty
parasites
that the tolerance
of good people has its limits,
and purify our homes
once and for all!
Citizens of Rumble Town, I call
on you to rise up and fight!
[MAN]
Let's hunt them down!
[CROWD chanting]
Hunt them! Hunt them! Hunt them!
[chuckling]
I've never been so proud.
[CROWD chanting, continues]
[DRAGUNOV]
Damn it, Konrad.
I hoped I could spook you
into stopping.
But it looks like my warning
only motivated you
to faster action.
You have to know that I won't
just stand by and do nothing.
[CROWD angrily yelling out]
[SETH]
Crap...
Taj, where are you?
[MELIE]
Crazy.
All of these seemingly normal
people have been consumed
by their fear of the unknown.
We can't let that mob find Taj
before we do!
[MELIE]
Let's hurry!
[CROWD yelling, continues]
[DOC]
Whoa.
No clue what's gotten
into these people,
but I know I don't like it.
I need to get outta this town
by yesterday.
[DOC panting, grunts]
-[rhythmic thumping]
-What's that noise?
I'll just take a peek.
Ahh!
N-Nemeses!
How?
There's no way a Nemesis nest
would go unnoticed here
in the middle of town.
But if the Inquisitors
know about it,
and still chose to do nothing...
[shudders]
oh.
Come on!
You already made up your mind
to go back to Artemis, okay?
Uhh. Yeah.
What happens here
isn't my concern now.
They can deal with it.
And what kind of a difference
could a coward
like me make, anyway?
[grunts]
I meant what I said.
I'm goin' home, that's that!
But...
I couldn't live with myself
if I didn't at least let those
morons know what I saw here.
Huh? Uhh...
[INQUISITION SOLDIER]
Too bad for you.
[DOC gasps, whimpers]
[CROWD yelling, indistinct]
[TAJ]
What's wrong with you?!
Why are you doing this?!
This one's an immigrant
and he's infected!
Only one way
to deal with this monster.
[TAJ]
Please!
I'm not a monster, I swear!
[MAN A]
Shut up!
And stop pretending
you're a normal kid!
[MAN B] Yeah! It's
not like we want to do this!
But Captain Konrad
said we have to.
It's the only way to protect
our families!
We have no choice!
[TAJ crying out]
Help me!
-[SETH grunts]
-[MEN gasp]
Get the hell away from him!
No! It's another sorcerer!
-[screams]
-[SETH] That's right.
I am and I just infected you
with the curse of sorcery.
[MAN B]
No!
No, not the curse!
Spare me, I beg you!
[MEN yelling]
[MAN A]
We were just following
Captain Konrad's orders!
Who's Konrad?
[MAN C]
We need help!
Call for backup!
-[TAJ crying]
-[SETH gasps]
[gasps]
Seth.
You saved me.
They can't hurt you now.
I won't let them.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
[MELIE]
Come on!
Let's get out of here.
Right!
[SOLDIER]
Captain!
We received word
from the north gate
that the sorcerers were spotted
flying nearby.
[KONRAD]
So they've shown themselves.
Excellent.
All right.
Then relay this order
to the cannon crews.
They are to take aim above
the north gate.
[SOLDIER] But the shots
would land in the city, sir.
And we haven't evacuated
the citizens yet.
We cannot afford
to waste this chance
for such a trivial reason.
Collateral damage is a sad fact
of any war.
Also, it's only
the northern district.
Where the immigrants live.
[SOLDIER shudders]
[KONRAD]
This is an order.
Prepare the bombardment.
[SETH lightly grunts]
'Kay.
We should be safe up here.
-[TAJ panting]
-Taj.
Where are your parents,
are they okay?
[TAJ gasps]
Not really.
They were taken away by the
Inquisitors for sheltering me
when I got infected.
-[SETH gasps]
-That's horrible.
[haltingly]
It's just so messed up.
None of us did anything wrong,
did we?
So why?
Why did this happen?
[TAJ sniffles]
[SETH]
Taj.
You're right.
You didn't do anything wrong,
and you don't deserve this.
You don't.
It felt like that mob
came from nowhere,
but something tells me
that's not true.
The people weren't
this angry before.
It's like someone riled them up.
[SETH gasps]
[MAN] We were just following
Captain Konrad's orders!
Captain Konrad.
He's behind this!
[huffs]
I'll make him regret it.
[MAN]
There they are!
-The sorcerers!
-[SETH gasps]
[SETH]
They already found us?
That was way too fast.
Get ready Melie!
We need to fly outta here.
[TAJ screams]
[SETH]
Did you hear me, or--
[gasps]
-Run away? I don't think so.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
If these idiots really wanna
pick a fight with us,
then I'm gonna give them
the fight they want.
I'm about to blow
these thugs sky high.
Whoa!
Just hang on a sec!
Calm it down.
[MELIE]
Calm it down?!
The bastards were about to
burn this kid alive.
So, they can't complain
if I do the same to them.
[SETH] But think about what
you were saying before!
If that Konrad guy's the one
who got them to do it,
then we just need
to get rid of him!
So, they're guilt-free just
cause they had orders?
Don't be stupid, these guys
would kill us if they could.
That doesn't matter.
Our only real enemies are that
Captain Konrad guy
-and his Inquisitors!
-[TAJ gasps]
[CROWD yelling, indistinct]
[SETH]
Oh, forget it!
You had better let go of me!
-Seth!
-Shut up!
If I put you down,
you'll go ballistic
on everything in sight!
These people are
only acting like this
because they're scared of us!
They're not evil.
They're just afraid of what
they can't understand!
If we attack them now,
we'll only be confirming
their fears were justified.
That's not an option.
There's only one way
we can end this.
We find Captain Konrad.
And make him stop!
[TAJ]
Seth.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
-[gasps]
[explosion]
This is your one warning,
you infected scum.
My men have this
district completely surrounded.
You will surrender quietly.
And if you refuse,
the Inquisition will bring
its full might to bear.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Konrad denounces
Seth and his friends
as criminals,
and launches
a fearsome attack
on Rumble Town's
immigrant district.
Cruelty rains down on the many
who've nowhere left to run,
whilst Konrad advances
with overwhelming might.
Then, the mysterious girl who's
been lurking in the shadows,
enters the fray.
Next time on Radiant.
"The Bell Tolls
the Sound of Destruction."