[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them,
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
Seth is a sorcerer in training.
He has lofty goals, but there’s
no telling if he’ll reach them.
[SETH snoring]
[SETH]
I had a dream.
It started like a nightmare...
from my childhood with Alma.
People’s fear of the Nemesis
made them scared of me.
Which was strange, because only
a sorcerer like me
could’ve protected
them from one.
Except I was just a kid.
All but powerless.
Alma was the strong one.
She was the protector.
I’ve met a lot of sorcerers
since then,
but she’s the greatest by far.
Someday, I’ll be just like her,
and then I’ll show the world
that sorcerers are amazing!
[SETH groans]
Huh?
[SETH] I can’t believe I’ve been
here a whole month.
[NARRATOR]
“Broom of Memories.”
[CROWD cheering]
[SETH laughs]
I didn’t know we were havin’
a big party today.
They put on a festival here
once every few months or so,
whenever Master Lord Majesty
feels like throwing one, really.
So he can put on a massive
festival like this
on just a whim?
Huh...
that’s actually impressive.
There’ll be a ton of stalls
and what not to check out, too.
It should be a lot of fun.
Will there be a bunch
of cool magic gizmos?
Yeah!
Why don’t we take a look
at everything later today?
For sure!
I suppose even that weirdo cat
can do something cool
every once in a while, huh?
[DOC]
What are you talkin’ about?
[BOTH]
Huh? Doc!
This wasn’t on a whim.
Majesty throws these festivals
to raise cash.
Tourists flock in from around
the world,
and empty their pockets.
[SETH]
Oh, I get’cha.
Yeah, that does sound
more his style.
It also allows him to strengthen
our relationships
with other countries.
Which means that if
the Inquisition
wants to come after Artemis,
they’ll have to consider the
diplomatic repercussions first.
It’s a delicate balance
that keeps the city
of Artemis afloat.
[SETH]
Hmm?
-What does that mean?
-Um...
[DOC] If ya don’t get it,
don’t worry about it.
Cool!
One more thing.
If you’re plannin’ to buy
somethin’ at those stalls,
why not try your luck
in the broom race
and win some prize money first?
Hold on, there’s a broom race?
You wanna check it out with me?
[MAJESTY]
Oooh!
Beloved students
of my a-cat-emy!
The moment has arrived.
The daring among you
will soon "purrticipate"
in our festival’s broom race!
I shall now tell you
the prize "fur" winning.
It's...
ten million smackaroos!
[CROWD chanting]
Majesty! Majesty! Majesty!
Huh? You gotta pay to enter?
[EMPLOYEE] The race itself does
cost money to put on.
So, yeah.
[SETH]
Man...
I’ve been getting really good
at flying lately, too.
I wanted everyone to see
my awesome broom technique.
It’s too bad we don’t
have any money.
Maybe next time.
[SETH]
Guess so.
[NICK]
You’re better off this way.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NICK chuckles]
The mere thought of racing
against a classless punk
like yourself makes me laugh.
-Who’re you?
-Uh... same question here.
What?! Don’t you pretend
not to know me.
I mean, you’re both residents
of Artemis, are you not?
-Well...
-Yeah,
last time I checked at least.
Well, If you don’t know,
then I’m sure my associates
would be happy
to alleviate your ignorance.
Go.
This is the one and only Nick:
the uncontested champion of the
last two festival broom races!
Not only that,
he’s also the son
of one of the town’s
most renowned citizens,
and he’s been hailed
as the number one
up-and-coming sorcerer
in Artemis!
[BOTH] You’re looking
at a legend in the making!
Please, don’t flatter me so,
I find it embarrassing.
[HENCHMAN A] Oh, that’s just
because you’re so humble!
[HENCHMAN B] You’re amazing, and
the world should know it!
What’s the deal with these guys?
Oh, I think I’ve heard of you
after all.
You’re the Nick who likes to let
everyone know
how rich he is, right?
The one who has nothing else
going for him,
but still wins because
he has no...“scruples”?
No, I think you must have me
confused with a different Nick.
[exhales]
But not to worry!
I’m quite forgiving
when it comes to the ladies.
[HENCHMAN A]
You’re so magnanimous, Nick!
[HENCHMAN B] That’s why
all the ladies love you!
Wait, do you pay those guys
to say that stuff?
Of course I don’t!
[clears throat]
I seem to recall that you’re one
of the city’s newest arrivals.
Your name was Seth?
Oh...yeah.
And you’re associated
with a well-known sorcerer.
Somewhat well known.
I believe that her name
was Alma?
Uh...
As a matter of fact, I’ve been
told you were her apprentice.
Are you saying you
know her, too?
No, but I do know of her.
[NICK]
They say she’s quite capable,
but she refused to work
with Artemis
in order to keep her
lone-wolf image intact.
I’ve only heard rumors,
so personally, I have my doubts
about how talented
she really is.
I can’t think of any good reason
for a sorcerer
to refuse to join our city.
Although, I suppose it might be
that she’s just a cheapskate.
[SETH huffs]
But what I think’s
even more likely,
is she’s afraid someone’ll
see her in action,
and realize how weak she is!
[laughs]
[HENCHMAN A] It’s so like you
to say that, Nick!
[HENCHMAN B] You’re amazing,
and the world should know it!
[SETH] Hey,
don’t you dare bad-mouth Alma.
-Say what?
-[HENCHMEN] Huh?
[SETH] She might look like
a grumpy old hag,
and she’s definitely twice
as mean as she looks.
But she’s also a great sorcerer!
So don’t talk crap about her.
Especially when
you’ve never met her!
Wow.
It looks like I struck a nerve.
Well if she’s as powerful
a sorcerer as you claim,
why not prove it yourself
as her apprentice?
You could do it by taking me on
in this broom race.
Manage to defeat me,
and I’ll take it all back.
You’ve got yourself
a match, jerk!
But the money...
[chuckles]
Well,
I’ll leave you to practice
begging for mercy.
[NICK laughs]
That was a super cool exit line!
[HENCHMAN B] Yeah, your laugh’s
the best, Nick!
Man, that guy really knows
how to make me angry!
What the heck gives him
the right to make fun of Alma?!
If you don’t mind me saying so,
it’s sweet how much faith
you have in your old master.
You think?
So, what was she like
as a person?
Oh... I guess I never told ya
too much about her.
Hmph.
Alma was...
well...
[SETH]
This is stupid!
What’s the point of cleaning
outside the house?
I should hear a lot less whining
and a lot more scrubbing.
I just punched a rock!
You punched a boulder,
which was large enough to wreck
an entire cattle ranch.
And let’s not forget
that it caused the cattle
to stampede through the village,
turning every person
in it against us.
And this is after you started
the plantation fire
that dried out a whole lake!
I’m banning you
from setting so much
as a foot on that island
for a while.
[SETH]
Aw, for how long?!
Until I’m convinced
that you won’t be a menace!
Mess up badly enough,
and they’ll send someone
from the royal capital
to arrest and execute you.
[SETH grunting]
[ALMA] Also, if you think
I didn’t notice
that you’ve been stealing
my grimoires, you’re wrong.
No more of that either.
But, I only borrowed them
because I wanna become
a respectable sorcerer
as soon as I possibly can--!
-[ALMA] Quiet!
-[SETH whimpers]
[ALMA] You haven’t even become
a respectable person yet,
all right?!
[SETH groans]
Well, if you’d stop treating me
like a little kid.
[SETH]
Hmm...
Mmm? Mm?
Hmm.
All right!
The coast is clear.
[SETH chuckles]
Just where do you think
you’re going?
Uh-- I--
I just thought
I’d take a stroll!
I already know
what this is about,
so don’t bother
trying to hide it.
[SETH groans]
You’re determined to go?
Yeah.
There’s no point
in trying to stop me.
I have no intention
of making you stay.
Huh?
But where do you plan to start,
it’s not like
you have any leads.
Well, I don’t have leads...
-but I do have plenty of spirit!
-[ALMA groans] Ugh...
[ALMA]
You won’t leave with nothing.
Take this stuff with you.
You’ll need it.
Wait a second.
You’re not seriously
giving me your broom?
Don’t you need it?
I’d rather you took it.
What’s a sorcerer
who can’t fly, right?
You’ll never really look
the part
if you don’t even
have your own broom.
Thanks, Alma.
But, um, maybe I should--
Also, let me see your hand.
[SETH exhales]
[ALMA]
Seth...
-promise me something.
-Huh?
Swear you won’t
become a monster.
[gasps]
I won’t become a monster,
you have my word.
All I’m gonna be
is the greatest sorcerer
in the whole world!
[softly chuckles]
Is that so?
I won’t worry then.
All right.
I’ll see ya!
[SETH panting]
[SETH panting slows, stops]
[SETH crying]
[SETH crying continues]
Hey, Alma...
thank you.
[ALMA]
Take care of yourself, you hear?
[SETH crying, sniffling]
All right, then.
I’m shoving off.
So do it.
Go on, you’re burning daylight.
[SETH softly laughs]
[SETH grunts]
[MELIE]
Oh, cool!
So that broom was Alma’s
before she gave it to you.
Yeah, she’s awesome.
She’s also super scary
when she’s mad.
Seriously, I’d take on a Nemesis
over her any day of the week!
[giggles]
Okay, but even if she’s scary.
I can tell she means
a lot to you.
Right, which is why
I can’t lose.
I gotta do her proud.
[MAJESTY]
Ladies and gentlemen!
-Are we "feline" good yet?
-[CROWD cheering]
The moment you’ve been
fur-vently waiting for.
The climax of our Festival.
The Artemis Broom Race
will begin meow-mentarily!
That's it?
I guess my awesome broomstick
must’ve scared everyone else
outta the race...huh?
Whoa! What is that thing?
What do you think?
You ever seen
a racing broom before?
[SETH gasping for air]
[NICK] I’m surprised you didn’t
lose your nerve and back out,
bumpkin.
[SETH]
Hey! Was it “Neck?”
It’s Nick,
and don’t you forget it!
His broom is the latest model,
that’s been heavily customized.
The design had to be widened
to accommodate two
additional sub-boosters,
but it’s still super aerodynamic
thanks to its streamlined shape.
Everything about it
screams that he has
a need for speed
and money to burn!
That’s one rich-boy broom!
I can’t say I understood
much of that.
But you’re pretty much
just saying
that his broom
cost lots of money, yeah?
[NICK laughs]
If you’re hoping to get one for
yourself, you can’t afford it.
Why would I want a goofy
lookin’ broom like that?
[NICK laughing]
It’s so like you
to say that, Nick!
You’re on a roll
today, it’s amazing!
That boy.
His name was Seth, was it?
I hear the odds on him
are one in ten thousand.
Definitely a dark horse,
but looks like
Nick’s got him marked.
[SETH growling]
-[MELIE] Seth!
-Huh--
Huh? Melie?
Why are you here?
I figured I’d join
the race, too!
-Huh?
-Lookit,
I don’t care about winning.
I just wanna help you show
that cocky rich boy
how great Alma is!
[SETH]
Oh, thanks!
[DOC crying]
Those two...
how did I let them talk me into
payin’ their entry fee for them?
I was broke enough before!
Listen up, ya little imp!
Your odds are one
in 10,000,
so I put all my money on ya!
It’s rags or riches for me now!
So you win, even if it kills ya!
[MAJESTY]
Your brooms should be purring
behind the starting line,
or else they’ll
magically combust.
[SETH]
One to 10,000 odds, my butt.
I’ve been training crazy hard
since I first got here.
Oh yeah.
You’re impressed.
-Ah!
-Stupid fool!
All you did was gather Fantasia
in your fist and punch with it!
That doesn’t even qualify
as a spell!
Wait, really?!
[SETH]
Meteor Drops!
Just drop already,
ya dumb meteors!
-[DOC groans]
-[SETH] Meteor Drops!
[SETH, with an accent]
Meteor Drops!
Ya can’t brute force your way
through everything, kid.
[SETH yells]
[gasping]
This time I’ve got it.
Meteor Drops!
[explosion]
[DOC screams]
[DOC]
I’ll be back.
-You killed Doc!
-I killed Doc!
[SETH grunting]
[explosions]
Melie! This isn’t funny!
So stop messing around!
I’m dead serious, Seth!
I suggest you start
fighting back!
No way am I gonna do that.
I don’t wanna hurt you!
[MELIE] You say that like
you think it’d be easy!
Oh crap, oh crap, oh crap!
[explosion]
[SETH screaming]
[cracking]
[SETH screams]
-[cracking]
-[SETH groaning]
It’s almost like she’s actually
tryin’ to kill me.
-[MELIE] Pathetic.
-[SETH gasps]
How’s a brat with no backbone
like you expect
to become a warrior?
You make me sick.
This isn’t the place
for a sparring match, Melie!
Whatever, stop with the whining.
Here comes round two!
Oh no!
Wait!
Blow away!
[SETH]
Uhh--
Melie, no! Ti--
[MELIE]
Huh--
She’s too far away!
No choice then.
Come on, Fantasia.
I need you to work with me,
this time!
Meteor Drops!
[SETH]
Melie!
I did it! I really did it!
You saw, didn’t you?
Well, of course you did--
so cool!
I just cast Meteor Drops
for the first time!
[SETH] If I’m really
gonna be the first sorcerer
to find Radiant,
then winning this race
should be a piece of cake.
[MAJESTY]
Go!
[fireworks]
[CROWD cheering]
[gasps]
It looks like we’ve got some
catching up to do, Melie!
Let’s make a break
for the lead!
-Sounds good!
-[SETH screaming]
[RACE PARTICIPANTS scream, gasp]
[FEMALE PARTICIPANT gasps]
That boy really is
something special.
[MALE PARTICIPANT] I’m surprised
to see that kind of speed
from such an old broom.
[CROWD cheering continues]
[DOC]
Wow...
I figured he would have gotten
the hang of flyin’
by now, but...
how’s he this fast
on that old broom?
[YAGA]
It might not look fancy,
but that’s a superior broom
Seth has.
Whoa! You could scare someone!
And thanks to my
constant training,
the boy’s gained a fairly
significant amount of power
in the past few weeks.
None of the rookie sorcerers in
this race are any match for him.
[DOC] There’s actually a chance
I might get rich!
[SETH]
I’m comin’ for ya!
[SETH laughs]
[NICK]
Huh?
Don’t get ahead of yourself,
you little punk.
I still have the lead!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL PARTICIPANTS]
What the heck is that thing?!
-[CROWD chanting] Majesty!
-Oh no!
The Majesty Robot!
The cat’s tastes
are as tacky as ever, I see.
One in 10,000 odds
against you,
yet you’re "pawsturing"
for victory somehow!
There’s a lot of money
riding on this race, though,
and I just can’t
"purrmit" an upset!
Soo...yeah.
Go Majestic Wing!
[SETH]
What? No fair!
[PARTICIPANTS screaming]
Best of luck clawing
your way out of debt once
I’ve "tabbied" up
your new balance!
[laughs]
Now first place is all mine!
That was close, he nearly
knocked me out of the sky!
[MAJESTY] If you think I’m done,
you’re "kitten" yourself!
Majestic Punch!
[screaming]
If you’re okay,
-then we can still win this!
-I'm good!
[MAJESTY]
Majestic Missiles!
Ugh! It feels like there’s
no end to these things.
-[HENCHMEN gasp]
-You two be careful!
Those broomsticks
were expensive!
Don’t let them get damaged!
[BOTH HENCHMEN]
Whatever you say, Nick.
Ahh! Thanks, Melie!
I’m happy to help,
but that shield’s
not gonna last for long.
I’ve got this!
[chuckling]
I like playing cat and mouse.
-[SETH yelling]
-Huh?
You can’t shoot me down
if I’m right above you!
No, you’re cat-egorically wrong.
[MAJESTY]
Majestic Fire!
[screams]
Seth, no!
No!
Seth’s dead and I’m broke again!
-Oh, he’s fine, relax.
-Huh?!
That blast was nothing,
not compared to the spells
I’ve been throwing at him!
[DOC yelling]
-How did you--?
-Yay, yay, yay!
Now, it’s my turn!
Titan Punch!
[explosion]
-[emergency alarms]
-No!
E-meow-gency escape!
As long as we’re "cat" it,
we had better self-destruct!
-[MELIE screams]
-[SETH grunts]
Thanks for the save.
I know that you’d do
the same for me.
Yeah, but it’s not over.
Leave me behind so you
can win the race.
You can still catch up
with Nick and his friends.
There’s no way
I’m leaving you behind!
We’ll finish this together.
Thank you.
Well, this race
is nearing its end,
and it looks like
Nick’s gonna win
for the third year
in a row, easy!
I take everything back, the kid
with one in 10,000 odds
is comin’ in hot!
Do whatever it takes, Seth!
Your buddy Doc needs
his coffee money back!
Dammit... how’s that old
dust broom even flying?
It’s not an old dust broom!
It used to belong
to a Nemesis Hunter,
the strongest one in the world!
It’s an antique!
And my broom’s the latest model!
Let me show you just
how big the difference is!
-You two ready?
-[HENCHMEN] Yeah! Lead the way!
Hang on tight,
we’re gonna speed up!
[MELIE]
Right!
[MC]
Incredible!
They’re almost neck and neck!
The boy with one in 10,000
odds is gaining on Nick fast!
Ugh!
I just have to push harder!
I can’t let this punk win!
-[HENCHMEN] Ahh!
-[SETH gasps]
[MC]
Nick wins!
[CROWD cheering]
And let that be a lesson
to you, kid.
Uh--
[MC]
What’s this?!
The one in 10,000 kid
is nowhere to be seen!
[NICK]
Uh...
[SETH grunts]
[MC]
Look at that!
He quit the race to save
his fallen competitors!
[gasps]
Uh, thanks a bunch.
Thought we were s’posed
to be your rivals.
Don’t worry about that.
Alma wouldn’t have let you
fall either.
[MC] He gave up the race
to rescue his opponents!
Talk about a good sport!
[NICK]
How could you give up the win
just to help your opponent?
[MAJESTY]
Nick is our Champion once again!
Thank you both
for a "supurrb" match!
And special thanks to all
of our spectators "fur"
making this event "pawsible" by
litter-ing us with your money!
[CROWD cheering]
[pounds fist on table]
[DOC]
What?!
No prize money if you don’t
cross the finish line?!
[MELIE sighs]
And after we put in all that
effort, it’s just too bad.
Yeah...right...
I really wanted to beat Neck.
We were close though!
Don’t take this so lightly!
Those exorbitant entry fees
were just added onto our debt!
How can I get this
through your thick skulls?!
I get it, but with all the debt
we have, what’s a little more?
You've got to learn
the value of money!
[giggles]
At any rate,
I was thinking...
we should probably
start looking for work.
[DOC]
Are you listening to me?!
[giggling]
I’m down!
[GRIMM]
Rumble Town...
it’s been quite a few years
since Grimm has worked
in a city this large.
With humans crammed into
every fetid corner,
there may well be
a few casualties.
Secrecy will be of
the essence here.
Luckily...
that’s how Grimm works best.
[NARRATOR]
Doc receives a job request
involving an unknown Nemesis.
When Seth and Melie find out,
they harass Doc
until he agrees to take the job,
and bring them along to...
Rumble Town.
Here, the Inquisition’s presence
has awakened discrimination
against both sorcerers
and immigrants.
Leading to the rise of some
irrational political policies.
Next time on Radiant.
“The City That Roars
Like Thunder.”