[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
If you wanna call yourself
a wall, that's fine.
'Cause I'm gonna smash
right through it either way!
Skull...
Burst!
-[KONRAD] Huh--
-[explosion]
[CITIZENS scream]
[moans]
-[SETH grunts]
-[chain thuds]
[SETH groans, sighs]
[NARRATOR] "Fly High and Pierce
Through the Storm"
[MAN A]
Hey, look at the wall!
That kid busted
right through it!
Yeah! We can
all get away now!
We're gonna make it!
-[TAJ sighs]
-[MAN B] We're free!
It's Taj! He's okay!
Hey there, sis.
Come on, Dad!
Lay off, that hurts!
Oh, Tajy, I'm so glad
you're safe and sound.
[sighs]
[DRAGUNOV] There's a warrant out
for your arrest.
Uh-- [lightly gasps]
[SETH]
Wait. You're the guy from-
I suggest that you come quietly.
[SETH] Is this really the time
for that crap?
[DRAGUNOV] I have a job,
and I aim to do it--
-[rumbling crash]
-[SETH] Ah!
[MAN A]
The aerial stabilizers!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[MAN B]
This whole town is done for!
[DRAGUNOV]
Hold it.
Ugh! What is your problem?
Thousands of people's lives
are in danger right now.
So if you're a soldier,
then doing your job
should mean protecting them!
Who is it
that you're fighting for?
[annoyed exhale]
I fight to protect others, true.
But... you've yet to convince me
you do the same.
This, nest of the Nemesis.
Do you truly believe it exists?
Radiant is out there.
I'll find it.
And smash the whole
damn place into pieces!
There's more prejudice
in this world than I can stand.
So I'm fighting to change it!
That's a bold goal to be sure.
All right.
But before you go
and change the world,
why don't you do something
about that Nemesis charmer?
I was planning to
before you asked me.
Hmph.
As soon as this mess
has been dealt with,
I'm throwing you
in a black silver cage.
[SETH]
Feel free to try.
"It's my duty to report
Captain Marbourg's misconduct.
"He aided and abetted a Domitor.
"I found evidence
to prove it.
"The situation here
is most dire.
-Signed, Captain Dart Dragunov."
-[ding]
I don't believe it for a second.
Konrad's a straight-shooter.
The man's a psychopath,
a compulsive liar
and a segregationist
to the core.
Dragunov had me work
with him once.
[TEPPES] Yeah, I betcha Dart's
the one who's at fault here.
The man's a useless coward,
if you ask me.
-Except we didn't ask you.
-[TEPPES] Huh?!
Oh my.
I'm sure it was
a female sorcerer behind this.
She led him from the light
and into sin.
I've read all about this
in the holy scripture.
It warns of witches using spells
to seduce virile men.
Santori? Would you care
to share your opinion?
[SANTORI snoring]
Wake up!
Santori!
We're discussing
something serious!
[SANTORI gasps]
[SANTORI] Yes. And I have
serious thoughts about it.
Thoughts which I will now share.
Many years ago,
I made a strenuous journey
across the Green Desert.
I was searching for the tomb
of Nefertuktu, you see.
Go back to sleep, old man.
[SANTORI snoring]
[TORQUE]
In his message,
Captain Dragunov claims
to have evidence.
[TEPPES]
What of it, Sir?
Soon enough, we can judge
the truth of his claims
for ourselves.
That said,
this matter has nothing to do
with our true objective.
[TORQUE]
Have you sensed anything?
Nah, nothin' so far.
It's surprising.
I think I'll go scout
things out, if ya don't mind.
Stop acting like
you need my permission.
That an order?
Try and catch up
before the island sinks.
[chuckles]
[whoosh]
[sighs]
[TORQUE] Our top priority
is that horned sorcerer.
And what about
the other sorcerers there?
We will send them to join
their comrades in the red room.
[SETH panting]
[panting continues]
-[SETH gasps]
-[rumbling crashes]
[GRIMM] Grimm has yet to ask you
the most important question.
[HAMELINE playing flute]
[GRIMM gasps]
[GRIMM]
Procella!
[gasp]
How dare you throw spells
at my brothers?
-[HAMELINE grunts]
-[metal clangs]
[GRIMM]
Caeca.
Nube!
[HAMELINE grunts]
[snap]
[explosion]
He conjured a smokescreen.
[HAMELINE gasps]
[GRIMM]
Speak.
You're skilled in the ways
of the Domitor.
Who was it that taught
you their arts?
Most would have to be mentored
for many years
to reach your level of mastery.
Was your teacher Behemoth?
Or Sirin?
[HAMELINE whimpering]
[GRIMM]
No change in your pulse.
Disappointing that you've
no connection to them.
In that case, Grimm will dispose
of the Nemeses and leave.
[HAMELINE]
Like hell you will!
[GRIMM]
A hidden blade.
[shrieks]
Blood!
[HAMELINE]
That was close.
[breathing shakily]
[distant explosion]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping,
alarmed]
-[MELIE gasps]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
[MELIE]
I failed, yet again.
[crying]
I was too broken...
to help.
[sniffles]
It's exactly like before.
♪
[MELIE crying]
[explosions]
[blade slices]
Ahh!
[breathing heavily]
-[MELIE grunts]
-It's me!
You found me.
[SETH] Phew, I'm glad
I caught your hand.
I do not wanna
get blown away right now.
[whimpering]
I'm sorry, Seth.
-[MELIE crying]
-[SETH] Oh--
You're good.
What happened, Melie?
[MELIE]
It's Doc, Seth. He was--
-He's gone.
-[SETH] Huh?
What do you mean?
I've got Doc right here
in this pouch.
[MELIE]
Huh?
See?
He turned into a baby.
[BOTH scream]
Yeah, I sensed
some weird Fantasia earlier,
so I decided
to follow the trail.
[panting]
[SETH] And, well,
before I'd gone too far,
I found Doc lyin' on the ground.
[SETH screams]
Hey Doc, ya takin' a nap?
Come on, Doc, snap out of it
and say something back!
Wait a second,
why is he so still?
-Holy crap! Something's moving!
-Ah, that's better!
I thought I was gonna
suffocate down there!
That was almost
lights out for me.
Hey, Seth,
good to see ya.
So did one of those
Inquisitor types
decide to cover me in a blanket
of rubble, or somethin?
Sheesh. Hm?
Uhh...
Oh, no, someone killed me!
[SETH] So, yeah, that's how
it all happened.
[DOC] It looks like
my curse is molting.
Who woulda guessed it?
[SETH] Tough break,
that's a really gross one.
What's wrong with you?!
[MELIE]
I'm so glad you're safe!
-[DOC grunting, struggling]
-That really is you, right?
I'm so sorry for leaving you.
I honestly thought
you were dead!
Look! If you keep squeezin' me
like this, I will die!
[MELIE]
Not only do I get you back,
you're a cute lil baby now!
[DOC]
Stop swingin' me around!
My baby bones can't take it!
I'm really gonna snap! Really!
Ahh--
hey look, there's a light.
What's that about?
My mark spell.
It should only go off like that
if Grimm is somewhere nearby.
[gasps]
[GRIMM] An impressive use
of marking magic.
-[MELIE and SETH gasp]
-[GRIMM] You may be wary,
but Grimm is not your foe.
Grimm has come to warn you all.
Warn us of what?
[GRIMM] The Domitor and her
Nemeses are powerful.
Fighting them is beyond
your capabilities.
[SETH gasps]
[GRIMM] You should take
advantage of this chaos,
and flee the island.
You think you can
beat her by yourself?
[GRIMM]
Not without killing her.
-[MELIE gasps]
-Not a chance, I won't let you!
[GRIMM] Do you have
an alternative in mind?
I'll think of something.
I'm not just gonna watch,
that's for sure!
Um. I might have an idea.
-Wanna hear it?
-Huh?
If you distract them,
then I can drain the strength
of the Source Nemesis.
And by doing that,
it'll free you two up
to deal with the Domitor.
[GRIMM] You truly have
the ability to drain
a Nemesis of its strength?
Using what?
An item.
The only catch is that
I have to get close.
[GRIMM] Grimm still has work
to do in this world.
Throwing this life away
is not an option.
However, if you're
confident in your plan,
then Grimm will assist you.
-[SETH] Nice!
-[MELIE] Oh, cool!
Hey! Hold on for a minute!
You don't plan
to take me, do ya?
That's not safe, I'm a baby!
I'm a little bit worried
about Mister Boobrie, too.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[GRIMM]
Not a problem.
Grimm has a place where the...
less formidable members
of your party
can be kept safe
from any danger.
Um... is it off
of this island?
'Cause that's where
I'd like to be.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[rumbling, crashing destruction]
They gave no mercy.
So treat them in kind. [gasps]
Ah... so you've thrown in your
lot with those that despise you.
Very well.
If you protect this island,
then I'll destroy you with it.
[SETH and MELIE gasp]
[GRIMM]
Seems the Domitor was keeping
more Echo Nemeses concealed.
Are they heading for us,
or for the town?
Doesn't matter.
Cause I'm gonna
take 'em all out!
[MELIE]
Seth, wait!
Here goes!
Skull Burst!
[chuckles]
-[GRIMM, impressed] Hm.
-That's amazing.
[gasps]
[GRIMM]
So many.
He's in trouble.
[SETH grunting]
Look out!
[SETH grunting continues]
[moaning]
[gasps]
[groans]
What just happened?
Man, that hurts.
Am I inside the tower?
I need to get back.
-[PIODON] I'm surprised at you.
-[SETH] Hm?
You'd be dead if I hadn't
enhanced your guard.
[SETH]
Who are you?
[gasps]
Let's just say I'm a friend.
Seth no!
[GRIMM]
Don't worry. He's alive.
How such a miracle
occurred is unclear.
But Grimm can still detect
Seth's heartbeat
through the feather bandage
Grimm wrapped around his arm.
'Kay.
We can't allow any more of those
Echoes to attack the town.
The plan can still work,
let's keep fighting.
[GRIMM]
Understood.
[sharp inhale]
[GRIMM]
Caeca... Nube!
[HAMELINE grunts]
That trick won't work
a second time!
[HAMELINE gasps]
Wait, where did the girl go?
[gasps]
[yelling]
[HAMELINE grunts]
Furtum Potentiam!
[gasping]
[HAMELINE grunting, struggling]
These are my brothers.
I won't let you hurt them
any more than you have!
[MELIE gasps in pain]
[HAMELINE grunting, yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[HAMELINE screams]
[playing flute]
[MELIE screams]
[whimpering]
The degenerates of this town
all deserve to die.
If you insist
on protecting them,
then you will share
in their fate.
[heavy breathing]
They did wrong.
But I'm asking you
to show them mercy.
How dare you ask for anything?
You slew my brothers.
The only beings I care
about in this world!
I didn't realize those
Echoes were your friends.
I was only trying to stop them
from attacking the city.
I'm so sorry.
Stop talking as though
you understand my pain!
But I... I feel like...
I do understand
some parts of it.
At least I know
what it's like to be lonely.
To miss the warmth of a friend.
But, look,
you're only spreading
more of that misery!
Don't talk to me
about misery!
The people of this city
took everything I had!
The kids they killed,
they were my family!
And the only man
that showed us kindness
was murdered
by the bastard they obey!
And now it's their turn.
I'm gonna take everything
from them too!
[MELIE gasps]
I had to try.
Are you planning to fight me
together this time?
Or, let me guess,
you're picking her up
so you can flee on your broom.
[GRIMM]
There's no cause to flee.
This young sorceress
did her part,
and now Grimm will do his.
[scoffs]
No idea what that means.
But my brother's wounds
have healed.
And there's no one
in this world
who can stand against
our strength combined!
[whimpering gasp]
What happened to my Fantasia?
You won't be able to cast
any more spells at us.
I have bound you
to the Plundering Lamp.
Any Fantasia you attempt
to gather for yourself
will be diverted
and used as fuel for its flame!
I see it now.
So that's what she was doing.
You can no longer make use
of any kind of magic.
Which means you can
no longer command
those Nemeses to help you!
[GRIMM] Your Nemeses
are feral beasts now.
They're nothing to be feared.
They're far more than that,
don't underestimate our bond!
We'll destroy you both.
Exactly like we did to your
little friend with the horns!
[GRIMM]
I take it you mean Seth.
He is unharmed.
The boy was adamant
that Grimm should not kill you.
The hell are you getting at?
[GRIMM]
Nothing really.
Grimm is no longer capable
of taking human life.
[BOTH gasp]
[GRIMM]
You had best keep your distance.
Kannibal is a fine weapon,
but it requires a great
deal of space to wield.
[BOTH gasp]
[GRIMM]
Now then... it begins.
[gasping, grunting]
[HAMELINE gasps]
[GRIMM] You needn't fear,
Grimm won't slay you.
Only the Nemeses
in your thrall.
[SETH]
Really though.
You gonna tell me who you are?
[PIODON] For the time being, you
may as well just call me Piodon.
-[SETH] And what do you want?
-[PIODON] Not a whole lot.
Let's just say
I'm a spectator
who enjoys observing
this world's mechanisms.
-[SETH] Huh?
-[PIODON] Well, it's your turn.
-What should I call you?
-Uh... I'm Seth.
It's nice to meet you.
So, tell me, Seth.
What made you decide
to keep that sealed away?
Sealed away?
Are you talking
about my bandage?
[PIODON] You can't fight at full
strength while it's on, right?
I'm not sure what you mean.
This bandage
is covering up a scar
I got from being attacked
by a Nemesis when I was a kid.
It's what keeps my curse
from spreading any further.
Hmm?
[SETH]
Alma-- [sighs]
The sorcerer
who raised me told me that.
It's not anything weird
like a seal, okay?
[PIODON]
Mm...
I get it.
Guess your understanding
of Fantasia
leaves a lot to be desired,
but that's hardly your fault.
Listen, Seth.
The way you are at the moment,
you're only able to access
a small fragment
of your real potential.
[SETH]
Hmm?
[PIODON]
I'd love to do something
about that pesky seal for you,
but I doubt
you'd even let me try.
Hey, you do wanna be powerful,
don't you, Seth?
[SETH]
Huh?
What kinda question is that?
[PIODON] I can understand
why you'd be cautious.
You don't know if
I'm a friend or foe yet.
Well, Seth,
why don't you tell me?
Which side would ya say
that you're on?
[SETH]
Huh?
[PIODON] Who is it
that you're fighting for?
Fancy yourself a defender
of the defenseless?
Sounds nice...
but those are the same people
that treat
the infected like dirt.
Even kill 'em sometimes.
So, maybe... you'd rather fight
for the infected?
If so...
Do you plan to act
like that Domitor
and massacre those
who would persecute you?
You know,
you could always fight
for the Inquisition.
But if you did,
there's little doubt
that you would have to work
with people like Konrad
at some point.
[SETH exhales]
[PIODON] I'll ask once again:
where do you stand?
Why and for whom,
do you fight?
-I'm fighting for--
-[rumbling crash]
[gasps]
They need my help.
[SETH grunts]
Where ya goin'?
I'm not done talkin' to ya.
[SETH yelling out]
I owe you one!
I didn't really follow much
of what you were saying,
but thanks for the save!
I'll catch ya later!
[PIODON] Huh. The kid's
certainly full of energy.
Ah, well, I'll be seeing him
again soon enough.
You better not die
on me, okay, Seth?
You don't even know
that we're family yet.
We can't end it like that.
[GRIMM] Without their Domitor,
these Echoes have no direction.
Hunting them
will be a simple feat.
Hm?
[HAMELINE] I don't call them
my brothers for no reason.
You people have no idea
how powerful our bond is!
[GRIMM]
She saved the Nemeses
by recalling them
into that scroll.
[MELIE]
Ah!
[GRIMM] Grimm's control of
Kannibal is at its limit.
I can only bind
the Plundering Lamp
to one enemy at a time.
She's using
the Nemeses' Fantasia now.
So the Lamp doesn't have
any way of absorbing it!
[GRIMM] Grimm failed
to account for this.
Now, I'll blow everything away,
and there's nothing
you can do to stop me!
Please don't do this, Hameline!
These people wronged you,
but they don't deserve to die!
If you don't like
what we're doing,
then you should come
and make us stop.
That's assuming you can get
close enough to try.
[ground cracking open]
[SETH grunts]
-Ah!
-[MELIE gasps]
-[GRIMM chuckles]
-Ah, there we go.
I'm finally here.
[NARRATOR] As the battle
reaches its final stage,
Hameline brings all of her rage
to bear against Seth.
But it isn't her attack
that causes Seth to waver.
It's her tragic past, and how
it resonates with his own.
"Swear you won't
become a monster."
Will Seth's voice be able
to reach Hameline's heart?
Next time on Radiant,
"To Stop the Sound
of the Wind."