[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
-[bell ringing]
-[wind rushing]
-[crash]
-[MAN] The bell!
-[wind rushing, continues]
-[panicked chatter, indistinct]
[KONRAD]
No...
impossible!
That's the center of town.
District 6!
It... hit the armory,
and the iron foundry, too.
Even the Inquisition
Headquarters!
And the castle I constructed
from the ground up!
[SETH gasps]
[KONRAD]
I don't understand.
How did this happen?!
-[HAMELINE laughing]
-[SETH] Huh?
[HAMELINE laughing, continues]
Witch! You played me for a fool.
Why?!
[HAMELINE chuckles]
I'd like to share a little story
with these fine people.
A sad, sad story of the past.
[NARRATOR] "With Fists
Like Shooting Stars"
[HAMELINE]
A little over 15 years ago,
the Inquisition took custody
of a group of infected children.
The plan was to train them
as soldiers against The Nemesis.
Hans, Poucet, Gretta,
and Hameline.
These children were dubbed
the "Nemesis Defense Force."
And after receiving
a warm welcome
from the people of Rumble Town,
they were quartered in a prison,
to live alongside
heinous criminals
and illegal immigrants.
Every day they spent
in that prison was hell.
But at least they weren't alone.
The children supported
one another
and tried their best to live.
Then, one day...
[CITIZEN A] Get these
monsters out of our city!
-No sorcerers in Rumble Town!
-[CITIZENS yelling out]
[CITIZEN B]
Get rid of those tainted brats!
Better dead than infected!
[YOUNG HAMELINE crying]
I'm scared.
[POUCET]
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
Why are all of those people
acting like this?
Why do they hate us so much?
Are-- are we really monsters?
-Or-- huh?
-[flute playing]
[flute playing continues]
Not all of us see you
young ones as monsters.
[MAN] Try to ignore
those people for now.
They'll get tired
and stop in time.
And if the shouting ever becomes
too much to ignore,
you can do this.
[starts playing flute again]
-[YOUNG HAMELINE gasps quietly]
-[ALL groan]
[laughing] Hey, you kinda suck
at playing that.
-[ALL laughing]
-That I do.
[HANS]
Yeah, you really do.
[laughter continues]
What's your name, mister?
I'm Major Oxumare
and I'm at your service.
And tell you what,
why don't you keep this?
[YOUNG HAMELINE]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[OXUMARE]
Music's a wonderful thing.
No matter a person's
language or culture,
a good melody
can soothe their heart.
-[YOUNG HAMELINE gasps]
-And someday,
you'll each meet someone
who wants nothing more
than to hear you play.
So you may as well start
practicing now.
Go on.
-Try it.
-[YOUNG HAMELINE] Uh...huh...
[playing flute, badly]
[YOUNG HAMELINE gasps]
[laughing]
You're almost as much
of a natural as I am!
[ALL laughing]
[HAMELINE] Oxumare's presence
changed the mood in that prison.
Brightened it, just a little.
But...
there was someone who didn't
care for that change.
[YOUNG KONRAD angrily exhales]
[YOUNG HAMELINE
practicing the flute]
[footsteps approaching]
-[ALL gasp]
-[YOUNG HAMELINE whimpering]
-[YOUNG KONRAD] Hey.
-[ALL gasp, in fear]
Someone tosses you
disgusting mongrels a bone,
and you're putty
in their hands.
I'd say you were
just like animals,
but you're more
dangerous than that.
You're monsters.
Don't give me those
pathetic looks.
You're not fooling me.
I know what you are.
Shut your wretched mouths
and go cower in the corner
of your cell right now.
-[cocks crossbow]
-Or else...
[CHILDREN whimpering]
[OXUMARE]
What's going on here?
[YOUNG KONRAD] Eh--
nothing at all, Major Oxumare.
I was only warning them
to be quiet at night.
[whimpering, continues]
[OXUMARE] Your name is Konrad,
is that correct?
What's the crossbow for?
Sir! It's for self-defense
in case of an emergency.
[OXUMARE] I've been told that
you have a problematic attitude
towards these children,
and the prison's
immigrant populace.
You need to understand that
these people are human beings.
No different from you and me.
[YOUNG KONRAD] You're saying
that I'm no better
than an immigrant,
or the infected?
[OXUMARE] That's right,
know that to fear others
for their differences
betrays a lack of strength.
You think I'm scared?
Scared and weak?
Hm? There a problem?
[YOUNG KONRAD]
No, sir.
Excuse me.
I'll resume my rounds.
[YOUNG HAMELINE whimpering]
[HAMELINE]
Later that night...
[cell door creaks]
[HAMELINE]
...the same man returned,
called himself their ally,
and opened their cell
so they could escape.
The children were too
young and naive
to guess at Konrad's
true motive.
This was no act of kindness,
but a vicious scheme.
[YOUNG KONRAD chuckles]
[HAMELINE] The children
found themselves in a hell worse
than anything
they had faced in prison.
[ALL whimpering]
[HAMELINE] Konrad had spread
word of the Nemesis
Defense Force's
escape in advance,
making them out to be a terror
unleashed upon the town,
and poisoning the people's minds
with a gleeful desire...
-...to kill.
-[shovels clanging]
-[OXUMARE gaps]
-[HAMELINE] By the time
-Oxumare could intervene...
-[OXUMARE] Stop this!
[HAMELINE]
it was already far too late.
I was put back
into our cell, alone.
The Major reached
through the bars...
and gently held me,
so we could mourn
my friends' deaths together.
But to Konrad,
even that quiet act of sympathy
was despicable.
He was already beginning to form
his next devious plan.
Sometime after the breakout,
on an otherwise normal day,
the thunderous roar
of a sudden end...
[crash]
...came crashing down
from the sky.
[CITIZEN A]
No! It’s a Nemesis!
-[YOUNG HAMELINE gasps]
-[CITIZENS screaming]
-[CITIZEN B] Help me!
-[CITIZEN C] Run for your lives!
[CITIZEN D]
Make for the command center!
[YOUNG HAMELINE] Rumble Town
suddenly found itself
facing an insurmountable threat.
The Nemesis had come.
[OXUMARE]
Hm?
Excuse me, sir,
we've confirmed the appearance
of multiple Nemeses...
what should we do?
Our first duty is
to protect the people.
We must get the civilians
to safety.
Yes, sir.
Perhaps we could house
the residents
of the Northeastern District
right here?
[OXUMARE]
That's absurd, this is a prison!
But it's built like a fortress,
which makes it far safer
than anywhere else
in District 13.
And furthermore,
I think we should deploy
the Nemesis Defense Force.
Don't be a fool.
Only one of them is alive.
What hope would that child
have in a battle?
With respect...
"that child" has a better chance
than we do.
If you're that concerned
for her life,
then perhaps you could protect
her in battle personally, sir.
-Hmm...hm?
-[crash]
Please, Major,
we don't have time!
For the sake of your people,
we need your decision at once!
[sighs]
Very well, then.
You organize the evacuation
while I'm gone.
[YOUNG KONRAD] Yes, sir!
Thank you, sir!
[YOUNG KONRAD
chuckles evilly]
-[CITIZENS screaming]
-[booming crashes]
[OXUMARE]
I'm sorry.
But no one has the power
to stop this except you.
I know you must be scared,
but I'm asking for your help.
[SOLDIER panting]
Major!
The Echo Nemeses are closing in.
Requesting immediate orders!
[OXUMARE]
Just a moment.
Hameline...
you have nothing to fear.
I'll be protecting you myself.
Let's show the people
who you truly are.
[OXUMARE grunts]
[YOUNG HAMELINE]
Huh?
-[OXUMARE groans, gasps]
-[blade slashes]
-So sorry.
-[SOLDIER breathing shakily]
But I think you're quite overdue
for retirement, Major.
No.
[haltingly]
Konrad, you can't do this,
you craven bastard!
[gasps, screams]
[crying]
Oxumare! Oxumare!
[SOLDIER]
Konrad...
you killed the Major!
Have you lost your mind?!
[SOLDIER grunts]
[YOUNG HAMELINE sobbing]
[YOUNG KONRAD]
My apologies, old friend.
But I do this for the sake
of my town and its future.
Now then...
[laughs]
I'm sure I would enjoy
watching you die
while fighting
your fellow monsters.
But I could also just--
[OXUMARE yells]
[OXUMARE] Run for your life!
As far as you can!
[whimpering]
[OXUMARE]
What are you doing?!
Go!
[whimpering]
[YOUNG KONRAD]
The brat's escaping.
Damn you!
Just die already!
[YOUNG HAMELINE
panting, crying]
[YOUNG HAMELINE]
Poucet... Hans...
Gretta... Oxumare...
[screams]
[crying]
They're all gone.
What am I supposed to do?
[sniffles]
I don't belong anywhere now.
[OXUMARE]
Music's a wonderful thing.
No matter a person's language
or culture,
a good melody
can soothe their heart.
[YOUNG HAMELINE gasps]
And someday,
you'll each meet someone
who wants nothing more
than to hear you play.
[steadies breathing]
[playing flute beautifully]
[flute playing continues]
Huh?
[YOUNG HAMELINE lightly gasps]
No! Go away, you monsters!
Don't come any closer!
[crying]
Leave me alone!
Just leave me alone!
[panting]
Wait...
you're not attacking me.
How come?
You are Nemeses, aren't you?
[panting, gasping]
Could it be this?
[playing flute]
They really do seem to like
listening to my music.
[lightly gasps]
Wait, are you hurt?
[YOUNG HAMELINE
breathes heavily, whimpers]
[gasps]
I get it now.
You're just like me.
[crying] Nobody wants you
to be around either, do they?
[sniffles]
I bet you didn't even wanna
come to this island.
I bet you never had a choice.
[explosion]
Whoa!
Was that--?
[YOUNG HAMELINE screams]
[explosions]
[crashing, explosions]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[CITIZENS screaming
continues]
[HAMELINE]
Buildings, people,
the very ground
beneath their feet.
All was lost.
As I watched District 13
plummet...
I could feel my heart
begin to freeze over.
Are you truly the child
from all those years ago?
Bit ironic, isn't it?
I was brought to this town
in order to protect you
from The Nemesis,
but instead they ended up
protecting me from you.
Well, at any rate,
I haven't even begun to tell
the best part of this story.
What do you know?
After he'd murdered the last
human to ever care for me,
Konrad pinned the Major's death
on a non-existent cell
of immigrant terrorists.
The only way to save the town
-was by sacrificing District 13.
-[CITIZEN] What?
[HAMELINE] At least, that's what
he told his captain at the time.
Konrad is why that district
was lost.
That terrorist cell
was very much real!
If I had allowed them
to multiply any further,
it would've meant
Rumble Town's ruin!
I sullied my hands because
I had no other choice!
[HAMELINE] I guess you'd
give the same excuse
for what you're doing right now.
Oh, and when I said
I could help you kill off
this new batch of immigrants
a few months ago...
let's see...
I believe you paid my asking
price without a second thought.
[SETH gasps]
The witch is lying!
I'd never stoop so low
as to work side by side
with an infected.
My convictions are as strong
as they were 15 years ago.
The immigrants are a cancer,
killing us from within!
They must be wiped out
at any cost!
Even if people who aren't
immigrants get killed as well?
Of course!
No evil can be vanquished
without sacrifice!
If it lets me claim the victory,
I'll build a mountain of bodies
and climb to the top!
[CITIZEN A]
Huh? To hell with that!
What gives you the right
to decide who lives or dies?
[CITIZEN B] What have we done?
The man's a maniac!
And we were fools
for following him!
[CITIZEN C]
That sorcerer girl...
she went through all of this
just to expose him!
To make sure he'd face justice!
So, does this mean she plans
to save us from him?
Maybe, I mean, she did drop
the clocktower bell
on top of his castle.
[HAMELINE] So sorry if I
misled you fine people,
but I am in no way on your side.
[MAN A]
Huh?
[explosion]
[CITIZENS screaming]
Ahh!
[HAMELINE scoffs]
[HAMELINE]
See, I dropped that bell
so it might ring out
the sound of judgment.
You are all going to die.
Here and now.
[CITIZENS screaming]
[HAMELINE]
Why the surprise?
You can't be so delusional
as to think your hands
are not bloodied in this?
You're guilty, too!
[HAMELINE]
This scumbag was only able
to succeed in his
screwed-up plot
because he had your support!
[CITIZEN A]
I wasn't there 15 years ago!
[CITIZEN B] I had nothin'
to do with it, either!
You really think that?
I don't care if you weren't here
back then,
look at the people you
just attacked,
the district you set ablaze!
You are exactly like Konrad!
But... we were told--
[HAMELINE]
The people of this town
haven't changed a bit
in all this time!
Alone, you're as meek as cattle,
but put you in a group
and shout some crap
about an "enemy"?!
There's no cruelty
you won't commit!
It was the same
when we escaped prison.
No matter how we screamed,
they wouldn't stop hitting us.
It's been 15 years
and I still have
nightmares about that day.
Don't you dare drop your torches
and pitchforks
and claim innocence!
Everyone in this town
is at least an accomplice.
You are all my enemies!
You haven't learned a thing.
You all did exactly
as Konrad told you.
You never bothered
to question it.
You tried to burn a child
at the stake!
[sighs]
You lot are simply a bunch
of natural-born followers.
You need someone to make
your decisions for you.
Well, if that's how you want it.
Then I'll go ahead
and decide your fates.
[wind starts rushing]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[HAMELINE] All of you
will fall with this island.
I've waited 15 long years
for this moment to come.
I'll play one last song
as this worthless town
sinks into the clouds.
Now pray.
Tremble!
Feel hope slip away.
And then... perish!
[GRIMM] Sorry to interrupt you
at such a crucial moment.
But Grimm would have
words with you.
[HAMELINE gasps]
[explosion, wind rushing]
[KONRAD]
Go, now!
Round up whatever weapons
are left
and resume the bombardment
of District 12!
-But sir, there's--
-[KONRAD] Silence!
I have as little use
for defiant soldiers
as I do for those immigrants!
This town must be purified
at any cost.
You will do as you're
ordered or else.
[SOLDIERS in unison]
Right. Yes, sir!
[chuckles]
[SETH]
So, you were behind all of it.
[KONRAD]
Hmm?
[SETH] It was you who
started this riot,
and it was you who turned
that domitor girl
against the whole town.
It was you!
It's all because of you!
[KONRAD laughs]
[KONRAD]
Think you can make me pay?
I'm the champion of Rumble Town.
The most powerful warrior
you'll ever meet.
[SETH]
That's a joke.
You're as weak as they come!
[KONRAD]
What?
You only got this far
by lying to everyone.
That's how I know you're weak.
'Cause if you had any strength
in you,
then you wouldn't be
afraid of the truth!
You think I'm afraid?
You call me weak?
I am not afraid
of anything, boy!
You are a tainted sorcerer.
A disgusting infected!
You are even less
than an insect,
and yet, you have the nerve
to call me a weakling?!
I'd be scared, too,
if I were you.
Because you're weak!
And you always have been!
[KONRAD]
Shut the hell up!
[booming crash]
[gasps]
[KONRAD]
Impossible.
He parried my attack
with one hand!
And I don't see a single trace
of Fantasia!
Curse you!
[KONRAD grunts]
[laughs]
[SETH grunts]
[gasps]
I'm comin' for ya!
-[SETH grunts]
-[KONRAD groans]
[BOTH straining]
You damn infected are
a crime against nature,
and immigrants
are a sin against God.
They are foul vermin,
and you are a monster!
It's only right you
should be destroyed.
They are not vermin,
they're people!
And the only monster
I can see...
is you!
[groaning]
[KONRAD grunts]
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[KONRAD]
I just don't understand it.
How do his attacks have
so much force behind them?
Throwing a kick like that
with his bare foot,
it should've shattered
every bone in his leg!
-[KONRAD growls]
-[SETH grunts]
[KONRAD]
Huh?
He's concentrating
an enormous amount of Fantasia
around one part of his body
at a time.
It's the Fantasia he's using to
strike me and deflect my blows.
His body doesn't even
feel the impact!
He can manipulate Fantasia
without casting any spells!
[KONRAD growls]
-[KONRAD grunts]
-[SETH screams]
[SETH whimpers]
-[ALL crying]
-He got Seth.
Seth, no!
[laughs]
It's been my distinct pleasure
to personally send
everyone who's dared
defy me to their grave!
Now, you're about to join their
inglorious ranks, sorcerer!
[gasping]
[chain rattling]
[laughs]
You were doomed from the start.
For you face Konrad de Marbourg!
I am the champion
of Rumble Town,
the unbreakable wall
it counts on to defend it!
[laughs]
[gasps]
-[chain rattling]
-Mmm!
[KONRAD] He's absorbed
the tip of my lance.
Just like that one did
with the cannonballs!
If you wanna call yourself
a wall, that's fine.
'Cause I'm gonna smash
right through it either way!
Skull Burst!
[screaming]
[growling]
[KONRAD]
I... am a champion.
All my life, I've fought
for my ideals,
for beauty,
nobility,
strength.
-I am Rumble Town's wall.
-[cracking]
[KONRAD]
I can never be broken.
[SETH screaming]
[KONRAD screaming]
[KONRAD]
I am righteous.
I am the wall.
[booming crash]
[NARRATOR]
A man brings Seth
inside the clocktower,
where he asks Seth questions
about what he fights for,
and where his future
loyalties might lie.
Meanwhile,
Hameline and her Nemeses
move to bring about
the destruction of Rumble Town.
And even working together,
Seth, Grimm, and Melie will be
hard-pressed to stop her.
Next time on Radiant.
"Fly High and Pierce
Through the Storm."