[NARRATOR]
This world is overflowing
with a power known as Fantasia.
Those who wield this power,
can become either
heroes or villains.
Here, terrifying monsters fall
from the sky.
Is this divine retribution?
Demonic malice?
Or a symptom of
Mother Nature’s wrath?
The one thing known for
certain is that these monsters,
called the Nemesis, leave
disaster in their wake.
They are terrifying to behold
and can kill
with the slightest touch.
Those few humans who
cross their paths and survive
are forever cursed.
But along with their curses,
they receive power.
The power to stand
against the Nemesis.
Now, these tainted humans fight.
And at times, they can be
even more fearsome
than the Nemeses themselves.
They’re known as sorcerers.
This is the story of a boy,
who strives to become a great
sorcerer, and save the world.
[NARRATOR]
“The Young Sorcerer.”
Rise and shine, kitty!
I’m taking these!
So tasty!
Oh, crap!
I was supposed to meet Tommy!
[mooing]
Guess he’s running late, again.
Hey!
Sorry I’m late!
Seth. Where have you been?
My bad! Got distracted.
I hope I didn’t keep
you waiting too long.
You kinda did.
I hiked all the way out here at
the crack of dawn
‘cause you said you’d
show me your magic!
Did I mention that I’m sorry?
Well anyway, don’t worry, I
know how I can make it up to ya.
I’ma show ya my
very best stuff!
D’ya mean it?
Ta-da!
[TOMMY gasps]
Yeah, it’s awesome.
I’m definitely not supposed to
be showing these to anybody.
They’re secret
grimoires, ya know?
Wait a second.
You didn’t take all these from
Alma’s bookshelf
without asking her, did you?
No!
Maybe, but as long as
I put ‘em back
before she notices they’re
gone, it’s no harm no foul.
Now try not to blink.
The magic show’s about to begin.
Meteor.
Drops!
I’m pretty sure I didn’t blink.
This never happens, I swear!
Okay, let’s try this one!
Re-pulse!
It’s no big deal.
But if you can’t actually
do magic,
you should probably
just admit it.
Okay, forget this boring stuff.
I’m about to show you some
original magic!
My very own spell!
Watch and be amazed.
Wow.
Here... we... go!
Titan punch!
No way!
That’s amazing, Seth!
Mm-hmm.
-[shouts]
-A stampede!
-I feel like we should run now.
-Yeah!
Why does stuff like this
always happen
when I hang out with you?
Less talking, more running,
okay Tommy?
[WOMAN]
What? You’re joking.
I’m terribly sorry, Madame,
but I’m afraid it’s true.
I sold the very last of my
rope and boards
earlier today, you see.
Try some other time.
-You’re full of it.
-Huh?
I can clearly see that you
have more in the back.
If you don’t wanna do
business with me, then say so.
What’s the deal?
Don’t hurt me.
I’m begging you.
Not in front of my wife!
What makes you think
that I would hurt you?
I know who you are!
You’re the sorcerer
who’s been floating
above the edge of our island.
Begone!
I don’t do business
with sorcerers!
You’ll just use the rope
and boards to steal our children
and sacrifice them
to the Nemesis!
Oh, boy.
So first of all,
I’m just asking
for airship supplies.
Secondly, I’ve never
kidnapped or sacrificed anyone.
My third point--
is that you have no choice
but to sell to me.
'Cause I’ll blow
your shop to bits
if you don’t do as I say!
I’ll get your items
right away, Ma’am!
Wait, dear!
Trying to convince me
you’re sold out.
[rumbling]
[MALE VILLAGER]
It's an earthquake.
What's the commotion about?
[indistinct worried chatter]
What the-- is that Seth?
Hold on, I’m pretty sure
those are our cattle.
Someone must’ve torn up
our fence.
Look, it’s that Seth kid!
You mean he’s at it again?!
Everybody stay calm, okay?
No need to worry. I got this.
[CROWD in unison]
What the hell can you do?
Man, I really blew it!
If Alma finds out
I screwed up again,
I’ll be done for!
[growls]
She knows!
If the cows don’t
kill me, she will!
Why did your magic have
to be punching?
That idiot boy is
always getting into something.
Ow.
That hurt.
Like a lot.
Well, it serves you right.
Alma!
Would it kill you
to go one day
without destroying something?
Well, see.
I kinda punched
a boulder so hard
that it flew into the ranch.
I should punch you just as hard.
No! No, please have mercy.
I’m sorry!
Hey sorcerer!
We’ve had it up to here with
you messin’ up our village!
[MAN 2] And don’t forget
about our cattle ranch.
You made a mess
out of that as well.
Whoa, hold on.
I was the one who did that,
it had nothin’ to do with Alma.
She only used her magic to
help you.
[MAN 2]
Shut up!
All you people do
is make trouble.
You’re tainted, infected!
[MAN 3] And we don’t
want you around here!
Are you serious?
Sorry, Seth.
[MAN 2]
Tommy!
Were you playing with that
sorcerer boy again?
You know full well your
father told you
to stay away from him!
Yeah, I know, but he’s-
[WOMAN] The Nemesis
aren’t even out here.
These sorcerers are nothing
but bad luck.
I’ll pay for the damage.
But Alma!
Talking isn’t gonna do us
any good at this point.
Understand?
Now, let’s go.
[MAN 1]
That isn’t good enough!
And as for you.
I’m sorry you had to put up
with this idiot.
You there!
Why’d they have to go
and blame you?
It was me that screwed up.
Uh huh.
It was all your fault.
Problem is, these things are
far more complicated than that.
How many times have I told you?
It’s fear that drives them
to act the way they do.
This is stupid!
What’s the point of
cleaning outside the house?
I should hear a lot less whining
and a lot more scrubbing.
I just punched a rock.
You punched a boulder which
was large enough
to wreck an entire cattle ranch.
And let’s not forget that
it caused the cattle to stampede
through the village,
turning every person in it
against us.
And this is after you
started the plantation fire
that dried out a whole lake.
I’m banning you from setting
so much as a foot on that
island for a while.
Aw, for how long?
Until I’m convinced that you
won’t be a menace.
Mess up badly enough and
they’ll send someone
from the royal capital to
arrest and execute you.
Also, If you think I didn’t
notice that you’ve been stealing
my grimoires, you’re wrong.
-No more of that either.
-But--
I only borrowed them because
I wanna become
a respectable sorcerer as soon
as I possibly can!
Quiet!
You haven’t even become
a respectable person yet,
all right?
Well, if you’d stop treating
me like a little kid.
And why should I?
If you wanna
get treated like an adult,
then stop groaning
and earn your keep.
Fine.
-Alma?
-Huh?
Why did you let those
villagers pin the blame on you?
You’re an amazing sorcerer,
they should respect you!
To them, there’s little
difference between us sorcerers
and a Nemesis that wrecks
their lives.
We’re monsters too, the way
they see it.
But they’re wrong,
you’re not a monster!
I’m sure they’re kind to each
other, but...
these towns folk
want nothing to do
with what they can’t understand.
But you’re one of the people who
protects them from the Nemesis!
How can they not
understand that?
I suspect that if all the
damn things were to disappear.
I’d be telling you a completely
different story right now.
So, if I could only...
Don’t’ cha go getting any
funny ideas!
Nothing good has ever come out
of you tryin’ to use your head.
Hey, that’s mean!
Just shut up and finish your
work already.
[ALMA]
Come on.
Not again.
Alma.
What now?
Could you pull me up
for a second?
I really gotta take a leak.
So do it.
Alma!
[SETH]
“Don’t get any ideas.”
That’d fix it.
If we could get rid of
The Nemesis.
It’d solve just about everything
and the sorcerers wouldn’t
have to fight any longer.
Well, that pretty much
settles it then.
I’ve gotta become
a super-powerful sorcerer
so I can start kickin’ butt!
I’ll be just like Alma!
This is it.
I really found the answer.
[SETH]
Meteor Drops!
That’s not good!
It really hurts!
It burns! It burns! It burns!
You’re supposed to show up where
my hand is pointing,
not right on top of it!
-Hey Seth?
-Stupid fire.
Maybe you should stop
trying to do this.
I mean didn’t Alma yell at
you about it just yesterday?
But that’s why I’m doing this,
to prove to her that I can
handle it!
Anyway, I was talking to my mom
and she said... that I shouldn’t
play with a sorcerer after all.
Huh? Why would she say that?
I don’t get it either.
But she said that all
of the other grown-ups
had a problem with it so...
That’s just because they don’t
understand
how awesome magic can be.
I’ve been watching you use
magic for a while now,
and I still don’t know if it’s
awesome or not.
Well, I’m still training
but I’m gonna get way more
impressive later.
After all, if I wanna take down
a whole bunch of the Nemesis,
I’ve gotta become a powerful
sorcerer first.
Wait, so do you wanna become
a Nemesis hunter?
Well yeah, ‘cause if all
of those guys are gone,
then everyone’ll be
happy, won’t they?
So the way I see it, a Nemesis
hunter is the thing to be!
Thing is,
I’ve never actually even
seen one,
so I don’t really understand
what you’d be hunting.
They are awful monsters that
fall from the sky
and attack people
all over the world.
Alma’s been fighting them for
a really long time now.
And someday, I’ll be
strong enough to beat up
every last one of them!
It’d be pretty lame of me to
stand around
and let Alma deal with them
forever, y’know?
Look there.
What do you think that is?
It looks like a Nemesis Egg!
A Nemesis Egg, and it’s heading
straight for the village.
Come on, Seth, we have to tell
Alma so she can come help!
Alma can’t save us.
‘Cause today she’s gone off
to fight a Nemesis
on some other island.
So what should we do?
You need to warn everybody and
get them to hide somewhere safe.
And you?
I’m gonna fight
that thing myself!
Don’t worry about me,
I’m a sorcerer too.
[villagers yelling]
What is that thing?
It just fell out of nowhere.
[indistinct chatter]
Aw, yeah!
Got my explosive bottle,
healing potions, magic
talismans and magic swords.
And some other shiny stuff.
I’m all geared up for battle!
Oh,
I guess I might be a bit heavy!
[TOMMY]
Get back!
Everyone get away
from that egg right now!
The Nemesis could hatch
any second!
[MAN 4]
Did you say Nemesis?
[WOMAN]
Oh, no.
They’ve really come here?
[OLD MAN] Now, everything
will be destroyed.
Disaster has finally
fallen upon the peaceful
village of Pompo Hills!
[MAN 2]
We need to inform the state.
Listen to me!
-You have to run away!
-[OLD MAN] I know!
That woman! Let’s make her
deal with it!
[MAN 1]
Good thinking,
that’s what sorcerers
are for, right?
[MAN 4] They’re already
infected, so contact with
a Nemesis won’t kill them!
The least they could do is
make themselves useful now!
It’s dangerous! We have to run--
[crash, rumbling]
Whoa...
What was that?
Great, don’t tell me
another one fell.
Oh... man.
For a second there, I thought
I was a goner.
[MAN 2]
It’s that Seth kid!
[MAN 1] The same brat who
wrecked our ranch!
Hey guys!
Now that I’m here,
your worries are over!
Just point me
to the Nemesis, okay?
[MAN 1]
Look under your feet!
The Nemesis egg!
You’re standing on it, genius!
[CROWD exclaiming]
[SETH]
Whoa! You're right!
This really is the Nemesis Egg!
[MAN 1]
Where’s that woman sorcerer?
Nobody asked for you to come!
I don’t need Alma’s help,
I can take care of this sucker
all by myself!
[MAN 1]
Don't do it!
I just need to get it away
from here, right?
It hasn’t hatched yet, so it’s
round enough to roll.
Bet I can just push it off
the edge of the island.
[cracking]
[MAN 2]
Look! The egg’s cracking!
[SETH]
Run!
It ended up hatching.
Well then, let’s see how it
likes an explosion to the face!
Nailed it.
Uh?
It's not even hurt.
All right, fine.
Magic sword, you’re up!
It punched him
right into my shop!
-[TOMMY] Seth!
-It's dangerous, come back!
Not too shabby.
Think I might have to
stop goin’ easy on ya.
Oooh.
[TOMMY]
Are you okay?!
[SETH]
Tommy?
Oooh.
Tommy, run!
[gasps]
[whimpering]
You saved me.
Are you okay, Tommy?
That was a crazy thing to do.
I’m sorry.
I thought that--
Go somewhere safe.
I can hold it.
[TOMMY] But--
Just get out of here.
Don’t think about me!
Help him!
He can’t take on
that thing by himself!
Get your big,
fat fist off my back!
I can’t let this be the end.
This is my chance to show
them that sorcerers aren’t bad.
We’re the good guys!
If Alma were here,
she would show them!
But she can’t.
I’m sick of seeing her get
treated like a monster
just because they don’t
understand.
Sorcerers risk their lives to
protect people!
I have to make them see!
Ahh!
He’s losing!
It’ll crush him.
Someone help.
Somebody save my friend!
Bravery Destroyer!
Where did that come from?
An impressive display!
You faced a Nemesis on your own,
risking your life to defend
the people.
Brave stuff.
But even the bravest
of sorcerers
need a little back-up
now and then.
So, you’re sorcerers?
[NARRATOR] The Nemesis, monsters
that wreak havoc on mankind.
Only those humans
called sorcerers,
who wield Fantasia,
can fight them.
A mysterious
band of sorcerers
called the Bravery Quartet
has appeared before young Seth.
But who exactly are they?
In the chaos to come,
Seth will have to decide who
and what he’s fighting for.
Next time on "Radiant":
“True Courage.”