[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded with fear
and distrust.
“A Paradise of Wisdom and Hope.”
♪
[SETH laughs]
-Whoa!
-Hey.
Why don’t’ cha calm it
down some?
‘Cause this is exciting! Uh--
Hey, what’s that?
It’s a security spell.
A magic circle of inspection.
-Ohh...
-They’re stationed
at every entry point
to make sure
no one brings in anything
illegal or dangerous.
Ohh!
[SETH gasps]
These ships!
Are they all owned by sorcerers?
Yeah, of course they are!
And they’re all really
beautiful, don’t you think?
Nothing like Doc’s
dinky little boat here.
Lay off it!
No worries, Doc.
I like your ship fine!
Don’t try to get
on my good side.
I don’t have one.
All right, get off my boat.
[SETH]
Aye-aye!
[indistinct chatter]
What goes on over there?
That’s just a checkpoint.
They’ll have to ask you
a few questions
before you’ll be allowed
to go into the city.
[DOC sighs]
Why me?
Hello, young man.
Is this your
first time visiting?
-Yeah!
-Great!
And I take it you’re accompanied
by a citizen of Artemis?
-Uh-huh! I’m with Doc!
-Damn it all. This is awful.
-It’s total garbage.
-Oh, I see.
I guess this gentleman
must be your guardian, then.
So, were you planning
to register as a citizen?
What do you mean?
To work as a Hunter or take
advantage of the services here,
you would have to register
as a citizen first.
It’s a pretty good deal,
if you ask me.
-[DOC groans]
-[SETH] That sounds nice,
but I’m just here to find Yaga.
I don’t really wanna
live here all the time.
You could be a citizen.
Yeah, that’s perfect! Say yes!
Just do it!
Yaga won’t agree to meet you
unless you’re a citizen!
You should definitely register.
-Oh... sure--
-So, when’s the next ceremony?
I think there’s one scheduled
to start in just a moment.
Then we had better get going.
Come along with me,
you crazy little scamp.
Doc?
[SETH screams]
[DOC] Stop draggin’
your feet! Move it!
[MELIE]
Don’t just leave me behind!
Um, you need to sign in.
Hm... wait a sec.
Did I find out if that Doc guy
was really his guardian?
Oh, well. Next!
[SETH panting]
And we’re here!
[DOC groans]
So pretty.
You can tell this really
is a city of sorcerers.
And there’s no other place
like it in the world.
People here call Artemis
"the Sorcerers’ Paradise."
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Yeah, no one’ll
treat us weird here.
So we don’t ever have
to hide what we are.
Pretty sweet.
I could get used to this place.
Glad to hear it.
-Wait 'til you see more!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps happily]
[DOC groaning]
Hey!
You can’t stop here or you’ll be
late for the admission ceremony.
It’ll be at least a few weeks
before they have the next one.
You wanna find this “Yaga”
person fast, don’t you?
Well, yeah.
That’s why I came here.
Alma said that
he could help me out.
Let’s go. The admission ceremony
is held in a big castle
just a little ways above us.
[SETH]
Sounds good. Let’s do it!
-Doc, hop to!
-What. Me?
No! I’m fine right here.
You’re the one that needs
to become a citizen.
-[DOC yelling]
-Come on lazylegs,
we’re gonna be late!
I just finished telling you
to go there without me!
Hurry, if I screw up this early,
I’ll never hear
the end of it from Alma!
[SETH laughs]
Woo!
-Why are you guys always...
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
...leaving me behind?
Did that kid say “Alma”?
[fireworks exploding]
[excited chatter]
[SETH] Looks like
we made it just in time.
-Ladies and gentlemen!
-[DOC panting, groans]
First of all,
I’d like to thank each of you
for attending this fine
admission ceremony.
And now, without further ado,
allow me to introduce
our wonderful leader!
Are you people ready
to clap and scream
like you never have before?
I give you the founder
of this crazy Institute.
The one and only...
[drumroll]
Master... Lord...
Majesty!
[cheering]
[CEREMONY CROWD]
Majesty! Majesty! Majesty!
So this is the yellow cat.
Greetings, pawsome
subjects of mine.
We have gathered here today
to bolster our ranks.
Neow please join me in welcoming
our soon-to-be comrades,
who shall live among us,
and assist us
in our great mission.
If we all work
in purrfect harmony,
I have no doubt that we can
one day render the curses
that cause us such needless
suffering catatonic.
[CEREMONY CROWD]
Woo-hoo!
Is that even possible?
No one knows, but Majesty’s
been working really hard
-to find out if it is.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Oh yeah? That’s a pretty
impressive goal, for a cat.
[MAJESTY]
Aspiring citizens!
The time is neow!
[MC]
Come on up here, don’t be shy!
Get a move on,
don’t keep them waiting.
Oh. Sure.
[CEREMONY CROWD cheering]
[MAJESTY] Welcome to
the Artemis Institute,
brave young sorcerers.
Once you’re full-fledged
members of Artemis,
you’ll have access to all
the academy’s facilities.
And you’ll be purr-mitted
to attend lectures and classes
given by remeowned
sorcerers, too.
All that can be yours,
if you just sign
these cute little contracts!
Here! Take it! Sign!
Huh? I’m not
all that interested.
Aww! Come on,
just do it. I know!
Why don’t I lend you
my very own pen so you can sign?
Go on. Write
your name. Yeah.
-[SETH] Hmm...
-Sign it neow.
-Sign. It. Neow!
-Why not?
[giggles]
The contracts have been signed.
Let’s hear a warm round
of applause
for our mew-est
comrades in arms!
[CEREMONY CROWD cheering]
[laughs]
Wait. What’s all that?
[YOUNG SORCERERS gasp]
Promissory note?
You charged us
for the pens we used?
Three thousand freaking dimes?
And four thousand
for...the ink?
Why are you pretending
that this stuff costs so much?
I dunno,
why are you signing
stuff ya haven’t even read yet?
Anyway, each of you now owes
a pawsitively massive debt
-to yours truly.
-[YOUNG SORCERERS] Huh?
And if you intend
to get square with me,
you’ll have to make repurrations
by participating in missions
as Artemis Hunters.
[YOUNG SOCERERS]
Huh?!
-[HECKLER 1] Good luck, newbies!
-[CROWD laughs]
[HECKLER 2]
We’ve all been there!
[HECKLER 1]
You’ll do fine!
[YOUNG SOCERERS]
Huh?!
And with that, our 854th
admission ceremony
is meow concluded!
Bye-bye!
-Hey! Come back here!
-What a greedy little furball!
This isn’t over, you hear me?
[CEREMONY CROWD
indistinct chatter]
[DOC chuckles]
I played my hand perfectly.
The kid’ll be so busy,
he won’t know up from down!
With any luck,
I’ll never see him again!
[GOVERNMENT WORKER]
Excuse me, Doc?
This young man entered Artemis
-with you today, correct?
-Huh?
We have you registered
as his guardian.
And as per the academy’s rules,
it states here,
you are legally responsible
for any debt
that’s accrued by your ward.
You’re kidding!
Why does this fall onto me?
You’d best pay quickly,
before the interest kicks in.
[DOC groans, strained]
-[DOC groaning, cries]
-Doc?
This isn’t the best place
for lying down.
-Um. Doc?
-That kid’ll be the death of me.
[SETH] “Make sure to avoid
the yellow cat if you can,”
right, Alma?
Guess this is what I get
for not listening.
Man. I’m in so much debt,
it’s all I can see.
Did the same thing
happen to you, Melie?
That it did.
But I’m not very good
with paperwork and what not,
so I just left it all to Doc.
And then I forgot
it ever happened.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps, annoyed]
Huh, maybe I’ll forget
about it.
-[DOC panics]
-What’s that swindling cat
gonna do if I
ignore him, scratch me?
That’s a very good point.
No, it’s not! Look.
That debt of yours is on
my head too now, so pay it!
I see where you’re
comin’ from, Doc.
-All of this was my fault.
-Oh. Wow, you actually get it.
So as soon as I track down
this Yaga person
and find out
where Radiant is,
-I’ll ditch this town for good!
-Huh?
But then... wouldn’t
that just leave me
to deal with your
horrible debt by myself?
-No. Wait a sec.
-All right! It’s a plan.
-Let’s do this thing, Doc!
-Hey. I--
And needless to say, you can
count on us to help you out.
No. Look. You can’t--
Thanks a bunch, Melie,
and you too, Boobrie!
-Listen.
-We’re comin’ for ya, Yaga!
-[DOC] No, no, no, no, no.
-[MELIE] You know,
-this is kind of exciting!
-My credit! You can’t do this.
You’ll ruin me!
[DOC] You need to pay the stupid
cat his money, okay?
[DOC breathing heavily]
So, hey. How are we
gonna find this guy?
With all the twisting alleys
and unexpected intersections,
it’s kinda hard to find
our way around.
Well, for the time being,
we can just explore.
-Yeah!
-Huh? No, you can’t.
Everything has a price
in this town, okay?
[SETH]
Let’s start over there!
No! Wait!
-[DOC sighs]
-[MELIE] There are two
different bridges...
We should definitely
use this one.
[SETH]
Hmm...
Come on!
-Slow down, Seth! Wait for us!
-Why are you kids so dumb?
[cash register dings]
So cool!
We don’t even have to walk here!
This does make life much easier.
Stop wasting money-hop
over the side!
Quick! Maybe you haven’t
-been charged yet!
-[BOTH] Huh?
[cash register dings]
[DOC panting]
Hey, Doc? Why are you so sweaty?
Why don’t you use this, dearie?
Oh! Thank you.
-Here ya go, Doc.
-Huh?!
Some nice old lady
gave it to us.
Yeah, for only
58-hundred dimes!
[cash register dings]
[MELIE] When you’re
looking for information,
-I start at the pub!
-[DOC sighs]
Oh wow, this is a place
where grown-ups hang out.
Don’t you dare order something!
We’re just here
to talk to people, okay?
-We’re only here to chat.
-Welcome to the Magician’s bar.
Have you decided
what you’d like to order yet?
You know what,
I could go for some milk.
[DOC angrily scoffs]
[cash register dings]
What the actual hell
is wrong with you?
I’m sorry, I couldn’t help it!
Um. Hi.
Would you mind
if I asked you something?
[groans]
Uh, fine.
Have you ever met
a sorcerer named Yaga?
[growls]
Course not. Go away.
I’m trying to enjoy a drink.
Uh...
Get outta here, kid.
I bet your mommy
is looking for you.
-[laughs]
-[MELIE growls]
[DRUNKARD] Oops,
looks like I’m empty.
Hey, refill!
[MELIE] I got somethin’
you can fill up on right here,
you knuckle-dragging lush.
Huh? Ah!
How about a face-full
of my magic?
Crap, it’s Crazy Melie?
Open up, dirtbag!
-Take it like a man!
-Oh, no!
Please, Melie,
don’t do this to me!
Now, blow away!
[crash]
[yelling]
Why’d you blow me away too?!
[cash register dings]
[CHILD]
Papa! Papa!
[ALL groaning, sighing]
I just wanna find Yaga.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
[delirious] I owe more cash...
than I’ve ever had.
I owe more cash...
Hey, look at
this month’s debt king!
Best of luck
paying it all back.
[SETH]
Thanks!
-What does “debt king” mean?
-It’s a very impressive title.
You can only be called
the debt king
if you owe more money
than any other sorcerer
in the whole city!
Oh, yeah? I wonder
who they were talking about.
They were talking about me,
you dumb screw-up!
Look, this only
happened to me
because you two were
so recklessly stupid!
I’ve gotta tell ya Doc,
you don’t look so good.
And whose fault
d’ya think that is?
-[DOC] Mommy.
-[BOTH gasp]
So uh... did he just need a nap?
Don’t worry. Doc’s pretty
much always like that.
-Oh, okay!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
But anyway, debt aside,
this really is a haven
for sorcerers.
[MELIE]
Yeah...
[MAN]
I was skeptical at first, but...
I guess home
is where you make it.
-Huh...?
-[WOMAN] Compared to
when we lived on the outside,
this place has been a paradise
I’m glad we came.
[MAN]
Yeah, you can say that again.
All the people here
seem so happy.
[MAN, muffled]
Hmph, it’s about
time you took notice
of that fact.
Uh... huh?
-Huh. Weird.
-It’s a cauldron.
[MAN, muffled]
What about it?
-[BOTH scream]
-The cauldron just talked to us!
Did your curse turn you
into a cauldron, sir?
Stop callin’ me a damn cauldron!
Okay?
Oh, I get it.
He must just live in there.
Pardon, but might I ask
who you are, sir?
I’m nobody that’s worth
knowing by name.
But I heard that you kids
are looking for someone
named Yaga, right?
Yeah, do you have any idea
where he might be?
I might be willing
to share that with you,
but first I’d like
to ask you a little question.
-Ask away.
-Just what do you think
of the academy Master
Lord Majesty has built here?
Hm?
You really wanna know
what I think?
Well, that cat’s a total creep.
But... this is the first town
I’ve been to where nobody
called me “infected,”
or treated me like crap.
I can be myself here.
And use magic without
getting suspicious looks.
Everything costs way
too much money,
but the people who
live here are smiling.
Hm, interesting.
Do you have any idea
why Majesty tries to squeeze all
that money out of his subjects?
I thought he said,
that it’s for research
on how to break
our curses, right?
That’s only half of it.
-[SETH] Uh--
-[MELIE] Oh.
Does this have anything to do
with where Yaga is, 'cause--
[alarm blaring]
That’s the alarm. Which means--
Crap! The city’s under attack!
-Wait. Do you think it’s--
-It has to be!
The Inquisition
followed us here!
-I knew running was a bad idea.
-[SETH gasps]
Huh. This is great timing.
You can see it firsthand now.
Sit back and watch
your money get to work.
[wind whooshing]
Sir, the troops are at
their stations, ready to fight.
Good. Tell the men to prepare
to enter Artemis in force.
We’ll apprehend that brat and
his companions, then withdraw.
I’m not sure
if that’s possible, sir.
[VICE]
Uh...
[SOLDIER 1]
Message from the homeland!
We have new orders.
We’re to suspend all tasks
and immediately retreat
from this airspace, sir.
What?! Madness!
Why should we back down?
[DRAGUNOV]
It would seem Artemis
is putting their influence
to good use.
Greetings, Captain Dragunov.
Forgive me, sir.
but, what are you saying?
What’s it sound like I’m saying?
The Inquisition may be a
powerful force in this country,
but that doesn’t mean
it’s the only one.
You know of
Master Lord Majesty.
He did this, and it must’ve
cost him a small fortune.
[VICE exhales]
At any rate, there are members
of the 13 Sorcerer Coven
living in that town.
Any one of them could take
on a thousand of us.
There are both military
and political forces
to be reckoned with.
Fighting them would be like
going to war with a nation.
And we don’t want
to start a war.
Right, Vice Captain?
[VICE gulps]
So. We have our orders. Retreat.
-Take us to headquarters.
-Yes, sir!
[VICE]
You heard him! Retreat at once!
But still,
this is far from over.
That boy had horns
and used magic barehanded.
General Torque needs
to be informed of this.
Ohh, man.
Between the cost
of mobilizing our forces,
and the glorified bribes we sent
to those inquisitor bosses,
we spent some real coin.
It was no consequence, really.
We only had to raise
a paw in threat,
and the pesky insects
flitted away.
[slurps]
[SETH]
Amazing!
They actually sent
those guys packing!
-[DOC] Yeah. We’re saved!
-[MELIE] Thank goodness.
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps in relief]
[MAN]
So now do you understand?
This is the power
of the Artemis Institute,
and its Majesty
who amassed it.
He’s built the world’s
only sanctuary
for persecuted sorcerers,
who’ve nowhere else to go.
[SETH sighs]
He’ll use any means
he deems necessary
towards the goal
of keeping them all safe.
I guess that cat’s not
such a creep after all.
So. Tell me.
What do you plan to do
once you meet Yaga?
That one’s easy!
I’m’a ask him where
I can find Radiant,
-and then I’ll destroy it!
-Heh!
-That’s just a pipe dream, kid.
-Hm?
If you wish to help sorcerers,
then there’s
a far more realistic
approach you could take.
Oh yeah? What?
You’ve seen firsthand what
this place has accomplished.
Prejudice has no place
here in Artemis.
And it’s well out of
the Inquisition’s reach.
No one even knows
if Radiant actually exists.
So wouldn’t it make
more sense to stay here,
and use your strength to protect
this paradise instead?
What do you say?
-[MAN] Hm?
-Hmm...
Maybe, but even
if you’re right.
My goal’s the same.
Oh?
But why?
[DOC exhales]
This place may be safe, sure.
But there are countless
people out there,
still living in fear
of the Nemesis.
And if we want
to help those people,
that’ll mean we’re gonna have
to change the world itself.
Ha! Do you actually believe
that a runt like yourself
can change the world?
I don’t know,
and I won’t know until I try!
If no one else’ll do it, I will.
I’ll change this world.
Well, if nothing else,
you seem to be just
as stubborn as Alma.
[SETH]
Huh?
You’ve passed your first test.
Come with me.
Oh, so I guess this means you’re
gonna take me to meet Yaga now?
Have you still not
figured it out, you fool?
Huh?
It’s me.
I’m Yaga.
[ALL]
Huh?
What?!
[TORQUE]
How unexpected.
It’s a rare thing indeed
when a sorcerer manages
to escape your watchful eye.
Sir.
While it’s true
that Artemis interfered,
I still failed.
I will accept any punishment.
No. Reprimanding you
now would be pointless.
But I will ask you
one final time
if you’re certain that this
sorcerer used magic barehanded.
Yes. I know exactly
what I saw, sir.
[DRAGUNOV]
Hmm...
I want you to watch all traffic
to and from Artemis.
If you see him again,
inform me at once.
And for the time being,
keep this matter confidential.
As you command.
So, he found a sorcerer boy
with horns,
who can use Fantasia barehanded.
We are both well aware
of the danger
that this sorcerer could pose.
The boy must be captured.
[NARRATOR]
The sorcerer Yaga
tells Seth he won’t accept him
as a pupil
unless he can prove his skill.
Melie offers to help Seth train,
but unfortunately,
neither of them are especially
versatile sorcerers.
Just how far will Seth have to
go to earn Yaga’s approval?
The next phase of his training
gets off to a rocky start.
Next time on Radiant.
“Drops of Friendship.”