[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
-[wind rushing]
-[SETH screaming]
[hand powering up]
Let's try Skull...
Huh? Wha--
Crap.
I thought I pulled it off
that time.
Mm?
Oh no, I ruined my gloves
all over again!
[SETH stammering]
That's what you get
for not listening.
[SETH]
You don't understand.
These were a gift from Alma.
[SETH whining]
-Listen here, kid.
-[SETH] Huh?
[YAGA] I want you to hand
those gloves to me.
[SETH] Uh... but you
and Alma always say
I shouldn't use magic
without gloves.
Don't worry, boy.
You can borrow these.
Hold on.
What the heck are these things?
They're a set of gauntlets
I had constructed out
of a special material.
Like what?
[YAGA] It's a metal that's
extremely resistant to Fantasia,
called Black Silver.
-What?
-[YAGA] That's right.
As long as you wear
those gloves,
you won't be able
to use magic at all.
Well, that sucks.
Quit messing around
and help me get ‘em off.
-[zap]
-[SETH stammering]
[YAGA]
Oops.
I forgot to mention.
If you try to remove them,
they'll electrocute you.
Then...
Why'd you put them on me?
How am I s'posed to train
like this?
As you are at present,
you're unworthy of
receiving instruction from me.
Huh? Why?
What do you mean by that?
The channeling of Fantasia
into magic
is something between
a science and an art!
But you'd never know it from
watching your haphazard
attempts to fling it about.
Would you like to know
how your gloves were ruined?
You gathered more Fantasia
than you could handle,
and tried to brute force
it into magic without thinking!
Which tells me the time I spent
on you has been wasted.
What are you trying to say?
Sure, I don't know
how to use it yet,
but if I can gather lots of
Fantasia, that's a good thing.
It just means I'm gonna
be powerful, right?
[sighs]
What good can power hope
to achieve without restraint?
Ugh!
You're the one who says
I can't go after Radiant
until I get strong,
so why're you changing
your mind now?
There's nothing wrong
with acquiring power in itself.
But nor is there
any intrinsic good in it.
What matters is how
it's wielded.
Look, if you wanna
tell me something, spit it out!
You've become so
doggedly focused
on the goal
of acquiring power
that you've lost sight
of something crucial.
And I want those gloves
to stay on you
until you can figure out
what that is.
So... if I take ‘em off,
what'll my punishment be?
What do you think?
Expulsion!
Whaaaaaa?
[NARRATOR]
"Proof of Strength."
[SETH with mouth full]
Sheesh.
What's Yaga's problem, anyway?
[bites, chewing]
If he won't let me use magic
he should at least say why!
[MELBA]
Oh, dear.
Seth, you look like
you're feeling
a little frustrated
right now.
Yeah, Seth has been in a really
bad mood all day.
-[PAPA] Here we go.
-Aw, that's a shame.
If you're gonna come
and eat here every day,
you should at least take time
to taste the food!
-Appreciate it!
-I'm sorry.
I eat fast when I'm mad
and Yaga keeps saying stuff
that makes no sense.
"There's nothing wrong
about acquiring power.
Although, there's nothing
good either."
[PAPA]
That's a terrible impression.
"What matters is
how it's wielded."
Stuff like that, see?
That's him, all right.
Never met an old coot
more stubborn than Yaga.
But he's not one for talk
without purpose.
So you think he has a point?
That I do.
[SETH] But you can't tell me
what his point is?
-[MELIE sighs]
-[SETH bites sandwich]
I finally found you!
How can you kids just sit there
and eat without a care?
[BOTH]
Hey, Doc.
Begone, you damn vermin!
Here to make another pass
at my daughter, are you?
Oh, be nice to him, Papa.
-[PAPA muttering]
-Good to see you again, Doc.
Would you care for a cup
of special herbal tea?
You know it, Melba.
I'd love nothing else.
A cup of your special tea
sounds delightful,
but sadly I can't partake.
Unfortunately, I have
some urgent business today.
What kind of urgent business
is it you have exactly?
It has to do with Master
Lord Majesty himself.
He's summoned all three of us
to his chambers!
[MAJESTY]
As I'm sure you purr-dicted,
I called you here
today for a reason.
Care to guess
what that might be?
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-No clue.
Haven't got the slightest idea.
[DOC shivering]
This is uncomfortable,
but according to my
in-fur-mation,
your debt has soared
to heights
once considered
quite im-paw-sible.
-Really?
-[DOC] Gah!
No one's ever owed ya this much?
No.
Your debt is the highest
that's ever been accrued
in the history of this
A-cat-emy!
You're saying we set
some kinda record?
Holy cow!
Way to go us, right?
-Yeah!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
This is nothin' to celebrate.
How dumb can you be?
[DOC] That debt is on my head,
too, thanks to you!
[sighs]
It's a terrible shame.
[MAJESTY] I love every last one
of the citizens of Artemis
like they're my own kittens.
But the pawsition I'm in
is awkward to say the least.
I can't just let you
out of this fur free!
If puss comes to shove,
I'll banish you.
-[DOC whimpers]
-That would be terrible.
So, what do you want us to do?
If you can't pay your debt
in full right neow,
I suppose I could
offur an alternative.
Interested?
[DOC, SETH and MELIE]
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
I mew you would be.
[SETH panting]
[SETH]
Huh?
[BOTH humming]
[SETH]
Too bad I can't use magic.
This would go a lot faster.
Hmm.
Can't let Melie
show me up too bad.
All right!
[SETH yelling]
Rub-a-dub dub!
-[MELIE inhales]
-[SETH] Yeah, take that, dirt!
[SETH laughs]
I sure hope that Doc isn't
having too hard of a time
working all by himself.
[DOC grunting, strained]
[DOC groaning]
Come on.
Just power through it, buddy.
Remember, you're doing this
for sweet Melba!
[romantic music plays]
-[DOC laughs]
-[MELBA] Oh, my!
I'll stroll anywhere as long
as I'm strolling with you, baby.
[MELBA]
You've been working out!
-Hey Doc?
-Doll face?
Work hard so we can plan
our future together.
Don't keep me waiting.
Of course, Melba.
All that I want is a quiet life
spent at your side.
A life placid and calm.
Towards that goal,
I intend to work
my absolute hardest.
Come, my love. Marry me.
-Yes! A hundred times yes!
-[DOC laughs]
[laughing]
My coffee queen!
-Ahh!
-[crank whirls]
Phew.
The place is startin'
to look pretty shiny!
[MELIE]
Hey Seth!
I just finished wiping down
the walls over that way.
[SETH]
That was fast, way to go!
I'm glad to be of service--
uh...
Hey, take a look up there.
[SETH]
Huh? What'd do you mean?
Oh, I see.
What is it?
-[SETH] Huh...
-I'm not sure, but it kinda
seems to be heading
toward the service entrance.
All right, I'm'a go ahead
and check it out.
Huh?
Seth, wait!
Let's see.
It was somewhere around
this way, right?
[DON BOSSMAN]
Hop to, boys!
We're on a schedule!
Right. Sorry, Boss.
We're on it!
I've gotta say, Boss.
I'm impressed that you
managed to figure out
where these Artemis guys
keep their treasure.
[laughs]
That was child's play.
I've always been
the imitative type.
Uh, Boss?
I'm pretty sure you mean
"innovative," right?
Yeah, some people call it that.
[DON BOSSMAN]
Now then,
Let's nab us some treasure
before the guards get on to us
and make this difficult.
[SETH]
Hey! What're you guys doing?
You're not s'posed to be
up here!
-[SETH] Ahh!
-[DON BOSSMAN] Whoa-ohh!
[BOTH screaming]
[SETH]
The Buck-Naked Quartet?
[BRAVERY QUARTET]
Ahh!
Ugh, well I see that you're
still as snarky as ever.
Show him, boys!
-[BOTH] Right, Boss!
-Weh...
[DON BOSSMAN]
We're a wandering band
of sorcerer thieves,
the likes of which
have never been seen!
And we go by...
The Bravery...
[ALL]
Quartet!
Whoa!
You guys changed up your intro.
[DON BOSSMAN laughs]
Yeah, we like to keep things
fresh for our fans.
[SETH] Hold on, didn't Alma
capture you guys?
Yeah, the old hag's the one
who stripped us to our skivvies.
She caught us and put us
in the village custody.
But we gave those hicks
the slip no problem!
[ALL laugh]
Hey, who's that?
Lookit!
Who's he talking to?
[screams]
So lewd!
Melie, be careful.
These guys suck.
They're con artists
who rob innocent people.
They're as ruthless
as they come!
[DON BOSSMAN]
Really?
There's no need to be hostile.
[SETH] I don't know what
you guys are plotting
but I'm sure
it's nothing good!
[DON BOSSMAN] Way to go,
you're right on the money!
Or should I say
we're right on the money,
'cause there's a pile
of priceless treasure
beneath this trap door!
We're just gonna help ourselves
to as much as we can carry.
I won't let you!
Hang back, Seth,
I'll handle this!
Meteor Drops!
[explosion]
[SETH] I thought attack spells
weren't your strong suit.
Well, you're not the only one
who's been training lately.
Uhh! How're they able
to use magic?
They don't have any conduits
that I can see.
[SETH]
Weird.
[laughs]
You've had your turn,
now it's ours!
[ALL]
Bravery...
Missile!
[BRAVERY QUARTET A and B]
And Chains!
Repulse!
Nice one, Melie.
Think you saved my butt there.
[MELIE]
Speaking of butts.
Pretty sure I've figured
out their secret.
It's... their underwear!
Underwear?
[DON BOSSMAN laughs]
You're perceptive, and I can't
blame ya for lookin'.
Yeah! These babies
are custom made.
And also...
woven from the same fabric
as magic gloves
so they're
surprisingly soft!
I knew these guys
were devious,
but I didn't realize
they were a bunch'a perverts.
Nothin' pervy about it!
No clothing can tell you as much
about a man as his knickers!
Not only is the material we've
crafted ours from comfortable.
It's practical.
Now stay still so I can give you
a brief demonstration.
Are ya ready?
Bravery Bomb!
That is so gross.
Meteor Drops!
[BRAVERY QUARTET]
Ahh!
Did you blow ‘em away?
Hmph. Offensive magic
might not be my strong suit,
but I won't lose!
-[gasps]
-[DON BOSSMAN laughs]
Better luck next time, girlie.
They're a bunch'a weirdos,
but even in their
unmentionables,
they're pretty skilled
at combat magic.
We graciously accept
your acclamation.
Hey, Boss.
I think you meant to say--
[ALL question]
I said it right that time,
damn it!
So, I can't help but notice
that you haven't been
using magic, boy.
[exhales]
[DON BOSSMAN]
Those gloves you're wearing,
they're made out of
Black Silver, aren't they?
They might be,
but so what if you're right?
What say we cut a deal?
Turn a blind eye to
our little operation here,
and I'll help you free up
your hands in exchange.
I might even throw in
a nice pair of undies.
[SETH breathing heavily]
Don't do it.
You made a promise to Yaga.
Believe it or not,
when I make a deal,
I keep my word.
[SETH]
I'm not gonna make any deals
with a scumbag like you.
Well, ya can't blame
a guy for tryin'.
It's a shame, kid.
I know it's not mutual,
but I have a lotta
respect for you.
Ya did put a hole
in that Nemesis.
You've got a right hook
like nothin' else I've seen.
It was enough to knock me
off my feet in one hit.
Not every day I meet a sorcerer
as young as you who
has that kinda firepower.
After watchin' ya do all that,
why wouldn't I
treat you with respect?
I understand.
It must be hard for you to find
yourself in this position.
My sympathies.
[sighs]
Power is everything
in this world.
If you don't have
any of your own,
you're doomed to be preyed upon
by those who do.
That's not true.
Thing is...
once you do have power,
you suddenly make everything
in life go your way!
Whatever you want's yours!
I would suffer too if someone
took that from me.
I'm nothing like you,
so stop talking like I am!
Is that so?
[BOTH]
Huh?
I wanna be strong,
of course I do,
but that's not the reason!
Unlike you,
I don't look at people
who are weaker than me
as victims to prey on!
The whole point of being strong
is to help them!
Well said.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I guess we can't make a deal.
But as you are right now,
what do you expect to achieve?
Even without magic,
I can still take you guys out.
Keep runnin' your mouth.
Let ‘em have it, boys!
[ALL]
Will do, Boss!
Ultimate...
Bravery...
[BRAVERY QUARTET]
Attack!
[ALL gasp]
[DON BOSSMAN laughs]
Too easy!
Well that's what they get for
underestimating our strength.
What?
Listen.
There's nothing more obnoxious
than a bunch of pigs
pretending to be wolves.
-Awesome.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I'm gonna shut you up,
and make myself some bacon
at the same time.
Ready or not.
Ignis Rumpere!
[BRAVERY QUARTET scream]
Only managed to get two of ‘em.
Great work as always, Jiji.
Nothing gets past your
impenetrable bravery shield!
Benatrable.
If I wanna take out
that bearded hog,
I'm gonna have to do something
about the shield first.
-Melie, do that again!
-Say what?
I just said there's no point.
That shield's in the way.
-Hmm.
-Huh?
All right.
Don't blame me when
it goes to hell.
Here goes.
Ignis Rumpere!
[JIJI]
Ahh!
[laughs]
If you feel like bangin'
your head against a brick wall,
knock yourself out!
Whoa! How'd he get up there?
He must've used the explosion
from the spell
to push himself
into the air.
You bet I did!
This is Alma's special move.
Brace yourself
for a Punishing Axe Kick!
-[SETH grunts]
-[DON BOSSMAN groans]
Weh...
I think you had better take
a nap with the others.
[JIJI]
Ehh-- oh!
That was amazing.
We make a pretty good team.
Honestly.
If I had messed up
even a little,
I would've blasted you, too.
Then I guess it's a good thing
you never mess up.
Hmph.
Uh--
Hey, what do you say we get
those weirdos tied up
before they come
and try to kill us again?
Uh-- [gasps]
Melie!
[laughs]
I bravely played dead,
to give you the slip.
-Sorry.
-All right.
You do exactly as I say,
or it's lights out
for the girlie.
[MISTER BOOBRIE battle cry]
What're you doing, Boobrie?!
Get off me!
What the hell kinda
little monster is this?
My eyes!
-Stop your pecking!
-[MELIE] Ahh!
Stop! Go away!
-I can't see anything!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[DON BOSSMAN grunting]
Leave me alone!
Stop!
-[DON BOSSMAN] I'm warning you!
-[SETH] Oh, no!
-[MELIE] Wait!
-[DON BOSSMAN] Get back!
[screams]
[panting]
[SETH grunts]
Seth, no! You can't fly!
I can't save him without magic.
If I take 'em off,
what'll my punishment be?
[YAGA]
What do you think?
Expulsion!
That isn't what
matters right now!
-[SETH pained struggle]
-[electricity crackling]
Just fight through it!
[screams]
Ahh...!
-Don't die.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[SETH] Melie!
-[gasps]
[SETH] I hope I didn't
worry you too much.
[MELIE]
You made it!
[chuckles]
I'm so sorry, I messed up.
Bottom line,
I broke my word.
[grumbles]
[MELIE]
Yeah, he tried to keep it.
He would've, even if it
got him beat up,
he would've kept his word,
but he had no choice!
-See?
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[SETH] Thank you for worrying,
but it's okay.
I don't regret anything
that I've done.
-But Seth--
-It's no big deal.
This'll be a setback,
but it's not gonna stop me.
[MELIE]
You sure?
[sighs]
I don't recall saying
you were expelled just yet.
So I fail to see what you're
getting so damn worked up over.
[BOTH]
Huh?
But didn't you say
that if I took those gloves off,
that would be that?
Yeah, that's what I said,
and at the time,
I didn't expect
to make exceptions.
[MELIE and SETH gasp]
Considering the circumstances,
I'll give you a pass this once.
[MELIE and SETH gasp]
I get to stay on!
Congratulations!
That's awesome!
Well, Boy.
Huh?
Have you figured out
what you lost sight of?
I have!
All right.
In that case, I've got
something for you.
Here.
[SETH]
Cool.
[YAGA] There was enough
intact fabric left for me
to remake your gloves
into a fingerless design.
While you're still an amateur
when it comes
to wielding Fantasia,
that's not really why you've
been struggling to gather it.
[SETH]
Uh--
You see,
while most sorcerers can only
gather Fantasia with a conduit,
you can only do it
with your skin.
So, you've been gathering
Fantasia with your arms,
and trying to force it
into your gloves,
causing most of it
to disperse in the process,
and making your magic
far weaker than it could be.
But why would Alma give me
gloves that made my magic worse?
I can assure you, she knew
what she was doing
and acted with your
best interest at heart.
There are two ways that you
could've attracted
the Inquisition's attention.
By using magic bare-handed,
or by giving the world
a demonstration
of your full potential.
So you're saying, she held him
back to protect him?
[SETH exhales]
Those gloves have been
patched up many times.
That woman must care
a great deal for you.
[SETH]
Yeah.
Now that you've been provided
with fingerless gloves,
you should be able
to make better use
of the talent
you were born with.
Here goes.
Hm...
Ahh--!
That's amazing.
Not too shabby.
You can expect your training
to get a lot harder
from this day on.
Sounds good.
Do your worst, old man!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I'm so glad
everything worked out.
That said,
I feel like there's something
we're forgetting.
Meh.
Who cares? Let's go.
[SETH yells, distant]
Yaga!
[MAJESTY laughing]
Stopping those thieves wouldn't
have been easy on the purrse
if those kids hadn't whiskered
them away for me.
Neow instead of paying
to formally deploy the troops,
I only have to reduce
their debt by a little.
I'm pawsitively robbing
the sweet fools.
Looks like my meowsterful plan
paid off.
Ahh-- mmm...
Nothing's better than
a shaved ice snack
when you're feline good
about your choices!
[MAJESTY exclaims]
-[DOC groaning]
-[wheel moving]
What the heck kind of machine
is this, anyway?
And how long do
I have to crank it for?
Neow seconds!
[NARRATOR] Dragunov's
laid-back style of command
causes one of the new recruits
to doubt the captain's ability.
Then, his unit receives
an emergency message,
a request for aid
from an allied vessel,
which was shipwrecked
in a Nemesis attack.
Faced with a difficult truth,
Dragunov is forced
to make a choice.
Next time on "Radiant,"
"Those Who Hunt Heretics."