[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
Seth left Alma,
the woman who raised him,
and set off
in search of Radiant.
But in this world of adversity,
there’s no telling
what he’ll find when he meets
his journey’s end.
[engine puffing]
[MAN]
Hey! You Alma?
You the one with
the Nemesis corpse?
The name is Doc.
Nemesis research professional!
[VICE]
Captain Dragunov,
we’ll soon enter the airspace
described in the report.
As for the sorcerer
we caught on the way,
what would you
have us do with her?
Well, we can hardly
toss her overboard.
So, we’ll just have
to keep her for now.
[VICE]
Sir.
Poor fools.
These imbecilic sorcerers.
[NARRATOR]
“A Meeting in the Sky.”
[DOC] Man. They weren’t kidding
when they said this island
was out in the sticks.
It took me forever to find it.
[ALMA] I contacted Artemis
three days back.
Would it kill you people
to at least send word
if you’re gonna be late?
Huh? But I did send word.
My assistant was s’posed
to let you know I was coming.
Redhead. Sound familiar?
-Not in the slightest.
-Hmm...
Try to come up
with a better excuse next time.
No way.
Did that girl actually
get lost again?
-What’s that?
-Oh. I’m just talking to myself.
So, listen.
My traveling expenses
were pretty substantial.
And once you’ve delivered
the Nemesis corpse to Artemis,
you’ll be paid plenty.
Did you really think
I wouldn’t know that?
You greasy little miser.
Crap! This hag’s a wily one.
Who’d’a guessed?
-Huh?
-So hey, I’m thinkin’,
maybe I should go
pick up those remains?
[nervously laughs] Before the
inquisition gets here?
[air whooshing]
[sighs]
I can’t believe
it’s been three days.
Hope Seth hasn’t gotten himself
into much trouble yet.
[SETH]
Titan Punch!
[SOLDIER #1 yells]
[SOLDIERS muttering]
The kid’s using some
weird technique, be careful!
Plenty of fist where
that came from
and its first come first serve!
[SOLDIER #2]
What the heck’s with this guy?
What’s with you guys?
And what’s with those
stupid helmets!
They’re covering your eyes!
How ya gonna fight like that?!
What’s the commotion about?
This kid crashed his broom
into our ship, sir!
-Did he now?
-[SETH] Hey! Watch it!
Quit pushin’ me!
He flew towards the ship,
we thought he looked suspicious.
Just as we’d decided to pick
him up for questioning,
he collided with us.
And then he started fighting.
I don’t even wanna be here,
so leave me alone!
Don’t push me around! Ughh!
[DRAGUNOV]
Hmm...
Oh, come on!
I didn’t mean
to hit your dumb ship.
I’m just not that good
at flying a broom yet, okay?
Ugh!
[SETH]
I said, no pushing!
-[explosion]
-[SOLDIERS scream]
Ahh. Impressive magic,
little sorcerer.
Yeah. I’m pretty cool.
The name’s Seth,
and I’m a Nemesis Hunter.
Though, you could say
I’m still in training.
Just how stupid are you?
Hey, back off!
Only idiots call people idiots.
I know ‘cause Alma told me so!
This idiot’s as ignorant
as they come.
If word of the law has yet
to reach the hinterlands,
then it’s our duty
to make it known.
-Proceed.
-Right! Young man.
All of us present have witnessed
your use of magic.
Which means that, unless you can
show us identification,
and the requisite permit,
we shall be forced
to arrest you.
You can’t arrest me.
I didn’t do anything wrong!
Maybe not, but you might later.
Say what?!
[DRAGUNOV] Sorry young man,
but that is the law now.
And as inquisitors,
we are sworn to enforce
such laws throughout the land.
Yeah, but--
[SOLDIER]
Apprehend him!
[SOLDIERS
yelling, charging]
-[SETH yelling in pain]
-[crashing, fighting]
[growling]
Mm?
[SETH growls angrily]
Hold on, that’s mine!
What’re you doin’
with my stuff, you thief?
Lemme have it!
I want my stuff,
and I want it now!
Alright, fine!
This cage is nothin’,
-[triumphant music]
-against my Titan Punch!
[metal bars rattling]
-[music ends]
-Ahhhh...
I think I just broke a finger.
[groans]
That’s weird.
I can’t gather Fantasia.
What’s going on?
First off,
it’s a black silver cage,
designed to block Fantasia.
And secondly, we’ve taken
your gloves away, remember?
We’re well aware
of how to deal with your kind.
So what are you
gonna do with me?
You’ll spend the next ten years
in the capital dungeon.
But if you put me in a dungeon
then I won’t be able
to look for Radiant!
What’s Radiant?
Just a fairy tale that’s grown
popular among sorcerers.
It’s the place
the Nemesis come from.
-Or so they say.
-Ah. Tell me.
Do you truly believe
that such a place exists, boy?
Of course!
And once I make it there,
I’m’a crush
The Nemesis for good!
I get it.
This one’s so desperate to be
released, he’ll say anything.
No. I’m fairly sure
that this kid’s just an idiot.
You call me an idiot
all you want,
-but Alma says--!
-[DRAGUNOV] Mm-mm.
No one cared the first time
you told us.
[SETH growls]
I doubt you’ll listen,
but I feel compelled
to tell you, for your own good.
That’s not a word you should be
tossing around lightly.
Watch where you say it.
-And to whom.
-Huh?
You’d do well to stop talking,
so as not to add
to your list of crimes.
What do you mean, what crimes?
Hush. Just behave yourself.
-Sir?
-[DRAGUNOV] Hmm?
Please forgive my intrusion,
but I only wanted to ask you:
Are sorcerers really cursed?
[VICE]
Of course they are!
That’s why we inquisitors
have to watch them.
Indeed.
These are tainted beings.
Every one of them
is forever marred
by the touch of the Nemesis.
The curses they bear come
with the power to use magic.
But, they also cause all other
beings to despise them.
What? It’s not our curses
that makes you hate us,
you’re just a bunch’a
stupid jerks!
Hey! Come back, you coward!
We’re not done here!
Wait, what’s this?
A trapdoor?
Come on,
don’t put me down there.
At least lemme stay on deck!
Hey!
[groans]
It’s no use.
I guess this is why Alma
would always nag me
to keep my horns hidden.
[ALMA]
And another thing, Seth.
Where exactly do you plan
to start searching?
-[SETH] Huh?
-[ALMA] That’s not an answer.
-Well. Up maybe?
-[ALMA groans]
How ‘bout down?
-[SETH] Way below the clouds.
-[ALMA groans angrily]
Ugh...
I know where you can start.
Make your way to a flying city
called Artemis.
Yeah, why should I?
How do you expect
to find Radiant
when you don’t have
a single clue
about where to start looking?!
Oh, so you’re sayin’
if I go there,
then I’ll find some clues?!
I’m not convinced
there are clues to be found.
That said, your chances’ll
be slightly better
there than anywhere else.
What’s the place like, anyway?
It’s a research town.
Mostly populated by sorcerers.
[SETH]
Wow!
Once you get there, you should
look for someone named Yaga.
That’s a name?
[ALMA] Try to be respectful
towards him.
He’s one of the stronger
sorcerers around.
He’s gonna tell me
all of his secrets!
[YAGA]
Yaga the mighty!
[ALMA]
Assuming that Radiant is real,
he might know something.
Also, that place is fairly safe,
but make sure to avoid
the yellow cat if you can,
got it?
[SETH] She said to go
to the city of sorcerers.
To find Yaga, and something
about a yellow cat.
-[chirping]
-Huh?
[chirps]
-Ahhh!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE continues]
-Ayy!
-[SETH whimpers]
[MELIE groaning]
Huh?
♪
[MELIE yawns]
That was one great nap.
Oh! Good morning, friend!
Uh... hi there.
My name’s Seth. What’s yours?
Hi Seth, I’m Melie!
I was trying to find
my way to Island 21
of Pompo Hills
for my job,
but I ended up
getting lost somehow.
Island 21...? Wait.
Oh, believe it or not,
I was just on it.
What a coincidence!
I was planning
to meet my boss there
to help him pick up
the corpse of a Nemesis!
A Nemesis?
What kind of job do you have?
I’m a sorcerer with
the Artemis Institute.
They’re the ones who sent me.
You’re from Artemis?
Sure am!
-Whoa, what’s that?
-His name is Mister Boobrie.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
-He’s a pet?
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chittering]
He’s more like a friend.
Okay. So it’s Melie, right?
Why’d they decide to arrest you?
Aren’t you an official
Artemis sorcerer?
Well technically I’m still
in training right now.
-[SETH] Oh, gotcha.
-And since I got lost,
I’ve been separated
from the only person
who could’ve
verified my identity.
He’s an Artemis
researcher named Doc,
and I’m sure he’ll come and make
those soldiers release me
once he finds out
why I’m missing.
Good luck with that.
-[MELIE] Hey. Those horns!
-Hmm?
That’s such an awesome curse!
Uh. You think so?
Lemme guess, do you fight
by shooting magic out of them?
-Like. Puh-puh-puh-pew!
-Not even close.
Aww. Well, that’s disappointing.
What? You weirdo!
Sorry I can’t shoot death rays!
[giggling]
It’s nice to meet you, Seth!
Huh? Uh...
-Come on.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-Shake it.
-Uh...
-Eh? It won’t bite--
-[rumbling]
-[BOTH scream]
Whoa!
[DOC] Hello, gentlemen.
So, I have an ID.
There. Look.
See? That’s my face!
-Yeah. See? Take a look!
-[boinging]
Guess who has their own ID?
I do!
[DOC] If these Inquisition
stiffs find out
I’m carrying Nemesis remains,
that’ll be it for old Doc.
[MELIE]
Oh wow, Doc!
-That was fast!
-Huh?
Hey! I was just telling Seth
you’d come to rescue me!
[shuddering]
What the heck are you
doing in that cell, Melie?
I told ‘em I was gonna
help you pick up a Nemesis,
-and they locked me up!
-[VICE] Interesting.
[DOC yelling]
[VICE] So I take it this girl
is with you.
Say what? That girl?!
I’ve never seen her
before in my life!
[nervously laughs]
-Y’know this guy?
-Mm-hmm.
[DOC]
That’s not true!
You’re lying, she’s lying,
stop lying,
-you weird, crazy stranger!
-[DRAGUNOV] About your cargo.
I don’t suppose it would be the
Nemesis that fell on Island 21.
[VICE]
Captain.
I thank you for
saving us the trouble
of having to track it down.
Go ahead and cage him as well.
-[VICE] Sir!
-[DOC] What?!
[whimpering]
I was just doin’
my job, I swear.
I only went in
to clean up the thing
‘cause they asked me to!
[DOC screaming]
Hold on!
[metal door closes]
[DOC]
Please, good sir,
there’s been some
kind of mistake.
I’m not a criminal!
Can’t we talk about this?
I assure you, I have nothing
but respect
for The Inquisition
and the noble work you do!
-Hey, Doc.
-Huh?
What’d they arrest you for?
How is that a question?!
They locked me up ‘cause you
went and blabbed on me!
-[MELIE laughs]
-[SETH] Hmm?
Oh, that’s Doc,
he’s my boss.
I’ve been assisting him
with his Nemesis research.
Hey!
Hasn’t that big mouth of yours
gotten us in enough trouble?
What the heck possessed you
to tell the Inquisition
what we were up to?
-Well. They asked me.
-Why did I even send you?!
Tryin’ to rush this job along
definitely backfired on me!
[sighs]
There’s no gettin’
out of this one.
Wait a second.
Were you at Pompo Hills earlier?
Huh?
Depends who’s asking.
Well, my name’s Seth!
And I’m the hunter that beat
that Nemesis you picked up.
-What?
-So, I guess you must be
an Artemis sorcerer
just like Melie, right?
I’m a researcher,
and I’m good at my job.
It’s as simple as that.
I heard I could get
some remains on that island.
So I went down
and picked ‘em up.
What did you plan
to do with them?
Turn them in.
A solid corpse
is worth good money.
That said...
this one was
pretty much shredded!
Which means it’s worth
practically nothing!
Oh, too bad.
That part wasn’t me though.
[groans]
My poor wallet.
So. Why don’t you just
-hunt them yourself, then?
-Huh?
Then, you could sell
a whole bunch.
I don’t hunt The Nemesis,
‘cause I don’t wanna die.
[SETH]
Mm?
[DOC]
Giving my all. Taking risks.
Getting rocks in my shoes.
I can’t stand
that sort of thing!
I’m perfectly okay
leaving that type a’ work
to sorcerers like you.
Monsters fall
from the sky like rain,
and all you Nemesis Hunters
can do is play catch-up.
That’s just the way
of the world, kid.
You track down and destroy
The Nemesis one at a time.
It’s a never-ending task,
but doin’ it’s the only reason
sorcerers are even tolerated.
[SETH] You really think
it’ll never end?
-[DOC] Course I do.
-[scheming chirp]
Then wait until ya hear my plan!
What’s that?
I’m gonna find Radiant and
introduce it to my right fist!
Radiant?
[giggling]
Your words make you sound
like a crazy person,
but you say it all
so confidently!
Good luck.
That place is just a fairy tale.
It doesn’t matter
what you think it is.
I promised Alma, I’d destroy it.
Hm? Alma?!
Wait...
Are you tryin’ to tell me
you’re the apprentice
of that mean old sorcerer lady
from Pompo Hills?
Well, specifically,
Alma’s more like my mom.
I mean she did raise me,
after all.
What exactly are you?
So are you goin’ back to Artemis
after we get outta here?
Would you mind
if I tagged along?
I’m not goin’ anywhere, kid,
I’m stuck in a cage.
Huh? Who’s there?
-[happy chirps]
-[MELIE] Mister Boobrie!
[MELIE gasps] Lookit!
-[DOC] Whaa--?
-[SETH] Hey, no way!
Alright!
Way to go, Mister Boobrie,
you did great! [giggles]
I can’t believe I’m doing this.
This is actually insane.
If I get caught,
they’ll execute me.
Not to interrupt
your complaining,
but we should probably
get a move on.
I know that!
[wind whistling]
[GROUP panting, yelling]
I don’t know about you guys,
but my heart’s racing.
I feel like mine’s about
to sputter out on me.
So, should we make a break
for Doc’s ship now, or what?
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps determinedly]
Before I can do that, I gotta
reclaim some stolen property.
-[MELIE gasps]
-[DOC grunts]
Nothing in here.
Aw man.
Where the heck
did they stash my broom?
This is dumb. Like really dumb.
We need to get out of here.
[footsteps]
[ALL gasp]
-That was totally your stuff!
-Uh-huh!
Don’t just walk up,
they’ll catch you!
I wouldn’t care
if it were just you,
but at this rate,
you’ll get me caught too!
Yeah but, I want my things back.
-[DRAGUNOV] Hello there.
-[ALL gasp, whimper]
Out for a little stroll, are we?
Guess we’re caught.
This would’ve
gone better for you
if you’d stayed put and behaved.
Against this eye of mine,
there is no hiding.
[door slams shut]
Capture them!
[SOLDIERS
yelling, charging]
[MELIE, DOC and SETH scream]
Jail-breaking is
a serious offense.
Yeah, like you’re one to talk.
You guys stole all my stuff!
[DRAGUNOV]
Oh, did we?
I know what this
looks like, Captain,
but I’ve done
nothing wrong, I swear!
You see, the kid
forced me to escape!
[SETH groans]
Right, Melie?
Please give us our ship back!
Seth has to get to Radiant
as quick as he can!
-[chirping]
-[DOC whimpers]
No.
[yelling]
[groans]
Fine!
Titan Punch!
Ahh!
[SOLDIERS scream]
Hm?
[grunts]
-Grab my gear for me!
-[BOTH] Huh?
[DOC and MELIE scream]
[crashing]
[groans]
Oh, cool. Found my ID.
[whoosh]
[MELIE]
Ow!
[VICE]
Archers, ready?
[gasps]
And loose!
Here! Repulse!
Looks like a shield spell.
Holy cow, that’s amazing, Melie!
Defensive magic like this shield
is kind of my specialty.
Fire second volley!
So, just how many arrows
can you block?
Uh. Probably only this many.
[SETH screams]
[explosion]
Draw your blades!
[VICE]
Seize them!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[breathes heavily]
It would appear that this
is checkmate...huh?
Don’t worry, Melie,
you’ll be fine.
[determined voice] I don’t need
your reassurance, kid.
Huh?
We just gotta blow ‘em away.
Right? Sounds easy enough to me!
Ahhh--
-[explosion]
-[screaming]
[DOC whimpers]
[SETH grunts]
[wind rushing]
What the heck was
that all about?
-It’s her curse.
-Huh?
[DOC] When Melie comes
under extreme stress,
her personality does
a total 180.
-[SETH] Really?!
-[overjoyed chirps]
I’ll torment you all
you want later, Boobrie,
at the moment
I’m busy with these jerks.
Showing your true colors, witch?
Give us back our ship now.
Or I’ll grind you
into a pulp.
We of the Inquisition
shan’t falter.
It is our sacred duty
to stand against cursed
beings like yourself.
[MELIE]
Oh, really?
You’d best watch
your step, then.
Huh? Wait. What’s going on?
Brace yourself.
Not that it’ll help.
[echoing]
Ignis Rumpere!
-[explosion]
-[SOLDIERS scream]
You’ll pay for that,
you scoundrel!
Who’s grabbing me?!
[SOLDIER #1]
Sorry, sir!
[SOLDIER #2]
Vice Captain!
Please don’t let go!
[VICE] Just wait till
I get back up there!
[whimpers]
They’ll put a price
on all our heads!
So cool!
[SETH]
Hey! My stuff!
-Hm.
-[DRAGUNOV] A curse, eh?
This is the problem
with you sorcerers.
No sense of accountability.
You should’ve kept
your true nature hidden.
Blame your curse
all you want,
I don’t care why you tried
to murder my men.
By this miracle of God,
I sentence you to death
by this arrow.
[screaming]
This day could not
get any worse!
-Hey, you!
-[BOTH] Huh?
[SETH] Get away from Melie
right this second!
[DOC]
Don’t do it, Seth! Calm down!
Let’s just all
apologize together!
Titan...
Punch!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL yelling]
[grunts]
[SETH]
Doc! Melie! Let’s go!
[DOC panicking]
I’m gonna need you guys
to hang on tight, okay?
[air whooshing]
[MELIE] Don’t tell me
what to do, ya damn brat!
[DOC screams]
[DOC yelling]
This isn’t my fault!
I’ve done nothing wrong!
[DRAGUNOV]
Not bad.
They win this round.
-[VICE] Captain!
-Hmm?
The cannon is ready.
Shall I shoot them down?
[DRAGUNOV]
Forget it.
They’re well out of range.
[VICE groans]
Considering how close
we are to Artemis,
we can’t do anything too bold.
That horned boy...
He used magic
with his bare hands.
[chirp]
[normal voice] Sorry.
Whenever
I get too worked up,
my personality takes a turn.
It’s okay.
And that’s the trouble
with you.
It’s why you’re never
gonna be a true sorcerer.
[MELIE cries]
Yeah. I’ll try to
do better, sir.
Are you kidding?
That was awesome!
Huh?
You kicked those guys’ butts!
They all went flying.
You’ve gotta teach me
that spell sometime!
Uh. Okay.
Really? Aw, yeah!
-Yeah, yeah, yeah...
-Oh no, wait! I should tell you
that normally I only use
defensive magic.
-[whimpers]
-[SETH] I wanna learn somethin’
that hits with a bang!
You’re weird. And funny.
Oh hey! Doc?
How much longer’s it gonna be
until we reach Artemis anyway?
We’re close.
You should see it any second.
[SETH]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[SETH]
So that’s the Artemis Institute!
The city of Sorcerers!
[NARRATOR] Seth and company
finally arrive at Artemis,
the city of Sorcerers.
At first glance, it looks like
a wondrous, dazzling place.
But in reality,
it’s a cutthroat town
where everything
comes at a price.
After getting conned
into taking on a massive debt,
how will Seth find the resolve
to press forward
in his adventure?
Next time on Radiant.
“A Paradise
of Wisdom and Hope.”