[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[SETH] What?
How am I s'posed to afford that?
No wonder it's covered
in dust, dude.
Charging this much
is practically robbery.
[SHOPKEEPER] Folding brooms are
legitimately expensive!
You don't know anything,
so mind what you say!
[SETH]
Huh?
[ALMA]
That's odd.
Thought you already
had a broom,
and not the kind that folds.
[SETH]
This one's for Melie.
We lost everything we had on us
back in Rumble Town.
[ALMA]
Mm-hmm...
So, about this Melie girl...
I won't repeat
what her letter said,
but you really did
give her a scare.
-[SETH gasps]
-[ALMA sighs]
Making a girl worry like that...
thought I taught you better,
but it seems I was wrong.
What? But why would anyone
be worried about me?
I'm good enough at magic
to take care of myself now.
[SETH grunting]
Good grief.
That's enough foolin' around.
Let's go.
Wait a second.
Where are we going?
You're supposed to take me
to see Yaga today, remember?
Oh yeah, I forgot!
You two go way back, right?
What were you plannin'
to talk to him about?
It has something to do
with Radiant.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
"In Search of the Future"
-[ALMA exhales]
-[SETH] Huh?
[ALMA]
The heck is this?
[SETH]
Hmm...
It says, "Please don't
look for me."
[ALMA]
That senile coward.
Can't believe he went this far
to avoid facing me!
I'm confused.
Isn't he an old friend of yours?
I've known him a long time.
He's been deathly scared of me
for most of it.
-[SETH] Huh?
-Gimme the note.
What else does it say?
"Alma...
"it has been quite a long time.
"It's regrettable that, by
the time you read this letter,
"I'll be far away.
"Somewhere that you
could never find me,
no matter how hard you--"
Get to the point,
you old bastard!
[YAGA] "Tell Seth to go
to Caislean Merlin.
"I have it on good authority
that the Knight-sorcerers
"who call it home
are searching for Radiant.
They should be able to aid him
in his quest."
Caislean Merlin, what's that?
That'd be the capital
of Cyfandir.
Which is a nation on
the neighboring continent.
Ohh...
[YAGA]
"He should be warned, though.
"Perhaps as a result
of recent events,
"the Inquisition
is planning to begin
"a sorcerer-hunt
in Caislean Merlin.
They're desperate, it seems."
The Inquisition lost
a lot of influence.
It's likely that they're just
doing this
to try and salvage
their reputation.
So, they're gonna make
scapegoats out of sorcerers
who've done nothing wrong?
Gah, no way
we can let that happen!
[YAGA]
"Alma...
"In the short time
I've worked with him,
"the apprentice you sent me
has developed a great deal.
"We've reached a point
"where what happens next
will depend on him.
"He's as foolish as they come,
to be sure,
"but I have faith in the boy,
"and I believe that
he'll find his answer,
"long as he carves
his own path forward.
"Which, in this old man's
opinion,
is what it means to search
for Radiant in the first place."
[ALMA]
Hmph.
-Are you all right?
-[ALMA gasps]
I was just thinkin'.
What else did he write in there?
Anything about where
he thinks Radiant might be?
He says that you should carve
your own path forward.
What the heck's
that s'posed to mean?
It means that from here on out,
you should start deciding
what's right for yourself.
[SETH exhales]
[DOC]
No way! Not happenin'!
Why do you even wanna go
to Caislean Merlin?
And what could've hit you
on the head
so hard that you thought
I might wanna go with you?
The Inquisition's planning to go
after all those sorcerers,
so they're gonna need
all the help they can get!
We can't just stand by
while it happens!
There ain't a day of the week
the Inquisitors aren't
goin' after someone!
We can't always be chargin' off
to stop 'em.
[huffs]
What's your problem?
The three of us are supposed
to search for Radiant together,
did you forget?
[DOC] When did I agree to that?
Where's the contract?
-Why would I sign it?!
-[PINK GUY hums]
[DOC] I let you stick around me
for financial reasons only,
and I'm reluctant about that!
-[PINK GUY sighs]
-[SETH] Come on.
If you really want me
to help you with this,
then before you do anything,
you gotta make enough
dough to pay off
every cent
that I owe in your name.
Once you've settled that,
I might be willing to accept
your request as a job.
[SETH groans]
Look Doc,
I have to tell you,
I don't have any problem
with helping him, personally--
I understand that, Melie,
but at the end of the day,
you need to remember that
you're here as my assistant.
I get it, but I can't
just leave Seth
to face danger
by himself, you know?
It's not like he has to face
danger, he's lookin' for it!
This numbskull tracked
down danger
all the way
to another continent!
-[SETH growls]
-I'm not going!
There's no way you can
convince me
to do somethin' scary like that!
Oh my goodness.
That doesn't sound like you,
Doc, what happened?
Oh, nothin' to worry about.
I was just explaining to young
Seth here
that bein' careless
isn't the same as bein' brave!
That's seems like good advice.
You have such a mature outlook.
[PAPA] Ha! Sounds to me
like he's bein' chicken.
Makes sense,
he can't even use magic!
-[DOC growls]
-[PAPA] What?
Be nice, Papa.
Doc's not a fighter,
he's a researcher.
That's correct,
I am a man of science!
I've devoted my life
to investigating
the many mysteries
of the world we live in.
-You expect me to buy that?
-[DOC] Uhh...
About my latest project, Melie.
Yeah?
[DOC] Could you run
a little errand for me?
I need ya to pick some...
spotted mushrooms, for science.
Well I don't mind,
but do you need them
right this instant?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I've got an enormous debt
to start payin' off, by myself.
So, I need to concoct somethin'
that'll rake in money and fast.
I am so busy.
-[SETH groans]
-Come on, Doc.
Won't you at least
try to understand
how Seth feels right now?
Huh?! What about how I feel,
I almost died!
I know, and I'm sure it was
really scary for you, but--
It was! Have you ever been born
through your own stomach?!
Stop lecturing me
and go do your job!
Go on, you're not changin'
my mind about this.
[MELIE]
Hmm...
why do you have to be
so stubborn?!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I think you upset her.
[SETH sighs]
What's your problem?
You're supposed to be
our friend, so act like it.
That's what I'm doin'.
You were lucky to make it out
of Rumble Town alive.
But even now, you're planning
to go pick fights
with more
dangerous thaumaturges,
-and psychopaths like Konrad.
-[SETH gasps]
Think of Melie.
Do you really wanna put her into
even more danger than you have?
[SETH breathes shakily]
Hmm...
♪
[wind rushing]
[SETH] Yeah... I was lucky
to make it out of there alive.
If I really wanna find Radiant,
it's possible that fights
like that will be unavoidable.
The worst part's that I still
have no idea what Radiant is.
The Nemesis aren't evil,
not in the slightest.
So please, don't treat them
like monsters.
[SETH]
I don't get it.
If the Nemesis aren't evil,
then what the heck are they?
Hmm?
Well... I guess that's even
more reason to keep going.
If I wanna learn more
about the Nemesis,
there's no better place
to start than Radiant!
-[SETH chuckles]
-[MAJESTY] Ahh!
It's the hero of
the Rumble Town riot!
[SETH screams]
[groans]
[SETH]
Majesty!
One King to another,
you don't "appurr"
to be "feline"
so good right meow.
If you'd like to re-finance
some of your debt,
I'm here for you.
Fees may apply,
-but your interest rates--
-[SETH] No.
This has nothing to do
with my debt.
[MAJESTY cackles]
Then what's the matter?
It isn't like you
to act this way.
How exactly am I supposed
to be acting?
If I had to describe
your "ar-cat-ype,"
I suppose it would be
a snot-nosed kid
-making weird noises
-[SETH growls]
with a "purr-pawsterous" grin
on his face.
What the heck
do you think I am?!
[SETH]
Oh--
Are you planning to leave
for Caislean Merlin soon?
How did you know?
I didn't become king of Artemis
through cuteness alone.
And since you yourself are about
as sharp as a sack of wet mice,
guessing what you plan
to do next was easy.
[SETH]
Hmph...
Hey, from what you know
of Caislean Merlin,
does it seem dangerous?
[MAJESTY]
Hmm...
aside from Artemis,
there is no place in this world
that can claim to be
safe for sorcerers.
[lightly gasps]
Cyfandir is no exception.
Wherever you go in your travels,
you'll be "purr-secuted."
Why is that? Why do people
treat us sorcerers
like we're barely even human?
You've seen
the reason "fur" that
with your own eyes.
Human beings are pre-disposed
to hate and fear
those who are unlike them.
Oh, speaking of mistreating
your fellow man.
I went ahead and added
the "clawst" of our recent party
to your debt.
What?
You're kidding!
If anything, my debt
should've been lowered!
[MAJESTY]
Don't forget that I arranged
for a train to bring you home.
Even if we put that aside,
the entailed cost of your use
of our facilities
still outweighs
any reward you earned.
[ALMA] Still the same greedy
fat-cat I remember.
-Eh, Majesty?
-[SETH lightly gasps]
Oh-- Alma!
[cackles]
Hello there!
About time you decided
to visit home.
You know full well that
this place isn't my home.
Artemis is a home
for every sorcerer alive,
whether they
contribute or not.
You might've liked it here,
if you'd "pawsed"
before judging.
Ugh... I'm only here at
the moment because of my work.
[MAJESTY]
Tell me "somefang,"
is this the child
you spoke of?
The one you raised yourself?
That he is.
-[SETH] Huh?
-[MAJESTY cackles]
Be sure that you come back here
to settle your "tabby."
All right, King of Debt?
[lightly gasps]
You don't actually think he'd
run off without paying, do you?
Of course I don't.
It won't even cross
the snot-nosed imbecile's mind.
True...
My point is I can't have you
dying out there.
Scratch that-- even if you die,
I still want my money.
That's harsh!
And by the way,
my nose isn't snotty at all!
[MAJESTY cackles]
[SETH straining, stammering
in anger]
[GRIMM]
Caislean Merlin, eh?
Given the nature of his quest,
he's bound to run into
the Knight-Sorcerers there.
In that case...
-[siren blaring]
-[GRIMM] Hmm?
-[BOTH] Hmm?
-What's going on?
[siren continues]
Those look like Nemesis eggs.
-How are there so many?
-[MAJESTY] Hmm...
It would appear that Artemis
has entered
a fairly dangerous
part of the sky.
Thought this city
was supposed to be safe.
[MAJESTY cackles]
[MAJESTY]
Deploy the defensive barrier!
[energy charging]
Mobilize our forces!
Intercept the foe!
[SETH]
Hmph...
Tone it down, people!
What's with all the ruckus
out here?!
-Oh, dear...
-Got a business to run.
Nemesis eggs,
and so many.
Hope they don't break
through the barrier.
Think they can handle this?
Yeah.
The Artemis Institute
is well protected.
If you're sure...
-[ALMA] Seth.
-[SETH] Hmm?
I'm heading back
to my ship for now.
Try not to do anything stupid
while I'm gone.
Uh-- right.
[explosions]
[sighs]
[NICK]
What's the matter, Seth?
You look a bit uneasy.
[SETH excitedly]
Nick, hey.
Care to explain why
you're just standing there?
Wait, I don't suppose it's
because you're frozen in terror?
But if that's the case,
then all those stories
of your exploits in Rumble Town
must've been made up.
Right?
[BOTH HENCHMEN] Nice one,
Nick, you could be a detective!
Well, I, for one,
already knew you were
a cowardly little charlatan.
I'll take care of the scary
Nemeses,
you just watch and learn.
Wait, don't attack them!
I found out from Hameline
that not all Nemeses are bad!
Huh?
The hell you trying to say?!
Bringing an end to the scourge
of the Nemesis
is what any sorcerer who's
worth their salt lives for!
[HENCHMAN A]
Yeah, Nick, that's the spirit!
[HENCHMAN B] Wow!
That's one heck of a reason
to live, Nick!
-[whooshing]
-[SETH gasps]
[gasps]
-[loud boom]
-[NICK] Gah!
Looks like one of them
slipped past our defenses!
I'd have stopped it,
but you distracted me.
[SETH huffs]
-[DOC] Hey!
-[SETH] Huh?
[panting]
Seth!
[SETH]
What's wrong?!
It's about Melie!
She went off to pick mushrooms
on an island over that way.
You mean she's not here?
-[nervously exhales]
-[DOC] That's right.
And she might not even know
what's going on.
[NICK scoffs]
Sounds like your friend's gotten
herself into quite the pickle.
[SETH] I'm sorry about this,
but Imma need to borrow
your broom, Nick!
[NICK screams]
-[NICK groans]
-[NICK'S HENCHMEN] Nick!
[SETH]
Thanks! I'll return this later,
-I promise!
-[broom whooshing]
[NICK yelps]
Hey!
Get back here.
Doc is really being a jerk.
If he needs these mushrooms
so badly,
he should be
picking them with me.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps
in agreement]
[MISTER BOOBRIE]
Huh?
[whooshing]
-[crash]
-[MELIE screams]
-[BOTH whimpering]
-[MELIE] Huh?
[MELIE]
Wait...
that looks like a Nemesis egg!
[crackling]
-[explosion]
-[NEMESIS roars]
[NEMESIS snarls]
[BOTH gasp]
[screaming]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-Thanks, Mister Boobrie!
Try to hang in there!
Huh?
[screams]
[NEMESIS roars]
[whimpering]
[SETH]
Phew! Melie, Boobrie.
You all right?
You found us.
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[BOTH gasp]
[NEMESIS growls]
That looks like
a strong one.
Make sure to hang on tight,
okay?
Right!
[NEMESIS roars]
[NEMESIS growls]
[explosion]
[NEMESIS roars]
I just can't shake it.
I have an idea.
[NEMESIS roars]
[NEMESIS growls]
[SETH grunts]
[MELIE]
Gravem Carserem!
[NEMESIS squawks]
[MELIE]
Here's your chance, Seth!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[SETH]
Right!
Skull... Attack!
[explosion]
[NEMESIS groans]
We actually beat it!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[water sloshing]
-[SETH sighs]
[SETH]
Please be calm.
Don't force us to kill you.
-[MELIE] Seth...
-[SETH gasps]
Thank you so much for coming!
If it wasn't for you,
we'd be in that thing's belly.
You were
seriously amazing, Seth,
-I don't know how to thank you!
-[SETH gasps]
-[NEMESIS bleats]
-[SETH] Melie!
[MELIE]
Huh?!
[SETH grunts]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-Oh, no!
[SETH straining]
♪
[muffled scream]
Let him go!
[SETH growls]
[explosion]
[BOTH scream]
[SETH roaring]
[ALMA grunts]
This isn't one of
my usual headaches.
What's wrong, Seth?
[BOTH roaring]
[boom]
[explosion]
-Whoa, Seth...
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[sighs]
[exhales]
Huh?
[breathes shakily]
What did I do?
Not again.
[BOTH whimper]
♪
[GRIMM] That boy's power is
in equal parts unnatural...
and dangerous.
This mystery warrants
further investigation.
Grimm will have to see more.
♪
[sighs]
Hmph.
[SHOPKEEPER humming]
[SHOPKEEPER] Oh, another day
of hard work comes to a close.
Oh, how I've been
looking forward
to an evening
of peace and quiet.
-[chuckles]
-[SETH] Please, wait!
[SHOPKEEPER exclaims]
I wanna get that
broom after all.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
Hmph.
Morning Seth!
Do ya wanna come
get some coffee? Uh--
Huh...?
His stuff's gone.
[whimpers]
[sighs]
[lightly gasps]
[SETH] "Before I say
anything else,
"thanks for everything.
"I guess I'm just starting
to realize
"how dangerous
this journey'll be.
"And I don't wanna cause you
any more trouble.
So, I'm leaving."
-[whimpers]
[SETH] "The broom on the table
is a parting gift.
I hope you like it."
[MELIE crying]
Why?
[ALMA] Starting to wish you'd
told them goodbye?
[SETH]
Hmph...
if I had, then I would've
wanted to stay with them.
And I can't.
Least not as I am.
Until I learn to control
this power,
I'm just as likely to hurt
my friends as to help them.
So, there's no other choice.
Fair enough.
You've made your decision,
it doesn't matter to me.
[SETH sighs]
Seth took off.
And he didn't even bother
tellin' us goodbye.
-That's awful.
-[PAPA groans]
The boy had a lot on his mind,
and that includes all of you.
He didn't wish to cause you
-any further trouble.
-[DOC] Huh?
That's my guess.
Yeah, the kid could be
a nuisance sometimes,
but I didn't want him to just--
No, come to think of it,
I'm better off havin'
that brat outta my hair.
I'm actually relieved.
[DOC laughing]
[MELBA]
Are you sure you're okay?
Putting up a tough front, I see.
♪
This is just the beginning,
so best of luck.
[PIODON] There's something
I want to learn about,
and it's in the direction
you're heading.
Show me the answer...
Seth.
♪