[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[MELIE] Not much time
has passed since the conflict
in Rumble Town,
but we're starting to settle
back into life at Artemis.
Thing is...
Seth has been acting
pretty strange.
[NARRATOR]
"The World That You Changed."
-[sips]
-Ahh.
Oh, my, oh, my, oh, my, oh, my,
oh, my, oh, my, oh, my!
[laughter]
Welcome back!
It's great to see you!
-[PAPA] Uh-huh.
-Yeah, right back at ya!
Has business been good?
I hope you and your dad
are well.
Oh, we've been swell.
It's great to see you kids
are safe!
Hmm? Wait a sec.
Shouldn't Doc be with you too?
[DOC shuddering]
[PAPA]
Come to think of it.
Ahh, well, ya see, Doc--
-He's behind me.
-[DOC and MELIE gasp]
-Here.
-[MELIE] Oh, boy.
-[MELBA] Really?
-[DOC] Uh?
Whaat? You telling me
that annoying pest
-turned into this baby?
-[DOC sighs]
[MELIE]
Yeah, turns out his curse
makes him molt a little bit.
Oh, my goodness.
-[DOC] No. It's over.
-[MELBA] Doc.
-[DOC whimpering] It's all over.
-[MELBA] How? How?
How did you get so cute?!
-[DOC] Huh?
-[BOTH] Uh...
[MELBA]
Wow, you are so adorable!
[DOC]
Yeah?
Ya think so?
[MELBA making cutesy sounds]
[DOC giggling]
[DOC] This is the closest
I've ever been to Miss Melba.
This level of intimacy
is something
I could never have dreamed
of as an adult.
I got mixed feelings about that,
but for now, I'm happy!
Uh-oh, smell that?
-You need your diaper changed.
-[DOC] Huh?!
Don't worry, Doc,
there's no need to be shy.
[DOC]
You say that, but uh-
[MELBA] Hey, is it all right if
I change Doc's diaper for you?
-[DOC exclaims]
-[MELIE] Yeah, of course.
Are you sure you want to?
[MELBA]
Just leave it to me!
Whoa! Hold on. I-I--
I'm not ready.
It sure was nice
of her to offer.
Yeah, you're right
about that much.
[DOC]
But...
Melba's really gonna see me
in my birthday suit?
-No! Not like this!
-[heart beating loudly]
-Not covered in--
-Sit still now, Doc.
Get in there, Papa!
Can do.
Huh?
[PAPA] I have experience with
this sort of work.
I'm gonna wipe that bottom
as clean as a sanded down board.
Wha--? No, wait,
come on!
-[PAPA] Hya!
-[DOC screaming]
[PAPA giggling]
[silverware clanging]
-[SETH sighs]
-[DOC whimpering]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps, belches]
That meal was
absolutely delicious!
I think
Mr. Melba Papa's cooking
might be the best
in this whole town!
Well of course it is!
Whoa, don't get cocky, okay?
That said, we're very glad
you enjoyed your meal.
After all, Papa and I did work
hard to make it special.
Aw, did you really?
-Yeah, of course we did!
-[DOC continues whimpering]
This was the least we could do
to offer our thanks
to the heroes who
saved Rumble Town.
[DOC]
Huh?
The heroes who saved
Rumble Town,
-are you talking about us?
-[SETH exhales]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
-[MELBA] Why didn't you hear?
-[DOC] Hm?
[MELBA]
You three are the talk of the
Artemis Institute right now!
It's a big deal.
[DOC exhales]
[PAPA grunts]
See, just take a look
at this article!
There's your picture!
[MELIE] Wow! We're actually
in the newspaper!
That's amazing!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[DOC]
Let's see what it says.
"Artemis's King of Debt defeats
corrupt Inquisition leader
and evil Domitor
in Rumble Town."
"Not only did the King of Debt
liberate the people
"from Captain Konrad
de Marbourg's tyranny,
"he also saved them
from a vicious Domitor
and her army of Nemeses."
I thought you were
the Debt King.
Well, apparently, it's Seth now.
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps in agreement]
[MELIE] I never
expected us to end up
in the spotlight like this.
It feels kinda strange,
to be honest.
A "vicious Domitor," huh?
[SETH] That's what they're
saying she was?
That's how she'll be remembered?
[MELIE]
Seth...
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps, concerned]
[DOC]
Aw...
[ALL]
Uh?
-[ALL] Huh?
-[explosion]
[MELIE]
Is that Master Lord Majesty?!
-[MELBA] I think it is!
-[MAJESTY clearing hairball]
[MAJESTY]
Ahem!
Greetings,
beloved children of Artemis.
I want you to know that
your sovereign
is immensely proud
of your recent achievements.
So proud in fact,
that I have decided
to demonstrate my gratitude
by hosting a party for you
this very evening at my castle!
[MELIE]
No puns?
So "kitten" my palace,
and witness our "expurrt"
telling of the "hiss-toric tail"
of your "fur-vent" battle
for the "furrydom"
of Rumble Town!
-Meow, meow, meow!
-[ALL gasp]
[MELIE]
A party at the castle!
I’m sure it’s gonna be
super glamorous! [squeals]
Don't forget that it's being
planned by Master Lord Majesty.
We shouldn't assume that he'd
throw us a party for free.
[MELIE]
We didn't ask him to throw it.
No way he would
charge us this time.
[DOC] I have
a bad feeling about this!
Oh, wow, a party?
-Well, that sounds fun!
-[DOC] Huh?!
You should come along with us,
Melba, it'll be exciting!
-[DOC gasps]
-[MELBA] Hmm.
-Would that be okay with you?
-[PAPA] Hmm...
-No way!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
So... Melba's goin'
to the party now?
[MELBA]
Oh!
Yes! Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh, ho, yeah!
[PAPA chuckling]
What a man!
Excuse me, might I be
able to cut in?
Oh... I'm sorry, but
I don't think that'll work.
I mean, I'd have loved to dance
with you before,
but you're a bit
too short right now.
[DOC exclaims, heartbroken]
-[DOC] Wait! No!
-[MELBA and MAN laughing]
[DOC] Don't do this, please!
Don't go with him!
Come back to me!
We can dance just fine
if I stand on your shoes!
I say we should do it!
We could learn quite a lot
from seeing the food
they serve at the castle.
You can be social
while I handle the espionage.
-[DOC sobbing]
-Sounds great.
-I would love that.
-Then, it's decided!
Let's go to the party together
and have a great time!
[ALL but DOC]
Yeah!
[giggles]
I guess this means I should
pick out a nice outfit.
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps, panicked]
[SETH]
Ahhh...
Look at what you're doing!
You're gonna eat
Mister Boobrie!
[MELIE] Put the sandwich
down right now!
Mister Boobrie is not food!
Not food!
-Let him go!
-Mm-ahh...
[PARTY GOERS
chatter, indistinct]
[MELIE]
Look at all these people!
[MELIE giggles]
And they're all dressed
so beautifully, too.
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps in agreement]
So... why do I have
to wear this stuff?
-[DOC] Huh?
-Because it looks great on you!
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps in agreement]
Thanks, but I feel like
I'm suffocating.
Hey, you stop with the
complainin', will ya?
I'll have you know that's
the best dang suit I got!
-Oh, by the way.
-[DOC] Huh?
Is it me, or did you get
a little bigger?
It took this long to notice?!
Well, actually...
[MELIE]
You sure about this?
You're a really cute baby.
[DOC] I know I am, but I need
to dance with Miss Melba,
and I can't
when I'm like this!
Uh... could you ever?
My point is that I need to grow
up again, whatever it takes!
[SHOPKEEPER]
Hi! Are you customers?
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
Sure are! Hook me up
with a growth potion, will ya?
We have those in stock,
but perhaps such things
are not for you!
They're expensive,
you baby!
Heh! You want money?
Here!
[SHOPKEEPER]
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
Just a moment, please!
[MELIE] Hey, Doc.
Where'd you get that money?
[DOC]
It's my emergency stash.
[SHOPKEEPER] Thank you
for waiting, good sir!
Here's the growth potion
requested. Enjoy!
Nice!
Once I drink this,
I can reclaim my manhood!
And when Doc is back...
[DOC chuckles, charmingly]
Good evening, beautiful.
You have the charm
of a watermelon,
and all the fragrance
of a ripe banana.
It would be my honor
if you graced me with a dance.
Yes! But of course!
From now on, I'm your princess
and you're my prince.
[PAPA]
He's our prince.
Oh...
I like the sound of that.
[chuckling]
Down the hatch then!
[gulping]
-[ALL scream]
-[MELIE] Doc?! You okay?!
Hang in there, Doc.
Just try to be strong.
It'll all be over soon,
probably.
[roaring]
Yup.
That's how that little
cookie crumbled.
You didn't explain why
Doc's still a kid, though.
Well, apparently, the growth
potion's effect
is completely random.
-You're kidding.
-Nah, it's true.
There's no tellin' what age
those things'll take you to.
Huh...
well, then it sounds to me
like you should've just taken
another potion.
What?! You think
I could do something
that scary two times?!
Besides! What if the next potion
I drank aged me too much?
I could've ended up becoming
a doddering old man!
These old bones can still dance.
Yeah, fair point.
I gave it my best shot,
but I'm still too small
to go dancin' with Melba.
[DOC crying, whimpering]
You're okay, don't let it
get'cha down, Doc.
Hey! I bet sweets'll
cheer you up.
[MELIE]
Just look at all these pastries!
They were each handmade
by the most famous pâtissiers
-in Artemis Academy!
-[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[SETH] They've got a lot
of fancy dinner foods, too.
[DOC] And I recognize the faces
of some prominent researchers.
This is already everything
I hoped it would be.
Seth? Let's have
a good time, okay?
Yeah, okay.
[SETH and PARTY GOERS]
Huh?
[MELIE]
I guess Majesty's gonna show.
[PARTY GOERS murmuring]
[MC]
Ladies and gentlemen!
It is my distinguished pleasure
to welcome you
to the most majestic
party of the year!
-[PARTY GOERS cheering]
-[MC imitating air horn]
What, what!
And now, to kick off the show,
let's get the star of the party
up here on this stage!
He is our very own
King of Debt...
Seth!
[fanfare plays]
[PARTY GOERS cheer, chanting]
King of Debt! King of Debt!
King of debt!
King of debt! King of debt!
Neow! Come and take
your place on the stage.
No need to be shy, brave hero!
[SETH yelling]
-Good luck, Seth!
-[DOC and MISTER BOOBRIE panic]
[SETH struggling, yelling]
-[skidding]
-[SETH groans]
Heroic as ever.
Amazing! The boy plunges
face-first into danger!
[MAJESTY]
That's our hero for you!
Always one to throw
"claw-tion" to the wind.
[PARTY GOERS cheering]
[SETH]
Ow...
Hey, what's the deal?
That hurt!
Listen closely, everyone!
"Fur" I'm about to regale you
with the story of a hero.
Before coming here,
the boy was just an ordinary
sorcerer from Pompo Hills.
[MC]
Mm-hmm!
But then, to his great fortune,
this hapless bumpkin
was lucky enough
to meet the great and benevolent
leader of Artemis!
Tell me, who do I speak of?
Does anyone know his name?
[PARTY GOERS, in unison]
Master Lord Majesty!
That's correct, it was me!
That feckless young idiot
knelt before
my "impurrvious" presence
in awe.
I magnanimously extended
my paw to his hand.
Okay, guys, ya didn't tell me
we were putting on a whole play!
[MAJESTY]
After that "fur-mative" moment,
his life changed for good.
[MAJESTY] He bested
a mighty Inquisition Captain.
Defended the innocent
against a Domitor.
Struck down a Thaumaturge
with a single swipe.
And after all that,
he even managed to capture
dozens of Nemeses alive!
[PARTY GOERS in awe, murmuring]
But don't forget
his greatest achievement,
which is breaking the record
for the highest debt
held in the Institute's
"hiss-tory!"
It has "kitten" me
great pleasure
to watch this boy as he matured
under my leadership!
Ahh!
And now!
Let all of us join together
to extoll our hero's
valiant deeds!
[PARTY GOERS cheer, chanting]
King of Debt! King of Debt!
You guys think I'm a hero?
[inaudible]
Of course that's what we think!
You're the liberator
of Rumble Town.
You deserve all the "purr-aise"
you're hearing.
Although, I should note
that this won't be
lowering your debt at all.
-[MAJESTY laughing]
-You're wrong.
I'm nobody's hero.
[DOC gasps]
But Seth...
[MISTER BOOBRIE
chirps sadly]
[continues laughing]
You're far too young
to be this modest, hero.
We're all "ameowzed" to hear
of your accomplishments
and we have high hopes
for your future!
Isn't that right?
[MAN A]
Yeah! King of Debt!
[MAN B]
You rock man!
You're on a
whole other level!
[MAN C] You're gonna
be a living legend, ya hear me?
-[cheering continues]
-[MAJESTY laughs]
Sounds like your fans
have great expectations!
[coughs]
What "meow?"
What do you have planned
for your next great exploit?
[SETH] If you're asking
what my goal is, then...
it's simple.
I'll find Radiant
and destroy it.
Oh, my.
[MAN D] Radiant?
What's that?
[MAN E]
I thought it was a myth.
[PARTY GOERS continue
murmuring, confused]
[SETH exhales]
[MAN F]
Don't know much about it,
but I bet our hero
can destroy
ten or twenty Radiants!
[MAN G]
Nah, I'd say a hundred!
[MAN H]
King of Debt! King of Debt!
[laughing]
Say! Get in there and give those
kitties a post to scratch on?
-[SETH screaming]
-[PARTY GOERS exclaiming]
[FEMALE PARTY GOERS
screaming]
[WOMAN A]
King of Debt! Over here!
[WOMAN B]
What a charming boy!
[WOMAN C]
What cute horns! And these...
Oh, no, Doc, Seth's in trouble!
Uh,
y-yeah...
but there's no way
we can get any closer to him.
-[FEMALE PARTY GOERS continue]
-[SETH panting, struggling]
[takes deep breath]
Wow.
-That was not a good time.
-[footsteps approaching]
Huh?
It's been quite a while,
hasn't it, Seth?
Well, if it isn't...
-Neck, wasn't it?
-[NICK exclaiming]
[HENCHMEN]
Are you okay?
The name's Nick!
I'm the guy who challenged you
to the Artemis Festival
broom race,
and destroyed you, remember?
Oh, yeah, it's all
comin' back now.
How have you guys been?
-Good!
-Yeah.
Well!
I see you're just as childish
as you've always been.
We both know that you're only
enjoying this level of fame
because you got lucky!
So don't let it
get to your head!
Not sure I know what'cha mean.
It was only a coincidence
that you went
to Rumble Town when you did!
-Ha! I'd've done just as well.
-[SETH] Hm?
Only I would've taken care
of it the smart way.
[HENCHMEN]
Of course you would!
And to prove that point...
I shall face you in a duel!
You wanna fight?
Enter in this tournament
so I can pit
my strength against yours.
That's right, we'll fight
our way to the top,
then I'll defeat you,
proving once and for all
I'm the greatest hero
in Artemis!
[SETH]
Think I'll pass.
[NICK]
Huh?!
Sorry to let you down,
but I don't care who's stronger.
So, that kinda competition...
it just... doesn't really
matter to me.
[NICK cackling]
I get it now.
You're afraid that
I'm going to expose
your true nature,
aren't you?
What?
These supposed
exploits of yours:
the capture of those
live Nemeses.
How do we know it wasn’t
all a big lie?
I didn't lie.
Not about any part of this.
Hmph! Well in that case,
the Domitor you fought must've
been an incompetent fool.
-[SETH growls]
-[NICK] And a weakling, to boot.
I mean, Domitors are
the lowest of the low
when it comes
to sorcery, anyway.
When a scumbag gets infected
but lacks any real power
of their own,
they end up cozying up
with monsters to try and--
-[SETH grunts]
-[NICK screams]
-[NICK grunts]
-[BOTH] He dueled you after all!
You don't know anything
about who Hameline was.
You have no idea
how much she suffered,
or what it was that drove her
to go after Rumble Town.
You've never felt
an ounce of her pain!
Stop acting like you have
any right to judge her!
-[SETH echoing]
-[PARTY GOERS gasp, murmur]
[MELIE gasps]
-[DOC exhales]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE whimpers]
She was a kid.
Just trying her best
to stay alive.
All her friends were murdered.
And she had nothing.
Only the Nemesis and revenge.
[SETH]
There are so many sorcerers
out there who are suffering
just like she was.
So many people living in fear
of the Nemesis!
If I find Radiant,
I can make it all stop!
I can bring all this
suffering to an end!
[SETH panting]
Hey! Can any of you tell me
where I should start looking?
[SETH sighs, annoyed]
All these sorcerers,
and none of you have a clue?
[exhales]
[MELIE gasps]
[HAMELINE] They aren't evil,
not in the slightest.
So, don't treat them
like monsters.
Not even all the Nemesis
are evil.
So, who am I s'posed
to fight for?
Damn it.
I don't know what to do.
[ALMA]
Those are some cute Nemeses.
That fur's pretty nice
to look at.
-[SETH] Alma?!
-It's been a while, Seth.
Why are you here?
I mean it's good to see you
and all, but--
Well, that's a surprise!
The hero of Rumble Town
remembers who I am.
Well, then.
[SETH grunts]
[ALMA]
Care to explain
why you haven't tried
to get in touch
even once since you left,
you idiot?!
Do you even know how long
it's been since you ran off?!
For all I knew, you were dead
in some back-alley dumpster.
And then, when I make
the trek out to visit,
ya can't even be bothered
to gimme a decent greeting.
Honestly!
I'm starting to think
your head's gotten
even emptier
than it used to be.
-Am I right?
-[SETH] I'm sorry, Alma.
-[ALMA] Admit it!
-[SETH] You're right!
-[ALMA] That's better.
[SETH sighs]
Your friend Melie is the only
reason I'm here right now.
I had no idea
what had become of you.
You talked to Melie?
Yeah.
She seemed to think
that you'd need my help
coming to your senses.
[ALMA]
I like her.
She's a nice girl.
[SETH]
Yeah.
[ALMA] Sounds like Rumble Town
gave you a hard time.
[SETH] When they call me a hero,
and I think of Hameline,
I feel sick.
I didn't "liberate" anything.
I just turned into a monster
and went berserk.
[ALMA sighs]
So, since I left Pompo Hills,
what have I been doing?
Feels like...
I was just causing trouble.
-[thud]
-[SETH screams]
[ALMA] Enough! Quit acting
like a spoiled brat!
Alma! Ugh!
Why do you gotta keep
trying to hurt me?!
-[ALMA] Hm...
-[SETH] Uh--
I got this letter.
You need to read it.
Mm--
"Dear Seth..."
Wait! It's from Taj!
[TAJ]
Hi Seth.
It's been pretty crazy here
since everything that happened.
But after you took out Konrad,
things actually changed.
The people here came around.
All of us are thinking
for ourselves now.
We're working together to build
a new Rumble Town.
A kinder one.
And I promise,
we'll never forget who it was
that saved us.
That showed us a better way.
So, thank you, Seth.
Someday...
I'll go to Artemis, too.
And I'll become
an amazing sorcerer,
exactly like you.
When that day comes,
you'll see me again.
Till then...
Taj.
[SETH exhales]
[ALMA]
Look, Seth.
It's true that there will
always be people
who you just can’t save.
But it's also true that things
have changed for the better
because of your actions.
[SETH]
Huh?
I saw the same change
in the people of Pompo Hills.
After seeing what you did
for them,
they've been downright
friendly toward me...
at times.
Things are nothing like
what they were before.
[SETH]
Seriously?
And then there's
your friend Melie.
[SETH]
Huh?
[ALMA] She was injured herself
after Rumble Town,
but she put off treating her
own wounds to look after you.
[SETH]
But why?
[ALMA]
I asked that, too.
She said,
"Because he saved me."
[SETH exhales]
[ALMA]
Well, Seth?
Are you gonna reply with another
pointlessly gloomy comment?
[SETH]
No, I'm all right now.
Thank you for coming, Alma.
I'll destroy Radiant
and change this world.
No matter how hard the journey.
Well, that's nice, but before
you get into that,
take some time to thank the
people who got you this far.
[SETH]
Melie! Doc! Boobrie!
[chuckles]
[ALL excited, chattering]
[SETH]
I feel a whole lot better now!
Sorry for makin' you
guys worry so much.
[MELIE annoyed, tense]
Huh? Say what?
I wasn't worried at all!
[DOC]
Look Seth, I've already got
my heart set on
someone else, so let go!
[MELIE] Why would I care
how you feel? You’re a punk!
[NARRATOR] Trust in
the Inquisition has wavered
since Konrad's misdeeds
were exposed.
This takes its toll
on Captain Dragunov
when he's unable
to restock his supplies.
Meanwhile, the fall
of Rumble Town
has also affected their trade
and distribution networks.
And so Doc takes on a desperate
mission to acquire coffee beans.
Next time on Radiant,
"Omen."