[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans who can stand
against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[PIODON]
I'll ask once again.
Where do you stand?
Why, and for whom,
do you fight?
-I'm fighting for--
-[rumbling crash]
[gasps]
They need my help.
[SETH grunts]
Where ya goin'?
I'm not done talkin' to ya.
[SETH]
I owe you one!
I didn't really follow much
of what you were saying,
but thanks for the save!
I'll catch ya later!
Now I'll blow everything away,
and there's nothing you
can do to stop me!
Please don't do this,
Hameline!
These people wronged you,
but they don't deserve to die!
If you don't like
what we're doing,
then you should come
and make us stop.
That's assuming you can get
close enough to try.
[rumbling, cracking]
-[HAMELINE yells]
-[SETH grunts]
-Ah!
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
-Ah, there we go.
I'm finally here.
[NARRATOR]
"To Stop the Sound of the Wind"
[BOTH grunting]
So you're the one.
The Domitor who sent all these
Nemeses to attack the city.
And you're the young sorcerer
who defeated Captain Konrad.
The name's Seth.
[HAMELINE] I'm impressed
that you managed
to survive that fall.
You must have had
some remarkably good luck.
I thought
I was a goner, too.
But I can't die yet.
I've got work to do.
[scoffs] Throwing your
second chance away.
How stupid of you.
-[screams]
-[blade scrapes]
[BOTH grunting]
[screaming]
[SETH grunts]
Tell me.
What exactly did you hope
to achieve
by coming here to fight me?
I came to stop
your stupid plan, obviously!
You think I'd let you destroy
this whole Island?
No way!
Like you can stop me.
[blasts]
Wait! Seth is gonna
need our help.
Please, Grimm,
we have to turn around!
That tower's unstable
and may fall soon.
If crushed by the rubble,
you and Grimm can help no one.
The choice is between fleeing
the tower or falling with it.
But Seth is--
[screaming]
[grunts] This is nothing
compared to Alma's punishments
and Yaga's training!
[HAMELINE]
Too close!
[groaning]
[grunts]
Do your worst!
No one else dies here!
Skull Burst!
[straining]
You're putting up a real fight,
but it's not enough!
[straining]
Don't you get it?
-I'm not your enemy.
-[straining]
Those people, the bloodthirsty
mob you're fighting
to protect right now,
they're against us!
The hell are you
talking about?
That's not true!
They're defenseless
and need my help!
They need your help?
[huffs]
I needed help!
I got none!
These people don't deserve
to be saved.
Just let them die!
[straining]
[explosion]
[gasps]
[CITIZENS gasp]
[exhales]
-[rumble falls]
-[grunting, groaning]
This isn't those people's fault.
They were just following
that crazy muscle-head.
You exposed him,
and I beat him, so now--
-So now what?
-[SETH gasps]
Will my friends
come back to life?
Will the people suddenly
give up their prejudice
and strive to do better?
You think getting rid of
one Inquisitor is enough?
Not by a long shot.
[SETH]
What?
The cruelty we've witnessed was
always in these people's hearts.
Their leader just helped them
to unleash it.
They call people like you
and me "infected,"
and treat us like
we're less than human.
It's because of them.
They're the reason
why people like Konrad
are able to get their way!
That doesn't make any sense.
I know that a lot of them
are prejudiced,
but that doesn't really
justify killing them all.
You're damn right it does.
Seems to me, you're doing
the same thing Konrad did.
[sighs]
Judge me as you will.
Listen well.
No matter how hard you
try to win these people over,
the truth is they will never
accept you as one of them.
You can fight for them,
even die for them,
but they will always see you--
see us--
as monsters to be feared.
I didn't want this.
I never asked for magic,
or for the curse
that came with it.
Look, Seth.
I think you must
know in your heart
whose side it is that you
should be fighting for now.
[gasps]
Why don't you tell me?
Which side wouldja say
that you're on?
[SETH]
Which side am I on?
I'm...
I don't think like that!
I'll use my magic to save
as many people as I can,
no matter who they are!
Then it would appear that
you and I are very different.
You're like a beaten dog
who's still loyal to its master.
[gasps]
Go ahead and save those
good, fine people
from being persecuted
by the nasty sorcerer!
[blasts]
[SETH screaming]
[HAMELINE]
But you should know.
Those good, fine people,
they tore me away
from my mother's arms!
They beat my friends
to death!
They torment people
like you and me for fun!
But then, the moment
a Nemesis appears, they want us
to march out and die for them!
[screams, grunts]
[groaning, gasps]
If you believe people like that
are worth protecting.
Then you...
are nothing like me.
[SETH straining]
[HAMELINE screaming]
You're my foe!
[powering up]
[blasting]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[sighs]
[MELIE]
No! Seth's in trouble!
[GRIMM]
Veneficium...
Revelare.
[straining]
No, you're wrong!
[HAMELINE]
They called us monsters
and tossed us in a cage.
[SETH]
You're wrong!
[HAMELINE] They tied us up,
and tried to burn us alive.
[SETH]
You're wrong!
[HAMELINE]
They took everything we had!
[SETH]
You're wrong!
-[SETH straining]
-[HAMELINE] That's who
these people are!
And you're fighting
to protect them?!
You're just
a delusional kid,
and the two of us
are nothing alike!
[SETH]
You're wrong!
[straining, grunting]
[screaming]
You're wrong!
[voice echoing]
I'm like you.
In more ways
than you could know.
[blasting, wind rushing]
[rumbling]
[chain rattling]
-[chain rattling]
-[crash]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[GRIMM]
Oh, of course.
[MELIE]
What do you mean, Grimm?
Are you able to tell
what's going on over there?
Indeed.
It would appear that this battle
is already over.
[MELIE]
What?!
Did Seth escape?
The warring Fantasia
has vanished,
not because Seth lost,
but because he stopped fighting.
To express what's happening
in musical terms,
the two of them are now
performing in harmony.
[MELIE] I don't really
get what that means.
[GRIMM]
It means that Hameline and Seth
have reached an agreement.
[SETH]
I know how you feel.
They hurt me, too.
In ways I couldn't forgive.
I can't guess how many times
I've wished
I could just destroy them all.
[HAMELINE]
And how do you feel now?
In all the time you've
endured their hate,
have any of them grown kinder?
Or do you feel
any more accepted?
In all of that time,
have they given you any reason
to fight the Nemesis for them?
Not one.
I still have these
nightmares... from childhood.
The years I spent on the run,
hiding from those
who'd hurt me.
I had powerful magic,
so I could've fought back.
But Alma told me that wasn't
an option, no matter what.
So, I've stuck to that.
Still...
it was frightening
and so frustrating.
Then you see.
You understand why I had to come
out of hiding and fight back.
It was necessary to make those
people face what they've done.
You know I'm not
just doing this out of
lust for revenge, don't you?
I know...
I understand.
[HAMELINE inhales sharply]
[HAMELINE crying]
But... I refuse to become the
monster that they think I am.
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[gasping, angry]
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[blasting, wind rushing]
[gasping]
[CITIZEN 1]
Is it over?
[CITIZEN 2]
The island stopped shaking.
[CITIZEN 3]
Can anyone see what's going on?
[SETH breathing, shakily]
That was a real
clever farce, kid.
Played me for a lonely fool.
And I let you take me in.
So, even now, you're following
your master's orders
-like a good dog, huh?
-It isn't that.
[HAMELINE]
Then what the hell is it?!
-[SETH] Stop.
-Don't pretend you care
before you let them
burn me at the stake!
-[SETH] I won't!
-You have to!
It's either that or just kill me
yourself, here and now!
How else can you prove you're
loyal to the masters down there?
I told you it's not like that!
I won't kill you
or throw you to a mob.
And I won't let the Inquisition
have you, either.
[HAMELINE]
Then, what are you gonna do?
There are no other options.
You're such a fool.
[SETH]
You're the fool.
Where did you think
this would get you?
How was acting like the people
who hurt you gonna fix anything?
Did you think this would
make you happy?
[HAMELINE]
There's been a rift between
normal people and sorcerers
for almost as long
as there's been Nemesis.
There's nothing we can do
to fix it!
There's nothing anyone can do!
The only choice left to us
is to pick a side and fight.
And anyone who says
otherwise is just naïve.
That, or a traitor
to their kind.
I told you it isn't like that.
[inhales]
[SETH]
It's not all decided for us.
You can do what's right
without choosing a side.
So is that all you have to say?
In that case,
you'll never have allies
or a real home.
You'll never have a goal
that's worth living for.
[SETH]
My allies are my friends!
-We have a goal and so can you.
-[HAMELINE gasps]
Come with me.
And help us destroy Radiant!
[gasps]
Once Radiant
has been dealt with,
The Nemesis will disappear.
After that, there won't be
any more reason to fight.
We can both be friends
with everyone!
'Kay? You'll help, right?
But that's just
a crazy pipe dream.
-It could never wo--
-Sure it can!
Pipe dream or not,
it got me this far at least.
[SETH chuckles]
Come with me.
And help me change this world.
[gasps]
[huffs]
You're still a fool.
But even so...
I wish I had seen things
like you did.
So do it now!
It's never too late
to make a change.
[gasps]
-[rumbling crash]
-[gasps]
[SETH]
Uh... what is that?
♪
[SANTORI laughs]
Rest assured, citizens,
these sorcerers shall
do you no further harm.
Nor shall they
escape my grasp.
[laughs]
Just when I thought things
couldn't get weirder.
-Look there, a battleship!
-[CITIZEN 4] Huh?
[CITIZEN 5]
It's looks like the Inquisition!
[CITIZEB 6]
Yes! We're saved!
[CITIZEN 7] They better hurry up
and capture those infected!
[ROOKIE]
That battleship.
It's full of reinforcements,
right, sir?
[DRAGUNOV]
That it is.
Though, I have to say,
it doesn't bode well
to see them use a miracle
so early in the fight.
[ROOKIE] But that Domitor
is completely out of control.
Shouldn't this be expected?
The situation
is certainly serious.
But the Thaumaturges
are only sent to fight foes
that ordinary troops
can't hope to beat,
-so it's a rare sight.
-[ROOKIE gasps]
[DRAGUNOV]
What are they so afraid of?
Could it be there's more to that
sorcerer boy than I suspected?
[SANTORI laughs]
My goodness!
Working miracles really makes
you feel as though life
is worth living,
wouldn't you agree, my friends?
-[MELIE] You okay?
-[SETH] Melie!
Grimm, you're here!
So is that thing magic or what?
No, Grimm does not
sense Fantasia.
This is a power exclusive
to certain elites
within the Inquisition.
It's known as a "miracle."
[SETH]
A miracle?
[SANTORI]
Now, then.
You would do well to drop
your weapons at once,
and surrender the horned
sorcerer to our custody.
That sorcerer is
a fugitive criminal.
He is wanted under suspicion
of several felonious acts.
What? The guy's after me?!
[HAMELINE scoffs]
[SANTORI]
Chiefly,
he is suspected
of the unprovoked
and cold-blooded murder
of Inquisition Colonel
Viviane Dire.
Of wanton destruction inflicted
upon Castelbosque Castle.
Of attempting to murder not one,
-but two councilors of Ponantan.
-There's no way.
Seth wouldn't do all that.
[SANTORI] Of the theft
of various Inquisition weapons.
Of the act of kidnapping,
committed during
the Meden-Vallee invasion.
[SETH scoffs]
What are you talking about?
[SANTORI] He is accused,
at the very least,
of complicity in the massacres
at Vivicine and Paul au Prune.
And of arson
in the northern sector
of the Forest of Septentrium.
Is all that true?
[SETH]I don't know a thing
about any of that stuff.
Still, those names.
I don't know why,
but they feel familiar.
Yo!
Giant old guy,
I'm right here!
But I think you got
the wrong idea.
Ah!
Hey, what the heck
are you doing?
No problem, Inquisitor.
You do as I ask, and I'll hand
the boy over alive.
Oh, yeah.
You two had better stay put.
Make one move and I'll kill him.
[BOTH gasp]
[SANTORI laughing]
Well, who could
have seen this coming?
Shall I take this as an act of
repentance for your wicked past?
-[HAMELINE] Something like that.
-[SETH] This isn't you.
[SANTORI]
Before we speak further,
who are you?
Name's Hameline.
[SANTORI]
I see.
Well, Hameline.
I must inform you that the
Inquisition does not negotiate
with heinous criminals
such as yourself.
That might be
your official position.
But the fact that someone
like you bothered coming here
must mean the boy's important.
And furthermore, it's obvious
that letting him die
isn't an option for you.
'Cause if it was, you would've
crushed us all by now.
Come on,
don't do this, Hameline.
[HAMELINE]
Did you think you could
talk him into letting you go?
It looks like you're
a pretty big deal, Seth.
I'm gonna get as much use
out of you as I can.
You are such a jerk.
[HAMELINE]
Well, Inquisitor,
are we making a deal,
or should I slit his throat now?
[SANTORI]
Hmm.
Let's hear your demand.
I want you to release
every sorcerer
you're currently
holding prisoner.
And enact a non-discrimination
policy on the rest.
[SANTORI]
I refuse.
[HAMELINE]
Thought it was worth a shot.
If you won't do that,
I have a different request.
I'd like for you,
and all your compatriots,
to burn in hell.
-[blast]
-[SANTORI yelling]
She's a feisty little witch,
with the power
to match her attitude.
Only rarely am I made to feel
pain through my projection.
What just happened?
Don't tell me you were defeated,
Santori.
[laughing]
Don't be absurd!
She surprised me,
but she did little damage.
There's no doubt that I can make
short work of her.
I swear it by this very beard.
You need to get up
and run, Seth.
Right now.
The battleship is going
to reach us any second.
My brothers are in that scroll.
Look after them, will you?
They aren't evil.
Not in the slightest.
So don't treat them
like monsters.
Hold on.
Know what?
I like that expression.
It's the open gaze
of an unbiased child
who knows nothing.
Yeah, you hold onto
that feeling for me.
Goodbye Seth.
Take care.
[SETH gasps]
[SETH grunts]
[MELIE]
Are you okay?
[HAMELINE]
You need to leave.
Make that stupid
pipe dream come true.
I've got a war to fight
and allies to protect.
[grunting]
[blasting]
[screaming]
-[MELIE] Seth!
-[SETH] Turn us around!
Let go of me!
If I don't help her,
she'll get caught!
You should respect
the girl's parting wish.
She's doing this to buy time
while you escape.
[HAMELINE]
Seth...
I never wanted to believe
in someone this badly.
If you know that it's real,
then keep running.
Run till you find
your way to Radiant.
[blast]
[exhales, gasps]
[weakly]
Go Seth.
Don't let anyone stop you.
Change the whole world.
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] The Thaumaturges:
Torque, Santori,
Teppes, Ullmina, and Lisellotte
have stepped into the fray.
Out of his mind with rage,
Seth begins to change.
His hidden power
goes berserk.
but General Torque, "The Beast,"
surpasses even Seth in strength.
Next time on "Radiant,"
"The Light That Follows
the Darkness."