[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[KONRAD]
Well, sorcerers,
you have been warned!
I shall give you
10 seconds to surrender!
[growls]
[SETH yells]
Titan... Punch!
-[SOLDIERS yell, grunt]
-[shattering]
Shields at the ready.
Form up!
Meteor Drops!
-[meteors firing]
-[SETH] Gah!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
Second line, go!
[SOLDIERS groan]
Melie!
Don't just stand there, move!
Surrender or die.
The infected will not be
suffered in this town.
I am Konrad de Marbourg:
Inquisition Captain.
And as Rumble Town's
stalwart wall,
none shall escape my grasp!
[NARRATOR] "The Bell Tolls
the Sound of Destruction."
-[SETH] Ahh!
-[KONRAD growling]
-[arrow hits wand]
-[MELIE gasps]
Ugh!
No sudden moves.
My next mark
will be your head.
[KONRAD]
Captain Dragunov.
You finish drinking my wine?
I appreciate your assistance in
the capture of these sorcerers.
[SETH gasps]
From the airship.
[SETH growls]
I wouldn't test my speed
against Dragunov's arrow
-if I were you, sorcerer.
-Huh?
Especially since we have
a friend of yours in custody.
[DOC groans]
[SETH]
Doc?!
[gasps]
[SETH]
What are you doing here?!
I thought you were
going back to Artemis!
[DOC breathing heavily]
Me too.
[KONRAD] Throw that witch
in the cage with the sick one.
Bring the snot-nosed
runt to me.
[SOLDIER]
Sir!
[MELIE grunts]
Damn you!
[KONRAD growls]
-[SETH] Ahh!
-[KONRAD grunts]
Seth, no!
By all means, subdue him.
But mind that you aren't
too rough.
General Torque says he wants
the boy captured alive.
[KONRAD chuckles]
Very well.
But I have other uses for this
sorcerer while he's in my town.
Good luck using
your filthy magic
without those tainted
gloves of yours.
[DRAGUNOV]
Fair warning, Konrad.
The boy is stronger
than he looks.
-Do not underestimate him.
-What's that?
Are you suggesting
he could beat me?
[KONRAD grunts]
Captain Dragunov!
Where are you going?
I aim to continue
my investigation.
[KONRAD]
Hmph.
-[SOLDIER] Captain!
-[KONRAD] Hm?
District 12 is in chaos, sir.
Armed citizens
are attacking immigrants
all over 12th Street.
It's out of control!
[evil chuckle]
Then I'd best go
and have a word with them.
Before Dragunov
finds out anything else
that isn't his business.
[MELIE groaning, moaning]
-[DOC moaning]
-[MELIE] Seth... Taj.
I have to do something.
But they took my wand.
-[DOC] Doesn't matter.
-[MELIE gasps]
Wouldn't work... in here.
The cage is...
made from black silver.
So...
even with your wand,
you can't use any... Fantasia.
You look even sicker
than before, Doc.
[chuckling, weakly]
I bet, but more importantly.
I saw a bunch of Nemeses
in one of the--
-[DOC grunts, groans]
-[MELIE gasps] Doc? Doc?!
[MELIE crying]
Doc!
You have
to stay with me.
Please!
-[SETH groans, weakly] Huh?
-[bell ringing quickly]
[KONRAD] Brave citizens
who've come to District 12
to defend your freedom!
Thanks to you,
we've captured this sorcerer,
as well as his newly infected
immigrant accomplice!
All our fears
have been proven true!
[CITIZEN 1] I knew that
we were right to attack first!
[CITIZEN 2] The people
are with you, Captain Konrad!
No. It can't be.
-He has Taj!
-[TAJ whimpering]
[MRS. ZEDA]
No, not my baby.
We escaped but we can't leave
without our boy.
[KONRAD]
And that's not all!
We now know that
they've been hiding
a horde of Nemeses
in the slums.
They plan to unleash them
to obliterate us.
[CITIZEN 3]
The Nemesis? Here?!
You're wrong!
They're controlled by a Domitor!
We've got nothing to do
with those things!
[KONRAD, amused]
Hmph.
You think I don't realize that?
What?!
[KONRAD]
Good people.
Our past kindness
has all but undone us.
But the time for open doors
and hands extended is over.
What we need now
is the courage to fight!
To take back our home for good!
[CITIZEN 4] Yeah,
this is our town, not theirs!
[CITIZEN 5]
Captain Konrad is right!
[CITIZEN 6] No more
letting them walk over us!
I thank you all
for your support.
Your words have renewed
my own courage.
Indeed, you've shown me that
I'm making the right choice.
Close the gate at once,
let no one through!
[gears cranking]
[CROWD murmuring]
No! We're trapped!
Just what is that madman
planning to do?
[CITIZEN 1] Wait, he's
leaving us with the immigrants?
[CITIZEN 2]
Why'd you lock us in?!
[KONRAD] We can't afford
to waste a single moment.
But as loyal citizens,
you'll be glad to know
that your deaths shall mark
the start
of a new era for our town!
[CITIZEN 2]
No, you can't do this!
[CITIZEN 3]
Please! We're regular people!
We're not like them!
Tank corps, at the ready!
Start with 12th Street.
-Then raze the whole district.
-[CROWD screaming]
Don't do this!
You're just gonna murder
all these people?
That's insane, and you think
they're the bad guys?
[KONRAD growls]
The foreigners
are trying to conceal it,
but they're invading.
Bringing their barbaric culture
and their backwards ideas
with them.
They are not like us!
[SETH]
So, that's it.
You're doing this
because they're different?!
There's no way!
How can you gather so much
Fantasia without wearing gloves?
[SETH]
I'm pretty different myself!
Why don't I show you
what I mean!
-[crashing, rumbling]
-[KONRAD] Ahh!
-[crash]
-[KONRAD grunts]
[SOLDIER]
Captain Konrad, sir!
[KONRAD growling]
[growling growing louder]
Rahh!
What the heck is he?
I said to open fire.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
They're civilians!
Don't do this!
Huh?
[gasps]
[GRIMM hums]
[KONRAD]
Hmm?!
[SOLDIER] Did that sorcerer
just absorb all our shells?
Yeah, he seems stronger
than the first one.
[GRIMM] Boy, it's time
for a heart-to-heart talk.
Don't bother lying.
Grimm will know
instantly if you do.
What are you-- huh?
[GRIMM]
The girl with the flute,
the Domitor, as they're called.
Is she your ally?
Ally?! I didn't even know
that it was a girl!
I've never met her, okay?
No one said to stop.
Reload. Now!
Then why did Grimm catch you
acting in tandem
with the Echo Nemeses?
I'm a Nemesis hunter.
I was trying to catch them!
Hm? The pain is gone.
[GRIMM] Grimm's bandages
were specially woven
from a feather tree.
It's first aid
rendered with Fantasia.
[SOLDIERS grunt, scream]
-[explosion]
-[SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIER]
Our tanks.
He destroyed every one of them!
I don't get it.
Why are you suddenly helping me?
[GRIMM]
Sincerest apologies.
Grimm was not sure
of your intentions before.
Just as you were
uncertain of Grimm's.
Grimm came to Rumble Town
in search of a certain Domitor.
I guess that'd be the girl with
the flute you mentioned earlier?
If she is the Domitor who Grimm
is trying to find then--
-[wind whistles]
-[SETH] Huh?
Where the heck is all
this Fantasia coming from?
[GRIMM]
Speak of the devil.
She's finally making her move,
it seems.
-[wind whistling]
-[flute playing]
[CITIZEN 1]
Whoa!
Where did all this wind
come from?
[CITIZEN 2]
Look at the clock tower!
There's a tornado around it!
[flute playing continues]
[bell ringing]
[SETH gasps]
[gasps]
Go and wreak some havoc.
The tolling of the bell
will herald the beginning.
♪
Oh crap.
She sicced the Nemeses
on the town!
Oh!
[GRIMM] She needs to be
taken care of quickly,
-or this will only get worse.
-[SETH gasps]
You run!
Go hide somewhere!
I'll find you once the Nemeses
are dealt with.
[TAJ]
'Kay! Good luck!
-[KONRAD] Hold it!
-Huh?
-[chain cranking]
-[impact]
You're not going anywhere
until our fight is through!
[chain cranking]
[impact, crash]
Huh!
[KONRAD grunts]
If you think you can escape,
go on and try.
We can settle
the score later, Crazy!
This town is in serious trouble
right now!
Oh, that? I didn't expect her
to put on this much of a show.
But this works for me.
I'll just say she's
with the immigrants.
And checkmate.
Not only did you attack
District 12,
you're also the one
behind all this?!
That's right, and it wasn't
cheap for me to get done.
That Domitor girl
was expensive to hire.
So you weren't just ignoring
the Nemeses,
you were using them!
And now that
you're aware of that,
it's time for you to die.
[MELIE]
Doc! Doc!
Wake up.
Please be okay.
-[wind whistling]
-[bell ringing]
No. No pulse.
[crying]
He's already...
[continues crying]
[SOLDIER 1]
It's all over!
[SOLDIER 2]
I don't wanna die!
[MELIE gasps]
It's open.
[whimpering]
But what's the point?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
-[smack]
-[MELIE] Ah!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
[SOLDIERS whimper, yell]
[MELIE]
This is my fault.
If that other me hadn't
shown up when she did,
then I could've gotten
all of my friends to safety.
I failed them,
and because of that.
Doc's gone.
I refuse to watch
any more people die!
[wand powers up]
[CITIZENS screaming]
-[impact]
-[thud]
[flute playing continues]
Why'd she choose to make
her move now of all times?
And for her to act with
such indiscriminate violence,
after so many nights
spent in hiding.
This isn't the behavior
of a regular mercenary.
That much is certain.
So then, what is it?
What is she scheming?
And why?
[KONRAD]
Ahhh!
[SETH]
Repulse!
[evil laughter]
No...
I can't hold him!
[SETH grunts]
Skull Attack!
[KONRAD grunts]
That was a clever ploy.
Most sorcerers are helpless
without a conduit.
I assumed you were the same.
But luckily, that trick's
all you've got going.
Without the element
of surprise.
You're just a weakling!
[SETH yelling]
Ahhh!
[KONRAD grunts]
My turn!
[KONRAD]
Huh?
[SETH yelling]
Ahhh!
You arrogant fool!
Oh, crap.
Repulse!
-[explosion]
-[KONRAD laughs]
You managed to weaken
the impact with Fantasia.
Still, your magic will have
no effect on my lance!
As you can see for yourself!
Damn it!
How--
what's the deal
with that thing?
[KONRAD]
Why, haven't you heard?
White silver is one of the most
Fantasia-resistant materials
known to man.
And wouldn't you know it?
This lance of mine
has a purity of 72%.
[SETH] I was talkin'
about your mustache.
Huh?
How's that monster stay up?
Must take a lot of wax, huh?
[KONRAD growls]
I'll teach you to mock me!
-[KONRAD] Ahh!
-[powerful thud]
Seth, you can't--
[gasps]
[TAJ]
Everybody's trapped down there.
But the only way I can
get the gate open
is by running past him.
[FEMALE CITIZEN panting]
Thank goodness!
Please, I need your help!
[SOLDIER]
Stop where you are!
We have orders
to let no one pass!
I'm begging you!
At least save my girl!
-[SOLDIERS gasp]
-No, it's a Nemesis!
-[SOLDIERS scream]
-[FEMALE CITIZEN panting]
[DRAGUNOV]
Defend the people...
even if it costs you
your own life.
That's a standing order
for every Inquisitor.
[SOLDIER gasps]
It's Captain Dragunov!
You can execute that order,
or be executed yourselves.
Do you understand my meaning?
But we can't.
-The Nemeses are too--
-[VICE] Fear not.
Facing them with clear minds,
we're more than a match
for the monsters.
But... they're so...
Fight through your fear,
and reclaim your courage.
Hmm.
[crash]
-[MELIE panting]
-It's already dead.
[panting continues]
Good. One more down.
I can pull this off.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[MELIE gasps]
[whimpers]
[MELIE]
He'll shoot me if I move.
But if I get captured,
then who'll protect these people
from the Nemesis?
[arrow whooshes]
-[MISTER BOOBRIE screams]
-[MELIE] Uh--
[gasps]
This is no time to lose focus.
We have a whole city's
worth of people to save.
[SOLDIER grunts]
Right.
Captain, about that sorcerer.
Shouldn't we arrest her?
[DRAGUNOV]
Execute or be executed.
-[SOLDIERS] Huh?
-Remember?
Huh?
[MALE CITIZEN]
Look up there!
-The bell’s going crazy!
-[wind rushing]
[bell ringing]
[flute playing continues,
powering up]
[HAMELINE] Greetings,
people of Rumble Town.
It seems you've found yourselves
in a rough situation.
But if you ask me,
it serves you right.
-A woman's voice?
-Yeah, where's it coming from?
Immigrants.
Sorcerers.
-And The Nemesis.
-
It takes me back
to the devastation wrought
15 years ago.
I remember it well.
This is almost
a perfect re-enactment.
But one thing's missing.
Yes...
the wanton destruction
of an entire district.
What the hell?
I never said she could give
any damn speeches.
Now,
allow me to set this stage
in a way which
befits this final act.
-[flute playing starts again]
-[explosion]
[bell ringing intensifies,
echoes]
Does she plan to use the bell?
There's no time to waste.
[CITIZENS scream, whimper]
[groans]
[GRIMM]
Uhh-ahh!
[whimpers]
[TAJ] Seth is busy trying
to hold Konrad off.
There's no one who can open
that gate except for me!
[TAJ inhales deeply]
[screams]
I thought some rats
might try to flee the ship.
Ahhh!
[growls]
Die! Huh--
[TAJ whimpers]
Don't stop running, Taj!
You get that gate open!
I will!
Struggle all you want,
it makes no difference.
[groaning, straining]
[BOTH yell]
[SETH]
Meteor Drops!
Skull Attack!
Titan Punch!
[SETH grunting]
[KONRAD]
You still don't get it.
-[SETH] Huh?!
-If that was as much power
as you're able to muster,
then you can give up any hope
of bringing down a wall
-as sturdy as I--
-[SETH] Titan... Boots!
[KONRAD growls]
-[gasps]
-[SETH screams]
[KONRAD grunts]
[KONRAD] So it isn't just your
hands that can wield Fantasia,
it's your whole body.
You're corrupted all the way
to your tainted core!
[TAJ whimpers]
[SETH laughs]
Oh, hey look at me!
They call me
Konrad de Macho Man.
I've got six feet of muscle
and no brain to use it!
Ugh! Why,
I oughtta grind you into a--
[growls]
[KONRAD scoffs, laughs]
I'm not going to fall
for it, punk.
You're just tryin' to buy time,
aren't you?
'Cause your left arm gave out.
You never had a real chance,
but now that you're injured,
this fight is as good as over.
[CITIZENS chattering, yelling]
[SOLDIER 1]
Hey, are you sure that this
is the right thing to do?
[SOLDIER 2]
What are you saying?
Are you questioning
the Captain's orders?
[SOLDIER 1]
I'm not, it's just--
-[TAJ] Open up!
-[SOLDIER 2] Huh?
[chains cranking]
[SOLDIER 2]
You dirty little brat!
What have you done?!
Gotcha!
[laughs, weakly]
I got it open.
Huh?!
[CITIZENS complaining, worried]
[SETH grunts]
Guess your infected immigrant
friend blew his chance.
Good thing I had
a second portcullis
put on the entry
to this district.
[SETH groans, straining]
-This isn't finished yet.
-I disagree.
For I'm the one
who knows what comes next.
[bell ringing, continues]
[cracking, boom]
-[CITZENS scream]
-[MALE CITIZEN] The bell!
[SETH]
If she drops that bell.
they'll all die!
-Not all of them.
-Huh?!
The only victims
of this "disaster"
will be the filth
of District 12.
You're kidding me.
Just what in the hell
is the matter with you?
These immigrant weeds
have proven impossible
to tear out by the root.
So instead, I'll salt the soil,
and let it be the foundation
of a beautiful, purified,
Rumble Town!
[evil laughter]
Oh, how I've waited
for this day! Finally!
[HAMELINE scoffs]
After all this time,
the day has arrived.
Now,
let the final act begin.
[NARRATOR]
Hameline takes the stage
at last, resolved to force
Rumble Town to pay the piper.
The Domitor
and her monstrous allies
seem hell-bent on revenge.
But before she acts, she tells
the true story of District 13.
A cruel and tragic tale,
15 years in the making.
Next time on "Radiant,"
"With Fists
Like Shooting Stars."