[NARRATOR]
Beasts known as The Nemesis
wreak havoc on mankind.
The only humans
who can stand against them
are those called sorcerers.
However, sorcerers are seen
as tainted by most,
and are regarded
with fear and distrust.
[HAMELINE gasping]
Go, Seth.
Don't let anyone stop you.
Change the whole world.
[blade withdraws]
♪
[screaming]
[MELIE]
Seth, wait!
[screaming continues]
[SETH straining, grunts]
He's hurt.
Let that be a lesson to you,
ya damn insect!
[TORQUE]
Von Teppes.
It ill-befits an Inquisitor
of your station
-to act so impul--
-I realize that, General.
But since you say
this one is dangerous,
it seems important
that we be sure
the brat's down for the count.
Please, no!
[BOTH gasp]
[TEPPES screams]
[MELIE gasps]
[TORQUE]
Is this it?
[wind rushing, whistling]
[SETH groans]
[NARRATOR] "The Light That
Follows the Darkness"
[wind rushing, whistling]
[GRIMM] That's a tremendous
amount of Fantasia.
How'd he undergo
such a change?
I've got no idea.
I've seen Seth fight,
but I've never seen him
do anything like this.
[SANTORI]
Oh!
[laughs]
Such awe-inspiring power.
A boy with horns
is one to be feared.
Focus, Santori.
We're supporting you
in this fight,
don't waste our strength.
Forgive my distractible nature.
[TEPPES groaning]
That repugnant little brat!
How dare he leave
a mark on my face?!
What did I just
tell you, Von Teppes?
Time to die!
[grunts]
[booming thud]
I'll have words for that fool.
[GRIMM] He defeated
a Thaumaturge with ease.
I...I'm not sure
-Seth's in there.
-[SETH growls]
[SANTORI grunts]
[SETH growls]
[SANTORI laughs]
That boy is quite something
once his anger's aroused.
I shall require about two
minutes for rest and recovery.
[ULLMINA] Santori, look!
Rubble's falling on the town!
[LISELOTTE and SANTORI]
Hmm?
[CITIZENS screaming]
[SANTORI]
Rest easy, citizens!
You are now under the protection
of the Thaumaturges!
[SETH growls]
[TORQUE]
You're like a rampaging beast.
It seems I'll have
to put you down
before you destroy
what's left of this city.
[screaming]
Father of the Inquisition
and founder of all miracles.
Let darkness give way
to the brilliance of your light.
[SETH growls]
-[TORQUE grunts]
-[SETH yells, groans]
The wound I've given you
will soon nullify your ability
to ever wield Fantasia.
You won't hold that form
for much longer.
[SETH growls, grunts]
[TORQUE]
Hmm?
[wind rushing]
[SANTORI grunting]
How has that boy lasted this
long against General Torque?
Once Santori's done
licking his wounds, we can help.
[laughs]
It won't be long now.
-[SETH straining]
-[TORQUE straining, grunts]
[SANTORI grunts]
[crumbling]
He escaped our grasp.
Did you see what became
of the other two sorcerers?
[SANTORI]
Please forgive me, General.
I was focused on
protecting the people below,
and lost sight of them.
[TORQUE]
It's fine.
Many people were saved today
because of your efforts.
For now, that's good enough.
Liselotte will handle
reconnaissance,
and Ullmina
will lead the rescue team.
Relay these orders.
I'll go and find out
what happened
to that fool Von Teppes.
[SANTORI]
Very well, General.
We shall do as you command.
[MELIE]
Seth...
what happened back there?
It was like something...
possessed you.
[GRIMM] There isn't time
to reflect on the past.
This area will soon be crawling
with Inquisition search parties.
In that case,
why did we land here?
[GRIMM] Because Grimm
has unfinished business.
You're free.
Return to your homes.
[MELIE nervously exhales]
--[ZOMBIES moaning]
-[MELIE yelping]
Grimm? You mind
explaining yourself?
[GRIMM]
These are people who either
came into contact
with the Nemeses,
or witnessed
Konrad's evil deeds.
What?
[GRIMM]
Their lives were in danger,
so Grimm put them
somewhere safe.
[MELIE] You mean, you were
behind all those abductions,
but you only did it
to protect the people?
[GRIMM]
Those "abductions?"
Hmm... Grimm understands now.
You're describing how Grimm's
actions were perceived, yes?
Yeah. That's right.
[MELIE] Making his intentions
clear to people
doesn't seem to be
Grimm's strong suit.
-[DOC grunting, straining]
-[MELIE gasps]
-[MELIE] Doc!
-[DOC shrieks]
I don't wanna be shut up
inside stuff anymore.
I don't wanna!
First, it was that
smelly old dumpster,
and now, it's this weird,
dark coffin.
Get me outta here
Melie, I wanna go home!
Okay, first of all,
please quiet down.
If you keep screaming like that,
you're gonna get all of us
locked up in something
called a prison cell,
and we don't want
that now do we?
How are we gonna get off
this island with Doc and Seth,
this is terrible--
[GRIMM] Seems that problem
solved itself.
Look there.
[DOC and MELIE scream]
[train chugging, dinging]
[MELIE]
Hold on...
that thing's from Artemis!
You think it came for us?
[MC over loudspeaker]
What's up, y'all!
I come out here
at King Majesty's request!
Is The Debt King
down there with ya?
-[train whistle blows]
-[DOC and MELIE gasp]
[ULLMINA]
Everyone.
Do keep in mind that aiding
the wounded is our top priority!
Searching for the escaped
sorcerer can wait until later.
It's awful...
to think that he managed
to escape General Torque.
Only the most despicably
cunning of sorcerers
could achieve such a feat.
We face a truly fearsome foe.
[BOTH SOLDIERS]
Right.
Uh...
-[TORQUE] Dragunov.
-[DRAGUNOV] Huh?
[DRAGUNOV]
General Torque.
I listened to your report
regarding Captain Konrad.
My deepest apologies.
I tried, but was still unable
to stop his rampage.
[TORQUE] That was due
to a failure of my own.
All accounts indicate that
you stayed calm under duress
and led the effort to save
these blameless people.
[DRAGUNOV]
Sir...
[TORQUE] Konrad was unable to
keep his emotions in check,
and so he was
brought to justice.
That's all there
is to be said.
[DRAGUNOV exhales]
[SANTORI snoring]
-[fireworks explode]
-[SANTORI] Huh?
What?!
We're being attacked
yet again, it seems!
But why, and from where,
and by whom?
Don't let the light
show distract you.
They're trying to use it
as cover so they can escape.
Whoa. 'Scuse me, but look!
[fireworks exploding, continues]
[LISELOTTE scoffs]
Decoy balloons?
Those sorcerers are ridiculous.
♪
[MALE CITIZEN]
Fireworks!
[FEMALE CITIZEN
So pretty.
Feels like a festival.
[BABY laughs]
Perhaps it's to finally signal
the conflict's end.
I'll take it as a sign
that things will get better
from this day forward.
Thanks, Seth.
You really made
a difference here.
[sniffles]
[fireworks exploding, continues]
[MELIE exhales]
[train chugging]
[train whistles]
[MELIE shudders]
[MC over loudspeaker]
Thank you for flying with us.
Our next stop
is the end of the line:
The Artemis Institute!
[SETH groaning, pained]
[SETH]
Where... am I?
♪
[inaudible]
-[inaudible]
-[SETH gasps]
[inaudible]
♪
Wait...
did I just watch...
my own memories?
[gasps]
You're here with me,
Hameline?
I'm sorry...
If not for me,
you wouldn't have...
[HAMELINE exhales]
[HAMELINE] Goodbye Seth.
Take care.
[SETH crying softly]
There must've been
a way to save her.
I shouldn't have run.
I only went there
to capture a Nemesis.
How did things end up
turning out this way?
Ultimately,
all I did was add
to the chaos.
What did you do to me?
Hey Piodon!
I just asked you a question.
Answer it!
I had no choice,
because you were about
to get yourself killed.
There was only one way to save
your life and that was it.
No one asked you
to do that!
What was your preference?
Are you really gonna tell me
that you would rather
I let you and your friends
be killed by the Thaumaturges?
[SETH exhales]
I'm glad to be alive,
but I couldn't
tell friend from foe.
And also,
while I was berserk,
I saw these strange images.
Like memories, but not mine.
So was it you, or not?
What did you do to me?
Not a lot.
That was your own power
you were just fighting with.
It's been dormant,
but it was always inside of you.
You're saying that was me?
[PIODON] Everything you see
surrounding you now,
is a part of who you are.
All of this is mine?
Okay, but what is it?
[PIODON]
Well...
there are parts of yourself
that you still have
trouble accessing.
Powers and memories
that, for one reason
or another,
are locked away.
All I did was let a little
out of the cage for you.
[SETH exhales]
I don't understand this.
Why would you help me?
Who are you?
And why do you look like me?
We're not brothers. Are we?
Ya worked it out... huh...
Yeah... of course we are.
[SETH gasps]
It's the truth.
You're my kid brother, Seth.
[SETH gasps]
[SETH]
So...
we're really family?
How do you know?
[PIODON]
I just do.
Don't believe me?
[SETH]
I'm not sure...
[PIODON]
That's all right.
[SETH breathes shakily]
[PIODON] You seem pretty
down in the dumps.
[sighs] I thought that whenever
I met a bad guy,
I could just beat them
senseless,
and everything would
work out all right.
But then...
I met Hameline and realized
how naïve that was.
In the end...
I couldn't help her.
Don't beat yourself up.
You still managed
to take down Konrad.
[SETH] Yeah, but I know there
are lots more people out there
who are just like him.
People who discriminate,
who hurt others
because they're
different from them.
Maybe I'm a fool to think
I can change the world.
Even if I have
the power you say I do,
even if I find Radiant,
will it be enough?
Is there even
any point in trying?
I can't tell you,
because I don't know
one way or the other.
[SETH] Please.
Just let me be alone right now.
See you later.
[SETH exhales]
I'm... useless.
I couldn't save her.
I couldn't save anyone.
♪
[MELIE]
Come on.
How long is the punk
gonna stay asleep for?
The sorcerer who was
treating his injuries
told me that we could
expect him to wake up
just about any minute now.
Do you mind tellin' me
what the heck happened to him?
I'm planning to
ask that myself,
if he'd wake up and get out
of my damn bed already.
It can't bother you
too much,
or you would have
kicked him out
instead of lookin'
after him like this.
You must be
pretty worried, huh?
-Huh?
-[DOC shrieks]
No violence, please!
Ya gotta be gentle with me,
I'm a baby!
[MELIE]
Shove it in your ear.
You're still an old man inside!
[DOC]
Have some sympathy, will ya?!
You think I wanted
to get sick, and molt,
and crawl outta myself
as an infant?
That really is
a disgusting curse.
Do you think I don't know that
without havin' you tell me?!
Oh, man. How am I gonna
explain this body to Melba?
Once she's seen me
as a weird baby,
any chance I might've had
with her will go kaput!
Yeah...
there wasn't much chance
to start.
Hey, take it back!
-[SETH groans]
-[DOC and MELIE gasp]
-[DOC] Seth!
You feelin' okay, buddy?
Hey, Doc.
Melie.
You scared me.
Uh--
[huffs]
[gasps]
Seth, I...
[crying]
I'm so glad that you're okay.
[MELIE continues crying]
Don't cry.
Wait a sec.
Where are we?
We're in Melie's bedroom
back at Artemis.
Believe it or not,
you've been unconscious
for about a week now.
For a whole week?
Yeah, you just wouldn't wake up
even after you were treated,
and no one
had any idea why.
It was horrible.
I was starting to think
you would never wake up.
I had no idea
how to help you.
Sorry, Melie, I'm okay.
[groans]
Huh?
[SETH]
These bandages...
did Grimm do this?
[DOC yells] Ahh! Why'd you
have to say his name?!
You're playin' with fire, kid!
What if that bandaged
creep shows up again?
[GRIMM]
Grimm will assume
that you're referring to
a different bandaged creep.
[DOC screams]
He really did show up!
-[DOC swoons]
-[SETH] Grimm, hey!
[GRIMM]
You seem to have recovered.
Grimm is happy to see that.
It looks like you
saved my butt again.
I owe you big.
[GRIMM]
No need for thanks.
[SETH]
Mm--
[GRIMM]
If Grimm had not mistaken
your party for companions
of that Domitor,
Grimm could have lent you
his assistance sooner.
-Yeah, you got that right!
-[SETH] Hm?
I had the wrong
idea about you at first, too.
Anyway, if it weren't for--
-[SETH groans in pain]
-[MELIE] Seth!
[GRIMM] Those wounds were
inflicted by General Torque.
Among his miracles,
is the power
to nullify Fantasia.
His blade can slice
through magic with ease,
and render a sorcerer's
catalyst unusable.
Wounds inflicted by
that power of his,
cannot be healed
by any magic.
[SETH exhales]
[GRIMM]
In the worst case,
you may never be able to wield
Fantasia with that arm again.
That sure would suck.
Although come to think of it,
that might actually be
for the best.
-[MELIE exhales]
-[DOC] Huh?
What do I use these arms to do?
They mostly just hurt people.
♪
[MELIE and DOC sigh]
[GRIMM]
Hmm.
How could I forget to ask?
What happened to Rumble Town?
[GRIMM] The Thaumaturges
have restored order.
And the rebuilding
process has begun.
As for what the
town's future will look like...
there's no telling.
But with Konrad gone,
it should at least be better off
than it was before.
That's good to hear.
So despite all our efforts,
turns out it was the Inquisition
who saved Rumble town.
Come on!
You helped, too.
More importantly, I was stressed
out and exhausted
and I got nothin' for it!
I was so determined
to run away
that I even forgot to collect
my money from the client!
And now I look like an infant!
[crying] It could be
eighteen years before Melba
sees me as a man again!
[sobbing]
Maybe you should to woo someone
who likes you back, like Devi!
Devi and I aren't even
the same species!
[MELIE] As long as you have
love, you can overcome anything!
-[DOC] No! Not a chance!
-[MELIE] Sure there is!
Just go for it!
[DOC] There's nothing to go for,
ya big weirdo!
-[SETH] Hey Melie.
-[DOC and MELIE gasp]
What about her
Nemesis brothers?
We brought them back with us.
The academy has
a whole enclosure
for captured Nemeses.
They're living
there peacefully.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad we could protect them,
if nothing else.
-[DOC sighs]
-[MELIE] Aw...
[MAJESTY chewing]
Mmm! Yummy!
[chewing and humming]
[MC]
Between the Magic Locomotive,
and the fireworks and balloons
we used as a diversion,
you ended up burning through
quite a bit of funding
just to save one boy.
[MAJESTY] Hmm... meow,
did I give any such order?
I suddenly forget.
[MAJESTY]
You're pushing your luck,
"inpurrupting" my snack time.
Shoo! Shoo!
[MC] Right then.
I'll leave ya to it, Majesty.
[MAJESTY]
Hmm.
Well, meow.
I dare say, the claws
are about to come out.
Eh, boy?
♪
[NARRATOR] Now that they've
returned to Artemis,
Seth, Melie, and Doc
are all three hailed
as champions for exposing
the evils of the Inquisition.
Despite the merriment
around him,
Seth finds his heart
still tormented
by grief and resentment.
And that's when he finds
Alma has come
to pay him a visit.
Next time on Radiant,
"The World That You Changed."