♪ opening song ♪
The legendary number
one headband.
It's promise is power.
Omnipotence. Immortality.
But at what cost?
One that is greater than
any man can imagine,
and heavier than
any man can bear.
No soul who has ever
worn it's tattered grace
has ever escaped
the torment of
it's infinite burden.
ARGGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!
(spoken in unison
with a French accent)
Ze headband shall be...
Ours!
(spoken in French)
Touché!!!!
Quois?
Die Afro Samurai!
Go to hell, you bastard!
Son...
Father!?
Urgh... ergh.... ahh...
Afro...
A...Afro...
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Jinno!?
Jinno!!
Do you remember me?
I remember you.
And all that you have done...
Murderer. Monster!
How many hundreds of
lives have you ended?
How many thousands have
you made mourn the loss
of their loved ones?
Now it's your turn.
I know the one thing
you care about.
And when I bring him
back from the dead‐‐
I'm going to toy
with him. Torture him.
Your father will
suffer the punishment
for your sins, Afro Samurai.
Unless, you find the
number 2 headband
and try to stop me.
Do you have the balls?
So go fetch boy!
Urgh!
Come for me, Afro Samurai.
With the No.1 headband
on my forehead,
you are bound by
your samurai code.
Take the bait, find the
number 2... come for me...
...so I can crush your heart and
body as you have crushed mine.
Now don't we look like shit.
How you been, man?
Ain't seen you in a while.
Ohhh, you gettin'
kinda old ain't ya?
Look at this poor blade.
It's all jacked up.
Man, things sure have changed.
So how come you're not
wearing the No.1 headband? Huh?
I've had my revenge.
Ain't you learned nothin' yet?
Whatever your reasons,
once you put on the headband,
you can't never really escape...
(quickly jumping to a new topic)
But anyway...
How is that Teddy Bear
guy still alive?
Didn't you dead
him already? Guess not!
Cause he on a strong rebound and
put much foot in your black ass!
Oooh! And didja catch that
honey he was ridin' with?
She the new numero
uno now? Damn!
She major bootylicious too!
She got ass for days, ya heard?!
Even in that cold‐ass rain
she had me hot to trot!
It begins again.
Awight! Now that's
what I'm talkin' about!
We road dogs again! Hee hee!
But if you goin'
anywhere with me‐‐
we gots to get you cleaned‐up
and ready‐to‐rumble!
Are you sure these fragments
of bone are enough?
Heh, heh, heh.
Please rest assured.
In two weeks we shall
be witness to a miracle.
Sio‐‐ My heartfelt
gratitude for your
generous help
with my experiments.
With the completion
of this ultimate being,
we shall supersede
the power of GOD himself.
The world will be in our hands.
I shall be the one to decide how
we use this "miracle,"
Professor Dharman.
And it is you who is helping US.
Don't forget that.
(patronizingly)
My apologies,
your highness, Ms. Sio.
(with a snicker)
This is simply a perfect
coincidence of interests.
Please be assured
that I will use all
of my resources
for your service,
my most noble
and beautiful lady Sio.
(expressionless)
Very wise of you.
Yes!
Setting of the restructuring
system is complete!
Hmm...
You three, monitor Afro and
keep me posted on his moves.
Understood.
The time is finally upon us.
All preparations have been made
to get our revenge
on Afro Samurai.
You're lookin' a
little refreshed now.
Course that didn't wipe
that pissed look off your face.
You know...
I mean to steal your
daddy's funky‐ass
remains in the
middle of a storm...
That's just creepy, right?
All decomposed and shit.
I mean, who does
that? For real?
But I'm feeling you!
This pissed you
off SO much,
that you gonna hit the
road again to find the
#2 headband AGAIN
just so you can
fight the #1 AGAIN?
All this just to get back your
daddy's nasty ass skull?
Hey man‐‐
he dead already!
What's the big deal?
Give me the 411!
I have no choice.
My father must rest in peace.
Can't you just leave
well enough alone?
(Thick Jamaican accent‐‐
spelling is phonetic)
Wise man say de state of de tang
and blade of a sword iz a
reflection of a man's soul.
Only de blade is
clean now, me bruder.
De rest iz up to you.
Afro has begun to move.
Keep your eyes on him.
We don't gotta do this you know.
Come on, maybe
you oughta just chill?
Know what I mean?
Change over to menthols,
pick‐up a sport or somethin'...?
I mean check me out.
I'm happy cause
I smile all the time.
You don't never smile therefore
people don't LIKE you.
I betcha even without any damn
headband everybody still
gonna wanna fight you.
You just ain't no fun, bro!
You always focused
on killin' this guy
and killin' that guy.
How ya gonna pull a lady?
Yeah, well,
I‐I guess the strong silent
types do always seem to get the
girls in the end and all but...
Hold up, hold up, hold up!
Wait a minute. You know,
I just realized
this the first time
I seen you without
the #2 headband!
And you know what?
You look kinda funny!
It's weird man!
I knew something was off!
I mean‐‐your
forehead's huge bro!
I thought your hair was big!
But damn!
That's a
four‐times‐four‐times‐forehead!
That's what they mean when
they say headquarters!
You're a big headliner!
A headmaster a‐‐
Shut up.
Oh, oh, oh... Now I remember.
The strong,
silent and sensitive type.
Hey‐‐ where we goin?
Is it true?
He's heading this way?!
Oh yeah. It's him!
Can't forget those eyes.
That hair!
The cursed creature who
cut down JUSTICE at Mt. Shumi...
...the demon who slaughtered
those we loved...
(excited with hate)
We can't let this
opportunity pass us by.
Revenge will be ours!
I don't think we
can take him down.
He's too strong!
We... we're not ready yet!
There ain't enough of us!
Come on! They say he hasn't
held his blade in years!
It's true! He's weak!
Now is the only chance.
We strike now!
Hey, how come you
guys know so much?
That lady over there,
she knows all about him.
None of you know nothin!!
What good is
killing him gonna do!?
Everything's already
gone to shit anyway!
You're wrong.
It was after Afro Samurai
killed Justice that the world
descended into chaos.
Men had always killed
for the headbands,
but after Justice died and
Afro refused to replace him,
men began to kill
for the joy of killing...
That is when my husband fell...
Yo! He's coming!
Yo! Afro Samurai is coming!
Heh...
As Lady Sio had anticipated...
Things are moving,
just as she planned.
Yo Afro, you might need this.
Y...Y... You murdered my father!
You murdered him!
You killed my only brother!
...and my best friend!
This is for my dead son!
A curse on you demon!
You will burn in hell!
You will drown in the blood of
those innocents you have slain!
You will suffer
the endless bullets
and blades of all of us‐‐
Even after death!
Curse on you Afro Samurai!
Ow! Snap! Now this
here is more like it!
Yo man, let me hold some gold!
The Afro Samurai is here.
(over the intercom)
Send him in, won't you?
OK now. Here's the plan.
You... ummm... do somethin.
And uh...
I'm gonna get a lap dance
and meet you in
five minutes! Wowww!
Hold up, noo, make that ten!
Oideyasu.
(Slowly)
The Number Two Headband.
I am afraid
I cannot give you the
location of the #2
headband for free.
But, If you can defeat me...
(stopping Afro)
Oh no, no.
Not by sword. We play these.
If you win, I'll tell you
where to find the #2.
If I win, I have your head.
Do we have a deal?
Escort Mr. Afro
to the gamblin' area.
Unlike you, Brother One,
I only play games
that I know I will win.
(stroking his beard)
Heh, heh, heh, heh....
Now that was off da chizaiiiin!
Yo Afro I got a
two‐for‐one dance, man!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Hey what'd I miss?
Oh we gamblin now? Cool!
Let us start the game!
Bet on black! Oops!
Wrong game, heh heh heh heh!
Call!
Odd.
Even...
Double ones! Even!
(with a satisfied and
somewhat knowing look)
Afro Samurai, now that you've
lost fair and square,
I must ask you to fulfill your‐‐
Fair?
That cheatin' son‐of‐a‐bitch!
I want a free lap
dance behind dat!
(Slowly) The Number
Two Headband.
The No.2 is a ronin
named Shichogoro.
He is in a village called
Machi‐City to the west...
Man... Couldn't we
have stayed a
few more minutes
at that gamblin' house?
This shit is boring, man‐‐
You boring!
The very demon of revenge
seeks divine guidance? Hah!
Do you really think
you can absolve
yourself from sin by
sculpting stupid little toys?
Whoa! Now that's some shit
you don't see every day.
You've fallen so far...
Coward. I've been watching you.
Can you even raise your
sword against another?
Where is the cold blooded
killer you once were?
Do you no longer have
the stomach to fight?
Will you remain a coward,
even as your father suffers...?
Aw now that just ain't nice.
You don't have
to listen to that shit.
(taunting)
And you have such
a long long way to go...
to save your
poor tortured father.
I've almost revived
his rotten bones.
Oh, he will live again...
...to feel pain, to suffer.
(mocking) And you
don't even have
the #2 headband yet.
So I have a few more days,
or maybe even weeks,
to enjoy your father's
pain before you
even have the right
to challenge me...
(slowly with anger)
Watch... your damn... mouth.
Cause I'm comin' for my dad.
Then we comin' to get you bitch!
Finally you are
awake my hated love.
Now the fun begins...
Whoa. She don't know
who she's fuckin' with.
Jinno...
At last, he has begun to move...
All is proceeding as planned.
We will have our revenge.
But, to succeed,
you and I, my love,
must walk the path of demons.
I am truly sorry but it is the
only way to make him feel the
eternal sadness
that we have felt,
to make him suffer
as we have suffered.
So please...
...forgive me.
Just remember that there
was no alternative.
I will always love you...
My beloved brother.
Your luck sucks, man.
Everybody knows this is the
first day of the yearly
parade around here.
You ain't gonna get no info
from these party people
about that #2 headband.
His name was Shichogoro right?
You even got any idea
what he look like? I don't!
How we even know that's
his real damn name?!?
The point I am trying to make
is that this is all a bad idea!
Help! Help! Help!
What the?
Out of my way!
A kidnappin' in broad daylight?
That's a damn shame.
(suddenly realizes)
Ah shit... Afro Samurai?
‐‐Out of my way!
‐‐Whoa! Damn!
I said move
you son of a bitch!!!
Gun! Afro! Gun! Heater!
Rosco! Gat! Duck!
Gahhh!!!!
Waa! Waa!
(Off‐screen) Kotaro!
(crying) Oh Daddy!!
Kotaro.
I told you to stay close.
I'm sorry...
You. You have my thanks.
(to the dead body) This
coward kidnapped my boy to...
(changes his mind) Forget it.
Let me buy you a drink...
(points with his thumb).
...I know a spot nearby.
Uh‐oh. I think I lost
a Ninja boot! Wait!
I'm drowning! Hey! Afro!
Don't leave a brotha!
I'm home old man!
Hey hey! You brought
a friend today?
This man saved Kotaro'S life.
So maybe he's strong enough
not to die from
your stew ole man.
Watch your mouth when
you talk about my oden
Shichogoro, or you might
find a hot pepper in your bowl.
You call this crap oden? Ha!
More like chunky rat poison!
Anyway, give me and the kid two
of the usual and throw in
a couple cups of sake. Hot.
Coming right up!
(Happily)
Chunky rat poison!
Just for you,
you little street rat!
You're the street rat!
Hey I'm back! Found my shoe too!
Oh, ya getting' your
grub on? Oh, ewwww...
Somethin' smells funky!
Oh shit! That's the dude!?!
(smiling at Afro)
Whaddya have, partner?
Sukiyaki.
Double that!
Here's to you.
Oh, not a drinker, eh?
Don't know what you're missin'!
Lemonade, then?
Kidding. Kidding.
(takes the bottle for himself.)
Forget it. I'll drink both.
You aren't here for
the festival, are you..?
Me neither.
Just passing through.
But, I guess
we overstayed a bit.
We had our chuckles
at the festival.
But, it's best we move on.
Ya know, it sucks
that you gotta kill this dude.
I gotta say, he ain't
so bad! Kinda cool...
It's always lonely
after the festival.
At least this
is the last time I'll
have to eat
your lousy rat poison!
You'll be sorry.
I make the best stew
for miles around.
When you come back‐‐
remind me to charge you double.
Jeeeeesus! This is the best?
Afro, maybe you oughta kill
this motha fucka too for lying.
This stew sucks!
Lemonade. Please. Help yourself.
That guy earlier...
That man you cut down.
You want to know why
he tried to kidnap Kotaro?
Hell, no.
Do you want to know why anyone
bothers with a street kid
and a drunk like me?
Hell, no.
(Trying to interrupt)
Shichogoro...
It's OK, ole man.
Okay, tell us.
I got something
everybody wants...
One minute he's
stuffing his face,
the next he's passed out.
He ain't even mine.
He's an orphan‐‐
the son of a pal who
got himself murdered.
I promised to watch him if he
ever got in trouble or killed.
Me and that old bastard
were like brothers.
He wasn't the brightest,
but he was a good man.
He died when this kid was a pup.
I heard the man who killed
him had a weird look.
An Afro hairdo with
a greenish tint
if you look real close.
Now you listen to
me and you listen good.
In this world,
there are bonds
deeper than blood...
(Suddenly waking‐up)
Huh? Wha?
My pal, that dumb
son‐of‐a‐bitch,
he was like so
many fools who went
after those headbands of legend.
All he wound‐up
was dead. (Pause)
Know what he said to me
when I found him dying?
"No more," he whispered.
So, I got that #2 headband
myself and I hid it.
Been on the run ever since.
But now you've come...
(Looking at Afro)
...and now we're even.
So, let's get this over with.
(Enthusiastically)
Oh damn! It's ON now!
No more Mr. Nice Afro!
Shichogoro...!
(smiles) Keep that
poison hot ole man.
I'll be back in a flash.
Hm...
(chuckle)
I thought if Kotaro
and me just kept movin...
...maybe folks
would forget about
it all and I could
honor my pal's
wish of peace for his son.
But I guess there ain't
no hidin' from fate. Dammit.
All these damn headbands do is
make dead buddies and orphans.
You hear me Afro?
Dead bodies and orphans!
So, I ain't givin you
the #2 headband.
You'll have to
kill me to get it.
Not because I'm playin' by
the headband rules,
and not because
I'm out to save
the world neither!
Yo Afro! What's‐up
with the formal stance?
He cool and all,
but he ain't your pal!
Just dent this fool!
It's because I keep my promises.
Don't think I don't know
you Afro Samurai.
I saw what you
did on the boardwalk.
Killing a man without
a moment of hesitation‐‐
like he was nothin'
but a fly on your face.
Maybe it's time
someone swatted you.
Maybe I feel like
I'm the guy to do it.
You gonna let
him talk all that trash?
Slice him and dice him, Afro!
Sayonara Afro Samurai.
Now that's just wack.
You gonna die creep!
(painful grunt)
Guh!!!
Shit! This guy's slick!
I'm impressed! He just
might kill your ass!
Aww man, you runnin?
You makin' us look bad dude!
Where you going?
Ahhh, I knew you
was bein' devious!
We ain't never run
from nobody,
and we ain't about to
pick today to start running!
Hey man! Keep on swingin'!
Whilst I get my groove on!
Let's paaaarrrttaaayyyy!
Awwwwww shit!
Now we partyin' like rockstars!
Light show! Light show!
(pumping his voice to the beat)
Mmm... mmm!
Bring it baby.
Yeah, boom boom.
Yeah yeah, whuddup yo!
We're gonna get this party
crackin' right now!
Now on center stage:
we got the man with
the No.2 headband!
Don't stop, get it, get it!
Buzza buzza boom! Buzza boom!
(Dropping his light sticks)
Hey! Where'd they come from?
Urgh! This is only half‐cooked.
You expect me to eat this?
I broke my teeth on this crap.
This is disgusting.
How do you even
stay in business?
Come on, let's get out of here.
This place should be shut down.
Dad...?
Kotaro?
Aww man!
You've killed the music!
Why you always got to
wreck the party!?!
Well, that was an
unnecessary distraction.
Still want to die?
You want it that much?
It's just a piece
of cloth you idiot.
If you're feeling so lucky‐‐
come and get it.
What the fu... (reaction)
Shut up.
Sumanai.
("sorry" in samurai dialect)
Man you always got to
bust‐up the fun don't you.
I was ravin' til the
break a dawn man!
Light sticks and everything!
Why'd you go and ruin it?
I bet they even
cancel the damn thing
next year and
its all your fault.
And another thing...
you ain't all that,
just cause you back
to being the #2 again!
Don't you get it?
We walkin' the demon path again!
It ain't the right way!
Ah well. Whatever.
So where we goin' next?
How about getting
a little 'push push' first?
Know what I'm sayin'?!?!
Man we never party!
Damn, now what's
fin to jump off?
Whoa wait. Didn't they
already kick your ass?
They coming after you again?
Your blade stains
the world with blood.
(sarcastic)
Oh you think!?
You kill only for your
selfish petty reasons...
Have you no heart?
Uh... Urgh... Uh...
(panicking)
This can't be real man.
Who the hell are these people!
This ain't possible!
Grrrrrgggrgargagrgargggghhhh!!!
I don't think so.
You should restrain yourself or
risk another
humiliating beating.
You don't want to risk
breaking my new toy do you?
He's ever so fragile right now.
Go to the Cherry Hill‐‐
or he dies again.
But this time (slowly)
much much much more slowly.
Watch... your damn... mouth!
Bin!
My lady!
Step back.
Um. Damn. You alright, man?
NO!
Jinno!
Hey easy little sis!
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, Sio?
How've you been, princess?
Good!
And our foster parents?
How are they?
They've been great!
They're like real parents.
And, they got this
guy named Bin-san.
He's kinda strict and scary.
And this other guy Michael‐san‐‐
He plays with me lots.
(excitedly)
Oh, oh, then this
lady Tomoe-san,
teaches me to be
like a real princess!
I even learned to dance and
have tea and everything!
(Sincerely)
Wow. That's great.
(With a sad expression)
I wish you could
be here with me.
(with a firm, yet loving voice)
I know little sister.
But you're safe here.
This family wanted a daughter
of their own to
replace the one they lost.
Now I see they've
accepted you as their own.
We should both be grateful.
I'll try to visit more, OK?
Hey there's someone
I want you to meet.
This is Afro. Afro‐‐this
is Sio‐‐my sister.
Oh! Hi Afro.
Um. Hi.
He's a newcomer at the sword
school. But he's real good‐‐
almost as good as me!
He's like a brother.
Brother?
Uh‐huh.
(to Afro) So I guess that
makes you my brother too?
Umm.. Yeah I guess.
Cool!
I just got another brother!
Yup.
Can I see the sword
school someday too?
Yeah. Sure. Anytime.
You're shy.
And you're hair is funny!
Um... nice to meet you too...
You will soon be free...
You can't just toy with
science like that lady Sio!
Are you mad!?!
Once he's complete he could very
well be the ULTIMATE SAMURAI!
But, if his growth
is interrupted‐‐
he could end‐up just a
pile of worthless protein jelly!
Mad? That's a
strange word coming
from the very image of madness.
But, our plans could
have been ruined!
Ah, it's part of the
process dear professor.
The more I taunt
Afro, the better.
I want his suffering
to be long and slow.
His death is not my goal‐‐
only the final
exclamation point.
Don't you know me by now?
(stuttering)
Of course Lady Sio.
You are truly twisted.
But, it's j..just...
The risks...
(laughter)
What a refreshing experience!
I've twisted the most twisted
scientist in the world
with MY twistedness!
Don't fear
my round friend.
Everything is
moving so deliciously.
Have a little faith!
Yes, my Lady.
With my guidance,
it won't end as badly
as your failed masterpiece KUMA.
(OS) Look at him.
You've repaired him so many
times that there's
no human left at all.
He's just a mindless
samurai doll.
Soulless. Dead. (Pause)
It disgusts you doesn't it?
The failure‐‐I mean‐‐
the frustratingly
crude limits of the human body.
But even your full mechanical
works have been destroyed.
The Afro Droid‐‐
Ha! Scrap metal at the bottom
of the ruined temple
of the Empty Seven.
But now...
(OS) Muscle, bone,
blood, bile, merged
with nano‐technology, chemically
programmed neuro‐receptors,
and things so forbidden
it's more Alchemy,
than bio‐technology.
You truly are the
world's most wicked,
shit‐faced genius scientist.
You'll burn in hell for your
insults against nature.
You praise me so
wonderfully Lady Sio.
I am not worthy
of your poetry...
You scum. History will mourn the
atrocities you now commit.
You should be burned alive.
Ahhhh...!
Afro will chase me‐‐
and my brother‐‐
to the ruined city.
When he arrives, he will see
the consequences of his sins.
His twice‐killed only friend...
...and his beloved
father shall impale
him with their vengeful blades.
And then‐‐at the last moment,
these hands will be the ones
that end the life of
Afro Samurai.
He's not even worthy to die
by your erotic and wicked hands!
But his end will not bring
him bliss, my professor.
Damn it's hot up in this piece!
Ain't there a quicker
way to Cherry Hill?
And by the way, you know
that bitch Sio is walkin'
us into a trap don't ya?
That was one weird
family reunion too‐‐
eh Afro? I'm sure
lots of folks would
love to see their dead
daddies alive again.
But, I'm not so sure seeing a
living head with nasty ass guts
and shit is what most
folks had in mind!
I mean, how could
he be alive, huh?
Maybe it wasn't him!
(sudden enthusiasm)
It's a trick!
Maybe it was another
robot like that Afro Droid
you killed a while back.
Or, maybe it was like a muppet!
You know, like controlled by
her hand or something (pause).
OK that was stupid.
It ain't no muppet.
But whatever it was‐‐
one thing is for sure.
That bitch is... crazy!
She must really hate you to
do all of this unnatural shit.
And what's up with KUMA?
Ain't he normally the cryin'
and complainin' type?
Dude didn't say a damn word!
Now that creeps me out.
Sumpin' is wrong
and I don't like it!
Oh... And... Uh...
Whaddya wanna do
'bout that kid followin' us?
So... What like
you like killed his
paps and now he's
probably trying to axe you.
That sounds familiar
don't it? Heee hee!
Well don't sweat iut.
Kid ain't gonna
last much longer.
Little bit's been
draggin' behind
us in this damn heat for days.
(with a deadly serious voice)
He'll be dead by morning.
I'm sorry Daddy...
I wish you three could have
seen the look on his face when
I showed him the living head
of his own dead father.
Never forget that
it was Afro Samurai
that made you what you are.
He will live in Hell on Earth
for what he has done to us.
You will enjoy every second of
excrutiating agony
that I inflict upon him.
You will watch as he bleeds
from his very pores,
listen to the sound
of his breaking bones,
smell his fear
and his burning flesh.
His death will be so filled
with horror,
it will pass into legend.
And I will too‐‐
as his legendary executioner!
Mountain Climbing?
How'd I get talked
into this, man?
We got no equipment!
I need a sports drink!
You got a rope?
You sure we goin' the right way?
The air's getting' thin Afro!
I think I'm gonna die, man!
Or at least have a stroke.
You stressin' me out!
I hate heights!
(Whistles in amazement
then speaks)
Is this the meeting spot? Damn!
I bet back in the day
this place was SWEET!
It's like a messed‐up
theme park!
Bet they had Candy Corn,
Funnel Cakes...
...some mean ass
coasters, the works!
Ain't nobody home now, though..
(Reverently)
But what happened to it man?
Shame it all's in ruins.
Who did this?
Hey, Afro, are you sure this is
the place that the chick said
she'd be waiting for you?
(briefly seeing JUSTICE)
Check it out, that's JUSTICE!
(changing subjects quickly)
You know you never did
ask for directions
along the way.
Yo Afro!
(Skeptical, but not afraid)
Umm. Now whose these is?
Costume party?
Welcome committee?
Comedy troupe?
(to the masked trio)
Yeah thanks. But umm...
no thanks...
...we gotta go to a meeting, OK?
(steps forward a little)
Okay! Let's see. Yo Funny Face!
You seen a crazy
sexy bitch with
a teddy bear headed
dude around here?
That ain't no blunt!
Aw...! What the...?
Ohhhhhh Afro!
Am I gonna die again?
Lady Sio is... not here.
You don't remember us, do you?
Afro Samurai...
Who would have imagined
that the boy we once knew...
...would return as
such a mad executioner...
Driven only by
his murderous rage...
...to bring death
and chaos to the world...
Draw your sword, Afro Samurai.
Now you die!
Professor...
What ails you, my lady?
Please rejoice.
The restoration of Afro'S father
has entered the final stage.
However, this stage
is very sensitive.
If the slightest error occurs,
we still could lose everything.
They are gone.
What's this?
They would never undertake
anything without my orders.
What have you done?
Perhaps they went into town?
What do you mean?
Or perhaps...
They challenged Afro
SAMURAI without you...
But don't fear. Who knows‐‐
they might just win.
After all, you might
be surprised to
hear that they all have quite an
impressive array of
gadgets engineered
on their bodies not to mention
a special drug injection or two.
L...Lady Sio?
What sport is this?
My, my, my.
What a hasty princess
we have here.
The regeneration is not yet...
Heh heh heh. You've done such a
splendid job, dear Professor.
You've equipped
all of the players
with all the right
modifications.
I owe you my thanks.
Now it's time for you to
take a well‐deserved break.
Good night Professor!
The other "executioner"
is about to awaken...
No matter your intentions...
There are things that we
cannot allow you to do...
We must not allow our Lady Sio
to tread the path of darkness...
Such a sweet lady she is...
...we will not allow her
to fall from grace.
(holds up his dagger)
Instead, we will be the sinners.
All I wanted was for Afro to
see the town he destroyed.
I wanted him to see the
consequences of his sin
before I slit his throat.
But now my vassals
are most likely dead.
Fools rush in where
angels fear to tread.
MICHAEL! SHOOT HIM NOW!
What are you waiting for? Do it!
(OS) Shoot them...
She's dead already...
Do it... for our Lady Sio...
Tomoe!
Afro Samurai...
I knew that sooner or later
this day would come.
I will die with you.
What the hell?
(long yell)
Yo Afro! Afro!!!!
Afro! You made it!
How'd you survive home boy?
Tell me what I missed! Ya know,
I got hit by a sleeping
dart. Hurt too!
But I'm a tough, so don't worry.
So did you whack some
crazy moth a fuckas?
What the...?!
Follow me, son.
HOLY FUCK!
Now I HAVE
officially seen it all!
Sio... Jinno...
Hey Afro. why you got to
walk directly into every trap?
You stupid or what?
Up there is the
crazy bitch who been
pullin' the strings
this whole time
AND your old revived robo‐pal‐‐
who don't like your ass neither!
On top of that,
we followin' some
freak o nature that
you think is your dad!
That is my real father.
(exasperated)
Ergh! Wrong answer. That's it.
You're an idiot. And this is as
far as I can go. See ya!
I'm so happy you've made it.
We've have so much to...
talk about!
I have come for my father
and the #1 headband.
(Dry Sarcasm)
What a surprise...
But what can you possibly do
with your body
so utterly destroyed?
We're going to torture you.
Death will come slowly.
(groan)
Why didn't you wear
the No. 1 headband?
I just wanted revenge...
for you.
Whatever your reason,
one must shoulder the burden of
destiny the instant he
puts on the headband.
You should know that by now.
Become the No. 1.
You can never escape
the cycle of blood.
The No. 1 kills or is killed.
You don't have the luxury to
choose whose blood you spill.
Take back your headband.
Fear not... my son...
Urgh... father... wait...
Father...
Look... Look my dear brother.
Afro Samurai is
about to meet his end...
Just as I planned‐‐
at the hands of his own father!
He will finally pay for
the pain he's caused us‐‐
for the pain he's caused
thousands... like us!
Jinno! Jinno!
(excited) Kill him! Kill him!
Once and for all! (laughter)
(Struggling) Ahh....
...Afro....
(groan)
Kill him Afro! Waste him!
That ain't your real father!
That's it! Finish it! Do it!
I cannot kill my father...
Wha... then this
is the end of Afro!
Did you see that, Jinno?
We did it! We finally
brought him to justice!
And it was we...
we who killed him!!
Look, look my dear brother!
(realizes the change in Jinno)
Jinno? Jinno?
(in whisper) Afro...
Af...ro...
Afro!!!!
What have you done...
What have you done to Afro?!!
Why...?
Jinno! Why are you
protecting Afro?!
He's dead now! It's no use!
Have you forgotten what
Afro did to us? To you!?!
Jinno!
(groan)
Afro...
(V.O. during Sio flashback).
My... dearest... brother...
I must...
...protect Swordmaster's dojo...
...must protect everyone...
...including my brother... Afro.
I love you my Jinno...
My brother...
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, Sio?
How have you been, princess?
Jin...no...
(groan)
Run, Afro! You can't win.
I said run, damn it!
You can't win this one.
He's too strong! He ain't human!
Don't! Don't!
Shut...
...up.
It'll soon be over.
Forgive me.
But, you are not my father.
My father died a long time ago.
Fear not...
Father!
(frightened sob)
Anytime you're ready.
Will it ever end?
(sigh) Guess not.
Huh. From the look of your face,
I'd say you had a
hell of a rough day.
You knew this
already didn't you?
You knew it don't
ever end once it starts.
I knew, Afro Samurai.
But, I won't say anything.
Not anymore.
But, y'know.
Not turning your back...
...that's the only
choice you've ever had.
Been waiting a
long time for you.