[NARRATOR]
The treasured sword Rukhnabad
is seen as proof of
kingship in Pars.
Gieve and Hilmes fought
for possession of the sword,
only to watch in dismay
as it was carried off
by the remnants of
the Temple Knights.
Hilmes immediately set out to
follow Archpriest Bodin's trail.
[BOTH yelling]
You might as well
give up now, bastard!
[BANDIT C]
You're dead!
[BANDIT E]
We're gonna kill you all!
It's only a troop of bandits.
Nothing to do with us.
[BANDIT D] You think
you're some kinda hero?
You should go.
Do not waste your life.
I've accompanied you this far.
There's no way I'm
going to give up now.
[JOVANNA]
My lady, get back!
[BANDIT C]
Die!
Who is that?
He's wearing a mask.
[BANDIT D]
Get them!
[yelling]
[MERLANE] We owe you
our lives. Many thanks.
It's lucky for us that a couple
of Parsian Knights
happened to be in the area.
Pardon.
[JOVANNA]
My lady!
You men are from Pars?
We are searching for
a countryman of yours,
a Prince Hilmes.
Perhaps you'd be able to tell
us where we might find him?
I'm sorry, but I don't
think we can help you.
I know that voice.
Lord Hilmes, is that you?
[IRINA] Lord Hilmes.
That is you, isn't it?
I am Irina. Princess of Maryam.
You must know me!
I said I cannot help you.
You pig! Can't you at
least show some courtesy?
[HILMES]
If you're headed for Ecbatana,
I would advise against it.
Take that token and make
for Zabul Fortress instead.
They will give you protection.
[MERLANE]
Hey! Don't walk away!
We should do as he suggested.
Let's set out for
Zabul Fortress.
Should we turn back, sir?
That woman. She seemed
to know who you were.
[HILMES]
That's none of your business.
Right.
[HILMES]
I have yet to regain the throne
that was stolen from me.
How could I even think
about facing her?
[screams]
[HILMES]
Lord Uncle!
Why would you do this?
[SANJEH]
As far as everybody knows,
you died in the fire
as you were supposed to.
Who the hell are you?
[SANJEH]
No one in particular.
If it matters, I knew your
Grandfather, Gotarzes the 2nd.
[HILMES]
Was it you?
Were you the one who saved me?
It was your bitter hatred
that drew me to you.
You summoned us with the rage
you felt against your uncle,
the rage you felt
against the world.
Why did you save my life?
What do you want from me?
Oh, not much, only
chaos and disaster.
I imagine you'll create both
when the time comes for you
to pursue your revenge.
It will be some years yet,
but I believe that it
will be worth the wait.
For now, you must leave Pars,
but you will return to us when
you've grown stronger.
And then, we will be
your eyes and ears
as you fight to
reclaim what you lost.
[HILMES]
You wished to see me?
I hear that you were up
in the middle of the night
practicing with your sword.
I'm harboring you
out of kindness.
Don't take that for granted.
Understand? I don't
want you doing anything
that will arouse
undue suspicion.
Behave yourself.
If folk knew you were
that Parsian King's brat,
I'd be in serious trouble.
Though I suppose that you're not
the only problem
child around here.
[GORNER chuckles]
[HILMES] What's wrong
with you? Are you blind?
Why bother gathering flowers?
[IRINA]
I can't see them.
But that doesn't mean I
don't enjoy smelling them.
Do you know this flower?
It's called the zeria.
Oh?
Its petals are bluish-purple.
And they fade gradually into
white toward the center.
They're round and full. And...
Words can only do so much.
Here. Try feeling it.
A zeria.
And what do they call you?
Are you so shy?
[HILMES]
Hilmes.
Hello, Lord Hilmes.
[HILMES]
Stop!
A bandage.
So you're injured then.
Well, as long as you have that,
I won't mistake you
for someone else.
Are you going to
tell me your name?
Well, since you ask, I'm Irina.
[JOVANNA]
My lady!
Must I always chase after you?
There's such a chill
in the air today.
And you know your
health isn't good.
Won't you please come inside?
Is something the matter?
[IRINA laughing]
We can't stay out much longer.
They'll be worried about you.
[IRINA] Not Jovanna. She'll
be running errands all day.
And I can assure you that
everybody else at the castle
will be perfectly happy
not to have me around.
Is that because of your eyes?
[IRINA]
Yes.
Princesses aren't supposed
to be blind, you know.
[IRINA]
Now, Lord Hilmes,
will you tell me what
the clouds look like?
[HILMES] Hm. Well they're
particularly large today.
[IRINA]
How large are they?
I'd say they're almost
as big as countries.
Wow!
And they're floating
away quickly.
Like they have
someplace else to be.
[IRINA] Listening to
you describe things,
I feel like I can see.
It makes me happy.
[HILMES]
Talking to me makes you happy?
Yes.
I'm glad.
[HILMES]
You know, Irina,
on the other side of this sea
lies the Kingdom of Pars.
[IRINA]
Yes.
From what I hear, it's a
very prosperous country.
You should know.
I'm actually a Prince of Pars.
[IRINA]
Huh?
[HILMES] For now I must live
like this, hiding my identity.
But someday I will
take the throne back.
I don't understand.
[HILMES]
Once I'm King,
I'll be able to return
and help you.
I'll come back to Maryam.
And free you.
[gasps]
It seems the time has come.
[HILMES]
You! It's been so long.
I thought you'd like to know
that King Andragoras
has given his son
the title of Crown Prince.
Crown Prince? That title
belongs to me and no one else!
If you're interested,
the boy's name is Arslan.
Seek what's yours.
Follow your destiny.
Your path will
reveal itself to you.
Hey!
Lusitanian soldiers?
What's happening?
[GORNER]
It won't be long now.
Maryam is already on
the verge of surrendering
to the Lusitanian invaders.
It would be a good idea
to be on the winning side.
Don't you think?
[HILMES]
You bastard!
Selling out your own country?!
Well, the price was right.
And I thought I might as well
sell you while I was at it.
Along with the poor,
blind Princess.
Can't let her go
to waste, can we?
Get back!
No, stop! I can help you!
Please just spare me!
[JOVANNA]
This way, my lady.
The guards! They'll come
to help, won't they?
Hello, there. I think we're
gonna have fun together.
[chuckles]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER H]
Who are you?
Lord Hilmes!
That is you, isn't it?
Stay away!
[HILMES] This is the
beginning of everything.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Lord Hilmes, please--
My name is Prince Hilmes.
My father's name was Osroes.
And I am the rightful
King of Pars.
The throne is mine!
[HILMES] I never thought
we would meet again,
and certainly not like this.
Irina.
[MESSENGER A]
A report from Lord S.
[ZANDEH]
Did he find their trail?
Yes.
The Temple Knights have traveled
to what was once Maryam.
They're in contact with members
of the former royalty there.
[HILMES] So, Archpriest Bodin
hopes to use ruined nobles
to regain his power.
Let's go, Zandeh.
Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR] Peshawar Fortress
was in a state of shock.
King Andragoras had escaped
his Lusitanian captors
and made his way to the border,
bringing Queen Tahamenay
along with him.
These are my orders,
Arslan. Listen well.
I will require more
men to retake Pars,
and you will assemble
them for me.
And don't bother showing
your face here again
until you amassed a force
of at least 50,000.
[ARSLAN] Sir, I humbly
accept the royal mandate.
What are you waiting for?
You've received your
orders, haven't you?
Make the necessary provisions
and depart immediately.
Majesty.
I don't doubt the Crown Prince
will obey your mandate,
as is only proper.
And, if your Majesty
does not object,
those of us who have served
His Highness thus far
would humbly request
to continue doing so.
No, Narsus. I will require
your services here.
As well as Daryun's.
You do not have my permission
to accompany Arslan.
He may not use the word,
but this is banishment!
Considering everything
Prince Arslan has accomplished,
he should be celebrated.
It seems the stories about
the tyrant of Pars were true.
Rumors say Arslan is not
of Andragoras's blood.
Given the difference
in their temperaments,
that does seem more
and more plausible.
The Queen didn't even
bother to see him.
[NARSUS] It's possible that
the King wouldn't let her.
If it was her own choice,
then it was a cruel one.
At any rate, we have
plans to make.
Our goal had been to
reach the Royal Capital
and rescue His Majesty
from the Lusitanians.
Clearly, that has now changed.
It's not complicated.
I'll serve Prince Arslan
and that's all there is to it.
If I were to leave
his service now,
the last High Kahina's spirit
would cast a curse upon me.
To be perfectly honest,
I fear a curse from the dead
far more than the King's wrath.
And what about you, Gieve?
What will you do?
I feel no particular obligation
to obey the so-called-King,
Andragoras.
Interesting.
It almost sounds as if
you're enjoying this conflict
that's arisen between
the King and Prince Arslan.
Oh really? Is that
what it sounds like?
Yes, it absolutely is.
Well! I never knew you were a
mind-reader, Mistress Farangis.
What a delightful discovery!
Must you always be so obnoxious?
Your timing couldn't
be worse if you tried.
What are you doing here?
Sorry to drop in like this,
but the soldiers are watching.
I have a message
from Lord Narsus.
[ARSLAN]
I thought I was ready for this.
Surely if I was his true son,
he wouldn't have sent me away.
But--
No. I will not think
of this as banishment.
But as being given my freedom.
Because that way,
I don't have to hate him.
My friends, thank
you for everything.
[KISHWARD] Your Majesty,
I thought you might like to know
that Crown Prince
Arslan has departed.
Tell me, Kishward.
What comes first to you,
loyalty to the kingdom,
or loyalty to Arslan?
[KISHWARD]
Sir.
I don't think anyone
could doubt that I am,
and always have been,
a loyal subject of Pars.
I promise that my loyalty
has never wavered.
If that's true,
then bend the knee.
Swear fealty to
your rightful King
and pledge your life
into my service.
[KISHWARD]
Yes, sir!
Do something! Why are
you just sitting there?
You fret unnecessarily, Daryun.
Really, it's not as
if His Highness
is headed for
enemy country.
He's been exil--
[tapping]
[DARYUN]
"Play along."
[NARSUS] I've explained the
situation to Elam and Alfar+d.
They're taking care of it.
Right. Sorry.
I was overreacting.
I'm sure His Highness will
be fine without our help.
[NARSUS] They may be young,
but they're clever.
They know what to do.
Of that I have no doubt.
We just have to trust
them and wait.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER A]
Fire!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER B]
Hurry!
What's that?
What's going on?
[PARSIAN SOLDIER E]
I'm sorry, sir.
The stables and
watchtowers are on fire!
What?
[PARSIAN SOLDIER F]
Get water! Quick!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER H]
Don't let it spread!
[PARSIAN SOLDIER G]
Lord Daryun!
Get out of my way!
Go notify Lord Kishward!
Right!
Sindhura is my homeland,
and I left it for one reason
and one reason only:
Because I owe my life to
Prince Arslan thrice over.
I have no intention
of leaving his side
until I have repaid him.
Honor is such a
cumbersome thing.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER L]
Halt!
But I suppose there's
no helping it, is there?
A man must be true to his heart.
[ELAM]
Lord Narsus!
Damn it!
[ALFARID]
Narsus!
Keep moving!
Right!
Stand down, Kishward.
Turn back now.
Before it's too late.
[DARYUN]
I'm doing what I must.
I don't want to fight you,
but I will if I have to.
Please, step aside.
I wish I could, Daryun.
But I still have my orders,
and I cannot disobey
the King of Pars.
[DARYUN] I understand
why you feel that way.
And I hope that you
understand my choice
to stand by Prince
Arslan as well.
[KISHWARD] You seek to honor
Elder Vahriz's final wish.
That's part of it. It's true.
But more than anything,
I'm doing this for myself!
Very well then.
I have no choice.
I'm sorry.
I cannot let you pass.
I'll do everything
I can to stop you!
[yelling]
I'm not going to make
this easy for you.
I must do my duty to my King!
Even with you as my opponent,
I will hold nothing back!
[yells]
[FARANGIS]
I have to admit,
I find your notion
of honor ridiculous.
You spoke a vow to your King,
and now you're
bound by it forever.
Yet you don't give a damn
whether following that vow
is the right thing to do.
Coming?
Indeed.
[FARANGIS] Let's gain as
much ground as we can.
What are you waiting for?
After them! Go!
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[KISHWARD]
I'm sure you will do your best.
But against them, I doubt
that you will succeed.
[AZRAEL crying]
[ARSLAN]
Time to go.
[AZRAEL crying]
It's Azrael!
I guess I'm not
completely alone.
[DARYUN]
Your Highness!
[ARSLAN]
Daryun! Narsus! Elam! Farangis!
Alfar+d! Gieve! Jaswant!
Your Highness, we're willing
to accept your rebuke,
and we will endure
His Majesty's anger,
but we believe we can give
our lives as we see fit.
And so we offer them
to you, my Prince.
It's been a very long
and very difficult road.
And yet through all of it,
you have stood by me.
Well, we should get going.
We have much to do.
[ALFARID chuckles]
Not going to yell at us?
Or tell us to leave?
At this point, I know it
would be a waste of breath.
How could I ever think
to send you away?
Surely the gods would
punish such idiocy.
I'm so glad you came.
I could not do this without you.
[NARRATOR] Prince Arslan's
path was no longer
a sad and solitary one.
To do as King Andragoras
had ordered,
he still needed 49,993 soldiers.
But with his friends
at his back,
at least he wouldn't be
seeking them alone.
They set off for the south
to the port of Gilan.
[NARRATOR] Shaghad is a
distant relative of Narsus.
His father's elder sister's
husband's cousin's son?
Next time, "A City of Land
and a City of Water."
And thus would the
boy become King.