[NARRATOR]
Arslan and his companions
put an end to Shaghad's plot
and freed the port city of Gilan
from his corrupt influence.
Unfortunately, the peace was
short-lived,
ending when an unexpected
visitor arrived in Gilan
seeking an audience with Arslan.
Just slow down.
Gather your thoughts,
then tell me what's going on.
It's King Innocentis.
He's being held prisoner.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
He asked me to help him,
and I did my best.
But instead I was framed
and branded a traitor.
I didn't know what I could do
or where else I could go.
So, I came here.
I'm in no position
to ask for favors,
but please, will you
march to Ecbatana
and free His Majesty?
[GUISCARD] My Lord Brother
survived the attack on his life.
We are fortunate indeed that
he was not taken from us.
He may rule for years yet.
See that he is well
guarded as he recovers.
Sir.
We must bring Silver
Mask to justice.
He has made it clear that
he is no longer our ally.
I want him dead!
No matter what it takes!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Guiscard's persistent.
Looks like he's sent the whole
Lusitanian army after us.
Charge the enemy!
Protect your Prince!
Damn it!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER I]
There're too many!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER J]
Retreat!
[ZANDEH]
Lord S! Good to see you.
And you. Thought we
could lend a hand.
We appreciate it.
What of Zabul?
We set fire to the fortress
upon our departure.
[ZANDEH]
You did what?
[SM] A long-standing order
from His Highness.
It felt like a waste,
but better that than let
the Lusitanians have it.
He's correct.
Zabul was a small, outlying
fortress of little consequence.
You did well to burn it.
[SM]
Sir.
And what of Rukhnabad?
Did you find it?
Yes, in what once was Maryam.
Very well. Then that
is where we are headed.
I will have that sword.
The King has been
removed from power.
Prince Guiscard rules now.
He's the King's own brother.
How could he conspire
against His Majesty?
It's nothing new.
He may not have the title,
but Guiscard has
held all the power
in Lusitania for some time.
That aside, do you understand
what you're asking of us?
Your King invaded Pars.
Yes, I know that!
I do. I realize that what
I'm asking is crazy.
Even so, I had to try.
I didn't know who I could
turn to besides you.
I'm glad you came, but--
Oh. Well.
I see there have been some
interesting developments
while I was away.
And here I didn't
think the Prince
was particularly skilled
in that department.
Keep your speculations
to yourself.
[GIEVE]
Mistress Farangis told me we had
some unexpected visitors,
and I can see now exactly
how correct she was.
Of course I was correct.
The Djinn don't lie.
By the bye, who is this
strapping young man?
My name is Merlane.
I'm a member of the Zot Clan.
Wait, the Zot Clan?
I hadn't planned
to seek you out,
but then Étoile
told me that my--
[ALFARáD] I heard
Étoile's here. Is it true?
[MERLANE] You stop right there.
Oh, hey, big brother.
That's her brother?
[MI want some answers!
Where have you been
all these months?
That's none of your business!
[MERLANE]
Don't you run from me!
We're going to have
a nice, long talk!
There's nothing I
wanna talk about!
Quit pretending you've
forgotten our father's wishes!
[ALFARáD]
I don't care what he said.
I have no interest
in becoming Chief!
She say Chief?
I don't see why you
just can't do it.
You're older than I am,
and I don't want to!
But I'm not the
one Father chose.
And I certainly can't ignore
the man's dying wish!
[ALFARáD]
Why not?
It's not like you and
he got along anyway.
If I can ignore what he
wanted, then so can you!
Are you joking? She's next
in line to be clan chief?
No! I am Narsus's wife,
and that's all I want to be!
Wouldn't it be a good
idea for you to step in
and say something
right about now?
I mean, this is a matter that
concerns you too, after all.
No, it does not.
I look forward to
hearing the whole story,
but for now, allow me
to welcome you.
We're happy to have
Alfar+d's brother with us.
And thank you for escorting
Étoile all this way.
I am grateful.
I should thank you.
For looking after my sister
until I could track her down.
No small feat.
[ALFARáD grumbles]
And what of Ecbatana?
Can you tell us the
state of things there?
[MERLANE]
Certainly, Your Highness.
The capital is anxious.
Guiscard is hunting down
a man named Hilmes,
and he's having
a hard time of it.
[gasps]
What did you just say?
Listen to me!
It was Hilmes who
killed our father!
We have to make him pay!
[MERLANE]
Him? He killed our father?
Damn it! I spoke to the man.
If I had known, I would've
cut him down instead!
[DARYUN]
Interesting.
After all this time, Silver Mask
has parted ways with Lusitania.
Which he was planning
to do all along.
At least, I would assume so.
[DARYUN] You know what
his next move'll be.
[NARSUS] Yes, to take
back the Royal Capital.
What now, Hilmes?
[NARRATOR]
July.
Peshawar Fortress was in a
state of heightened tension,
its soldiers ready and waiting.
At long last, the time
was approaching
for them to launch
a full-scale assault
on the Lusitanian invaders.
[ZARAVANT] I am a knight
of Pars, and as such,
my position dictates
that I serve His Majesty.
Still.
I saw how he treated the Prince.
Just thinking about
it makes me furious.
How can I follow such a man?
[KISHWARD]
Do not be ruled by your temper.
Remember why we're
fighting in the first place.
We are trying to free
the people of Pars.
Our main concern is ridding
our kingdom of invaders.
Is it?
Forget the royal
family and the Court.
The people are what matters!
Where did you come from?
Poor Lord Kishward.
You're walking
around like you got
the weight of the world
on your shoulders.
Piece of advice.
This life can be
ugly and unfair.
Best not to take
it too seriously.
[KISHWARD]
Can I ask you something?
Why are you here? Why did
you remain at Peshawar?
I recall the battle of
Atropatene well enough.
Didn't you abandon the line
of battle before anyone else?
I wasn't keen on
following a ruler
who would run from
the battlefield.
That hasn't changed.
To be honest, I'm a
lot more interested
to find out what the future
holds for young Prince Arslan.
Making it all the more
strange that you stayed.
We Marzbs are a rare breed
at this point, Kishward.
Not many of us left.
I dunno, guess I couldn't
stand the thought
of your pitiful face if
I left you here all alone.
[laughing]
[KISHWARD]
I wonder...
What does the future hold
for Prince Arslan?
[clatter]
[KISHWARD]
What's this?
Elder Vahriz sent a
message before his death.
Lord Bahman must have hidden it.
And he took care
to hide it well.
No surprise it wasn't
found until today.
I wonder what could have
been so important.
Hello, Lord Kishward.
Good evening, My Lady Queen.
Forgive me, but I wasn't
expecting you at such an hour.
I'll take that paper
you hold into my keeping.
A loyal servant of the
Crown has no need of it.
I am pleased, Lord Kishward.
It seems that you are more than
a valiant soldier and general.
You fully understand your place
as a servant of the Crown.
I, for one, believe
the Kingdom of Parse
is lucky to have you.
And I'm pleased to
learn no rift has arisen
between Lord and vassal after
what has recently transpired.
Sir... If I may ask.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Yes?
Before Lord Bahman's death,
he changed suddenly
and inexplicably.
Could it have been due to the
contents of that message?
That is possible.
However...
[KISHWARD gasps]
What's done is done.
The past cannot be changed.
[ANDRAGORAS] Human nature
is a dark, twisted thing.
There may be those who
like to pretend otherwise,
but even royals are human.
There is not a royal
family in this world
that is beyond reproach.
Does not matter if they
are adorned with jewels
and draped in the finest silks.
Look past those
trappings of wealth
and do you know
what you will find?
Lies, bloodshed, and intrigue.
Do you understand?
I do.
[KISHWARD] If the blood of
the royal family of Pars
truly does not flow through
Prince Arslan's veins,
then that means he has
nothing to do with the spell
that binds the royal family.
And if that is the case,
it could be a wonderful
thing indeed.
[ARSLAN]
Interesting.
I didn't realize that
things had fallen
into such disorder
in Ecbatana.
This may very well turn
out to be a situation
that we can use
to our advantage.
Yes.
All I'm asking is that you
help me rescue His Majesty.
Then our troops will
withdraw quietly.
We will return any riches
we have plundered,
and offer apology to the dead.
I promise you.
Except that your promise
is not the one we need.
How can you presume to
offer us such assurances
when you are neither the ruler
of Lusitania nor its Regent?
I know I can persuade
my Lord King.
He'll understand the situation.
He will listen. He's a good man.
Oh, I'm sure he's
a wonderful man.
Thanks to him a million
Parsians are dead.
He could be the nicest
person in the world
and it wouldn't matter.
A man can only be judged by the
right and wrong of his actions.
[ARSLAN]
The one who holds power
has no understanding of
his responsibilities,
and the one who does
understand the responsibilities
holds no power.
She bears the burden
of this senseless situation all
on her own.
[ELAM]
Your Highness!
Lord Narsus!
[NARSUS] Yes, Elam, is
there some kind of problem.
Word of King Andragoras's army.
They've set out from Peshawar.
They're on the way to Ecbatana.
What?
[BODIN] O devout followers
of the God of Yaldabaoth,
together we have borne
the unbearable.
Now here we stand,
united in our faith.
From this devastated land
that once was Maryam,
we launch our holy war anew
to cleanse this world
of the heathen menace.
[FOLLOWERS gasping]
Behold!
My valiant Temple Knights
journeyed to far-off
Mount Demavant
and brought back this prize.
It is the treasured sword
of Pars. Rukhnabad!
The Parsians are
weak and foolish.
They won't stand before us.
I hold their precious sword.
What better proof could there
be that God has forsaken them?
Our God bids us to bring
his light to the heathens
and destroy them
if they will not see.
We will rule this Earth
in his holy name
and bring his glory
to all its people!
[FOLLOWERS cheer]
[BODIN] This sword is
but a heathen trinket.
I would love nothing more
than to destroy it.
Unfortunately, it is
a powerful symbol
and much too useful against
the people of Pars and Maryam
to dispose of.
[chuckles]
[HILMES]
Put down the sword, you thief!
Only the rightful King of Pars
may lay his hands upon
treasured Rukhnabad!
[BODIN]
You! Silver Mask!
[BODIN] How did you
know where to find me?
I'm blessed with talented
men under my command.
All who live along the
Continental Highway
know the legend of the
treasured sword Rukhnabad.
It's not something that
can easily be hidden.
You escaped at Mount
Demavant, not again!
[yells]
Damn you! Kill them all!
Move aside!
You bastard! What of
your ally, Guiscard?
You might say we had
a parting of the ways.
He is no longer of use to me.
That's all you care about:
Finding a way to use others
for your personal gain.
I'll kill you! I'll kill
you! I'll kill you!
The threats of a delusional
old zealot don't scare me.
[growls, yells]
I weary of you.
[TEMPLE KNIGHT I]
Lord Archpriest!
I am God's messenger. I cannot
die now! My work is not done!
Fight, men. Protect me!
[TEMPLE KNIGHT I]
Yes, sir!
Take care not to kill civilians!
Silver Mask!
It's only a matter of time
before you are
stricken by God's wrath!
[ZANDEH yells]
[BODIN]
You will be punished for this!
Yes, this is where you
belong. In my hands.
O great Rukhnabad.
[SM]
This is as it should be.
To bring order to
the chaos in Pars,
our only choice is to
follow the rightful King.
At last, it is time.
To consign the
usurper to oblivion.
And retake the Royal Capital!
Now it's time we
march to Ecbatana.
Highness, our
troop strength is...
Low. We're well short
of the 50,000 we need.
Yes.
[GIEVE] I'm not the tactical
genius around here,
but wouldn't it be considerably
more convenient
for us to stay where we are
and let the others sort
things out themselves?
A tempting idea,
but no. We can't.
First and foremost, know this.
We remain loyal to
Pars and her King.
That being said, here are
my thoughts on the matter.
Zealotry, prejudice, and hatred
have harmed Lusitanians.
More than anything else.
If they can see that,
there will be no more
need for us to fight them.
What are you saying,
Your Highness?
You won't kill the enemy?
[ARSLAN] I do not believe
there is any reason
to destroy a whole people.
In my opinion,
it would be enough
for them just to leave Pars.
As for my father, I doubt
he will show any mercy.
He will annihilate them,
and in doing so,
perpetuate the cycle
of bloodshed.
We can't let that happen.
Somebody has to stop him, and we
are the only people who can!
Daryun. Narsus.
There must be a way.
A path that is my own
and not my Lord Father's.
Is that not right?
Yes indeed, Your Highness.
Quite right.
Then we are all in
agreement. Good.
And if our plan also
accomplishes Étoile's goals,
surely there's nothing
so wrong with that.
Open the doors now.
Sir.
Eavesdropping?
Forgive me, but
do you mean to say
we're going through
with the girl's plan?
I'm confused, Highness.
More like incorporating
it into our own.
Go, don't be shy!
Seems you've been outwitted.
How does it feel?
[NARSUS sighs]
Guess it was bound to happen.
This is the path we must take.
You have spoken with great
wisdom and eloquence, Highness,
and your words will
form the foundation
of our future policies.
The wind is strong today.
Once the sun rises,
I am sure we will see the dust
clouds dance most fiercely.
Yes.
Now, men, follow your King
and be certain you
do not fall behind.
[GUISCARD] Look at how
run-down and lifeless
this city has become.
It's barely worth
fighting for anymore.
Even so, my rage
remains undiminished.
I hate these filthy heathens,
and their bestial King.
I want that man dead. Dead!
We will show these Parsian fools
just how unwise it is to resist.
And when we're finished,
they'll know who is
truly the supreme ruler
of the Continental Highway!
Daryun.
Sir.
Should the worst happen,
it is possible that I
will end up in conflict
with my Lord Father,
and I've dragged all
of you into it with me.
You didn't drag me anywhere.
I follow you willingly,
Your Highness,
and nothing is going
to change that.
[NARSUS]
We are heading down a path
from which there
can be no return.
Narsus. Do you have to
sound so happy about it?
Why shouldn't I?
His Highness is embarking
on a great journey.
How can I not rejoice?
Don't even try to tell
me you're not excited.
I can see it on your face.
What? You cannot!
[ARSLAN laughing]
There's nothing more comforting
than the two of you bickering.
Daryun. Narsus.
Ecbatana will be ours again.
Yes, sir!
Indeed, Your Highness.
All right, men,
the time has come.
Today we march for
the Royal Capital!
[PARSIAN SOLDIERS yells]
[ARSLAN] There is still
so much about my identity
that I am unsure of.
However, that doesn't seem
as important as it once did.
I am a vessel.
I can become anyone.
And so, I shall become the King
that everyone wishes me to be.
[NARRATOR]
After many bloody months,
all the forces vying
for control of Pars
were at last charging toward
a single point on the map:
The Royal Capital of Ecbatana.
Born of fear, and anger,
and determination,
a bloody storm would arise
in the narrow space
between the Heavens
and the Earth.
In the midst of the bloodshed
and dancing dust clouds,
history was about to take yet
another transformative turn.
[Yashasuiin!