[NARRATOR]
Pars Era, the year 321. June.
Six months earlier,
after seizing the Royal
Capital of Ecbatana,
Lusitanian forces were
drunk with victory,
but now, no hint of their
former glory remained.
The Royal Capital lay in ruins,
and morale among the
troops steadily declined.
Guiscard took advantage
of the confusion
following Andragoras's escape
to imprison his brother
Innocentis the Seventh,
and seize for himself the power
that he had coveted for so long.
However, any satisfaction
he might have felt
was overshadowed
by the difficulties
the Lusitanian forces now faced.
[SECRETARY A] Our water supplies
are dangerously low.
The troops won't survive
for long without water,
and they certainly
won't be able to fight.
What do you advise
that we do, Your Highness?
Cut water rations.
[SECRETARY A] The men
won't be happy about that.
Yet another problem we
can lay at Bodin's feet.
If he hadn't destroyed
the aqueduct,
our supplies would be fine.
That blind fool doesn't
care what havoc he wreaks
as long as it means
killing heathens.
We need water!
Push the Parsians harder.
Get that aqueduct repaired.
Yes, sir. We'll do all we can.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A]
A report for you, sir.
Some of the men
are getting restless.
They're calling for a
massacre of the Parsians.
That's simply not
going to happen.
It was decreed
that they were not
to be killed
indiscriminately.
We can't go back on that now.
Get them out of here before
they can cause trouble.
Tell them they've been chosen
to strengthen our defenses
outside the city walls.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER A]
Yes, sir.
Damn those fanatics.
At least we can put them
to use as human shields.
[NARRATOR] Having parted
ways with Arslan's party,
Étoile arrived in Ecbatana
and spent every day
seeking aid for the wounded that
she had brought back with her.
Unfortunately, despite
all her efforts,
she found no one who
was willing to help,
and the situation began
to seem hopeless.
[INNOCENTIS]
Over here.
What is it? Who are you?
Surely you know who I am!
[gasps] It can't be!
Are you His Majesty the King?
[INNOCENTIS]
Indeed, I am.
The rightful ruler of Lusitania,
and god's proxy upon this earth.
What about you, young man?
I'm guessing you're a soldier.
Yes, sire.
Newly returned from the battle
at the Keep of Saint Emmanuel.
My name is Étoile,
Your Majesty. I am a squire.
I brought our wounded
back following the battle.
[INNOCENTIS] Wonderful, well
done. Most courageous of you.
Listen, I can see that you
are worthy of my trust.
There is a favor
I would ask of you.
I am the victim of treachery!
Men who serve my brother,
Prince Guiscard,
have imprisoned me
in this tower.
I cannot believe
that my brother
is aware of what
his men have done.
No.
My own flesh and blood couldn't
be responsible for this.
Please, will you speak with him
and tell him what has happened?
I am yours to command,
Your Majesty.
[INNOCENTIS]
Thank you, Squire Étoile.
Do this for me,
and I will see to it
that you are made a knight.
The guards are coming.
You must leave, quickly!
[ÉTOILE]
Yes, sir.
[ÉTOILE] His Majesty
is being held prisoner
by men who serve under
Prince Guiscard?
If that's the case,
I'll have to speak with
the Prince in person.
Safe journey.
And if you find yourself
in any trouble,
you might try removing the axel
on the cart's right front wheel.
You should find
something of use there.
[ÉTOILE]
He is a heathen and a Parsian.
And yet he showed us
such compassion.
While those who supposedly
follow our own faith do nothing.
I'll use this money to see
that everyone is looked after.
And then...
[GUISCARD]
I didn't kill the man
because I thought he
might be useful later,
and it almost cost
me everything.
Never again.
From now on, I will eliminate
problems as soon as they arise.
But, fool though he may be,
he is still my brother.
I don't care for the idea
of soiling my own hands
with his blood.
[MONTFERRAT]
Pardon me, sir.
You remember the soldiers
we sent outside the walls?
They said they have
captured somebody
who claims to be a
Princess of Maryam.
Except that Bodin
and the Temple Knights
are supposed to have burned the
royal family of Maryam to death.
I believe she is an imposter,
but what would you
like us to do?
[GUISCARD]
Actually.
I heard that some princesses of
the blood escaped the slaughter.
I will meet with her.
Leave us now.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIERS]
Sir!
May I ask your name?
Why are your eyes closed?
Are you blind?
Earthly light has
been lost to me,
but I can see all I need to
with the God of
Yaldabaoth as my guide.
How pious.
I hear that you are a princess
of the blood of Maryam.
Every day I spend on this earth,
I wish that weren't true.
You Lusitanians
couldn't be content
with simply conquering
our kingdom.
You had to kill its royalty,
even though you had
promised you would not.
You set fire to
the royal palace.
Somehow, I managed to escape
with my elder sister Militsa
and a few of our retainers.
We ran to a castle on the
northwestern seaboard.
But in the end, that castle
fell just like the palace.
My sister gave her life for me,
sacrificing herself
so I could escape.
So, yes, I am a Princess of
Maryam. But I wish I wasn't.
Because then my
family might still live!
I can see that you have
suffered most bitterly.
It is understandable that
you would bear ill will
toward the King of Lusitania.
Who are you?
[JOVANNA] Honestly. What good
are you as a bodyguard?
You didn't even bother
trying to defend us!
[MERLANE] Putting up a fight
against that many soldiers
would only have
gotten us killed,
and now we're positioned in
the heart of the enemy camp.
[JOVANNA]
How is that a good thing?
Just stay calm.
I will rescue the Princess.
I promise you that.
My dear girl. My Princess.
How will she fare among
these barbarians?
I suppose this is an unfortunate
turn of events for you as well.
I know you're searching
for your sister
so you can resolve the issue
of your clan's leadership.
That will be difficult to do
from inside a dungeon.
Don't worry on my account.
[JOVANNA] Why would you go to
such lengths for the Princess?
[MERLANE]
I don't know.
I just don't like the
thought of her on her own.
Does that mean?
I'm going to find the Princess
and get her out of this castle.
Take advantage of the commotion
to make your own escape.
[GUISCARD] The girl's not
lying. She is a Princess.
[BAUDOUIN]
You're sure?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER
D] Pardon me, sir.
Yes, what is it?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
We captured someone
who was sneaking
into the palace.
A spy or assassin?
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
It's rather odd, sir.
He's dressed as
one of our soldiers,
and he says he wishes to
speak to Prince Guiscard.
[GUISCARD]
Well, boy,
my men tell me that you
sneaked into the palace
in order to speak to me.
You will have to say something
very interesting indeed
to avoid being punished
for your stupidity.
I didn't know what else
to do, Your Highness.
Forgive me, but are you aware
that His Majesty is
being held prisoner?
[GUISCARD] And why would you say
something like that, squire?
Your Highness, I'm acting
on His Majesty's command.
He asked me to make
sure you were informed
about what had happened.
Whatever my brother
may have told you
about being held
captive was not true.
[ÉTOILE]
I don't understand.
Why would His Majesty lie
about something like that?
It's sad to say, but I'm afraid
my brother is quite ill.
For his own safety,
I'm housing him in the
tower until he can recover.
[ÉTOILE]
He seemed perfectly well to me.
Will it allay your fears
if I visit my brother personally
and reassure him
that my men do not
mean him any harm?
Yes!
[GUISCARD] We have a Princess
hungry for revenge
and a squire whose loyalty
blinds him to all else.
Who knew the solution
to our problems
would simply fall into our laps?
[BAUDOUIN]
A beautiful Maryami princess
bribed an impressionable
young squire
to bring her close
enough to the King
that she could take his life.
I assume that is how the story
of his assassination will go.
A tidy solution, eh?
This should tie up a lot
of loose ends for us,
and we'll barely
have to do anything.
[ÉTOILE]
This way, sire.
Thank you.
I wasn't certain that you were
actually going to help me.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER E]
Huh?
What is it?
That's His Majesty.
But who is that
other man with him?
[INNOCENTIS]
In recognition of your service,
I shall formally appoint
you to be a knight.
We can hold the ceremony
tomorrow if you'd like.
That is a precious
gift you offer me.
But instead I would
ask Your Majesty
for a place where the refugees
from the Keep of Saint
Emmanuel might find peace.
[INNOCENTIS] You may ask
for whatever you like.
[ÉTOILE] The Prince is
waiting for you in here.
He says he'll clear up
this misunderstanding.
And if you've been mistreated,
he will beg you for forgiveness.
[INNOCENTIS]
Yes.
[ÉTOILE] I have brought
His Majesty to see you.
The King? Here?
Well, Guiscard.
Explain why your men have
abused me in such a manner.
Call if you have
need of me, Majesty.
Uh. Huh?
Are you truly Innocentis
the Seventh,
King of Lusitania?
Indeed, I am.
And what of you?
What's your name?
What are you doing here?
Where is my brother, Guiscard?
Thank you, God.
I won't waste the
opportunity for vengeance
you have granted me.
What's the matter?
Why are your eyes
closed like that?
For the royal family of Maryam.
Blood.
[screams]
What is the meaning of this?
I must've missed his throat.
[INNOCENTIS whimpering]
Help me! Is anyone out there?
Squire?
O God of Yaldabaoth,
have mercy! Someone save me!
[INNOCENTIS]
Please, God! Please!
I beg you, God of Yaldabaoth!
Allow me to slay this barbarian
who destroyed the
Kingdom of Maryam!
His cruelty and
disregard for human life
bring disgrace to your name!
No. No. No. No! Please, no!
[INNOCENTIS screaming]
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER E]
Your Majesty!
O God.
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER D]
Quick! Alert the Prince!
[LUSITANIAN SOLDIER E]
Tell Prince Guiscard
that the Maryami Princess
has stabbed His Majesty!
I'm coming!
Does he live?
Yes. Sir.
His Majesty's wound
is deep but not fatal.
As a larger man, the king has
a substantial layer of fat
that protected his vital organs.
I'm sure none of us is more
relieved than you, Highness.
[GUISCARD]
So much for my brilliant plan.
I need to get rid of
the other two
before they can say anything.
This is the soldier, sir.
I saw this one leading
His Majesty away.
So then you were behind
the assassination attempt?
[ÉTOILE]
No! What are you saying?
I would never do
something like that!
Prepare the squire
for execution.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir.
Prince Guiscard!
Please don't do this!
You have the wrong person!
I would never harm
the King! I swear it!
No one believes your lies.
[ÉTOILE]
It's true!
I'm being punished for
a crime I didn't commit!
You won't be forgiven
unless you confess.
In the name of the
God of Yaldabaoth,
I did not harm the King!
[MERLANE]
I'll wait until the last moment,
then shoot that bastard
and rescue the Princess
in the resulting confusion.
This woman tried to
assassinate the King.
For that, she'll
burn at the stake.
The one who
orchestrated this plot,
Squire Étoile,
shall be beheaded.
[IRINA]
O God of Yaldabaoth.
I was finally able to strike
a blow against the man
who ordered the
murder of my family.
For that I thank you.
[IRINA] Lord Father,
Lady Mother, dear sister....
I will be with you soon.
Goodbye, Lord Hilmes.
[horse whinnies]
That man again.
Hilmes!
[MERLANE]
Hilmes?
So the Princess was right.
It really was him we met.
You came back for me.
[GUISCARD]
Hilmes!
Get back here! What the
hell are you doing?
[HILMES] Framing the
Princess of another kingdom
for attempted regicide?
What were you thinking?
I don't see any point now in
our continued collaboration.
We're finished.
[GUISCARD]
Bastard!
You're in Prince Hilmes's way!
We're through here.
[ZANDEH]
Sir!
What do you want with me?
[MERLANE]
We can talk later.
Why would Silver Mask come
to Princess Irina's rescue?
[GUISCARD]
Damn that man!
I knew we couldn't trust him,
but I hadn't expected him
to do something like this.
We will have no further
dealings with him.
I officially declare him
an enemy of Lusitania.
If I had to guess,
I'd say that they'll make
for Zabul Fortress.
Ride after them!
I want that treacherous
snake to die!
Yes, sir.
[MERLANE]
It looks like we lost 'em.
[ÉTOILE] Who are you?
Why did you save me?
[MERLANE] I hate the idea of
someone getting beheaded
for a crime they didn't commit.
Whatever the reason,
I'm alive because of you.
You have my thanks.
Oh please.
Something tells me you'd
've found a way to escape
even without my help.
A girl who can pass
herself off as a soldier
must be resourceful.
I guess Alfar+d isn't
the only young woman
going rogue these days.
[ÉTOILE]
Alfar+d?
Oh, sorry.
That's my little sister.
Why do you look so confused?
[ÉTOILE]
Is that a common name here?
How many girls in Pars
are called Alfar+d?
How would I know
something like that?
Though I doubt there are many
who are 16 years old,
have red hair,
and wear a light blue cloth
wrapped around their heads.
[ÉTOILE] Is she a fighter?
A skilled horsewoman and archer?
No ordinary man would stand
a chance against her.
[ÉTOILE] I've met her.
I know your sister!
You do? Can you tell
me where she is?
It's been a while
since I've seen her,
but she should be with Crown
Prince Arslan of Pars.
You're kidding.
I wouldn't have thought she
had enough feminine charm
to seduce royalty.
[MERLANE]
Fine.
Track down the Prince
and I find my sister. Uh.
What are you doing?
I'm coming with you.
And why would you do that?
I have no further
business with you.
[ÉTOILE] Nor do I have
any business with you,
but I do wish to
see Prince Arslan.
You people hate the
Parsians. Why seek him?
Because while he is a heathen,
he is also a man
who we can trust.
[NARRATOR]
Thus, in a single night,
fate took a number of turns,
sending more than one person
off in unexpected directions.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
as these events were unfolding
in the Royal Captial,
Arslan and his party
remained in Gilan.
Did you say Safdie Island?
[DARYUN]
Yes.
It is a small island located
approximately ten Farsangs
off the coast of
the harbor here.
And is there something of
interest on this island?
Yes.
I've been speaking to the
pirate captain we captured,
and if we can believe
what he says,
there's a treasure of
considerable value
on that island.
Really, pirate treasure?
So the captain says, anyway.
Hidden there by the
Pirate King Ahabek.
He was a well-known
bandit of the seas
off Gilan about 80 years ago.
The treasure is said to be
something around
100 million gold pieces.
Huh.
A positively obscene
amount of money!
One mention of gold and you
suddenly look like a child
who's been given a new toy.
Hidden treasure? I don't know.