[HILMES]
My name is Hilmes.
My father's name was Osroes.
I am the rightful King of Pars.
The throne will be mine.
[SORCERER A]
You did what?
And here I'd been
under the impression
you were a responsible,
intelligent man.
My mistake.
[HILMES]
Say what you will,
I don't think revealing
my identity was a mistake.
[SORCERER A]
You do like to push your luck.
You crossed swords with
Arslan and his underlings
at the Keep of Saint Emmanuel,
and yet the Prince still lives.
[HILMES]
When I finally defeat him,
I want it to be both
thorough and painful.
And for that, I need your help.
[SORCERER A]
Hmm...
The legendary sword Rukhnabad.
[HILMES] The sword of the
Hero King Kaykhusraw.
The stories say it was forged
from a piece of the sun.
Does it truly exist?
[SORCERER A]
A gift from the gods.
There's no greater symbol
of a man's right to rule.
Tell me where I can find it!
[SORCERER A] If you're truly
the descendant of the Hero King,
you should be able
to wield his sword.
But do not attempt that lightly.
I can wield it.
Once the sword is in my hands,
I'll give you all the
proof you could want.
[TjRNIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
[PARSIAN SOLDIER D]
Stay strong!
Peshawar Fortress is famed
for its impregnability,
but that ends today
with our conquest.
Charge!
[TjRNIAN SOLDIERS yelling]
They know that we're undermanned
because of the Lusitanian war.
Opportunistic savages.
These cowards cringe
behind their walls
because they lost their
capital to savages.
Show no mercy. Put the
mongrels out of their misery!
[yells]
What's this?
Your Highness!
Yashasuiin!
The Prince came for us!
Prince Arslan!
He's here!
You men stood fast
against overwhelming odds.
Now let us repay you.
[yelling]
[ILTERISH] From your armor,
I assume you are Daryun,
the Knight in Black.
That I am!
I am Jinong Eelt'rish of Tkr.
Many of my countrymen
have fallen to your sword
throughout the years.
I'm looking forward
to making you pay!
[DARYUN]
I don't know who you are,
but whatever grudge you
may have against me,
I will not let
you win this day.
I still have far
too much left to do.
Tkr saw that their
neighbor was weak
so they launched
an unjust war.
Time to show these pathetic
cowards their mistake!
Am I the only one who finds
this situation really annoying?
We're right back where
we started from!
Knowing Peshawar was
going to be attacked,
what else could we do
but turn around?
Yes, I know, but it's still
annoying. Right, Narsus?
I agree it's unfortunate we
had to turn the army back.
However, I am glad
we made it in time.
This simply means Lusitania
is not our only foe.
True. Which I think you
had already predicted.
That's my husband!
[ELAM grumbles]
Hear me, warriors of Tkr.
Do not rely upon the divine
protection of Dayang.
For you no longer have it!
Damn it. They're
attacking on both fronts!
How did they know
our battle plans?
[TjRNIAN CAVALRYMAN R screams]
Tch. I hope I haven't gotten
too rusty between battles!
Can't afford to waste any time
with this many men to kill!
[KUBARD]
So long!
An officer of Pars, eh?
Your head is mine!
[JIMSA laughs]
Say your prayers!
My Lord Kubard.
I know that you enjoy a fight,
but you should be more
careful with your life.
Kubard? I've heard that name.
"The Braggart."
That's what they call you.
Oh, is it? But perhaps
I'm some other Kubard.
It's not that unusual a name.
We're losing this battle.
We should return
to camp and regroup.
Fine, we'll go.
Damn these overreaching
Parsian mongrels.
[TjRNIAN SOLDIER E]
Retreat!
[TjRNIAN SOLDIER F]
All units, fall back!
Excellent! We made
it just in time.
Yes. That we did.
[NARRATOR] Lusitania was
not the only country
to covet the rich lands of Pars.
Seeing an opportunity, Tkr,
the country of nomads
to the north,
attacked Peshawar Fortress.
One month before,
Arslan and his army
had left the fortress
for Ecbatana.
They were halfway
to their destination
when the message came and
they were forced to turn back.
The month is now June of
the year 321, Pars Era.
Crown Prince Arslan has
accomplished much,
but greater trials
still await him.
[LUCIAN]
Thank you, Prince Arslan,
for turning back to bring
us reinforcements.
It's you who deserve my thanks
for holding until I returned.
Your Highness is too kind.
[ARSLAN] Peshawar stands
sentinel at our border.
If we were to lose
this fortress,
our other victories
would be hollow.
Even if we succeeded
in retaking the capital.
Highness, do we
know what became
of King Rajendra's
reinforcements?
Until recently,
Tkr was our ally,
so it's natural I would be
hesitant to fight them.
I did send word of their attack.
And now I shall
just have to pray
for the safety of Prince Arslan.
He's probably praying
to his gods as we speak,
pleading that our army and
Tkr's destroy one another.
He is a crafty man.
Yes, he is.
And what of Tkr's army?
[LUCIAN]
Following their retreat,
they reassembled roughly
one Farsang to the west.
[DARYUN] So they aren't
simply returning home, then.
[NARSUS]
The mounted nomads of Tkr
place great value on bravery
and success in the battlefield.
Defeating them will
not be easily done.
True. But we can't
afford to stay too long.
We must leave for Ecbatana soon.
Narsus, do you have
any suggestions?
[DARYUN] This is where
you've been hiding.
Elam was looking for you.
[NARSUS]
Oh?
[DARYUN] I hear the army
Rajendra dispatched
has finally reached the border,
but it seems they intend to
let matters run their course.
[NARSUS]
Hmph.
I can't say that I'm
especially surprised.
[DARYUN] What is it?
Something has you worried.
Actually, it's the lack of
something that has me worried.
Meaning?
When we pulled back,
the forces in Ecbatana
made no move against us.
That's what's bothering you?
They probably just assumed
it was one of your traps.
[NARSUS]
I hope that's the case.
Is there some reason
to think it's not?
My gut tells me something
else may be going on.
It's just a feeling, nothing
I can put a finger to yet.
Great.
Or I may be imagining it all.
As an artist,
I am far too sensitive
to be involved in
such earthly affairs.
I can't wait until this
is finally finished
and I can return to
the world of painting.
I doubt the world of
painting misses you much.
According to Lord Narsus,
they're not likely to launch
another attack immediately.
Which means that you
can relax for now.
[ARSLAN]
Yes. Assuming I'm able to.
[ELAM] You'll want to get
whatever rest you can
in case some crisis
does come up.
I know you've had
a hard time sleeping
since you decided to
return to Peshawar.
Uh. It's that obvious?
Only to somebody who's
paying close attention.
Nothing gets by you, does it?
Your health is very important.
We'd be lost without our Prince.
Please take care of yourself.
Yes. I'll try.
[ARSLAN]
Tell me, Elam.
What do you think Gieve
would do if he were here?
Would he distract us with a
merry song or a funny story?
[ELAM chuckles]
Perhaps he would.
I wonder where his travels
have taken him by now.
With him, there's no telling.
Knowing Gieve,
it's likely someplace
we couldn't even imagine.
[chuckles] I bet you're right.
[GIEVE] This situation
is deeply troubling.
I haven't seen a woman's
face in almost three days.
At this point if I encountered
a hideous hag,
I might think her a beauty.
I don't think I could ever
forgive myself for that.
Oh? And what's this?
No honest folk would
ever dare to go near
the treacherous
Mountain of Demavant.
I'm only here because
it's where my mission
for the Prince led me.
But what about you, Silver Mask?
[HILMES'S SOLDIER B] Lord Silver
Mask! We have found it!
[HILMES'S SOLDIER C]
The royal tomb of Kaykhusraw!
[HILMES'S SOLDIER D]
It really exists!
I thought it was just a legend.
Remember, men, we are
not tomb-raiding savages.
What we do is preserve the
rightful royal lineage of Pars.
[ZANDEH] You will touch
nothing but the sword!
We will commit no act of
sacrilege against the Hero King.
O Kaykhusraw, great founder,
Hero King, and forbearer,
I ask that you bestow
your righteousness
and courage upon me,
your descendant.
[HILMES] So this is the
treasured sword Rukhnabad.
None dare question
the man who wields it.
[GIEVE] Heh. I wondered
what you were up to.
I didn't realize you'd fallen on
such hard times, Silver Mask.
I would've thought looting a
grave was beneath even you.
The inept minstrel,
always barging in where
you're not wanted.
Have you come prepared to sing
a song mourning your own death?
I'd rather not defile
the royal tomb.
Go now and you may live.
I'll stay, thanks.
I can't leave a
treasure like that
in the hands of somebody
who's so unworthy of it.
That was nobly put,
if I do say so myself.
That's why you're here,
because you know the true
nature of this sword?
[GIEVE] Traveling musicians hear
more tales than most people,
but even I had to wander far
before I learned
of its existence.
Without a minstrel's gift for
ferreting out information,
I'm amazed you were
able to find it.
[HILMES]
You had your chance,
but it seems you do
wish to die here!
[GIEVE] Not at all. I've never
liked the idea of dying.
It sounds far too permanent.
[HILMES]
Ridiculous clown!
Give it back!
As far as I'm concerned,
this is just an antique.
Even so, it's an undeniable
symbol of a king's ascendency.
I will take this treasured
sword to Prince Arslan.
And with it, he will prove
his right to rule.
[HILMES]
You'll die first. Stop him!
[ZANDEH] That sword belongs
to the rightful king!
[GIEVE]
Oh! Good heavens!
Got it! Uh? What is this?!
Damn you!
[ZANDEH yells]
[HILMES] Get down there.
I want that sword found!
[HILMES' SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[ZANDEH]
Bastard.
[GIEVE]
What is this?
What do you want with the sword?
[ZANDEH yells]
Easy. I don't have what
you're after anymore.
[HILMES] Zandeh! They're
escaping with Rukhnabad!
[ZANDEH]
Who are they?!
That sigil... Temple Knights.
They must have been
sent here by Bodin.
[GIEVE]
How unfortunate.
I wasn't expecting
so much competition.
With so many players
getting involved,
I may need to bow out
of the game for now.
So...
[NARRATOR] Days after receiving
word of the defeat
at the Keep of Saint Emmanuel,
Prince Guiscard decided
to pay his first visit
to King Andragoras.
Knowing that Silver Mask's
true name was Prince Hilmes,
he sought to learn more
about the man's intentions.
[GUISCARD]
Greetings, Andragoras.
We have not met before.
I am the younger brother
of the Emperor.
My name is Prince Guiscard.
Guiscard, eh?
And what does a member
of the royal family
of Lusitania want with me?
I've come because
I would like to learn
more about your nephew.
The son of your late brother,
the former king, Osroes.
He calls himself Hilmes.
[ANDRAGORAS]
Hilmes died a long time ago.
Did he?
If your brother's son truly
is dead, then tell me,
who is the man
in the silver mask
who orchestrated your
defeat at Atropatene?
[ANDRAGORAS] A man wearing
a mask mysteriously appears
and tells you that his
name is Prince Hilmes,
and you take him at his word
without asking any other
questions of him?
As I've said, that's
the reason I came.
I want to learn more about
this man and his intentions.
I want to understand the
history you have with him.
[laughing]
Iron chain fighting,
developed by slaves in
the Kingdom of Nabataea.
Are you some kind of monster?
If you had such strength,
why not use it before now?
[ANDRAGORAS]
Unlike gold, iron rots.
If it soaks up sweat and soup in
the same places for half a year,
it crumbles.
In time, you can tear it apart.
[ANDRAGORAS] This was the
chance I was waiting for.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
You're much too valuable
a hostage for that.
Your life is the coin
I wil use to buy safety
for myself and the Queen.
[ANDRAGORAS laughing]
What's your business?
No one passes through without
the proper authorization.
I was in service to Count
Barcacion. Squire Étoile.
I bring the injured
from the battle of the
Keep of Saint Emmanuel.
Will you deny us entry?
[LUSITANIAN GUARD C]
Wait here a moment.
I'll confirm this at once.
[ÉTOILE]
Ecbatana. We're finally here.
[ÉTOILE] Basically,
what you're trying to say
is that you're abandoning us.
You've dragged us
with you all this way,
and now we're on our own.
I'm sorry, but I have no choice.
I have to turn back.
One of your most important
outposts is under attack.
Of course you have
to return to it.
[ÉTOILE]
What are you waiting for?
You do understand.
Thanks, Étoile.
Make sure you come back alive.
Everybody knows that
you heathens go to hell
when you die.
[ÉTOILE gasps]
What happened?
s this... really Ecbatana?
But it's a deserted ruin.
I am pleased to see
how well you look.
Tahamenay, dear wife and Queen.
How many years has it been
now since I stole you away?
And in all that time
you've never shown me a single
moment of love or affection.
You shut your heart
to the world.
And even if you wanted to,
you wouldn't know how
to open it again.
Can you blame me?
What more could you
possibly have expected?
I loved my child.
It is natural for a
mother to love her child.
Only a monstrous one would not.
I want my child! Give me back
the child you stole from me!
Please, I'm begging you!
Give me back my child!
[chuckles]
I'm impatient too, Azrael.
We must settle things here
as quickly as we can
and head for Ecbatana.
[NARRATOR] Events had taken
an unexpected turn.
And in the besieged
land of Pars,
the season of scorching heat
was fast approaching.
[NARRATOR] The Tkrians
roused Prince Arslan's anger
with their careless brutality.
Would he give them
cause to regret it?
Next time, "The Monarch
Versus the Conqueror."
And thus would the
boy become King.