[NARRATOR]
Safdie Island.
Also known as Treasure
Island by the pirates,
who claimed it was home
to the hidden treasure
of a legendary Pirate King.
Upon learning of the
supposed treasure,
some of Arslan's party
set out for the island.
Surely such riches would make
for an enviable war chest.
One hundred million gold pieces.
I find such a great number
difficult to believe.
[ALFARáD] It would take someone
a long time to count that high.
We couldn't ask for a better
opportunity than this.
The prince's most valued
fighters have set off
in search of a
nonexistent treasure.
Their absence leaves his
headquarters thinly defended
and ripe for the taking.
Soon this city will
be ours once more.
Are you ready, men?
[PIRATES yelling]
Poor, Narsus.
If only you had been content
to remain in seclusion,
then you wouldn't
have to die today.
[PIRATE A]
Move!
[PIRATE B] Thanks. Master
Shaghad's plan is working?
Yeah.
The little Princeling fell for
it hook, line, and sinker.
[PARSIAN SOLDIER D]
What's going on?
Quick! The pirates
have come ashore!
Prince Arslan!
The pirates have attacked!
They're headed this way!
They made no move until Daryun
and the others had departed.
Clearly, this is being
orchestrated from the inside.
Surely not!
Under Viceroy Pelagius's rule,
nothing like this ever--
Oh! I mean--
This building will be
their primary target.
Do not open the gates.
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
Yes, sir!
It's unfolding just as
Lord Narsus said it would.
Well, of course. Narsus's
calculations are never wrong.
No, he's been wrong once.
When? And what about?
Allowing you to
remain by his side.
It may be the only incorrect
decision of his whole life,
but it's a serious one.
After all I've done--
[ELAM]
Here they come.
Fire!
[PARSIAN ARCHER A]
Damn pirate scum!
[SHAGHAD]
There's no point resisting.
Be smart and open
the gates at once.
So, Shaghad,
it was you all along.
You've been pulling the
strings this whole time!
[SHAGHAD]
Yes, I have.
For a long while now,
this city has been
mine to run as I see fit.
Then you lot came
and tried to take it over
for that fool Prince of yours.
That's simply not
something I can accept.
You know, that sounds an
awful lot like treason!
The Prince will die in battle.
It will be a noble
enough end for him.
Far better for him to
end his life that way
than as the failed ruler of
a once prosperous city.
[growls]
Heh. The prince's best
fighters have left his side.
How will he fare without them?
You're nothing but
a selfish coward.
How could a man like you ever
have been Lord Narsus' friend?
[chuckles]
Narsus may think himself clever,
but he is a fool,
a naïve dreamer.
He simply can't accept that
people are inherently unequal.
If he's unable to see
something so clear,
how could he be considered wise?
[ELAM]
Take that back!
I see now!
You're envious of Narsus,
and you always have been!
You know you'll never
be half the man that he is.
That must really get to you!
[growls]
You think I envy him?
That's just ridiculous.
The poor man lives
in a fantasy world.
He thinks he can
abolish slavery?
What an idiotic dream.
He acts like I'm
the disappointment,
but it's the other way around.
[SHAGHAD]
What's that?
--[PIRATE F] Take cover!
--[PIRATE E] Damn it!
[PIRATE G]
Where'd that come from?
Good timing!
Why is the Zot Clan here?
You bastard.
Finally, you've shown your
true colors for everyone to see.
You've got a silver tongue,
but you won't talk your
way out of this one.
Remember, we're fighting
for Lady Alfar+d's husband.
Don't hold back, men!
Show 'em what we're made of!
[ZOT CLANSMEN cheer]
Well, Chief, your orders?
Eliminate the pirate threat!
Yashasuiin!
Thanks! Well done, you two.
Good job keeping the
enemy's attention off of us!
Happy to, my Lord!
[ZOT CLANSMAN A]
Don't worry, Lady Alfar+d!
We'll take care of the pirates!
I know you will!
Enjoy the fight!
I don't understand, sir.
It's Narsus. He's brought
us some reinforcements.
Wait. Your Highness.
You were only pretending
to be defenseless?
The enemy took the bait,
just as we expected he would.
This battle is crucial.
We'll expose the
corruption in this city,
and we will destroy it!
[PIRATE K]
Since when does the Zot Clan
take orders from
the Parsian Prince?
Your days of piracy end now.
You will be punished
according to your crimes.
The Prince is fair.
Surrender now and
perhaps he'll be merciful.
No! I'd rather die!
[JASWANT]
And what about the rest of you?
Do you want to die like your
misguided friend here?
It's an ambush!
[FARANGIS] O avaricious ones,
befouled with greed,
know that these arrows represent
the divine Mithra's wrath!
Let's get outta here!
Outta the way! Unless
you've got a death wish!
I'd say you're the one
with the death wish.
People of Gilan! How long are
you willing to live like this?
[GRZE]
Will you continue to be ruled
by your fear of these
cowardly mongrels?
Prince Arslan is here now.
He is trying to rid Gilan
of the corruption
that's festered for so long.
We're tired of living under
someone else's thumb.
Tonight, we're going
to take our city back!
[CITIZENS cheering]
Run! Let's go!
Get outta here!
You filth!
[CITIZEN C] This city
belongs to us, not you!
[CITIZEN D]
Damn thieving cowards!
Well done, ladies.
Brilliant, in fact.
Who needs a sword
and shield to fight
when you've got a sturdy pot?
I promise you won't regret this.
Prince Arslan will see that
your city is ruled fairly.
[LADIES]
Good! Take that!
[PIRATE H]
Damn it!
This is your doing, Narsus.
You deceived me.
[NARSUS]
You're not exactly one to talk.
Really, Shaghad. The initial
deception was actually yours.
I just made use of it, turning
it back on its original author.
The treasure of a Pirate King
hidden on a desert island?
You couldn't come up with
anything better than that?
You were so confident
in your plan
that you failed
to see its flaws.
[SHAGHAD]
You've always been like this.
An arrogant bastard
who thinks he's smarter
than everybody else.
Fire at will! I want
that man dead!
What?
[DARYUN]
Sorry, Narsus,
it doesn't look like your
reunion is going so well.
Such a shame when
friendships turn sour.
[PIRATE E]
Get 'im, boys!
Ugh! I've had enough!
Come back!
You're not escaping
me, merchant!
[SHAGHAD]
Hold him off!
Me?
Get out of my way!
[NARSUS]
Your Highness. Daryun.
I'm sorry, but I would rather
settle matters with Shaghad
on my own terms.
Get her out to sea!
Shaghad.
Narsus.
I've always thought of
you as a clever man,
but even the smartest person
will be undone in the end
with an overabundance
of arrogance and greed.
Kill him now.
[PIRATES yelling]
Narsus!
What did he do?
[GRZE]
Lord Daryun!
Master Gre.
Can we give you a ride?
[GRZE] Come on, men!
We've got work to do.
We're gonna make
sure those pirates
never mess with us again!
So you knew. What was
it that tipped you off?
The conversation we had
after we dealt with Pelagius.
It's about making money.
Whoever makes the
most is the victor.
That's all that matters.
Spoken like a
bloodless merchant.
Who wouldn't have suspected
you after that speech?
Your overconfidence in your own
cunning made you careless.
You should've known better
and held your tongue.
[SHAGHAD]
You were such a recluse.
I always assumed you
would stay holed up
in those mountains forever.
Why did you reappear now,
after all this time?
If I'm being honest, it was
something of a whim at first,
but not anymore.
I follow my Prince
wholeheartedly
because I believe in his
vision for the future.
You and Daryun are
both accomplished men.
What about that boy makes
you so eager to follow him?
You've obviously
lost the ability
to judge someone's character,
assuming you had
it to begin with.
If you cannot yet see why
we follow Prince Arslan,
I'd say there's very
little hope left for you.
Condescending as always!
Maybe someday you'll realize
that you don't know everything!
[PIRATE K]
Master Shaghad! Ships!
They're gonna be right
on top of us before long!
Forward!
It's Daryun!
You can talk about freeing
slaves all you want.
But I promise you,
it's never gonna happen!
You'll die trying to
achieve some silly dream!
You have all the
compassion of a stone.
No wonder you aren't
even willing to try!
Talking about compassion?
That doesn't seem like
the kind of quality
a military strategist
should prize.
A strategist devises plans
in order to attain victory.
As important as
winning, however,
is one's conduct
when the fight ends.
Despots and petty tyrants
reign all over the world.
We can do something to
change that, however small.
For me that's serving the
Prince in any way I can.
For as long as he needs me.
The Prince is little
more than a boy.
Do you truly think he's going
to change the world?
[NARSUS] If you weren't so
heartless and blinded by greed,
you could help.
You've gotten rich off
the suffering of others.
What will you do
with all that wealth?
Do you care nothing
for your kingdom?
[SHAGHAD]
I've heard enough!
[yells]
[screams]
I'm sorry, Shaghad.
I tried so hard to keep
you from the wrong path.
Go on!
Don't touch me!
Like it or not,
slaves are necessary.
If you were a slave, I might
even consider buying you.
For a copper piece or two.
Somebody has to
empty chamber pots
and dig graves for
camels, you know.
[SHAGAHD laughing]
We should make a
paste of hot chilies
and smear it on his tongue.
That's what we do
in my homeland.
When someone speaks
so disrespectfully,
we punish the tongue that
uttered the offending words.
King Rajendra's mouth
must always be on fire.
That was quite a risk you took!
You're not hurt right?
Not a scratch on me.
[ALFARáD]
Good! Once again,
My Narsus uses his cunning to
bring a villain to justice!
You make it sound as
if I did this alone.
But Shaghad's luck ran out
the day Prince Arslan and
his comrades rode into Gilan.
[ALFARáD]
Aww!
Anxious to learn what
your fate will be?
For my part, I bet you'll hang
after everything
that you've done.
[ARSLAN]
Shaghad.
When you leave here,
you will be handed to a slaver.
What?
For a whole year,
you will live in chains.
You will know the harsh,
relentlessly miserable
life of a slave.
You will be worked
to utter exhaustion.
You will know no
comfort or kindness.
For all that you were
born a human being,
you will be traded
like livestock.
That is your punishment.
Such a verdict is worthy of the
Sage King Jimshid's wisdom.
He speaks through the
lips of the Crown Prince.
One year? You really
are soft-hearted.
Once that year has passed
and I'm no longer in chains,
I'll be free to seek my revenge.
You might want to rethink that.
I happen to be a man
with a very long memory.
It doesn't matter if it's
one year later or 100.
I won't forget your crimes or
what you said here today.
[DARYUN]
Do not seek out His Highness
once your sentence is over.
Don't think for even a
second of doing him harm.
Or I will make your time as a
slave seem like a fond memory.
Bastard.
I don't know if it is true,
but I have heard that you
were once a man of wisdom.
I sincerely hope that
you will now become
a man of compassion.
For the sake of Narsus,
who once called you friend.
I will leave the rest
to you, Gre.
Make the arrangements
as you see fit.
[GRZE]
Yes, sir.
Pardon the intrusion.
I thought you might
like some tea.
Shall I bring you a cup?
No, thank you.
Elam, have you ever
heard the saying,
"With two hands, you cannot
hold three goblets"?
It's an old Parsian
proverb, I believe.
To pick something up,
you must put something down.
To gain, you must lose.
There was no avoiding it,
but to lose an old friend
is still a difficult thing.
[ELAM]
Lord Narsus, look.
[MAN A] Thank you for
seeing us, Crown Prince.
We citizens of Gilan are eager
to swear our loyalty
to Your Highness.
[MAN B] We are truly
grateful for the changes
you have brought to our city.
It is our hope that your
influence will soon extend...
And who exactly
are these people?
Wealthy men from the
areas surrounding Gilan.
One can't help but wonder
why they're coming out
of the woodwork now.
Thank you for your support.
I look forward to
working with you.
[NARRATOR] At last, Gilan was
free of its corrupt leaders
and firmly in Arslan's control.
[NARRATOR]
A fleet led by Gre
and accompanied by
Arslan's companions
attacked the pirates'
base of operations.
With Shaghad and
their captain gone,
the pirates were
easily rooted out.
The seas near Gilan were
made safe once more.
[ALFARáD] This banner
is for the Zot Clan?
Yes. We owe your
clan a great deal.
Without your reinforcements, we
surely would have lost the city.
Look at our fine banner!
I say.
From this day forward,
let us always fly this banner.
Let it be the symbol
of the Zot Clan.
And when we look up at it,
let us remember
that it is our duty
to fight against injustice
however we can!
[ZOT CLANSMEN cheering]
The Djinn have been
clamoring furiously.
Now I can see
the reason for it.
We seem to have
unexpected visitors.
[ARSLAN]
Étoile, what are you doing here?
[ÉTOILE]
Arslan, please.
I came to ask you to
send troops to Ecbatana.
It's King Innocentis.
I beg of you, help him!
[BOTH gasp]