Number 4, locked in.
Roger!
Number 2 here, also locked in.
Roger, Number 2.
Number 3, locked in.
Number 1, locked in.
Roger that, both.
All right, Inspector,
all the cars have been deployed!
Mm.
Advance squad,
how is it inside?
You called it, Inspector.
The whole security system's
been taken out.
And the diamond?
It's gone!
He snatched it from the case!
This is Team B.
No targets descending
from the emergency stairs.
We're heading up.
Don't concern yourself
with whispering.
Just assume you'll be
driving him to the roof.
Roger.
Right.
Now let's go over
the plan again.
Wherever he jumps out,
we'll blow him into the Tsukishima River
with the jet stream from the four cars in place
and then scoop him out like the
fishy little ne'er-do-well he is.
He's not getting away today,
no, sirree!
Do you think
he'll be taken in that easily?
There's a good chance he'll fight
back with that card gun of his.
They're tough little suckers,
but they're still just cards.
They're no match
for wind power!
All he can do is hang from that
glider-cape of his and shoot those cards.
Kid has style,
but wind is his weakness!
Kid! Kid! Kid!
Kid! Kid! Kid! Kid!
Inspector!
Hmm? So there you are, Kid!
Everyone get in position!
Sir!
This diamond and I
will be leaving now.
Who's the knockoff?
Commence operation. Capture Kid!
All cars, start your turbines!
He's heading east!
Numbers Two and Four,
Pattern B!
We got him!
What have we here?
Too stunned
to use your kite, Kid?
Fifty meters
to Tsukishima River!
Tsukishima River
capture squad, bring it up!
Hmm.
Kid fired a gun!
Live rounds fired!
Kid has an actual handgun?
Yahoo!
Kid is using the pleasure boats
to escape up the Tsukishima River!
Can't we use a chopper?
We didn't prep any
for this operation!
He shot off a live round?
we can use instead!
Coming through!
Move that damn fishing net
out of the way!
We can't pursue him
any farther!
Huh?
Hold it, Kid!
Ah.
No, you don't!
Should have known
that'd be too easy.
Zantetsuken.
How about that?
You should have said so
from the start...
...Lupin III.
He's Lupin III, a world traveler who
obtains anything he targets using his skills
as a master phantom thief.
His partner's Daisuke Jigen.
He's a professional
with a .3-second quick draw,
a cool gunman
with a strong sense of duty.
Goemon Ishikawa XIII.
With his mastery
of sword-drawing,
he can slice anything in two,
making him a man
you don't want to cross.
And there's one more...
the mysterious Fujiko Mine.
Is she a pirate, a spy?
Not even Lupin knows.
With all the trouble
she gets him into,
I don't know why
he keeps her in the gang.
Lupin has a weakness
for cute girls.
Figures.
The high school
detective, Shinichi Kudo.
While at a theme park with his
childhood friend and classmate Ran Mori,
he witnessed a shady business deal
between a pair of scary-looking men in black.
But he was so distracted
by the guys in front of him
that he didn't notice one of their
partners sneaking up from behind.
The man forced
some poison down his gullet,
and he awoke to the surprise
to end all surprises!
He discovered
that his body had shrunk.
If those no-goodniks got wind
Shinichi Kudo was still alive,
his life and the lives of his loved ones
would be in jeopardy, so to hide his identity
he took on
the name Conan Edogawa.
He now lives with Ran and her father,
who happens to be a private detective.
Oh, forget it.
I'll just have
to ask Kid instead.
Wha... Kid?
Kid the Phantom Thief. Heard of him?
Sure, I have!
They call the sneaky bastard
the Moonlight Magician,
but he's still
just a high-school brat.
Wonderful!
You gotta tell me where he is!
Come on, Lupin. Which
high school does he go to?
I stole it as Kid,
just like you wanted me to.
Evening, Lupin.
That was quite the show
you put on back there.
You knowing it was me
saves us a lot of time.
You can cancel
the detonation code now.
Sorry. 'Fraid I can't.
What do you mean?
Well, it's just that you say
you'll serve me if I spare this woman,
but can you really be trusted?
A test, huh?
Apologies.
You come highly recommended
by a certain acquaintance.
He said Lupin III was the only thief
capable of stealing the Cherry Sapphire.
You're gonna make me cry.
So? Don't keep me in
suspense. Did I pass?
With flying colors.
Contact me once you have
the Cherry Sapphire.
Bring it to me, and the
bomb's as good as deactivated.
Oh, and by the way, you should find tracing
this number to be a waste of precious time.
Looks like it.
Where does it say
the call is from, pray tell?
Before, it was some mountain in China,
and now it's a satellite over the U.S.
That's enough.
You're good. I admit it.
I see you're someone
I've gotta be serious with.
I'm glad
we understand each other.
I'll be sure not to forget
I'm dealing with Lupin III.
Hmm.
Huh?
The thing's
cut clean in two.
What kind of weapon
could do this?
Even cut through
the bulletproof carbon.
What terrifying power.
Like I thought,
this one is more suited to you.
...dispose of it in the bucket of some
stranger on the side of the road. I mean,
why bother stealing it
in the first place?
To stir up trouble, maybe?
If that was his aim, he
certainly succeeded. I mean...
Conan's been
watching TV all day.
...all they got
was three fish?
He seems down.
It's 'cause he tries to do everything
alone, and now that he can't, he's sulking.
Well, he fought
that Goemon guy and lost, right?
Yeah, and check this out. There's tons of
info saying Lupin III is currently in Japan.
And Goemon
is one of Lupin's pals.
So does this mean
he's in the city?
It's time for that quiz you
kiddos have been waiting for!
Aww.
You wanna do another pun quiz?
We're not really in the mood.
Yeah, sorry.
Don't be like that.
Come on, you guys.
Help him out.
We can't start
without a good pun quiz!
I am totally
looking forward to it!
I hope I guess
the right answer!
Hurry up!
Oh, boy. How obvious
can those kids be?
I love quizzes!
I prepped the white board.
You ready?
Yeah!
Yeah! Let's do it!
I've been
waiting for this!
Look this way!
I'm looking!
Lupin absolutely loves beans,
but which one of these
four types is his favorite?
Well, do you know?
I'll give you five minutes
to think about the answer.
So, which is the right bean?
Um...
A bean's a bean, right?
They come out of the same place
once you eat 'em.
Genta.
If only the bean in your head
would work a little harder.
The answer's three,
fava beans.
Really, now? Why's that?
The other three beans are all
what's known as alkaline foods.
Fava beans are acidic,
which shares
a Japanese word for "third."
"Acidic" and "third," huh?
Eh?
Lupin...
The third!
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
Are they trying
to pick a fight?
Rising Italian idol Emilio Baretti
arrived in Japan this morning.
The guy's an
unpredictable world traveler,
but I can't say I ever
expected to see him again.
Look, Conan! Emilio is gonna
have a live concert here in Japan!
The Singing Nobleman,
Emilio Baretti!
He's super popular
all over the country!
...I know him personally!
You're kidding.
You see that?
Definitely.
She was amazing, right?
Super amazing.
Maybe his manager?
Whoever she is,
she's really beautiful!
Isn't she?!
Men'll be men, I see,
even when they're kids.
A pretty lady shows up,
and they're totally captivated.
I'm electing not to comment.
This was live
from Haneda Airport.
Wow, how exciting to have
a major star here with us.
That was
definitely Daisuke Jigen.
Even Conan's looking!
No! You've got it all wrong!
How jerky.
Unbelievable!
Knock it off!
You were looking!
I was not!
This is the diamond
that was stolen by mistake.
And here are the bullets
that were fired at the crane.
Did you say, "mistake," sir?
That's a heck of a mistake.
Well, that's Lupin.
He made it a point
to imitate Kid,
and then he took off with
a diamond he didn't even want
and chucked it
into a fisherman's bucket.
Way I see it, that's
a challenge directly to us.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
But that's not
what's going on here at all.
You think he's
screwing around like always,
Inspector Zenigata?
The crook wants a gem, and his
sights are set on the Cherry Sapphire.
So you remember, Takagi.
The only ICPO investigator who
deals exclusively with Lupin III.
Yeah, I'm Zenigata.
Inspector, from what you know of
Lupin, are pranks like this his M.O.?
Yes.
We're gonna need some out-of-the-box
thinking on this one, folks.
If that's the case, sir,
why do you think he's really
after the Cherry Sapphire?
That's a good point.
It could just be another prank.
He texted me.
He actually sends you texts?
Sometimes,
but obviously I can't reply.
They're texting buddies!
That's crazy.
Look.
Hey, everyone take it easy.
Well, what do you say? Can I
borrow a couple of these guys, Megure?
I'm not sure they're fit for the
job. But I'm not gonna turn you down.
Say what?! I could be
part of the hunt for Lupin?
The Second Investigation
Division usually handles it,
but unfortunately Inspector
Nakamori has been suspended.
Makes sense, considering
the Tsukishima incident.
Then...
They need some First
Division members to fill in...
Me! Me! Pick me! Me!
Hey, what's with the shouting?
Please, me, too!
I never dreamed I would get the
chance to play a part in Lupin's arrest.
Funny enough, Lupin III
was Officer Sato's first love.
Takagi!
I see. That's why
you raised your hand first.
That's not it, sir.
I wouldn't volunteer
for such a frivolous reason.
I'm fine with it.
I get
wanting to arrest an old flame.
There are just some things
you gotta do yourself.
I'm expecting your best.
Thanks, Inspector.
I'll give my all, sir!
In a sense,
I'd say I love Lupin, too.
It's just too funny. Why
would anyone park here?
Don't know, but they'll see what happens
when you cross the Traffic Division.
But hang on a ticket.
The plates don't check out.
What do you think it means?
It means these aren't your
run-of-the-mill fake plates.
So this car could belong
to a shady syndicate?
It's sure
steamy with suspicion.
Do people still say, "steamy"?
Wait. You don't?
Wow, sir.
You really parked here?
In fact, it was an Interpol car.
That doesn't really mean much
to our Traffic Division.
Miyamoto and Miike again.
I'll head
to the Traffic Division!
Will there be a fine?
It's Sonoko.
How's it going? Things okay?
Check the news? Right now?
Welcome to Japan. What's
your favorite Japanese food?
Yeah. I'm watching.
It's natto.
Then guess who I get to see
after school tomorrow.
That's right, Emilio!
The hottie himself!
I know what hotel
he's staying at!
Get outta here!
How'd you pull off
something like that?
It's all thanks
to our intelligence network.
Made it easy.
You are something else. That's
personal information, you know.
Huh?
Wow, and his manager
is a beauty!
Seriously?
That Sonoko is such a goof.
She could have waited 'til
tomorrow to talk about homework.
You're going to meet him,
aren't you?
Oh, boy.
What a knockout!
He's just
a grown-up version of the boys.
I'm going, too.
Huh?!
You think
all this is necessary?
He often escapes
by helicopter.
So your plan
is to shoot him down instead?
Are you sure
this is going to work out?
We might need to think
about moving the gem.
Personally, I think the safest
place for it is right here.
The more you move it, the more
chances Lupin has to nab it.
Exactly. Let's check
the vault one more time.
Sir!
Uh, wait for me!
Ah! Now this is a vault!
And what about
the sapphire's owner?
You reach him?
Yes.
When I got ahold of him, I asked about
temporarily moving the gem to another location,
but Mr. Eishin Wakagomo said...
No need for that.
I have absolute faith
in the Japanese police force.
He's got
a lot of confidence in you.
We're gonna get him for sure!
So please leave everything
to us! Right, Ms. Sato?!
What are you...
You, too!
Let's work together
and do our best!
Yeah!
You're embarrassing me.
Take it down a notch.
Five minutes 'til the time
on Lupin's theft notice!
Put roadblocks on all streets!
All through traffic
is now prohibited!
Everyone not on bank security,
switch to Channel B for comms!
There ever been an occasion
when Lupin wasn't punctual?
No.
If that's accurate...
there's a minute left.
Which means he has to be
somewhere nearby, right?
Yeah. He could be disguised as
one of us at this very moment.
Wait!
What? Who?!
Ms. Sato,
what are you doing?!
Don't you move, or I'll shoot.
But I...
He doesn't always
imitate a person.
What?
He can be other things, too?
That's the first
I'm hearing of this!
What would you do
if Lupin masqueraded
as that vault door there?
Sorry.
Just trying to defuse
some of the tension, you know?
Thought that'd get a laugh
out of everyone. Sheesh.
Oh, look at the time.
It's already past 1:00.
Really?
But nothing's happening.
Maybe all the security forced
him to reschedule his attempt?
No, that's not his style.
The man gets what he wants.
That's just
who Lupin III is.
Are you're saying
Lupin already found a way
to sneak inside the vault?
I saw it in a movie.
It was a heist flick
where the thieves
dug a tunnel
directly under the vault.
Got a camera in there?
There are privacy issues
which prohibit such a thing.
Let's take a look,
just to be sure.
- All clear.
There's not a hole to be found.
Oh, thank goodness!
Hey, is it possible
he found some other way
to get to the Cherry Sapphire?
You think he already
made off with it?
- There's just no way!
It's impossible!
Don't you need two keys
to open the box?
Indeed. Mr. Eishin
entrusted me with them both.
Ah, it's here.
The Cherry Sapphire is safe.
It's three past the time
he announced he'd steal it.
Hmm.
You think maybe, just maybe...
It's possible
everyone's watches
are running three minutes fast?
Wha?!
It's 1:00 now!
Of course. Earlier...
Lupin disguised himself
as Takagi
and adjusted our watches
three minutes forward!
What a brilliant deduction.
Right on time.
I'll be taking this, Pops.
Have a break, courtesy of me.
Farewell, my first love!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
That hurts, you know!
Agh! You're gonna break it!
When you say
you're gonna do something,
you see it through.
A strong, beautiful lady
caught you.
You should cheer up.
- Come on, Pops.
This isn't fair.
You're taking advantage
of the fact
I won't get rough
with a woman, you cheat.
There we go.
Setting it back
three minutes.
Lupin III, as of 1:02 P.M.,
I hereby place you
under arrest for theft.
Brilliant! Simply brilliant!
Your talents are wasted
as a police detective!
'Scuse me. I hate to break up
this touching moment, but...
But what? Move, and you
get a bullet in the rear.
I'd listen. She's not someone
you want to tick off.
You mind
checking your watches?
I slipped some
silver-colored stickers on 'em.
They still there?
A sticker?
Yeah, I see it. What's it for?
Those are electrifying
stickers from yours truly.
I designed them
to be stronger than a stun gun.
I think these are yours, Miss.
Sorry to trouble you.
Huh?
Don't you move!
You are a stubborn one, Pops.
Another jolt should do it.
Sorry to catch you up
in that, Miss.
It's nothing personal.
You're gonna get it!
Holy cow. How are you
not counting sheep right now?
I don't think the lady could
take it if I zapped you again.
Toodles!
Lupin, you lousy,
good-for-nothing...
So scary.
We found Lupin!
Hurry! He's hiding in the vault!
He's disguised
as Inspector Zenigata!
What?
- Lupin is here!
- Take him down!
Come on!
- That's right, boys!
Go and get 'im!
- You idiots!
I'm not the phony!
It's not me!
Lupin is currently
in the bank!
Again, he's in the...
Here you go.
It's Lupin!
No!
The real one's over here!
The third Lupin is in custody.
Wait. There's a fourth one
in front of the tobacco shop.
We believe this one
to be a fake.
- We work in TV!
- Damn thing won't come off.
Commander, sir, is there a way
to tell which Lupin is real?
There's a canine Lupin
at Beika Park.
Friendly little pupper.
We've got a squad in pursuit
at Beika Park's north entrance!
Had to run out
of masks eventually!
Lupin has entered
Beika Street!
Head to the south entrance!
Don't mean
to disturb your shopping!
- Hey, how's business?
- Whoa!
Nice gutting technique!
Check out
my mackerel smackerel!
'Kay, boys! Get inked!
Everybody stand back!
What a world
we live in, eh, Granny?
You are the sweetest.
Would you like to meet
my granddaughter?
That meeting's
gonna have to wait!
Damn it!
Don't you realize you're
playing right into his hands?
- What do we do, sir?
Call HQ for more reinforcements?
- The opposite.
Call off the investigation.
- Huh?
- He's long gone.
Sir, where are you going?
Fried my watch.
Damn it. I liked this one, too.
What just happened?
We've lost all trace of Lupin.
Strong legs are an essential
tool for a master thief,
which is why I can't
get enough of a good chase.
Huh? It's you.
If you weren't using a car
and didn't have a chopper,
then Beika Station...
Problem is, it would
go into lockdown too quickly.
There'd be too much distance
between the bank
and the subway station.
I had the very same thought
at first
until I discovered the position
of the ventilation shafts
and workers' entrance.
I could fall
for a gal like you.
Brainsandgrit.
But can't you give me a break?
You don't know how badly
I need this gem, Miss.
Wait!
Once the numbness wears off,
let's play again.
I'm certain that door leads
to the power company's
utility conduit.
I can't let him get through.
Accident 100 meters
before Nishi Beika Station!
Ms. Sato...
you okay?
Oh. Takagi.
I'm glad I got to you in time.
Would you try
being less reckless?
Eh, you're a fine one
to talk about being cautious.
I mean, really.
Getting captured
by the same thief you're after.
- You're right.
Sorry about that.
He caught me off guard.
Jeez.
Sato...
I vow to never
leave your side again.
Whatever you say.
Wha... You're cuffing me? Why?
Because you're really Lupin.
Takagi would never act that way.
Whoops!
Guess you caught me red-handed!
Hey!
Get back here! Lupin!
Eh?
Hmm? What's the matter?
Did you hear
Officer Sato just now?
- Say what?
I think you're hearing things.
Sorry my dad's tagging along.
Not a problem.
It'd be weird
if he liked Emilio,
but he's after the manager,
right?
Who am I to judge his love life?
Well, this is the place,
Princess Ran.
Oh, cut that out!
Coming here
sure brings back memories.
- What do you mean?
It hasn't been that long, silly!
- That's true.
- You can wait here
while I go
and get the manager.
You're going to get him?
I'm the famous sleuth
who stopped
the attempted poisoning
of the Vespanian Princess.
Kogoro Mori.
Nice to make your acquaintance.
What are you up to over here?
My assistant
made an appointment.
Your what?
Why is he like this?
Smooth-talking a clerk
won't help us.
But it might not hurt, either.
I'll handle it from here.
Detective Mori,
let's take this elsewhere.
- Please, this way.
- Ah, sure!
What just happened?
Hey, what happened?
You're confused, too?
Of course I'm confused.
Let's follow 'em!
Why not?
Wait for me!
I don't care
if it's Interpol!
A violation's a violation.
Our directive
is to collect the towing fee,
no matter who it's from.
It'll be a boon
to the national treasury.
He should get
his own car, anyway!
How about a nice dent?
The key is inside, isn't it?
It's under the left visor,
like in the West.
What the... Officer Takagi's
all cooped up in the back!
Really? How come?
What are you doing back here?
The other guests have gathered
in the conference room.
Waiting on me to get started,
are they?
Sorry for the holdup.
Hmm?
Here's our stop.
To the left, down the hall.
Got you.
The room is over here.
It is good to be back.
Sorry to burst in!
Dad,
you should knock first!
What happened? Huh?
- Eh?
- No. Sorry. It's nothing.
- Huh?
- Inspector Shiratori!
- Uh...
- Ohh.
Mori?
Uh, hey, Inspector.
What are you doing here?
- Hello, sir.
- Is he here? Is he?
Mr. Megure,
who are these people?
There's nothing
to worry about. This is...
I'm Japan's
number one detective,
Kogoro Mori, here to serve
at your pleasure,signorina.
- Good to know.
- Eh?
I'm so sorry.
I'm this one's daughter,
Ran Mori.
I'm his assistant,
Miss Suzuki...
but call me Sonoko!
You are both hopeless.
The inspectors
were called in.
Interesting.
So the doorman recognized Pops
and thought he was
part of the team.
Eh? Hey, did something happen?
Doesn't pertain
to why we're here.
...without you two
getting into trouble?
- That hurts!
- There's news.
Takagi is safe,
but the Cherry Sapphire was...
Lupin?!
Lupin, darling!
Fujicakes!
I was so worried!
Did they hurt you?
No, but I was scared
out of my mind.
- I bet.
And them making you wear
this tacky necklace
couldn't have helped.
You got a lousy sense
of fashion! You know that?
I just want to end this.
Now hand it over to Fujiko.
Someone's impatient.
What, you're not
a fan of small talk?
Easy there, boys.
You think I'm dumb enough
to pull a gun here?
Just look at the situation
I'm in! Really.
Leave the box. I only require
the Cherry Sapphire inside.
You, sir, are no fun at all.
Well, it looks like he
didn't plant anything in here.
Hmm?
Apologies, doll.
So you're really with him,
aren't you?
Funny thing about this collar,
it's a big, fat fake.
Which means...
Sorry, but you're not
getting this jewel, either.
You're cool with that, right?
Oh, and lose the guns.
- Hot damn!
That's my Fujicakes for you!
At least, that's what I'd
like to say right now,
but you were
a bit naive on this one.
Huh? How so?
Well, that explosive is
clearly the genuine article.
Are you for real?
Only a scumbag would fool
a defenseless woman!
If you want it that bad, here!
Well, what now?
Tell me, should I wish my head,
"Fare thee well,"
before you blow it
to kingdom come?
It sounds as if you don't care
for my little machinations.
Not to worry, though.
Our business has ended.
As soon as our safety
is assured,
I'll see the collar is released.
Of course,
if this gem is a fake...
- Don't worry yourself.
It's the real deal.
So what's the word?
We done, or is this all
some big, elaborate test?
No test.
I've got what I want.
You can keep the van.
Consider the coat inside
as a gift.
'Ppreciate it.
Now we're done.
I never want
to see you lot again.
Allow me
to introduce you
to the concert's promoter,
Luciano Carnevale.
Greetings.
And this over here is...
- Claudia Bellucci.
It's a pleasure.
I work on the team
as Emilio's manager.
- And what a job you do!
- Uh...
anyway, the reason
we're here is...
Inspector, are you sure
it's okay to include him?
Despite how he comes across,
you can trust Mr. Mori.
Despite
the backhanded compliment,
he's right.
You can depend on me.
Hmm.
Fine, then.
Have a look.
It arrived for Emilio
this morning.
Hmm? Uh, what's inside?
Hmm?
What?! This is...
I have...
no clue what this says.
We went through
all that buildup,
and you can't even read it?
That's just like him.
Letters from a newspaper...
in Italian?
The message says,
"Cancel the concert.
Otherwise,
Emilio's a dead man."
No!
You're being threatened?
- A death threat, huh?
That's rough.
How many people
have touched this directly?
I haven't laid a hand on it.
Emilio and I
have both touched the letter.
So if we find fingerprints
other than yours,
there's a good chance
they belong to our perp.
If we could lift
the culprit's prints,
it'd sure make our job
a hell of a lot easier.
We should cancel it.
This is ridiculous!
Let's cancel
and be done with it!
Emilio!
We can't just cancel
at the drop of a hat!
Are you aware
how much money's been spent
just to set up
this concert here?
We even had them rush
renovations to Tohto Stadium,
and you're performing
to a sold-out house!
It's virtually impossible
to cancel the show
at this point, and you know it!
Please, Lupin!
He says if you don't,
this'll explode.
If you love me
like you say you do,
I know you'll take the gig.
Enough, already. Stop teasing.
Just say
I brought it on myself.
Hold your horses.
The part I wanna scold you about
is coming up.
Oh, forget it.
I'll just have to ask
Kid instead.
What's the big deal?
All this time,
and you still don't get it.
Get what?
When it comes
to protecting you,
there's only one man
for the job.
And that would be...
Lupin...
Winner! And for your prize...
Don't!
What's the matter?
You need to get away.
Otherwise...
If dying with you
is how I go out,
then what an ending.
Smarmy bastard.
Play me for a fool, will he?
His ass is grass!
Fujicakes, you took my clothes.
Was deactivating it
the right move?
It wouldn't do
to kill that woman.
If I did, Lupin would
surely come after us.
I can't afford that now.
It's imperative I get it
for our motherland.
The fact that Emilio
is residing at this hotel
while he's here hasn't
been made public knowledge.
As far as we're aware,
only the concert staff
and some
of the hotel employees know.
But we can't say for sure
the culprit wasn't an outsider.
Some enthusiastic fans
do everything in their power
to find out
where a celeb is staying.
It's probably just a prank,
but I'll put plainclothes
officers on guard duty.
- We'll have to play it by ear.
- I've figured it out!
Hmm?
What? Are you serious, Mori?!
Sure am! The person who sent
this threat was clearly...
Lupin III!
- Lupin?!
- Uh...
You think so?
Really, Pops?
The burglar who's been
causing a fuss in this town
for the last couple of days.
He made a big production
out of stealing a gem
and then threw it away. Hmph.
I guess the bauble
didn't suit his fancy.
The phone call
you ducked out of here to take
was a report that Lupin had
gotten away with a new jewel.
Isn't that right, Shiratori?
What happened, Pops?
You're on fire for once.
Well, it's true enough
we just got a report,
but you believe
there's a connection
between that theft
and this threat?
It was all part of his plan,
but first
he needed a valuable gem
and the concert
to be shut down.
His goal...
Go on.
Miss Claudia!
As soon as all this
wears on you,
he'll give you the jewel as
a present to improve your mood.
Does that check out?
Sure!
He's going to all this trouble
just to put the moves on you!
It's dangerous here!
You should stay with me
just to be safe.
Emilio.
I'll be fine. All I'm
gonna do is go back to my room.
Man, I didn't even
get his autograph.
- Let's go, Sonoko.
Things here are pretty hectic.
You, too, Conan.
All right!
And him?
Dad's impossible
when he's like this.
Figures.
For your protection,
I'll post guards on this floor.
It'll all work out.
I mean, he already has
a reliable bodyguard, right?
Huh?
Smart boy.
You're very well informed.
I saw him on TV!
Conan!
Coming!
And you believe
you can depend on this guard?
It's said he tripled
the military might
of one country
by training its soldiers
with his
charismatic instruction.
Impressive, Papa.
Thanks for having us.
Hey, wasn't there
a sweets shop downstairs?
- Yeah, there was.
You've got sharp eyes.
Wanna stop by?
Sure. Let's go.
One floor above the lobby,
right?
Yep.
Conan? Wha...
Huh? Hey, brat,
knock it off,
or we're leaving you!
Please don't leave me!
So you girls
wanna get out of here?
Is that allowed?
Wow, the little brat
turned out all right,
- didn't he, Ran?
- Uh...
Sonoko, it's clearly not him!
It's like a miracle!
Sonoko!
Hmm.
Slow down. Wait!
Emilio and I
are running off together,
and his hand's
even on my shoulder.
It's a dream come true!
- Hold on!
Please, wait a second!
Stop running, already!
Oh, sorry.
Sonoko, you have
to think this through.
Aren't you even
gonna ask me if I'm okay?
That's enough! You know he
can't leave at a time like this.
- Why not?
- Did you forget?
Someone out there
wants to kill him.
If Emilio came to harm
because of us...
Don't tell me
you fell for a prank like that.
You can't prove it's a prank.
Or did you miss the letter
saying he'd be a dead man?
It doesn't ring a bell.
Get serious!
You took down the Vespanian
Kingdom's strongest bodyguard.
- We'll be fine!
- That was different.
I bet there aren't any threats
within ten kilometers of us!
Oh, Sonoko.
Here's an idea, ladies.
Let's take a trip up there.
Sure! Just lead the way!
Just watch.
We're gonna get
in big trouble for doing this!
You'll pollute your lungs
hanging around here.
But this is
the only place in the hotel
where you can smokeanddrink,
isn't it?
Heh. Yo, Great Detective.
This area is for adults.
Oh, I just came
to pick up Papa.
- Is that so?
Then can I offer you some juice?
An iced coffee will do.
- Huh?
- Be back in just a moment.
Come on.
You didn't think
you were the only one
with a taste for iced coffee
year round, did you?
What are you and your partners
up to in this town?
So, you're here
as Shinichi Kudo?
Thank you for your patience.
I also thought
you'd like dessert,
so I brought some lemon pie.
Ah, thanks, Mister!
Life's rough for you, too, huh?
You idiot.
Ah, so you do
say, "idiot," a lot.
And "I have to go
to the bathroom" as well.
Where are you
getting this from?!
Young as you are
and going like that,
you might want
to go to the doctor.
You know why I have to say it.
You should know
that adults can be scary.
Was that a threat?
Don't worry about it.
As long as you don't
stick your nose in my affairs,
the two of us have no problem.
- Question.
In those fancy notes of yours,
does it say
I'm the type of person
who gets fired up
when threatened?
You're a real pain in the ass.
Now for some pie!
- Not so fast!
You called me "Papa"!
You're late!
- It's me.
- What's wrong, Ran?
- You can't find Emilio?!
- You're with Emilio?!
- Why isn't he with you?
That's your job!
Yeah. Sonoko's here, too.
Everyone is looking for him.
He won't come back
until we go to the top,
so tell Dad and the others we...
I think I'll hold on to this!
No! Give that back!
Hey!
Sounds like
they're having a good time.
All right, I got you.
Mmm.
About your call...
So good!
Sounds like
they were with Emilio.
Seems that way.
You know where they are?
Can't say I do!
What say we make a deal
between us adults?
I'm heading out!
Okay, you win!
I'll rip up the notes!
Here! Look!
Papa's sorry.
It's so fast!
Incredible.
I don't know about this, guys.
What the hell
was that bodyguard doing?
Asking won't help us now.
We should try searching
the nearby area.
And the inspectors have left?
Yes, except for
that private detective.
Is he looking, too?
He is.
We should fire
that useless bodyguard.
My apologies.
But once this is over,
I'll be gone
before you get the chance.
If anywhere, it'd be here.
Ahh!
A beautiful sunset...
and a handsome guy!
Stand down.
That face could kill.
No way.
Everybody here looks suspicious.
Come on. Let's go back.
Doubt it's there, but...
might as well
check this room, too.
The kid even changed his shoes.
Hmm?
It's me.
Like I figured, it's not here.
Huh?
Maybe in some
concert equipment?
- What?
- Don't you "what" me.
Hmm. Weren't you tower bound?
I thought I'd go
with you instead, Papa.
Liar.
I'm surprised they let
the bodyguard have a spare key.
You gonna arrest me
despite my innocence?
The gun is reason enough
to take you in.
Hey, here's a piece of advice
from Papa to son.
This doesn't concern
you and your friends,
so why not leave it alone, huh?
Well?
Forget it.
Excuse me, Miss.
Yes? What is it? Need help?
You have
an Italian newspaper on hand?
Oh, I'm sorry,
but we only carry
English-language
newspapers here.
Is it urgent?
No. That's all right.
Well, thank you, anyway.
Can I ask a favor?
Yes, darling?
Mind if I stop in there?
Do what you need to do.
It sure took you long enough.
Huh? What does that mean?
Oh.
I know Lupin has been busy.
He got away
with the Cherry Sapphire,
despite it being
in a lockbox in Tohto Bank.
This gem he stole,
what's the deal?
As far as I can tell,
it's not particularly special.
It didn't even appear
in a web search.
But Lupin announced it
and everything.
Hang on!
This is about the jewel's owner!
Bingo.
And now you've caught up
to Genta and the other two.
Caught up to them?
You mean they're doing it again?
Not only that,
they're more fired up than ever.
This morning, they searched
abandoned homes in town,
from bushes to basements.
They're really looking
for his hideout?
But not even
the police can find it.
- Well, they did.
-What?!
The Cherry Sapphire's owner,
Eishin Wakagomo.
Why would the kind of man
who rents a safe-deposit box
at a bank
be in an abandoned repair shop?
Adding to their suspicion,
the front shutters
have recently been replaced.
They uncovered that much
all by themselves?
Professor's all in, too.
Of course he is.
Trying to stop them
is pointless.
Keep them there!
I'll explain the stakes
when I get back.
Of all the...
Let's capture Lupin
and then
take a vacation in Hawaii!
Yeah!
- Yeah, right.
- We might end up on TV!
Hello.
I forgot to get
to my main point.
It's regarding
Emilio's manager and promoter.
Got it.
Roger that.
I'll go ahead
and check it out.
So what are you going to do?
Talk about rude.
- Find him?
- No!
Maybe he headed back
without us.
Did he only pretend to go in?
I've had my eye on the door
the whole time.
He must have meant
to lose us from the start.
- But what for?
- I don't know,
but we gotta find him!
Yeah!
You're absolutely sure
it's Emilio?
Yeah. Uh...
He's not here.
I swear! It was him!
So you saw the Emilio
here all alone?
Did you say you saw Emilio?
And who are you, Miss?
Uh, I'm a staff member
for the tour.
- Oh, goodness.
Then he really is around here!
- You're a real cutie.
You know that?
After that, I ran off
to get an autograph board
for him to sign.
While in the middle
of your shift?
Uh, what are you doing, Miss?
You can't go in there!
Call the chief!
You're late.
Sorry. I still have
to buy a ticket, though.
Hmm. Here.
Golly! You're so nice!
Don't mock me.
What are you doing?!
Emilio!
What the... Ran?!
Why are you here?
Don't you know it's dangerous?
Stop screwing around.
Stay back!
Fine. Just tell me something.
Why are you doing this?
Because...
I don't want to do the concert.
Being tired
after all this makes sense.
Taking some time off
should do the trick, right?
I can't! Like it or not,
this is how it is.
It can't be cancelled.
No, don't say that.
And don't give in!
No concert is more important
than someone's life!
It's crazy to even suggest it!
If they can't see the show needs
to be cancelled, I'll... I'll...
Whatever I do,
you need to come away
from there, please!
We're the only riders, huh?
Hardly anyone comes up here
this late at night.
Anyway, you're certain they
came to the tower, aren't you?
Ran hasn't called
to say she's coming back yet.
Hey, Papa, do you and your gang
have a hideout
in this city, too?
Don't think
you'll get an answer out of me
just 'cause you ask the question
like a child.
So you do!
And why would you
assume that?!
You can't do this!
Please, I'm begging you.
I can't imagine how you feel,
but if you need to talk
to someone, talk to me!
Just don't do this!
I, uh...
Emilio.
Quick! Grab my arm!
Ran, I-I...
Everything's gonna be okay.
Look, can your feet
reach that ledge?
Uh, yeah.
Ran!
Sonoko!
Don't you get
all pathetic on me!
The Ran Mori I know
is a total badass!
Let's pull together!
One, two...
No!
Eh?
Sonoko!
Ran!
Mister, can you
open this window?!
Is the girl who's dangling
that friend of yours?
- Uh-huh.
- How thick is it?
Double pane, ten mil.
- What's going through?
- I am!
Twelve shots, then!
Ran, just don't let go
of Emilio's hand!
He's getting slapped after this!
How dare he drag
my best friend into this mess?!
Who does he think he is?!
I'll slap him so hard,
no one will ever
call him handsome again!
Oh, Sonoko.
Big enough?
I'm sorry, Sonoko.
I can't hang on anymore.
This is it.
Ran.
Ran!
- Ran!
- Ran, don't let go!
It's the brat!
Conan!
Thank you, Conan!
- Great job!
You really came through, brat,
so I'll grant you
a one-time-only super hug later!
I think I'll pass on that.
Sir, may I ask exactly
what it is you're doing?
What am I doing?
Saving people,
from the looks of it.
I'm telling you,
everything's fine.
Don't worry over nothing.
Emilio, you almost
got yourself killed,
and you put other people
in danger.
Your actions have consequences!
Is any of what I'm saying
sinking in?
Use your head in the future!
Please help us.
We can't do this alone.
Not to worry.
Nothing is going
to stop that concert.
That's good to hear.
However, it seems to me
our favorite idol
has been given
a touch too much freedom.
I trust you're aware that
standing out in a negative way
could interfere with the deal.
Did you just call
to pass on that piece of advice?
That, by its very nature,
creates unnecessary risk.
Yeah. There won't be any changes
to the time or place.
Does Claudia
know about it, too?
Yeah, she does.
She's known
from the very beginning
and is even helping them out.
So their deal is shady.
What does it entail?
No clue,
but based on how badly everybody
wants me on that concert stage,
that's when it will go down.
All of this started
when that Luciano guy
became your promoter, right?
Yeah, he changed everything...
the songs, the choreo,
interactions with TV stations.
No one even listened to my demo
before him.
But the biggest change
was in Claudia.
Her joy surpassed my own.
She loves my songs more
than anyone else in the world.
You thought
if the show got canceled,
it'd make the conspirators
call off the deal.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I really never had
any intention of jumping.
No, I'm the one
who jumped to conclusions.
Sorry for slapping you
the way I did.
I totally get it.
You just did it because you
cared about my well-being.
Sorry. Forgot to give this
back to you.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, it's Dad.
Hey.
Yeah. I know.
Uh-huh. I'm with him now.
Calm down. You don't
have to yell like that!
Take a look
at this scrap of paper.
Eh?
It was on the floor
in your room.
Oh. That was in my room?
There's no use in hiding it.
The fact is the hotel doesn't
carry Italian newspapers.
And since Claudia
clearly understood the threat,
all the spelling was correct.
In other words,
we both know the letter K
didn't just happen
to fall off the note on its own.
Good point.
If a letter was missing
when she opened it,
she would have noticed
right away.
I also discovered
light scratches on the table.
Guess you used a box cutter?
I suppose I'm busted.
We rarely use K
in the Italian alphabet.
Should've trashed this.
Too late, huh?
Don't be so sure.
Good hotels wait
to dispose of garbage.
When we get back, we better
hide the cutter and newspaper.
I should get rid of the glue
I left in there, too.
- Smart.
Japanese police are top-notch.
The tower save. Now this.
Tell me, just who are you?
Conan Edogawa.
I'm a detective.
That supposed to be
your catchphrase?
Good to know.
- Awesome.
You are one amazing kid.
- And you've got fans waiting.
Make this concert a success.
I'll ensure
this deal doesn't go down.
Trust me. These criminals
are as good as caught.
Hey!
I've been looking
all over for you!
You can't stroll around outside
at a time like this.
Do you know
how worried I was?!
Or for that matter,
how many people
you caused trouble for
by running away?
You have our thanks.
I hate to think
what might have happened
if you hadn't found him,
Mr. Mori.
There's no need for that.
Search-and-rescue is old hat
for me at this point.
Emilio, he may forgive
your selfishness,
but don't think
everyone will be so kind.
- I'm sorry!
- Huh?
I've been restless
since we got to Japan.
Won't happen again.
Please forgive me, Claudia.
I'll give my all at the concert
to prove I'm being sincere.
I'll make this
my best concert ever, Luciano!
Just you watch!
I think I'll head
to the staff room.
Don't forget
the stage-prep meeting tomorrow.
I won't,
but I need to apologize
to the staff
who know what happened.
Yes, that's true.
Good idea.
Mr. Mori,
what exactly did you say
to get through to Emilio?
Huh? Uh...
Well, let's call it
some advice on growing up.
Hello. It is me.
You should ditch
that hideout while you can.
I have it on good authority
that the detective brat's
little buddies
are gonna come barging in soon.
And if that were to happen,
what shall I do?
They've all got
their phones turned off.
Could they be over there?
They went to bed early
to prep for tomorrow.
Doc is already out like a light.
- You think they...
- I hope not.
He's pointing
right at me for some reason.
They didn't...
Yes, they did indeed.
We've looked up to you
for a real long time now.
Yeah! Welcome to Japan!
I can't even tell you
how cool this is!
It's not much, but please...
Take this!
It's yummy!
Nothing strange in there!
It's all yours.
I appreciate
your thoughtfulness.
- Hear that?
- This is working like a charm.
When he falls asleep...
We'll tie him up.
The square knot should do it.
And after we wrangle him...
I'll make some tea for you.
They asleep?
Never suspected a thing.
I don't see why I had to hide
in the first place.
Don't they know not
to take drinks from strangers?
Some Detective League you are.
Let's see if they
have anything valuable.
Will you strip her, too?
Lay off the S-word!
Hmm?
Huh?
Fujicakes!
Well, this is
where we part ways.
Because of you lot, I was
fired from the bodyguard gig,
so it looks
like there's no reason
for us to keep palling around.
Catch you later.
You're gonna do something
terrible to my friends!
You can cry
your tear ducts dry.
I'm not always gonna
play along with your act.
I am the adult here.
Thief!
Hey, shut it!
You know I can't
let you go on like that.
- Crafty bastard.
- Look at this!
I just received some
new information on Luciano.
Are you listening?!
The Italian mafia?
The info's from headquarters.
Apparently he's making
a huge deal here in Japan.
Will Lupin show?
Probably.
That sounds rather uncertain
coming from you, Inspector.
Is there something
not sitting right with you?
- It's far too petty.
If he's after a jewel,
then why is he interested
in ruining this deal?
So you're saying
it's out of character.
This guy's not the sort
he deals with.
Oh, he has a type, does he?
How are you faring?
Investigation's done,
not that
it'll matter much anymore.
Uh, why do you say that?
It seems they're not gonna
file a criminal complaint.
- That felt off from the start.
Does it make sense
for people who are
about to make a shady deal
to call in the police?
I get what you're saying.
One of them
wants to end this mess.
We should investigate.
What are
those doohickeys?
Don't know, but they're all
grade-A gadgets,
that's for sure.
This is the work
of a skilled artisan.
But who the hell is giving
stuff like this to kids?
Not any responsible adult.
So, Fujicakes,
what are you doing?
- Hmm?
- Skipping out?
What do you mean?
I'm off to crush those guys.
She speaks of violence
with reckless abandon.
It's dangerous to go alone.
Who'll be alone, huh?
Don't tell me
you're calling your friends.
Already asked.
Where are they coming from,
you know?
Everywhere.
A world war in the making.
Oh, relax.
I promise
that I won't get in your way.
Besides, I told my friends
to stick to more conventional
weapons on this one.
Is that meant to calm us?
Did you at least
do some probing first?
Like I said,
I'm not going to be in the way.
Oh, Fujicakes!
- Pile those kids in.
I'll drop them off as I go.
Huh?
You're going somewhere?
Did you expect me
to use this dirty, old hideout?
I just came by for the weapons.
Let's call it quits here.
We'll do as you say
and intercept it.
At the concert venue?
- Yeah.
Tell Zenigata and the cops.
Then back off.
A detective shouldn't go
any further than that.
This is your second warning.
You won't get a third.
I told him I'd stop this deal,
and I'll do it,
'cause I keep my promises!
Tell that to Lupin!
Good evening, Miss.
Fujiko Mine.
What should I do
with these kids?
The poor dears could
catch a cold being outside.
It'd be great if you
could take them off my hands.
The catch is...
I want you to come with me
instead, if you'd please.
Singing Nobleman
Emilio Baretti is here!
Tune in, because tomorrow
we'll get to hear him sing live.
That's a wrap!
Next,
let's interview some fans
who've been waiting
in line all night.
Making a deal
in a crowded place like that?
I've really
gotta hand it to 'em.
- Yeah, it's smart.
Once the concert starts,
every eye in the house
will be riveted on the stage.
It would also seem
Luciano had a say
in the stadium's renovations.
There's a dressing room
for the backing band
and a pit below the stage.
People won't go there
while the show's going on.
Did you hack
the stadium camera?
Already done.
Do you realize
how dangerous that was?!
You'd be dead
if those weren't knockout drops!
Good grief, kids!
I can't believe
you went without me!
Professor!
You're right. I'm sorry.
I'll handle the situation
with Ai from here on.
- 'Kay.
- Okay.
You're all grounded!
'Kay.
Everything's going as planned!
Nothing's gonna
get in our way.
Ai did a great job
getting in with the baddies.
I wonder if Conan
will be surprised
when he finds out!
We'll hit
the ground running
as soon as we hear from Ai!
Yeah!
Jeez.
Yeah, I'm fine,
all things considered.
It's quite luxurious, actually.
All right. I'll keep
the real location to myself.
The kids'll never find out.
Sorry for the hassle, but
they won't let it go otherwise.
Who's on the phone?
Is it that boy?
Let me speak to him.
Long time, no talk,
not since the submarine.
- He hung up.
- Aww, why?
Maybe he'd
rather not remember.
But why? I kept things PG.
What are you doing?
Isn't that cute?
Did your breasts shrink
with the rest of you?
Or were they also that fun-sized
back in your "Sherry" days?
Oh, don't be so ridiculous.
Obviously they should
be more...
No. I refuse to fall for this.
Here's an idea. Why don't we
team up and perfect that drug?
You could bring your ideal form
of Apotoxin to fruition.
What would you do
once it was done?
I'd use it on myself to
rejuvenate my youthful visage.
Eternal youth
is every woman's dream.
Imagine the fortune
we'd make selling it.
Hate to disappoint you...
Huh?
but my creation
isn't the miracle drug
you think it is.
I'm not sure what happened
to you, but in the past,
you were a thief
who followed her desires
and used her wiles
to enchant men the world over.
You were a woman
who'd keep racing ahead
until she obtained her target,
never looking back to see
who she'd left in the dust.
When a woman
becomes a slave to youth,
it's all over from there.
Right, Fujiko Mine?
Yeah.
This is too small!
There'll be lots of smoke
at the top!
Got it!
Ah, looking good.
The staff's teamwork
seems even better than usual.
Emilio's enthusiasm
is very infectious.
Yeah. After we're done here,
we'll return to Europe.
We deserve a vacation.
Is the deal going
to take place in this room?
- What's this?
You interested all of sudden?
Or do you feel...
some false sense of justice?
- Mr. Mori!
- Hmm?
I'm sorry for calling over
such a famous detective
for a job like this.
- Oh, not at all.
I choose assignments
based on my highly refined
sense of values.
- P.A.! Is something there?
- Tomorrow's it.
I doubt we'll sleep a wink.
At this point, there's
nothing left for me to do.
Think I might grab a nightcap
and hit the sack.
I'm thrilled to have
a bodyguard I can count on.
- Leave it to me!
Miss Claudia is...
- Claudia?
- Uh, what I meant was
Emilio is in good hands with me.
Rest assured!
Miss Claudia?
Ran, it's you.
Finding it hard to relax, huh?
Guess so.
But I just can't rest
until the stadium
is full of fans tomorrow.
That's just how it is.
Even though the tickets
have already sold out?
As silly as this will sound,
I sometimes have nightmares
of running around alone
in an empty venue.
Where are you running to?
I bolt to various seats,
pretending to be
audience members.
I guess
I'm trying to stop Emilio
from noticing what's going on.
Good thing it's just a dream.
- It's very real.
- Huh?
Look. Someone's placing
surveys and ads
for the next concert
on the seats.
That used to be
one of my duties.
At one of our gigs,
we had less than 30 people.
That must have been difficult.
You'd better believe it.
We were hurting for money.
It was hard being
so darn powerless
and harder still
not being able to help Emilio.
I can only imagine.
Come on in.
Place hasn't changed one iota.
And thankfully,
neither have my skills.
I got everything
you asked for.
You found an unused Walther?
I had the grip
and trigger spring
customized for you, too.
It's light.
Still as good as they come.
You'll find your payment
in the case.
- That can wait.
- Huh?
You can pay me after you've
come to an agreement
with the client in back.
Figures.
No wonder I didn't notice you.
Sayin' I'm a ghost?
I'm shocked
you're still in Japan.
You already got the sapphire,
didn't you?
You're the same ol' King,
always in the know.
It's not biz info.
If Lupin III moves,
it's news.
So why are you here?
A first-class ticket
to Naples.
You fancy going back home?
This a joke?
No cameras here, pal.
I just want you to walk away
from Luciano's job.
It's not my style
to interfere with business,
but in this case, it's a no-go.
I'm being
a straight shooter here.
Who is she?
- A kid.
- Eh?
Did you mess up?
Whatever you're thinking,
let me assure you
you're dead wrong.
But even if you're right,
I didn't "mess up"
as you put it.
For the trouble.
What have you got there?
A shot of Yoko Okino.
Wha...
And...
an embarrassing pic
of Fujicakes.
All right, everyone!
Here we go!
I need to hit the bathroom.
You know, I do, too!
I'll be on duty
guarding him from the wings.
Guess I'm on my own,
but such is life.
Sing it, Emilio!
Strange. I haven't seen
Lupin or Luciano anywhere.
Our last sighting
of Luciano was...
here.
- It's from a half an hour ago.
- Details?
It's a door that leads
straight to the basement,
but no cars
have left the parking lot.
Check this out.
The underground corridor
has been extended.
But why?
Apparently,
it's a secret V.I.P. passage.
How'd we miss this
during our search?
Could you see me?
No sight of you
entering the underground tunnel.
They duped us! It runs
alongside a local street.
Wait! What about the cameras
from this parking lot?
From that location?
No good.
Your car is just out of sight.
Try playing back the footage.
We may be able to tell
which direction he went.
Smart thinking.
Checking the cars that went by.
What the...
Look.
I-It's Conan.
Conan?
He's not picking up.
- What a kid.
He always run off like this?
Usually,
but this is different.
Surely, I can't be the only one
who's picked up on that, right?
What's the move?
You two use that technology
to track the boy.
Me...
I'll do some sleuthing
using my gut.
So he knew all along.
Emilio never lost his faith.
He believed in you, Claudia.
And he doesn't want you
to do any more wrong,
whether on his behalf
or otherwise.
Let's see.
20 daikon radishes,
some cabbages, wha...
and a broken cash register?
Hello. This is Takagi,
the dummy who screwed things up
while on the Lupin case,
and is now being punished
by sorting out expenses.
How may I assist you?
Oh, and I finished
the written apology.
What apology?
Is Officer Takagi there?
Oh, it's just you guys!
What can I do for you?
- Huh?!
- Heads up.
There are more receipts.
Sorry! Can you
take care of the rest?
- What?!
You've gotta be kidding!
I knew he was the one
to call at a time like this.
Yeah!
He actually believes us!
Ai is such a meanie!
Why would she give us
the wrong address?
Maybe she received
some diabolical threat,
forcing her
to give out misinformation.
We have to hurry and save her!
But Conan told us
to leave things to him!
First let's meet
with Officer Takagi.
Then we'll
catch those bad guys!
Yeah!
- Hmm.
- What wrong?
You've been using my computer
for a good while now.
Sending your friends
false info?
I don't wanna put them
in danger, so yes.
Betrayal comes easy
to you, then?
Like how you betrayed
your organization?
- Oh, well.
Don't let it get you down.
Betrayal is
a woman's greatest asset.
You're leaving?
Yup. You're free to go.
A thief who uses her wiles
to enchant men the world over
can't abide
being tricked by one.
Wanna come?
There'll be lots of danger.
Ah, so we meet
in person, at last.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Luciano.
As you know, I am Alan Smithee.
Alan Smithee, huh?
So he's the one
on the other side of this deal?
Luciano's only mentioned
the name to me once before.
Did he say where
the deal would be happening?
No, he hasn't
given that information out
to anyone to my knowledge.
I see.
You kept it here at the airport
as spare equipment.
Yes. It's treated as goods
that have yet
to enter the country.
But even if someone
were to peek inside,
they wouldn't find much.
What have we here? A keyboard?
I think
what you're looking for...
are these.
Quite easy to process.
Then we've reached
the end of our arrangement.
As agreed upon,
the Cherry Sapphire is yours.
- Sapphire?
What the hell is that?
Is this some kind of a joke?
What do you mean?
You sure picked a complicated
place to hide it in.
Take it easy on me next time.
A fake!
Eh? Huh?
Remember what I told you?
The next time we met,
I'd take you in.
You're always so brash, kid.
I'm pretty sure Papa told you
to quit playing detective.
Damn it.
Back-stabbing scum!
You did fire me.
This, kid,
is a special last chance.
Walk away now,
and as a farewell gift,
I'll forget you were here.
You idiot.
There's no way
I'm gonna overlook this.
Ever fired one of those?
'Course I have.
I learned how to shoot
at a firing range in Hawaii.
What's going on here?
What's all
this jewel business?!
It would seem we were set up.
Do you know a man
by the name of Kein Gejidasu?
Kein?! Who is that?
Never heard of him!
This is on me.
Kein Gejidasu, huh?
So you figured it out,
Detective Nerdling.
And I'm impressed
you found out about this place.
Know how?
Later.
That's right. Terminate them.
This is just your scene.
Secret Sword! Reverse Tornado!
Hey, Goemon, now things
are twice as dangerous!
My bad.
No time to dwell on that now.
Out of the way!
The unworthy
are cut down without mercy.
You've got nothin' on me!
Lupin, you're under arrest!
The brakes
aren't working!
- Don't move!
- Hands in the air!
There's more of you?!
- That's my Jigen!
- You're better than ever!
It wasn't me.
Nor was it by my hand.
Well, duh.
But who was it then?
Freeze!
I got you, Lupin.
I'm Jodie Starling
with the FBI, perp,
and as of this moment,
you're in my custody.
A shootout at Haneda?
Turns out
the former maintenance area
doubles as a parking apron
for private jets.
So that was his getaway plan.
Areas A, B, and C are clear!
- Mm-hmm.
Guard up, all the same.
You know
who we're dealing with.
Why would the FBI
be poking its nose into this?
Because I called them.
Did you really think I'd come
to a dangerous place like this
without some backup?
I can't get a good shot.
He's standing in the way
on purpose.
We get to call our own shots
while we're in the country,
so my partner and I figured
it wouldn't be a bad idea
to put the Japanese police
in our debt by apprehending
an internationally wanted
felon like you.
Okay, you can go ahead
and cuff him, Jodie.
Got you.
Now you behave, hear?
I will!
Wait!
Be extra careful
when you touch him.
You never know
what he's got
planted on his body.
You little brat.
I want both hands
behind your head,
you on your knees,
- and no funny business!
- Yeah, yeah.
And just to ensure
you behave...
nighty-night.
You despicable runt.
Bastard!
Enough!
If you want to shoot me,
go right ahead. Do it.
Even if you get me in the head,
the trigger will fire.
As for the boy, well...
I'll be taking the case.
Everyone hold your positions.
All of you back away from me
as far as possible.
Don't make me shoot him!
All right, all right.
Let's all keep our heads here.
Isn't this your chance, brat?
Huh?
Alan, please wait!
What about the money
you promised me?
Wasn't that our deal?
Pilot, are you hearing me?
-Yes, sir.
-Start the engine.
- We're leaving.
-Roger.
- Take the case.
You'll find money inside.
Bring the car!
Right. Just a sec!
This is Sato.
We'll be there in three minutes.
Please have
the gate open for us!
Takagi, why the hell
are you here?!
Oh, it's, uh, well, you see...
Step on it, Doc!
They're gonna beat us
to the action!
Officer Takagi's with us,
so we'll be fine!
Then let's go!
Let's not. This is bad!
Civilian car, let us pass!
So where'd you park yours?
Why would we have driven
a noisy car to an ambush?
I just called for a chopper.
They're gonna escape.
Hey, what if
they start shooting?
Put the gun down.
They wouldn't dare shoot.
Start up. We're taking off now.
Ignore traffic control.
My poor Alfa Romeo.
- What's your plan now?
You gonna run after them?
Not a clue.
- Lupin!
- Hmm?
Fujicakes!
- Who?
- Fujiko Mine...
bust 99, waist 55,
and her hips 88.
Oh, and she's also
an internationally wanted felon.
Ohh.
We miss the party?
- Not at all.
Party's just starting.
Lupin and the FBI.
They both backed off,
all to keep you safe.
But why?
Just who are you, kid?
Why am I the one
who has to steer?!
Would you like
to shoot instead?
Don't worry.
This won't take long.
Hold your fire there,
Fujicakes!
The brat's still
onboard that plane, you know!
And your point being?
If you're gonna blow them up,
I'll have no choice
but to make a sharp turn
- and crash this bike!
- Tell me the drug's secret,
and it won't come to that.
It's a deal.
In that case...
That was
a perfectly good weapon!
I'll be using these. Floor it!
Shift up!
Wow.
You're full of surprises,
"Sherry."
I used to own a Harley
back in the day.
What's the big deal?
Keep your eyes on him
at all times.
Right.
- All right, then.
Let's take off.
We're getting
some push-back from control.
GB27! Please stop at once!
An aircraft
is making its approach!
- JNA301...
- GB27!
- it is not safe to land!
You're not gonna do
what I think you are...
A head-on collision
will stop them!
Why'd I sign up for this?
We're at V1.
Then take off.
Time to fly!
- Gear up.
JNA pilot, are you hearing me?
Just keep flying.
We'll avoid you.
I need ambulances
at the former maintenance area.
We've got a lot of wounded!
Why won't
you guys let us in?!
I guess it's a no-go.
We've got
an officer in here!
Easy with that.
Yeah, give it
to 'em straight, Takagi!
It's great
to hear your voice, Ai!
- Are you safe?
- Give what to 'em?
Show these guys your badge!
Say that again!
Conan's on board a what?
What are
they doing in that cockpit?!
I know, right?
The bastards nearly threw me
clear off this thing.
What?!
You're just full of tricks,
aren't you, brat?
Huh?
But don't you think
all that subterfuge
was just a tad overdone?
- I'm lost.
- Try caught.
A shootout that big, but not
a single person ends up dead?
The FBI must have
been placed just so
and by none other
than you, right?
You kept the power balance
of the field in mind
so there'd be no fatal injuries.
Gah!
Killjoy!
If you'd have let
those pesky pricks
perforate each other,
this would've been over!
You would have liked that,
wouldn't you?
Damn right,
and I almost got my wish!
Wanna leave the rest
to me, too?
Just don't blame me if this
doesn't go the way you want.
So you got it at last,
Captain!
Yes. Now Jiranba
can fight as well.
Wow! Talk about
having a thick skull.
Idiot!
Don't even try it!
He brought this fate
on himself!
We can't let things end
with a tie now, can we?
We'll be fine.
I can smell the sea breeze.
You do realize
we could have just died?
Then let's go thank the pilot.
Respect for keeping
the craft under control.
I'll take over.
The throttle is still intact.
But the wing and tail controls
are heavy.
Copy that. Hey, brat...
No oil pressure.
The plane has a backup
on board, doesn't it?
How curious.
Tell me, who are you, really?
Just rest. Got it? The kid's...
Shinichi Kudo.
I'm a high school detective.
A high schooler.
You're still...
capable...
of doing...
anything.
There are many young people...
in my country, too.
Right now,
his country
is basically being treated
as a lowly colony
by a neighboring state,
one with vast military power.
I wonder
what his real name was?
"Alan Smithee"
is only a pseudonym.
Who cares in the end?
"Alan Smithee" works.
They're shooting it down?!
The order came directly
from the Jiranban embassy.
Please, you have
got to listen to me!
There's a boy aboard that plane!
Connect me to Superintendent
Matsumoto on the double!
We're flying ahead
to Hachijo Island.
Wouldn't you rather
go back to Haneda and surrender?
The feds are there.
You're hilarious.
I wouldn't do that.
Shoot me,
and down goes this birdie, runt.
Oh, I think
I'll find a way to manage.
Puh-lease! I'm doing
my damndest to fly this.
It ain't easy.
Focus on fixing
the comms and radar.
Yeah, yeah.
After I fix this,
are you gonna radio Vespania?
Now, what an interesting thing
to suggest.
When'd you find out?
To be honest,
I've suspected the Vespanian ore
was part of the deal
for a while now.
Back at the hotel,
your buddy Daisuke Jigen
had his dowsing bars out.
I take it
he was trying to use them
to search for the Vespanian ore.
He showed 'em off
back in Vespania.
Why would he do that?
But that's not enough to be sure
Vespanian ore was involved.
Not at the time, no.
When he opened the case,
he checked to see
if it was the real thing, right?
- Who checked?
What are you on about?
Jigen was
releasing microwaves.
In trace amounts, sure,
but enough to dim the lights.
Should I start from the top?
Why not?
Make it a good deduction,
since it might be
your final one.
It's hardly even worth
calling a deduction.
More like child's play.
The Cherry Sapphire
was entrusted to the bank
by Eishin Wakagomo.
And there was the name mentioned
during the deal earlier.
Do you know a man
by the name of Kein Gejidasu?
Kein?! Who is that?
"Eishin Wakagomo"
is Goemon Ishikawa,
and "Kein Gejidasu"
is Daisuke Jigen.
They're anagrams.
You couldn't have been
any cleverer than that?
Even the Junior Detective League
saw through "Eishin Wakagomo."
That's made them
so overconfident
that they barged
into your hideout.
What a rude accusation.
Jigen and Goemon wracked
their brains on those names.
- So there.
- Back to what I was saying.
You then went to the trouble
of stealing the Cherry Sapphire
after having Goemon
put it in the bank.
What's more, Jigen,
aka Kein Gejidasu,
listed the Cherry Sapphire
as a condition
for the deal with Alan.
And who did he recommend
to steal it?
Why, none other
than Lupin III.
To put it another way,
your true objective
was never the Cherry Sapphire.
You wanted to get close
to Alan, whose obsession
was trying to obtain
the stolen Vespanian ore.
After doing so,
you'd simply figure out
who he was trying
to buy the ore from,
and then it would be
a matter of stealing it back.
And if that Cherry Sapphire
happened to be yours
from the start,
I'm sure
it came with a homing device.
I honed in
on the signal with this,
which is also how I knew
where the deal would go down.
Incidentally, I have a hunch
Fujiko Mine was in on the plan
to take back the ore.
If you need more proof
about the ore,
its theft was
all over the Internet.
You've lost it!
Returning stolen rocks
does not a payday make,
so why indulge
in profitless actions?
You can deny it,
but I'm positive
you tried to get it back.
The question is why.
No clue. I wish
you'd stop with the riddles.
Well...
the late Queen Sakura
of Vespania gave her life
to protect
her country's reserves of ore.
I'm sure her daughter
reached out for help.
You remember her, don't you,
that tomboy princess?
If you'd only been
a little faster
at working out the fact
that Luciano had stolen the ore,
you wouldn't have
had to sneak into Japan
and have
that big shootout, right?
So I wasn't on my A game.
Sue me.
Though I only did it
so I could link up
with a cheeky Great Detective.
You're incorrigible.
Okay, this should work for now.
Appreciate it.
You know how this goes.
"You know too much,"
yadda-yadda.
Your image
is important in our world.
If people knew Lupin III
was helping someone...
I might have actually
taken you seriously
if you'd have cocked
the Walther first.
Talk about lame.
Eagle One
to operations center.
Final code is 1027. Confirm.
Final code confirmed.
You have the all-clear
to fire the missile.
I repeat...
you are cleared
to fire the missile.
The Vespanian royal family?
If we can't get it back,
we'll have to go to plan B.
Which is?
Destroying the ore
before it leaves Japan.
Simple as that.
You should have prepared
for this! Come on, man!
Yeah, but who could
prepare for you?!
You disguised yourself as Kid!
Of course I'd come after you!
Only 'cause you
can't take a joke!
Huh?
It's coming!
Maximum throttle!
- We've got chaff!
- Fire!
Attacking Eagle,
this is the Jiranban plane!
Do you co...
The target
has countered with chaff.
The missile
did not hit its mark.
This is a joint demand
from Vespania
and the Jiranba Republic.
Release an AAM10!
Roger!
They're going
for the kill this time.
And we're all out
of defenses! Eh?
That there
is the Cherry Sapphire.
I personally carved
that beauty out of rock.
Hold on.
Did you carve it
out ofthatrock?
Sure did! The one
that Fujiko brought back!
It was pure Vespanian ore.
Get to the high-voltage panel
in the bay!
On it!
It's used for more
than just stealth.
Apply a certain voltage,
and it nullifies
electronics, too.
If something like that
fell into the hands
of a military state,
the world's...
...balance of
military power would collapse.
That's it!
What's the holdup, you brat?!
You taking a nap?!
Crap!
- Heads up!
They've locked on to us!
We have to ascend,
then do a free fall!
I see what you're driving at.
Hang on tight now, brat!
A little more.
Just one chance.
Let's go!
Don't miss.
-The controls!
- What the...
- Scrub the mission!
Eagle One, do you copy?
Scrub the mission!
There are civilians
aboard the craft!
Abort the termination mission
immediately!
Eagle One, roger! But look!
The target is plummeting
along with a mysterious light.
A boat?!
This is Eagle One.
I have just spotted
a lone parachute.
Confirming location
at point 0925.
It looks like they saw us.
Even better,
they're not shooting at us.
Well, I guess
your FBI buddies are waiting?
Or the Maritime
Self-Defense Force?
- Come on. Lighten up.
I didn't go that far.
No way, brat!
Lousy snitch! Get off!
- Hey, cut it out! Ow! Quit it!
- Fall!
- You're hurting my arms! Ow!
- You're like a squid!
Emilio! Emilio!
- Emilio! Emilio!
- Encore! Encore!
Emilio! Emilio!
- Hmm?
- Emilio!
- Did you see?
- Yes. You were great.
- Emilio! Emilio!
- Would you keep...
- Encore!
standing by my side,
watching me?
Encore!
- Get out there.
- Encore!
It's where
you belong, truly.
Encore!
- Encore!
Okay, let's go!
Mm-hmm.
I see. Excellent.
Inspector, because of you,
I could watch to the end.
Thank you for all you've done.
What's this?
You going away?
Eh?
Aww, man.
Everything ended up
at the bottom of the damn ocean.
I hate when it ends that way.
That's a creepy look.
You wanna tell me
what that smirk is all about?
Don't act like you're
not hiding a smile deep down.
But I understand why.
Helping others
can be embarrassing, too.
I have to say,
it's like a phantom thief
has forced open a door
deep into your heart.
Idiot.
Th-This submarine...
Bringing back bad memories?
Hi! You boys doing okay?
Did something
really go down between you two?
Man, do I hate
cramped places.
Yes, agreed.
I see
you're as tenacious as ever.
Ai? You're here, too?
- What's with that tone?
If not for me,
you'd have been burned
to a crisp at Haneda.
That's true. If she
hadn't agreed to my request,
I was going to fire.
What request?
Yeah, what are
you talking about?
- Wait a sec!
You're betraying me?
Betrayal can be
a woman's greatest asset, right?
Oh, nooooo!
Emilio!
Come back real soon!
Thank you, Conan Edogawa.
He's been through a lot,
hasn't he?
But with the support
of all these adoring fans,
I have a feeling
he'll be okay.
So what do you think Lupin
and company are up to right now?
Not sure.
But knowing them,
they're going after
the treasure
of some unsuspecting country.
Your favorite thief
is in the house.
How naive can they be?
As if I'd come
all the way to Japan
and not leave with
an obscenely expensive souvenir.
Huh?
What?!
Where's the treasure? Uh...
Sorry. I was first.
Kid, the Phantom Thief.
You're under arrest, Lupin!
I don't believe this!
- Don't let him get away!
- You're not getting away!
I didn't do it this time,
Pops! You gotta believe me!
Who would ever believe you?!
I see the game you're playing,
Kid, you no good scum-bucket!
I'll get you for this.
Just you wait!
You gotta be kidding me.