- ( theme music playing )
- GOVERNOR, WHEN WE RETURN
TO THE HOTEL,
YOU HAVE A MEETING SCHEDULED
WITH MR. MILLER
- OF THE SAFETY COMMISSION.
- I KNOW.
IT'S IMPERATIVE THAT THE BILL
I'M SUBMITTING BE PASSED
AT THE NEXT SESSION
OF THE STATE ASSEMBLY.
IT'S THE KEY TO BRINGING THE
CRIMINAL ELEMENT UNDER CONTROL.
- ( tires screeching )
- HMM?
- ( snarling )
- ( bullets ricochet )
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- ( screaming )
- ( snarls )
- Man on TV: The highway here
was completely destroyed.
According to the city
Safety Commission,
this catastrophe was caused
by an undetected structural flaw
leading to the collapse
of the highway support column.
Ten people were involved
in the incident,
including the state governor
Svart Lukeson.
- AS YOU'VE SEEN,
THE ORGMEN WE DISPATCHED
COMPLETED HIS MISSION
SUCCESSFULLY.
NOW OUR SUPPORTERS
IN THE OPPOSITION PARTY
CAN EXPAND THEIR POWER BASE
AND EVENTUALLY GAIN CONTROL
OF THE ASSEMBLY.
MILLENNION WILL GROW BIGGER
AND STRONGER THAN EVER.
AND THE PERSON AT THE VERY
TOP OF THE LADDER,
BOSS, IT'LL BE YOU.
- LEE, LOOK AT THIS VIEW.
EVERYTHING WE CAN
SEE IS MINE.
I'M CLOSE.
VERY CLOSE TO HAVING THE KIND OF
FREEDOM I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED OF.
THE FREEDOM TO GIVE AND TAKE
AS MUCH AS I WANT,
WHENEVER I WANT.
- BOSS, YOU ALREADY
HAVE THAT FREEDOM.
- NO, IT'S NOT ENOUGH,
NOT YET.
TO HAVE THAT KIND OF FREEDOM,
I NEED TO CLIMB TO A MUCH
HIGHER PLACE THAN THIS.
AND I WILL BECAUSE
FOR HARRY MACDOWEL,
FREEDOM IS THE MOST PRECIOUS
THING THERE IS.
- Man: THOSE CRATES REPRESENT
A 400 MILLION YULE OF PROFIT.
- WISH I COULD BE THERE
WHEN WHOEVER'S GETTING THEM
SEES WHAT'S IN 'EM.  THEY'RE
GONNA BE TOTALLY SPEECHLESS.
- YEAH, THEY SHOULD BE,
CONSIDERING THAT THERE ARE
200 ORGMEN INSIDE.
- SO WHERE TO THIS TIME?
- THE MIDDLE EAST.
THE MORE THEY FIGHT,
THE MORE ORGMEN THEY NEED.
FOR MILLENNION, THAT PLACE
IS A GOLD MINE.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH THE ORGANIZATION
IS MAKING A YEAR?
- NOPE.
- 23 BILLION YULE.
- REALLY?  THAT'S ALMOST
AS MUCH AS THE NATIONAL BUDGET.
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE BOSS IS GOING TO DO
WITH ALL THAT MONEY?
- MAYBE HE'S PLANNING
TO BUY THE MOON OR SOMETHING.
- ( all laughing )
- IF ANYONE COULD DO IT,
IT'S THE BOSS.
HE IS BLOODY HARRY AFTER ALL.
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- YOU TALK TOO MUCH.
- WE'RE REALLY SORRY, SIR.
- NOW GET BACK TO WORK.
- Both: YES, SIR!
- MILLENNION'S GOTTEN SO BIG
IT'S DRAINED THE TALENT POOL.
MOST OF THESE ROOKIES
ARE USELESS.
- HOW MANY ORGMEN CAN WE PRODUCE
AT FULL CAPACITY?
- APPROXIMATELY 400 PER MONTH.
- THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.  CAN'T YOU
RAISE THE PRODUCTION RATE?
- ORGMENIZATION WILL SUCCEED
ONLY WHEN THE SUBJECT
CAN WITHSTAND THE EXCRUCIATING
PAIN OF BEING TRANSMUTED
FROM ONE PHYSICAL ENTITY
INTO ANOTHER.
IF CURRENT PRODUCTION LEVELS
AREN'T SATISFACTORY,
YOU'LL NEED TO PROVIDE ME
WITH BETTER PHYSICAL SPECIMENS
TO WORK WITH.
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- WHAT ABOUT
THE SUPERIORIZATION PROCESS?
- WE'VE LEARNED THAT
SUPERIORIZATION REQUIRES
THE QUALITIES OF NOT ONLY
GREAT PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
BUT ALSO EXTREME MENTAL ACUITY.
SIMILAR IN FACT
TO THE ATTRIBUTES POSSESSED
BY ONE OF YOUR TOP EXECUTIVES.
BALLADBIRD LEE.
ON TOP OF THAT--
- ( grunting )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M SORRY, BEAR.
IT'S JUST THAT I STILL
HAVEN'T LEARNED HOW
TO CONTROL EVERYTHING YET.
WHOA.
- ( laughing )
WONDERFUL.  AN ORGMEN
WHO CAN THINK FOR HIMSELF.
BOB HERE IS A SUPERIOR,
YOU SEE.
- ORGMEN.  SUPERIOR.
THEY ARE THE DEVIL'S WORK.
AND IN HELPING TO CREATE THEM,
I BECAME RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR ACTIONS.
BIG DADDY,
IF YOU COULD SEE ME NOW,
YOU'D PROBABLY LAUGH
AND WONDER HOW I GOT MYSELF
INTO THIS MESS.
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE,
IS FOR MY DAUGHTER.
FOR SHERRY.
- IS IT ALL READY?
- YES, SIR.
AS USUAL, WE'VE GATHERED
THE CANDIDATES WHO FAILED
TO REACH THE MINIMUM LEVEL
OF PHYSICAL CONDITIONING
NEEDED FOR ORGANIZATION.
- WELL DONE.
NOW OPEN THE DOOR, PLEASE.
- MR. LEE,
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
IS IT REALLY NECESSARY?
- NECESSARY?
A SILLY QUESTION.
BUT I'LL ANSWER YOU ANYWAY.
TO KEEP UP
WITH HARRY MACDOWEL,
I HAVE TO RID MYSELF
OF EMOTIONAL WEAKNESS.
I HAVE TO STAY AS SHARP
AND AS MERCILESS AS HE IS.
IT'S NOT EASY.
IT TAKES A LOT OF PRACTICE.
( laughing )
- ( gasping )
- ( laughing )
- ( slashing )
- ( screaming )
- OPEN THIS DOOR.
YOU HEAR ME?  OPEN IT!
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE!
- ( screaming )
- HELP ME!  PLEASE HELP ME!
- LOOK, HARRY'S BACK.
HI, HARRY.
- ( clamoring )
- HEY, YOU GUYS.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU.
- DID YOU BRING US ANY PRESENTS?
DID YOU?  DID YOU?
- I THINK I HAVE SOME PRESENTS
HERE SOMEWHERE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, I BROUGHT
YOU EVERYTHING YOU ASKED ME FOR
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
- Sherry:
HE HAS SUCH ENORMOUS POWER.
YET, HE'S STILL SO SWEET
AND SO KIND.
OH, HARRY.
MY WONDERFUL HARRY MACDOWEL.
- ( laughs )
- Harry: SORRY.
THAT'S A DEAL BREAKER.
SO YOU'LL SIMPLY DELETE IT
FROM THE CONTRACT.
I'M SURE YOUR BOARD
WILL ACCEPT OUR OFFER,
BUT I STILL THINK
I SHOULD REMIND YOU
THAT REJECTION
IS NOT AN OPTION.
YOU SIMPLY HAVE NO CHOICE
IN THE MATTER.
DO WE HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING?
UNLESS OF COURSE YOU WANT
TO FOLLOW IN THE FOOTSTEPS
OF OUR DEAR DEPARTED GOVERNOR.
( laughs )
EXCELLENT.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO HEARING FROM YOU.
- SIR, I'VE GOT
SOME NEWS FOR YOU.
- ( whispering )
- MARIA.  HMM.
MARIA.  MARIA.
OH, THAT MARIA.
OF COURSE.
AND SHE HAS A LITTLE GIRL
TO KEEP HER COMPANY.
- THAT'S WONDERFUL.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT US TO DO?
BIG DADDY'S DAUGHTER.
WELL, WE WOULDN'T WANT
TO DISPUTE OVER WHO SUCCEEDS ME.
WHY DON'T WE LET
RINGO HANDLE IT?
- RIGHT.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, BOSS.
- SO FINALLY,
I'LL BE RID OF EVERYTHING THAT
REMINDS ME OF THE OLD MAN.
- HEY, MOM, I'M HOME.
- Maria:
WELCOME HOME, MIKA.
- HOW WAS SCHOOL TODAY?
- NOTHING SPECIAL, REALLY.
SAME OLD THING.
SCHOOL STUFF, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, I KNOW.
SO TO YOU,
NOTHING SPECIAL MEANS
HAVING A NORMAL
EVERYDAY LIFE.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
- Both: A NORMAL EVERYDAY LIFE.
- ( laughing )
- WE BOTH FEEL EXACTLY
THE SAME WAY, MOM.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- GOOD EVENING, MADAME.
MISS MIKA.
MAY I SERVE SOME
FRESHLY BREWED TEA?
- THAT WOULD BE LOVELY.
THANK YOU.
- IF YOU'D ASKED ME,
I WOULD HAVE MADE TEA FOR YOU.
OH.  DON'T WORRY.
I'LL FIX IT.
I DROPPED YOU, DAD.
SORRY.  OH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, DEAR?
- MOM, WHO'S THIS?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, DEAR, IT'S JUST..
THAT MAN IN THE PICTURE
WAS A VERY GOOD FRIEND
OF MINE.
HIS NAME WAS BRANDON.
BRANDON HEAT.
- BRANDON HEAT.
BRANDON.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- Mika: SO YOU GUYS WERE
REALLY JUST FRIENDS?
WASN'T HE YOUR BOYFRIEND
BEFORE YOU MET DAD?
- NO, HE WASN'T.
- SO DAD WAS YOUR ONE
AND ONLY THEN, RIGHT?
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA ANSWER,
THEN THERE WAS
SOMETHING GOING ON
WITH THIS GUY FOR SURE.
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT THE TWO OF THEM.
- MM-HMM.
IF YOU SAY SO.
- ( wind howling )
- THE WIND HAS CERTAINLY
PICKED UP OUT THERE.
- THERE'S A STORM COMING.
IT'LL BE COLD TONIGHT.
- I SUPPOSE WE MIGHT EVEN
GET A LITTLE SNOW.
Maria: THIS IS OUR 13th
WINTER HERE.
AND YET, SOMEHOW IT FEELS
LIKE WE JUST ARRIVED.
- I'M SURE YOUR LIFE HERE
WOULD HAVE MADE THE MASTER
VERY HAPPY.
MISS MIKA IS
GRACIOUS, HONEST AND KIND.
QUITE AN IMPRESSIVE
YOUNG LADY,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- ( gasps )
MR. TOKIOKA,
PLEASE KEEP MY DAUGHTER SAFE.
- YOU HAVE MY WORD.
- YOU MADE ME A PROMISE,
REMEMBER?
- YES, MADAM, I UNDERSTAND.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S WRONG, MR. TOKIOKA?
- PLEASE, MISS, WE'VE GOT
TO MOVE AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
- MOM, WHY?
WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON?
I STILL DON'T UNDER--
HEY, THAT'S A--
- MIKA, YOU'VE GOT
TO GO RIGHT NOW,
FIND A PLACE WHERE THE
ORGANIZATION CAN'T REACH YOU.
- ORGANIZATION?
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO GO?
- WHEREVER HE IS.
WHEREVER HE IS, MIKA.
- IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHEREVER WHO IS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- MR. TOKIOKA, PLEASE GO NOW!
- TAKE CARE, MADAM.
- MOM, WHY?
WHY, MOM, WHY?  MOM!
- MY DARLING,
PLEASE PROTECT MIKA.
STAY AT HER SIDE
AND GUIDE HER
TO WHEREVER BRANDON IS.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( engine turns over )
- MOMMY!  MOMMY!
MOMMY.  MOMMY.
MOMMY!
- YOU LET THE DAUGHTER GET AWAY?
YOU DIMWITS!
SHE WAS THE PRIMARY TARGET.
THE BOSS SAID,
"WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T LET HER ESCAPE.
USE ORGMEN IF YOU HAVE TO,
BUT GET HER!"
- ( engines turn over )
- Maria:
MY DARLING.
PLEASE, GUIDE OUR LITTLE GIRL.
TAKE HER
TO WHERE HE IS.
- ( crying ) MOMMY.  MOMMY.
STOP, LET ME OUT.
PLEASE LET ME OUT.
I WANNA GO BACK TO MY MOM.
TAKE ME BACK TO HER.
- I CAN'T.
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE HER DEATH WILL
HAVE BEEN FOR NOTHING.
AND I WON'T ALLOW THAT.
- DEATH?  SHE'S--
( wailing )
MOMMY, NO!
- MISS, PLEASE.
GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF.
- WHY US, MR. TOKIOKA?
WHAT IS IT THAT MAKES THEM
ATTACK US?
WHO WOULD DO SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
- IT WAS MILLENNION.
THE MAFIA.
- THE MAFIA?
- IT WAS PROBABLY MILLENNION'S
BOSS HARRY MACDOWEL
WHO ORDERED THE ATTACK.
HE'S BEEN RESPONSIBLE
FOR SO MANY DEATHS
THAT EVEN HIS OWN MEN
CALL HIM BLOODY HARRY.
- BUT WHAT'S THE MAFIA
WANT WITH US?
- MISS, THIS MAY BE DIFFICULT
FOR YOU TO HEAR,
BUT PLEASE LISTEN TO WHAT
I HAVE TO SAY.
YOUR FATHER WAS A MEMBER
OF THE MAFIA.
- ( gasps )
IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
MY FATHER, BIG DADDY.
HE WAS THE BOSS
OF MILLENNION.
- ( tires screeching )
- AND IT WAS HARRY MACDOWEL...
...WHO KILLED MY MOM.
IT WAS BLOODY HARRY.
- MISS.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU EVER TELL ME?
WHY DID YOU WAIT TILL NOW?
- IT WAS WHAT MADAME WANTED.
SHE THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE HAPPIER
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THE ORGANIZATION.
- MR. TOKIOKA,
WHERE ARE WE GONNA GO?
WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO US?
- DON'T WORRY, MISS.
I KNOW A MAN
WHO CAN PROTECT YOU,
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT I KNOW WHERE TO FIND HIM.
- PROTECT ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET A MAN
NAMED BRANDON HEAT.
- TO MEET THAT MAN.
- YES, ON 24th AVENUE
IN THE 12A DISTRICT.
THAT'S WHERE BRANDON HEAT
AND MY YOUNGER BROTHER
ARE CURRENTLY LOCATED,
BUT FIRST,
PLEASE HAVE A LOOK AT THE CASE
BY YOUR FEET.
NOW TAKE A LOOK INSIDE.
YOU HAVE TO DO WHATEVER
IS NECESSARY TO SURVIVE,
UNTIL YOU GET
TO MY BROTHER'S LABORATORY.
- I'VE NEVER USED ONE BEFORE.
- ( gasps )
- ( growling )
- ( screaming )
- ( roars )
- MR. TOKIOKA!
- ( straining )
RUN AWAY, MISS, RUN, GO ON.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- GO, HURRY,
TAKE THE CASE WITH YOU.
- ALL RIGHT.
( grunting )
- ( groaning )
- ( snarling )
- STAY SAFE, MISS.
- MOMMY.  MR. TOKIOKA.
NOW WHAT?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO ME?
I WONDER IF I'LL END UP
GETTING KILLED BY THE MAFIA.
CRYING WON'T GET
ME ANYWHERE.
HAVE TO GET THERE.
HAVE TO GET TO DISTRICT A12,
24th AVENUE.
HAVE TO MEET THAT PERSON.
I HAVE TO SURVIVE
UNTIL I GET THERE.
I HAVE TO AVENGE
MY MOTHER!
- WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- HMM?
- THAT CASE.
COULD IT BE?
- ARE YOU--
- THIS MAN,
I KNOW WHO HE IS.
HE'S THE GUY IN THE PHOTOGRAPH.
THAT GUY IS BRANDON HEAT.
- ( crashing )
- ( screaming )
- ( alarm blaring )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- IT'S THE ORGMEN.
THEY HAVE US SURROUNDED.
- WHAT?!
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- THEY SHOULD PITY MIKA.
- MOMMY!  MOMMY!
PLEASE HELP ME!
I DON'T WANNA DIE!
MOMMY!
- THE SYSTEM'S BEEN ACTIVATED.
- ( gunfire )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Man: THE MAN WHO WOKE
FROM THE DARKNESS SUFFERS
FROM MUDDLED MEMORIES,
BUT HIS RESOLVE REMAINS FIRM.
HIS DETERMINATION
UNDIMINISHED.
HIS NAME IS
"BEYOND THE GRAVE."