( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Maria: I DIDN'T KNOW IF I'D
EVER GET TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
AND NOW YOU ARE HERE,
I CAN HARDLY BELIEVE IT.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
OH, BRANDON I'M SO HAPPY.
- ALL I CAN SAY IS THANK GOD.
- Brandon: HMM.
I TRIED TO GET IN
TOUCH WITH YOU.
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
WHERE YOU WERE.
HOW TO FIND YOU.
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU WAS
THAT DAY AT THE CEMETERY.
I COULD SEE YOU WERE IN DANGER.
BUT THEY SAID WE HAD
TO LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
I HAD NO CHOICE.
BUT STILL, I'M, I'M SORRY.
- Brandon: THANK YOU.
- Maria: HUH?
THANK YOU, MARIA.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE I JOINED MILLENNION,
I FELT A SENSE OF CONTENTMENT
AND HOPE. I'D FOUND MARIA.
AND THE FACT THAT SHE
WAS HERE, IN THE SAME TOWN,
AND THAT HARRY WAS TOO...
MADE ME FEEL BETTER
ABOUT MY LIFE HERE.
THOSE WERE THE IMPORTANT THINGS.
THE ONLY THINGS THAT MATTERED.
IT WASN'T MUCH.
BUT IT WAS ALL I NEEDED.
OF COURSE AT THE TIME I HAD NO
IDEA HOW DIFFICULT IT COULD BE
FOR A PERSON TO PROTECT WHAT
WAS MOST IMPORTANT TO HIM.
THAT WOULD COME LATER.
BUT AT THAT TIME, I WAS CONTENT.
SORRY I'M LATE.
- VERY LATE. WHO GAVE
YOU THE MORNING OFF?
YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS?
- YEAH SORRY.
- A GIRL RIGHT?
- WELL I...
- YOU CAN'T SAY NO, CAN YOU?
- YEAH! I KNEW IT ALL ALONG.
WELL WHAT DO YOU
KNOW ABOUT THAT?
A GUY WHO HARDLY
EVER SAYS A WORD,
AND HAS A SOCIAL LIFE
OF A TIBETIAN MONK,
GOT HIMSELF A DATE.
DATING IS FINE SEE, BUT IF YOU
GET HITCHED BEFORE I DO...
- I'LL KILL YA...
- KILL ME, WHY?
- UGH! YOU JUST DON'T
GET IT, DO YOU?
JUST GET ME A WOMAN. ANY WOMAN,
JUST GET ME ONE , WILL YA...
- LIGHTEN UP GARY.
GIVE HIM A BREAK.
- CUSTOMER NUMBER 153
DIDN'T PAY ON TIME.
GO ROUGH HIM UP A LITTLE.
- AYE-AYE, SIR, I'M ON MY WAY.
YO, BRANDON.
YOU CAN FILL ME IN ALL THE
DETAILS LATER. ALL RIGHT?
- LISTEN BRANDON, DON'T EVER
GO NEAR THAT GIRL SCHOOL AGAIN.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I DON'T KNOW WHO
WROTE THE ORDER.
BUT THIS IS AN UPPER
LEVEL DIRECTIVE.
SO, MUST HAVE COME
STRAIGHT FROM THE TOP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BRANDON?
WHO IS THIS GIRL?
IF YOU DON'T WANNA TALK,
THAT'S FINE.
BUT LISTEN UP! IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU NEVER FORGET.
NO MATTER HOW LOW YOU
ARE ON THE FOOD CHAIN,
YOU'RE STILL A PART OF
THIS ORGANIZATION.
WHOSE MEMBERS KNOW,
THAT ORDERS FROM THE
UPPER LEVEL ARE ABSOLUTE.
AND TO BE FOLLOWED
WITHOUT QUESTION.
THATS WHAT IT MEANS TO BE
PART OF MILLENNION...
OTHERWISE PUNKS LIKE US
WOULD STILL BE FIGHTING
AND DYING IN THE STREETS.
UNDERSTAND?
- YES.
- WELL THEN, AS LONG AS
WE ARE ON THE SUBJECT.
I'M GOING TO
TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY,
TO TELL YOU WHY
OUR BOSS, BIG DADDY,
ESTABLISHED THE
MILLENNION ORGANIZATION.
AND WHAT HE TRULY
INTENDED IT TO BE.
- Harry: I SEE.
SO, YOU SAW MARIA.
I FIGURED YOU
WOULD SOONER OR LATER.
AND WITHIN 24 HOURS UPPER LEVEL
SENT YOU A WARNING. RIGHT?
- YA, BUT WHY?
- THINK ABOUT IT.
LOOK, SINCE SHE LIVES IN
BIG DADDY'S MANSION...
THERE ARE THOSE WHO MIGHT
TRY TO USE HER TO GAIN ACCESS
TO THE ORGANIZATION'S
TOP PEOPLE.
AND THINK ABOUT WHAT
WOULD HAPPEN,
IF AN OPPOSING ORGANIZATION THAT
WANTED TO TARGET BIG DADDY,
FOUND OUT SHE WAS LIVING THERE?
THEY'D BOTH BE IN DANGER.
THE FEWER PEOPLE SHE KNOWS,
THE LESS RISK THERE
IS OF THAT HAPPENING.
THATS WHY YOU GOT THE WARNING.
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
LOOK, I KNEW THAT
THIS WOULD HAPPEN
IF I TOLD YOU WHERE SHE WAS.
BUT I WANTED TO ANYWAY.
EVEN IF IT GOT ME IN TROUBLE.
IF YOU'D BEEN IN MY SHOES
YOU WOULD HAVE
DONE THE SAME FOR ME.
- SORRY IF I GOT
YOU IN TROUBLE, HARRY.
- HUH! FORGET IT.
- Man: ARE YOU BRANDON HEAT?
- Brandon: YA.
- Harry: HMM.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( knocking on door )
- Man: WE BROUGHT HIM, SIR.
- Big Daddy: AH! SEND HIM IN.
GIVE ME A MINUTE, WILL YOU?
THIS WON'T TAKE LONG.
VERY NICE.
TELL ME. DO YOU LIKE TO FISH?
HUH? TO FISH. YOU KNOW FISHING?
- I DON'T KNOW SIR.
I'VE NEVER DONE IT.
- WELL, THEN FOLLOW ME.
YES THATS RIGHT.
YOU MAKE THE FLY MOVE THROUGH
THE WATER AS IF IT'S ALIVE.
THAT'S WHAT ATTRACTS THE FISH.
HMM, GOOD VERY GOOD.
YOU HAVE A REAL KNACK FOR IT.
THIS FRIEND I ONCE HAD. IN FACT
I CONSIDERED HIM MY BEST FRIEND.
IT MUST BE WHAT
15 YEARS AGO NOW.
MY FRIEND MADE A TERRIBLE
MISTAKE. HE COMMITTED A CRIME.
IN ORDER TO MAKE RESTITUTION
HE BECAME THE GUARDIAN
OF A YOUNG CHILD. A LITTLE GIRL.
HE WAS DETERMINED TO MAKE
HER NEEDS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANYTHING ELSE IN HIS LIFE.
AND TO RAISE HER IN THE
LIGHT OF THE REAL WORLD.
NOT IN THE SHADOWS, OF THE
DARK WORLD HE LEFT BEHIND.
BUT WHEN HE DIED, HIS WISH
HAD YET TO BE FULFILLED.
SO I DECIDED TO MAKE
HIS WISH MY OWN
AND TAKE CARE OF
THE GIRL IN HIS PLACE.
- YOU MEAN MARIA...
- WELL, DO YOU RESENT ME
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE?
- NO SIR.
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
THANK YOU, BRANDON HEAT.
- Brandon: I REALLY...
I SHOULD...
- IF YOU WANT TO SEE HER,
IT'S FINE WITH ME.
AS LONG AS YOU VISIT HER
HERE AT THE MANSION.
BUT BRANDON, PLEASE DON'T
TRY TO SEE HER ANYWHERE ELSE.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- I UNDERSTAND SIR.
- MY ORGANIZATION
AND MY FAMILY
WILL USE ALL THEIR
POWER TO PROTECT HER.
BY WHATEVER MEANS NECESSARY.
HMM? YOUR LINES TIPPING
I THINK YOU'VE HOOKED ONE.
WHOA! TAKE IT EASY.
IF YOU PULL TOO HARD, THE LINE
WILL BREAK AND YOU'LL LOSE HIM.
ANTICIPATE HIS MOVES AND
REEL HIM IN SLOWLY.
YES, GOOD JOB. THAT'S THE WAY!
VERY WELL DONE!
- Widge: WHEN BIG DADDY
FIRST IMMIGRATED HERE.
THIS WAS JUST A SMALL TOWN.
SURROUNDED BY NOTHING
BUT ROCKS AND DESSERT.
BACK IN THOSE DAYS, THINGS
WERE A LOT MORE CHAOTIC
THAN THEY ARE NOW.
THERE WAS FIGHTING IN
THE STREETS ON A DAILY BASIS.
RIGHT AND WRONG DIDN'T MATTER.
ALL THAT MATTERED WAS SURVIVAL.
HE FOUGHT FOR HIS LIFE.
AS WELL AS THE LIVES OF HIS
FRIENDS AND NEIGHBORS.
BIG DADDY TOOK IT UPON
HIMSELF TO PROTECT THEM.
AS THE TOWN GOT BIGGER THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE BIG DADDY
HAD TO PROTECT GREW TOO.
AND SOON THERE WERE
HUNDREDS OF THEM.
TO HIM, EVERYONE OF THEM WAS
A MEMBER OF HIS FAMILY.
IN ORDER TO PROTECT THEM, BIG
DADDY FOUNDED AN ORGANIZATION...
WHICH HE CALLED, MILLENNION.
TO PROTECT.
YES, IN ORDER TO
PROTECT HIS FAMILY.
- Gary: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
YA THINK, THIS IS GONNA MAKE FOR
SHOWING UP 2 DAYS LATE IN A ROW?
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH THE DAMN THING YOU MORON?
GO ON FIND US A WOMAN
OR COOK IT FOR US.
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU THINKING?
- I'M SORRY.
- ( LAUGHS ) THAT'S ALRIGHT,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL ASK MY MOTHER TO DO IT.
HEY! I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WHY DON'T YOU TWO COME OVER TO
MY HOUSE FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
- IT'S A GOOD BOURBON, BOSS?
- YA I'LL OPEN IT FOR YOU.
- ALL RIGHT!
GOOD JOB, BRANDON!
WAY TO GO! THANKS FOR THE FISH!
- YOUR FULL OF
SURPRISES BRANDON.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU LIKED TO FISH.
- Gary: FISH TALK EVEN
LESS THAN HE DOES.
MAYBE THATS WHY THEY
GET ALONG SO WELL.
- YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT...
- ( both laugh )
- WELCOME, SIR.
I WAS TOLD TO EXPECT YOU.
MY NAME IS TOKIOKA.
BIG DADDY'S HEAD BUTLER.
- THANK YOU.
- THE MANSION'S REALLY
HUGE , ISN'T IT?
I HAD A HARD TIME
GETTING USED TO IT AT FIRST.
BRANDON, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING THESE DAYS?
NOTHING DANGEROUS I HOPE?
- I'M WORKING FOR
A COURIER SERVICE.
- IS THAT WHAT HARRY DOES TOO?
- YEAH.
- THATS WONDERFUL.
YOU BOTH HAVE REAL JOBS NOW.
DOESN'T SEEM FAIR THAT I'M
THE ONLY ONE WHO GETS TO LIVE
IN SUCH A GORGEOUS PLACE.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT THAT.
BUT THAT'S ALRIGHT.
AFTER ALL I'M NOT GOING
TO LIVE HERE FOREVER.
ONCE I GRADUATE, EVERYTHING
IS GOING TO CHANGE.
FIRST, I'LL FIND A JOB. THEN I
CAN START LIVING ON MY OWN.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO SURVIVE...
- Big Daddy: AHA! SO THAT'S
WHAT YOU TWO HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT ALL THIS TIME?
DID I HEAR RIGHT?
YOU ARE PLANNING ON MOVING
OUT OF THE MANSION?
- OH, GOOD AFTERNOON
UNCLE ASAGI PLEASE JOIN US.
- AS FAR AS I AM CONCERNED,
YOU CAN LIVE HERE FOREVER.
- BUT ONLY AS LONG
AS IT SUITS YOU.
- THANK YOU UNCLE ASAGI...
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU TO
A FRIEND OF MINE.
UNCLE, THIS IS BRANDON.
- I'M ASAGI.
- I'M BRANDON HEAT, SIR.
WELL, BRANDON HEAT.
I HOPE THAT MARIA'S WELFARE
WILL BE AS IMPORTANT
TO YOU AS IT IS TO ME.
- YES, SIR.
- WELL AS THE SAYING
GOES, THREE IS A CROWD.
SORRY TO BUTT IN LIKE THIS.
- YOU'VE DONE NO SUCH THING.
- BESIDES, I BAKED A FRESH PIE.
AND WE WERE JUST
ABOUT TO HAVE SOME.
- WON'T YOU JOIN US?
- Big Daddy: I'D LOVE TO.
- ♪ I'VE FOUND ♪
- ♪ HURTS IN HERE ♪
♪ I FOUND ♪
- ♪ SPACE TO FEEL ♪
- ♪ AND THE WORLD
KEEPS ON SPINNING ♪
- ♪ ROUND AND ROUND ♪
- ♪ SO I LAY STILL AND WAIT ♪
- ♪ WILL WE EVER
HAVE THE WORDS ♪
KNOW THE PAIN? ♪
- ♪ WILL WE EVER BE
BACK THERE AGAIN? ♪
- Brandon: HUH!
- ( gun firing )
- ( gasps )
- Randy: CANCEL THE PARTY?
- Man: WHY, RANDY?
- ITS COME TO
OUR ATTENTION,
THAT A MAFIA GROUP
CALLED LIGHTNING
HAS BEEN UNUSUALLY BUSY
THE PAST FEW DAYS.
ACCORDING TO AN INFORMANT THEY
MIGHT TRY TO PULL SOME SORT OF
STUNT DURING
TONIGHTS FESTIVITIES.
- BUT THIS EVENT IS BIG
DADDY'S OPPORTUNITY
TO REINFORCE HIS RELATIONSHIPS,
WITH OUR MOST IMPORTANT
BUSINESS ASSOCIATES.
IT'S FAR TOO LATE TO
CANCEL IT NOW.
- AND IF IT TURNS INTO A
WORST-CASE SCENARIO,
WHAT THEN?
- Bear: THE PARTY WILL
TAKE PLACE AS PLANNED.
COLLECT EVERY BIT OF INFORMATION
YOU CAN MANAGE TO SCRAPE UP
ON THESE LIGHTNING GUYS.
LEAVE THE REST TO ME AND MY MEN.
WE WILL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- Randy: WE ARE
DEPENDING ON YOU, BEAR.
- Bear: OF COURSE.
- HARRY'S GONNA LOVE THIS.
- ( humming )
- GOT SOME GOOD NEWS
FOR YOU HARRY. BOB'S DONE IT.
- HUH?
- HERE TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS A CHANCE
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
START GATHERING INFORMATION
ABOUT THIS LIGHTNING GROUP.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH IT COSTS.
- ALRIGHT HARRY BUT ONLY IF I
GET TO COME ALONG FOR THE RIDE.
- WELL NATURALLY.
- BRANDON!
WOW! THAT TUX LOOKS
REALLY GREAT ON YOU.
BUT THE HAIR?
I WAS JUST JOKING. NOW, COME
AND DANCE WITH ME.
- I...
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
- ALRIGHT THEN I'M
GOING TO TEACH YOU.
- ON BEHALF OF MY COMPANY, I
WANNA TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO REAFFIRM OUR
COMMITMENT TO BUILDING A CLOSER
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE
MILLENNION ORGANIZATION,
AND ITS AFFILIATES.
- THAT'S GREAT BRANDON.
- Man 1: THE ONLY ONE WE ARE
AFTER IS MILLENNION'S BOSS.
THE OTHERS ARE OF NO IMPORTANCE.
- Man 2: UNDERSTOOD. ANYTHING
ELSE WE SHOULD KNOW?
- EVERYTHING IS GOING JUST FINE.
ONE OF OUR GUYS
IS ALREADY INSIDE.
- Man 2: IT'S TIME.
- HEY YOU! GET OUT
OF THE WAY. MOVE IT.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
LOOKS LIKE NO ONE CAN
USE THIS ROAD RIGHT NOW.
AND THAT INCLUDES
YOU LIGHTENING GUYS.
- WHAT IN THE!
- MILLENNION?
- GIVE THAT MAN A PRIZE.
- ( gun firing )
- ( inaudible )
- ( applause )
- Harry: THESE GUYS ARE...
- Bear: MEMBERS OF LIGHTNING.
- YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
WE'VE MET BEFORE HAVEN'T WE?
- JUST ONCE . I'VE NEVER
GOT THE CHANCE TO THANK YOU.
IT WAS A GREAT LEARNING
EXPERIENCE. YOU TAUGHT ME A LOT.
HARRY MACDOWEL OF MILLENNION,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
WHEN I FOUND OUT THEY
WERE GOING TO ATTACK US.
I KNEW I HAD TO ACT QUICKLY.
SIR, FORGIVE ME FOR NOT
ASKING YOUR PERMISSION.
- YOU WANT TO CLIMB THE
LADDER, DON'T YOU?
- YES SIR.
- HMM. ALRIGHT. NO PROMISES.
BUT I'LL KEEP YOU GUYS IN MIND.
NOW GO HOME. YOU'VE DONE
ENOUGH FOR ONE NIGHT.
WE'LL CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
IT'S THE LEAST WE CAN DO.
- ( laughing )
- ( man screams )
- OUR COMPANY IS COMMITTED
WITH ALL OF ITS AVAILABLE
RESOURCES TO COMPLETING
THIS PROJECT AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
FURTHERMORE OUR LEGAL EXPERTS
WILL DRAFT THE NEW AGREEMENT...
- YOUNG BRANDON.
- ( gunfire )
- ( screams )
- BIG DADDY!
- ( chattering )
- ( screams )
- NO BRANDON!
PLEASE BRANDON, HOLD ON.
YOU HEAR ME?
- IF IT WEREN'T FOR
THAT YOUNG MAN...
- CALL THE PARAMEDICS TELL THEM
TO SEND AN AMBULANCE. HURRY!
- BUT BIG DADDY, IF I LEAVE YOU,
YOU'LL BE ALL BY YOURSELF.
- JUST DO IT...
- IN THAT CASE BE CAREFUL
BIG DADDY. REAL CAREFUL.
- Maria: BRANDON, WHAT'S
TAKING HIM SO LONG?
- WHY BRANDON? WHY
DID YOU SAVE ME?
FOR MILLENNION'S SAKE OR...
FOR MARIA'S...
- ( gasping )
- BRANDON!
- Brandon: WHY? WHY DID I
DO IT? WHY DID I PROTECT HIM?
WHY DID I FIRE A GUN?
WHY DID I KILL?
AS I BEGAN TO LOSE CONSCIOUSNESS
I SAW MARIA'S FACE.
AND HARRY'S TOO.
AND I KEPT THINKING ABOUT
WHAT IT REALLY MEANS
TO PROTECT SOMEONE.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: THE MAN PULLS THE
TRIGGER IN SILENCE.
A BRIGHT DEADLY FLASH TAKES
ANOTHER SOUL.
BRANDON HEAT OF MILLENNION,
THE MAN THEY CALL "THE SWEEPER."