( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Brandon: I'M GOING TO TURN
THIS PLACE INTO A BATTLEFIELD.
I WON'T LET THOSE
BASTARDS ESCAPE.
I DON'T CARE IF I WIN OR LOSE.
IT'S ENOUGH TO DIE
ON EACH OTHER'S SWORD.
- WHAT'S UP, LITTLE BUDDY?
YOU WANNA GO TO WAR
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- Brandon: YEAH.
- VERY INTERESTING...
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
- Brandon: I'LL PROTECT...
I'LL PROTECT...
BECAUSE I'M...
- ( gunfire )
- HMM?
- SO, LITTLE BUDDY...
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF MY PET
MONSTERS, IMPRESSIVE HUH?
THEY WANT ONLY ONE THING.
TO MAKE SURE MY
DREAMS COME TRUE.
- Blood War: YOU CAN'T
KILL THEM LIKE THAT.
TRY BLASTING THEM INTO PIECES.
- ( gun clicks )
- D-POINTS, HUH?
YOU'RE WELL PREPARED.
WANNA GO OUT IN A BLAZE OF
GLORY, RIGHT, LITTLE BUDDY?
WELL, IT'S NOT MUCH
OF A BATTLEFIELD,
BUT IT'LL HAVE TO DO.
AND I'LL BE RIGHT HERE
WITH YOU TILL THE VERY END.
- DON'T TRY ANYTHING,
LEE. YOU MAY BE FAST,
BUT EVEN YOU CAN'T
BEAT A BULLET.
- MAYBE. MAYBE NOT.
AS A RULE, BULLETS
AREN'T VERY EFFECTIVE
UNLESS THE PERSON
WHO IS FIRING THEM
CAN HIT THE INTENDED TARGET.
- HMM! YOU THINK
I'M A RANK AMATEUR...
( gasps )
- Balladbird: ELIMINATE ANY
HINT OF ONE'S EXISTENCE...
I WAS TRAINED BY EXPERTS, HARRY.
- ( groans in pain )
- DAMN, THAT HURTS!
WHERE...
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
- ( gunfire )
- A BULLETPROOF VEST?
EVEN SO, YOU GOT AT LEAST
A COUPLE OF BROKEN RIBS,
LITTLE BUDDY,
I'M SURE YOU DO.
BUT YOU TOOK OUT
SIX OF MY GUYS.
THAT'S A PRETTY
IMPRESSIVE PERFORMANCE.
BE A REAL SHAME TO WASTE
ALL THAT TALENT BY KILLING YOU.
SO LISTEN, WHY DON'T YOU JOIN
ME? WE'D MAKE A GREAT TEAM.
- ( panting )
- FINE. YOU'LL DIE FIRST
AND THEN JOIN ME.
IT'S ALMOST TOO GOOD
TO BE TRUE, ISN'T IT?
MY PARTNER, CANNON VULCAN,
GOT HOLD OF A NEW TECHNOLOGY
THAT ALLOWS HIM TO
REVIVE THE DEAD
AND TURN THEM INTO UNSTOPPABLE
KILLERS UNDER OUR CONTROL.
IT'S A PROCESS
CALLED NECROLYZATION.
AND WHEN YOU'RE DEAD,
WE'LL REVIVE YOU THE SAME
WAY, LITTLE BUDDY.
AFTER YOU'VE BEEN NECROLYZED,
YOUR FIRST MISSION WILL
BE TO KILL YOUR BOSS,
BIG DADDY OF MILLENNION.
( laughs )
NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL DRAMATIC.
I'M SURE THE AUDIENCE
WILL LOVE IT.
- ( gunshots )
- I OWE YOU GUYS.
AND NOW, IT'S PAYBACK TIME.
BUNJI KUGASHIRA STYLE!
SOMEONE DOES A NUMBER ON ME,
THERE'S NO WAY I'M NOT
GONNA PAY HIM BACK.
- LOOKS LIKE I'M ABOUT TO GET
ANOTHER PAWN TO NECROLYZE.
- CHECKMATE. GAME'S OVER.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE HISTORY,
HARRY MACDOWEL.
- YOU KNOW, THIS JUST
ISN'T LIKE YOU, LEE...
WHATEVER YOU'RE THINKING,
THINK ABOUT THIS TOO.
IF YOU WANNA GET TO THE
TOP, THEN LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU'RE GONNA BE
BETTER OFF WITH ME
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO SAVE YOUR SKIN.
- TAKE A LOOK AROUND, LEE.
- WHY...
YOU COULD'VE HAD
ME KILLED ANY TIME.
- ( laughs )
- BECAUSE THEIR TARGET
WAS BALLADBIRD LEE.
I DIDN'T LET THEM SHOOT
BECAUSE IT WAS YOU.
I HAD TO GET THROUGH
THAT THICK SKULL OF YOURS
TO MAKE YOU SEE THAT WE SHOULD
BE WORKING TOGETHER,
NOT AGAINST EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW ME
BETTER THAN ANYONE, LEE.
YOU KNOW MY AGENDA,
YOU KNOW WHAT MY GOALS ARE.
SO I HAVE NO DOUBT YOU KNOW
WHAT MY PLANS ARE
FOR MILLENNION'S FUTURE.
IF YOU FOLLOW MY LEAD
AND JOIN BRANDON AND BOB
AS A MEMBER OF THE TEAM,
YOU'LL GET TO THE TOP,
I PROMISE YOU.
I NEED YOU.
SO I'LL TAKE YOU WITH ME.
ALONG WITH YOUR AMBITIONS.
I'LL TAKE YOU WHERE
YOU WANNA GO, LEE.
- WHAT ABOUT
THE CODE OF IRON?
I'VE BETRAYED THE
ORGANIZATION...
- WHAT I'M OFFERING YOU
IS THE KIND OF FREEDOM
THAT TRANSCENDS
THE CODE OF IRON.
FREEDOM.
- YOU'VE BEEN BLASTING AWAY
FOR QUITE A WHILE NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A BREAK? GIVE
THEM A LITTLE TIME TO RECOVER?
- NO WAY!
- YOU AREN'T AS USED TO
BEING IN HELL AS I AM.
- BUNJI!
- DAMN MILLENNION TO HELL!
JUST HANG IN THERE!
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT...
I KNEW IT WAS COMING.
BUT THOSE MONSTERS ARE
ABOUT TO GET UP AGAIN,
WHICH I FIND PRETTY DAMN
ANNOYING, DON'T YOU?
- YEAH.
- COME ON, YOU WIMPS!
DON'T STOP NOW.
THIS PLACE IS FINALLY TURNING
INTO A DECENT BATTLEFIELD!
COME ON!
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!
- I WONDER IF BRANDON
IS ALL RIGHT...
- Man: PLEASE, SIR! IF
YOU JUST WAIT HERE...
HARRY ISN'T IN
RIGHT NOW AND...
- TELL ME WHERE I CAN
FIND BRANDON HEAT?
- TWENTY YEARS...
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN TWENTY YEARS,
I FEEL LIKE I'VE FINALLY BECOME
WHAT I WAS MEANT TO BE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, LEE?
I TOLD YOU NOT TO COME HERE,
DIDN'T I?
YOU SHOULD BE AT MILLENNION,
MAINTAINING YOUR COVER
AS A LOYAL MEMBER
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
- IS THAT WHAT YOU HAD IN
MIND FROM THE BEGINNING
WHEN YOU KILLED OUR
FATHER AND SENT ME
TO JOIN MILLENNION?
- Vulcan: ANCIENT HISTORY.
- SO TELL ME, BIG BROTHER.
IF YOUR PLAN WORKS AND YOU
TAKE OVER MILLENNION...
WHAT THEN? WHAT DO YOU
PLAN TO DO NEXT?
- I PLAN TO GO TO WAR.
- GO TO WAR?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER WHERE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHO.
I'LL GO TO WAR
AGAINST THE WORLD.
BLOOD AND I WERE DRAFTED
TO FIGHT IN A WAR,
OUR GOVERNMENT STARTED
FOR IT'S OWN SELFISH REASONS.
WE WENT THROUGH HELL
IN THAT SHITHOLE OF A PLACE
MORE TIMES
THAN I CARE TO REMEMBER.
BUT WE DO REMEMBER...
NEITHER BLOOD NOR I
WILL EVER FORGET IT...
WHICH IS WHY NEITHER OF US
WILL EVER FORGET THAT SUNSET.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
IF THERE'S GONNA BE A WAR,
WE'LL BE THE ONES WHO START IT.
WHEREVER WE WANT,
WHENEVER WE WANT...
- Balladbird: THAT'S NONSENSE.
- WHAT?
- I SAID THAT'S NONSENSE.
BESIDES, WITH SUCH
PETTY AMBITIONS,
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
OF BEATING THE GUY
YOU'RE COMPETING AGAINST.
THE GUY BY THE NAME
OF HARRY MACDOWEL!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ( gunfire )
- BUNJI!
- DON'T WORRY. I'M STILL HERE.
- SO WHAT NOW, LEE?
YOU GONNA KILL YOUR OWN
BLOOD BROTHER?
BECAUSE MACDOWEL'S
TURNED YOU AGAINST ME?
- NO! BECAUSE WHAT YOU SAID
IS SO DISAPPOINTING.
MY GOAL IS TO
END UP AT THE TOP.
AND WITH HARRY,
I KNOW I CAN GET THERE.
I'LL BE BALLADBIRD LEE,
MILLENNION EXECUTIVE!
NECROLYZATION?
- YOU'RE A STUPID MAN.
- ( gunfire )
- BRO!
- IT'S A REAL SHAME...
- IT CERTAINLY IS.
- IT WAS A GOOD FIGHT.
IT WAS A GOOD BATTLEFIELD.
WELL, GUYS, IT'S BEEN FUN.
- Brandon: I GUESS THIS IS IT.
- WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON, TOKIOKA?
- THE RESULTS
THAT I WAS EXPECTING.
THE DURATION OF THE
NECROLYZATION EFFECT
IS ONE WEEK AT THE MOST. AS
MY CALCULATIONS PREDICTED.
- YOU KNEW, ALL ALONG.
- IMPOSSIBLE AMBITIONS
TEND TO DISINTEGRATE
IN THE FACE OF REALITY.
HISTORY IS FULL OF
OVERLY AMBITIOUS MEN
WHO FAILED AND YOU WILL, TOO.
- YOU BASTARD!
- BROTHER...
PREPARE YOURSELF!
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHY'RE THEY JUST LYING THERE?
WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG WITH THEM?
- THEY BROKE.
- HUH? YOU'RE HISTORY,
LITTLE BUDDY.
( gasps )
- NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND, LEE?
YOU'VE REACHED YOUR LIMIT.
BUT LIMITS LIKE THAT
DON'T EXIST.
WHEN YOU'RE A MEMBER
OF MILLENNION.
YOU CHOSE ME,
AND MILLENNION.
THIS IS WHAT IT
MEANS TO CHOOSE.
- BUNJI...
- YEAH?
I'M STILL AMONG THE LIVING,
AT LEAST I THINK.
- YOU WERE CONDUCTING A
SECRET INVESTIGATION INTO
LIGHTNING'S ACTIVITIES.
YOU'LL BE A HERO.
- HEY, HARRY. I'M
GLAD I FOUND YOU!
- WHY? WHAT'S UP?
- WE'VE JUST BEEN PUTTING ONE
OF THOSE LIGHTNING GUYS
THROUGH THE WRINGER...
HE'S TELLING US THAT BRANDON
AND BLOOD WAR ARE TRYING
TO KILL EACH OTHER.
- WHAT?
- UNBELIEVABLE...
BETRAYED BY MY OWN
LITTLE BROTHER...
DAMN IT. HOW EMBARRASSING!
- I CAN'T AFFORD TO DIE.
NOT HERE.
AND NOT AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
THE WAR HAS JUST BEGUN.
- BUT THIS IS
A BATTLEFIELD TOO...
- YEAH. IT IS A BATTLEFIELD...
- LOOKS LIKE WE GET TO DIE
ON THE BATTLEFIELD AFTER ALL...
ON OUR OWN BATTLEFIELD...
- GUESS SO...
I DON'T WANNA DIE
IN A SHITTY PLACE LIKE THIS...
ESPECIALLY WHEN WE'RE GETTING
BOSSED AROUND BY SOME
GOOD-FOR- NOTHING
SNOT-NOSED PUNK.
- Vulcan: YEAH. THIS
IS NO WAY TO DIE.
NO WAY I'M GONNA
LET THAT HAPPEN.
- Blood War: IF I'M GONNA DIE,
I'M GONNA DO IT IN MY WAY.
GO OUT IN STYLE WITH
A WHOLE BUNCH OF FIREWORKS!
- Vulcan: AND I'LL BE
RIGHT THERE WITH YOU.
I'LL MAKE THE BULLETS, AND
YOU'LL PULL THE TRIGGER. DEAL?
- ( laughs )
- Blood War: SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
SOUNDS LIKE A WHOLE LOT OF FUN.
UNTIL THEN, I'M
LEAVING MY PARTNER
WITH YOU, CANNON VULCAN.
- I ACCEPT, BLOOD WAR.
I WONDER HOW MANY TIMES
YOU SAVED MY ASS...
- ABOUT AS MANY
AS YOU SAVED MINE...
- WE SHOULD HAVE DIED IN THAT
WAR A MILLION TIMES OVER...
BUT WE DIDN'T.
- Brandon: BLOOD WAR...
- IS THAT YOU, LITTLE BUDDY?
THAT'S RIGHT...
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
AT THE END,
THERE'S GOTTA BE LOTS OF
FIREWORKS, TO GO OUT IN STYLE.
- ( gunshot )
- WHAT THE HELL? HOW COULD
HE JUST GIVE UP LIKE THAT?
- NECROLYZATION...
- WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
- YO! BRANDON! BUNJI!
- IT'S HARRY!
- GET DOWN!
- I THINK IT'S TIME TO GO!
- HE DOESN'T.
- LEE!
- IT'S NOTHING. JUST A SCRATCH.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
ME, HARRY. JUST MAKE SURE
YOU STAY ALIVE, ALL RIGHT?
FOR YOUR SAKE AND MINE.
- THIS WAY!
- HIS POWER IS AMAZING!
- ( roaring )
- HEY, IT'S BEAR WALKEN...
- FOR THE RECORD, THIS
OPERATION WASN'T MY IDEA.
THE REASON WE'RE HERE
IS BECAUSE BIG DADDY
ORDERED US TO PROTECT YOU!
- ( growls )
- OVERKILLS, FIRE!
WHAT THE...
- UNBELIEVABLE...
-HEY, BRO...
- HOLD ON, BRANDON.
- PROTECT MILLENNION...
I'VE GOT TO PROTECT MILLENNION.
I'M JUST DOING...
MY JOB!
- BRANDON...
- Brandon: I CAN'T HEAR IT...
MARIA'S VOICE,
I CAN'T HEAR IT ANY MORE.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: WHAT HAVE I ATTAINED
IN THE PAST THREE YEARS,
IS IT HOPE OR IS IT REGRET?
WE RUN AND RUN
AND KEEP ON RUNNING.
WITHOUT EVER STOPPING.