- ( theme music playing )
- ( screaming )
- ( glass shattering )
- MR. LEE, PLEASE,
TRY TO CALM DOWN!
- MR. LEE!
- ( screams )
( yells )
- LEE, THAT'S QUITE
ENOUGH OF THAT NOW.
- YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
BEAR WALKEN,
BUT BOB POUNDMAX
IS NEVER EVER COMING BACK,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THAT TRAITOR.
HE KILLED MY BEST FRIEND
LIKE SOME KIND OF BARBARIAN.
- I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
WE'RE TRYING TO LOCATE HIM.
THE ENTIRE ORGANIZATION'S
INVOLVED IN THE SEARCH.
- IF YOU DO HAPPEN
TO TRACK HIM DOWN,
I REQUEST THAT YOU DON'T
LET ANYONE LAY A HAND ON HIM.
BECAUSE I WANT TO
EXECUTE HIM MYSELF.
I'LL CUT HIM INTO LITTLE PIECES,
LEAVING NOTHING BEHIND.
- ( exhales )
- ( gunshot )
- ( inaudible )
- Mika: UM, EXCUSE ME?
YOU KNEW MY MOM WHEN
SHE WAS YOUNG, DIDN'T YOU?
SO TELL ME, WHAT WAS MOM LIKE
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNGER?
WAS SHE REAL NICE?
WAS SHE PRETTY?
I BET SHE WAS REALLY BEAUTIFUL,
WASN'T SHE?
AND I'M GUESSING THAT
SHE WAS ALSO PRETTY POPULAR
BECAUSE SHE WAS SO CUTE.
AM I RIGHT?
I ASSUME THAT
SHE PROBABLY HAD
QUITE A FEW BOYFRIENDS AS WELL.
YOU AND MY MOM WERE CLOSE,
WEREN'T YOU?
WOULD YOU PLEASE
TELL ME ABOUT HER?
HEY, YOU!
- HUH?
- WERE YOU EVEN LISTENING
TO ANYTHING I WAS SAYING?
YOU KNOW, YOU BOYS REALLY
NEED TO PAY CLOSER ATTENTION
TO THE THINGS
THAT A GIRL SAYS.
OH, JEEZ. YOU'RE ALWAYS
SO QUIET LIKE THIS.
IF YOU NEVER SAY ANYTHING,
YOU WON'T EVER GET
THE GIRLS TO LIKE YOU.
SERIOUSLY.
IT WOULDN'T HURT YOU
TO TALK TO ME FOR A LITTLE BIT,
NOW WOULD IT?
IT FEELS SO SILLY
SITTING HERE TALKING TO MYSELF.
BUT WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, GRAVE?
IS THIS YOUNG LADY
GIVING YOU A HARD TIME AGAIN?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- JUST NOW,
I WENT UP TO THE ROOF
AND TOOK A LOOK OUTSIDE,
AND I SAW QUITE A FEW
MILLENNION AGENTS.
YOU KILLED ONE OF THE BIG FOUR
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
IN RETURN, IT'S ONLY NATURAL
FOR THEM TO HEAT THINGS UP.
IN ANY CASE,
ROUND ONE IS PRETTY MUCH OVER.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, MISS?
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
- ( sighs )
- IF YOU THINK THIS
IS ALL MEANINGLESS,
I SUGGEST THAT
YOU QUIT NOW.
OTHERWISE, YOU'LL REGRET IT
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
JUST LIKE I DO.
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I DON'T WANT TO
SEE ANYONE DIE.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
EVEN SO,
I STILL...
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
REGARDLESS OF HOW
YOU FEEL ABOUT IT, MISS,
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS MAN
IS DETERMINED
TO CUT YOU A PATH
THROUGH ALL THOSE BATTLES.
- I WANT YOU TO MAKE
AN ANNOUNCEMENT
THAT BOB POUNDMAX'S DEATH
WAS DUE TO A BLOOD CLOT
FROM HIGH CHOLESTEROL LEVELS.
MAKE SURE NO ONE
ON THE OUTSIDE
EVER DISCOVERS THAT IT WAS
A TRAITOR THAT KILLED HIM.
- UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
- Harry: THE NECROLIZED
HAS PREVAILED
OVER THE SUPERIORILIZED.
BUT HERE'S SOMETHING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW ON EARTH
WAS HE ACTIVATED?
HE MUST HAVE HAD
AN ACCOMPLICE.
OF COURSE!
TOKIOKA.
WAIT A MINUTE,
THAT INCIDENT.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN
THE ONE WHO DESTROYED
THE OUT-OF-CONTROL
NECROLIZER.
I GET IT NOW.
THAT MUST BE WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU'VE BEEN TRYING TO
RUIN THINGS FOR ME
FOR 13 YEARS, BRANDON.
YOU WANT REVENGE THAT BADLY.
( chuckles )
SO, YOU HATE ME THAT MUCH?
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
BRANDON?
- ( panting )
( grunts )
- HOLD IT!
- ( murmurs )
( grunts )
( gasps )
( whimpers )
- WHY DID YOU TRY
TO RUN AWAY?
YOU GOT INFORMATION,
DON'T YOU?
- IF YOU KNOW WHERE THE MAN
AND THE LITTLE GIRL ARE HIDING,
I RECOMMEND YOU TELL US,
YOU GOT THAT?
- UH...
I DON'T KNOW, I SWEAR.
- DON'T LIE TO US.
- I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
- THEN WHY WERE YOU RUNNING?
- I OWE PEOPLE MONEY
AND I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE LOAN SHARKS.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO LISTEN TO YOUR STORIES.
YOU'D BETTER
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- YOU MAY NOT BELIEVE ME,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
I JUST DON'T KNOW.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
- ( murmurs )
- ( grunts )
- HURRY!  RUN!
- ( panting )
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasps, grunts )
( groans )
( grunts )
WHOA!
OH...
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S HER.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- TAKE A LOOK FOR YOURSELF.
LOOKS LIKE WE FOUND THE GIRL
WHO WAS WITH THE TARGET.
- GOOD, I GOT IT.
I'LL GO REPORT IT
TO HEADQUARTERS.
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HERE...
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
- ( gasps )
- IF I'M INVOLVED
WITH YOU GUYS,
NO MATTER HOW MANY LIVES I HAVE,
IT WON'T BE ENOUGH.
SO STAY THE HELL
AWAY FROM ME.
( grunts )
( sighs )
- WHY DON'T WE GO
AND SEE MARIA?
- HUH?
- ( truck horn blares )
- ( cellphone rings )
( beeps )
- Man: ( through cellphone )
UH, IS THIS BIG BRO BUNJI?
I JUST RECEIVED A REPORT
THAT TWO OF OUR GUYS
GOT WORKED OVER REAL GOOD
IN SECTION "C."
I'M THINKING IT WAS
MOST LIKELY OUR TARGET.
- Bunji: I SEE.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN UP.
I WANT EVERYBODY PULLED OUT
OF SECTION "C" RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SURE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
PULL 'EM ALL OUT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THE TARGET.
I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
- Mika: REALLY?
SO MY MOM ACTUALLY
USED TO LIVE IN THIS PLACE?
- Grave: YEAH.
- HURRY.
COME ON, HURRY.
GEE, YOU SURE ARE SLOW, GRAVE.
( sighs )
THIS IS THE PLACE WHERE
MY MOM USED TO LIVE.
THIS IS WHERE
MY MOM GREW UP.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S BEEN AWHILE
SINCE ANYONE LIVED HERE.
NOW LET ME SEE...
I THINK THERE WAS PROBABLY
A COUCH RIGHT OVER THERE,
AND ANOTHER ONE
RIGHT OVER HERE.
AND THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
A TABLE THIS BIG
RIGHT HERE IN THE CENTER.
THIS IS WHERE
THE SIDE TABLE WOULD BE,
AND A STAND WOULD GO HERE.
I'M GUESSING THIS IS PROBABLY
WHERE THE CABINET WAS.
AND THEN MY MOM
WOULD BE SITTING HERE
KNITTING.
I CAN SEE HER NOW.
- BRANDON?
- ( gasps )
- MARIA.
- OH, BRANDON.
YOU GOT IN ANOTHER FIGHT,
DIDN'T YOU?
YOU CAN BE SO HOPELESS,
REALLY.
DID YOU HAVE TO GET
YOURSELF HURT SO BADLY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
DOES IT HURT?
YOU DON'T SAY MUCH
TO ME, DO YOU?
YOU'RE ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
SO SILENT.
ALL YOU DO IS LOOK AT ME
WITHOUT SAYING A WORD.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SAY ANYTHING.
I CAN STILL HEAR YOU.
I WILL ALWAYS BE ABLE
TO HEAR YOU LIKE THAT.
NO MATTER HOW SAD
OR HOW PAINFUL IT MAY BE,
YOUR VOICE ALWAYS
MANAGES TO REACH ME
LOUD AND CLEAR.
SO PLEASE,
JUST HOLD ME FOR NOW,
BRANDON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SAY A WORD.
I JUST WANT TO BE
IN YOUR ARMS HERE, LIKE THIS.
- MARIA.
- BRANDON.
- GRAVE!
- HMM?
- HEY, WHAT'D I SAY ABOUT
PAYING ATTENTION TO LADIES?
- ( chuckles )
- BY THE WAY,
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S TIME
THAT YOU TELL ME?
I MEAN, ABOUT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH MOM.
- ( exhales )
- MY LEGS ARE NUMB FROM
RUNNING AROUND LOOKING FOR YOU.
BIG GUY.
- ( exhales )
- ( gasps )
- DAMN.
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOUR OLD REFLEXES
ARE COMING BACK.
- BUNJI KUGASHIRA.
- SO THEN YOU REMEMBER ME?
- KUGASHIRA?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
HE'S PART OF MILLENNION.
- IT'S YOU.
SO YOU'RE BIG DADDY'S
DAUGHTER.
HIS ONLY OFFSPRING.
- ( gasps )
- SORRY, BUT I'M NOT
INTERESTED IN A KID.
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE
YOURSELF DISAPPEAR?
- YOU AND YOUR GUYS
KILLED MY MOM, DIDN'T YOU?
- YEAH, I GUESS WE DID.
- TELL ME WHY.
WHAT IS IT MY MOM
EVER DID TO YOU GUYS?
ALL SHE WAS DOING WAS
LEADING A NORMAL LIFE!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO KILL HER?
- I TAKE IT THAT HARRY MACDOWEL
JUST ISN'T TOO FOND
OF ANYTHING THAT'LL
REMIND HIM OF BIG DADDY,
THAT'S ALL.
- ( gasps )
NO WAY.
THAT CAN'T BE THE REASON.
- IT WAS ALL
'CAUSE OF YOU.
YOU WERE THE ORIGINAL REASON,
BIG GUY.
- ( gasps )
- YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU
WERE GONNA CLIMB
UP THE LADDER TOGETHER
WITH HARRY,
AND THE REASON I AGREED
TO JOIN MILLENNION
WAS IN ORDER TO SUPPORT
THE TWO OF YOU.
BUT YOU QUIT MIDSTREAM.
IT WAS ALL YOUR FAULT.
AND EVEN NOW
AFTER YOU'RE DEAD,
YOU STILL MANAGE
TO GET IN OUR WAY.
WHY IS THAT?
ANSWER ME!
YOU DON'T WANT TO ANSWER?
OR IS IT THAT
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
WELL, WHATEVER.
EITHER WAY,
IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
TRAITORS CANNOT BE FORGIVEN.
AND YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO TAUGHT ME THAT, RIGHT?
THE SO-CALLED
"CODE OF IRON."
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
OH, GRAVE.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
THAT YOU'VE BEEN NECROLIZED.
AND I HAVE TO ADMIT,
THAT PUTS ME AT
A DISADVANTAGE,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
THAT'S WHY...
YOU'LL EXCUSE ME
IF I USE THIS.
- ( gasps )
OH, GRAVE.
- THIS LITTLE TOY HERE
WAS CUSTOM MADE
AT OUR RESEARCH CENTER.
IT PARALYZES
THE TISSUES IN THE BODY
UNTIL THEY
COMPLETELY BREAK DOWN.
I HEARD THAT IT WORKS
REAL WELL ON DEAD BODIES.
BYE, BRO.
- ( grunts )
- ( beeps )
- HMM?
- ( grunts )
( straining )
( groans )
- WHY'D YOU DO IT?
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO GO
AND BETRAY MILLENNION?
I'M ASKING YOU
TO TELL ME WHY.
- OH!
( grunts )
- THERE WAS NO DOUBT THAT
YOU WERE THE NUMBER-ONE SWEEPER.
AND YOU WERE THE BEST SWEEPER
MILLENNION EVER HAD.
WEREN'T YOU DOING
EVERYTHING YOU COULD
SO THAT HARRY COULD
BECOME THE BOSS?
SO WHY'D YOU BETRAY US?
ANSWER ME.
- ( grunts )
- DO YOU KNOW WHY
I DECIDED TO COME HERE
ALL BY MYSELF?
IT'S BECAUSE
THE WAY I SEE IT,
I WAS YOUR FIRST APPRENTICE.
BECAUSE YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO TAUGHT ME ABOUT
THE CODE OF IRON.
THAT'S WHY.
I'VE GOTTA KILL YOU.
- ( grunts )
- STOP IT!
I BEG YOU,
PLEASE DON'T SHOOT.
WEREN'T YOU BOTH
IN THE SAME GROUP?
DOESN'T THAT MAKE
THE TWO OF YOU COMRADES?
- HEY, DON'T BLAME ME.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO WENT
AND BETRAYED THE GROUP.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I KNOW I'VE ONLY
JUST MET HIM,
BUT IN THE SHORT TIME
THAT I'VE KNOWN HIM,
I CAN TELL THAT HE'S NOT
THE TYPE OF PERSON
WHO'S CAPABLE OF
BETRAYING ANYBODY.
I'M SURE THAT HE HAD TO
HAVE A GOOD REASON.
- YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
- HUH?
- BUT REGARDLESS OF WHAT
ACTUALLY HAPPENED BACK THEN,
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
THAT HE ABANDONED US.
AND NOW HE'S COME BACK TO GET
REVENGE AGAINST
THE ORGANIZATION.
IT'S MY JOB TO KILL HIM
AND MAKE SURE
HE STAYS THAT WAY.
THAT'S THE RULE.
NO EXCEPTIONS.
- PLEASE DON'T!
- SHUT YOUR TRAP.
- PLEASE DON'T DO IT.
YOU MUSTN'T!
- DIDN'T I JUST TELL YOU
TO SHUT UP?
- ( crying )
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS!
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO SHUT UP!
- I'M BEGGING YOU,
PLEASE!
- ( groans )
FOR THE LAST TIME,
SHUT UP.
- PLEASE, DON'T!
- SHUT UP OR ELSE!
- ( screams )
NO, STOP!
GRAVE, HELP ME!
( screams )
STOP IT!
PLEASE, I'M SORRY!
STOP!  JUST STOP!
( crying )
- WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY
KNOW ABOUT ANYTHING?
YOU DON'T KNOW A SINGLE
THING ABOUT ANY OF US,
DO YOU HEAR ME?
AND YOU DEFINITELY
DON'T KNOW JACK SHIT ABOUT ME.
- ( crying )
- THIS IS NOTHING FOR A KID
TO BE INVOLVED WITH.
- BUNJI...
- HUH?
- BUNJI!
( shouts )
- ( grunts )
( stammers )
( groans )
( chuckles )
- BUNJI.
- ( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- Bunji: BIG GUY,
PLEASE DON'T
BETRAY THE FAMILY.
- ( computer keys clacking )
- UM, SO HOW IS GRAVE DOING?
- WHATEVER THAT STUFF WAS
THEY SHOT INTO HIM
WAS VERY DANGEROUS.
WITH THE EQUIPMENT
WE HAVE HERE,
EVEN IF HE DOES RECOVER,
HE'LL ONLY BE ABLE TO REGAIN
ABOUT 70% OF HIS ABILITIES.
- OH, NO.
ON THAT DAY,
I THINK I ACTUALLY
HEARD HIM CRY.
IT WAS A REALLY
AWFUL SOUND.
SUCH A SAD
AND POWERFUL VOICE,
SO FULL OF PAIN.
JUST LIKE AN ANIMAL'S CRY.
AND THAT WAS WHEN
IT STARTED SNOWING.
- ( breathes deeply )
( grunts )
- GRAVE!
- ( gasps )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
REALLY, YOU CAN STOP NOW.
( crying )
- ( groans )
- GRAVE?
- I WOULD NEVER BETRAY.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Grave: A REUNION WITH
THE ONE WHO SAVED MY LIFE
WHEN I WAS JUST A ROOKIE.
WE WERE LIKE A FAMILY
FOR AWHILE.
IT ENDS WITH A TRAGEDY
AND A SCREAM--
A SAD SCREAM THAT SHAKES
THE ENTIRE CITY.