( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Brandon: I REMEMBER...
THE BLUE SKY.
I REMEMBER...
GLOWING CLOUDS.
MY FRIEND SHOUTING.
- Harry: I WANNA BE FREE...
FREE FROM PAIN...
FREE FROM FEAR...
FREE TO TAKE AS MUCH AS I WANT
AND GIVE AS MUCH AS I WANT.
AND SOMEDAY, SOMEHOW,
THAT'S THE WAY IT'S GONNA BE...
IN ADDITION, TO THE ONGOING
OPERATIONS MENTIONED EARLIER,
WE JUST SIGNED CONTRACTS FOR
A JOINT BUSINESS VENTURE
WITH 8 NEW TRADING CORPORATIONS.
SO, THE AMOUNT COMING BACK
TO THE ORGANIZATION WILL BE
5 PERCENT OF TOTAL SALES.
- A VERY IMPRESSIVE DEAL, HARRY.
YOU'VE DONE EXCELLENT
WORK AS USUAL.
AT THIS RATE, WE WILL BE ABLE
TO FORM PARTNERSHIPS
WITH ALL THE CORPORATIONS.
- THAT MIGHT BE TOO AMBITIOUS.
RIGHT, BRANDON?
- FOR ANYONE ELSE, IT WOULD BE.
- ( laughs ) OH, COME ON.
GET SERIOUS, WILL YOU?
- REMEMBER HARRY, THE SUCCESS
OF THE ORGANIZATION WILL
DEPEND ON WORKING IN
HARMONY WITH OUR ALLIES.
THE ORGANIZATION CAN EXIST
ONLY SO LONG AS THE SOCIETY,
OF WHICH IT'S A PART,
IS FUNCTIONING SMOOTHLY.
THE USE OF FORCE IS DISRUPTIVE.
SO, BUILD RELATIONSHIPS
THAT ARE MUTUALLY ADVANTAGEOUS.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
NEVER BETRAY THOSE
TO WHOM YOU HAVE
PROMISED LOYALTY.
THE SOCIETY, THE ORGANIZATION
AND THE FAMILY.
- OF COURSE.
I'M WELL AWARE OF THAT.
- I'M SORRY. CHALK IT
UP TO AN OLD MAN
FEELING HIS OWN MORTALITY,
LOOKING FOR PEACE OF MIND.
- I'LL BE SURE TO
REMEMBER THAT, BIG DADDY.
- TO THE ORGANIZATION.
- Harry: ( sighs )
THIS WINE'S DELICIOUS.
ONLY THE BEST AS USUAL.
- TOKIOKA.
- Big Daddy: WELL,
I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
- YOU HAVING FUN, GUYS?
- AH, MARIA.
- HI, MARIA. LONG TIME NO SEE.
- YOUR LOOKING GOOD, HARRY.
- THANKS, RIGHT BACK AT YOU...
- IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE.
- YEAH.
- UH...
- DEAR, WILL YOU TAKE
SOME TIME OFF TODAY?
- YES, THAT'S
THE PLAN, DEAR.
- CAN I TALK TO YOU?
A LITTLE LATER.
- WELL, OF COURSE.
ANYTIME YOU WANT.
- Harry: WHAT THE
HELL WAS THAT ABOUT?
SINCE WHEN HAVE THOSE
TWO GOTTEN SO CLOSE?
BRANDON, DOESN'T
THAT BOTHER YOU?
- BIG DADDY FOUNDED
THE ORGANIZATION,
AND HAS DEVOTED HIS
LIFE TO IT, EVER SINCE.
NOW, WE SHOULD FREE HIM OF
ANY FURTHER RESPONSIBILITY.
- BRANDON...
- I WANNA HELP,
MAKE HER HAPPY AGAIN.
- ( grunts ) YOU IDIOT.
DON'T BE SUCH A CHUMP.
- SORRY, BRANDON.
I'M VERY SORRY, REALLY I AM.
BUT I WON'T BE HAVING DINNER
WITH YOU TONIGHT.
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I FEEL NAUSEOUS AND DIZZY.
- HMM...
- BRANDON, I LOVE HIM. I DO.
I LOVE HIM.
I'M SURE IT'S ALL FOR THE BEST,
THAT EVERYTHING TURNED OUT
THE WAY IT WAS SUPPOSED TO.
I BELIEVE THAT. I'M RIGHT,
AREN'T I, BRANDON?
- CONGRATULATIONS, MARIA.
BESIDES, I GOT A LOT
OF WORK TO DO.
- HM?
- IT'S GONNA BE HARD WORK,
CLIMBING UP THE LADDER
WITH HARRY MACDOWEL.
AND MAKING HIM THE NEXT
BOSS OF MILLENION, BUT
WE CAN HANDLE IT.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- ( laughs )
YEAH, BRANDON. I AGREE.
- Man 1: WHATEVER'S COMING
DOWN MUST BE PRETTY IMPORTANT.
I HEAR BIG DADDY'S SENT FOR
EVERY MAJOR PLAYER
IN THE FAMILY.
- Man 2: ACCORDING TO
THE RUMOR I HEARD,
HE'S GONNA ANNOUNCE WHO
THE NEXT BOSS IS GONNA BE.
- Man 3: IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WITH NO BLOOD RELATIVES IN
THE ORGANIZATION,
HE'S GOT TO PICK
A SUCCESSOR,
WAY IN ADVANCE, YOU KNOW.
- Man 2: BET YOU BEAR WALKEN
WILL BE THE NEXT BOSS.
- Man 3: HOW ABOUT THIS MACDOWEL
GUY? COULD HE BE THE ONE?
- Man 2: HARRY? YOU CAN'T BE
SERIOUS. HE'S WAY TOO YOUNG.
- Man 1: MAYBE, BUT HE
KNOWS MORE ABOUT
MILLENION'S OPERATIONS
THAN ANYONE.
AND HE'S GOT POWERFUL
FRIENDS. INCLUDING SOME
OF THE MOST INFLUENTIAL
MEMBERS OF THE FAMILY.
- Man 3: HE IS ONE SHREWD
FELLA, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- Man 2: WHICH IS WHY HE MIGHT
TURN OUT TO BE THE NEXT BOSS
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
- Big Daddy:
THE TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
BUT WE, THE MEMBERS OF THE
MILLENION ORGANIZATION
HAVE NOT ALLOWED THE PASSING
YEARS TO WEAKEN OUR RESOLVE.
FOR WE HAVE CREATED A
FOUNDATION MADE UNSHAKABLE
BY YOUR SOLIDARITY AND SUPPORT.
FORGIVE ME GENTLEMEN, IF I CUT
SHORT THE TRADITIONAL ORATORY.
BUT LET'S GET TO THE HEART
OF THE MATTER, SHALL WE?
AS SOME OF YOU MAY KNOW,
I ASKED YOU HERE TODAY BECAUSE
VERY SOON NOW,
I WILL OFFER MY RESIGNATION.
IT'S BEEN 35 YEARS SINCE
I ESTABLISHED
THE ORGANIZATION
CALLED MILLENNION.
THANKS TO YOU, THE LOYAL
MEMBERS OF THE FAMILY
OUR ORGANIZATION HAS GROWN
INTO A SUCCESSFUL ENTERPRISE.
AND FOR THAT, I THANK YOU.
HOWEVER I AM NO
LONGER A YOUNG MAN.
AND THEREFORE I AM PASSING
THIS RESPONSIBILITY
TO THE COLLEAGUE WHO
IS NEXT IN LINE FOR IT.
- ( all murmuring )
MR. ALZAC TINO.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE OVER.
- WHAT? DID I HEAR YOU, RIGHT?
DID YOU SAY YOU WANTED
ME TO TAKE OVER?
- IS HE CRAZY?
- HE MUST BE!
- ( all murmuring )
- ( gasps )
- ( Harry applauding )
- HEY BRO, WHAT'S SHAKIN'?
- HE DECIDED ON ALZAC TINO
AS A SUCCESSOR.
WHICH I ADMIT,
IS A REASONABLE DECISION.
YOU ALREADY KNEW?
BUT YOU COULDN'T UNLESS...
- HMM...
- HEY, I ONLY DID IT 'CAUSE
WE ALL WANTED TO BE LISTENING
WHEN BIG DADDY SAID,
THAT YOU WERE GONNA BE
THE NEW BOSS, BUT THEN...
- BUT THEN, HARRY MACDOWEL
WAS EMBARRASSED
TO LEARN HE'S A LOSER.
- STOP THAT.
- NICE CANS, BOB. SOUNDS
LIKE A REAL STUDIO IN HERE.
- Big Daddy: NOW, TELL ME
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF HIM?
ESPECIALLY WHETHER OR
NOT YOU FEEL HE'S WORTH
CONSIDERING FOR
THE TOP POSITION.
- Brandon: I THINK SO.
- BIG DADDY AND BRANDON...
- I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN, EVERYONE
EXPECTED HARRY MACDOWEL
WOULD BE MY CHOICE,
AS THE NEXT BOSS OF MILLENION.
BUT HE'S NOT. I SURPRISED THEM
AND CHOSE ALZAC INSTEAD.
ANY OBJECTION TO THAT?
- THAT'S IRRELEVANT, SIR.
- YOU SEE, VERY TALENTED GUYS
LIKE HARRY, HAVE NATURAL GIFTS
WHICH ALLOW THEM TO SUCCEED
WITHOUT MUCH EFFORT.
THEY WORK AS LITTLE AS THEY CAN,
AND LOOK FOR SHORTCUTS.
SHORTCUTS WORRY ME. NOT THAT
HARRY ISN'T DOING A FINE JOB.
THE GROWTH OF THE ORGANIZATION
LATELY IS DUE MAINLY TO HARRY.
HE'S CERTAINLY QUALIFIED
TO BE MILLENION'S NEXT BOSS.
NOR DO I QUESTION HIS LOYALTY.
BUT SOMETHING IN MY GUT,
TELLS ME TO BE AWARE OF AN
UNKNOWN DANGER. A HIDDEN THREAT.
I PROMISE YOU THIS, IF HARRY
MACDOWEL DOES ANY DAMAGE
TO THIS ORGANIZATION,
HE'LL REGRET...
- HARRY IS NOT A TRAITOR
AND HE NEVER WILL BE.
YOU'VE GOT MY WORD.
- ( chuckles )
- HOWEVER, EACH AND EVERY
TRAITOR WHO BREAKS
THE CODE OF IRON,
WILL RECEIVE
THE SAME PUNISHMENT.
NO MORE, NO LESS.
REGARDLESS OF RANK OR STATUS.
NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE.
- ( gasps )
THOSE ARE THE RULES
YOU ASK THE MEMBERS
OF THIS ORGANIZATION TO LIVE BY,
AND I DO SO,
TO THE BEST OF MY ABILITY.
MY DUTY IS TO KILL TRAITORS,
WHENEVER AND WHEREVER
I FIND THEM, NO MATTER
WHO THEY ARE.
- HARRY, IS THERE
SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- HEY BRO, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
- NOTHING, GUYS. NOTHING AT ALL.
- SO, DID YOU
HEAR ANYTHING, HARRY?
- YEAH, YOU MIGHT SAY THAT.
- HMM, WHAT?
- SHE WAS HOT WHOEVER SHE WAS.
SHE WAS COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
( laughs )
- All: HMM?
- Harry: HEY.
- Brandon: HEY HARRY, WHAT'S UP?
YOU GOT SOME TIME TO KILL,
BEFORE YOU SHOW UP
AT THAT MEETING?
- Harry: YEAH, A WHILE ANYWAY.
HANG OUT WITH ME, WILL YA?
WE'RE BOTH SO BUSY ALL THE TIME.
LET'S TAKE A LITTLE TIME OFF,
FOR A CHANGE. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- Brandon: YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
- SO, HOW'S SHERRY DOING?
- JUST FINE.
SHE REALLY SEEMS TO BE
ENJOYING HERSELF AT SCHOOL.
BUT HER RELATIONSHIP
WITH HER FATHER
ISN'T GETTING ANY
BETTER, LATELY.
- BECAUSE YOU AND
SHERRY ARE TOGETHER?
- HOPE NOT. BRANDON,
LET ME GET YOU A DATE
AND THE FOUR OF US CAN
DOUBLE, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YESTERDAY, THEY TOOK ALZAC
TO THE HOSPITAL.
- ( gasps )
- HE'S CRITICAL, I HEAR.
THREE MONTHS AFTER
HE TOOK OVER.
POOR GUY DESERVED
BETTER, YOU KNOW.
( scoffs ) GUESS HE
RAN OUT OF LUCK.
♪ RAIN, HERE COMES THE RAIN ♪
♪ HERE COMES THE RAIN ♪
♪ RIGHT FROM THE
MOMENT I MET YOU ♪
♪ I KNEW THAT I
COULD NEVER FORGET ♪
- HARRY, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
WANNA GO SAY "HELLO?"
- WHO TO? HUH?
- FRIENDS OF OURS.
- I MEAN KENNY AND THE OTHERS.
- KENNY?
- ( gasps )
- OH! OF COURSE! NO PROBLEM!
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I DID PROMISE THOSE GUYS
ONCE WE CLIMB THE
LADDER, WE'D COME BACK
AND BUILD THEM THE
MOST SPECTACULAR
GRAVES THIS TOWN HAS
EVER SEEN. REMEMBER?
HELL, I CAN AFFORD THE
WHOLE CEMETERY NOW.
- I'LL JUST GIVE THEM THE
CASH AND THEY CAN START
BUILDING THE NEW
GRAVES FOR THESE...
- HARRY...
- HASN'T CHANGED A BIT.
TAKES YOU BACK, DOESN'T IT?
- YEAH...
- GUESS SHE'S THE ONE WHO
RUNS THE ORPHANAGE NOW,
INSTEAD OF THAT OLD
BASTARD WE HATED SO MUCH.
THERE WAS THAT ONE TIME,
REMEMBER THAT?
- YEAH.
- Harry: THE WIND WAS
REALLY STRONG THAT DAY.
THAT SHEET JUMPED OFF THE
CLOTHES LINE LIKE IT HAD
A WILL OF IT'S OWN.
IT STARTED FLYING AROUND,
LIKE IT WAS ALIVE.
WE RAN AND RAN AND RAN.
CHASING THAT SHEET,
DETERMINED TO FOLLOW IT,
NO MATTER HOW FAR WE HAD TO GO.
IN SEARCH OF FREEDOM.
HIGHER...
AND THEN THAT MEAN OLD BASTARD
BEAT THE HELL OUT OF US
FOR PLAYING WITH
THE DAMN LAUNDRY.
- HE WAS TOUGH ON BOTH OF US...
- WISH HE WAS ALIVE. WOULD
HAVE BEEN FUN TO PAY HIM BACK
FOR WHAT HE DID
TO US, BACK THEN.
- ( starts engine )
- YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GONNA
BUY THE WHOLE DAMN ORPHANAGE.
THEN I'LL BUILD THE TOWN
A BRAND NEW ONE.
- ( whirring )
- THE BOSS HAS GOT TO DIE.
- ( gasps )
- I'VE ACQUIRED SOMETHING.
SO POWERFUL THAT WE CAN
CONTROL THIS ENTIRE CITY.
NO, SOMETHING EVEN BIGGER.
BIG DADDY IS JUST
A FEEBLE OLD MAN,
WHOSE DECIDED HE'S OUTLIVED
HIS USEFULNESS.
YET HIS INFLUENCE
IS UNDIMINISHED.
HE WON'T GET OUT OF THE WAY.
NOT TO MENTION THAT WITHOUT
BIG DADDY AROUND...
MARIA WILL BE YOURS
FOR THE TAKING.
- ( grunts )
- ( gun clatters )
- ( Brandon whimpering )
- BRANDON...
- ( gasps )
( shouting ) BRANDON!
- Brandon: I REMEMBER...
THE BLUE SKY.
I REMEMBER...
GLOWING CLOUDS.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: BRANDON HEAT
DIED, AND A DARK,
GRITTY WIND SWEPT
OVER MILLENNION.
IS FEELING SMOTHERED
BY THE VERY AIR WE BREATHE,
A SIGN OF THINGS TO COME?