- ( collar jingles )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- BEYOND THE GRAVE.
NO.
BRANDON HEAT...
YOU PATHETIC BASTARD.
YOU LOOK MORE DEAD
THAN ALIVE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT,
THANKS TO DR. TOKIOKA.
HE NECROLIZED YOU,
DIDN'T HE?
- YEAH.
- WHO THE HELL
ASKED HIM TO?
HE SHOULD HAVE
STAYED OUT OF IT.
- THAT WAS MY CHOICE.
I ASKED HIM TO
BEFORE I WAS KILLED.
- BIG DADDY TOLD ME
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU
BEFORE HE LEFT US.
AND THAT WAS WHEN
I LEARNED THAT YOU KNEW
EVERYTHING I'D DONE
IN ORDER TO CLIMB
THE LADDER TO THE TOP.
- THAT'S RIGHT!
I DID WHATEVER
HAD TO BE DONE!
GOT RID OF ANYONE
IN MY WAY
TO GET ANOTHER STEP
UP THE LADDER.
RANDY AND THEN ALZAC
EVEN BIG DADDY.
AND THEN IN SECRET,
I FUNDED THE RESEARCH
THAT LED TO NECROLIZATION.
AND YOU WERE WATCHING
EVERY MOVE I MADE
AND NEVER TOLD ME!
( sighs )
YOU WERE THE SAME WAY
AS A KID, YOU KNOW?
YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED A BIT.
ALWAYS CALM,
ALWAYS READY TO
FOLLOW MY LEAD.
ALWAYS THERE IF I NEEDED YOU.
- DID YOU THINK
I WAS A FOOL
FOR BEING SO AMBITIOUS?
THAT I WAS JUST LIKE ALL
THE OTHER COCKY YOUNG PUNKS
TRYING DESPERATELY
TO DO THE IMPOSSIBLE?
- WHY DIDN'T YOU SHOOT ME
WHEN YOU HAD THE CHANCE?
YOU HAD EVERY RIGHT TO KILL ME
FOR BETRAYING THE ORGANIZATION,
BUT YOU CHOSE NOT TO.
WHY?
- I THOUGHT YOU WOULD
BECOME THE BOSS OF MILLENNION.
- WHO, ME?
I'M THAT AND MORE.
I CONTROL
THE ENTIRE ORGANIZATION
AND THE ENTIRE CITY AS WELL.
AND EVERYONE DOES
AS THEY'RE TOLD.
IF I SAY BLACK IS WHITE,
THEN FROM NOW ON,
IT'S WHITE.
IT'S MINE, ALL OF IT.
I CAN TAKE WHAT I WANT
AND GIVE WHAT I WANT.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
MILLENNION'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
- MILLENNION IS WHATEVER
THE BOSS SAYS IT IS,
AND THAT'S ME.
- IT'S A BETRAYAL.
- YOU'RE THE TRAITOR,
NOT ME.
( chuckles )
WHAT'S DONE IS DONE.
WE CAN'T CHANGE THE PAST,
BUT WE CAN CELEBRATE
OUR REUNION WITH A DRINK.
IT'S A 43-YEAR-OLD BOURBON
CALLED "TIAN SATTY."
IT WAS MADE
THE YEAR WE WERE BORN.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT
MAKES IT SO GOOD.
WELL?
( chuckles )
BOTTOMS UP.
AHH.
THAT'S GOOD.
HAVE SOME.
I REMEMBER THE TIME
I ASKED BIG DADDY
IF HE'D LIKE TO TRY
A LITTLE TASTE OF THIS STUFF.
BUT BIG DADDY SAID BOURBON'S
JUST A DERIVATIVE OF WHISKEY.
WHY BOTHER WHEN YOU CAN HAVE
THE GENUINE ARTICLE?
IN OTHER WORDS,
I'M BOURBON,
AND HE'S WHISKEY.
AM I BIG DADDY'S DERIVATIVE?
A WATERED DOWN VERSION
OF THE REAL THING?
HOW DARE HE ACT
SO HIGH AND MIGHTY.
HE COMMITS GOD KNOWS
HOW MANY CRIMES
TO GET TO THE TOP,
AND THEN STARTS PREACHING
PEACE AND HARMONY,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN EVERYBODY
THINKS HE'S SOME KIND OF SAINT.
THE OLD FART WAS
NOTHING BUT A HYPOCRITE,
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
- HMM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- BIG DADDY KNEW
THAT HE HAD DONE A LOT OF
BAD THINGS IN THIS LIFE.
HE WAS AWARE OF
HIS OWN WEAKNESSES.
THAT'S WHY HARMONY AND ORDER
WERE SO IMPORTANT TO HIM.
AND WHY HE FELT
THEY WERE THE KEY...
TO MILLENNION'S FUTURE.
- I HATE IT.
I HATE THE THOUGHT
OF YOU BEING DUPED
INTO BELIEVING
THAT OLD FART'S BULLSHIT!
HE ROBBED ME.
STOLE THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IN MY LIFE FROM ME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?!
WHAT HE STOLE
WAS IRREPLACEABLE!
HE'S ABOUT TO LEARN
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GONNA STEAL FROM HIM?!
EVERYTHING HE'S GOT!
- ( chuckles )
( blows )
WERE WE WRONG, BRANDON?
DID WE MAKE THE WRONG
DECISION AFTER ALL?
I CAN'T SEEM TO REMEMBER
WHEN THINGS STARTED TO
TAKE A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
EITHER WAY, IN THE END,
IT TURNED OUT LIKE THIS.
BUT NOW THAT THE PIECES
ARE BROKEN APART,
THEY CAN'T BE
PUT BACK TOGETHER.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
BRANDON?
- ( gasps )
- YOU RECOGNIZE IT,
DON'T YOU?
SURE.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
THIS IS YOUR GUN.
THE ONE YOU WERE GONNA
USE TO KILL ME.
AND THIS...
IS THE ONE I USED
TO KILL YOU.
- WHY?
- OH, AS MEMENTOS,
I SUPPOSE.
( sighs )
LET'S SETTLE
THE OLD SCORE.
- ( guns cock )
- ( chuckles )
I'LL KILL YOU
ALL OVER AGAIN.
KILL YOU ONCE
AND FOR ALL!
- ( gunshot )
- ( groans )
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
( panting )
- ( groans )
- ( chuckles )
OH, HOW THE MIGHTY
HAVE FALLEN.
AND NOW,
I'M A WANTED MAN.
- SEND US EVERYONE YOU'VE GOT.
- ( guns cock )
- ( gunfire )
- ( exhales )
- ( gunshots )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( groans )
- HMM?
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- ( shudders )
- ( gunshots )
- ( gasps )
- ( exhales, grunts )
- ( grunts )
- ( whimpers )
( gasps )
( grunts )
- ( groans )
( panting )
- ( murmurs )
- ( shivers )
- ( grunts )
- ( exhales )
( groans )
- BRANDON.
BRANDON, WHY ARE YOU...
PROTECTING ME?
WHY ARE YOU HELPING ME?
TELL ME WHY!
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH THOSE TWO.
IF GRAVE CAME HERE
TO KILL HIM,
WHY'S HE PROTECTING THE GUY?
- DOESN'T MATTER.
WE'RE GONNA
KILL THEM BOTH ANYWAY.
HEY, GUYS.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE USING
THAT ANTI-NECROLIZER AMMO.
- ALL RIGHT.  UNDERSTOOD.
- ( phone beeps )
- YOUNG LADY,
BRANDON HEAT'S LOCATION
HAS JUST BEEN CONFIRMED.
- THAT'S WONDERFUL.
WHERE IS HE?
- HE'S IN THE SLUM
ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF
THE WEST DISTRICT.
- PLEASE, TAKE ME THERE.
HE NEEDS MY HELP.
- WE CAN'T DO THAT.
- WHY NOT?
- HE'S NOT ALONE.
BRANDON HEAT IS WITH
HARRY MACDOWEL.
- ( gasps )
- MEMBERS OF THE ORGANIZATION
HAVE THE AREA
COMPLETELY SURROUNDED.
AND THEIR ORDERS ARE
TO EXECUTE BOTH OF THEM.
- NO WAY!
OH, PLEASE.
PLEASE, STOP THEM!
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO.
- I CAN'T.
- PLEASE, SIR!
I BEG YOU.
- THE ANSWER IS NO!
- ( gasps )
( cries )
( panting )
- LET HER GO.
- EVEN IF SHE GETS THERE,
THERE'S NOTHING
SHE CAN DO.
THEIR DESTINY
HAS ALREADY BEEN DECIDED.
- ( gunfire )
( gunfire continues )
- HUH?
- ( gunfire )
- AAH!
- ( grunts )
( grunts )
- ( men gasp )
- ( groans )
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- ( men shouting )
- FALL BACK!
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
- ( groans )
- HARRY?
- THEY FINALLY GOT ME.
EVER SINCE THE FIRST JOB
I EVER PULLED,
I'VE BEEN PROUD OF THE FACT
THAT I'VE NEVER
TAKEN A BULLET.
( chuckles )
BUT I GUESS MY LUCK
JUST RAN OUT.
( groans )
- BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY,
RIGHT?
- ( groans )
- ( gun cocks )
- TAKES ME BACK...
TO THE DAYS
WE USED TO LIVE HERE.
I CAN STILL SMELL
JOLICE'S COOKING.
HE WAS ONE HELL OF
A COOK, WASN'T HE?
- KENNY, NATHAN,
AND JOLICE.
THOSE WERE THE DAYS.
SURE, IT WAS HARD
TO MAKE ENDS MEET,
BUT IT WAS SO MUCH FUN.
- ( chuckles )
WE'RE BACK TOGETHER
AFTER SUCH A LONG TIME.
SO WHAT THE HELL
ARE WE DOING THIS FOR?
- BRANDON!
- ( sighs )
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING WAY OVER THERE?
COME JOIN US.
YOU TOO, HARRY.
- HURRY UP.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
- HOLD ON, CHILL OUT.
I'VE STILL GOT
A LOT TO TALK ABOUT...
WITH MY BUDDY HERE.
- SAVE IT.  I MEAN,
YOU DON'T WANT TO
KEEP HER WAITING,
DO YOU?
- HUH?
MARIA?
- BRANDON.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR
PROTECTING MIKA.
- SORRY, BRANDON,
FOR CAUSING YOU
ALL THAT TROUBLE.
- Maria: BRANDON.
- Big Daddy: BRANDON.
- ( groans )
BY THE WAY,
I ASKED YOU A QUESTION BEFORE
AND YOU NEVER ANSWERED IT.
WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO HELP ME?
I THOUGHT...
THAT YOU CAME BACK HERE
TO KILL ME.
ISN'T THAT WHY
YOU CAME BACK FROM THE GRAVE?
FOR REVENGE?
( grunts )
I SENT THE TEAM
THAT KILLED MARIA,
THE LOVE OF YOUR LIFE.
I KILLED BIG DADDY,
AND YOU LOVED HIM TOO.
YOU HAVE EVERY REASON
TO HATE ME.
I'M YOUR ENEMY, RIGHT?
- ( grunts )
- COME ON, BRANDON.
HERE I AM,
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
USE THAT GUN OF YOURS.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
YOU MOCKING ME,
YOU SON OF A BITCH?!
SAY SOMETHING!
( groans )
( chuckles )
I KNOW.
IT'S MY FAULT, NOT YOURS.
( sighs )
LEE AND BOB.
BEAR AND BUNJI.
ORGMEN AND I
INVESTED SO MUCH TIME
AND MONEY IN... GONE.
ALL GONE.
SHERRY TOO.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING LEFT.
KILL ME.
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
IN DISGRACE ANYMORE.
KILL ME, BRANDON.
I'M...
BEGGING YOU.
KILL ME!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
( panting )
WHAT WAS THAT?
- ( car horn honking )
- YOUNG LADY,
GET IN THE CAR.
- HARRY.
HARRY.
( sighs )
FOREVER.
MY LOVE.
HARRY.
- SHERRY.
- TAKE CARE OF MY DAUGHTER,
HARRY MACDOWEL.
- I WILL, DAD.
- ( chews )
THIS'LL DO IT, ALL RIGHT,
IF WE USE THIS
PIECE OF INFO
TO BLACKMAIL THEM.
- WE CAN TAKE OVER THEIR
SOUTHPORT DISTRIBUTION ROUTES.
THE WHOLE DISTRICT
WILL BELONG TO US.
- THAT'S ABOUT IT.
- THAT'S BRILLIANT, BOB.
BRILLIANT.
- OF COURSE,
IT MIGHT GET UGLY,
CONSIDERING WHO
WE'RE DEALING WITH.
- HEY, NO PROBLEM, BIG GUY.
YOU CAN LEAVE 'EM TO ME.
I CAN'T WAIT.
- Harry: GOOD.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU, BUNJI.
YOU TOO, BRANDON.
- YEAH.
- BRANDON.
- ( gunfire )
- Harry: BRANDON.
BRANDON.
BRANDON...
- THEY MUST BE DEAD.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
BUT A PILE OF RUBBLE.
- THAT ONE LITTLE EXPLOSION
LEVELED THIS WHOLE BUILDING.
GUESS IT MUST HAVE BEEN
AS DILAPIDATED AS THEY WERE.
- ( men laughing )
- ( grunts )
- BRANDON.
- GUESS NONE OF US ARE GONNA
EARN THAT BONUS THEY OFFERED US.
- YEAH.  PRETTY PATHETIC
WAY TO GO FOR A GUY
THEY CALLED "BLOODY HARRY."
- HUH?
- ( straining )
AAH!
- ( men gasp )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunting )
- HUH?!
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
OH!
- ( groans )
( grunts )
- BRANDON, TAKE IT!
- ( gunshots )
- ( shouts )
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
( exhales )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( grunts )
( groans )
( breathes deep )
( shouts )
- THAT'S RIGHT.
PULL EVERYONE BACK.
STOP THE ATTACK NOW.
YOU IDIOT,
RELAY THAT ORDER IMMEDIATELY!
RIGHT NOW, DO YOU HEAR?!
- ( moans )
( grunts )
BRANDON.
( chuckles )
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T DIE,
YOU STUBBORN
SON OF A BITCH.
- I KEEP...
MAKING THE SAME MISTAKE.
- HUH?
- CHOOSING HARRY MACDOWEL...
OVER MILLENNION.
BUT...
I HAVE NO REGRETS NOW...
THAT I COULDN'T KILL...
MY BEST FRIEND.
- ( gasps )
BRANDON!
I'M SORRY!
( sobbing )
Harry: I WISH WE COULD
GO BACK TO THOSE DAYS.
TO THE OLD DAYS,
AND BE FREE AGAIN.
FREE FROM EVERYTHING.
THE WAY WE WERE THEN.
- LET'S GO HOME,
HARRY MACDOWEL.
- LET'S DO THAT,
BRANDON HEAT.
- HARRY.
- BRANDON.
- ( panting )
- MRS. MIKA!
- HEY, YOU!
WAIT A MINUTE.
- I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
GRAVE, I LOVE YOU.
- ( panting )
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A GREAT LIFE...
WITHOUT ME.
TODAY...
AND TOMORROW.
AND FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
- BRANDON!
BRANDON!
( grunts )
YOU AND I...
ARE A FAMILY, RIGHT?
WE'RE A FAMILY.
FOREVER.
AND EVER.
- HARRY?
HARRY...
- GRAVE.
- HARRY.
- BRANDON HEAT.
- BIG GUY.
- BRANDON.
- Both: HARRY.
- YO, BRANDON.
- BRANDON.
BRANDON...
- DAMN IT.
( spits )
I'LL SHOW HIM.
SOME DAY, I'LL SHOW
THAT OLD FART.
HEY.
ARE YOU THE ONE WHO
CAME HERE YESTERDAY?
- MM-HMM.
- THE NAME'S HARRY MACDOWEL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- BRANDON HEAT.
- BRANDON HEAT, HUH?
( chuckles )
NICE MEETING YOU, BRANDON.
- Maria: WELCOME HOME.