- ( theme music playing )
- SO KUGASHIRO ORDERED
ALL OF OUR MEN
IN SECTION "C" TO PULL OUT?
- YES, SIR.
HE ALSO TOOK AN E-BRID
COUNTER-NECROLIZER FROM THE LAB.
WE BELIEVE HE INTENDS
TO CONTACT OUR TARGET.
- I THINK THAT I MIGHT
UNDERSTAND WHY HE DID IT.
KUGASHIRO WANTS TO SETTLE
THIS THING MAN-TO-MAN.
WHERE'S KUGASHIRO NOW?
- WE LOST TRACK OF HIM, SIR.
- HMM?
I SEE.
KUGASHIRO'S ONE OF
THE BEST WE'VE GOT,
AND HE NEVER GIVES UP.
MAYBE, HE JUST MIGHT.
- JUST MIGHT WHAT, SIR?
- HEH.  I WORRY TOO MUCH.
- BEAR WALKEN.
- HMM?
- IS THE TARGET
REALLY GONNA TRY
TO DESTROY MILLENNION
BY HIMSELF?
- DESTROY MILLENNION?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I DOUBT IT.
I THINK IT'S JUST
THE BOSS HE WANTS.
IN FACT,
IF THAT GUY IS BRANDON HEAT,
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- ( sighs )
WE'VE GOT DOZENS OF ORGMEN
OUT THERE SEARCHING FOR HIM NOW.
AND YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT YOU
STILL HAVEN'T FOUND THE TARGET?
- WE'RE TRYING HARD, SIR.
WE'RE SEARCHING ROUND THE CLOCK.
- SEARCHING?
ALWAYS SEARCHING.
I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF HEARING THAT WORD.
- ( gasps )
- CALM DOWN, WILL YOU?
- YES, SIR.
- HMM...
- ( shakily )
EXCUSE ME.
- ( door opens, closes )
- I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW MUCH
I'D REGRET LOSING BOB POUNDMAX.
WE REALLY COULD HAVE
USED HIS HELP.
NOW THAT HE'S GONE,
HIS PERSONAL INTELLIGENCE
NETWORK IS INACCESSIBLE.
- HE WAS ALWAYS VERY CAREFUL
IN REGARD TO SECURITY.
HE NEVER GAVE HIS CONTACTS
TO ANYONE, NOT EVEN ME.
- NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
HE WAS THE VERY BEST.
- THAT'S TRUE.
AND HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
- I KNOW.
BELIEVE ME,
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
WE WILL FIND HIM.
MILLENNION OWNS THIS CITY.
HE'S OUR ENEMY,
AND EVERYONE KNOWS IT,
SO THEY WON'T DARE
TRY TO HELP HIM.
OH, WE'LL FIND HIM, ALL RIGHT.
THEN HE'S ALL YOURS.
TEACH HIM THE WAY
I DO BUSINESS--
THE MILLENNION WAY
OF DOING BUSINESS.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I HAVE A FEW ERRANDS TO RUN.
GOOD-BYE.
I'LL RETURN TOMORROW MORNING.
MEET ME HERE.
AND PLEASE, BE CAREFUL.
- Announcer on TV: TODAY'S THIRD
RACE IS FULL OF SURPRISES.
SNAIL-GUNNER, THE 12-TO-ONE...
- SAME OLD, SAME OLD.
HOW BORING.
THIS IS NO FUN ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHEN DID EVERYTHING START GOING
DOWN THE DRAIN? WHAT WENT WRONG?
YOU GOT ME.
- ( doorbell ringing )
- HUH?
WHO THE HELL
COULD THAT BE?
AND AT THIS HOUR?
- ( doorbell continues ringing )
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
KEEP YOUR PANTS ON.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NICE WOUND YOU GOT.
YOU'RE ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF TOWN, AREN'T YOU?
LOOK, I GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE ORGANIZATION ANYMORE.
YOU GOT NO BUSINESS HERE.
GET LOST.
FOLKS FROM THE OTHER SIDE
AREN'T WELCOME HERE.
TAKE YOUR HAND OFF THE DOOR.
- I AM BRANDON.
- HUH?
- BRANDON HEAT.
- UH, DID YOU SAY BRANDON?
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE BRANDON HEAT!
FELLA, YOU GOT
A LOUSY SENSE OF HUMOR.
THAT GUY'S DEAD!
- GARY?
I KNOW HIS VOICE.
IT'S TRUE, GARY, IT'S HIM.
- WHAT?!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, BOSS?
HOW COULD HE BE?
BRANDON DIED YEARS AGO.
- MY HEARING'S GOTTEN A LOT
SHARPER SINCE I LOST MY SIGHT.
IT'S BRANDON, ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE OF IT.
I'D KNOW HIS VOICE ANYWHERE.
- UH-- ( sighs )
FOR REAL YOU'RE BRANDON HEAT?
- EXCUSE ME? DO YOU THINK WE
COULD TALK ABOUT THIS INSIDE?
IT'S A LONG STORY.
- MAN, OH, MAN!
I'VE READ SOME STRANGE STORIES,
BUT NONE OF THEM
AS WEIRD AS THIS ONE.
I KNOW MILLENNION'S GOT A BUNCH
OF THOSE CREEPAZOID FREAKS.
BUT NOW YOU TELL US
THAT BRANDON'S A MONSTER TOO?
AND TO TOP IT ALL OFF,
YOU TELL US THAT
YOU'RE BIG DADDY'S DAUGHTER?
- I'VE BEEN HEARING RUMORS
RECENTLY
ABOUT SOMETHING GOING ON
WITHIN THE ORGANIZATION,
SOMETHING THAT HAS TO DO
WITH YOU AND BRANDON, MISS.
NOW I SEE WHY.
- BRANDON, TELL ME.
WHAT WAS IT THAT
MADE YOU BETRAY MILLENNION?
- GARY, WHY EVEN BOTHER TO ASK?
YOU'VE SEEN WHAT KIND OF
ORGANIZATION IT IS NOW.
- YEAH.  USING MONSTERS
TO TAKE WHAT THEY WANT,
USING FEAR TO CONTROL
THE WHOLE CITY.
DAMN.  IT WAS NEVER THE SAME
AFTER THEY KILLED BIG DADDY.
- ( gasps )
- MY FATHER WAS--
- GARY!
- I'M SORRY.
I ASSUMED YOU MUST HAVE KNOWN
HOW HE DIED.
- MY FATHER...
MY FATHER WAS MURDERED?
- IT'S A RUMOR.
JUST A RUMOR, THAT'S ALL.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
MY MOM, MY DAD,
MR. TOKIOKA...
THEY KILLED EVERYONE.
( sobs )
OH, NO.
NO!
( crying )
- THERE SEEMS TO BE
NO SURVEILLANCE.
- I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE ALIVE.
- I THINK IT WOULD
BE MORE ACCURATE
TO SAY THAT I FAILED TO DIE.
MILLENNION MUSTN'T FIND OUT.
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
- HERE'S THE ORGMEN REFERENCE
MATERIAL YOU ASKED FOR,
AS WELL AS EVERYTHING
I COULD FIND
ON THE SUPERIORIZATION PROCESS.
- THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY TO HAVE MADE YOU
TREAD ON SUCH DANGEROUS GROUND.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IF THEY WEREN'T HOLDING
MY FAMILY HOSTAGE,
I'D BE OUT THERE WITH YOU,
FIGHTING THEM.
- ( exhales )
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
AND STAY SAFE.
HOLD ON A LITTLE WHILE LONGER
AND WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO
RESCUE YOUR FAMILY.
- DOCTOR.
- HOWEVER, I'M AFRAID,
YOU MUSTN'T COUNT ON THAT.
- ( tires screeching )
- Both: HUH?
- ( exhales )
- DOCTOR!
- ( gunfire )
- HOW LONG'S IT BEEN SINCE WE
HAD A DRINK TOGETHER LIKE THIS?
- AT LEAST 20 YEARS OR SO.
- WELL, THEN, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
IT'S A SHAME
YOU CAN'T TASTE IT.
MUST BE ROUGH LIVING IN
THE KIND OF BODY YOU GOT NOW.
- ( exhales )
- WE KNOW, BRANDON.
YOU WANT US TO PROTECT
THE YOUNG LADY,
WHILE YOU'RE GONE.
- DON'T WORRY, BRANDON.
WE COMPLETELY CUT OUR TIES
WITH THE ORGANIZATION.
YOU SEE, THE TRUTH IS
THEY FIRED US.
BETTIN' ON THE PONIES
ISN'T WHAT IT USED TO BE.
THESE DAYS, EVERYTHING'S
HANDLED BY A COMPUTER.
THEY DON'T NEED
OLD FARTS LIKE US ANYMORE.
WE'RE OBSOLETE.
- HEY, IT WAS TIME
FOR US TO LEAVE ANYWAY,
BECAUSE WE WERE LOYAL
TO THE ORGANIZATION
BIG DADDY CREATED,
THE OLD MILLENNION.
BUT THAT'S LONG GONE NOW.
EVERYTHING WE HAVE--
THIS HOME, A COMFORTABLE LIFE--
WE OWE IT ALL TO YOU,
BRANDON,
BECAUSE OF THE GOOD WORD YOU
PUT IN FOR US WITH BIG DADDY.
WE BOTH GOT PROMOTED.
AND I COULD TAKE CARE OF MOM
UNTIL SHE DIED.
- WE NEVER HAD A CHANCE
TO RETURN THE FAVOR,
SO NOW WE'D LIKE TO
PAY YOU BACK FOR WHAT YOU DID.
- AND PAY BIG DADDY BACK
AS WELL.
- MR. FORMALITY,
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
- AND STILL QUIET TOO.
- ( Gary laughs )
SO...
YOU LEAVIN' ALREADY?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA SAY
GOOD-BYE TO THE YOUNG LADY, HUH?
YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD
AT THAT, ARE YOU?
THAT'S SO LIKE YOU, BRANDON.
BUT WE CONSIDER YOU
A MEMBER OF THE FAMILY.
YOU CAN ALWAYS DEPEND ON US.
- YEAH.
- Widge's voice: BRANDON,
MILLENNION'S ON THE WRONG TRACK,
HEADED IN THE WRONG DIRECTION.
IT'S NO LONGER THE ORGANIZATION
BIG DADDY INTENDED IT TO BE.
- HARRY...
( groans )
- ( tires screeching )
- ( grunts, exhales )
- ( grunts )
- EXCUSE ME, SIR.
BUT YOU HAD SEVERAL DRINKS,
THEN SAID YOU COULDN'T PAY.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH THAT?
LAST TIME.
GET LOST, ASSHOLE!
- ( grunts )
- HEY, LISTEN UP, PAL.
YOU OUGHTA THANK ME,
CONSIDERING THE MESS YOU'RE IN.
I'M LETTING YOU OFF EASY.
I COULD SEND FOR THE GUYS
FROM MILLENNION IF I WANTED TO.
- ( chuckles )
YEAH, RIGHT.
MILLENNION-- WHAT A JOKE.
( coughs, spits )
- ( groans )
WHO THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE?!
- ( both grunting )
- ( gasps )
HEY!  THAT'S THE GUY!
CALL HEADQUARTERS.
HE'S A WANTED CRIMINAL.
- ( growling )
- WHAT THE--?
- ( shouts, grunts )
- ( gunshots )
- WHAT?  YOU MEAN THE TARGET?
- HUH?
- SO HE APPROACHED THE
POLICE VOLUNTARILY?
HE CAME TO US ON HIS OWN?
IN A CAR?
( chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
IN THAT CASE, CONTACT LOCKE
AND TELL HIM TO SEND
AN ORGMEN SQUAD TO THAT LOCATION
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
- ORGMEN?
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO TAKE
HIM OUT YOURSELF, ONE-ON-ONE.
- ONCE WE HAVE THE MAN IN
CUSTODY, I CAN DO THAT ANYTIME.
HOWEVER, DESTROYING BRANDON HEAT
ISN'T MY ONLY CONCERN.
HE'S GOT TO BE GETTING HELP
FROM COLLABORATORS
OTHER THAN TOKIOKA.
SO I NEED TO EXPOSE ALL OF THEM
AND DESTROY THEIR NETWORK,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
MY FEELINGS ABOUT THE DEATH
OF BOB POUNDMAX...
ARE VERY INTENSE,
BURNING WITHIN ME.
- HMM.
SHOW HIM THE POWER
OF MILLENNION.
- YES, SIR.
- NO, WAIT.  PLEASE.
WAIT, MISS!
YOU CAN'T GO OUTSIDE.
YOU'RE A TARGET, MISS.
THEY'LL SPOT YOU FOR SURE.
- BUT I--
- I'M AFRAID GARY'S RIGHT,
YOUNG LADY.
I WONDER IF YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW BRANDON FEELS.
- HOW HE FEELS?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- QUITE HONESTLY...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY HE'S PROTECTING ME.
I KNOW THAT HE WAS
A FRIEND OF MY MOM'S
AND THAT HE KNEW MY DAD,
BUT IS THAT ENOUGH REASON
FOR HIM TO GO THIS FAR?
- HMM?
- MY MOM AND DAD
WERE KILLED BY THE ORGANIZATION,
KILLED BY HARRY MACDOWEL.
THAT'S WHY I HATE
BLOODY HARRY SO MUCH
AND THE ORGANIZATION.
SO I KNOW WHY GRAVE
HATES HARRY MACDOWEL.
AFTER ALL, BLOODY HARRY
KILLED HIM TOO.
BUT NONE OF THAT WOULD GIVE HIM
A REASON TO PROTECT ME.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
HE'S GOT A GOOD REASON.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SURE DOES.
- THEN WHY?
- BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
MILLENNION WAS FOR.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOUNG LADY...
WHEN BIG DADDY WAS MILLENNION'S
HEAD HONCHO,
IT WAS QUITE DIFFERENT
THAN IT IS NOW.
DO YOU KNOW WHY YOUR FATHER
FOUNDED THE ORGANIZATION?
- MM-MM.
- BRANDON DIDN'T EITHER.
AND SO, I'M GOING TO TELL
YOU JUST AS I TOLD HIM
MANY YEARS AGO.
( sighs )
- Male Reporter:
THIS JUST IN...
AN EXPLOSION OF UNKNOWN
ORIGIN HAS OCCURRED
AT SOUTH GATE NUMBER ONE.
ALTERNATE ROUTES ARE...
- DON'T TELL ME...
- ( growls )
- Mika:
TO PROTECT?
- THAT'S RIGHT,
TO PROTECT--
NEIGHBORS, FRIENDS, FAMILIES.
TO PROTECT THEM,
HE NEEDED POWER.
TO HAVE THAT POWER,
HE NEEDED THE ORGANIZATION.
TO MAINTAIN IT,
HE NEEDED THE CODE OF IRON
THAT MADE BETRAYAL
PUNISHABLE BY DEATH.
BRANDON WAS ACCUSED
OF BETRAYING THE ORGANIZATION.
BUT IF HE WERE A TRAITOR,
HE WOULDN'T HAVE COME BACK
AFTER HIS DEATH.
HE COULD HAVE ONLY ONE REASON
FOR DOING THAT.
- THE CODE OF IRON.
- EXACTLY.
BRANDON HEAT
IS MILLENNION ITSELF.
EVEN AFTER HIS DEATH,
HE CONTINUES TO BE DEVOTED
TO MILLENNION.
SO NOW WE'LL PROTECT YOU,
YOUNG LADY.
- BUT I CAN'T--
I MEAN, I--
I CAN'T GIVE YOU
ANYTHING IN RETURN.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GIVE US A THING.
THAT'S WHAT BEING A FAMILY
IS ALL ABOUT.
AS LONG AS WE DON'T
BETRAY ONE ANOTHER,
WE'LL HAVE A BOND BETWEEN US
THAT CAN NEVER BE BROKEN.
- ALL OF A SUDDEN I FEEL LIKE
I HAVE TWO NEW GRANDPAS.
- HEY!  HOLD ON!
I AIN'T OLD ENOUGH
TO BE A GRANDPA.
BUT I GUESS UNCLE
WOULD BE ALL RIGHT.
- ( all laugh )
- HMM?
- HUH?
- GARY.
- ( slightly gasps )
- IT AIN'T GOOD, BOSS.
THEY'RE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
- GARY, TAKE THE YOUNG LADY
AND GO OUT THE BACK DOOR.
HURRY.
- YOU GOT IT, BOSS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
- WHAT'S UP?
- AAH!
- EXCUSE THE DRAMATIC ENTRANCE,
BUT LOCKED DOORS
ARE SO INCONVENIENT.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- I'M BALLADBIRD LEE.
THOUGH IT'S TOO LATE
TO DO YOU ANY GOOD...
ALLOW ME TO GIVE YOU
A PIECE OF ADVICE.
- HUH?
- CHOOSE THOSE YOU LEND
YOUR CAR TO MORE CAREFULLY.
IF YOU HAD, YOU MIGHT HAVE LIVED
AT LEAST A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
- THAT GUY'S ONE OF
THE BIG FOUR OF MILLENNION.
- UH-HUH.
SO YOU'RE BIG DADDY'S
LITTLE GIRL?
MY GOODNESS,
WHAT A CUTE YOUNG LADY YOU ARE.
LOOKS LIKE BIG DADDY MUST HAVE
HAD A LITTLE SOMETHING EXTRA
FOR A MAN HIS AGE, HUH?
( chuckles )
I ENVY THE GUY,
I REALLY DO.
- TELL ME, HOW IN THE WORLD
DID SOMEONE AS STUPID AS YOU
GET TO BE A SENIOR EXECUTIVE?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE A GUN
IN YOUR HAND, DO YOU?
WHAT THE--?
- ORGMEN.
- I'M A SUPERIOR.
IN ORDER TO SHOW
HOW TRULY LOYAL I AM
TO HARRY MACDOWEL
AND TO HONOR THE MEMORY
OF AN OLD FRIEND,
I ASKED TO BE GIVEN
THIS POWER.
- A SUPERIOR?
- THAT'S CORRECT.
- AAH!
( groaning )
- ( screams )
- GARY, WHAT'S WRONG?
GARY!
- ( groaning )
- GARY!
- AAH!
- ( groaning )
- ( screams )
( whimpers )
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- YOU'RE LUCKY.
VERY LUCKY, OLD MAN.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
CROSS OVER TO THE OTHER WORLD
WITHOUT SEEING THE HORRIBLE WAY
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
- ( exhales )
( grunts )
- ( screams )
- AAH!
- ( grunting )
- ( groans )
- YOU'RE IN NO CONDITION
TO PUSH YOURSELF SO HARD.
- ( radio static )
- HUH?
- Mika:
I'M SORRY, GRAVE.
- ( gasps )
- I'M SORRY...
GRAVE.
( crying )
I'M SORRY, GRAVE.
I'M SORRY...
GRAVE.
- MI-- MIKA...
( gasps )
- ( gasps )
- ( organ music playing )
- ( silently )
- ( grunts )
( whimpers )
( crying quietly )
( screaming )
- ( door opens )
- HEY.
IS THIS THE PLACE WHERE
I CAN FIND
THE COLD-BLOODED FREAK
WHO CALLS HIMSELF A SCIENTIST?
- IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU, SIR?
- OTHERWISE, I NEVER
WOULD HAVE COME TO THIS
DAMN HAUNTED HOUSE OF YOURS.
I'M HERE TO GIVE YOU
MY BODY, DOC.
- HMM?
- USE YOUR TECHNOLOGY TO MAKE
IT AS STRONG AS POSSIBLE.
- HMM.
( chuckles )
( giggles )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( man singing in Japanese )
- Brandon Heat:
A NECROLIZED MAN,
A SUPERIORIZED MAN--
NON-HUMANS FIGHT
EACH OTHER WITH EMOTION
ONLY HUMANS CAN POSSESS.
THE TWILIGHT DARKENS
FOR THOSE WHO DESTROY.