( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- ( footsteps )
- ( both laughing )
- ( breathing heavily )
( laughing )
- COME ON, HURRY UP WILL YOU!
- I'M COMING, HOLD ON!
- FIRST, LET ME THANK
ALL OF YOU.
THE ENTIRE MILLENNION FAMILY
FOR COMING TODAY
NOW, I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO TWO YOUNG MEN
WHO'VE JUST BECOME THE
NEWEST MEMBERS OF OUR FAMILY.
HARRY MACDOWEL.
AND BRANDON HEAT.
HARRY AND BRANDON HAVE JOINED US
TO CONTRIBUTE TO OUR PROSPERITY,
AS WELL AS TO DO WHATEVER
THEY CAN TO PROTECT OUR FAMILY.
PLEASE JOIN ME IN WELCOMING
THESE TWO VERY
SPECIAL YOUNG MEN.
- ( applause )
- Brandon: THE FAMILY...
MILLENNION'S UPPER
LEVEL EXECUTIVES
AND THOSE ACKNOWLEDGED
BY BIG DADDY
AS MEMBERS OF THE
ORGANIZATION'S INNER CIRCLE.
ALL UNITED BY
THE CODE OF IRON.
THERE IS ONLY ONE PROMISE
WE MUST MAKE,
NEVER BETRAY THE FAMILY
NEVER EVER BETRAY THE FAMILY.
- Harry: YOU MUST BE
MR. GALARDE.
I'M HARRY MACDOWEL SIR.
- MY NAME IS BRANDON HEAT.
- I'VE HEARD GOOD THINGS
ABOUT YOU TWO. KEEP IT UP GUYS.
- Brandon: YES, SIR.
- Harry: THANK YOU SIR.
- Bear: SID!
- HUH?
- IS THAT...
BEAR, BEAR WALKEN!
- SID GALARDE!
- ( both laughing )
- YOU LOOK A LOT OLDER
THAN THE LAST TIME WE MET
YOU'VE GOT SO MANY NEW WRINKLES
I BARELY RECOGNIZED YOU.
- THE SAME GOES FOR YOU!
- Sherry: HI UNCLE SID,
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU,
- SHERRY! YOU GOT SO BIG!
GUESS WE HAVE GOTTEN OLD.
- YES INDEED.
- I'D LIKE MY SON TO
JOIN THE FAMILY TOO
BUT HE GETS INTO TROUBLE
ALL THE TIME.
I WISH HE WERE A LOT MORE
LIKE THESE TWO YOUNG MEN.
- HAVE YOU TWO
INTRODUCED YOURSELVES?
- YES, SIR. WE HAVE.
- EXCUSE ME FATHER,
I HAVEN'T BEEN INTRODUCED YET.
- YES DEAR, YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER.
- HOW DO YOU DO?
MY NAME'S SHERRY WALKEN.
- WELL HELLO THERE,
I'M A NEW MEMBER OF THE FAMILY.
I'M HARRY MACDOWEL.
- I'M BRANDON HEAT.
- OH!
- SOMETHING WRONG?
WELL, UM...
THERE ARE SOME
DELICIOUS LOOKING DESSERTS
ON THAT TABLE OVER THERE.
IF YOU'D LIKE
WE COULD TASTE THEM TOGETHER.
- I'D LOVE TO.
- LOOKS LIKE YOUR PARTNER
IS A REAL LADIES MAN.
- LET HARRY KNOW,
THAT IF HE FOOLS WITH MY
DAUGHTER IN ANY WAY WHATSOEVER
I'LL KILL HIM, UNDERSTAND?
- I'LL TELL HIM SIR.
- A PROTECTIVE FATHER.
- OH BEAR, SO THERE
YOU ARE,
I'M GLAD YOU COULD
JOIN US TODAY.
- SORRY I CAME SO LATE.
I APOLOGIZE SIR. THERE WAS A
MINOR TERRITORIAL DISPUTE,
BUT IT'S SETTLED NOW.
- COME NOW,
I KNOW HOW BUSY YOU ARE.
THERE'S NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
- THANK YOU SIR.
- WELL, SID.
I SEE YOU'VE ALREADY
MET MY NEW SON.
PLEASE TAKE GOOD
CARE OF HIM FOR ME.
- I CERTAINLY WILL,
BIG DADDY.
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT THOSE YOUNGSTERS
ARE ALREADY MEMBERS
OF THE FAMILY.
BIG DADDY'S BEEN
IN CONTROL OF MILLENNION
SINCE HE FOUNDED
IT 30 YEARS AGO.
DOES HE HAVE A
SUCCESSOR IN MIND?
- NOT YET, HE'S STILL YOUNG.
IT'S GONNA BE A WHILE.
- YEAH, BUT THE BOSS
DOESN'T HAVE ANY CHILDREN.
SO SINCE HE HAS NO NATURAL
HEIR, HE SHOULD DECIDE
WHO IT'S GOING TO BE.
- I KNOW OF VERY FEW MEN
WHO WOULD BE ABLE
TO TAKE HIS PLACE.
- WELL, WHAT ABOUT YOU BEAR?
- NOT ME.
HMM.
- ( door closing )
WHAT'S UP?
TWO MEN WERE ROBBED AND KILLED.
IT HAPPENED IN MY TERRITORY.
THE MONEY'S NO BIG DEAL BUT
ONE WAS A GUEST FROM ALGERIA.
- HMM.
- THE KILLER WILL HAVE TO BE
DEALT WITH AT ONCE.
OR THE ORGANIZATION
WILL LOSE FACE.
WHICH WILL MAKE BIG DADDY'S
JOB EVEN MORE DIFFICULT.
- WELL, I GUESS IN THIS
BUSINESS THERE'S ALWAYS
GONNA BE SOME
KIND OF TROUBLE
BUT IT HAS TO BE DEALT WITH.
- THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
- ( laughing ) YES,
EXACTLY RIGHT.
- ( man groaning )
- Balladbird: SO, HOW WAS YOUR
DEBUT AT THE FAMILY PARTY?
- BIT NERVE-WRACKING
EVEN FOR ME.
- IF YOU ASK ME,
IT'S NOT FAIR YOU
AND BRANDON JOINING THE
FAMILY WITHOUT US.
- YOU'LL GET IN.
JUST GIVE ME SOME TIME.
ONCE I'VE GOT A LITTLE MORE
CLOUT IN THE FAMILY,
I CAN RECOMMEND YOU
GUYS TO MY BOSS.
WERE COUNTING ON YOU HARRY.
- OF COURSE. 'CAUSE
I'M NOT STOPPING
TILL I GET WHERE
I WANNA GO.
THIS IS THE LIST
OF EVERYONE IN THE FAMILY, BOB.
FIND OUT EVERYTHING YOU CAN
ABOUT THEM, BUT DO IT SECRETLY.
- Bob: I GOT YOU, HARRY.
- THEY CLAIM TO BELIEVE
IN THE CODE OF IRON
BUT IT'S A BIG FAMILY.
I'M SURE THERE ARE
SKELETONS HIDDEN SOMEWHERE.
- WOW, YOU'RE KIND OF SCARY.
- I GOTTA FIND OUT
IF ANY OF THEM ARE TRAITORS
FOR THE SAKE OF THE FAMILY.
AND FOR MY SAKE AS WELL.
- AH!
( sighing )
- Brandon: HOW'S IT GOING?
- OH, HEY BRO.
THANKS A LOT.
MAN, ARE YOU QUIET.
- I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
YOU'D COME IN.
- SO SEEN THE TARGET?
- NOT YET.
THE CURTAINS ARE CLOSED,
AND THE LIGHTS ARE TURNED OFF.
- HE'S THERE.
- HUH?
- I'LL GO CHECK IT OUT.
- IS THIS GUY A MONSTER OR WHAT?
- Brandon: IT'S TAKEN CARE OF.
- I SEE, GOOD WORK YOU TWO.
I'LL CONTACT YOU
SHORTLY. LOOKS LIKE
I'LL NEED ANOTHER FAVOR.
- ANYTIME SIR.
- Bunji: EXCUSE US.
- HEY, I'M SORRY.
RELAX, I WAS JUST TESTING YOU.
- THEY BEAT YOU SID.
- DID YOU TRAIN THEM?
- YEAH.
- NO WONDER. LOOKS LIKE
BRANDON HERE TURNED OUT
TO BE ONE HELL OF A GOOD STUDENT
- HIS FRIEND HERE DID TOO.
- BUNJI KUGASHIRA SIR.
- I'LL REMEMBER THAT.
COME ON HAVE A DRINK WITH US.
YOU DO LIKE TO DRINK,
- DON'T YOU?
- SURE.
- ( Sid laughing )
- BEAR AND I HAD JUST
JOINED THE MAFIA
WE WERE FIGHTING EACH OTHER
TOOTH AND NAIL TRYING
TO GRAB MORE TERRITORY.
AND NEITHER ONE OF US
WOULD GIVE AN INCH
SO STUPID AND STUBBORN,
WE ALMOST SHOT EACH OTHER.
AND WE PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
IF BIG DADDY HADN'T SHOWN UP
AND OFFERED TO
MEDIATE OUR DISPUTE.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH
THE WAY I SEE IT
IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR BIG DADDY,
ONE OF US WOULD HAVE ENDED
UP IN THE NEXT WORLD FOR SURE.
- ONE OF US, MEANING YOU!
- IS THAT SO?
( laughing ) NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IN THOSE DAYS YOU
WERE STRONG AS
A DEVIL AND TWICE AS ARMORY.
- BUT YOU WERE
A LOT MORE POPULAR.
- YEAH RIGHT, ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
EVERYONE LIKES SID GALARDE.
COME ON, HAVE ANOTHER DRINK.
- THANK YOU, I HAVE ONE, SIR.
- LOTS MORE WHERE THAT
CAME FROM, RIGHT?
- Bunji: HEY BRO...
TELL ME, ARE THOSE GUYS
WHAT YOU CALL FAMILY?
YOU SEE, I'M AN ORPHAN.
SO I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT A FAMILY IS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- NEITHER DO I.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'RE NOT THE TYPE
TO GET THIS DRUNK.
WHAT'S UP SID?
- I SUPPOSE I JUST
GOT CARRIED AWAY,
REMEMBERING HOW
THINGS USED TO BE.
- YOU'RE GETTING OLD, SID.
- OH YEAH? LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
HEY, BEAR...
GREAT BEING YOUNG
LIKE THOSE TWO ARE.
JUST STARTING UP THE LADDER AND
LOOKING FORWARD TO THE FUTURE.
- BUT YOUNGSTERS DO
STUPID THINGS SOMETIMES.
- YEAH, THEY DO. DON'T THEY?
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT...
- IT'S HARRY MACDOWEL.
DO YOU KNOW IF BIG
DADDY READ THE MATERIAL
I SENT IN THE OTHER DAY?
I UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, IT WAS PRETTY UNSETTLING.
BUT I KNEW I HAD TO SEND IT
IN ORDER TO PROTECT THE FAMILY.
YES, SIR. WHEN YOU
SEE BIG DADDY,
WOULD YOU PLEASE
GIVE HIM MY BEST?
RIGHT, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- Sherry: SORRY TO
KEEP YOU WAITING.
- THAT'S OKAY,
I JUST GOT HERE MYSELF.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL DRESS,
YOU LOOK GREAT!
- THANK YOU, MR. MACDOWEL.
- PLEASE, CALL ME HARRY.
- ( gasping ) OH!
- PRETTY SWEET!
- ( phone ringing )
- HELLO?
IT'S FOR YOU.
- THIS IS BRANDON.
- WHAT A STUPID THING TO DO.
BRAT!
IDIOT...
- HUH?
- Sid: WHERE'S EDDIE?
- WHAT'S GOING ON OLD MAN?
- ( groaning in pain )
- I ASKED YOU WHERE EDDIE IS,
NOW ANSWER ME.
- HE'S IN THE BACK, SIR!
- ( door opening )
- HUH, OH, HI!
WHAT'S UP DAD?
HEY WAIT TILL YOU HEAR THIS.
I GOT A TIP THAT ALGERIA
PULLED UP A BIG HEIST
AND EVERYTHING THEY
GOT IS OURS NOW.
( groaning in pain )
- YOU STUPID IDIOT!
- HUH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THIS JOB CAME OFF
WITHOUT A HITCH.
AND ALL WITNESSES ARE DEAD,
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING ME.
( groaning in pain )
- YOU ACTED WITHOUT PERMISSION!
- I'M NOT ALLOWED TO DO
ANYTHING ON MY OWN.
WELL THAT'S GONNA CHANGE
STARTING NOW.
- YOU THINK I'D LET A
SCUMBAG LIKE YOU DECIDE
HOW TO RUN THE BUSINESS?
ONE OF THOSE MEN YOU KILLED,
WAS BEAR WALKEN'S GUEST,
YOU NITWIT.
- HUH! UNCLE BEAR'S?
HOLY SHIT! IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
HOW WAS I SUPPOSE TO KNOW
WHO HE WAS?
- WHETHER YOU KNEW
WHO HE WAS OR NOT,
DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT YOU KILLED A GUY!
THE ORGANIZATION WILL LOSE
FACE AND BE DISGRACED
BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
- ( crying )
HELP ME. OH PLEASE HELP ME,
I DON'T WANNA DIE.
PLEASE DAD, PLEASE,
PLEASE I'M BEGGING YOU.
HELP ME...
HELP ME DAD! PLEASE!
HELP ME, DAD! HELP ME!
( crying )
- THAT STUPID IDIOT!
- UNCLE ASAGI.
- FOR GOODNESS SAKE,
DRINKING AT THIS HOUR?
IT'S A LITTLE EARLY ISN'T IT?
WHAT IS IT UNCLE?
- AS A LEADER I'M RESPONSIBLE
FOR MAKING A LOT OF DECISIONS.
DECISIONS WHICH ARE
SOMETIMES VERY DIFFICULT.
SOMETIMES I'M FORCED
TO MAKE CHOICES
THAT IN MY HEART,
I FEEL ARE WRONG.
I'VE HAD TO MAKE
DECISIONS LIKE THAT
EVER SINCE I WAS A YOUNG MAN.
BUT I STILL HAVEN'T
GOTTEN USED TO IT.
SID...
SID GALARDE...
- YOU MIND, IF I SIT DOWN?
- HAVE A SEAT.
HMM.
- Sid: HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND ME?
- THIS IS THE TERRITORY
YOU AND I USED TO FIGHT OVER.
- Sid: YOU THINK WE
RISKED OUR LIVES FIGHTING
FOR A WORTHLESS PLACE LIKE THIS?
- Bear: YEAH.
WE WERE PRETTY DUMB.
- ( Both laughing )
- SO HOW LONG HAVE
YOU KNOWN BEAR?
- SINCE THAT NIGHT
WHEN YOU SAID YOU
DIDN'T WANNA GO HOME
AND FELL ASLEEP ON MY COUCH.
THAT WASN'T LIKE YOU, SID.
IT SURE AS HELL WASN'T LIKE
THE SID GALARDE I KNOW.
- HMM, I SEE...
- IT JUST WASN'T LIKE YOU.
- Sherry: YOU MEAN UNCLE SID?
- YEAH, HE AND YOUR FATHER
SEEM TO BE VERY GOOD FRIENDS.
- YES THEY ARE.
THEY'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A REAL LONG TIME,
SINCE BEFORE I WAS BORN.
- I SEE. SO THEY'RE
REALLY CLOSE THEN.
- YEAH, SURE.
I ONCE ASKED MY DAD
WHO HIS BEST FRIEND WAS
AND HE SAID IT WAS UNCLE SID.
- HE'S LIKE FAMILY TO ME.
- IS THAT SO...
- I THINK YOUR DAD'S
A REALLY GENTLE HEARTED MAN.
- AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
OH MAN, BREAKS YOUR HEART.
- BEAR, I'M HOPELESSLY DUMB.
EVEN DUMBER THAN I USED TO BE.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID THAT LOYALTY
TO THE ORGANIZATION
WAS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANYTHING.
WHEN I HAD A
CHANCE TO PROVE IT,
I CHOSE MY SCUMBAG
OF A SON INSTEAD.
- Sid: TAKE IT AND
GET OUT OF TOWN!
- BUT DAD!
- DON'T EVER COME BACK AGAIN.
ANYONE FROM THE ORGANIZATION
WHO SEES YOU WILL KILL YOU.
EVEN IF IT'S ME! I'LL KILL YOU!
FOR THE ORGANIZATION.
- BUT DAD...
- GET THE HELL OUT! RIGHT NOW!
- ( crying ) WHERE WILL I GO?
- NOW, GET GOING!
- IF WE SAY THE KILLER ESCAPED
THEY'LL QUESTION OUR INTEGRITY
OUR REPUTATION WILL
SUFFER IRREPARABLE DAMAGE
WHAT HAPPENS IN MY TERRITORY
INCLUDING MISCONDUCT,
IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
AS A MEMBER OF THE ORGANIZATION
AND AS A FATHER,
I ACCEPT THAT RESPONSIBILITY.
SORRY IF YOU
FIND THIS BOTHERSOME.
- I CERTAINLY DO.
- ( Sid crying )
EDDIE!
- Brandon: THE CODE OF IRON...
I WANTED TO SEE MARIA.
OH, HOW I LONGED TO SEE HER...
BUT HOW COULD I?
I WAS NO LONGER WORTHY.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: THE MAN
APPEARED SUDDENLY,
BLOCKING BRANDON'S PATH.
THE MAN STOOD IN FRONT OF
MILLENNION, BARRING HIS WAY.
THE MAN IS BLOOD WAR.
A MAN WHO SUMMONS
BLOODY WARFARE.