( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Maria: I HAVEN'T SEEN
HIM FOR THREE YEARS.
- Man 1: DID YOU
SAY BRANDON HEAT?
- Man 2: YEAH. THE PARTNER OF
THAT INFAMOUS HARRY MACDOWEL.
HE'S A DANGEROUS MAN.
- Man 1: INDEED HE IS,
FROM WHAT I HAVE HEARD
HIS TRUE GRAVE UNIT IS
EVEN MORE EFFICIENT
THAN BEAR WALKEN'S OVERKILLS.
- Man 2: HE'S QUIET,
HONEST, AND HIGHLY SKILLED.
THERE'S NO WAY BIG
DADDY WOULD LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- TAKE A LOOK, HERE COMES
THE YOUNG MAN NOW.
- SO, THAT'S HIM...
- BETTER LATE,
THAN NEVER BRANDON.
- MY APOLOGIES.
GENTLEMEN I'M BRANDON HEAT
OF MILLENNION.
- YOU'VE BEEN INVITED HERE TODAY
BECAUSE THERE IS SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
EACH OF YOU OWNS HOTELS
IN THE EAST DISTRICT.
WE'D LIKE YOU TO TRANSFER THE
OWNERSHIP OF THOSE HOTELS TO US
INCLUDING OF COURSE THE
CASINOS INSIDE THE HOTELS.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- HOW MUCH YOU
OFFERING PER HOTEL?
- HOW DOES ONE
MILLION YULE SOUND?
- LIKE A JOKE!
IT'S NOT NEARLY ENOUGH!
- IT'S OUT OF THE QUESTION!
- THIS ENTIRE DISCUSSION
IS TOTALLY UNNECESSARY
- BOB, WHAT'S THEIR
CURRENT STATUS?
- THE LATEST
INFORMATION INDICATES,
THAT RIGHT NOW, 40 PERCENT
OF THE HOTELS IN THE EAST
DISTRICT ARE IN THE RED.
IF THIS IS ALLOWED
TO CONTINUE,
IT WILL BECOME A
FINANCIAL DISASTER.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT? THE PROBLEMS
WE ARE HAVING STARTED
LESS THAN A YEAR AGO.
- AND THEN FOR NO APPARENT
REASON WE COULDN'T
MAKE ANY MONEY.
- WHICH YOU COULD
HAVE ARRANGED
IN ORDER TO HELP
US ACCEPT YOU...
- ( gunshot )
- Harry: PLEASE LISTEN TO WHAT I
HAVE TO SAY, I HAVE A PROPOSAL.
IN ORDER TO ENSURE YOUR
FINANCIAL STABILITY,
WE'RE OFFERING TO LEND YOU
THE FUNDING AND SECURITY
THAT ONLY THE MILLENION
ORGANIZATION CAN PROVIDE.
- WHY DID YOU CUT A DEAL
WITH THOSE GUYS, WHEN YOU
COULD HAVE JUST
KILLED THEM, HARRY?
- WELL, THE DEAD ARE
NOTORIOUSLY UNPRODUCTIVE.
ALIVE, THEY MAY PROVE
A BIT MORE USEFUL.
- YOU NEVER CEASE TO
AMAZE ME, HARRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW EASY IT WAS
FOR YOU TO GET THEM TO AGREE.
- IT WAS BRANDON.
HE HAS BECOME THE SYMBOL
OF MILLENNION'S POWER.
HE'S MAINTAINING THE
ORGANIZATION'S IMAGE
FROM THE FOUNDATION UP.
- WHICH MAKES YOUR
JOB A LOT EASIER.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WITH THE CASINO OWNERS
OUT OF THE WAY,
WE'VE NEUTRALIZED
OVER 80 PERCENT
OF THE FORCES WHICH
OPPOSE THIS ORGANIZATION.
JUST A FEW MORE.
A FEW MORE TO GO.
- BUT LATELY, I WONDER IF
WHAT WE'VE BEEN DOING
HASN'T BEEN A LITTLE
TOO HEAVY-HANDED.
- REALLY?
- ACCORDING TO BOB'S
INFORMATION,
RANDY'S HENCHMEN SEEM TO HAVE
BEEN SNOOPING AROUND,
INVESTIGATING YOUR ACTIVITIES.
- Harry: OH? WELL DONE, BOB.
- WHAT DO YOU PLAN
TO DO ABOUT IT?
- THROUGHOUT HISTORY,
THE TRANSITION OF POWER
FROM ONE GENERATION
TO ANOTHER HAS ALWAYS BEEN
A LITTLE CHAOTIC AND DISORDERLY.
- JUST LET ME KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- HERE'S HOW IT'S GONNA WORK.
BRANDON IN PLAIN SIGHT.
YOU, WORKING FROM
BEHIND THE SCENES.
- HARRY, IT'S ABOUT
THAT TIME, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF I'M LATE AGAIN I'LL HAVE
TO LISTEN TO SHERRY WHINE
ABOUT IT ALL NIGHT.
- YEAH, YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO MAKE AN ENEMY
OUT OF BEAR WALKEN,
WOULD YOU, HARRY?
- WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'VE LOVED HER FROM
THE FIRST DAY I SAW HER.
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
- SO, HOW DID IT
ALL GO, BOSS MAN?
- HARRY WAS BRILLIANT, BUNJI.
- I'M SURE, HE WAS.
- A BONUS FOR OUR GUYS.
THEY EARNED IT.
- YOU KNOW, WE CAN'T SPEND
ALL THAT IN ONE NIGHT, BIG GUY.
- TELL SPENCER TO STAY HERE.
HIS TIMING'S A LITTLE OFF.
- ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER
YOU SAY, BRO.
- Harry: BRANDON, I THINK IT'S
TIME FOR THE TWO OF YOU
TO BE FORMALLY INTRODUCED.
I BELIEVE YOU ALREADY KNOW HER.
THIS IS SHERRY WALKEN.
WE'RE GONNA BE SEEING
A WHOLE LOT OF EACH OTHER.
- I SEE...
- MY PLAN IS TO MARRY HER,
IF SHE'LL HAVE ME, OF COURSE.
- CONGRATULATIONS, HARRY.
CONGRATULATIONS, SHERRY.
- THANK YOU, VERY MUCH.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU SEEING ANYONE?
DON'T YOU HAVE SOMEONE
SPECIAL IN YOUR LIFE?
- AFRAID NOT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OF COURSE HE DOES, SHERRY.
A VERY SPECIAL SOMEONE.
- OH, SURE YOU DO.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
OF COURSE YOU'VE GOT SOMEONE.
I'D BE SURPRISED IF YOU DIDN'T.
- Big Daddy: BRANDON,
WE MISSED YOU
AT MARIA'S BIRTHDAY
PARTY LAST MONTH.
WE WERE EXPECTING
TO SEE YOU THERE.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU COME?
- I HAD TO WORK.
- SHE'S REALLY QUITE
FOND OF THE DRESS
YOU GAVE HER AS A BIRTHDAY GIFT.
IT'S THE SAME BRAND SHE'S
TAKEN A LIKING TOO, LATELY.
- I ASKED YOUR BUTLER
WHAT KIND SHE LIKED.
- AH, YES, I SEE...
- YES, SIR.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO AND SEE HER?
I KNOW THAT SHE IS VERY
CONCERNED ABOUT YOU.
- IS THAT A REQUEST, OR
IS IT AN ORDER FROM
THE BOSS OF THE ORGANIZATION?
- IF YOU KEEP THINKING THAT
WAY, YOUR GONNA WIND UP
SPENDING THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
AS A LONELY BACHELOR,
LIKE I HAVE.
- DO YOU REGRET IT?
- WELL, I'M BEGINNING TO.
IN THAT REGARD, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO FOLLOWING IN MY FOOTSTEPS.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL
ABOUT YOU, BRANDON.
- Man 1: HERE'S TO BRANDON!
- Man 2: HERE'S TO TRUE GRAVE!
- All: CHEERS!
- BUNJI! SORRY TO
BOTHER YOU, SIR.
- WELL?
- THE NEXT TIME YOU SEE THE
BIG MAN, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD TELL HIM,
"THANKS A LOT."
- THANKS FOR WHAT?
- I FOUND OUT
THAT HE PAID OFF
ALL MY MOM'S MEDICAL EXPENSES.
AND HE DID IT WITHOUT
EVEN TELLING ME.
SHE'S BEEN IN THE HOSPITAL
FOR OVER A MONTH.
I NEVER MENTIONED IT TO HIM.
- THANK HIM YOURSELF.
- ME? I'M JUST AN INTERN.
I CAN'T JUST WALK UP AND
TALK TO BRANDON HEAT.
I'M TOTALLY IN AWE OF THE GUY.
- SO YOU CAN'T TALK TO HIM?
BUT YOU GOT NO PROBLEM
TALKING TO ME, RIGHT?
- ( groaning )
THERE'S ONE THING
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND...
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHY
A GUY LIKE BRANDON
WOULD JOIN THE MAFIA
TO BEGIN WITH.
IT MAKES SENSE FOR GUYS
LIKE THE ONES OVER THERE.
THEY WANT MONEY.
THEY WANNA MAKE IT BIG.
THEY WANT BEAUTIFUL WOMEN.
THEY LIKE GETTING ROWDY
WITH THEIR BUDDIES.
I'M SURE THERE'S LOTS
OF OTHER REASONS,
BUT THEY ALL PRETTY MUCH
WANT THE SAME THING.
BUT BRANDON'S NOT
THAT KIND OF GUY,
HE'S DIFFERENT SOMEHOW.
- WANNA KNOW WHY?
- YEAH.
- THE ARMOR AROUND HIS HEART.
SOLID STEEL ARMOR SO STRONG THAT
NO ONE WILL EVER GET INSIDE.
- Man: EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THERE'S A CALL FROM
HEADQUARTERS ABOUT A JOB.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL TAKE IT.
- THANK YOU, HARRY.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN, TONIGHT.
- WELL, NEXT TIME WE'LL
HAVE EVEN MORE FUN.
TILL BREAKFAST TIME...
- NOW I'M BLUSHING.
- GOOD NIGHT, SHERRY.
- SHERRY...
- DADDY!
BUT DADDY, HOW COME? GIVE
ME ONE GOOD REASON WHY
I SHOULDN'T GO OUT WITH HARRY.
- HARRY MACDOWEL IS
A BONAFIDE MEMBER OF THE MAFIA.
THAT MAN IS
SURROUNDED BY DANGER.
WHICH MEANS THAT THOSE
WHO ARE CLOSE TO HIM,
ARE IN DANGER AS WELL.
- THEN I'M IN DANGER RIGHT NOW!
BECAUSE YOUR THE BIGGEST
MAFIOSO OF THEM ALL.
- DO YOU WANT TO END UP
LIKE YOUR MOTHER?
I CAN'T ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN.
NOT TO YOU.
- DADDY, I'M THE DAUGHTER
OF A GANGSTER.
I'VE BEEN PREPARING FOR
THIS MOMENT ALL MY LIFE.
I'M PREPARED TO DIE
FOR HARRY, IF I HAVE TO.
IN THE SAME WAY THAT YOUR
PREPARED TO DIE, FOR BIG DADDY.
- WHAT A STUBBORN YOUNG LADY.
- WELL, LIKE FATHER
LIKE DAUGHTER.
- RUNS IN THE FAMILY, I GUESS.
- I'LL PREVAIL IN THE END,
I KNOW IT.
MY LOVE WILL PREVAIL.
YOU'LL SEE.
- KIDNAPPING A POLITICIAN'S
DAUGHTER IS SO EASY.
AND YOU BLEW IT COMPLETELY,
YOU MORON. WHAT A PUNK.
SO, NOW I HAVE TO WASTE
MY TIME DOING THIS.
- ( Man ) THERE'S ONE THING,
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND...
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHY
A GUY LIKE BRANDON
WOULD JOIN THE MAFIA
TO BEGIN WITH.
- ( car engine starting )
- ( car crashing )
- ( exclaims )
- I MUST BE GETTING SENILE...
TO LET MYSELF BE CAUGHT
OFFGUARD BY A PUNK LIKE YOU.
- W-WAIT!
P-PLEASE! DON'T KILL ME!
PLEASE! I'M BEGGING YOU!
DON'T KILL ME!
( sobbing ) PLEASE DON'T KILL
ME... PLEASE DON'T KILL ME...
- YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF
YOURSELF, BUNJI KUGASHIRA.
- WHY DID YOU DO
THIS ON YOUR OWN?
ANSWER ME, BUNJI!
- IT WAS AN INSIGNIFICANT JOB.
- HE WAS JUST TRYING NOT
TO BOTHER YOU ABOUT IT, BRANDON.
I'M SURE HE WON'T
EVER DO IT AGAIN.
- ( groans )
- GO SEE THE DOCTOR.
- NAH, IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
- THAT'S AN ORDER.
- JUST GO. ALL RIGHT, BUNJI?
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO.
- LOOK BRANDON, YOU
HAVE TO MAKE HIM UNDERSTAND.
THAT WHAT HAPPENED
TONIGHT, IS PRECISELY WHY
WE DON'T HIM TO ACT ON HIS OWN.
TELL HIM THAT YOU'RE
WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
THAT YOUR HIS FRIEND.
- HE'S GOT A LOT OF PRIDE.
BUNJI KUGASHIRA
IS A TRUE MAN.
- I WAS TOLD THAT
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
- YES, MARIA.
- WHAT IS IT ABOUT, UNCLE?
- WELL, NO REAL REASON
IN PARTICULAR...
- WHY DON'T YOU HAVE A SEAT,
AND WE'LL TALK ALL RIGHT?
- SURE.
- THERE'S A YOUNG MAN, A
CHILDHOOD FRIEND OF YOURS,
WHO UP UNTIL ABOUT
THREE YEARS AGO,
USED TO COME HERE TO VISIT YOU.
- YOU MEAN BRANDON?
- THAT'S RIGHT. BRANDON.
BRANDON HEAT...
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO, I PUT
HIM AND HIS FRIEND IN CHARGE
OF ONE OF MY COMPANIES,
AND AS A RESULT,
THAT COMPANY HAS BEEN
DOING INCREDIBLY WELL LATELY.
- BRANDON AND HARRY?
- RIGHT. WELL, IT SEEMS
TO ME, THAT THEY BOTH
HAVE BRIGHT FUTURES.
AND SINCE THEY'RE NOT
STRANGERS TO ME, AND HAVE
SHOWN SO MUCH PROGRESS
I WAS WONDERING, WHAT
WOULD YOU THINK
OF MY ASKING THEM TO
BECOME MY PARTNERS?
TO HELP ME RUN MY COMPANY
AND TO EVENTUALLY SUCCEED ME.
NATURALLY, ONLY THEY
CAN DECIDE WHETHER
OR NOT TO ACCEPT MY OFFER.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT...
MARIA, I'D LIKE TO
KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT WHAT I'M
PLANNING TO DO.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK, MARIA?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- SO, BRANDON WILL
TAKE OVER THE ORGANIZATION...
- THE ORGANIZATION?
WHAT IN THE WORLD DO YOU MEAN?
- THANKS FOR YOUR SENSITIVITY,
UNCLE. BUT I ALREADY KNOW.
I KNOW WHAT YOU DO,
UNCLE. AND I KNOW
WHAT UNCLE JESTER
USED TO DO TOO.
I ALSO KNOW WHAT BRANDON AND
HARRY ARE DOING NOW.
- I SEE...
SO, YOU'VE KNOWN ALL ALONG.
- I FIGURED IT OUT
FOUR YEARS AGO.
IN ORDER TO VERIFY IT, I
DID SOME INVESTIGATING
ON MY OWN. OF YOU
AND A FEW OTHERS.
I'M SORRY.
- NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
MY REASON FOR HIDING
THE TRUTH FROM YOU...
- I KNOW THAT, TOO.
UNCLE JESTER DIDN'T WANT
ME TO BE INVOLVED.
HE WANTED ME TO LEAD
A NORMAL LIFE.
THAT'S WHY YOU TRIED TO RAISE ME
AS IF I WERE AN
ORDINARY GIRL.
LEADING AN ORDINARY LIFE.
FOR WHICH I'M GRATEFUL.
THANK YOU, UNCLE...
AFTER UNCLE JESTER
PASSED AWAY,
YOU OFFERED TO TAKE ME IN,
ABOUT SIX MONTHS LATER
BRANDON DROPPED BY TO SEE ME.
I REMEMBERED THAT FIRST TIME
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
I WAS SO HAPPY.
HAPPIER THAN I'D
EVER BEEN BEFORE.
BUT BY THEN, BRANDON HAD
ALREADY JOINED THE ORGANIZATION.
AT THE TIME, I HAD NO IDEA...
- IT WAS BECAUSE OF HIS FRIEND
HARRY, AND BECAUSE OF YOU,
I IMAGINE
THAT HE DECIDED TO JOIN
THE ORGANIZATION.
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING THAT
MATTERED TO HIM,
WAS HAVING ENOUGH POWER
TO PROTECT THE ONES HE LOVED.
EVEN IF HE HAD TO SACRIFICE
HIS OWN HUMANITY.
ONCE I GOT TO KNOW HIM,
I TOOK HIM UNDER MY WING.
WELL, DO YOU RESENT
ME FOR DOING IT?
- THAT'S JUST THE WAY HE IS.
HE NEVER GIVES UP OR GIVES IN.
HE'S DETERMINED
TO REACH
WHATEVER GOAL HE
SETS FOR HIMSELF
AND NEVER STOPS TRYING,
NO MATTER WHAT.
AS FOR HIS NOT COMING TO SEE ME
FOR THE PAST THREE YEARS, WELL,
I'M SURE HE HAS A GOOD REASON.
- PURE AWKWARDNESS.
HE THINKS BECAUSE HE
ABANDONED HIS HUMANITY,
HE CAN'T MAKE YOU HAPPY.
YET YOUR HAPPINESS MEANS
INFINITELY MORE TO HIM
THAN HIS OWN.
BECAUSE BRANDON
IS THAT KIND OF MAN.
AND BECAUSE HE LOVES YOU.
- ( crying )
BRANDON...
- MARIA, I'M SO VERY SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO CAUSE YOU
ALL THIS PAIN AND SORROW.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING WITHIN MY POWER,
I'LL ORDER HIM TO COME SEE YOU,
IF YOU ASK ME TOO.
- NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT...
IF HE WANTS ME TO BE HAPPY,
THEN I WILL BE, FOR HIS SAKE.
SO I WILL BE HAPPY.
I'LL MAKE MYSELF BE HAPPY.
FOR HIM. FOR HIS HAPPINESS.
FOR HIM...
- BIG MAN,
WE'VE JUST GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
THERE'S A TRAITOR
IN THE ORGANIZATION!
TRUE GRAVE HAS BEEN
GIVEN SOLE AUTHORITY
TO DEAL WITH THE SITUATION.
- RIGHT, LET'S GO.
- ( footsteps )
- ( rattling )
- HMM?
- Harry: DR. TOKIOKA.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- SO. IT'S YOU.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I WAS JUST REMEMBERING
OUR CONVERSATION,
THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU,
HARRY MACDOWEL.
WHAT? CONTINUE OUR
NECROLYZATION RESEARCH?
- Harry: THAT'S RIGHT.
I'LL SUPPLY ALL THE FUNDS
YOU NEED FOR YOUR RESEARCH.
AND I'LL GUARANTEE YOUR SAFETY,
AS WELL.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU'VE ALREADY WITNESSED
THE POWER OF NECROLYZATION!
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHAT YOU'VE SEEN
WITH YOUR OWN EYES?
IT'S EVIL.
IT'S THE TECHNOLOGY
OF THE SATAN!
- YOU KNEW THAT SOME TIME AGO.
BUT YOU DIDN'T LET IT STOP YOU
FROM CONTINUING YOUR RESEARCH,
DID YOU?
IF YOU HAD ANY REAL DEDICATION
TO MORALITY, DECENCY OR JUSTICE,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE CONTINUED
WITH YOUR SO CALLED
SATANIC RESEARCH,
EVEN WHEN YOU WERE BEING
THREATENED BY LIGHTNING.
BUT YOUR RESEARCH DIDN'T STOP.
YOU KEPT ON TRYING TO
CORRECT YOUR MISTAKES.
BECAUSE YOU WERE
ENSNARED IN THE TRAP
OF SCIENTIFIC AMBITION
AND COULDN'T ESCAPE.
- STILL, THE RESULTS
OF MY RESEARCH
MUST BE SEALED FOREVER.
- OH, WONDERFUL. I THOUGHT
YOU DIDN'T HAVE A
MORAL BONE IN
YOUR BODY, DOCTOR.
SO IMAGINE HOW SURPRISED
I AM BY YOUR DECISION
TO DIE HERE AND NOW,
WITHOUT LEAVING ANY PROOF
WHATSOEVER OF YOUR
SCIENTIFIC GENIUS.
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU,
THE TECHNOLOGY
YOU'VE ALREADY DEVELOPED
WILL CONTINUE TO EVOLVE.
YOU WILL EITHER QUIETLY
WITNESS IT FROM AFAR,
OR MAKE A INDELIBLE IMPRINT IN
THE HISTORICAL ANALS OF THE
INTERNATIONAL
SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY
AS AN UNPARALLELED GENIUS.
I DON'T NEED TO ASK
WHAT YOUR CHOICE IS.
THERE REALLY IS NO
CHOICE, IS THERE?
- WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO
WITH NECROLYZATION?
- NOTHING, NOTHING AT
ALL I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF USING IT. HOWEVER,
WE OF THE MILLENNION
ORGANIZATION HAVE TO
BE ABLE TO DEFEND OURSELVES.
AGAINST THE THREAT
OF DESTRUCTION
BY A GROUP SUCH AS LIGHTNING.
THINK OF IT AS A DETERRENT,
WHICH BY IT'S VERY EXISTENCE
WILL ELIMINATE SILLY
AND UNNECESSARY CONFLICTS.
SO, THIS IS NECROLYZATION?
- YES, I'M CALLING IT
VERSION NUMBER 2.
IN TERMS OF
SUSTAINED MAINTENANCE,
THE ENTIRE BLOOD SUPPLY IN
THE ENTITY MUST BE REPLACED
AS LONG AS THAT'S DONE,
IT WILL BE ALMOST
PERMANENTLY FUNCTIONAL.
IT'S SIMPLY AMAZING
HOW FAR WE'VE COME.
EVEN THOUGH THE ROAD WE'RE ON
IS LEADING US DOWN TO HELL.
- DOWN, DOCTOR?
YOU'RE WRONG, ABOUT THAT,
BELIEVE ME.
I'M GOING UP.
WHAT I'M HEADING FOR
ISN'T HELL, BUT FREEDOM.
THE FREEDOM TO TAKE WHATEVER
I LIKE, WHENEVER I LIKE
AND EVEN GIVE IT AWAY IF I LIKE.
THAT'S THE KIND OF FREEDOM
THAT IS WAITING FOR ME!
- UH...
- YES, THIS POWER WILL GIVE ME A
BOOST IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
ALL THE WAY UP, TO A MUCH,
MUCH HIGHER PLACE.
( maniacal laughter )
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: SHE WAS
LOOKING FOR COMFORT.
SHE WAS WISHING FOR HAPPINESS.
BUT I CANNOT
RESPOND TO HER NEEDS,
BECAUSE WHAT I WANT
IS ON THE OTHER SIDE.