( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- MAGRID OIL COMPANY...
MAGRID IS HUGE. IT'S ONE OF
THE BIGGEST OIL COMPANIES
IN THE WORLD.
- COME ON. LET'S GO
UP TO MY OFFICE.
- YOU MEAN IN THERE?
- RIGHT.
- ( laughs )
AWESOME! MILLENNION IS
AN AMAZING ORGANIZATION!
- Brandon: MILLENNION,
IF YOU'LL PARDON THE CLICHE,
IS ORGANIZED CRIME.
A CRIMINAL ORGANIZATION.
IT'S THE PREVAILING
POWER IN THIS TOWN.
CONTROLLING THE
UNDERGROUND COMMUNITY
AS WELL AS OPERATING
CORPORATIONS, TRADING FIRMS,
BANKS AS FRONTS FOR
IT'S CRIMINAL ACTIVITIES.
PREFFERING TO WORK
BEHIND THE SCENES,
IT'S OFTEN CALLED
"AUTHORITY OF THE SHADOWS"
AND HAS ENORMOUS INFLUENCE IN
ECONOMIC AND POLITICAL CIRCLES.
INCLUDING PERIPHERAL GROUPS,
IT CONSISTS OF APPROXIMATELY
8,000 MEMBERS,
OUT OF THOSE 8,000, THERE ARE
140 THAT THE BOSS, "BIG DADDY",
CONSIDERS THE FAMILY.
HIS ELITE INNER CIRCLE.
RANDY, THE GUY WHO BROUGHT
US HERE, IS ONE OF THEM.
HUGE AND ENORMOUSLY
POWERFUL MILLENNION.
BUT BACK THEN, I WASN'T THINKING
ABOUT THE ORGANIZATION.
ALL I WAS THINKING ABOUT WAS
MY PARTNER, STANDING NEXT TO ME.
AND MARIA.
IT WASN'T UNTIL I
MET THAT PERSON
THAT I STARTED
THINKING SERIOUSLY,
ABOUT THE ORGANIZATION
CALLED MILLENNION.
THAT'S RIGHT. THAT PERSON.
- ( commentator
indistinct on tv )
THERE ARE ONLY 30
YARDS TO THE FINISH LINE
AND THE UNDERDOG HAS
CLOSED THE GAP.
NOW HE'S NECK AND NECK
AND LOOK AT HIM GO.
HE'S COMING! THE WINNER IS
NUMBER 3, MICHAEL STAMPEDE!
AN AMAZING FINISH,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
- HEY, BOSS!
NUMBER 3 BEAT NUMBER 2!
- WHICH MEANS ANTHONY BLEW
30,000 ON THIS RACE.
HE'LL BE CALLING
ANY SECOND NOW.
- ( phone rings )
- THERE HE IS! THAT NEW FACE,
TELL HIM WE'LL LOAN HIM
AS MUCH AS HE WANTS!
WELL, SAY SOMETHING,
WILL YOU?
- GOOD AFTERNOON.
- YOU IDIOT.
HOW MANY TIMES DO
I NEED TO TELL YOU?
THE RACING PHONE'S ON THE RIGHT.
THE MIDDLE ONE'S FOR
BLACK MARKET STUFF.
AND THE ONE ON THE LEFT
IS FOR INTERNAL USE!
- WHY DON'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- I'M SORRY.
- DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I SAID...
- NAMES BRANDON HEAT...
- STRANGE NAME FOR A GUY
WHO'S COOL AND CALM.
- ( phone rings )
- WHEN YOU PICK UP THE PHONE...
- TALK TO ME.
- YOU PISS ME OFF,
YOU KNOW THAT? HEY!
- YEAH, IT'S ME. WHAT'S UP?
- I'M TALKING TO YOU!
- YEAH, I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- SO, WHAT'S UP, BOSS?
- IT'S A TIP FROM GWEN.
THAT'S SCALPER CARLASON. DIDN'T
PAY BACK THE 60,000 HE OWES US.
HE DIDN'T SHOW UP AT THE TRACK.
- LET'S GO, NEW FACE.
IT'S DROP-IN TIME.
- LOOKS LIKE THE BASTARD
JUST GOT BACK, BOSS.
- ALL RIGHT.
NEW FACE,
GARY AND I ARE GOING TO GO
IN TOGETHER FROM THE FRONT.
YOU KEEP AN EYE ON
THE BACK DOOR IN CASE
HE TRIES TO GIVE US THE SLIP.
NOW DON'T GET NERVOUS.
IN CASE OF AN EMERGENCY,
YOU CAN USE THIS.
BUT ONLY IF IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
- YOU'RE READY?
- YEAH.
- ( glass breaks )
- ( woman screams )
- HE'S COMING YOUR WAY!
- THAT'S HIM!
- WHO THE HELL'S
THIS PUNK?
OUT OF MY WAY, YOU BASTARD!
( screams )
YOU BASTARD! WHERE THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
- OH, MAN!
- NICE GOING, BRANDON HEAT.
YOU LIVE UP TO YOUR NAME.
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT SOME
FIRE IN YOU AFTER ALL.
GOOD.
- SAY SOMETHING, WILL YOU?
- THANK YOU.
- ( laughs )
- Brandon: RIGHT AFTER
I JOINED MILLENNION,
I GOT MY FIRST ASSIGNMENT.
I WAS TOLD TO GO TO A ROOM
IN A RUN DOWN BUILDING
ON THE WEST SIDE OF TOWN.
I LIVED AND WORKED AS PART OF A
CREW WHOSE JOB WAS TO COLLECT
MONEY FOR THE ORGANIZATION.
MILLENNION'S INCOME IN THIS
PARTICULAR DISTRICT CAME FROM
THE OPERATION AND MANAGEMENT
OF ILLEGAL RACE TRACK BETTING.
AND THE BLACK MARKET FINANCING
THAT WENT ALONG WITH IT.
THEY GAVE HIGH INTEREST LOANS
TO GAMBLERS AND WHEN THEY'D LOSE
WE KEPT RAISING THE INTEREST
RATES UNTIL THEY PAID US BACK.
IT WAS EXTORTION.
IF THEY DENIED THE DEBT
OR DIDN'T MAKE PAYMENTS ON TIME
WE DROPPED IN ON THEM.
WE DID THE SAME THING,
OVER AND OVER AGAIN
I FOUND IT TROUBLING AT FIRST.
BUT AFTER A WHILE, I LEARNED TO
HANDLE IT IN MY OWN WAY.
I WONDER IF HARRY WAS DOING
THE SAME THING SOMEPLACE ELSE.
I HADN'T SEEN HIM SINCE
WE PARTED WAYS THAT DAY.
AND I HADN'T
SEEN MARIA EITHER...
IT WENT ON THAT WAY
FOR NEARLY FOUR MONTHS.
- THE GUY WE'RE MEETING
IS ONE OF THE COLLECTORS.
THEY TAKE THE MONEY WE MAKE
TO ONE OF OUR AFFILIATES.
A MONEY LAUNDERING OPERATION
THAT MAKE THE FUNDS
LOOK LEGITIMATE.
THEN OUR EXECUTIVES
CAN USE THE MONEY
IN WHATEVER WAY THEY CHOOSE.
THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS.
'COURSE, SINCE YOU ARE AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE FOOD CHAIN,
YOU PROBABLY DON'T NEED
TO KNOW ALL THAT.
YOU DON'T TALK MUCH.
MY AUNT SAYS YOU QUIET TYPES
ARE THE MOST EMOTIONAL OF ALL.
'CAUSE OF ALL THOSE FEELINGS
YOU HAVE. HUDDLED UP INSIDE.
YOU THINK THAT'S TRUE?
I GUESS YOU'RE NOT GONNA ANSWER.
( laughs )
- YOU COLLECTED MORE THAN USUAL
THIS MONTH. WELL DONE.
HERE IS YOUR SHARE.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU, SIR.
- ( door opens )
- EXCUSE ME!
- YOUR TIMING
COULDN'T BE BETTER.
PUT THIS MONEY IN THE SAFE
FOR ME, WILL YOU HARRY?
- YES, SIR.
- HERE'S YOUR CUT.
- THANKS.
- I'M GONNA TAKE OFF. BUT YOU
CAN STAY AS LONG AS YOU LIKE.
THERE'S NO RUSH.
LOOKS LIKE YOU TWO HAVE
SOME CATCHING UP TO DO.
- HEY!
I HAVEN'T BEEN THERE VERY LONG.
ONLY ABOUT A WEEK OR SO.
SO THEY HAVEN'T GIVEN ME
A REAL ASSIGNMENT YET.
MOSTLY JUST ODDS AND ENDS.
OH, GOOD LOOKING SUIT, HUH?
MY BOSS TOLD ME TO GET
SOME DECENT CLOTHES.
YOU OUGHT TO DO THE SAME THING.
DRESS YOURSELF UP A LITTLE.
YOU GOT TO GET THEIR RESPECT
IF YOU WANT TO SURVIVE.
- ( both laugh )
- THIS IS IT, BRANDON.
IT'S MY FAVORITE HANGOUT.
HEY, COME ON, MAN.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU TO A
COUPLE OF FRIENDS OF MINE.
HEY GUYS.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
YO, HARRY. HOW YOU DOIN'?
I SEE YOUR APPETITE
IS AMAZING AS ALWAYS, BOB.
OF COURSE IT IS. IT'S MY
ONE OUTSTANDING QUALITY.
IF YOU TOOK THAT AWAY,
I HAVE NOTHING LEFT.
- SO, HARRY. THIS A
FRIEND OF YOURS?
YEAH, LET ME
INTRODUCE YOU TO HIM.
THIS IS BRANDON HEAT,
MY BEST FRIEND.
WE JOINED THE ORGANIZATION
AT THE SAME TIME.
- HELLO, THERE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
BALLADBIRD LEE ESQUIRE
AT YOUR SERVICE SIR.
BUT JUST CALL ME LEE,
ALL RIGHT?
- LEE HERE IS THE
PERSONAL ASSISTANT
TO THE TOP EXEC AT
ANOTHER DISTRICT.
HE'S ON OF THE
SHARPEST GUYS AROUND.
- COME ON. LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
TOOK ME ALMOST A YEAR AND HALF
TO GET TO WHERE I AM NOW.
BUT IT TOOK YOU
ONLY FOUR MONTHS.
SO WHEN YOU SAY HOW
GREAT YOU THINK I AM
IT ALMOST SOUNDS LIKE SARCASM.
WHAT KIND OF MAGIC
GOT YOU SO FAR SO FAST?
- SORRY, BUT THAT'S A
COMPANY SECRET.
- HEY, LEE. OKAY WITH YOU
IF I INTRODUCE MYSELF?
- OF COURSE. GO AHEAD.
- HI, THERE. MY NAME
IS BOB POUNDMAX.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU, BRANDON!
YES, INDEED, IT'S A REAL
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU ALL RIGHT.
- DIDN'T ANYONE TEACH YOU NOT
TO TALK WITH YOUR MOUTH FULL?
OH WELL, HE'S ALWAYS THIS WAY.
- YES, BUT BOB IS
A TRUE WHIZ KID.
- UNLIKE HIS IDIOTIC APPEARANCE.
- ( laughs )
- DO YOU UNDERSTAND? 10 MILLION,
A CHEQUE FOR 10 MILLION YULE!
AND IT'S NO BIG DEAL. CHEQUES
FOR THOSE KIND OF AMOUNTS
COME THROUGH OUR OFFICE EVERYDAY
AND NO ONE THINKS
TWICE ABOUT IT.
I NEVER COULD'VE IMAGINED HOW
AWESOME MILLENNION REALLY IS.
- THAT'S BECAUSE THE
TOP BOSS, BIG DADDY,
REALLY KNOWS WHAT HE IS DOING.
- WHO'S BIG DADDY?
- RIGHT NOW, BIG DADDY IS
SO FAR OUT OF OUR LEAGUE
HE MIGHT AS WELL BE
LIVING ON MOUNT OLYMPUS.
BUT IF WE CAN GET INVITED
INTO THE MILLENNION FAMILY,
BIG DADDY'S INNER CIRCLE,
WE'D BE AT THE VERY CENTER
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
WE'D LEARN HOW TO
GET ENOUGH POWER
TO CONTROL THIS ENTIRE CITY.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE AN
ATTRACTIVE PROPOSITION.
- BRANDON, LETS GO FOR IT.
GET INVITED INTO THE FAMILY.
- SURE.
- ME, TOO! ME, TOO!
- HEY, CUT IT OUT.
YOU'RE SPITTING FOOD.
- I'M SORRY, HARRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO, HONEST.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU
STILL DOING IT?
- BOB'S TABLE MANNERS
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN SPECTACULAR.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH, LEE.
UM, IF YOU'RE NOT
GONNA FINISH THAT...
- SURE. HELP YOURSELF, BOB.
- ARE YOU STILL EATING?
- UH-HUH.
- OH!
- THEY SAY SCRAWNY PEOPLE
ARE THE BIGGEST EATERS,
BUT YOU'RE OUT OF CONTROL.
- YOU THINK SO?
- ( laughs )
- I HAVEN'T HAD THIS MUCH
FUN FOR A LONG TIME.
- ME NEITHER.
- LOOK, BRANDON,
DON'T BE A STRANGER.
LETS STAY IN TOUCH, ALL RIGHT?
- SURE, HARRY.
- THAT'S WHERE
WE'RE HEADED, BRANDON.
ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
WE WILL BECOME PART
OF THE FAMILY.
- Brandon: YEAH.
- Gary: OKAY, OKAY. YOU'RE
BETTING 2000 ON A 4-5 EXACT
IN TOMORROW'S TENTH RACE.
YEAH, GOT IT.
YOU'RE ALL SET. THANKS.
BOSS?
- WE GOT WORK TO DO.
SOMEBODY PULLED OF A HEIST
AT ONE OF MILLENNION'S
WAREHOUSES LAST NIGHT.
PICKED IT CLEAN.
THEY STOLE JEWELRY
AND GOLD MOSTLY.
IF WE DON'T GET IT BACK,
THE ORGANIZATION WILL
LOSE 800,000 YULES.
- BUT HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO FIND THAT STUFF?
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO ROBBED THE PLACE.
- WELL, AS MATTER OF FACT,
WE HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
WHO DID IT AND WHERE THEY ARE.
OUR JOB IS TO TAKE BACK WHATEVER
THEY STOLE FROM US.
- WHY US?
MILLENNION'S GOT A BUNCH OF GUYS
BETTER SUITED FOR THIS JOB.
- HEY, LOOK. I DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANY MORE THAN YOU DO.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
WE JUST DO WHAT WE'RE TOLD.
- BRANDON.
- YEAH?
- THIS COULD UGLY. YOU READY?
- YEAH.
- ( men laughing )
- WE DID IT! WE HIT THE JACKPOT.
JUST LOOK AT IT, WILL YOU?
WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH DOUGH TO
GO ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
- WE'LL LEAVE IN THE MORNING
AND SELL IT LATER.
IN A DIFFERENT TOWN.
IT WILL BE SAFER THAT WAY.
- WE'LL BE FILTHY RICH
AND LIVE LIKE KINGS.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- WHAT THE HELL! AN OLD MAN.
- WANDERING ALONE
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS
CAN BE REAL BAD FOR YOUR HEALTH.
YOU BASTARD!
- WHAT DO YOU GUYS WANT FROM US?
- WE'RE FROM MILLENNION.
- MILLENNION? YOU MEAN...
- OH NO...
- I FOUND A COUPLE OF
THE ITEMS IN THEIR CAR, BOSS.
- I SEE. SO THAT AND THE STUFF
ON THE TABLE IS ALL OF IT, THEN?
- I...
- EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- YOU SHOULD NEVER HAVE
TOUCHED THE THINGS YOU STOLE.
WANNA KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE THOSE
ITEMS BELONG TO US.
PROPERTY OF THE
MILLENNION ORGANIZATION.
THE ORGANIZATION
HAS TO SAVE FACE.
HOW EMBARRASSING FOR US
THAT WE ALLOWED PUNKS
LIKE YOU TO STEAL OUR JEWELRY.
WE SHOULD NOTIFY THE POLICE
BUT THEN EVERYONE WOULD KNOW.
WE COULDN'T SAVE FACE
BY DOING THAT NOW, COULD WE?
- WE'LL RETURN IT.
EVERYTHING WE STOLE.
- NATURALLY, THAT
GOES WITHOUT SAYING.
BUT WHAT YOU'VE GOT
TO UNDERSTAND...
IS FROM OUR POINT OF VIEW,
THIS ROBBERY NEVER TOOK PLACE.
THE ITEMS REMAINED
IN THE WAREHOUSE.
WHICH MEANS THAT YOU
TWO NEVER STOLE THEM.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU TWO DON'T EXIST.
NOT IN THIS WORLD ANYWAY.
- ( both gasp )
- I'M SORRY.
BUT THE ORGANIZATION HAS IT'S
REPUTATION TO CONSIDER.
- ( gunshots )
- Widge: IT'S BEEN A LONG NIGHT.
SORRY I HAD TO ASK YOU TO COME
ALL THIS WAY TO BRING ME HOME.
- Gary: FORGET IT, BOSS.
NO PROBLEM.
- LISTEN, BRANDON.
THIS IS MILLENNION.
- YEAH.
- SEE YOU. GOOD NIGHT.
- WELCOME HOME, SON.
- MOTHER. YOU'RE STILL
UP AT THIS HOUR?
- I KNOW, BUT IT WAS
GETTING SO LATE
AND YOU STILL
HADN'T COME HOME...
I WAS TOO WORRIED TO SLEEP.
- I'M SORRY MOTHER.
I HAD TO WORK LATE.
NOW LETS GET
YOU INSIDE, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S CHILLY OUT HERE.
IT ISN'T GOOD FOR YOU.
- YOU LOOK TIRED.
YOU SHOULDN'T WORK SO HARD.
- I'M FINE. BESIDES, THE
REASON I'M SO BUSY IS BECAUSE
THE COMPANY IS MAKING
A LOT OF MONEY, RIGHT NOW.
- WELL, I SUPPOSE SO.
BUT STILL...
- LET'S GO TO BED. DON'T
FORGET TO TAKE YOUR MEDICINE.
- HEY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
MR. WIDGE HAS TO LIVE
WITH THAT SICKLY OLD LADY.
I MEAN YOU HEARD HER, RIGHT?
SHE DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE.
DOESN'T EVEN KNOW THAT
HER SON IS IN THE MAFIA.
SHE THINKS HE WORKS
AT SOME 9 TO 5 JOB SOMEWHERE.
BUT I ADMIRE HIM FOR
NOT TELLING HER.
TO KEEP HER FROM
WORRYING ABOUT HIM.
THAT'S THE WAY HE IS.
I MEAN HE COULD'VE TOLD US
TO KILL THOSE GUYS TONIGHT.
BUT HE FELT IT WAS
HIS RESPONSIBILITY.
THAT'S WHY I LIKE THE BOSS.
HE'S A STAND-UP GUY.
- HEY, IT'S ME! HOW YOU DOING?
- HARRY, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- THERE'S SOMETHING I WANTED
TO TELL YOU, THAT'S ALL.
BY THE WAY, THIS IS
TOO CARELESS OF YOU.
ILLEGAL BETTING
AND LOAN SHARKING.
A NICKLE AND DIME OPERATION
THAT WON'T GET YOU ANYWHERE.
YOU CAN'T GET AHEAD IN A
DEAD-END JOB LIKE THIS.
YOU NEED A HIGH PROFILE JOB
THAT'LL GET THEIR RESPECT.
LIKE THE ONE YOU HANDLED
EARLIER TONIGHT.
YOU SEE, I ASKED
THE GUYS AT THE TOP
TO GIVE YOU GUYS THE ASSIGNMENT.
NOW THAT YOU'VE DONE IT
AND PROVEN YOURSELF
I CAN RECOMMEND YOU TO MY BOSS.
YOU THINK WHAT I DID WAS WRONG?
- NO...
- GUESS I SHOULD'VE MINDED
MY OWN BUSINESS.
SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN TO
CAUSE YOU ANY TROUBLE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- BRANDON, YOU KNEW
MARIA WAS INVOLVED
IN THE ORGANIZATION, DIDN'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE,
ISN'T IT?
- NOW HOW DID YOU...
- YEAH, I THOUGHT SO. YOU IDIOT.
HERE. THIS IS THE ADDRESS
OF THE SCHOOL MARIA GOES TO.
I'VE HAD IT A WHILE BUT I
WASN'T GONNA GIVE IT TO YOU.
WANNA KNOW WHY?
HERE'S THE REASON.
MARIA'S AT THE MANSION.
SHE LIVES THERE WITH BIG DADDY.
THE BIG BOSS HIMSELF. THE
ORGANIZATION'S HEAD HONCHO.
I DON'T WHY OR WHAT THE
CIRCUMSTANCES WERE...
BUT FOR SOME REASON, BIG DADDY
INVITED HER INTO THE FAMILY.
THE ORGANIZATION'S
ELITE INNER CIRCLE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT MEANS?
IT MEANS THAT
SHE'S UNAPPROACHABLE.
PLEASE, BRANDON. TRY NOT
TO DO ANYTHING TOO STUPID.
'CAUSE IF YOU DO,
YOU WON'T SURVIVE.
- Brandon: I WANT TO SEE HER.
I WANT TO SEE MARIA.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT KEEPS ME GOING.
THE ONLY THING I HAVE
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
I WAS TOO ASHAMED TO
LOOK HER IN THE FACE
WHEN I'D HAD THE CHANCE...
AND NOW SHE IS WAY
OUT OF MY REACH.
BUT, I LONG FOR
THE SIGHT OF HER.
JUST ONE LOOK.
MARIA...
- BRANDON!
- MARIA...
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: HARRY BELONGED
TO MILLENNION.
MARIA BELONGED TO MILLENNION.
EVERYONE IMPORTANT TO ME
WAS A PART OF MILLENNION.
SO I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO FIGHT.
TO PROTECT WHAT WAS IMPORTANT.
TO PROTECT
THE ONES I LOVED.