- ( theme music playing )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( alarm blares )
- ( men shouting )
- ( groaning )
( shouts, growls )
- ( gunshots )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( shouts )
- ( groans )
- WHY?
WHY IS IT THAT YOU ALONE CAN
DESTROY MY ORGMEN SO EASILY?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
DOES THIS MEAN THAT
I'M INFERIOR TO DR. TOKIOKA?!
BEYOND THE GRAVE!
- Mika: THE WHOLE CITY
IS AT A STANDSTILL.
GRAVE SHUT IT DOWN
ALL BY HIMSELF.
- HEY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
PARTNER?
YOU'RE NOT AS PERKY
AS USUAL.
WHAT'S UP?
YOU GETTING HUNGRY
OR SOMETHING?
THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE GETTING HUNGRY, HUH?
YOU WANT A MEAL,
DON'T YOU?
A NICE, WARM MEAL.
THAT SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD,
DOESN'T IT?
WELL, THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
- HARRY, DARLING?
HARRY?
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M BEGGING YOU, HARRY,
LISTEN TO ME.
PLEASE, LISTEN!
- HMM?
WHAT WAS THAT, SHERRY?
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
YOU HEARD ME.
YOU'VE BEEN SO ODD LATELY.
COME ON, HARRY.
TELL ME WHAT'S THE MATTER.
- NOTHING.
- HARRY,
I CAN ALWAYS TELL WHEN
SOMETHING'S BOTHERING YOU.
PLEASE TELL ME WHAT
YOU'RE SO WORRIED ABOUT.
- LIKE I SAID,
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT ANYTHING.
- ARE YOU REALLY SURE?
- YES, I'M SURE.
- REALLY?
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT THEN?
I'VE JUST BEEN SO WORRIED
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN YOURSELF LATELY.
- FORGIVE ME.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING YOU'VE GOT
TO PROMISE ME, HARRY, OKAY?
- WHAT IS IT?
- PROMISE ME YOU WON'T
DIE BEFORE I DO.
THAT YOU WON'T LEAVE ME
BEHIND ALL ALONE.
- SURE.
YOU HAVE MY WORD ON IT.
- EXCUSE ME,
MASTER MACDOWEL.
- HMM?
YES, HARRISON?
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
- MASTER MACDOWEL,
I AM-- I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO TELL YOU THIS, BUT--
- ( gasps )
- I'M VERY SORRY ABOUT THIS.
VERY SORRY INDEED.
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps, groans )
- THE OVERKILLS,
JUST IN TIME.
- WE OVERKILLS
WILL DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO CARRY OUT BEAR WALKEN'S
INSTRUCTIONS
TO KEEP YOU AND MRS. MACDOWEL
OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- THANKS A LOT.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU GUYS.
- DON'T MENTION IT, SIR.
- IT'S OUR PLEASURE.
- SHERRY,
THEY SAY I'M GOOD
AT WHAT I DO,
BUT I'M NO MATCH
FOR YOUR FATHER.
- THANK YOU, DADDY.
- BY THE WAY, PARKER,
WHAT'S BECOME OF YOUR PLAN
FOR HARRY'S ASSASSINATION?
- IT FAILED.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE OVERKILLS
APPEAR TO BE ON
HARRY'S SIDE NOW.
- A TRICKY SITUATION.
- THEY'RE HIGHLY SKILLED,
BUT THERE'S LESS THAN
A DOZEN OF THEM LEFT.
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY CAN STOP US.
WHAT'LL WE DO
ABOUT THE ORGMEN?
- RIGHT.  THOSE THINGS
ARE PROGRAMMED TO FOLLOW
WHATEVER ORDERS
HARRY GIVES THEM.
THEY NEVER SURRENDER.
- WE FOUND A FORMER
LAB TECHNICIAN
WHO'S HELPING US WITH THAT.
PRODUCTION OF A SPECIAL
COUNTER ORGMEN HYBRID PROTOTYPE
HAS ALREADY BEGUN.
PARKER, WHICH EXECUTIVES
CAN WE COUNT ON FOR SUPPORT?
- WE'VE CONVINCED
WALTER, DANIEL, AND NICK
THAT IT WOULD BE
BEST TO JOIN US.
- BRIAN, ANTHONY, AND STEVE
WILL JOIN US
WHENEVER WE'RE READY
TO MAKE OUR MOVE.
- WHICH MEANS ONLY
PETE AND ERIC ARE LEFT.
- LEAVE THOSE TWO TO ME.
I'LL HAVE A TALK WITH THEM.
THEY'RE REASONABLE MEN.
I'M SURE I CAN
CONVINCE THEM.
MEANWHILE...
- MEANWHILE?
- MEANWHILE,
DON'T INTERFERE WITH THE TARGET.
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE AND LET
HIM DO WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
- I DON'T THINK THAT'S
A VERY GOOD IDEA.
HE'S PARALYZED
THE ENTIRE CITY.
IF WE REMAIN VULNERABLE,
IT WILL INVITE COMPETITION
AND INTERFERENCE
FROM OTHER ORGANIZATIONS.
- THEY'LL FIND OUT WE'RE
NOT QUITE AS VULNERABLE
AS THEY THINK.
OUR TARGET IS NO LONGER HIM.
IT'S HARRY MACDOWEL'S
MILLENNION.
WE'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK,
RIGHT, BIG DADDY?
- ( tires screech )
- ( both gasp )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunfire )
- IAN!  EVANS!
HEY, KYNE?
- HUH?
- ( both grunt )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( groans )
- ( screams )
- BACK US OUT OF HERE NOW!
- ( grunts )
- ( whimpers, cries )
- WHAT NOW, GRAVE?
YOU GONNA LEAVE AGAIN?
IS IT USELESS
TRYING TO STOP YOU?
GRAVE?
ARE THE TWO OF US...
HAVE WE BECOME A FAMILY?
- YEAH.
- ( chuckles )
THEN I KNOW YOU'LL COME BACK.
YOU'LL COME BACK
TO YOUR FAMILY.
I BELIEVE THAT.
( gasps )
YOUR BODY...
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU?
- I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
- NO WAY.
IF YOU LEAVE LIKE THIS,
YOU'LL NEVER COME BACK.
DON'T GO.
OH, PLEASE, DON'T GO!
FORGET REVENGE
AND MILLENNION
AND BLOODY HARRY.
WE CAN PUT ALL THAT
BEHIND US, PLEASE?
WE'LL GO AWAY,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY FROM HERE.
NO MATTER HOW HARD IT IS,
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP.
I'LL SURVIVE ON NOTHING MORE
THAN BREAD AND WATER
IF I HAVE TO.
I'LL STUDY HARD
AND LEARN BIO-MECHANICS
AND TAKE CARE OF YOU
LIKE DR. TOKIOKA.
DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE.
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE DON'T GO!
( sobs )
- MIKA, I'M SORRY.
I HAVE NO FUTURE.
NOT ANYMORE.
MY FUTURE'S DEAD,
JUST LIKE ME.
- YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE NOT DEAD,
I KNOW IT.
I KNOW IT!
- YOU'RE THE STRONGEST
PERSON I KNOW.
YOU CAN MAKE IT
ON YOUR OWN.
- OH, GRAVE.
- MIKA...
I HAVE TO GO NOW,
UNDERSTAND?
- DON'T GO.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO.
BECAUSE...
I LOVE YOU.
GRAVE, I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T
WANT YOU TO GO.
PLEASE, GRAVE.
PLEASE, DON'T GO.
( crying )
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A GREAT LIFE...
WITHOUT ME.
TODAY AND TOMORROW,
AND FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
THERE'S NO CHOICE.
- ( gasps )
DON'T GO.
- ( cat meows )
- ( bell jingles )
- HEY, BRO.
- ( exhales )
- ( gunshot )
- ( chuckles )
- LET'S GO,
BUNJI KUGASHIRA.
- OH, YEAH.
I'M READY WHENEVER YOU ARE,
BIG GUY.
( chuckles )
- SHERRY, I WANT YOU TO
STAY HERE AT THE HOTEL
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
- ONLY IF YOU'LL TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
- JUST SOME BUSINESS
MATTERS TO ATTEND TO.
I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHICH OF OUR EXECUTIVES
HIRED THOSE THUGS
WHO ATTACKED US TODAY,
AND THEN MAKE CERTAIN THAT
THE TRAITOR IS SUITABLY PUNISHED
FOR BREAKING
THE CODE OF IRON.
- IT'S TOO DANGEROUS, HARRY.
- SO WHAT SHOULD I DO?
RUN?
AS LONG AS I'M THE BOSS,
TRAITORS WILL GET
WHAT THEY DESERVE.
PLEASE TAKE GOOD CARE OF HER.
- I UNDERSTAND, SIR.
- HARRY.
- JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
DEAR.
WE SWORE TO EACH OTHER
THAT WE WOULD BE TOGETHER
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES,
AND WE WILL.
- OH, HARRY.
- SHERRY.
- ( clears throat )
WE REALLY SHOULD
GET MOVING, SIR.
- ( panting )
HARRY!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
- ( exhales )
-  ( gasps )
OH, NO.
SHERRY.
SHERRY!
DON'T WORRY, DARLING.
I'LL-- I'LL GET A DOCTOR
HERE AS FAST AS I CAN.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
IT'S NOTHING SERIOUS.
IT'S JUST A SCRATCH.
A LITTLE FLESH WOUND.
RIGHT, SWEETHEART?
- ( labored breathing )
HARRY...
THANK YOU...
HARRY.
( exhales )
- ( gasps )
( stammers )
( sobbing )
( shouts )
SHERRY!
- OH, GRAVE.
- ( grunts )
UH?
( gasps )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( panting )
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
( groans )
( shouts )
- ( chuckles )
- HMM.
( gasps )
( grunts )
- HUH?
WELL, BIG GUY,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE END
THIS THING ONCE AND FOR ALL?
- ( gasps )
YEAH.
SORRY IT HAD TO
END THIS WAY, BUNJI.
- HEY, BRO, THAT'S LIFE.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- SO I GUESS THIS IS
FINALLY IT THEN.
- THAT'S A NO-BRAINER.
I WISH YOU LUCK.
- ( gunshots )
- ( singing )
- HEY, PARTNER.
- ( bell jingles )
- ( meows )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Grave: A MAN WHO HAS FALLEN
FROM A GREAT HEIGHT,
A MAN WHO HAS NO FUTURE.
WHAT I REMEMBER IS WHAT
HE SAID BACK THEN.
THE WORDS OF THE VOW
FROM THE PAST,
AND THE ENCOUNTER
THAT THEY CREATED.