( theme music playing )
I KEEP WONDERING
OVER AND OVER AGAIN...
IF I MADE THE RIGHT CHOICE.
RIGHT OR WRONG...
I KNEW I WOULD GO TO HELL
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE.
AND I ACCEPT THAT.
BUT I WONDER IS IT NECESSARY
TO MAKE YOU COME WITH ME...
EVEN IF THAT IS WHAT
YOU WISHED FOR.
- WHAT A CATASTROPHE.
SO, HOW MANY DID WE LOSE?
- FOUR RESEARCHERS ARE DEAD.
FIVE OTHERS AND
DR. TOKIOKA ARE MISSING.
NO DOUBT, BURIED IN THE RUBBLE.
- THE THREE NECROLYZERS
WERE BLOWN OUT OF EXISTENCE.
OF COURSE, BY THEN, THEY HAD
ALREADY TRASHED THE LAB.
- BOSS, DO YOU REALLY THINK
THIS WAS AN ACCIDENT,
OR SOMETHING ELSE?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER, DOES IT?
EITHER WAY, YOUR EXPECTATIONS
WERE REALISTIC TO BEGIN WITH.
- AND WHO ARE YOU?
- A RESEARCHER
WITH THE R&amp;D TEAM,
MY NAME IS LAGUNA GLOCK.
- WHY DID YOU SAY OUR
EXPECTATIONS WEREN'T REALISTIC?
- DR. TOKIOKA WAS STUDYING
A PROCESS CALLED
NECROLYZATION...
HE CLAIMED HE WAS PERFECTING
A METHOD OF
REANIMATING THE DEAD.
BUT AFTER THOROUGHLY REVIEWING
THE PARAMETERS OF
HIS EXPERIMENTS,
I DISCOVERED THE PROCESS
WAS MORE EFFECTIVE
ON PEOPLE STILL ALIVE
RATHER THAN THOSE WHO WERE DEAD.
MEANING, THAT THE DOCTOR
INTENTIONALLY MADE THE PROCESS
MORE DIFFICULT
THAN IT HAD TO BE.
SIR, IF YOU PUT ME
IN CHARGE OF THIS PROJECT,
I PROMISE TO DEVELOP THE MOST
ADVANCED NECROLYZERS EVER SEEN
...AND BETTER YET,
A COMPLETELY NEW KIND OF
SOLDIER FOR MILLENNION.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
YOU HAVE TO SPEND.
JUST GET ME RESULTS AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE. UNDERSTAND?
- PERFECTLY. THANK YOU, SIR.
- BOSS, ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- YEAH, LEE.
I CAN SEE IT IN HIS EYES.
- HIS EYES, BOSS?
- HE HAS THE EYES OF A MAN WHO
WOULD SELL HIS SOUL TO SATAN
TO FIND THE ANSWERS
HE'S LOOKING FOR.
( he exclaims )
- I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
FOR 15 YEARS.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- THE MONEY YOU ASKED ME TO GET
FOR YOU IS IN THE TRUNK.
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT NOW?
ARE YOU LEAVING TOWN?
- AS SOON AS I CAN.
FIRST I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO DELIVER TWO THINGS.
THIS CASE AND A LETTER.
THERE'S A MAN I NEED TO
GET THEM TO RIGHT AWAY.
BIG DADDY HIMSELF,
THE BOSS OF MILLENNION.
- YOU MEAN MY MASTER?
- BROTHER, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU SAID YOU HAVE
A LETTER FOR MY MASTER?
- DO YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
YOU WORK FOR...
( crickets chirping )
- "DEAR BIG DADDY,"
"THE FACT THAT YOU ARE
READING THIS LETTER
MEANS THAT I NO LONGER
EXIST IN THIS WORLD."
"BUT THAT IS PART
OF MY DESTINY TOO.
ALONG WITH WHAT I CONFESS
TO YOU NOW IN THIS LETTER."
"I KNEW ALL ABOUT WHAT
MY FRIEND, HARRY MACDOWEL,
WAS DOING. I KNEW EVERYTHING."
"I KNEW HE WAS
WORKING FROM BEHIND THE SCENES
TO STRENGTHEN HIS TEAM..."
"...AND GET PROMOTED
MORE QUICKLY."
"I KNEW THAT HE WAS
PAYROLLING RESEARCH
AIMED AT REVIVING THE DEAD."
"AND THROUGH IT ALL,
I REMAINED SILENT.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU WHAT I KNEW."
"I HAD A REASONS."
"IT WAS EASY TO JUSTIFY."
"I TOLD MYSELF,
IF WHAT HARRY IS DOING WILL
BENEFIT THE ORGANIZATION,
"THEN IT MUST BE ALL RIGHT."
"I WANTED TO BELIEVE
IN HARRY MACDOWEL.
I WANTED TO BELIEVE
IN MY BEST FRIEND."
- BRANDON...
I PROMISE YOU THIS.
IF HARRY MACDOWEL DOES ANY
DAMAGE TO THIS ORGANIZATION...
- HARRY'S NOT A TRAITOR
AND HE NEVER WILL BE.
YOU'VE GOT MY WORD.
HOWEVER, EACH AND EVERY TRAITOR
WHO BREAKS THE CODE OF IRON
WILL RECEIVE
THE SAME PUNISHMENT.
NO MORE, NO LESS,
REGARDLESS OF RANK OR STATUS.
( loads gun )
- SO YOU ALREADY KNOW.
EVEN BACK THEN, YOU KNEW.
BUT TO BE PREPARED TO FACE
A THING LIKE THAT...
- NOT HARRY. OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT WHY?... WHY, BRANDON?
PLEASE TELL ME.
( he exclaims )
- BRANDON...
I KNOW YOU WANTED TO
PROTECT THE ORGANIZATION.
AND MARIA AS WELL...
- "BIG DADDY. I WANT TO BELIEVE
IN HARRY MACDOWEL."
"BUT IF HE FORGETS HIMSELF,
IF HE VEERS OFF COURSE,
HE'LL NEED TO BE STOPPED."
"AND THAT WILL BE MY JOB.
NO ONE ELSE'S."
"THAT'S WHY I MET WITH
DR. TOKIOKA SECRETLY
AND WHY HE GRANTED MY REQUEST."
"IN THE EVENT OF MY DEATH,
I WANT TO BE REVIVED.
TO BECOME A NECROLYZER."
"I WANT TO REMAIN IN THE
CONTAINMENT CHAMBER ASLEEP
UNTIL I'M NEEDED."
"IF THE ORGANIZATION
IS THREATENED,
OR IF HARRY VEERS OFF COURSE,"
"I WANT TO BE AWAKENED."
- BRANDON, WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
BRANDON...
BRANDON, YOU'RE SO AWKWARD.
YOU WERE FREE TO MAKE YOUR LIFE
WHATEVER YOU WANTED IT TO BE.
WHY DID YOU
THROW ALL THAT AWAY?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, BRANDON.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WAKE UP EVER AGAIN.
JUST REST PEACEFULLY.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
I CAN WISH FOR NOW.
REST, MY SON.
( he sobs )
- DR. TOKIOKA, I WON'T ASK
WHAT KIND OF EXPERIMENTS
YOU WERE CONDUCTING...
WHEN YOU CONSPIRED
WITH HARRY MACDOWEL.
OR WHAT SORT OF IMMORAL ACTS
YOU COMMITTED IN DOING SO.
WHAT I EXPECT IN RETURN
IS YOUR PROMISE TO LET
BRANDON REST IN PEACE FOREVER.
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU NEED
AND YOU'LL GET IT.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
IS THAT CLEAR?
- YES, BIG DADDY.
PERFECTLY CLEAR.
( he screams )
( loud thud )
- THAT WILL BE ALL NOW, DOCTOR.
( he grimaces )
( he chuckles )
- NOT NEARLY AS MUCH
PAIN AS I DESERVE
FOR THE THINGS I'VE DONE.
- WHAT AM I PUNISHING HIM FOR?
I'M THE ONE WHO DESERVES
TO BE CONDEMNED.
- MASTER, I JUST RECEIVED
A RATHER URGENT CALL
FROM THE MANSION.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- I'M AFRAID THAT MADAM MARIA
CAN'T BE FOUND, SIR.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- THEY'VE SEARCHED THE ENTIRE
ESTATE QUITE THOROUGHLY
AND COULDN'T FIND HER.
- LET'S GET GOING.
- BRANDON AND HARRY WERE
IN THE ORGANIZATION.
HARRY KILLED BRANDON
BECAUSE BRANDON BETRAYED
THE ORGANIZATION?
IT'S ABSURD!
HOW COULD HE?
THE TWO OF THEM WERE SO CLOSE...
IT JUST ISN'T POSSIBLE.
BUT IF IT'S TRUE, I'LL NEVER
FORGIVE HARRY MACDOWEL...
FOR KILLING MY BELOVED BRANDON.
- I THOUGHT I MIGHT
FIND YOU HERE.
- DARLING...!
- LET'S GO HOME.
DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU WANTED
TO RAISE OUR CHILD
NEW LIFE AWAY FROM THE GANG
WORLD?
YES, OF COURSE I DID, BUT...
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
COME, WE CAN TALK IN THE CAR.
MARIA, I UNDERSTAND YOUR GRIEF
AND HOW VERY DIFFICULT
THIS MUST BE FOR YOU.
FORTUNATELY, I WAS
ABLE TO PREVENT YOU
FROM MAKING A TRAGIC MISTAKE.
NOW THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
MARIA, I HAVE SOME
GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
I JUST FOUND OUT,
BRANDON IS ALIVE.
- WHAT?
- IT'S TRUE. I SWEAR.
I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU.
- WHERE IS HE...
WHERE IS BRANDON RIGHT
NOW? DO YOU KNOW?
- UNFORTUNATELY, HE WON'T BE
LIVING AROUND HERE ANYMORE.
PLANS ON DOING
A LOT OF TRAVELING.
I DON'T THINK WE'LL
SEE HIM AGAIN SOON.
IN FACT, WE MAY NEVER
SEE HIM AGAIN.
- DID YOU SEE HIM YOURSELF?
- NO, HE CONTACTED ME
THROUGH ONE OF MY AIDES
WHO TALKED TO HIM
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
- REALLY?
- YES.
- IF HE'S ALIVE...
( she sobs )
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME!
- LISTEN, BRANDON TOLD ME AIDE
TO TELL YOU
IF YOU EVER HAVE AN EMERGENCY
AND NEED HIS HELP,
YOU SHOULD USE THAT
CASE OVER THERE
TO LET HIM KNOW THAT
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE.
HE'LL COME TO YOU AS FAST AS
HE CAN NO MATTER WHERE YOU ARE.
BRANDON HAD ONE OTHER MESSAGE
THAT HE WANTED ME TO GIVE YOU.
HE PRAYS FOR ONE THING,
YOUR HAPPINESS, MARIA.
- YOUR ORDERS, SIR?
- TOKIOKA, TAKE CARE
OF MARIA FOR ME.
- ARE YOU LEAVING, MASTER?
- FOR SOME TIME NOW,
I HAD FORGOTTEN WHO I AM.
THAT I AM MILLENNION ITSELF.
- I UNDERSTAND, SIR.
- MARIA, DO YOUR BEST,
MY DARLING.
FIND A NEW LIFE WHERE OUR
CHILD CAN BE RAISED IN PEACE.
IT'S BEEN OVER 35 YEARS SINCE I
FOUNDED MILLENNION.
I'VE SPENT MOST OF MY LIFE
PROTECTING THE ORGANIZATION
AND THE FAMILY.
I'VE LIVED LIFE ON MY TERMS.
I HAVE NO REGRETS.
WELL, ONE PERHAPS.
THAT MY TIME WITH MARIA
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN LONGER.
BUT I'M GRATEFUL
THAT SHE CAME INTO MY LIFE.
IT'S BEEN LIKE A DREAM FOR ME.
AND BRANDON WAS THE ONE
WHO BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
THANK YOU, BRANDON.
AND I ALSO THANK YOU FOR
ENTRUSTING ME WITH THAT CASE.
BUT AS MUCH AS I
APPRECIATE THE GESTURE,
I HAVE NO INTENTION OF USING IT.
I HAVE GIVEN THE CASE TO MARIA
AND THE NEW LIFE WITHIN HER
THAT IS ABOUT TO BE BORN.
MY ONLY LEGACY.
AND SHOULD THEY EVER NEED YOU,
PLEASE RESPOND TO THEIR REQUEST.
I'M SORRY, BRANDON.
BUT AS THE FOUNDER AND OLDEST
MEMBER OF THIS ORGANIZATION,
IT'S ONLY FITTING THAT I HONOR
YOUR MEMORY IN THE PROPER WAY.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS ABOUT TIME
FOR YOU TO SHOW UP, BIG DADDY.
ACTUALLY I EXPECTED YOU SOONER.
MY GUYS TOLD ME THAT BOTH YOU
AND MARIA WERE HERE EARLIER
BUT THEN YOU
POSTPONED YOUR VISIT.
I WOULD HAVE ASKED
YOU TO COME UP BUT I
DIDN'T WANT TO INTRUDE,
SO I HELD MYSELF BACK.
ON THE OTHER HAND, MAYBE
I SHOULD HAVE COME OUT
AND SAID HELLO.
- TELL ME, HARRY MACDOWEL,
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS
FOR ALL THIS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO WITH
THE MILLENNION ORGANIZATION?
- WELL, SINCE IT
IS MY ORGANIZATION,
I'D APPRECIATE YOU KEEPING
YOUR NOSE OUT OF MY BUSINESS,
INCLUDING MY PLANS
FOR THE FUTURE.
- I AM MILLENNION.
MILLENNION IS ME
AND I'M MILLENNION.
- THINGS HAVE CHANGED, OLD
MAN. HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED?
HARRY MACDOWEL IS
MILLENNION NOW.
-PERHAPS THERE IS HARMONY
IN COMPROMISE.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
HARMONY IS AN OUTDATED
CONCEPT THAT HAS NO PLACE
IN A MODERN ECONOMY.
HARMONY JUST
LEADS TO STAGNATION.
WHEREAS COMPETITION AND RIVALRY
RESULT IN PROGRESS
AND PRODUCTIVITY.
HARMONY ISN'T ONE
OF OUR STRONG POINTS
AND OUR CLIENTS
LIKE IT THAT WAY.
YOU UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE REALLY
BEGINNING TO LOOK YOUR AGE,
BIG DADDY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
AND I'M NOT JUST
YANKING YOUR CHAIN HERE. I
THINK YOU SHOULD RETIRE.
TAKE A LOAD OFF.
HAVE A SEAT.
CAN I GET YOU
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
I HAPPENED TO GET MY HANDS
ON A BOTTLE OF 28-YEAR-OLD
BOURBON THE OTHER DAY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW!
THIS BOURBON WAS BOTTLED
THE SAME YEAR I WAS BORN.
IT MATURED ALMOST
AS WELL AS I HAVE.
- THANKS FOR THE OFFER
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
I DON'T DRINK BOURBON.
ONLY WHISKEY.
- OH? MAY I ASK WHY?
- BOURBON IS A DERIVATIVE,
DESCENDED FROM WHISKEY.
IT'S NOT THE ORIGINAL
AS IT WERE.
- WELL THEN, LET'S GET RID
OF EVERY OUNCE OF
WHISKEY IN EXISTENCE.
THEN BOURBON BECOMES
THE ORIGINAL, RIGHT?
- WHATEVER MAKES YOU THINK
THAT'S THE WAY THINGS ARE.
- MILLENNION IS A GOOD TEACHER.
I THINK THAT WAY
BECAUSE OF MILLENNION.
- IS THAT SO?
THEN I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
( cock gun )
( Harry chuckles )
- ARE YOU GOING TO SHOOT ME?
- I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
THINK OF IT AS PAYBACK FOR
BRANDON'S LOYALTY AND HIS LIFE!
( gunshot )
- SORRY, BUNJI, BUT WOULD YOU
MIND STEPPING OUT FOR A MOMENT?
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
( door shuts )
- AH, THAT'S GOOD.
NOW LOOK, BIG DADDY,
WHY DON'T YOU AND MARIA
GO LIVE IN A NICE
QUIET LITTLE TOWN?
YOU'RE STILL A WORTHWHILE
GUY TO HAVE AROUND.
I DON'T WANNA KILL YOU
IF I DON'T HAVE TO.
- BRANDON KNEW...
BRANDON KNEW EVERYTHING.
YOUR BETRAYALS AND SCAMS.
YOUR GRIMY LITTLE CONSPIRACIES.
BUT BRANDON STILL HAD
FAITH IN YOU.
BRANDON KNEW?
SO HE KNEW?
HE KNEW THAT I'D...
( Harry laughs )
- HARRY, IF YOU CARE
ABOUT BRANDON,
MAKE THIS AN ORGANIZATION
HE'D BE PROUD OF.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU SAYING,
YOU OLD BASTARD?
BRANDON DIED BECAUSE OF YOU.
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO
GOT HIM KILLED!
- BRANDON CARED A GREAT DEAL!
- DON'T YOU DARE SAY THAT NAME!
( gunshot )
YOU BASTARD! YOU BASTARD!
YOU TOOK HIM AWAY FROM ME!
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
YOU RIGHT NOW,
I COULD HAVE BEEN CLIMBING
THE LADDER WITH BRANDON!
WITH BRANDON!
( gun clicks )
NOW IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
KILLING YOU IS NOT ENOUGH.
I'LL ERASE YOU LIKE A VIDEO
TAPE. TOTAL OBLITERATION.
I, HARRY MACDOWEL,
THE ALL POWERFUL...
...WILL DESTROY EVERY TRACE
OF YOUR EXISTENCE
FROM THE FACE OF THIS PLANET.
- EVEN FROM THE GRAVE,
THE MAINTAINS HIS LOYALTY
TO THE ORGANIZATION.
SO LOYAL IS BRANDON HEAT.
NO... THAT NAME IS
NO LONGER APPROPRIATE.
BRANDON HEAT IS NO MORE.
YOU'VE COME BACK FROM
BEYOND THE GRAVE.
SO THAT WILL BE YOUR NAME.
FROM THIS POINT ON,
YOU ARE BEYOND THE GRAVE.
KEEP SLEEPING, GRAVE.
FOREVER...
- THIRTEEN YEARS IS LONG ENOUGH
TO CHANGE PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
BUT THERE'S ONE MAN
WHO STOPPED TIME.
HE HASN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
HE JUST KEEPS SLEEPING.