- ( theme music playing )
- Harry: THEY WANT ME DEAD.
THEY'VE ALREADY SEIZED
MY HIDDEN BANK ACCOUNTS,
AND NOW THE BASTARDS ARE
TEARING MY MANSION APART.
SHERRY...
STILL...
I AM MILLENNION.
- ( exhales )
( groans )
( breathes deep )
- TIME TO WAKE UP,
ORGMEN.
IT'S TIME TO WIPE OUT
THE TRAITORS.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I TAKE WHAT I WANT.
AND WHATEVER I TAKE,
I CAN CHOOSE TO GIVE BACK!
DAMN RIGHT.
KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE I'M HARRY MACDOWEL!
( laughs )
- SO THIS IS ONE OF
THE SPECIAL ANTI-ORGMEN BULLETS?
- YES, SIR.
A DIRECT HIT
WILL SCRAMBLE
THE ORGMEN'S PROGRAMMING
INTO USELESS BINARY FRAGMENTS
LEAVING IT
POWERLESS TO FIGHT
OR TO DEFEND ITSELF.
- SAVE THE SALE'S PITCH.
- UH.
- TELL ME,
WILL THIS DESTROY
AN ORGMEN OR WON'T IT?
- YES, SIR.
WE'VE ALREADY MANUFACTURED
OVER 6,000 ROUNDS
AND DISTRIBUTED THEM AMONG
SEVERAL OF THE MAJOR PLAYERS.
- VERY WELL.
- AMAZING THAT
THIS LITTLE BULLET
WILL DESTROY AN ORGMEN THAT
WE ONCE CONSIDERED INVINCIBLE.
- THE SURVIVAL OF THE FITTEST,
THE STRONG BEING VANQUISHED
BY THE STRONGER,
IS ALWAYS PART OF THE TRANSITION
FROM ONE AGE TO ANOTHER.
- THE AGE OF HARRY MACDOWEL
IS OVER.
- PROSPERITY TO
THE NEW MILLENNION.
- ( church organ playing )
- NO ONE ELSE THEN?
YOU'LL BE ATTENDING
THE SERVICE ALONE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- I SEE.
- Harry: SHERRY,
REST ASSURED,
I'LL GO ON BEING
WHO I'VE ALWAYS BEEN,
HARRY MACDOWEL
OF MILLENNION.
- ( groans )
- ( gunfire )
- Harry: SHERRY.
- ( growls )
( grunts )
- ( Mika panting )
GRAVE.
- WHO ARE YOU?
YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- I-- I'M A...
- HUH?
IT'S THE GIRL.
THE ONE HEADQUARTERS
TOLD US TO--
- ( gasps )
- HOLD IT.
- SIR.
- ( gasps )
- MISS MIKA ASAGI,
I PRESUME.
BIG DADDY'S CHILD.
THAT'S WHO YOU ARE,
RIGHT?
HARRY MACDOWEL,
OUR FORMER BOSS
AND THE MAN WHO
ORDERED YOUR DEATH,
HAS BEEN EXPELLED
FROM THE ORGANIZATION.
- HUH?
- HE'S THE ONE WE'RE AFTER,
MISS ASAGI, NOT YOU.
YOU'VE NOTHING
TO FEAR FROM US.
YOU'RE FREE NOW.
- I'M FREE?
- YES.
- JUST LIKE THAT?  FREE.
- HMM.
- IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
WHAT ABOUT ALL
THE PEOPLE WHO DIED?
MOM, DAD,
MR. TOKIOKA
AND DR. TOKIOKA,
WIDGE AND GARY.
WHAT DOES "FREE"
MEAN TO THEM?
THEY ALL DIED FOR NOTHING!
- WE UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU FEEL, MISS.
BUT WE WON'T APOLOGIZE.
A CHANGE OF LEADERSHIP
ALSO CHANGES THE WAY
AN ORGANIZATION
DOES BUSINESS.
YOU WERE IN THE WRONG PLACE
AT THE WRONG TIME.
A TWIST OF FATE,
NOTHING MORE, MISS.
- ( gasps )
- YOUNG LADY,
ON SEVERAL OCCASIONS
OUR FORMER BOSS BIG DADDY
WENT OUT OF HIS WAY
TO TAKE CARE OF ME.
HIS KINDNESS MEANT
A GREAT DEAL TO ME.
I OWE HIM
A DEBT OF GRATITUDE,
AND IT'S TIME I STARTED
PAYING IT BACK.
SO IF I CAN BE OF HELP
IN ANY WAY,
PLEASE LET ME KNOW.
- IT'S TOO LATE.
HELP ME FIND HIM.
- HUH?
- THE MAN...
THEY CALL "BEYOND THE GRAVE."
( sighs )
BUT HIS NAME'S BRANDON.
BRANDON HEAT.
THE ONLY FAMILY
I'VE GOT.
- Harry:
I'M NOT FINISHED YET.
YOU'LL SEE.
YOU DIDN'T TAKE ME SERIOUSLY,
DID YOU?
WELL, NOW YOU'RE
GONNA FIND OUT
WHO THE REAL BOSS IS.
- ( Orgmen groans )
- HUH?
- ( moans )
( yells )
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- IT'S HARRY MACDOWEL!
( grunts )
- ( inhales sharply )
- ( tires screech )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunfire )
- ( exhales )
CALL HEADQUARTERS NOW!
- Harry: ORGMEN...
MY ORGMEN...
SHIT.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
HUH?
- ( tires screech )
- ( gasps )
- ( gunfire )
- DAMN IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
WHERE THE HELL
DID I GO WRONG?
HOW IN THE WORLD...
( gasps )
- ( crashing )
- BRANDON.
- HARRY.
- ( breathes deep )
( strains )
HARRY.
HARRY MACDOWEL.
- BRANDON HEAT.
- ( groans )
( exhales )
- UNBELIEVABLE.
TWO AND THREE,
TWO AND THREE!
IT WAS OBVIOUS.
ANYONE COULD HAVE GUESSED
WHO WAS GONNA WIN THAT RACE.
IT WAS A SURE THING.
IT WAS BAD ENOUGH
THAT NATHAN SNUCK OFF
WITH MY GAMBLING DOUGH,
BUT FOR HIM TO BLOW
THE WHOLE THING
BETTING THE TWO-FIVE,
NOW THAT WAS
UN-FREAKING-BELIEVABLE.
I'M TELLING YOU, MAN,
THE GUY'S HOPELESS.
- ( woman screams )
- ( men laugh )
- STOP. STOP IT!
- AW, COME ON, CUTIE PIE.
DON'T BE SO ANTISOCIAL.
- ( cries )
LET GO OF ME!
- DON'T GET INVOLVED.
- HUH?
- WHAT GOOD WOULD IT DO?
IN THIS TOWN, PEOPLE GOTTA LEARN
TO DEAL WITH THEIR OWN PROBLEMS.
THE LUCKY ONES WILL MAKE IT,
AND THE UNLUCKY ONES WON'T,
WHETHER YOU HELP THEM
OR NOT, RIGHT?
- HMM.
- ( chuckles )
- ( exhales )
- UH?
BRANDON, WAIT!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
COME BACK HERE.
HOPELESS, COMPLETELY
AND UTTERLY HOPELESS.
( sighs )
- ( men laughing )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT, MISSY.
- STOP IT.
- SWEET LITTLE THING
ALL BY YOURSELF,
STRUTTING YOUR STUFF.
- HEY, LOOSEN UP, BABY.
- OH YEAH.
- BEEN A WHILE SINCE
WE GOT LUCKY,
BUT TONIGHT
WE HIT THE JACKPOT.
( chuckles )
HEY, CHILL OUT.
YOU'LL GET YOUR TURN
AFTER I'M DONE.
- HUH?
- CHILL, I SAID!
HUH?
UH...
( grunting )
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
WHOA!
- HELP!
- ( all grunting )
- HOW CAN I THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME LIKE THAT?
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- HOLD ON.
I'M NOT THE ONE
TO THANK FOR THAT.
YOUR KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOR
IS MR. BUTTINSKY HERE.
- OH.
( chuckles )
- HUH?
- WHAT?  ARE YOU SERIOUS?
BRANDON HAS A CRUSH ON HER?
ARE YOU SURE, HARRY?
- YEP.  ABSOLUTELY
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IT WAS LOVE
AT FIRST SIGHT.
- YOU'RE IN LOVE?
- COME ON, FESS UP, PAL.
HARRY'S AN EXPERT
ON WOMEN AND LOVE
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
MIGHT AS WELL ADMIT IT.
- ( sighs )
- ( chuckles )
- TELL ME,
JUST WHO IS SHE?
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
- HER NAME IS MARIA.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL AND GRACEFUL.
KIND OF SLIM.
MY AGE OR OLDER.
- Both: YOU DON'T SAY?
- HOW DO YOU THINK
SHE FEELS, HARRY?
- MY GUT FEELING IS...
IF HE'S NICE TO HER,
IF HE DOESN'T GIVE UP,
YEAH, I THINK SHE'LL
GO OUT WITH HIM.
- Both: SHE WILL?!
- ASK HER OUT,
YOU HEAR ME?!
( groans ) DIDN'T YOU HEAR
WHAT HARRY SAID?
YOU GOT A CHANCE WITH THIS GIRL.
- KENNY, TAKE YOUR SHOES OFF.
- SHE LIKES YOU.
SHE'LL GO ON A DATE WITH YOU.
- COME ON, KENNY.
- ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS ASK!
- EXCUSE ME?
- All: HMM?
- UM, SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I, UH--
WELL...
THIS IS FOR YOU, BRANDON.
- HUH?
- I BAKED YOU A PIE
TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HELP THAT NIGHT.
IF YOU'D LIKE,
I'M SURE THERE'S ENOUGH
FOR EVERYONE.
- UH...
YEAH.
- HMM.
YOU SEE?
- Both: BINGO!
- HUH?
UH...
- WELL?
- TOO FAR AWAY TO TELL.
- LET'S GET CLOSER.
- IT'S A LOVELY DAY.
- YEAH.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT'S HE WAITING FOR?
SHE WANTS HIM TO KISS HER.
ANY FOOL CAN SEE THAT.
- ( gasps )
- KISS HER, WILL YOU?
( kisses )
- KENNY...
- BRANDON WILL
HANDLE IT HIS WAY.
- All: HMM?
- HE HAS HIS OWN STYLE,
HIS OWN WAY
OF DOING THINGS.
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO
BE LIKE US OR ANYONE ELSE.
- HE'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
- BRANDON'S JUST BRANDON.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
- ( whistles )
- ( grunts )
I'M AFRAID WE DIDN'T
MAKE MUCH OF A PROFIT TODAY.
THIS IS ALL I COULD GET.
( sighs )
HERE YOU GO.
- ( both chew )
- HEY, BRANDON?
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHY DON'T YOU GET YOURSELF
A REAL JOB?
THAT OLD MAN,
MARIA'S UNCLE,
DOESN'T LIKE US.
IF YOU'RE REAL SERIOUS
ABOUT MARIA,
REINVENT YOURSELF.
GET YOURSELF
A DECENT JOB.
LEAD AN HONEST LIFE.
YOU CAN DO IT, BRANDON.
- AND YOU?
- WHO, ME?
( chuckles )
NO, THANKS.
I LIKE MY LIFE JUST FINE.
I'LL TEAM UP WITH
KENNY AND THE OTHER GUYS,
PULL A FEW JOBS,
DAZZLE THE LADIES,
AND CON THEM
OUT OF THEIR MONEY.
THE USUAL STUFF.
SO WHAT IF THEY
CALL US PUNKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T CARE.
I'M FREE.
AND THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
YES, SIR.
JUST FINE.
- ME TOO.
- HMM?
- I'M FINE WITH
THE WAY THINGS ARE.
- ( sighs )
( chuckles )
I GUESS MARIA'S IN
FOR ONE HELL OF A RIDE.
- ( all laughing )
- IT'S TRUE.
HE'D NEVER DONE IT.
HE HAD NO IDEA WHERE
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO GO.
- ( all laugh )
- BUT HE ACTS LIKE
HE'S REAL COOL AND SAYS
"DON'T MAKE ME
COME OVER THERE."
I SURE HOPE NOT!
- ( spits, laughs )
- WHAT A WEIRDO.
- REAL TOUGH GUY.
- HEY, YOU GUYS HUNGRY?
WELL?
- PROBLEM IS, HE'S 5'3"
AND COULDN'T PUNCH HIS WAY
THROUGH A STRONG WIND.
- THAT WAS SO DAMN FUNNY.
- ( laughing )
I LAUGHED SO HARD
I COULD BARELY MOVE.
- I HEAR YOU.
- WELL... ( sighs )
- HEY, WHERE YOU GOING, HARRY?
WHY YOU LEAVING SO EARLY?
BECAUSE YOU MADE ME
LAUGH SO DAMN HARD,
IT GAVE ME A HEADACHE.
I'LL CATCH YOU
LOWLIFES LATER.
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU DRINK TOO MUCH
OR SOMETHING?
- THESE ARE NON-ALCOHOLIC
DRINKS.
- OH YEAH.  THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( all laughing )
- ( sighs )
- ( boys chattering )
- ( chuckles )
- ( faucet running )
- ( sighs )
( gasps )
- ( stammers )
( exhales )
- I HATE THAT UGLY BASTARD.
- ( gasps )
- WHO DOES HE THINK HE IS,
TRYING TO RUN HIS OPERATION
ON OUR TURF?
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME...
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM,
ALL RIGHT?
HE'S JUST GOT
A LOT OF HOT AIR,
AND HIS GUYS ARE NOTHING.
WE'RE GONNA FLATTEN HIM.
COME ON, BRANDON.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
- HUH?
( sighs )
HMM?
OH...
( inhales sharply )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( chuckles )
( laughs )
- ( laughing )
- LET'S GO, BRANDON.
- YEAH.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Grave: WERE WE WRONG?
DID WE MAKE THE WRONG
DECISION AFTER ALL?
I CAN'T SEEM TO REMEMBER
WHEN THINGS STARTED TO
TAKE A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
IN THE END,
IT TURNED OUT LIKE THIS.
STILL.