( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
Nathan: JOLICE...
- Kenny: THIS CAN'T BE...
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- Nathan: I'M SORRY, JOLICE...
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
THIS NEVER WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF I DIDN'T ASK YOU
TO GET DINNER READY!
- Kenny: WHO DID IT?
WHO THE HELL KILLED HIM?
- Harry: THIS WASN'T A ROBBERY.
A THIEF WOULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
ANYONE HAD REASON TO KILL
A SHY, GENTLE GUY LIKE JOLICE.
WHICH MEANS HE WASN'T
THE TARGET.
THEY WERE LOOKING FOR US.
WE'RE THE ONES THEY'RE AFTER.
- Kenny: BUT, WHY?
WHO THE HELL IS IT?
- Nathan: WE JUST GOT
THE CRAP BEAT OUT OF US
SAVING YOUR SORRY
ASS, REMEMBER?
SO DON'T TRY TELLING US
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHO IT IS.
- Kenny: YOU SAYING
IT'S MY FAULT?
- Harry: WHO GIVES A DAMN WHY?
WE GOTTA RUN.
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
- Brandon: JOLICE IS GONE...
IN THIS CITY WHERE DEATH
IS EVERYONE'S NEIGHBOR,
HIS DEATH WAS JUST
A COMMONPLACE, ORDINARY THING.
- Woman 1: I KNEW THIS WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN SOONER OR LATER.
- Man: IT'S SHAMEFUL. HE WAS
JUST A KID FOR PETE'S SAKE.
- Woman 2: HIS FRIENDS ARE
UNLIKE THE OTHER PUNKS IN TOWN.
THEY ARE ALWAYS POLITE TO US.
- Woman 3:
THE KID WHO WAS MURDERED,
WASN'T HE THE REALLY QUIET ONE?
POOR THING...
- Woman 4:
IT'S AWFUL.
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD JUST
ISN'T SAFE ANY MORE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THE MONEY, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT,
I'M COUNTING ON YOU!
- ( chuckles )
THAT BASTARD HARRY
MUST BE SHAKING IN
HIS BOOTS RIGHT ABOUT NOW!
YEAH, HE AND HIS GANG
ARE RUNNING SCARED.
I WISH I COULD SEE
THE LOOK ON THE COWARD'S FACE.
- LISTEN, YOU IDIOT.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO GOT THE CRAP
BEAT OUT OF HIM BY THOSE COWARDS
WHO RAN AWAY JUST 'CAUSE ONE
OF THEIR FRIENDS GOT KILLED.
- ER, WELL, I UH...
- WELL, THEN WHY DON'T YOU
DO IT YOURSELF?
FOR A CHANGE.
INSTEAD OF COUNTING ON
OTHERS TO DO IT FOR YOU!
BESIDES, I HAVE SOME BUSINESS
OF MY OWN TO TAKE CARE OF.
- BUT, I MEAN, I...
- DON'T DO ANYTHING TO DRAW
ANYONE'S ATTENTION, ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'LL COOPERATE.
I'VE BEEN EXPECTING YOU.
JUST ONE THING.
I NEED TO TAKE
A LITTLE SIDE TRIP.
- HAVING A BAD DAY?
- NOT JUST BAD.
A FREAKIN' NIGHTMARE.
ONE OF MY GUYS
GOT MURDERED TODAY.
- I KNOW. HELL, EVERYBODY DOES.
- IT'S ALL OVER TOWN.
- WHO DID IT?
COME ON. YOU KNOW I'M NOT NICE
ENOUGH TO TELL YOU FOR FREE...
- ( thuds )
- WELL, SEEING AS YOU'RE
SUCH AN OLD FRIEND,
BAD NEWS HARRY.
LADD IS BACK.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT! DEED'S BIG
BROTHER IS BACK IN TOWN AGAIN.
- I THOUGHT HE WAS DEAD.
- YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN DREAMING.
THIS JUST IN.
"MAD DOG LADD" HAS COME BACK
AND NOW,
HE'S A MADE MAN,
A MEMBER OF THE MAFIA.
- HUH?
- IT'S WHAT YOU'D CALL
YOUR WORST CASE SCENARIO.
- ( men laughing )
- YOU BASTARD!
SO YOU SOLD ME OUT!
- UNDER DURESS.
SO DON'T HOLD IT AGAINST ME.
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL.
- HEY, GET BACK HERE.
- YOU SON OF A BITCH.
GO AHEAD, RUN.
I HOPE YOU DIE LIKE A DOG!
- HIS NAME IS LADD CARABEL.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT
HE'S AN EXPERT
AND HE WORKS WITH
SPEED AND PRECISION.
- WHERE IS HE?
- THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
- FIND HIM NO MATTER WHAT.
- OH, I'M SO HUNGRY...
- HARRY WILL GET BACK SOON.
HANG IN THERE.
HE'LL FIND A WAY
TO GET US OUT OF THIS.
HE ALWAYS DOES, RIGHT?
WITH HARRY AND
BRANDON ON OUR SIDE,
WE'LL GET OUT OF THIS MESS.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
SCREW IT UP.
- YOU BASTARD,
SAY ONE MORE WORD...
- KNOCK IT OFF.
- ( stomach growling )
- I CAN EVEN GET MAD.
I'M TOO HUNGRY.
- HEY, IT'S HARRY!
- ALL RIGHT! LET'S EAT.
- HEY, GUYS...
- HARRY! WHAT HAPPENED!
- THAT SON OF A BITCH, SCOTT,
HE SOLD US OUT.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU TAKING ABOUT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
HEY, HARRY!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HARRY!
- Harry: MAD DOG LADD...
DEED'S BIG BROTHER.
HE CAME BACK.
- ( tires screeching )
- BAD NEWS. REAL BAD NEWS.
- THEN, JOLICE, IT WAS HIM?
- DEED WANTS TO GET BACK AT US
BUT HE'S TOO SCARED.
SO WE WENT AND WHINED
TO HIS BROTHER.
- ( groans )
- WHAT IS IT? WHAT'S WRONG?
- HIT IN THE SIDE...
HURTS LIKE A SON OF A BITCH.
- SHIT! HOW ARE WE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE?
WHAT DO WE DO?
- ( thunder rumbles )
- HOW CAN I HELP YOU, SIR?
- ( gun shots firing )
- ( all gasp )
- GOOD EVENING TO YOU,
DR. TOKIOKA.
FIRST I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR IGNORING US,
REFUSING TO ACKNOWLEDGE
OUR REQUEST.
OH, I SEE. YOU'RE WELL PREPARED.
THAT'S ADMIRABLE.
BUT THIS IS ENEMY TERRITORY,
WE'LL HAVE TO GO SOMEWHERE
ELSE FOR A LITTLE CHAT.
AFTER ALL, YOU'RE SO YOUNG.
MUCH TOO YOUNG TO DIE.
SO I'M SURE YOU WON'T MIND
COMING WITH US?
DON'T FORGET TO SAY THANKS
TO THE BIG BOSS FOR ME.
NOW I CAN DO WHATEVER
THE HELL I WANT
AS LONG AS I STAY
OUT OF HIS WAY.
HURRY UP, WILL YOU?
IF IT TAKES TOO LONG,
MILLENNION WILL FIND OUT.
( chuckles )
- DON'T DO IT, BRANDON.
YOU'LL END UP LIKE ME.
HOW CAN I EXPLAIN...
I WAS KIDDING MYSELF, I SUPPOSE.
NO WORK ALL PLAY, PARTYING WITH
MY BUDDIES ALL NIGHT,
CONNING WOMEN
TO GET THEIR MONEY,
SPENDING IT ON WHATEVER
I WANTED.
THERE WOULD ALWAYS BE MORE
WHENEVER I NEEDED IT.
AS LONG AS I KEPT
PAYING MY DUES
TO THE BIG BOSS OF
THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
NO ONE GAVE ME ANY GRIEF.
I'VE BEEN A PUNK, A ROGUE
AND A SCOUNDREL
FOR TOO LONG TO
BE ANYTHING ELSE.
AND THE FUNNY THING IS,
I THOUGHT THIS WAS THE ONLY
WAY I COULD FIND THE FREEDOM
THAT I WANTED.
- ( groans )
- HARRY!
- BRANDON...
I WANT US ALL TO BE FREE.
- WE WILL BE, HARRY.
- I DON'T WANNA DIE.
- WE'LL SURVIVE.
ALL OF US.
- THAT'S GREAT. I HOPE SO.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- I'VE SEEN THAT DUDE BEFORE.
- HEY, THAT'S BRANDON,
ONE OF HARRY'S GUYS.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- LET'S SEE WHERE HE GOES.
WE CAN SELL THE INFO TO DEED
AND SCORE SOME GREEN.
- YEAH.
- YOU THINK THAT GUY
COULD HAVE DONE THIS?
- REPORT IT TO BIG DADDY.
- RIGHT AWAY, SIR.
- ( thunder crashing )
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOU AND YOUR BUDDIES.
YOU PLANTED THE SEED,
SO YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE CONSEQUENCES.
BUT I DON'T WANT MARIA
INVOLVED IN THIS.
IT'S NOT RIGHT COMING TO ME
JUST 'CAUSE YOU HAVE NO
ONE ELSE TO TURN TO.
- USE THIS.
- YOU WANT TO SURVIVE, THEN
LEAVE TOWN. RIGHT NOW, TONIGHT.
AND FORGET ABOUT MARIA.
BRANDON, YOU LOVE HER,
DON'T YOU?
STAY HERE AND YOU'LL DIE AND
HER HEART WILL DIE WITH YOU.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND? YOU CAN
ONLY CAUSE HER UNHAPPINESS.
I'VE NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
AND ALL I WANT FOR HER,
IS A LIFE
FILLED WITH ONLY HAPPINESS.
- ( gun shot fires )
- ( baby crying )
- TAKE THIS. I ASSUME
YOU KNOW HOW TO USE IT.
SURVIVE. FOR MARIA'S SAKE
AS WELL AS YOUR OWN.
- ( tires screech )
- WELL, LOOK HERE, IT'S BRANDON.
- BRANDON'S A PRETTY TOUGH DUDE.
HE'LL BE OKAY.
SHOULDN'T WE WAIT
UNTIL HE GETS BACK.
- YOU IDIOT! BRANDON
WOULDN'T HAVE A CHANCE
AGAINST MAD DOG LADD.
HE'S A PSYCHO KILLING MACHINE.
- THAT ASSHOLE...
- BUT NOBODY KNOWS
WHERE BRANDON WENT,
SO HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO FIND HIM?
- I DON'T THINK IT'S
REAL HARD TO GUESS
WHERE HE'S GOING
TO END UP TONIGHT.
OH, AT MARIA'S HOUSE!
- MOVE OVER, OLD MAN.
YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE, THAT SHOULD DO IT.
- YOU'RE GONNA PAY
FOR MAKING A FOOL OUT OF ME.
THAT'S RIGHT. I FOUND OUT.
LET'S GET ONE THING STRAIGHT.
THIS IS NO TOY
LIKE THE LAST TIME.
IT'S THE REAL DEAL.
- MARIA...
MARIA...
- SAY GOODBYE
- ( gun shot fires )
- ( groaning )
- GET LOST! AND DON'T EVER
COME NEAR HIM AGAIN!
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING, OLD MAN?
- ( gun shots firing )
- GO!
THE NEXT GOS THROUGH
YOUR HEART!
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL
"PUTTING YOUR PAST TO GOOD USE."
- ( gun shots firing )
- WE FOUND HIM, SIR.
- TAKE ME TO HIM.
HIGHLY SKILLED,
EX-MILITARY, PERHAPS.
OR A RETIRED POLICEMAN,
OR EVEN MORE LIKELY, ONE OF US.
MY POOR LITTLE BROTHER,
HE'S SO DAMN PITIFUL.
I TRIED TO LET HIM
TAKE THE CREDIT
FOR KILLING YOU, BRANDON.
- ( grunts )
- MARIA...
TELL MARIA THAT I'M SORRY.
MARIA...
- HEY...
HEY, YOU.
I'M TALKING TO YOU!
I THINK IT'S TIME TO HAVE
A LITTLE FUN.
- BRANDON. NO!
- OH, MY! LOOK WHO'S HERE.
LONG TIME NO SEE, HARRY BOY.
- YOU BASTARD...
- YOU'RE JUST IN TIME TO SAVE
YOUR FRIEND A WHOLE LOT OF PAIN.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TORTURE HIM
UNTIL HE TOLD ME WHERE YOU WERE.
EVER SO RARE
IS TRUE FRIENDSHIP, RIGHT?
- PLEASE. JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE FIGHT
WITH DEED AND HIS GUYS.
IT WAS MY FAULT
AND I APOLOGIZE.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
PLEASE, FORGIVE ME.
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
- ( gun shots firing )
- OH, SHIT, BRANDON!
YOU CRAZY SON OF A BITCH.
- HEY KENNY, GIVE ME YOUR GUN!
- WHAT? BUT NATHAN, IT WON'T...
I MEAN IT'S NOT...
- MAD DOG!
NOW YOU'RE GONNA DIE,
YOU CRAZY BASTARD.
- ( gun clicks )
- WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
THIS IS JUST A TOY!
- ( gun shot fires )
- ( both gasping )
- ( screams )
- NATHAN! NATHAN!
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO LOOK COOL...
- I TRIED TO TELL YOU...
- STUPID.
- REAL STUPID.
- ( gun shot fires )
- KENNY!
- DON'T WORRY, THERE'S NO RUSH.
I'LL PUT YOU OUT
OF YOUR MISERY SOON.
- ( tires screeching )
- IS YOUR NAME LADD CARABEL?
- WAIT A SEC.
YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
HEY, YOU'RE BEAR WALKEN,
AREN'T YOU?
( chuckles ) ISN'T THIS
A TREAT!
ONE OF MILLENNION'S TOP EXECS
HAS COME TO PAY A
VISIT TO ME IN PERSON.
- MILLENNION?
- BIG DADDY ISN'T GONNA
LIKE THIS.
WE NEED TO SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- THAT'S WHAT I WANT TOO.
WHAT I DID WAS PERSONAL, IT HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH OPERATIONS
IN MY TERRITORY
OR THE WAY I RAM THEM.
WHETHER I GO BACK WILLINGLY
OR NOT WON'T CHANGE THE OUTCOME.
I'M SURE THAT A
MADE GUY LIKE YOU
KNOWS THE PROTOCOLS
OF THE ORGANIZATION
ALL TOO WELL.
WELL, THE, AT LEAST LET ME
PICK MY OWN PLACE TO DIE.
- ( gun shots firing )
- GUYS LIKE YOU,
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
ANSWER ME!
- ( chuckles ) WOULD YOU
IF YOU WERE ME?
- NO, I WOULDN'T.
- THEN YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY I WON'T.
- I SEE. I SHOULD HAVE
EXPECTED AS MUCH.
YOU CAN TAKE REVENGE
FOR YOUR FRIENDS.
- ( screams )
- ( gun shot fires )
- THIS AREA
WILL HAVE TO BE CLEANED UP.
I LEAVE THAT TO YOU.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THE YOUNG LADY.
BUNCH OF STUPID,
HELPLESS BRATS.
- UNCLE?
UNCLE?
- ( police siren wailing
in the distance )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE'S MY BROTHER?
- YOUR BROTHER'S NO LONGER
WITH US, I'M AFRAID.
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
PLEASE, WAIT. JUST HOLD ON.
HE ACTED ON HIS OWN!
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
THE THINGS HE DID!
THAT'S THE TRUTH!
I'M INNOCENT!
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME!
NO! NO, DON'T. I BEG YOU.
NO, DEED.
YOU'RE NOT INNOCENT.
YOU ROBBED US OF MANY THINGS
WE CARED ABOUT.
BUT I... WON'T ROB YOU.
I WILL GIVE, NOT TAKE.
AND THE GIFT THAT I WILL GIVE
IS DEATH!
- ( gun shot fires )
- Brandon: LIFE AND DEATH ARE
LIKE TWO SIDES OF A COIN.
EACH OF US CAN TAKE,
AND EACH OF US CAN GIVE.
AND THE UNSEEN FORCE
THAT DECIDES
WHO WILL GIVE AND WHO WILL TAKE
POURS OVER EVERYONE
WITHOUT DISCRIMINATION.
JUST LIKE THIS RAIN.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: THE BELLS OF
REQUIEM ARE RINGING.
THE BELLS OF REGRET.
THE BELLS OF SADNESS.
AND THE RINGING OF THOSE BELLS
MAYBE AN INDICATION OF WHAT
THE FUTURE HOLDS FOR US ALL.