( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- ( monitor beeping )
- ( laughs )
- Bunji: IF YOU ASK ME, IT
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE LIGHTNING'S
GONNA MAKE A MOVE.
SEEMS LIKE ALL THESE RUMORS
ABOUT THEM GETTING READY
TO WAGE WAR AGAINST MILLENNION,
COULD HAVE BEEN A FALSE ALARM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I GUESS BLOOD WAR DIDN'T LIVE
UP TO HIS REPUTATION, DID HE?
HEY BRO?
- ARE YOU READY FOR THIS LITTLE
BUDDY? WE'LL HAVE TO SEE.
- IT'S BLOOD WAR!
- NOW, LET'S BEGIN...
THE WAR.
- ( people screaming )
- ( maniacal laughter )
MILLENNION...
FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
THIS IS OUR BATTLEFIELD!
- ( tire screeches )
- ( horn honks )
- YOU'RE BLOCKING THE
ROAD, YOU STUPID BASTARD!
- YOU BASTARDS!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- BOSS RUN PLEASE...
YOU GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE...
- HEY YOU GUYS! WHAT THE
HELL! NO, DON'T!
- HARRY! I JUST HEARD CARLOS
AND IRVINE WERE TAKEN OUT!
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THOSE GUYS WERE BOTH EXECUTIVES!
THOSE LIGHTNING BASTARDS...
- RIGHT. I AGREE, RANDY. YEAH.
TELL ALL THE EXECUTIVES
TO TIGHTEN UP
THEIR SECURITY RIGHT AWAY.
- WHAT ABOUT BIG
DADDY'S GUARD DETAIL?
- I'VE ALREADY SENT MY
OVER KILLS.
- Big Daddy: DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT
RIGHT NOW IS MARIA.
I WANT BODYGUARDS WATCHING
HER ROUND THE CLOCK.
BE AS DISCREET AS POSSIBLE,
I DON'T WANT HER TO NOTICE.
- Man: DON'T WORRY, MASTER.
IT'S ALREADY BEEN
TAKEN CARE OF, I ASSURE YOU.
- Man: HARRY, A CASINO
MANAGED BY
THE ORGANIZATION WAS ATTACKED!
SO WAS A WAREHOUSE THAT IT
USES AS A DISTRIBUTION CENTER!
- Harry: DAMN IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE
INVOLVING ORDINARY PEOPLE!
THAT BASTARD, BLOOD WAR!
I SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN RID
OF HIM WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
- HARRY, HUSSAN IS ON THE LINE!
SAYS LIGHTNING JUST GOT THERE.
- ALL RIGHT. TELL HIM
TO KILL THOSE BASTARDS.
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- TOUGH SHIT GUYS!
- ( gunshots )
- HUSSAN'S ENTIRE OFFICE
WAS WIPED OUT?
- YES, SIR. NO SURVIVORS.
THEY'RE ALL DEAD.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS! WE SENT
25 OF OUR BEST GUYS THERE!
- AND THERE WERE NO LIGHTNING
MEN AMONG THE DEAD?
- NO, NOT ONE.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE LIGHTNING
IS USING A BUNCH OF GUYS
JUST AS GOOD AS BRANDON.
- NO WAY LEE, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- Harry: HEY BOB!
YOU SAID BLOOD WAR IS IN COMMAND
OF A 23 MAN CREW, RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT AND
THE INFORMATION
IS ACCURATE TOO.
BELIEVE ME, HARRY!
- WE'VE HAD OVER 70 GUYS,
INCLUDING TWO EXECUTIVES,
KILLED SO FAR.
WE WERE WELL PREPARED BUT THEY
STILL CAUGHT US BY SURPRISE.
WHICH MEANS WE GOT A LEAK
SOMEWHERE, BIG TIME.
ON TOP OF THAT, THEY HAD NO
PROBLEM OVERPOWERING US
EVEN THOUGH WE OUTNUMBERED THEM.
SO, LIGHTNING MUST
HAVE A SECRET.
LIGHTNING, A MINOR PLAYER...
SUDDENLY DECIDES TO WAGE AN ALL
OUT WAR AGAINST MILLENION,
A WAR THEY THINK THEY CAN WIN.
BECAUSE OF THAT SECRET.
- IF THEY HAD A SECRET
WEAPON OR SOMETHING,
DON'T YOU THINK I'D
KNOW ABOUT BY NOW?
- Harry: EXACTLY MY POINT.
YOU'RE THE BEST THERE IS
AND IF YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE UP TO,
THEN NOBODY DOES
AND WE'RE FLYING BLIND.
- ( phone rings )
- YEAH?
- Jude: HARRY, IT'S ME.
- IS THAT YOU, JUDE?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- LIGHTNING, THEY WIPED
OUT ALL OUR GUYS!
- WHAT?
NO MATTER HOW MANY
TIMES WE SHOT AT THEM,
THEY KEPT GETTING UP HARRY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- Harry: THEY MUST BE
WEARING BODY ARMOR,
AIM AT THEIR HEADS AND LEGS!
- WE FIRED OF
THOUSANDS OF ROUNDS.
WE TURNED THEM INTO
SWISS CHEESE AND THEY JUST...
THEY STILL...
- ( gunfire )
- ( Jude screams )
- JUDE? JUDE!
- Gary: DAMN! DAMN!
DAMN, WHY THE HELL DID THOSE
STUPID LIGHTNING A-HOLES
HAVE TO START
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
- KEEP YOUR GUARD UP
AND STOP WHINING!
- OH, SHIT!
THAT NUT CASE BLOOD WAR, IT'S
REALLY GETTING OUT OF HAND!
- BLOOD WAR...
- NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
IT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO CALL MY BATTLEFIELD!
- MARIA, HAVE YOU
HEARD THE LATEST NEWS?
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED?
- NO, WHAT'S UP?
- THEY SAID TWO GROUPS
OF MAFIA GUYS OPENED FIRE
ON EACH OTHER IN WENST!
IT'S GETTING SO DANGEROUS.
I WONDER WHAT THE POLICE
ARE GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
- HEY, BRO. WE'RE
SMACK DAB IN THE MIDDLE
OF LIGHTNING TERRITORY.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL PAINT
A BULLSEYE ON YOUR BACK.
YOU'RE JUST ASKING
TO BE A TARGET.
- Brandon: THAT'S RIGHT.
- ARE YOU NUTS?
OH, YOU HAD GOING ME THERE FOR
A WHILE PAL, YOU REALLY DID.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
- IF YOU ASK ME, THIS IS
GONNA BE A REAL LONG WALK.
I'M DREAMING! RIGHT?
HEY WHAT'S WITH THESE GUYS?
WHY AREN'T THEY GOING DOWN?
- Blood War: LOOKS
LIKE I CAUGHT YOU NAPPING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF MY GUYS?
PRETTY TENACIOUS?
- BLOOD WAR... YOU...
- WELCOME TO THE BATTLEFIELD.
- SHAME ON YOU FOR ALLOWING
A MINOR PLAYER LIKE LIGHTNING
TO MAKE US LOSE FACE.
DO YOU NEED HELP,
HARRY?
- NO SIR, I'M HERE ONLY TO
GIVE A STATUS REPORT,
NOT TO ASK FOR ANYTHING.
EXCEPT THAT YOU ALLOW ME AND
BRANDON HEAT TO CONTINUE
HANDLING
THIS SITUATION.
- TWO EXECUTIVES
HAVE BEEN KILLED!
YOU CALL THAT
HANDLING THE MATTER?
- BICKERING AMONGST OURSELVES
IS A WASTE OF TIME,
WE MUST DEAL WITH
THE MATTER AT HAND.
- FIRST WE MUST
MAINTAIN OUR REPUTATION.
WHICH MEANS OUR LEADERS CAN'T
BE SEEN AS FRIGHTENED OLD MEN.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- HE'S RIGHT MR. ALZAC!
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO
NULLIFY THIS THREAT WITHOUT,
ADMITTING THAT ANYONE
IS STRONG ENOUGH TO THREATEN US.
- Bear: THREE DAYS.
GET IT DONE WITHIN THREE DAYS.
UNDERSTAND?
- UNDERSTOOD.
EVEN IF IT COSTS ME
MY LIFE, SIR.
- Bob: YOU SURE ABOUT THIS BOSS?
I MEAN SHOULDN'T WE ASK
THE FAMILY FOR HELP?
- YOU IDIOT! YOU SHOULD
KNOW THAT I NEVER DO
WHAT I DON'T WANNA DO.
- Bob: YEAH, SURE.
- Harry: HEY, WHAT WOULD YOU
DO IF YOU SAW A DIAMOND
IN THE ROUGH LYING ON THE ROAD?
- I'D PULL OVER AND GRAB IT
OF COURSE. WOULDN'T YOU?
- I'D BE LOOKING FOR THE DIAMOND
MINE WHERE IT CAME FROM.
WHY BE SATISFIED WITH ONLY ONE?
YOU GOT TO THINK OF THE FUTURE,
NOT JUST THE HERE AND NOW.
THINK OF THE FUTURE,
FAR INTO THE FUTURE.
- TELL ME SOMETHING GUYS.
DON'T YOU GET TIRED
OF STANDING IN THAT POSITION?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
SAY SOMETHING?
- DO YOU WANT A SMOKE,
LITTLE BUDDY?
SUIT YOURSELF.
THAT TASTES GOOD...
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE A CIGARETTE
YOU SMOKE IN THE FIRES OF WAR.
SOMEHOW IT MAKES YOU
FEEL MORE ALIVE.
- WHY HAVEN'T YOU KILLED US?
- I'M WONDERING ABOUT THAT TOO.
- WHY ARE YOU OUT
TO GET MILLENNION?
- TELL ME SOMETHING, ARE
YOU THE TYPE WHO ALWAYS
HAS TO HAVE A REASON TO FIGHT?
STOP THINKING ABOUT
THINGS SO MUCH...
AND PAY ATTENTION TO THIS,
THAT'S HOW GUYS
LIKE US STAY ALIVE.
A SENSE OF DUTY, OBLIGATION,
GRATITUDE AND VENGEANCE.
THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE
TO THINK ABOUT.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- THERE'S SOMETHING WE
WANT YOU TO GIVE US.
THE BIG BOSS, HIMSELF.
WE WANT YOU TO BRING
US BIG DADDY'S HEAD.
HEY, STOP GLARING AT ME
LIKE THAT.
I GET IT. YOU'RE COMPLETELY
LOYAL TO YOUR BOSS, RIGHT?
OF COURSE YOU ARE BUT
NOW THINK ABOUT THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN THE WAR'S OVER
AND YOUR BOSS ISN'T
AROUND ANYMORE?
BELIEVE ME, A
YOUNG MAN LIKE YOU
WOULD BE BETTER OFF
WORKING FOR ME.
YOU'VE GOT A CRAVING
FOR CONFLICT...
ACTION...
STIMULATION...
THE HEAT OF THE MOMENT WHEN
YOU'RE RISKING YOUR LIFE.
I WON'T EVER LET YOU GET
BORED. I'LL MAKE YOUR LIFE
MORE THRILLING THAN
IT'S BEEN BEFORE.
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND TOO BAD.
- ( laughs )
I KNEW I WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU!
I KNEW IT ALL ALONG.
COME SEE ME TOMORROW
NIGHT AT MIDNIGHT.
MEET ME AT THE HARBOR.
WAREHOUSE NUMBER 28.
- TILL THEN, NO MORE
ATTACKS, AGREED?
- AGREED, YOU HAVE
MY WORD ON IT.
SEE YOU THEN, KID.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
- SO, WHAT'S UP BRO?
WHAT DID HE WANT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT IS IT BRO?
- Cannon: SETTLE IT WITH ONE
ALL OUT ATTACK?
BLOOD OF THE BATTLEFIELD STYLE?
- Blood War: WHY JUST KILL
A FEW AT A TIME?
THE MORE BODIES WE CAN
LAY OUR HANDS ON,
THE BIGGER OUR
ADVANTAGE, RIGHT?
- SO YOU MEAN, NECROLYZE THEM?
- WE'LL HAVE THE MOST POWERFUL
ARMY IN THE WORLD.
A TOAST TO AMBITION AND SUCCESS.
BRINGS BACK MEMORIES...
CANNON, DO YOU REMEMBER
THE SUNSET THAT DAY?
- SURE. I'LL NEVER FORGET IT.
- Brandon: THIS MAY BE THE
LAST TIME I LAY EYES ON MARIA.
SOMEHOW THE PIERCING
EYES OF BLOOD WAR...
THE MAN THEY CALL THE BLOOD
OF THE BATTLEFIELD...
HAS MADE ME FEEL THIS WAY.
- Man on TV: AFTER TWO LONG DAYS
OF WIDESPREAD VIOLENCE,
THE FEUD BETWEEN TWO MAFIA
ORGANIZATIONS FINALLY SEEMS
TO HAVE COME TO AN END.
HOWEVER, KNOWLEDGEABLE
SOURCES HAVE TOLD US
THAT THEY ARE NOT OPTIMISTIC...
AND THAT THE VIOLENCE MAY
RESUME WITHOUT WARNING.
CITIZENS ARE THEREFORE ADVISED
TO TAKE EXTRA PRECAUTIONS.
- Brandon: I'LL TAKE THIS ONE.
- ARE YOU SURE? THE ONLY
AMMO YOU CAN USE
ON THAT GUN IS .45
CALIBER D POINTS.
SO IT'S NOT A REAL
PRACTICAL WEAPON,
THE KICK IS SO STRONG,
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE...
- AND A COUPLE OF THOUSAND
ROUNDS OF AMMO.
- HUH?
OF COURSE, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
HAPPY TO BE OF SERVICE.
- Bunji: BRANDON AND I
SHOT THEM WITH ENOUGH
LEAD TO SINK A BATTLESHIP.
WE SHOT THEM OVER AND OVER
AGAIN. IN THE HEART, THE HEAD.
THEY JUST KEPT COMING AT US.
- COME ON! THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- GUESS YOU MUST HAVE WATCHED
ONE TOO MANY HORROR MOVIES.
- Bunji: LISTEN YOU MORONS!
I'M NOT KIDDING!
THESE LIGHTNING GUYS ARE TOUGH.
WE CLOSE OUR EYES FOR
A SECOND AND THEY WIN.
- CAN'T BE...
- ( engine revving )
- THAT'S BRANDON'S CAR.
WHERE'S HE GOING?
DON'T TELL ME...
- ( gunshots )
- WHAT A SURPRISE.
SUCH A CLOSE FRIEND
IS A TRAITOR.
BOB WOULD BE DEVASTATED.
- HARRY... HOW DID YOU...
- IT WAS QUITE EASY.
I LOOKED FOR SOME
COMMON DENOMINATOR...
AMONG THE EXECUTIVES THAT
LIGHTNING ATTACKED.
ONLY A FEW OF US KNEW WHERE
THEIR SAFE HOUSES WERE.
SO I LOOKED AT THE PERSONNEL
FILES AND LOW AND BEHOLD,
YOU AND CANNON VULCAN ARE FROM
THE SAME HOMETOWN.
STUPID OF ME NOT TO
HAVE NOTICED IT BEFORE.
- HOW YOU DOING LITTLE BUDDY?
YOU'RE A REAL PUNCTUAL GUY,
I LIKE THAT.
- SO TELL ME, LEE...
WERE YOU LIGHTNING'S SPY
FROM THE GET GO?
- NO, IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
- WHAT'S LIGHTNING HIDING LEE?
WHAT'S THEIR SECRET?
- YOU, HARRY MACDOWEL...
ARE A VERY BRILLIANT
AND AMBITIOUS MAN.
- DON'T CHANGE THE SUBJECT.
- ALRIGHT THEN. IF I TELL
LIGHTNING'S SECRET,
WILL YOU LET ME GO?
- NO, OF COURSE I WON'T. YOU
KNOW THE CONSEQUENCES FOR
THE BREAKING THE CODE OF
IRON AS WELL AS I DO.
THE ORGANIZATION CAN ONLY
OFFER A TRAITOR ONE THING.
AND THAT IS DEATH.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- YOU'RE ALONE? WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT THE HELL IS
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
I TOLD YOU TO BRING YOUR BOSS.
SO WHERE IS HE?
WHERE'S BIG DADDY?
HUH?
YOU TRIED TO PLAY ME, DIDN'T YA?
- Lee: DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU
CAN BEAT ME?
HARRY MACDOWEL!
-TRY ME AND YOU'LL FIND OUT...
BALLADBIRD LEE!
- ( Blood war laughing )
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE YOU OUT FIRST,
AND THEN TURN THE ENTIRE CITY
INTO A BATTLEFIELD!
- Brandon: NO, THE
BATTLEFIELD IS HERE.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- IN A FEW MOMENTS I'LL TURN
THIS PLACE INTO A BATTLEFIELD.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: WHY DO I BELONG
TO THE ORGANIZATION?
WHY DO I PULL THE TRIGGER?
SCREAMING AS I FACE
SOMETHING INHUMAN.
BECAUSE THIS IS MILLENION,
THE CODE OF IRON.