- ( theme music plays )
- Mika: MOM, DAD,
MR. TOKIOKA,
DOCTOR, WIDGE, GARY.
FROM NOW ON,
NO MORE CRYING.
NO MORE TEARS.
( sobs )
( cries )
WAIT, WHAT NOW?
ANOTHER BATTLE?
DON'T GO.
IT'S ENOUGH.
NO MORE REVENGE.
DON'T GO, GRAVE.
STAY, PLEASE.
STAY WITH ME.
- Harry: AN EMERGENCY EXECUTIVE
MEETING AT THIS HOUR?
YOU ALL MUST BE
EXTREMELY BUSY.
SO LET'S CUT
TO THE CHASE, SHALL WE?
WHAT DID YOU
WANT TO DISCUSS?
- BOSS, YOU KNOW VERY WELL
WHY WE'RE HERE.
BOB POUNDMAX
AND BALLADBIRD LEE,
OUR INFORMANTS TELL US
THAT THEY WERE BOTH
KILLED BY THE TARGET.
- AND BUNJI KUGASHIRA
HAS VANISHED.
SO THREE OF YOUR CLOSEST AIDES
ARE EITHER DEAD OR MISSING.
- IT'S CAUSED
A LOT OF CONFUSION
REGARDING THE CHAIN OF COMMAND.
- AH, SO THAT'S IT.
YEAH, I GUESS
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
MY NEW PERSONAL AIDES
WILL BE CHOSEN
FROM AMONG THE MEN
SITTING AT THIS TABLE.
BRILLIANT AND USEFUL MEN
WILLING TO DEMONSTRATE
THEIR LOYALTY
AND COMMITMENT
TO THE ORGANIZATION
BY BECOMING SUPERIORS.
- BOSS,
PERHAPS THIS MIGHT
BE THE RIGHT TIME
FOR YOU TO STEP DOWN.
OUR TARGET IS BRANDON HEAT,
A FORMER SWEEPER
OF THE ORGANIZATION
AND YOUR CLOSEST FRIEND.
- WHEN YOU FOUND OUT
HE WAS A TRAITOR,
YOU KILLED HIM.
- BOSS, WE BELIEVE
THAT BRANDON HEAT
WANTS ONLY ONE
THING, REVENGE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IT'S YOU HE WANTS TO DESTROY.
NOT THE ORGANIZATION.
- SO THERE'S NO NEED FOR
THE ORGANIZATION TO BE INVOLVED.
ONCE YOU TWO SETTLE
YOUR DIFFERENCES,
THE CONFLICT WILL
BE OVER WITH,
WHICH IS WHY THIS MIGHT
BE THE RIGHT TIME.
- Harry: IS THIS A MUTINY?
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
WE'RE ONLY TRYING TO PROTECT
THE ORGANIZATION.
- YES, I UNDERSTAND PERFECTLY.
I BELIEVE IN PROTECTING
THE ORGANIZATION
AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
ALLOW ME TO GIVE YOU
A DEMONSTRATION.
- AN ORGMAN!
WHAT THE HELL?!
- ( guns click )
- ( men groan )
- ( bullets fire )
( gunfire stops)
- ( whimpers )
- ( guns click )
- THERE NOW.
I THINK THAT SHOULD
CLEAR UP ANY CONFUSION
REGARDING
THE CHAIN OF COMMAND.
BISCOE, STICK AROUND.
WHEN I'VE CHOSEN
THESE REPLACEMENTS,
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
THE REST OF YOU,
PUT ALL YOUR EFFORTS
INTO FINDING THE TARGET.
WELL, LET'S GET GOING, BEAR.
YOU AND I HAVE
A LUNCH-DATE WITH SHERRY.
- ONE OF MILLENNION'S
BIG FOUR ONCE SAID
THAT YOU WERE--
WELL, NOT YOU,
BUT THE YOU THAT
WAS BRANDON HEAT.
THEY SAID THAT BRANDON HEAT
AND MY MOM WERE IN LOVE.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
I'M HER DAUGHTER,
BUT I THINK I'M FINALLY
BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND
WHY SHE FELL IN LOVE
WITH YOU...
AND NEVER STOPPED
LOVING YOU.
GRAVE, I--
I DON'T WANT
YOU TO DISAPPEAR.
LET'S GO SOMEWHERE.
SOMEPLACE FAR AWAY,
SO FAR AWAY THE ORGANIZATION
CAN'T FIND US,
JUST THE TWO OF US TOGETHER.
PLEASE.
WHY'D YOU TURN HER DOWN?
WHY'D YOU DISTANCE
YOURSELF FROM MY MOM?
- I'LL BE YOUR GUARDIAN.
- ( gasps )
- I'LL PROTECT YOU,
BUT THAT IS ALL I CAN DO.
- BUT WHY?!
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE!
( cries )
I DON'T GET IT AT ALL.
- ( cutlery clinks )
- I APPRECIATE EVERYTHING
YOUR FATHER'S DONE
FOR THE ORGANIZATION.
BUT HE'S DONE ENOUGH
AND NOW HE SHOULD RETIRE
AND RELAX FOR A WHILE.
TELL HIM IT'S THE RIGHT THING
TO DO, WILL YOU, HONEY?
- HE'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE DONE ENOUGH.
- NOT AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED.
BESIDES, I'VE BEEN
DOING IT FOR SO LONG,
I CAN'T IMAGINE
DOING ANYTHING ELSE.
I KNOW IT'S UNREASONABLE,
BUT I'VE ASKED HARRY TO LET ME
KEEP WORKING FOR A WHILE.
- YES, YOU TOOK
THE HUMBLE APPROACH.
- BY THE WAY, HARRY,
I'M STILL WAITING
TO SEE MY GRANDCHILD.
NOT TOO MUCH LONGER, I HOPE.
- WE'RE STILL TRYING.
IN FACT, WE TRY ALL THE TIME.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, DEAR?
- HARRY, BEHAVE YOURSELF.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE SAYING
THINGS LIKE THAT
IN FRONT OF MY FATHER.
- ( phone vibrates )
- HMM?
- ( beeps )
- GO AHEAD.
YEAH.
YEAH, RIGHT.
- ( beeps )
- SOME BORING LITTLE
BUSINESS DEAL.
SORRY I HAVE TO LEAVE
SO SUDDENLY.
- OH, DADDY, WHAT A SHAME.
THE THREE OF US HAVEN'T
GOTTEN TOGETHER LIKE THIS
IN SUCH A LONG TIME.
- WE'LL DO IT
ANYTIME YOU LIKE.
ANYTIME AT ALL, RIGHT?
- THAT'S THE OTHER SIDE
OF HUMAN NATURE.
- HMM, WHAT, HARRY?
- OH, NOTHING.
IT WASN'T IMPORTANT.
- ( car approaches )
- WELL, HOW'S IT GOING?
- SO FAR SO GOOD, SIR.
THE TARGET'S STILL IN THERE.
- THANK YOU.
EXCELLENT WORK.
- THE OVERKILLS ARE
ON STANDBY ALERT
AWAITING YOUR ORDERS, SIR.
WE'LL BE READY TO MOVE
THE MINUTE YOU SAY IT'S A GO.
- VERY WELL.
NOW LISTEN, EVERYONE.
AS OF NOW, THE OVERKILLS
ARE HEREBY DISSOLVED.
- ( gasping )
- WHAT?
- ( muttering )
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS, SIR.
- AS I SAID, I'M DISSOLVING
THE OVERKILLS.
FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
YOU'RE FREE TO DO AS YOU WISH.
WHETHER YOU REMAIN
WITH THE ORGANIZATION
OR DECIDE TO TAKE
ANOTHER PATH IS UP TO YOU.
- BOSS.
- I'M COMPLETING THIS
MISSION MYSELF.
AND NOT AS A MEMBER
OF MILLENNION,
BUT AS AN INDIVIDUAL,
AS A MAN.
THE MAN WHO WILL CHALLENGE
BRANDON HEAT.
- ( gasping )
( mutters )
( whispers continue )
- BOSS!
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
THINK ABOUT HOW LUCKY WE WERE
TO HAVE A BOSS LIKE BEAR
AND WHAT WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED IF WE DIDN'T.
THE BOSS DIDN'T LET US
GET TURNED INTO
ORGMEN, DID HE?
FOR THAT REASON ALONE,
WE HAVE TO HONOR
THE BOSS'S FINAL ORDER,
THE LAST ORDER WE'LL EVER GET
FROM BEAR WALKEN.
- ( footsteps approach )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( gasps )
- WE NEED TO TALK.
IT'S A STRANGE FEELING
CARRYING ON A CONVERSATION
WITH SOMEONE
WHO'S ALREADY DIED,
BUT ISN'T DEAD.
IRONIC, ISN'T IT?
WHEN YOU WERE ALIVE,
YOU BARELY SAID A WORD TO ME.
BUT NOW THAT YOU'RE DEAD,
WE'RE TALKING.
THAT GIRL BACK THERE,
BIG DADDY'S LEGACY, I PRESUME?
WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING HER?
HER EXISTENCE WON'T CHANGE
WHAT THE ORGANIZATION
HAS BECOME.
THE MILLENNION
OF BIG DADDY'S DAY IS DEAD.
AND UNLIKE YOU,
IT'S GOING TO STAY THAT WAY.
- WHY?
TELL ME WHY!
- ( whimpers )
- YOU THINK THAT
WHAT I'VE DONE
MAKES ME A TRAITOR,
IS THAT IT?
I'VE APOLOGIZED TO BIG DADDY
COUNTLESS TIMES,
APOLOGIZED FROM
THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
BUT I HAVE NO REGRETS
ABOUT THE CHOICES
I'VE HAD TO MAKE.
NONE AT ALL.
MY DAUGHTER IS WITH HARRY,
HAPPIER THAN
SHE'S EVER BEEN.
AND I HOPE THAT
THEY'LL BE HAPPY TOGETHER
FOR THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
THAT'S WHY
I PROTECT MILLENNION
EVEN WHEN
IT MEANS DOING THINGS
BIG DADDY WOULD HAVE SAID
WERE WRONG.
I HAVE TO PROTECT
HARRY'S MILLENNION.
I CHALLENGE YOU
TO A DUEL.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU
AT MY ESTATE.
I WON'T LET ANYONE FROM THE
ORGANIZATION GET IN YOUR WAY.
YOUNG LADY, I APOLOGIZE
FOR YOUR MOTHER'S DEATH.
- ( gasps )
- WHEN PAINFUL CHOICES ARE MADE,
YOU MUST BE READY TO DEAL
WITH IT THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
- ( gasping )
- ( sniffing )
- Mika: ARE YOU GOING?
YOU KNOW, SOMEHOW,
THAT MAN NAMED BEAR WALKEN--
I JUST CAN'T THINK OF HIM
AS A BAD PERSON.
ARE YOU GOING TO FIGHT HIM?
- ( clicks )
- BUT WHY ARE YOU DOING IT?
- MILLENNION.
BECAUSE WE ARE MILLENNION.
WE ARE MILLENNION ITSELF.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
( cries )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- BEAR, I'M HOPELESSLY DUMB,
EVEN DUMBER
THAN I USED TO BE.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID THAT
LOYALTY TO THE ORGANIZATION
WAS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANYTHING.
BUT WHEN I HAD
A CHANCE TO PROVE IT,
I CHOSE MY SCUMBAG
OF A SON INSTEAD.
WHAT HAPPENS IN MY TERRITORY
INCLUDING HIS CONDUCT
IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
AS A MEMBER OF THE ORGANIZATION
AND AS A FATHER,
I ACCEPT THAT RESPONSIBILITY.
SORRY IF YOU FIND
THIS BOTHERSOME.
- NOW I KNOW
HOW IT FEELS, SID.
I'M DOING THE SAME
THING YOU DID
FOR EXACTLY
THE SAME REASON.
EVEN THOUGH
I KNOW IT'S WRONG,
I HAVE TO DO IT.
I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
HMPH, PATHETIC,
BOTH OF US.
RIGHT, SID?
- ( engine roars )
- ( gasping )
- ( whimpers )
- ( engine roars )
- BEYOND THE GRAVE?
NO.
BRANDON HEAT.
- YOU FOOL.
YOU FOOL.
- ( engine roars )
- HMM.
VERY CONSIDERATE
OF YOU, BRANDON,
BRINGING YOUR OWN COFFIN
TO THE PLACE WHERE
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S WHERE I'LL PUT
YOUR CORPSE WHEN WE'RE DONE.
( grunts )
( growls )
- ( rumbling )
- SO YOU AVOIDED IT.
- ( metal clangs )
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A NEW COFFIN.
TO MAKE SURE YOU WEREN'T
STRONGER THAN ME,
I'VE UNDERGONE
A CERTAIN TREATMENT.
- ( cracking )
- NO.
- I AM NOW A SUPERIOR.
HA!
- ( gunshots )
- ( rumbling )
- ( screams )
- ( whooshing )
- BRILLIANT AS ALWAYS,
BRANDON HEAT.
NEVERTHELESS, I CANNOT
ALLOW YOU TO WIN THIS FIGHT.
- ( grunts )
- ( gun clicks )
- ( growls )
( stretching )
( growls )
( screams )
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
( gags )
( strains )
- ( laughs )
IT'LL BE OVER SOON,
BRANDON HEAT.
- ( strains )
( gags )
- TIME TO RETURN
TO YOUR GRAVE.
REST IN PEACE,
BRANDON HEAT!
- ( screams )
( screams )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunshots )
- ( grunting )
- ( cracking )
- BUT HOW?
WHAT DID YOU--
I SEE.
THIS WAS CUSTOM-MADE,
WASN'T IT?
- ( cracking )
- I WAS STUPID.
THE MOMENT I BECAME
OVERCONFIDENT,
YOU USED IT AGAINST ME.
WELL DONE, BRANDON.
( groans )
BRANDON.
( raspy )
BRANDON HEAT.
FINISH IT.
- ( gun clicks )
- PLEASE.
SHERRY.
- ( gunshot echoes )
- ( cries )
( crying continues )
GRAVE!
( cries )
- ( theme music plays )
- LIKE WINE POURING
INTO CRYSTAL GOBLETS,
BULLETS ARE POURED
INTO MAGAZINES
AS MEN LOAD THEIR WEAPONS.
THE SOUND OF GUNFIRE
INSTEAD OF CELEBRATION.
BODIES EMBRACED BY BULLETS
INSTEAD OF ARMS.