- ( theme music playing )
- Female Announcer:
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY BROADCAST
FROM THE MILLENNION
ORGANIZATION.
MR. BRANDON HEAT,
WE HAVE YOUR COMPANION,
MISS MIKA ASAGI, IN CUSTODY.
YOUR IMMEDIATE PRESENCE
IS REQUIRED AT
SOUTHPORT STATION'S UNDERGROUND
PLATFORM NUMBER THREE.
- DON'T BE IMPATIENT, GRAVE.
- MR. HEAT, SHOULD YOU
FAIL TO APPEAR...
- IT WON'T TAKE LONG.
I NEED JUST A LITTLE MORE TIME.
JUST TWO OR THREE HOURS,
AND YOUR BODY WILL BE
IN OPTIMUM CONDITION.
I KNOW WHERE THE YOUNG LADY
IS BEING HELD.
THOSE ARROGANT
MILLENNION BASTARDS
WENT TO THE TROUBLE
OF MAKING SURE WE'D KNOW.
THIS TIME IT WON'T BE
LIKE IT WAS BEFORE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE ULTIMATE SHOOTOUT.
ALL THE MORE REASON WHY
THE ABILITIES OF BRANDON HEAT,
THE FORMER SWEEPER
OF MILLENNION,
AND THE ABILITIES OF THE
NECROLIZER, BEYOND THE GRAVE...
BOTH NEED TO BE MAXIMIZED.
PLEASE.
DON'T LET ME BE THE CAUSE OF
MORE SUFFERING AND PAIN.
- WHERE-- WHERE AM I?
- THIS IS MILLENNION
CORPORATE HEADQUARTERS.
- ( gasps slightly )
- ( chuckles )
MISS MIKA ASAGI.
HOW NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US.
- SO YOU'RE BALLADBIRD LEE,
RIGHT?
( gasps )
HEY, WHAT DID YOU DO TO THEM?!
TO THOSE TWO OLD MEN?!
- HA.  WHAT ARE YOU
ASKING ME FOR?
YOU WERE THERE, MISS.
YOU SAW ME CUT THEM
INTO PIECES, DIDN'T YOU?
- ( gasps )
THAT WAS... INHUMAN!
- ACTUALLY, YOU'RE QUITE
CORRECT, YOUNG LADY.
FOR YOU SEE,
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
THAT I'M NOT HUMAN ANYMORE.
NOT REALLY.
- ( whimpers )
- ( door opens )
- ( gasps )
- SO... SHE'S THE ONE.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- HOW DO YOU DO, YOUNG LADY?
- BLOODY HARRY!
- WELL NOW,
I GUESS IT WON'T BE NECESSARY
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
- YOU KILLED MY MOTHER
AND MR. TOKIOKA!
- AND YOUR FATHER AS WELL.
- ( gasps )
- OF COURSE IN YOUR FATHER'S
CASE, I DID IT MYSELF.
- I WON'T FORGIVE YOU.
I'LL NEVER EVER FORGIVE YOU!
- MISS ASAGI, BEFORE YOU START
YELLING YOUR HEAD OFF,
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND
YOUR SITUATION.
AT THE MOMENT,
YOU ARE IN OUR CUSTODY.
AND THAT MEANS I CAN END
YOUR EXISTENCE WHENEVER I LIKE.
UNDERSTAND?
- ( gasps )
( whimpers )
NO!
PLEASE HELP ME.
PLEASE, GRAVE.
- WHAT DID YOU CALL HIM?
- I CALLED HIM GRAVE.
HE WAS BRANDON HEAT.
NOW HE'S BEYOND THE GRAVE.
- GRAVE, YOU SAY.
( chuckles )
MY, WHAT AN IMPRESSIVE NAME.
THEN IT WOULD PROBABLY BE
MUCH MORE APPROPRIATE FOR ME
TO CALL HIM BEYOND THE GRAVE
AS WELL.
BESIDES, I WOULDN'T
WANNA CALL HIM BRANDON.
IT WOULD ONLY MAKE ME REMEMBER
THE WAY THINGS USED TO BE.
- HE WILL COME, MISS.
WE'VE TOLD HIM
WHERE TO FIND YOU,
AND I'M SURE HE'LL GET HERE
AS FAST AS HE CAN.
HE REALLY HAS NO CHOICE
IN THE MATTER.
AND WHEN HE SHOWS UP,
THAT'S WHEN I'LL FINALLY
TAKE MY REVENGE.
- YOUR REVENGE?
- FOR MY FRIEND--
MY BEST FRIEND, BOB POUNDMAX.
GRAVE WAS THE ONE
WHO KILLED HIM,
SO NOW I'M GOING
TO RETURN THE FAVOR.
( laughs )
BUT BEFORE I DO,
I'LL MAKE HIM WATCH
AS I CUT YOU TO PIECES.
I'LL SHATTER HIS HEART
AND THEN HIS BODY,
BUT SLOWLY,
A LITTLE AT A TIME...
TILL HE'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A BLOODY OFFERING
FOR THE WORMS TO GORGE ON.
- WERE WE TOO LATE?
BUT...
- BOSS, IS IT TRUE?
YOU LET LEE GO ALONE?
- NOT ALONE.
I HAD HIM TAKE 150 ORGMEN
ALONG WITH HIM.
- BESIDES, LEE HAS THE POWERS
OF A SUPERIOR, RIGHT?
A NECROLIZER LIKE GRAVE
DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
OF DEFEATING HIM.
- WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
WE SHOULD RESOLVE THIS SITUATION
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
SO WHY NOT THROW EVERYTHING
WE'VE GOT AT HIM
AND BURY THE GUY?
- LISTEN, LEE WANTS TO AVENGE
THE DEATH OF HIS BEST FRIEND.
SO LET HIM DO IT.
- BOB IS DEAD,
AND KUGASHIRA IS MISSING.
AT THIS RATE, THE BACKBONE OF
THE ORGANIZATION MAY COLLAPSE.
THERE ARE MORE THAN
A FEW MEMBERS OF THE FAMILY
WHO'VE EXPRESSED ADVERSE
SENTIMENTS ABOUT YOUR...
FORCEFUL STYLE OF MANAGEMENT.
IN THIS CASE, I THINK A MORE
CAUTIOUS APPROACH IS CALLED FOR.
- HA. WE HAVE OUR LOYAL ORGMEN
SERVANTS TO PROTECT US,
DON'T WE?
- OF COURSE.
OUR ORGMEN ARMY IS FAR SUPERIOR
TO MOST NATIONAL MILITIA GROUPS.
BUT THE PROPER FUNCTIONING
OF THIS ORGANIZATION
HAS NEVER DEPENDED
ON FORCE ALONE.
I AM CERTAIN THAT
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
IF LEE SHOULD
LOSE THIS FIGHT,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
GRAVE MYSELF.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
- YOU THINK THERE'S A CHANCE
HE MIGHT LOSE?
- AN UNLIKELY EVENT, I ADMIT.
BUT I INTEND TO BE READY,
JUST IN CASE THE UNLIKELY
SHOULD OCCUR.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
YOU'RE DOING THIS ON BEHALF
OF THE ORGANIZATION?
- YES, I AM.
AS I ALWAYS HAVE...
AND ALWAYS WILL.
- YOU KNOW...
IT JUST OCCURRED TO ME
THAT THIS PLACE
IS ABOUT TO BECOME
GRAVE'S GRAVE.
( laughs )
- EXCUSE ME.
- MM?
- CAN YOU TELL ME
ABOUT MY FATHER?
I NEVER GOT TO MEET HIM.
- YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
I'LL TELL YOU ABOUT HIM
UNTIL YOUR BUDDY GRAVE SHOWS UP.
IT'LL KILL SOME TIME.
BIG DADDY WAS THE TYPE
OF MAN WHO WAS RESPECTED
BY EVERYONE WHO KNEW HIM,
MYSELF INCLUDED.
HE HAD PERSONAL MAGNETISM
AND DIGNITY.
BUT BECAUSE OF
THE TYPE OF MAN HE WAS,
THERE WAS ONE THING
HE WAS LACKING.
IT WAS AMBITION.
HE HAD NO PASSION DRIVING HIM
UP THE LADDER OF SUCCESS.
- THOSE TWO NICE OLD GUYS
TOLD ME...
THAT MY FATHER STARTED
THE MILLENNION ORGANIZATION
TO PROTECT EVERYONE.
- WELL, IT'S HARRY MACDOWEL'S
MILLENNION NOW, NOT YOUR POP'S.
WHEN AN ORGANIZATION
GETS A NEW BOSS,
ITS POLICIES CHANGE.
IT'S SIMPLY THE NATURAL
PROGRESSION OF LIFE.
PERHAPS WHEN BRANDON HEAT
WAS KILLED,
HE DIED A MARTYR'S DEATH,
GIVING HIS LIFE FOR
BIG DADDY'S MILLENNION.
AND NOW I'M READY
TO GIVE MINE.
I'M READY AND WILLING TO DIE
FOR HARRY MACDOWEL'S MILLENNION.
GRAVE MAY SEEM NOBLE TO YOU,
BUT AS FAR AS WE'RE CONCERNED,
HE'S A TRAITOR
TO THE ORGANIZATION
JUST AS HE WAS
WHEN HARRY KILLED HIM.
NOW HE'S COME BACK
FROM THE DEAD, AND WHY?
TO PROTECT THE OFFSPRING
OF MILLENNION'S ENEMY.
( laughs )
HOW IRONIC.
- DON'T LAUGH AT HIM!
HE DESERVES MORE RESPECT
THAN THAT.
- WHY WOULD ANYONE
RESPECT A GUY LIKE THAT?
THE BOSS TOLD ME
ALL ABOUT HIM.
DID YOU KNOW THAT GRAVE
AND YOUR MOTHER MARIA
WERE HEAD OVER HEELS
IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER?
- ( exhales )
- YET HE PROTECTS YOU,
EVEN THOUGH
YOU'RE A CONSTANT REMINDER
THAT THE WOMAN HE LOVED
DUMPED HIM FOR ANOTHER GUY.
HOW CAN I RESPECT A MAN
LIKE THAT?
A DOG HAS MORE PRIDE.
I CAN'T HELP
LAUGHING AT THE GUY.
HE'S PATHETIC.
( chuckles )
- PLEASE STOP LAUGHING.
- ( continues laughing )
- STOP LAUGHING!
- HMM?
YOUR EYES...
THEY'RE JUST LIKE HIS.
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
I THINK OUR GUEST HAS ARRIVED.
HE ENTERS THE PORTAL TO HELL.
LET'S GIVE HIM
A PROPER WELCOME.
- ( Orgmen growling )
- ( screams )
- ( growls )
- ( grunts )
- HE'S FIGHTING
FOR THE ORGANIZATION.
THAT MY DAD CREATED.
FIGHTING FOR MY MOM'S...
AND FOR MINE...
TO PROTECT.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GIVE US A THING.
THAT'S WHAT BEING
A FAMILY IS ALL ABOUT.
AS LONG AS WE DON'T
BETRAY ONE ANOTHER,
WE'LL HAVE A BOND BETWEEN US
THAT CAN NEVER BE BROKEN.
- IF I CAN BECOME--
I WANT TO BECOME...
HIS FAMILY.
- ( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
BEYOND THE GRAVE...
- ( groans )
- THEY SAY YOU WERE
THE BEST SWEEPER
THE ORGANIZATION EVER HAD.
WELL-DESERVED ACCOLADE,
SINCE YOU JUST DESTROYED
150 ORGMEN SINGLEHANDEDLY.
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT,
BRANDON.
SORRY. BEYOND THE GRAVE.
- I KNOW YOU,
BALLADBIRD LEE.
- NOT TO BE INSULTING,
BUT YOU'RE PALE ENOUGH
TO BE BIG DADDY'S GHOST.
THE ONE I FEEL SORRY FOR
IS THE BOSS.
HE'S GONNA START
BAWLING LIKE A BABY
WHEN I TELL HIM HOW MUCH
HIS OLD FRIEND HAS CHANGED--
THE FRIEND
WHO WANTS TO BETRAY HIM.
WHOA.  EASY NOW.
( chuckles )
I HAVE A HOSTAGE, REMEMBER?
- ( gasps )
- ( whimpers )
- VERY WISE CHOICE.
- DON'T GIVE UP, GRAVE.
- THERE'S SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU,
SOMETHING I REALLY NEED
TO KNOW.
ARE YOU RESPONSIBLE
FOR BOB'S DEATH?
IT WAS YOU.
YOU KILLED HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?!
- YAH!
- ( grunts )
- HOW DARE YOU!
HOW DARE YOU.
HOW DARE YOU!
( grunting )
- STOP HURTING HIM!
STOP HURTING HIM!
- YOUNG LADY, STOP SCREAMING.
THE GAME'S JUST BEGUN.
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN THAT
TO KILL A NECROLIZER.
AT LEAST I HOPE SO.
THE LONGER IT TAKES HIM
TO DIE, THE BETTER.
BUT FOR THE MOMENT,
I CAN AT LEAST DO THIS MUCH!
- ( grunts )
( groaning )
- ( laughs )
I WANT YOU TO SUFFER
IN AGONY,
THE SAME WAY I DID
WHEN YOU KILLED MY FRIEND.
BUT FIRST,
I'M GOING TO SHATTER YOUR SPIRIT
AND SHRIVEL YOUR HEART.
OBSERVE.
BIG DADDY'S LITTLE LEGACY--
SO LOVELY, SO ALIVE.
I'LL CUT HER TO PIECES,
AN INCH AT A TIME.
- ( gasps slightly )
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs maniacally )
- NO!
- WHAT THE--?
- LEE!
- DR. TOKIOKA!
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- COME ON, LET'S GO!
HURRY!
- COME BACK HERE!
- ( gunfire )
- AAH!
GRAVE!
BULLETS CAN'T HURT ME,
YOU IDIOT!
YOU BASTARD!
MY, THOSE ARE PUNY WEAPONS.
( laughs )
( screeches )
- ARE YOU DOING
ALL RIGHT THERE, YOUNG LADY?
- YES.  I FEEL FINE, THANKS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
- I MAY HAVE PUSHED MYSELF
A LITTLE TOO HARD,
BUT I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THE ANTI-SUPERIOR AMMO
IS READY.
SO IF YOU'LL GIVE ME
YOUR GUNS--
- ( crashes )
- All: HUH?
- ( laughs maniacally )
SORRY, BUT THE FAT LADY
TOOK THE DAY OFF,
AND THE SHOW ISN'T OVER
UNTIL THE FAT LADY SINGS.
- ( gasps )
AAH!
- ACT ONE, SCENE ONE:
I CUT YOU TO PIECES
AND WATCH YOU DIE!
- HAS SHE PASSED OUT?
IT SHOULD BE ALL RIGHT.
- WHO CARES?
COME ON NOW, FOCUS!
FOCUS!
- ( grunts )
- ( laughs )
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO
DIE AGAIN SO SOON?
THEN AGAIN, IN YOUR CASE,
SINCE YOU'RE ALREADY DEAD...
I SUPPOSE YOU REALLY WOULDN'T
CALL IT DYING, WOULD YOU?
CALL IT WHAT YOU LIKE.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN!
YOU WANT IT, YOU GOT IT!
WHAT THE HELL?
- GRAVE, USE THIS!
I RELOADED IT FOR YOU.
- ( shouts )
( laughs )
DO YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT YOU
CAN DEFEAT A SUPERIOR LIKE ME?
( groans )
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
IS HAPPENING TO ME?
( groaning )
MY WHOLE BODY'S
BEING TORN APART.
- THOSE BULLETS WERE DESIGNED
TO KILL SUPERIORS LIKE YOU.
GUESS THEY WORK PRETTY WELL.
- ( screeches )
- ( gunshots )
- ( screams )
( groaning )
NOT HERE.
NOT NOW.
THIS ISN'T THE RIGHT PLACE
OR THE RIGHT TIME
FOR ME TO DIE.
AND HARRY STILL NEEDS...
MY...
( distorted )
HELP.
- GRAVE.
I'D LIKE YOU
TO DO ME A FAVOR.
IT'S THE LAST FAVOR
I'LL EVER ASK OF YOU.
AND I WON'T BE AROUND
TO ASK FOR MORE.
WITH THIS, YOU'LL HAVE
10 MORE DAYS OF MOBILITY.
I SUPPOSE
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH TIME
TO DESTROY AN ORGANIZATION
THE SIZE OF MILLENNION.
( chuckles softly )
I ONCE IGNORED THE VOICES
INSIDE MYSELF.
I USED TO HOLD ONTO
MY LIFE SO TIGHTLY.
I LET PEOPLE PUSH ME AROUND
BECAUSE I WAS AFRAID
TO CONFRONT ANYONE.
I GAVE IN
TO EVIL TEMPTATIONS
BECAUSE MY COWARDICE
WOULDN'T LET ME STOP.
NOW MY MEMORIES AND MY REGRETS
ARE BLURRED AND INDISTINCT.
THERE'S ONLY ONE REGRET
I CAN'T LET GO OF.
I NEVER GOT TO MAKE...
A DIFFERENCE.
- WHERE-- HOW DID I
GET BACK HERE IN THE TRAILER?
GRAVE?  DOCTOR?
HUH?
OH, GRAVE,
THANKS FOR SAVING ME.
YOU'RE PRETTY AMAZING,
YOU KNOW?
( gasps )
NO...
DR. TOKIOKA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
PLEASE ANSWER ME.
DOCTOR!
( crying )
THEY ALWAYS DIE.
EVERYONE ALWAYS DIES.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
IT'S NOT FAIR AT ALL.
WHY DID HE HAVE TO DIE?
WHY DO THEY ALWAYS
HAVE TO DIE?!
( screaming )
- ( rock music playing )
- ( man singing in Japanese )
- Brandon Heat:
THEY CONFRONT EACH OTHER
WITH NO POSSIBILITY
OF COMPROMISE.
HIS NEED TO PROTECT
HIS BELOVED'S DAUGHTER
IS MATCHED BY THE OTHER'S
NEED TO PROTECT HIM.
MILLENNION IS THE BATTLEGROUND.