( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Priest: SID GALARDE
HAS BEEN GRANTED
ETERNAL SALVATION,
AND RAISED ONTO HIS
HEAVENLY RESTING PLACE
WHERE HE IS FINALLY,
AND FOREVER MORE AT PEACE.
IN HEAVEN DEATH IS NOT
FEARED BUT WELCOMED,
FOR DEATH IS FORGIVENESS
AND REJUVENATION.
THE LORD IN HIS WISDOM...
- YOU MUST BE FEELING SAD,
AREN'T YOU SHERRY?
- MMM-MMM.
- NOW THAT HE'S PASSED AWAY
NO ONE WILL SAY ANYTHING
BAD ABOUT UNCLE SID.
BECAUSE NOBODY SPEAKS ILL OF
A PERSON WHOSE DIED.
- YOU'VE GOT REAL INNER
STRENGTH. I ADMIRE THAT.
- SHOULDN'T YOU GO THERE?
- I ALREADY SAID MY GOODBYES.
I TOLD HIM THE ONE THING HE
NEEDED TO HEAR BEFORE HE DIED,
THAT HE WOULDN'T BE
REMEMBERED AS A TRAITOR.
WHILE WE'RE ON THE
SUBJECT, BRANDON...
DON'T TAKE ON UNPLEASANT
CHORES SO WILLINGLY.
- ( crying )
- EDDIE!
- ( gunshot )
- YOU CAN RELAX A LITTLE
MORE. ALLOW YOURSELF
A LITTLE MORE FREEDOM.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
BEING FREE FEELS LIKE.
- THERE'S A LOT YOU DON'T KNOW.
AND THAT CAN MAKE
THINGS A LITTLE AWKWARD.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE OUR BOSS,
BIG DADDY.
- Brandon: HARRY SAID, "LET'S
KEEP CLIMBING THE LADDER"
AND, "LET'S FORCE
THE CODE OF IRON."
I NODDED WITHOUT
SAYING A WORD.
BECAUSE THE ORGANIZATION,
MILLENION... YES.
IT'S MY WHOLE WORLD NOW.
- ITS GOOD TO FINALLY SEE
YOU AGAIN, BIG GUY.
- THAT GUY KILLED 327 MEN AND HE
GETS OUT AFTER ONLY EIGHT YEARS?
- QUIET! YOU NEVER KNOW
WHO'S LISTENING.
SO UNLESS YOU'D WANT TO BE THE
328TH, I'D KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT.
- ALL RIGHT, I'VE WAITED LONG
ENOUGH. GIVE ME THAT THING.
- YOU GOT IT, BIG GUY.
- ( chuckles )
- THAT FEELS GOOD.
HI, PARTNER?
- SO, HOW'S THE BOSS?
- HE'S DOING JUST FINE.
THANKS TO YOU IT'S
BEEN SMOOTH SAILING,
SINCE YOU LEFT EIGHT YEARS AGO.
- GOOD, I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
I JUST HOPE I DON'T GET BORED.
- HEY BIG GUY.
- HUH?
- DIDN'T WASTE ANY TIME,
DID YOU?
- BECAUSE I TOLD YOU,
I'D RETURN THIS...
JUST AS SOON AS YOU GOT BACK.
- YOU'RE A MAN THAT KEEPS
HIS WORD. RIGHT PAL?
THEY SAY CANNON VULCAN
IS FASTER THAN A BULLET.
YOU LIVE UPTO YOUR REPUTATION.
- BLOOD WAR. TURN THE WORLD
INTO A BATTLEFIELD.
- ANY BIG CHANGES
IN THE PAST EIGHT YEARS?
- YEAH. TOO MANY, ACTUALLY.
THE ORGANIZATION I BELONG
TO, THE LIGHTNING GROUP,
IS ON THE ROPES.
- BECAUSE OF MILLENNION?
- YEAH. THEY 'VE GAINED A
LOT OF GROUND.
THEY'RE PROMINENT PLAYERS NOW,
A REAL SOLID ORGANIZATION.
- THAT'S WHY YOU GUYS NEED
VOLCANO'S HELP?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- LOOK, I'D LIKE TO HELP YOU.
BUT EVEN THOUGH WE'RE
SWORN BROTHERS,
MY BOSS WOULDN'T MOBILIZE
OUR GUYS FOR SOMETHING
THAT WOULDN'T MAKE US A PROFIT
OR GIVE US SOME
KIND OF ADVANTAGE.
- WHAT YOU GET WOULD BE A HUGE
ADVANTAGE AND A PROFIT.
COME WITH ME AND I'LL SHOW YOU.
- ARE YOU READY DOC?
- YES, WE'RE READY.
- THEN LET'S GET STARTED.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- I SAID LET'S GET STARTED!
- YES, SIR.
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
OPENING UP A PET STORE?
- YEAH. EXCEPT OUR PETS ARE
ANYTHING BUT TAME.
- IS IT ASLEEP?
- IT'S DEAD.
- HUH?
- WATCH IT CLOSELY.
DON'T TAKE YOUR EYES OFF IT.
DON'T EVEN BLINK.
THIS IS MY DREAM COME TRUE.
IT'S TAKEN ME SEVEN YEARS TO
TRANSFORM IT INTO A REALITY.
I GAVE UP EVERYTHING.
ALL MY MONEY,
MY FAMILY, EVERY FRIEND I HAD
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- ( roars )
- WHAT THE HELL! WHAT IS THIS,
SOME KIND OF MAGIC TRICK?
- IT'S NOT MAGIC BUT WIZARDRY.
TECHNOLOGICAL WIZARDRY.
AND IF WE USED IT ON HUMANS?
IMAGINE AN ARMY OF CREATURES
WITH THAT KIND OF POWER.
OUR ARMY, UNDER OUR CONTROL.
NO MISSILES, GUNS.
NOTHING TO BUILD.
FINDING DEAD BODIES IS A
LOT EASIER.
WHEN IT IS PERFECTED, MILLENNION
WON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- ( maniacal laughter )
- I WAS BORED OUT OF MY MIND FOR
EIGHT YEARS BUT NOT ANYMORE!
AWESOME, CANNON! MY BLOOD'S
BOILING, I'M ON FIRE AGAIN!
AND NOW LET'S LIGHT THE
FIRES OF WAR!
- ( growling )
- I HEARD ABOUT THE SID INCIDENT
AND WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
- I'M SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
- THESE ARE DIFFICULT TIMES,
BUT WE CAN ONLY HOPE THE WORLD
WILL BE MORE
HARMONIOUS SOMEDAY.
-HARRY AND I WILL CREATE
THAT WORLD, SIR.
- OH, YOU WILL?
- I'VE HEARD THAT YOU
HAVEN'T SEEN MARIA LATELY.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- AND WHY IS THAT?
YOU ARE AN AWKWARD GUY, BRANDON.
YOU KNOW THAT?
- SOMEONE SAID I WAS AWKWARD.
AS YOU ARE.
- AS I AM? WHOEVER IT WAS MUST
HAVE MEANT IT AS A COMPLIMENT.
( laughs )
- NICE!
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( APPLAUSE )
- YOU WOULDN'T HAVE SUNK
THAT EIGHT YEARS AGO.
- HUH! BLOOD WAR!
WELL, I'LL BE...
- WELCOME BACK BLOOD.
- BOSS.
- SO, HOW'RE YOU DOING?
- GREAT. THANKS TO YOU,
EVERYTHING IS GOING JUST FINE.
A FULL FLEDGED CIVILIAN AGAIN.
- STOP BEING POLITE, WILL YOU?
HEY, NO MORE GOLF TODAY.
- Girl: YES SIR.
- SO WHAT'LL IT BE? YOU
NAME IT. BOOZE, WOMEN,
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT,
I'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- THE ONLY THING I WANT IS OUT.
I WANT YOU TO LET ME
AND MY GUYS LEAVE VOLCANO.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I FOUND IT, BOSS.
I FOUND MY BATTLEFIELD.
- JOIN LIGHTNING? ARE YOU
SURE ABOUT THIS, BIG GUY?
- I'M SURE. MY BRO IN LIGHTNING
IS DEVELOPING A NEW PROCESS.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
TOTALLY AWESOME.
THE MOST AMAZING
THING I'VE EVER SEEN.
- I GUARANTEE IT WILL
BLOW YOUR MIND.
- Man: THAT'S AWESOME.
I'M WITH YOU ALL
THE WAY, BIG GUY.
I'VE BEEN ITCHING FOR
A FIGHT FOR EIGHT YEARS.
I'M READY TO GO WHENEVER
YOU SAY.
- ME, TOO. MY LIFE'S BEEN
IN YOUR HANDS EVER SINCE
I PLEDGED MY LOYALTY,
AND IT STILL IS.
- LIGHTNING IS IN MILLENNION'S
SPHERE OF INFLUENCE.
IF THEY FIND OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON,
LIGHTNING COULD BE WIPED OUT.
AND US RIGHT ALONG WITH THEM!
UH...
- GO AHEAD.
- WHAT? BIG GUY?
- COME ON, YOU SPINELESS COWARD.
WHY DON'T YOU STOP WHINING
AND SHOOT ME? HUH?
- HOLD ON. PLEASE,
LET ME EXPLAIN.
- BIG GUY, HIS WIFE JUST HAD A
LITTLE BOY, COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
- HEY! SHUT UP.
- I SEE.
HIS PAPA'S GOT NO BALLS.
- I'M WILLING TO RISK MY LIFE
TO FOLLOW THE BIG GUY. ARE YOU?
-I'M WITH YOU, BIG GUY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU TELL ME.
- IT WON'T BE BORING.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT,
BROTHER. THINGS NEVER
ARE WHEN BIG GUY IS AROUND.
- ( all laugh )
- GET READY TO MOVE!
- All: YES, SIR!
- I CAN SMELL THE
BATTLEFIELD, EAST.
- ( gunshots )
- BRANDON, SO, WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
- ARE ANY OF THEM GOOD ENOUGH?
- THREE OF THEM,
IF WE TRAIN THEM RIGHT.
- GOOD. TAKE THE ONES YOU
WANT UNDER YOUR WING.
- I'LL LEAVE THEIR
TRAINING UP TO YOU.
- SURE.
- WE'LL COMBINE OUR TWO UNITS.
THE GUYS FROM OVERKILL
AND TRUE GRAVE.
TOGETHER THEY WILL BECOME
MILLENNION'S MOST
POWERFUL WEAPON.
- SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
SIR. THEY JUST CALLED
AN EXECUTIVE MEETING.
- YES, ALL RIGHT.
- I APOLOGIZE TO YOU
ALL FOR MAKING YOU
COME ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
YOU SEE, I HAVE JUST
RECEIVED A TIP.
THAT SOME OF LIGHTNING'S
ACTIVITIES APPEAR
HIGHLY SUSPICIOUS.
- LIGHTNING, YOU SAY?
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT THE DAMAGE
WE INFLICTED ON THEM
FOUR YEARS AGO WOULD PREVENT
THEM FROM BECOMING A THREAT.
- ITS TRUE. THEY'RE A
TWO-BIT OUTFIT WHO
ARE BARELY MANAGING TO SURVIVE.
HARDLY WORTH
OUR ATTENTION.
- IT MAY WELL BE
A MINOR ISSUE.
HOWEVER, IF WHATEVER LIGHTNING'S
DOING INVOLVES SOMEONE
FROM THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE MOUNTAIN.
- MEANING? VOLCANO RIGHT?
- BUT WHY? BIG DADDY
AND VOLCANO
HAVE A VERY FRIENDLY
RELATIONSHIP.
- THEY AGREED TO A
NON-AGGRESSION PACT A WHILE AGO.
- CORRECT. HOWEVER, ONE OF THE
MEMBERS DISASSOCIATED HIMSELF
FROM THE VOLCANO FAMILY
ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
I'M SURE YOU ALL HAVE
HEARD OF HIM.
THE NAME OF THIS MAN IS WAR.
BLOOD WAR.
- AH, BLOOD WAR...
KNOWN AS BLOOD
OF THE BATTLEFIELD.
- VOLCANO'S A GOOD OUTFIT AND HE
WAS ONE OF THEIR TOP GUYS.
WHY WOULD HE GIVE THAT UP
TO JOIN LIGHTNING?
- WHAT THE HELL IS HE UP TO?
- SORRY, THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
- ALLOW US TO TAKE
CARE OF IT, SIR.
YOU CAN COUNT ON HARRY MACDOWEL
AND MY PARTNER BRANDON HEAT,
TO DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- YOU TWO JUST
JOINED THE FAMILY.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK...
- I'M IN FAVOR OF IT.
- BEAR WALKEN?
- I BELIEVE THAT THE TWO OF
THEM'D BE THE BEST MEN
FOR THIS JOB.
- AM I RIGHT?
- YES.
- I HOPE SO. BUT LET ME
TELL YOU ONE THING.
IF YOU UNDERESTIMATE
BLOOD WAR...
IT'LL BE THE LAST MISTAKE YOU
WILL EVER MAKE.
- I SEE. SO, YOU'RE SAYING
THAT THE VOLCANO FAMILY
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
- NOTHING AT ALL?
- OF COURSE NOT.
ONCE A GUY LEAVES
THE FAMILY
WHAT HE DOES IS NONE
OF MY BUSINESS.
- I AM NOT LOOKING FOR
ATTITUDE, BUT HARMONY.
- YEAH, SO AM I.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU STOP HIM?
- THERE ARE GUYS IN THIS WORLD
THAT REFUSE TO PLAY BY ANYONE'S
RULES BUT THEIR OWN.
- I SEE. AT ANY RATE, I'LL HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING THAT'S NECESSARY
TO PROTECT MY ORGANIZATION.
IS THAT UNDERSTOOD?
- I THINK IF I COULD JUST...
NO, NEVER MIND.
- I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
- BUT YOU KNOW.
- YEAH, I GOT IT.
- IT'S AGREED THEN. BLOOD WAR
AND HIS 23 UNDERLINGS...
WILL JOIN UP WITH
CANNON VULCAN.
THERE AREN'T VERY MANY OF THEM,
BUT I HANDPICKED EACH ONE.
USE THEM AS YOU LIKE.
- THEY'LL BE WELL
TAKEN CARE OF.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I
CAN FOR MY GUESTS.
- THAT'S REAL NICE OF YOU.
SMART, TOO.
LOT OF THOSE GUYS
HAVE A SHORT FUSE.
- YEAH. JUST LIKE YOU, BIG GUY.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING. BY THE
WAY HOW'S YOUR BOSS?
- HE DIED TWO WEEKS AGO.
I GAVE HIM A NICE FUNERAL.
I TOOK OVER THE ORGANIZATION.
- ( chuckles )
- SO YOU KILLED HIM, HUH?
ISN'T THAT NICE. NOW WE HAVE
NO MORE ROADBLOCKS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
- CAN'T TELL YOU YET.
- WHY NOT?
- EXCUSE ME, GENTLEMEN.
- WHAT'S UP? WE DIDN'T
ORDER ANYTHING!
- WELL, A GUEST SENT THEM
WITH HIS COMPLIMENTS.
- I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND
IF I JOIN YOU?
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU, PAL?
- OF COURSE, YOU'RE MORE THAN
WELCOME TO JOIN US.
WHAT A NICE DELIGHTFUL SURPRISE
RUNNING INTO YOU LIKE THIS,
HARRY MACDOWEL OF MILLENNION.
- FROM MILLENNION?
- I MUST SAY THAT I CONSIDER IT
AN HONOR YOU REMEMBERED MY NAME.
I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT TO
CELEBRATE, SO I PROPOSE A TOAST.
TO CANNON VULCAN FOR TAKING OVER
THE LEADERSHIP OF LIGHTNING.
AND TO BLOOD WAR FOR BEING
RELEASED FROM PRISON
AFTER EIGHT YEARS.
- HOW NICE.
-THINK YOU'RE CLEVER, DON'T YOU?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
IT TASTES LIKE PIG PISS FROM
A BIG FAT PIG.
WHO BELONGS TO A BIG,
FAT ORGANIZATION!
- I ASKED THE GUY AT THE BAR TO
MAKE IT EXTRA STRONG.
- NOT STRONG ENOUGH,
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
- TELL ME, WHAT BRINGS ONE
OF MILLENNION'S EXECUTIVES
TO A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- IF FLIES WERE BUZZING
AROUND YOUR FACE,
WOULDN'T IT BOTHER YOU A BIT?
- YOU'RE SAYING WE'RE FLIES?
- YES.
- SO WHY'D MILLENNION TAKE
NOTICE OF MERE INSECTS LIKE US?
- FUNNY, ISN'T IT?
EVEN COMICAL, I SUPPOSE.
BUT WHEN FLIES START BUZZING
AROUND, WE WONDER.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A REASON. BUT
WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND IT.
THAT GOT OUR ATTENTION.
- YOU HAVEN'T FOUND IT
BECAUSE IT ISN'T THERE.
- THAT'S RATHER HARD TO BELIEVE.
IF IT WERE TRUE, YOU'D
HAVE HAD NO REASON
TO KILL YOUR FORMER BOSS.
- YOU'RE SAYING I KILLED HIM?
- IT'S TRUE, ISN'T IT?
- HOW DARE YOU ACCUSE HIM
WITHOUT ANY PROOF? YOU BASTARD!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- HEY, THE GUY AT THE BAR,
IS HE A BUDDY OF YOURS?
- YES. HIS NAME IS BRANDON,
BRANDON HEAT.
- HE'S OUR SWEEPER...
VERY GOOD AT HIS JOB.
- IF WE'D STARTED SHOOTING,
WE'D HAVE KILLED EACH OTHER,
BRANDON HEAT.
- THAT'S A REAL SCARY GUY
YOU GOT THERE.
- HE'S RATHER DEPENDABLE, TOO.
- NOW THEN, YOU'RE READY
TO START EXPLAINING
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO?
YOU'VE BEEN RECRUITING A
LOT OF MANPOWER LATELY.
WHAT'S LIGHTNING GOING
TO USE THEM FOR?
- WE'RE A SMALL OUTFIT.
WE JUST NEEDED SOME EXTRA
HELP, THAT'S ALL.
- SURE, I UNDERSTAND.
AND I BELIEVE YOU, TOO.
BECAUSE GOOD RELATIONSHIPS
DEPEND ON TRUSTING ONE ANOTHER.
UNFORTUNATELY I'M A HOPELESSLY
SKEPTICAL KIND OF GUY.
SO I'VE GOT VERY FEW FRIENDS.
- I DON'T BELIEVE WE'RE UNDER
HARRY MACDOWEL'S MICROSCOPE.
THIS COULD GET REAL TRICKY.
- NO, CANNON. THE TRICKY
ONE IS THE OTHER GUY
WHO WAS HAVING A
DRINK OVER HERE.
THAT GUY WHO HE CALLED
BRANDON HEAT.
SOMETHING ABOUT HIM.
HE HAD ME IN HIS SIGHTS
AND I NEVER KNEW
HE WAS IN THE ROOM.
IF YOU'RE NOT SCARED OF
THIS GUY, YOU SHOULD BE.
- I'M NOT WORRIED.
I'VE GOT YOU, DON'T I?
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
IT'S GOING TO BE A HELL
OF A BATTLEFIELD!
- SO, CANNON VULCAN
AND BLOOD WAR...
THAT'S GONNA BE TOUGH BUT
WE'LL PULL IT OFF.
WE'VE GOT TO. WE CAN'T
AFFORD TO BOTCH THIS JOB.
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
AND THEN THE SKY'S THE LIMIT.
- BLOOD WAR?
I'VE HEARD RUMORS ABOUT HIM.
I'VE HEARD THAT HE WAS IN CHARGE
OF VOLCANO ORGANIZATION'S
SPECIAL COMBAT UNIT.
AND THAT BEFORE
HE WENT TO PRISON,
HE KILLED OVER 200 PEOPLE.
LISTEN, BRO, IF YOU
FIGHT THIS DUDE,
A WHOLE LOT OF GUYS,
HUNDREDS OF THEM
ARE GOING TO END UP
IN POOLS OF BLOOD.
YOU HAVE TO PREPARE YOURSELF
TO DEAL WITH THAT.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- NOTHING.
HARRY, DON'T DIE, OKAY?
- RIGHT BACK AT YOU, PAL.
- LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
TELL ME WHO YOU
GUYS ARE LOYAL TO?
- All: WE'RE LOYAL TO BLOOD WAR!
- YEAH THAT'S RIGHT. AND DO YOU
ALL BELIEVE IN BLOOD WAR?
- All: YES, SIR!
- DO YOU SWEAR, YOU'LL
SACRIFICE EVERYTHING
FOR BLOOD WAR?
- All: YES, SIR!
- I, BLOOD WAR,
AM GOING TO TAKE CONTROL
OF YOUR HEARTS AND SOULS.
- ( gun fires )
- ( men screaming )
- ( maniacal laughter )
- THE WAR IS ABOUT TO START!
WAIT FOR US, MILLENNION!
WAIT FOR US, BRANDON HEAT!
-I'VE JOINED FORCES
WITH BLOOD WAR.
- IF YOU TRULY UNDERSTAND WHAT
THAT MEANS FOR THE FUTURE,
YOU CAN CHOOSE ONLY ONE PATH.
- ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
BALLADBIRD LEE.
- CANNON VULCAN...
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: BLOOD WAR
AND CANNON VULCAN
WILL TURNED THIS CITY
INTO A WARZONE.
THEY'LL TRY TO DESTROY
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT
WHICH MILLENION
CAN'T ALLOW.
WHICH BRANDON HEAT WILL
NOT ALLOW.