- ( theme music playing )
- ( gunfire )
- ( beeps )
- ( snarling )
- ( both gasp )
- ( shrieks )
- SO, GRAVE, YOU'RE NOT
FULLY MOBILE YET, ARE YOU?
- ( shrieks )
- HIS NAME WAS BRANDON.
BRANDON HEAT.
( Mika shouts )
BRANDON!  BRANDON!
- ( grunts )
- ( shrieks )
- AMAZING.
- ( snarling )
- ( shrieks )
- SORRY I'M LATE.
- LET'S CUT STRAIGHT
TO THE CHASE, SHALL WE?
ACCORDING TO THE REPORT
WE RECEIVED,
THE ORGMEN WE SENT OUT
WERE DESTROYED.  IS THIS TRUE?
- IT'S TRUE ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NO SURVIVORS,
AND THERE'S NO WITNESSES.
HE EITHER--
THEY WERE COMPLETELY
ANNIHILATED.
- AND THOSE WERE THE SOLDIERS
YOU WERE BRAGGING ABOUT?
- YOU ARE INTIMATELY FAMILIAR
WITH THE EXTENT
OF THEIR ABILITIES.
SO THE ISSUE THAT
CONFRONTS US NOW
IS WHO COULD POSSIBLY
BE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO WIPE OUT SO MANY ORGMEN.
- COULD SUCH A HUMAN BEING
REALLY EXIST?
- WHO SAID IT HAD
TO BE A HUMAN?
BESIDES, THERE'S A SINGLE CASE
ON RECORD, ISN'T THERE?
AND I BELIEVE
IT DESCRIBES SOMEONE
WHO COULD ANNIHILATE
PROTOTYPE ORGMEN.
- THAT'S TRUE, BUT DIDN'T
THAT HAPPEN 13 YEARS AGO?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S THE SAME AS 13 YEARS AGO.
- HUH?
- THERE IS A CROWD OF SORTS.
THE TYPE OF CROWD
WHO WOULD RISE AGAINST US.
WHAT WOULD WE DO THEN?
WELL, THAT'S OBVIOUS.
DESTROY THEM,
CRUSH THEM WITH THE POWER
OF THE MILLENNION ORGANIZATION.
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
- BOSS, WHEN YOU FIND THE SPY,
LET ME KNOW.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- THE MEETING SEEMS
TO BE OVER.
- HEY, LEE,
WE SHOULD GET GOING, TOO.
- SURE.
BOSS, I FOUND THIS
AT THE MANSION
THAT I VISITED THE OTHER DAY.
- HMM?
HMM.
- IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
- ( laughing )
- Man: BRANDON HEAT.
WE MEET AGAIN, BRANDON.
I HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT YOU
IN QUITE SOME TIME.
( laughing )
- Mika: MY MOTHER TOLD ME
ABOUT HIM ONCE.
THAT MAN, BRANDON HEAT,
HE WAS AN OLD FRIEND
OF HERS.
- I KNOW NOTHING AT ALL
ABOUT THAT MAN'S PAST.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
HE WAS A GREAT SWEEPER.
- HE WAS?
- AND NOW I HAVE TO GO OUT
AND PICK UP SOME EQUIPMENT.
I'D APPRECIATE IT IF YOU
STAYED HERE AND KEPT QUIET.
ONE MORE THING.
HE'S NOT CALLED BRANDON.
THAT NAME NO LONGER
BELONGS TO HIM.
HE'S CALLED "GRAVE."
CALL HIM "BEYOND THE GRAVE."
- HIS NAME IS
BEYOND THE GRAVE?
I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE AN OLD FRIEND
OF MY MOTHER'S.
I'M SURE YOU'D LIKE
TO SEE HER AGAIN
AND TALK TO HER,
BUT YOU CAN'T.
YOU SEE, MY MOTHER IS NOT
IN THIS WORLD ANYMORE.
SHE WAS KILLED AND TOKIOKA
WHO TRIED TO PROTECT ME
DIED SHIELDING ME
WITH HIS BODY.
THE ONE WHO KILLED
THEM ALL WAS HARRY.
IT WAS HARRY MACDOWEL.
HE'S MILLENNION'S BOSS.
HE'S KNOWN AS BLOODY HARRY.
MY MOM WAS KILLED
BY HARRY.
- HARRY.
WHERE AM I?
WHO AM I?
- GUESS I NEED TO GET
SOME MORE BULLETS SOMEWHERE.
UM, EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
- FROM THE LOOK OF THAT SUIT,
YOU MUST BE DOING PRETTY WELL
FOR YOURSELF.
MAYBE THEY CAN HIRE ME, TOO.
- IS THIS--
AM I DREAMING?
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- Man:
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- BUT--
- IF HE HAD STAYED ASLEEP,
NOTHING WOULD HAVE CHANGED.
ONCE AWOKEN, HOWEVER,
HIS MIND WILL BE CONTROLLED
BY SOMETHING CALLED
THE PAST,
WHETHER HE LIKES
IT OR NOT.
- ( Mika whimpering )
ENOUGH ALREADY.
WHERE IN THE WORLD
IS THIS GUY GOING ANYWAY?
COME ON, I'M INJURED
JUST IN CASE YOU CARE.
- ( groaning )
( grunting )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Man: STILL WORKING OUT, HUH?
- Brandon: I KNOW.
- SAME OLD BRANDON. COME ON IN.
I GOT SOME JUICY STUFF
TO TELL YOU.
- Brandon: I KNOW THEM.
- YOU'RE GONNA GIVE IT TO MARIA,
IS THAT IT?
- Brandon: COMRADES.
- BRANDON.
- Brandon: AS FOR ME,
I'M COUNTING ON BRANDON.
- THEY'RE MY COMRADES.
- HEY, BRANDON.
- MY...
- BRANDON.
- FREE BRANDON.
- Brandon: THAT'S RIGHT.
- I WANNA BE FREE
TO TAKE WHAT I WANT
AND GIVE WHAT I WANT.
- MY NAME IS BRANDON HEAT.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( groaning )
THIS IS WHERE
I USED TO BE.
- ARE THESE ALL GRAVES?
IS SOMEONE YOU KNOW...
WELL, I GUESS THOSE PEOPLE MUST
HAVE BEEN DEAR TO YOU.
Mika:
I AM SUCH AN IDIOT.
AFTER THE ORGANIZATION
TOOK MY MOM AWAY FROM ME,
ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT WAS
GETTING BACK AT BLOODY HARRY
FOR KILLING HER.
I FORGOT ABOUT BURYING HER.
MY OWN MOTHER.
( crying )
I'M SO SORRY.
NO, THAT'S WAY TOO BIG.
- ( shouts )
- ( gasps )
WHAT IS THAT?
- Brandon:
WHAT IS IT?  WHO IS IT?
WHO ARE THEY?
- ( screams )
- WHY DO I PROTECT?
PROTECT?
Brandon:
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS
BUT THERE'S ONE THING
I KNOW FOR SURE.
TO PROTECT IS NOT
TO BETRAY.
NEVER BETRAY.  NEVER.
- ( snarls )
- ( men gasp )
- HMM.
- ( growling )
- GRAVE!
- ( roars )
( growls )
- OH!
- ( roaring )
- WELL, GRAVE, GONNA FIGHT?
- ( growls )
- ( both scream )
- ( gasps )
- ( groans )
- ( roaring )
- ( gasps )
MY MOM WAS KILLED
BY HARRY.
- Brandon:
SHE WAS MURDERED.
MARIA!
- ( growls )
- ( wincing )
- DOCTOR,
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HIM?
WHAT'S CAUSING GRAVE
TO SUFFER LIKE THAT?
- HE'S PROBABLY TRYING
TO FORCE HIMSELF TO REMEMBER.
- WHY IS REMEMBERING
SO HARD FOR HIM?
- BECAUSE HE DIED ONCE.
- HUH?
- REANIMATION AFTER DEATH
CAUSES MEMORY FRAGMENTATION,
A CONDITION IN WHICH MEMORIES
HAVE EITHER VANISHED ENTIRELY
OR HAVE BEEN BROKEN INTO PIECES
THAT MUST BE FIT TOGETHER
LIKE A JIGSAW PUZZLE.
HE'S TRYING TO BRING BACK
HIS PAST
FROM HIS FRAGMENTED MEMORIES.
- PLEASE, ISN'T THERE
ANYTHING YOU CAN DO FOR HIM?
- NOTHING, I'M AFRAID.
NOTHING AT ALL.
- OH, MAN.
- HOWEVER, I CAN TELL YOU THIS,
- OH!
- I'M NOT SURE WHY,
BUT EVIDENTLY YOU MEAN
A GREAT DEAL TO HIM.
TWICE NOW BEYOND THE GRAVE
HAS MADE EXTRAORDINARY EFFORTS
TO PROTECT YOU,
WHICH MEANS THERE MUST BE
A CONNECTION BETWEEN YOU
AND WHATEVER IT IS HE'S
STRUGGLING WITH WITHIN HIMSELF.
- ( sighs )
GRAVE IS PROTECTING ME.
- MIKE, YOU'VE GOT TO GO
RIGHT NOW.
FIND A PLACE WHERE THE
ORGANIZATION CAN'T REACH YOU.
- ORGANIZATION?
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO GO?
- WHEREVER HE IS.
WHEREVER HE IS, MIKA.
- DON'T WORRY, MISS.
I KNOW A MAN
WHO CAN PROTECT YOU,
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT I KNOW WHERE TO FIND HIM.
- PROTECT ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET A MAN
NAMED BRANDON HEAT.
- BRANDON HEAT.
HE DIED AND CAME BACK
FROM THE DEAD.
HE'S...
BEYOND THE GRAVE.
- Harry:
WHAT?  SHE GOT AWAY?
WHERE WAS THE DEATH SQUAD?
WE ADDED ORGMEN TO THE SQUAD
SO THEY'D BE FULLY PREPARED,
DIDN'T WE?
- Man: It seems the girl
had a bodyguard.
- WHAT KIND OF BODYGUARD?
- I went ahead
and forwarded you the data
that Bob has been able
to extract from the memory
of the fallen orgman.
Boss, you better
get ready for this.
What Bob found
is very surprising.
- ( gasping )
( laughing )
I SEE.
SO YOU ARE ALIVE,
BRANDON.
ARE YOU GOING TO BETRAY ME
ONCE AGAIN, BRANDON?
- BRANDON HEAT, YOU SAY?
- CORRECT.
HE WAS SEEN IN THE COMPANY
OF BIG DADDY'S DAUGHTER.
HE'S STRONG ENOUGH TO WITHSTAND
A DIRECT ATTACK BY THE ORGMEN,
AND EQUIPPED WITH ENOUGH
FIREPOWER TO DESTROY THEM.
- HE CAN'T BE ALIVE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- THE BOSS KILLED HIM.
- KUGASHIRA'S RIGHT.
THIRTEEN YEARS AGO
I SAW BRANDON'S CORPSE
WITH MY OWN EYES.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
BRANDON DID DIE 13 YEARS AGO.
HOWEVER--
- YOU'RE SAYING BRANDON
WAS NECROLIZED?
- YES, IF BRANDON HEAT WAS
NECROLIZED 13 YEARS AGO,
THEN EVERYTHING ELSE
FALLS INTO PLACE.
I BELIEVE IT'S THE ONLY
LOGICAL CONCLUSION.
IT WOULD EXPLAIN HIS ABILITY
TO DESTROY THE ORGMEN.
- UNDERSTOOD.
I'LL TAKE HIM OUT.
- HOLD ON, KUGASHIRA.
- WHY?
HE BETRAYED THE ORGANIZATION,
DIDN'T HE?
AND TRAITORS DESERVE ONLY THING
AND THAT'S DEATH.
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.  THAT'S
MILLENNION'S CODE OF IRON.
- BUT BRANDON HEAT'S
BEEN NECROLIZED.
- SO WHAT?
- WAIT A SEC, BUNJI.
IF IT'S OKAY WITH YOU,
I'LL TAKE THE GUY OUT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- BOB.
- FIGHTING AN OPPONENT LIKE THAT
WOULD BE THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO TRY OUT MY NEW POWERS
AS A SUPERIOR.
IT'S GONNA BE GREAT.
THE TRAITOR BRANDON HEAT
WILL BE EXECUTED
BY YOURS TRULY,
BOB POUNDMAX! ( laughing )
- GO ON FIGHTING.
THERE'S NO OTHER CHOICE,
IS THERE?
I HAVE TO KEEP FIGHTING
TO SURVIVE
AND TO TAKE REVENGE
ON MY MOTHER'S DEATH.
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT, AND I'M
GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP YOU.
I KNOW OF NO OTHER WAY
OF ATONING FOR WHAT I'VE DONE.
FOR HAVING ONCE SOLD MY SOUL
TO SATAN
AND FOR SELLING HIS AS WELL.
- I WAS TRYING
TO BRING BACK MY PAST.
BEWILDERED
BY DISJOINTED MEMORIES,
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING FROM
THAT PAST I HAVE TO PROTECT.
SOMETHING I CAN'T BETRAY.
THERE MUST BE,
I KNOW THERE IS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Brandon: A MAN IS REUNITED
WITH HIS BEST FRIEND.
BUT THERE'S A PROFOUND
DISAGREEMENT BETWEEN THEM.
BECAUSE FOR THEM,
EVEN LIFE AND DEATH ITSELF
MEAN DIFFERENT THINGS.
A CHASM REMAINS
BETWEEN THEM.