( theme music playing )
- ( inaudible )
- Brandon: WE COMPARE.
HUMANS ARE CREATURES
OF COMPARISON.
CONSTANTLY DECIDING WHETHER
THINGS ARE GOOD OR BAD
OR BETTER OR WORSE
THAN OTHER THINGS.
EVENTUALLY, WE MAKE
SO MANY COMPARISONS
THAT OUR OVERLOADED BRAINS
WILL ACCEPT ANYTHING.
GOOD OR BAD, RIGHT OR WRONG,
NOT CARING WHICH IS WHICH.
THERE WAS NOTHING
OUT OF THE ORDINARY
ABOUT BEING A CRIMINAL.
OR VICTIM OF A CRIME.
IT WAS AN EVERYDAY,
ORDINARY THING.
AND VIOLENCE WAS JUST
PART OF THE DAILY ROUTINE.
SO I, NO, WE, NEVER
THOUGHT TO QUESTION
THE WAY THINGS WERE
IN THIS CITY...
WHERE THINGS HAPPEN
AND SUDDEN DEATH
WAS JUST A FACT OF LIFE.
THAT'S RIGHT, BACK THEN
EVERYTHING WAS ORDINARY.
- ( police siren wailing )
- ( grunting )
- ( whistling )
HMM?
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, YOU BUM?
DON'T YOU BE SCROUNGING AROUND
IN SOMEBODY ELSE'S TRASH.
- I'M SORRY!
- GET LOST, YOU HYENA!
- YES, SIR! I'M GOING.
- POW!
( chuckles )
STILL WORKING OUT, HUH?
SAME OLD BRANDON!
COME ON IN, I GOT SOME
JUICY STUFF TO TELL YOU.
- I'M BACK!
- Jolice: WELCOME HOME, KENNY.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- SOMEWHERE NICE!
HEY, JOLICE, GET ME
SOMETHING TO DRINK, WILL YA?
- SURE. COMING RIGHT UP.
- IT'S THE WORST! THIS WEEK
IS THE ABSOLUTE WORST...
- HARRY! I GOT A
SURPRISE FOR YOU.
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT THIS!
- HUH?
- HEY, HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
- SCOTT WAS THE ONE WHO
TOLD ME WHERE I COULD FIND IT.
AND THEN I JUST DID MY USUAL
THING, IN THE USUAL WAY.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
I GOT PRETTY LUCKY
TODAY, DIDN'T I?
- YOU IDIOT. LIFTING A THING
LIKE THAT WON'T DO US ANY GOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- FIRST OF ALL,
IT'S A ONE OF A KIND ITEM
AND EASILY IDENTIFIABLE.
SO HOW ARE YOU GONNA SELL IT?
YOU MIGHT AS WELL WEAR
A SIGN SAYING, "I'M A THIEF,
WANNA BUY SOME
STOLEN MERCHANDISE?"
YOU'RE HOPELESS...
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THIS LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
- I WORKED SO HARD TO GET IT.
MAN, YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
- SURE YOU DID!
BUT YOUR HARD WORK ISN'T
GONNA PAYOFF THIS TIME.
- SORRY, BUDDY!
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, YOU GOT NO BUSINESS
LAUGHING AT ME, JOLICE!
- OH, SORRY.
- HMM? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHAT, WHAT'S THAT FOR?
DO YOU MEAN YOU WANNA BUY IT?
WELL NOW,
THAT IS A LOT LESS THAN
THE GOIN' RATE, YOU KNOW.
BUT, LOOKS LIKE TODAY
IS YOUR LUCKY DAY, BRANDON.
IT'S A DEAL.
- YOU'RE GONNA GIVE IT
TO MARIA, IS THAT IT?
I WOULDN'T, IF I WERE YOU.
IT'LL CAUSE NOTHING
BUT PROBLEMS FOR HER.
- HEY, NO WAY I AM GIVING
YOU A REFUND, PAL.
- FORGET ABOUT IT,
A DEAL'S A DEAL.
- HEY, IT'S DEED!
RIGHT NOW, HE'S GATHERING
ALL THE BEST FIGHTERS HE'S GOT.
- HMM. RETALIATING
FOR LAST TIME, HUH?
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- THE ANSWER'S OBVIOUS.
- YOU'RE ITCHING FOR
A FIGHT ALREADY?
JOLICE, YOU'RE IN CHARGE
UNTIL WE GET BACK.
- RIGHT. BE CAREFUL
OUT THERE, GUYS.
- I'LL FINALLY GET
TO SHOW THIS OFF.
- YOU SURE YOU KNOW
HOW TO USE THAT THING?
- YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
- WELL, AS FOR ME,
I'M COUNTING IN BRANDON.
- BYE, MARIA.
- BYE. SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- SORRY, WERE YOU WAITING LONG?
- GREAT. SO WHERE DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD GO TODAY?
- LET'S SEE...
- ( horn honking )
- IT'S MY UNCLE.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE
TO COME PICK ME UP.
- YEAH, I KNOW. BUT I GOT
OFF WORK EARLY TODAY.
- I PROMISED MY FRIEND
WE'D GO OUT FOR A CUP OF
COFFEE ON THE WAY HOME.
- YOU SHOULDN'T WANDER
AROUND TOWN LIKE THAT.
NOT WITH GUYS LIKE THAT AROUND.
- HUH?
- ( men grunting )
- BRANDON AND HARRY...
OH, UNCLE!
- YOU STAY OUT OF IT.
IT'S ONLY A FIGHT BETWEEN PUNKS.
- BUT...
- TRUTH IS, IF THEY SCREW UP,
THEY'RE GONNA END UP DEAD.
SO WHAT? THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO CHOSE TO LIVE THAT WAY.
- BUT UNCLE...
- PLEASE, DON'T UPSET ME
BY ARGUING MARIA, ALL RIGHT?
- ( grunting )
- NOT BAD.
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- ( grunting )
- NICELY DONE.
- ( sighs )
- WELL, DEED, WHAT'S IT
GONNA BE? YOU WANT SOME MORE?
- YOU BASTARD!
- AH, WOULD YOU LOOK AT
THAT, THE IDIOT'S GOT A GUN.
KENNY, GET YOURS OUT TOO.
- WELL, I, UM...
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
- WELL, IT'S NOT...
- KENNY!
- ( laughs )
- HEY, ARE YOU SOME KIND OF
AN IDIOT? OR WHAT?
( breathing heavily )
- COME BACK HERE.
COME ON, YOU COWARDS.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
OH MAN, IT'S A FREAKIN' TOY.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- THAT BASTARD!
- HEY HARRY,
REMIND ME, WILL YOU?
WHAT STARTED THIS THING?
WHY ARE WE FIGHTING THESE GUYS?
- BECAUSE OF A WOMAN,
THAT'S WHY.
HARRY WAS BIRD-DOGGIN
DEED'S LITTLE SUGAR LOVE.
- HEY, NO WAY. SHE WAS
THE ONE WHO CAME ON TO ME.
- SO THAT'S IT. NO WONDER
HE'S SO TICKED OFF.
- HE'S JUST PUTTING
ON THIS MACHO ACT
CAUSE HE WANTS TO BE LIKE
HIS BROTHER, YOU KNOW.
- OH, YOU MEAN
"MAD DOG LADD?"
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
MAD DOG WAS A BIG
CELEBRITY AROUND HERE.
- YEAH, ONE SCARY SON OF BITCH,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
DEED HAS TO FACE THE FACT
THAT HE'S A COWARD
AND ALWAYS WILL BE.
- AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH.
( laughs )
- SPEAKING OF MAD DOG,
HE GOT KILLED, DIDN'T HE?
- WHAT? WHEN?
- I HEARD THAT HE GOT INTO A
GUN FIGHT WITH SOME PUNK
AND THEY ENDED UP
SHOOTING EACH OTHER TO DEATH.
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING!
A BUDDY OF MINE TOLD ME
HE KILLED A BUNCH OF COPS
PULLING OFF SOME KINDA
SPECTACULAR ROBBERY.
AND THAT HE'S BEEN
ON THE RUN EVER SINCE.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT I HEARD WAS...
- HARRY!
OH, HARRY!
- HEY, KATHERINE.
- THERE YOU ARE, DARLING.
- GOOD.
THAT WAS EXCELLENT WORK.
YOUR GROUP HAS ALWAYS
BEEN REAL DEPENDABLE.
- WELL, OF COURSE...
- THANKS TO HARRY, MOST LIKELY?
- WELL, I GUESS YOU
COULD SAY THAT...
- HE'S YOUNG, BUT IMPRESSIVE.
HE'S PRETTY SMART, TOO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE HIM.
- Man: YOU WHIMPERING MORON.
THIS DOESN'T EVEN COVER
HALF OF WHAT YOU BORROWED.
- IS IT TRUE YOU AND DEEDS GANG
HAVE SOME KIND OF PROBLEM?
- WELL SIR, THEY'RE
THE ONES MESSING WITH US.
AND IT'S KIND OF
ANNOYING, YOU KNOW.
IF YOU COULD EVER
TALK TO THEM MR. DESCARTES,
WE SURE WOULD APPRECIATE IT.
- ( gunshots )
- DAMN. HE JUMPED
THE GUN AGAIN. THE IDIOT.
LOOK GUYS, I'LL TALK
TO DEED, ALL RIGHT?
SO, SEE YOU NEXT MONTH.
- YES, SIR. THANK YOU, SIR.
- NEXT TIME, FOR SURE, RIGHT?
YOU PROMISE ME, HARRY?
- OF COURSE. CROSS MY HEART.
- THEN I'LL BE WAITING.
- I'LL CALL YOU.
- GOOD NIGHT, HARRY.
- GOOD NIGHT, KATHERINE.
I LOVE YOU, DOLL. SEE YOU.
- ( car drives away )
- YOU THINK DESCARTES IS
REALLY GONNA TALK TO DEED?
COME ON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
- GOT BACK SAFE
AND SOUND, I SEE.
- YOU BETTER GET HER HOME
FAST BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- YO, MARIA.
- Maria: GOOD EVENING.
I SAW YOU EARLIER WHEN YOU WERE
FIGHTING THAT BUNCH OF GUYS.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED TO YOU.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T
THINK THEY'D WIN.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE FINE, BUT...
NOW I AM SURE.
- COME ON. STOP TALKING
AND GO SOMEWHERE, WILL YOU?
- SO SHE GETS THIS BOOB JOB.
IT MAKES IT LOOK LIKE THEIR...
HUH?
HEY, YOU WANT SOME
REPAIR WORK DONE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
THIS SHOP'S BEEN OUT
OF BUSINESS FOR A LONG TIME.
- YOU DEAF OR SOMETHING?
- ( men screaming )
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HELL?
- HEY!
- HEY DEED. WHAT KIND OF
GANG YOU RUNNING HERE?
YOU BETTER TEACH YOUR
GUYS SOME MANNERS.
- Deed: BIG BROTHER!
- Maria: BRANDON...
LISTEN TO ME.
WHY DON'T YOU QUIT?
WHY DO YOU KEEP FIGHTING?
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO WORK, I CAN
ASK MY UNCLE TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO SOME OF THE
PEOPLE HE KNOWS.
YOU COULD DO IT,
IF YOU REALLY WANTED TO.
THOSE FRIENDS OF YOURS...
THEY MEAN A LOT TO YOU?
BRANDON?
OF COURSE...
OF COURSE THEY DO.
- Brandon: I'LL TAKE YOU HOME.
- ( doorbell rings )
- WELL, YOU GOT
HOME LATE, MARIA.
- I'M SORRY TO BARGE IN
ON YOU LIKE THIS.
HOWEVER THE REASON FOR
COMING HERE TONIGHT
MADE IT UNAVOIDABLE.
WE'VE COME TO DELIVER
A MESSAGE FROM BIG DADDY.
- COME ON INSIDE.
- HEY, KENNY!
- HUH? SCOTT, YOU BASTARD.
THAT TIP YOU GAVE
ME WAS WORTHLESS.
I COULDN'T GET A CENT
FOR THAT THING.
- I'M SORRY, I'M A BIT
ABSENT MINDED.
SO, I'M GONNA MAKE IT UP
TO YOU WITH A HOT TIP.
THE BEST YOU EVER GOT.
- THANKS TO YOU, I CANT AFFORD
IT, YOU CHEAP SCUMBAG.
- NO CHARGE. JUST CALL IT
CUSTOMER SERVICE KID.
- HMM?
YOU'RE A TARGET.
MILANDA'S GUYS ARE OUT
LOOKING FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
- ( tires screeching )
- LET GO OF ME, YOU BASTARD.
- SORRY, PAL.
IT'S CALLED YOU SCRATCH MY BACK,
I'LL SCRATCH YOURS.
- GOOD NIGHT, THEN.
- ( footsteps approach )
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
- UNCLE...
- MARIA, I TOLD YOU NOT TO SEE
THAT GUY AGAIN, DIDN'T I?
- BUT...
- I WANT YOU TO LEAVE MY NIECE
ALONE, YOU UNDERSTAND?
- UNCLE!
- YOUNG MAN, I DON'T LIKE YOU.
OR THE GROUP YOU HANG OUT WITH.
- BRANDON...
- FIRST YOU GET YOUR ASS KICKED,
THEN YOU RUN LIKE
A SHAMELESS COWARD.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN ME IN AGES
AND YOU DARE TO TELL A
PATHETIC STORY LIKE THAT.
- I'M SORRY.
- FACT IS,
YOU'RE A PIECE OF TRASH.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MY BROTHER.
SO I'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
YOU DISGRACED OUR NAME.
IT'S MY DUTY TO RESTORE
OUR FAMILY'S HONOR.
- HEY, BRANDON.
SEEMS YOU'RE TAKING QUITE
A LIKING TO THAT THING.
- FORGET IT. NO WAY YOU'RE...
- HARRY!
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- IT'S KENNY. THEY GOT HIM.
- THEY DID?
- DO YOU KNOW WHO TOOK HIM?
- MILANDA.
THE NECKLACE HE STOLE
THE OTHER DAY,
IT CAME FROM MILANDA'S STORE.
- HE STOLE IT FROM
MILANDA? THAT STUPID KID.
NOBODY STEALS FROM HER.
NOT IF THEY WANT TO
KEEP BREATHING.
THE BITCH SAYS ONE WORD AND THE
WHOLE MOB STOPS IN IT'S TRACKS.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- WELL, HOW THE HELL
SHOULD I KNOW?
- ( jingles )
- SO WE TAKE IT BACK TO HER?
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- HEY, DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
GOING TO SEE MILANDA.
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
- WHY NOT?
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOU THINK SHE'S JUST
GONNA FORGIVE HIM
BECAUSE WE'RE RETURNING
WHAT HE STOLE?
- KENNY DID SOMETHING STUPID.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
SO WHAT, HE'S ONE OF US, RIGHT?
- OH, MAN!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT...
- I'LL GO TOO.
- YOU IDIOT, YOURS STAYIN' HERE.
- BUT, I, UH...
- YOUR JOB IS TO MAKE SURE
THERE'S A GOOD MEAL
WAITING FOR US.
DINNER FOR FIVE, ALL RIGHT?
- YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
- UNBELIEVABLE...
WHAT AN IDIOT!
- HEY, YOU'RE THE IDIOT.
- SO ARE YOU.
- HEY, WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT!
EVEN THE SKY IS LOOKING
PRETTY GLOOMY.
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET HOME.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- Milanda: START TALKING.
THE TRUTH THIS TIME.
NOW TELL ME WHERE
YOU'VE HIDDEN THE ITEM
YOU STOLE FROM MY STORE.
LIKE I ALREADY TOLD YOU, MA'AM,
I SOLD IT A LONG TIME AGO.
- IMPOSSIBLE. I'D HAVE KNOWN.
THE OPERATIVES IN MY
INTELLIGENCE NETWORK
ARE EXPERTS.
YOU WANT TO STRIKE BACK,
DON'T YOU? BE MY GUEST.
IF YOU'VE GOT THE GUTS
TO DO IT.
( laughs )
IF NOT, PLEASE DON'T
WASTE ANY MORE TIME.
I LOVE TO KEEP PEOPLE WAITING.
I HOWEVER REFUSE TO
WAIT FOR ANYONE.
- ( clicks )
- NOW, ANSWER ME.
HURRY.
- ( grunts )
- ( men screaming )
- WHAT IS IT NOW?
- SORRY TO DISTURB YOU
SO LATE AT NIGHT.
SORRY ABOUT THE RUDE ENTRANCE,
MRS. MILANDA. FORGIVE US.
- MISS MILANDA.
- PLEASE ACCEPT MY
SINCERE APOLOGY.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- THAT YOUNG MAN ON THE FLOOR
STOLE SOMETHING FROM YOU.
I CAME HERE TONIGHT
TO RETURN IT.
- EXPECTING A REWARD?
- FOR A JEWEL LIKE THAT?
NATURALLY, I'D BE A FOOL NOT TO.
- I LIKE HONESTY. SO,
WHAT DO YOU HAVE IN MIND?
- WHEN I LEAVE TONIGHT...
I WAS HOPING YOU'D ALLOW THIS
YOUNG MAN HERE TO COME WITH ME.
- ( Milanda laughs )
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU CAME
HERE TO RESCUE HIM
AFTER HE WAS STUPID ENOUGH
TO STEAL MY
MERCHANDISE, CORRECT?
- YES, MA'AM.
YOU'RE SHARP AS A TACK.
BUT IN ADDITION, JUST TO PROVE
TO YOU HOW GRATEFUL I AM,
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE ME AS WELL?
- HMM.
- I'VE BEEN POLISHING
MY SKILLS.
I'M IN GREAT SHAPE.
NOT TO MENTION
PRETTY GOOD LOOKING.
REST ASSURED, YOU'LL
HAVE A WONDERFUL TIME.
IN FACT, I GUARANTEE IT.
- I SEE. SOUNDS EXCITING.
WELL THEN, I'LL LEAVE
THE REST TO YOU.
- RIGHT.
- IT DIDN'T WORK HARRY,
NOW WHAT?
- I'M IN SHOCK.
- OH, GREAT!
- ( guns click )
- OH, BY THE WAY...
- HEY, ARE YOU GUYS ALIVE?
- I FEEL LIKE I'M ABOUT
TO DIE OR WORSE,
LIKE I'M ALREADY DEAD.
- DAMN THAT BITCH.
SHE HAD THEM WORK
US OVER OUT HERE,
SO THEY WOULDN'T
STAIN HER CARPET.
TO THAT BITCH, OUR LIVES
ARE WORTH LESS THAN A RUG!
- SO, YOU'D RATHER DIE THAN BE
THOUGHT OF AS WORTHLESS...
- HEY, BRANDON...
BRANDON?
BRANDON! COME ON, BRANDON.
SNAP OUT OF IT.
- ( door opens )
- HEY, WELCOME BACK...
- YEAH, I'M BACK.
- MY FORTUNE TELLING
CARDS WERE RIGHT.
THIS WAS THE WORST DAY EVER.
- JUST ONE OF YOU?
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
HMM. WELL, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
- ( gun shot )
- Brandon: ORDINARY.
EVERYTHING WAS ORDINARY.
EXCEPT FOR THE FACT,
THAT THE DEAD MAN IN FRONT
OF OUR EYES WAS ONE OF US.
TO ANYONE ELSE,
AN INSIGNIFICANT SCENE...
IN A PLACE WHERE THINGS
LIKE THIS WERE COMMON PLACE.
THEY WERE NOTHING MORE
THAN ORDINARY.
- ( pop song playing )
- ( man singing )
- Brandon: ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE WAS GONE.
LEAVING NOTHING
BUT A VAGUE MEMORY.
NOW, IT'S RAINING ON PLACES
WHERE THERE IS NO FREEDOM.
RAINING ENDLESSLY. AS IF
IT WILL WASH OUR LIVES AWAY.