[PAKA]
A hearty breakfast.
For after the
medicine wears off.
[KAIKOKU]
Medicine...?
[PAKA]
Anesthetic. Just a precaution,
as I'd rather not suffer
any further attacks from you.
[PAKA]
Anyway, I'll be keeping you
here in the White Room
until your team reaches
a hundred million views.
[PAKA] That's the ID bracelet
we use for you dropouts.
Makes it easier to
identify your corpse.
Any questions for me?
[inaudible]
[PAKA] Sorry, my boy,
you'll have to speak up.
[PAKA]
What are you, a junkyard mutt?!
[KAIKOKU] What'dya do
to my damn grandpa...?
[PAKA] I believe you're
overestimating me.
I can do a great many things,
but controlling life and death
is not one of them.
[PAKA] I'll leave you to get
settled now, Mr. Onigasaki.
Pleasant nightmares.
[PAKA]
Ah.
It seems like everywhere I turn,
there's another
confrontation waiting.
[ANYA] Shut up!
What did you do with Oni?!
[PAKA] Unfortunately,
Mr. Onigasaki violated
yet another taboo last night.
He invaded Floor 51 and
attempted to assault me.
The ruffian nearly
slit my throat
with that frightful
blade of his.
Such behavior is a hindrance
to our fun gaming atmo‐‐
[ZAKURO ] That's bullshit!
You probably pushed him to!
[PAKA]
I did nothing of the sort.
But I do wonder what could
have possibly inspired him
to take such drastic actions.
[PAKA] In any case, you'll
be completing the games
with seven players from
this point forward, so‐‐
I'm out.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[GROUP gasping]
[PAKA] Out? What do
you mean, Mr. Iride?
This is a protest.
You need to bring Kaikoku back.
'Cause until he's here,
I'm not playing anything.
[PAKA stammering]
Th‐This is so
unlike you, Mr. Iride!
You've always been such
an enthusiastic participant‐‐
so devoted to every game!
Don't tell me I'll be
forced to banish you to
the dreaded White Room as well!
I'm fine with it.
Besides, if you do,
then at least I'll be able
to keep him company.
[ZAKURO]
Iride...
I never liked listenin'
to you, anyway.
If Akatsuki's out, so am I.
Same goes for me.
This is too one‐sided.
[YUZU]
Here's an idea, Mr. Alpaca.
Why don't you postpone the
next challenge for a while?
We're all distraught over
what happened to Kai.
Even if you did make us play,
it wouldn't produce the
results you're looking for.
To be quite honest, even I'm
displeased with your decision.
[PAKA]
Hmm...
[KAIKOKU]
What do you think about Iride?
I'm asking you because
I'm suspicious of him.
[AKATSUKI]
Oshigiri.
[ZAKURO]
Oh, hey.
You should probably
eat something soon.
Take this! Himiko and the
others whipped up some lunches.
Karin made these mushrooms
with the meat
wrapped around them,
and that cute pink stuff
was Yuzu's creation!
[AKATSUKI] Oh, and I put the
seaweed on the panda rice balls.
Aren't they the greatest?
[ZAKURO] Sorry. I didn't
mean to worry everyone.
[ZAKURO]
Look.
[AKATSUKI]
Yeah?
[ZAKURO]
I hate to ask you this,
but you guys are on
our side, aren't you?
Ah?
[ZAKURO] Uh, never mind.
Just forget I said that.
You know what?
I really like you, Oshigiri.
I want to be on
your side forever.
Don't you worry.
We'll be back to
eight players real soon.
[ZAKURO grunts]
[PAKA]
Emergency notice!
Everyone, gather on
the first floor immediately.
[PAKA] For the next 72 hours, I
will afford you an opportunity
to rescue your
missing team member.
You can unlock the path
to the White Room
by deciphering a six‐digit code.
Without even a hint?
That'd take a million guesses.
[PAKA chuckles]
Behold.
[PAKA] Stage Eight is aptly
entitled "White Puzzle."
The hint is on one of
these 30,000 pieces.
Your job is to find the lonely
piece that doesn't fit in
with its friends.
[PAKA] Do you know why
I decided to give you a puzzle
for today's challenge,
Ms. Roromori?
[PAKA]
So that, for once in your life,
you will understand your place.
Hey! Lay off!
What's your beef with Yuzu?
It's fine, Anboy.
Let's get started,
the clock's ticking.
[ZAKURO]
It's her name.
What if Sakura's still here?
In the dungeons?
[KAIKOKU]
I can't let Oshigiri see this.
Hmm?
[gasps]
Where's this go?
[KAIKOKU]
A breeze..?
Is anyone down here?
Look. They've all got
numbers on the back.
[AKATSUKI] And they're six
digits, just like the passcode!
[KARIN] So the correct answer
must be on whatever piece
doesn't belong in the puzzle.
[ANYA] We're really gonna
put this whole thing together?
Wouldn't it be faster to
try each code one by one?
You'd think so, but no.
It'd be less efficient
since only one of us
could do it at a time.
Plus, it's always
possible we might input
a number incorrectly.
That's true,
and for all we know,
this puzzle could be
missing a few pieces.
I mean seriously, all of them
look practically identical.
[YUZU]
Oh, don't worry about that.
Look what happens with these
corner and border pieces.
[AKATSUKI]
Whoa! They stuck together!
The seam and the numbers
on the back disappear, too.
So it's impossible
to make a mistake.
Guess we should roll up
our sleeves and solve it, then.
That's what I recommend.
But, there's no need to
complete the entire thing.
Assuming it's a
200 by 150 piece‐puzzle,
the outer border and corner
pieces should total 696.
If they add up to that
when we count them,
we know we're looking
for an inside piece.
That leaves 29,305.
So we'll have to narrow
those down little by little.
Let's start by sorting corners,
borders, and insides.
[KAIKOKU grunts softly]
Whew. Took long enough.
I can't get over how quickly
Yuzu figured that out.
What is she,
some kind of genius?
I only know a little about
her from our online chats,
but I think she skipped
a grade or two and finished
her master's in another country.
She has a job at a lab
doing plant research,
both as a hobby and
as a source of income.
Weird that she's here with us.
[KARIN] Hmm. Forget what
kind of person she is,
now I want to know
how old she must be!
[AKATSUKI] It's my policy
to never ask a lady's age.
[YUZU huffs]
[KAIKOKU sighs]
[KAIKOKU] There's people
living here, no doubt about it.
‐‐[KAIKOKU gasps]
‐‐[bat clanks]
What's that for?
[KAIKOKU]
Aren't you an ugly bunch?
[CHIHIRO]
Who the hell are you?!
And you better
tell us the truth!
[KAIKOKU]
When asking someone's name,
it's polite to give them
your own name first.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh? Where do you get off,
tellin' me what to do?
[NANAMI]
Hiro.
[KAIKOKU]
Huh.
And I'd like you
to take off that mask
while you're at it. Hiro.
[CHIHIRO grunts] Listen,
I wasn't wearing that thing
'cause I wanted to!
[NANAMI]
Oh, dear.
Here we go. Just ignore him.
Hiro here may be an idiot,
but he's harmless.
You can call me Nanami.
[NANAMI grunts]
[KAIKOKU groans]
[NANAMI]
Pardon me.
I don't mean you
any harm, either.
[ZAKURO]
I'm here for a reason,
and I'm not gonna
let my search end.
I have to find my sister.
[KAIKOKU]
Who's there...?
Oshigiri...?
[KAIKOKU gasps]
You're Sakura!
Yeah, that's my name.
But who are you?
Heh! No way!
Ah! Get away from her!
Are you okay, Sakura?!
This creep is not to be trusted!
[SAKURA]
Relax, Hiro.
Don't go near him.
He'll do something inappropriate
if you get too close.
I can tell that by his face.
[CHIHIRO screams]
Check out this ugly bug
stuck to my back.
[CHIHIRO] You're gonna
snap my spine in half!
Oh, my! So you're awake!
Sorry about earlier.
But I had to determine
whether you were
friend or foe, of course.
I checked you out...
very thoroughly.
[CHIHIRO rasps] Quit, Nanami,
you're makin' him angry!
[NANAMI] And, judging by the
bracelet you're wearing... Hmph.
[KAIKOKU]
Tell me who you guys are.
[NANAMI]
Yes, of course. Introductions.
My name's Nanami Omejima.
[NANAMI]
That's Chihiro Akafuda.
And the young lady
is Sakura Oshigiri.
We're comrades now.
Let me welcome you...
to the underground.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I don't think
I've ever put together
a jigsaw puzzle.
How long does it usually
take people to finish?
Depends on the person, really.
It's taken me half a day
to do a 1,000 piece puzzle.
Half a day?
[ZAKURO]
So, 15 days for 30,000.
Divide by seven people,
and it's two days.
Oh! That means we can make it!
I dunno, that was
for a regular puzzle
with a picture printed on it.
These pieces are all blank,
so I imagine it'll take us
a lot longer to
complete this one.
[HIMIKO whimpers]
[YUZU]
Don't sweat it, Akki.
After all, puzzles
are my specialty!
Thirty‐thousand pieces
is child's play!
But I'll need everyone's
cooperation for this to work,
so we should dispense
with the chit‐chat.
Let's buckle down and get to it!
[ZAKURO]
Yeah, good point.
[HIMIKO]
We'll give it our best!
[puzzle pieces clacking]
[growls]
[NANAMI] Here you go.
Hopefully, they'll fit you.
Thanks for this.
[NANAMI] No trouble, everything
in here is stolen anyway.
Let's find you a new outfit.
Sneakers with
a kimono is so tacky.
[NANAMI] My, young people
these days are brazen!
Casually changing your clothes
in front of a stranger!
Have you no shame?!
[KAIKOKU] It's only awkward
if you make it awkward.
[NANAMI]
Anyway, it's quite a shock.
I never dreamed Sakura's
brother would end up here, too.
We should exchange information.
At the moment, it's just
the three of us residing
in this underground base.
I come from Ninth Avenue,
so I've been here
for about four years now.
Hiro and Sakura
are from Eleventh Avenue‐‐
Wait, slow down.
What do you mean when you say
"Ninth" and "Eleventh" Avenue?
So there are other
places like this one?
Wow, you really are in the dark.
No matter which
Avenue we mention,
we're actually referring
to the same place.
Ninth Avenue. Eleventh Avenue.
There's no difference.
The name is updated every time
a new crop of players comes in.
The truth is, we're on
a secluded island
far off in the sea.
People occasionally come
and go to restock supplies,
but the alpaca makes sure
those activities go unnoticed.
I knew there had to be
others involved besides him.
Yes. Helicopters
even fly in sometimes,
but you won't know it because
you're playing the games.
It's ironic.
Only those who have dropped out
can see the big picture here.
Hey! There's trouble!
It's Sakura.
I think she's missing!
[gasps]
[ANYA growls]
Wake up.
[gasps]
If you're that tired, go nap.
Uh, no, I'm okay!
Let's see, which part were
we working on right now?
[ANYA]
Hmm...
[HIMIKO sighs]
Hey!
Huh? I'm still awake!
I thought I told you
to go take a break!
I'm helping!
[ANYA]
Yeah, right! If you screw up
'cause you're tired,
you'll kill the whole operation!
What he means is:
"I want you to sleep because
I'm concerned for you.
Sweet dreams." Nice, huh?
[AKATSUKI rasps]
There's a nap room next door.
I'm so sorry.
[ZAKURO]
Good grief.
You've been working
pretty hard, too, though.
Aren't you sleepy?
Kaikoku needs us.
[ZAKURO]
Whoa, Aikawa...
[YUZU growls softly]
[KAIKOKU]
Hello there.
Ah! Oh, it's you.
Did you get a makeover?
No, not exactly.
Also, it isn't good to
wander off by yourself
without leaving
a note or something.
It's no big deal.
I do it all the time.
Those two are kind
of overprotective.
Heh!
[KAIKOKU]
Hmm.
Hold on, girl‐Oshigiri,
we're not done here.
[SAKURA]
Sakura.
Sakura. You do know this
isn't the way back, right?
I know. I just
wanted to check out
some radio parts up ahead
that might still work.
One of my tools broke
last time I came,
but now I'll get everything.
It shouldn't take long.
[KAIKOKU]
Hmm..
So, um...
[SAKURA]
Is Zakuro okay?
Couldn't say. But the last
time I saw the guy,
he was stuffing his face
with some mushroom pasta.
So I'd say he's just fine.
[SAKURA]
Hmm. He never changes.
[ZAKURO]
You awake?
You crashed about an hour
after Inaba laid down.
Remember that?
[ANYA gasps]
[ZAKURO]
Swap with me, since you're up.
I need to rest.
[ANYA]
What was that about earlier?!
[ZAKURO sighs]
What do you mean?
[ANYA]
In the lounge.
You said somethin' weird
to Akatsuki, didn't you?
Yuzu was actin' funny, too.
What are you hiding, huh?
[ANYA] Would you stop
secretly doubting people?
You sure know what you're doing.
[SAKURA]
I just copy Nanami.
He's amazingly talented!
He can build radios and
stun guns like it's nothing!
Ah. So that was his creation.
[SAKURA] He's been wanting
to get a hold of these parts.
And, uh... I'm surprising him!
[KAIKOKU] Yikes, poor Hiro. I'll
be nicer to him from now on.
[SAKURA] By the way, apparently
there are mermaids in here.
[KAIKOKU]
Mermaids?
[SAKURA] Nanami said he and a
friend saw one a long time ago,
and it had wispy
long hair like a ghost.
[KAIKOKU]
That's bizarre.
I know! A mermaid and a ghost.
A Mermost!
Wish I'd seen it!
I wonder how it
walks and breathes!
If I had to guess.
‐‐[KAIKOKU grunts]
‐‐[SAKURA] What's the matter?
Uh, something touched my leg.
[SAKURA gasps]
What's that?
Stay back!
[YUZU]
Impossible.
Impossible. Impossible!
Impossible! Impossible!
Impossible!
Puzzles are
the thing I'm best at!
I've solved thousands
upon thousands,
ever since I was a child!
So I can say, without a doubt,
we won't make it in time!
[KARIN]
Yuzu?
[YUZU gasps]
You doing okay?
Sure I am.
[KARIN]
But, your finger's bleeding.
[YUZU]
Oh, that's a bad habit of mine.
It's my way of staying focused.
You worry‐wort! So sweet!
[KARIN sighs softl]
Hey. Listen.
If we succeed in this,
then I'll do any one thing
you want. Don't give up.
Keep at it, all right?
That's it!
[GROUP]
Huh...?
[YUZU growls] What were the
numbers on the first two?
I can't remember!
Easy, "001453" and "017491."
[YUZU gasps]
Are you messing with me?
[KARIN]
What would be the point of that?
Trust me, I'm sure.
My mind's a steel trap‐‐
I remember everything
I see or hear.
Who knew Karin was so eccentric?
Don't call me that!
And you did know. I told you
when we first met in the forest.
I guess I forgot.
[gasps]
I get it now.
[YUZU]
I know what to do.
Everyone...
Lend me your strength.
[YUZU]
We can do this!
Let's save Kai so we
can smack him in the face!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
[KAIKOKU gasps]
[SAKURA gasps]
[KAIKOKU]
Is that... a mermaid?