[KAIKOKU]
Is everyone settled?
There's something we need
to discuss with you.
Let's hear it then.
Well, you see, there was
a bit of an incident
while you were busy
playing Stage 3.
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki.
Have you been tailing me?
Seriously.
You really ought to save that
stealth of yours for the game.
Hmph. I thought I'd
retrieve a new pelt
from a certain
disgusting animal.
[ZAKURO]
It's like everyone's vanished.
[KAIKOKU]
And not just here, either.
I walked to this place
from the forest
and every building
I passed was vacant.
Not a single soul in sight.
We're the only two
people in the area.
[ZAKURO] Wait, you think
the whole city is empty?
[KAIKOKU]
I doubt that alpaca
can run a city this
size on his own.
I'm certain there has to be
some link to the outside.
[PAKAMERA grunting]
[ZAKURO]
Time to head back.
If he finds us, we‐‐
[PAKA]
Oh, I've already found you.
[MONSTER A growls]
[KAIKOKU]
Uh.
[growls]
[ZAKURO gasps]
Oh, god, what is that?
[PAKA]
♪ Ding dong ding, neigh. ♪
Your attention, please.
The following is an
emergency announcement.
The rules have been broken,
guidelines ignored,
and therefore, a penalty
must be dispensed.
I've prepared a stage with
a difficulty level of "S."
The tower has been sealed.
We'll now begin Stage 4,
which I've titled...
..."Exterminate the
Mimicry Maneaters."
[ZAKURO grunting]
[growls]
Try not to get killed, idiot!
[KAIKOKU]
Watch your heads!
[ANYA gasps]
Were you trying to decapitate
me with that swing?!
No, I'm pretty sure
I helped you out.
You freakin' grazed me,
dumb ass!
That's hardly even a scratch.
Give it a lick and it'll heal.
My tongue can't reach that!
I'm not a damn lizard!
[ZAKURO]
All right. Calm down.
Why does everybody
fight so much?
I just don't understand.
[MONSTER A growling]
[AKATSUKI]
Uh, Yuzu?
Akki! Anboy!
We should split up,
take the long way around!
Meet in the basement
food storage room!
Gotcha!
[AKATSUKI panting]
[ANYA] You sounded so
enthusiastic about her plan.
The long way's really long.
[ANYA grunting]
Well, whatever.
Uh?
[ANYA]
You're gonna want one of these.
[AKATSUKI] You know I'm
only in Phys Ed. 2, right?
And I'm not expecting
much from you.
[AKATSUKI]
Is there something wrong?
[ANYA]
Nah, it's nothing.
We should get moving.
Huh?
[AKATSUKI]
Oh, hey, Karin.
Wait a sec.
Didn't you run off
the other way?
[laughs]
Uh. There's something
sketchy about her.
Are you okay?
It's not like you
to be so quiet.
Huh?
[ANYA]
Hey! Get away!
It's not her!
It's not the occult girl!
[AKATSUKI screams]
Ow, jeez! Get off me!
I taste terrible, I swear!
[ANYA]
You let him go!
[MONSTER A growls]
[ANYA grunts]
What the hell were you
thinking back there?
It was stupid, I know!
Look! We've almost
made it to the exit!
[ANYA grunting]
[AKATSUKI]
You okay?
[ANYA]
Go without me. I'll be fine.
[AKATSUKI]
Anya! Hey, get up!
[MONSTER A growls]
[AKATSUKI]
It's not attacking.
But why?
Because the sun set?
Yup, he's asleep.
He ran out of juice and now
he's down for the count.
Anboy here hasn't had a
proper full‐night's sleep
for the last few days now.
Do whatever you want,
he's not waking up.
[ZAKURO]
He can be such a nuisance.
Well, thank goodness. He's okay.
He said something
about medicine earlier.
[YUZU] I'm guessing
he meant sleeping pills.
He always carries
some around with him.
We can ask him what he meant
whenever he finally wakes up.
For now, we really
should focus on
figuring out what that
Karin look‐a‐like was.
It was probably one of those
Mimicry Maneaters
Paka mentioned.
If we're supposed to
exterminate them to win,
I've got a feeling there's gonna
be more than one of 'em.
Ugh.
[ZAKURO] Can you describe it
in exact detail for us?
[AKATSUKI] It seriously looked
identical to Karin. Although...
It did have this uncanny smile
that looked completely
foreign on her face.
[KARIN]
Hey, you're pissin' me off.
Then it pulled me close
and squeezed me tightly.
It was so traumatic.
You're really pissin'
me off! Hmph!
Not much to go on.
Which means it would be
smart for us to investigate.
Hey, Kai.
I'd like to grab some
things from my room.
Would you be kind enough to
accompany me as my bodyguard?
Sure. I'm always happy to help.
[YUZU]
Also. Zak and Akki.
I've got a different favor
I need from the two of you.
It's not moving
the slightest bit.
And it shrunk a whole bunch
since the last time I saw it.
[ZAKURO] Wonder what Roromori
wants to do with it?
No idea, but I trust
she has some sorta plan.
[ZAKURO]
So you two know each other?
I mean, from outside of here?
Well.
This is the first time we've
actually met in person.
She's kinda mysterious.
But it almost feels like
we've met before.
We got it.
Uh. Anya!
He just woke up
a few seconds ago.
Good morning. Or whatever.
[AKATSUKI]
Still half‐asleep, huh?
You worried me when you
collapsed like that.
Where are we?
[AKATSUKI]
The food storage room.
Seriously, I thought
you were dead.
Uh. So I straight‐up passed out?
Shit, that's embarrassing.
Don't be embarrassed.
I was just concerned.
[sighs] Well, it's not that
big of a deal, okay?
In my family, it's actually
not that unusual
to suffer from a
sleeping disorder.
I can't naturally fall asleep.
So I have to force it
with medicine.
It's either that or wait until
I hit my limit and collapse.
I started streaming to
pass the time at night.
Uh, story's over! Stop staring!
[AKATSUKI]
Well, that explains the bags.
Under your eyes, I mean.
Pretty much.
Is that why you always act
like such an irritable jerk?
Yeah, pretty much!
[ZAKURO]
Must've forgotten your makeup.
[ANYA] Huh? What the hell
are you tryin' to‐‐
[HIMIKO] Snack time, guys.
Hope you like bread!
[ANYA, AKATSUKI, ZAKURO gasp]
Oh, wow, it's so delicious.
[ANYA, AKATSUKI, ZAKURO]
Yeah, it's great.
[KARIN] Oh, Himiko.
She's getting so strong!
[YUZU] I know I put it
in here somewhere.
[DOLL]
I'll stomp you next time!
[KAIKOKU gasps]
Ooh! I knew it was here!
[KAIKOKU]
What is that stuff?
[YUZU]
The ace up my sleeve.
There's a poison within.
Why do you have poison?
[YUZU] Hmm? It's just
a hobby of mine.
[KAIKOKU grunts]
Is that Akatsuki?
Yuzu, you dropped thi‐‐
Something wrong?
[YUZU] You really can't
beat this stuff.
[YUZU hums]
Do me a favor
and don't tell Akki.
It's kind of embarrassing.
[KARIN]
Eradicate?
[YUZU]
Precisely.
While we've been busy running
around all over the place,
the vines have managed
to infest the tower.
I considered setting them on
fire, but we're inside, so...
Instead we'll wait for sunset
and begin the eradication then.
It'll be the quickest, easiest
way to handle things.
Divvy these up amongst you
and inject them into the roots.
[KARIN]
Whoa, what is this stuff?
[YUZU]
Poison, of course.
[gasps]
If you happen to stumble
across a Maneater,
give it a full syringe of this.
It'll die from the inside out.
[AKATSUKI] Whoa. I've never
seen anything like this.
It's such a pretty color.
[YUZU]
Yeah! I know, right?!
It's a raw, undiluted
solution manufactured
to ward off the most
vicious jungle predators!
The radiant color
is just mesmerizing.
Don't you agree?
You never let me down, Akki!
I knew you'd appreciate my work!
I do what I can.
[KARIN] Hang on! What happens
if one of those breaks?
Oh. Then he'd die
an awful death.
[ANYA grunts]
Stand up for yourself!
[ZAKURO]
Roromori.
You wanna tell us why
you even have that?
[YUZU] Heh. Don't tell me
you're that naive, Zak.
It can be dangerous
walking alone at night.
The best way to keep perverts
at bay is for a girl
to carry some of her
own personal poison.
[ZAKURO] P‐Personal poison?
I guess I am that naive.
I mean, I go to an
all boy's school.
Are you kidding?!
[YUZU]
Why don't you ask Himi here?
The smartest thing a girl
can do is arm herself.
You can't be too
prepared, right?
Absolutely, you've gotta
be able to defend yourself.
Poison is not a self‐defense!
[PAKA]
♪ Ding, dong, ding, neigh. ♪
[PLAYERS]
Uh?
[PAKA]
Good morning!
This is your host,
Paka, speaking.
One full day has now passed
since you began Stage 4.
I'm glad to see you all in
good health and high spirits.
Now, then. I have
some wonderful news!
Only a single week has passed
since your Real Life Let's Play
began, and oh, my goodness!
You've already exceeded
five million views,
which sets a brand‐new record!
No one has ever racked up so
many views that quickly before.
I hate to get mushy,
but as the supervisor
of 13th Avenue,
I am so proud of you.
[cries]
[blows nose, sobs]
[ZAKURO]
So if this is 13th Avenue,
are there other
cities like this?
Filled with other captives
being forced to play
games against their‐‐
[PAKA]
Mr. Oshigiri.
Did you honestly forget
the purpose of this stage?
[ZAKURO grunts]
[PAKA] Do either of you
have an apology for me?
We just got lost, okay?
[PAKA]
Really? Lost?
[PAKA] Go on and run if that's
how you'd like to play.
I hate to break it to you, but
I do love a good game of tag.
[KAIKOKU]
Then go play by yourself!
[ZAKURO]
Did you get him?
[KAIKOKU] I'm not sure,
but I know I hit something.
[PAKA grunting]
He's some kind of monster!
[PAKA]
There are rules in place
and breaking them
results in punishment.
Needless exploring
is a verboten taboo.
[YUZU]
Understand?
Try to pinpoint the core of
the ivy by following the vines.
It's crucial we all work
together in pairs.
Avoid being on your own,
even at night.
Got it.
I'll keep a handful of you here
to help hold down the fort.
My time will be spent
devising a follow‐up plan.
Karirin will be assisting me.
Himi is in charge
of preparing dinner.
And MakiMaki is
on sleeping duty.
[ANYA] Don't ya think he's
got it a little easy?
[YUZU] It may look that
way to you, but no.
Anyway.
Discerning between real and
fake people might be tough,
so I thought we should
come up with a password.
Hmm. I've got an idea.
What's that look on your face?
[YUZU] I say we make it
something about Karin!
If you've got any suggestions,
let's hear 'em.
How about face‐destroyer?
[YUZU] You're the only one
that applies to, Akki.
[AKATSUKI]
Okay, then short‐tempered.
[KAIKOKU]
Scaredy.
[ANYA]
Loud.
[YUZU]
All excellent ideas. Any others?
‐‐Chicken.
‐‐Gorilla.
[ZAKURO]
Chi‐Chickorilla.
[KARIN] You're all gonna think
twice about these suggestions
when I'm busy killing you.
Heads up, guys!
[YUZU]
Hmm?
[HIMIKO] You should all have a
serving before you head out.
[YUZU, AKATSUKI, KAIKOKU gasp]
That's perfect! All right, guys!
If you hear someone say "Karin,"
you respond with "Pudding!"
[ALL]
Right! Pudding, pudding!
Did she brainwash you?!
[YUZU] The operation
begins in 10 seconds!
I wish you all the best
of luck! Now go!
[PLAYERS]
Yeah!
[KARIN]
What'd you do to them?
They grow really quickly,
but they somehow
wither even faster.
We don't have time to
waste. Let's move on.
[AKATSUKI]
Hey, Anya.
[ANYA]
What?
I was just thinking,
that medication you said
you need to sleep?
[ANYA growls]
[AKATSUKI]
If you asked Paka about it,
I bet he could get some for you.
[ANYA]
Hell no! Ain't gonna happen.
Why would I ask the creep
who kidnapped us for a favor?
Fine, then let me
ask him for you.
[ANYA]
Mind your own damn business!
But‐‐
I don't want you asking
a favor from him either!
[AKATSUKI]
Hey, Paka.
You're watching this, right?
Can we talk in private later?
[PAKA]
As you wish, Mr. Iride.
[ZAKURO]
C'mon, man, don't do it.
Why not? It'd be a lot easier
if I take 'em both out.
[ZAKURO] Knock it off.
Aikawa's done nothing wrong.
If it were Kudou,
on the other hand...
I heard that!
[ZAKURO]
Doin' okay, Iride?
[ANYA] Bastard. I'm gonna beat
the hell out of you later.
Anyway, why is it even
active at night?
[ZAKURO]
Who knows?
Maybe it somehow saved up
enough energy during the day?
Makino. Karin!
I say Karin, you say‐‐
[ZAKURO] Don't even bother.
That's pointless.
[AKATSUKI]
Huh?
[ZAKURO]
Think about it.
Aikawa was fast asleep
when we picked the password!
[ANYA] Why didn't you
wake him up if you noticed?
[AKATSUKI] Wait. Do you think
it's actually sleeping?
Aww! I see that happen
on the train sometimes!
It's kinda sweet, huh?
It is not!
Can we just cut 'em
both down, already?
[ZAKURO]
Calm down!
Why is violence always
your first option?
[KAIKOKU]
Because I'm impatient!
[ANYA] What the hell?
They're both freakin' impostors!
[ANYA, KAIKOKU, ZAKURO
grunting, yelling]
[YUZU] Being restricted to
only the main facilities
turned out to be a
blessing in disguise.
It could only grow
in the hallways
since all the doors
were locked down.
Did you have enough
vials for them?
Yeah, and we've
still got five left.
Well, I've got plenty of
other plans for us to try.
We'll just have to see
what tomorrow brings.
[KARIN]
Hey, wake up. Hello?
[AKATSUKI gasping]
What is it? You okay?
[KARIN]
I've really gotta pee.
Uh.
Just come on! You have to!
We're supposed to stay in pairs!
[door creaks]
[KARIN] You really, really,
really, really better not leave!
Don't worry, I'm right here.
[AKATSUKI]
Great. Now I need to go.
Uh.
Y‐You really startled me.
But, Yuzu, you know this
is the men's room, right?
[laughs]
You okay? Huh?
[YUZU grunts]
[AKATSUKI gasps]
[YUZU]
Yep, right hand again.
Uh?
You clearly don't know this,
but Akki is functionally
ambidextrous.
Although exclusively left‐handed
throughout kindergarten,
he began to use his right
before elementary school.
Now, he writes with his left.
Chopsticks, left.
Handshakes, right.
Catching balls, right again.
Bats with either.
Turns faucets with left.
And when he raises a
defensive hand, it's his left.
But you just protected your
face with your right hand.
Oh. Did I now?
[YUZU] And you turned off
the faucet with it.
Communication, self‐defense,
the ability to lie.
You're a lot more advanced
than the other Maneaters.
Perhaps, could you be their
leader, the big boss of Stage 4?
[AKATSUKI]
Um. Yuzu?
It's really me. Akatsuki Iride.
[YUZU laughs]
Hey. Don't even try.
Since I've dedicated
my entire life
to the tireless
observation of Akki.
Driven by love,
resentment, and curiosity.
If you want the truth,
I couldn't care less if you
turned out to be the real Akki.
I've always dreamed
of dissecting you.
Because that is how
much I love you.
Your outside, your inside.
Everything.
I want to study
every part of you.
Ah... I just...
I want to be the missing
component that completes you!
I only want to understand you,
so... what are you, anyway?
[AKATSUKI chuckles]
Thanks to you, my research
had a practical application.
That smile wasn't fair, though.
You almost made me hesitate.
[ZAKURO] Looks like they've
all withered to dust.
Guess that means
the poison did its job.
Yeah, forget that,
I wanna know what's
up with those two?
[YUZU whines]
I know it's dumb,
but I can't help but feel
a little guilty, you know?
Uh. No, what are you saying?
[YUZU]
It's fine.
The only thing that matters
is that you're okay.
Well, thank you for saying so.
[YUZU]
Oh, I should've just kissed
that dumb thing
before I stabbed it!
[KARIN]
Hmm?
Anya?
[ANYA]
Huh?
[ANYA gasps]
[gasps]