What's that?
[KAIKOKU]
Stay back!
Is that... a mermaid?
[KAIKOKU]
Nope.
[SAKURA]
It's a goldfish.
[SAKURA] It's huge!
Wonder if it's a mutant.
Huh? Check out that mark
next to the dorsal fin!
It almost looks like
a person's face!
All right, let's head back.
[SAKURA]
Hey, you should watch your step.
That part gets pretty deep!
Let me lead.
You know the way?
I come here all
the time in secret.
[KAIKOKU] Now I know why her
brother worries about her.
[KAIKOKU grunts]
[crash, splashing]
Uh...?
[SAKURA]
Mister? Where'd you go?
Welcome back, Hiro.
Did you find Sakura?
[CHIHIRO whimpers]
She's really gone.
I checked her room, the shower,
and even the mushroom spot!
She's not anywhere!
Well, I'm sure she's out
on one of her excursions.
Huh? Where's the guy?
[NANAMI] If you mean Onigasaki,
I sent him to the waterway.
[CHIHIRO]
You're so stupid!
Hey, don't knock me over!
What if he ends up being
alone with poor Sakura?
[NANAMI]
It'd be for the best.
That way they could
walk home together.
[CHIHIRO]
Walk home together?!
Don't say stuff like that,
Nanami! I gotta go find her!
[NANAMI]
Not so fast!
I'm coming with you.
[ANYA] So, what's this
about a lasagna rhythm?
It's the "Luhn algorithm."
Huh?
[YUZU] A common example
is the sequence of numbers
on a credit card. At first
glance, they may seem random,
but they actually adhere
to a strict set of rules.
In fact, I'll use a
five‐by‐ten puzzle
to help you understand it.
The only numbers that
conform to the algorithm
are found in the
very first row‐‐
10, 20, 30, and so forth.
After the first row,
the numbers are random,
but they're never
greater than the number
in the next column over.
In other words, whether a piece
conforms to the algorithm
or not indicates whether
it's horizontal or vertical.
The important takeaway
here is that five‐by‐ten
is the number of row
and column pieces.
Therefore, if we split up the
puzzle into vertical sections,
we can suss out the piece
that doesn't belong.
Only one of the columns
will have an extra piece.
And once we assemble
the ones in that column,
then, whatever piece remains...
Should have the right
passcode on it!
[KAIKOKU]
Can't breathe!
[SAKURA grunts]
[BOTH coughing]
'Kay, let's go this way!
[gasps]
[roars]
Get down!
[NANAMI]
How nostalgic.
You're still alive, huh?
[SAKURA]
You know this fish?
[NANAMI] Yes. One of
the tests four years ago
was something called
"goldfish scooping."
And this resilient fellow
here was the target.
But I have to say,
he was much more adorable
back in the day.
[firecrackers popping]
[SAKURA gasping]
[NANAMI]
Now then, let's return.
Warn us before you do that!
Uh‐oh, it's still following us.
Ah yes, it's probably
thinking about
what a delicious little
snack you'd make.
[SAKURA]
Uh...
Please don't say
stuff like that!
Are you sure you'll
be okay by yourself?
Positive. We're done splitting
the puzzle into sections,
all that's left is to solve it.
It's nothing personal,
I just work better solo.
Then again, if you're
that worried,
you can leave Karirin
behind as my body pillow.
I don't know about that‐‐
[grunts]
[AKATSUKI]
I... mean...
...her... back... hand...
...can be real tough!
[YUZU]
I get the point.
In the unlikely case I fail,
Anboy's idea can be
our last‐ditch effort.
Akki and MakiMaki
haven't slept yet, right?
You should all go
rest till I'm done.
But you haven't
slept yet, either!
Huh?
We'll do that.
Give it your best.
[laughs]
[ZAKURO]
Roromori...
Never mind. Good luck.
[NANAMI] It looks awfully
humanlike when it's swimming,
doesn't it? That's why
Niki called it a mermaid.
[KAIKOKU]
Niki?
Oh, right, you don't know.
He was my former partner.
We were the ones who
dug that tunnel.
Uh‐huh.
And you should be
ashamed, Sakura.
How rude!
Dragging Onigasaki
into your antics.
[gasps]
It's all right to have some
fun, but don't be so wild!
[SAKURA] Uh, sorry.
I'll remember that. But...
[KAIKOKU]
Well, go on.
You have something
to give him, right?
Um. Yeah, but we don't have
to do this right now.
[SAKURA gasps]
[SAKURA]
Uh... For you.
I knew that you really
wanted those parts.
Oh. Yes. I sure did.
[KAIKOKU]
Mm‐hm!
[NANAMI]
Thanks a lot, Sakura.
But stop doing things like that.
I would be crushed if something
were to happen to you.
I get it! Sure! I'll watch out!
Be strong.
What's with you?
[YUZU]
Oh...
I'm so tired, Karirin.
Uh. You'll be okay.
[YUZU] Ugh, all I wanna
do is dive into bed.
Or better yet, dive into Akki.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
I mean, that doesn't
really make sense, but hey.
[KARIN] You're almost done.
So, hang in there.
Right.
Hey, what is this? Roleplay?
[KARIN]
Do you want me to stay or not?
A‐choo!
My, what an adorable
little sneeze you have!
I'm freezing.
Sorry about that.
I'm sure the shower
will be free soon.
Uh.
[KARIN]
What can I do to help you out?
Nothing.
[KARIN grunts]
But still, I want you here.
[KAIKOKU] I wonder if I
should go back there soon.
[NANAMI]
To the White Room?
I wouldn't worry about that.
Paka doesn't concern
himself with the dropouts.
[SAKURA]
Lots of sugar, please!
[CHIHIRO]
I want milk in mine.
[NANAMI]
Coming up.
That's true, nothing happened
when Hiro and I escaped
the White Room, either.
Guess maybe the surveillance
cameras didn't see us.
[KAIKOKU] But what if this
is what he wants?
It's possible he already knows
about the escape route,
and he's using me as
bait so he can catch
all of the dropouts at once.
[NANAMI]
That could be it.
In which case, we'll be
forced to put up a fight.
And if that happens,
we'll need your strength.
Onigasaki. What do you say
to joining our cause?
[KAIKOKU]
No thanks.
[NANAMI gasps]
[grunts]
Hate to say it, but sneaking
around isn't really my style.
I'd rather fly solo
and do my own thing.
I understand.
Either way, though,
we should still meet up
and trade intel sometimes.
[sneezes]
[NANAMI] Goodness, your
face is looking flushed.
[YUZU coughing]
Crap, I fell asleep.
[KARIN]
Yuzu!
Sorry. I threw up.
I'm just anemic.
[KARIN] Hang on‐‐
I'll go get somebody!
[YUZU]
No.
[KARIN] Don't argue
with me, you need help!
Karirin was crying.
I have to get back to work soon.
I need... touch.
I'm so lonely.
Oh, Sis, it's you.
[PAKA]
I'll help you this once.
You owe me.
[PAKA] Next time, don't forget
who your master is... Recorder.
[SAKURA]
Your temperature's high.
Wow, all this just because
of a little water?
You're so delicate.
[KAIKOKU grumbles]
Uh! Well, to be fair,
I'm sure you're exhausted
from being in an
unfamiliar place!
Uh?
Hey, what're those?
Oh, yeah.
Omejima gave these
to me earlier.
[KAIKOKU] Man. Four whole
years and he still has them.
Nanami refuses to give
up on his partner.
No matter what.
I guess he believes he'll
come back and save him,
but who knows?
So what do you plan to do?
Huh?
If you come with me,
you can see your brother.
[SAKURA gasping]
[DOOR 10A]
Correct passcode confirmed.
Access to special section
B‐13 is now available.
[SAKURA]
I don't think Hiro
would want to leave
Nanami behind.
[KAIKOKU]
Hmm...
[SAKURA] He was the same
way when I dropped out.
He got himself
banished on purpose
because he thought I would
be scared to go by myself.
Zakuro's my family, so of course
I want to see him, but...
The three of us are
a family now, too.
I can't abandon them.
Listen, we've got a situation!
Dunno how, but people
are calling for you!
They're outside the White Room!
[gasps]
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki! Open up!
Kaikoku, are you okay in there?
[ZAKURO]
Answer us!
I don't hear him.
[HIMIKO]
Oh no, what if he fainted?
[ANYA] What a pain in the ass.
Kick the door in!
[ZAKURO] All right.
We'll give it ten more seconds.
[NANAMI] Oh, dear. Who knew
these kids were so direct?
Hurry and bring him back, Hiro!
I have to think of a
way to buy some time.
Wait, I know!
Look! There's a piece of
paper under the door!
[ZAKURO]
"Occupied"?
[AKATSUKI]
What?
How do we know
that's really him?
The writing's all
cute and bubbly!
[ZAKURO] Hold on, there's
another one coming.
It is fake!
[AKATSUKI]
Kaikoku!
[NANAMI] I think I just
made things worse!
Shh!
[AKATSUKI] Kaikoku. I have
something important to tell you.
After you left, we played
a game to bring you back.
Please don't worry. You'll
be out of there soon, so‐‐!
[ZAKURO]
Listen.
[ZAKURO] Roromori's resting
in the infirmary right now.
Roro?
[ZAKURO] She worked so
hard to solve the puzzle
that she collapsed.
[ZAKURO]
So, come out!
We're waiting for you!
[SAKURA cries]
[ZAKURO]
Hey, Onigasaki!
Say something, already!
Open the door!
Why aren't you answering?
We need you on
the team, hurry!
[SAKURA cries]
Don't let Zakuro find out.
He can be emotional.
We'll see you.
There you are!
[KAIKOKU]
Yeah, sorry.
I didn't mean to make you wait‐‐
Uh!
What was that for?
It's punishment
for being stupid.
Not sure what you're
getting at, but okay.
Ah! Sorry, sorry, don't mind me!
[MAKINO exhales]
Why are you breathing on me?
It's a welcome‐back ritual!
[AKATSUKI, HIMIKO humming]
[ZAKURO]
You learned your lesson, right?
Don't pull a stunt
like that again.
Hey, give me your
hand for a sec.
[ZAKURO]
Why?
[KAIKOKU]
Just do it.
[ZAKURO]
Uh!
Onigasaki?
I'm happy you're safe.
[ZAKURO]
Huh? Oh, uh, thanks.
[KAIKOKU]
Sorry, Sakura.
I don't think your
message got through.
[knocking]
[door slides]
So, you're back. Good.
Yeah, sure am.
[KAIKOKU]
How do you feel?
As you can see,
I'm right as rain!
Although, my diligent nurse
is refusing to discharge me.
I should be back
in the game tomorrow.
[KAIKOKU]
I talked to Iride and Oshigiri.
You pushed yourself
way too hard.
It's all right.
What happened to you
was partly my fault.
You have questions
for me, don't you?
I'm all ears.
[KAIKOKU] I found some
questionable documents
in your room.
They were full of information
about the rest of us.
So, someone did disturb them.
I noticed my photos of Akki
were tilted differently,
and I had a suspicion
that you were responsible.
Those reports. They're recent.
Does that mean my grandpa‐‐?
Yes, it's true.
Sorry I stayed quiet.
You see, I am this
game's record keeper.
I work for Mr. Alpaca.
My job is to monitor
the game from the inside.
I give him information, though
he doesn't tell me much at all.
Facts about everyone's
participation,
the thoughts and feelings I
observe, progress, results,
things I learned through my own
involvement with the game.
I took this role on out
of pure curiosity.
As you already know, I've got
quite an obsession with Akki.
I was eager to do anything
that would give me a chance
to learn more about him.
I was happy, but...
Should I have been, really?
I didn't want the game to
continue without you or anyone.
It's understandable that
you don't trust me.
[YUZU] I'm aware that my
behavior is suspect, but...
...I'm not sure how long
I can play the clown.
[YUZU] You choose what to do,
with me and the files.
[exhales]
[KAIKOKU] I'm not good at
dealing with this stuff.
[YUZU]
Uh?
My only question
is whether I should consider
you a friend or a foe.
Nothing more.
If it's the former, we can
get back to gossiping.
If it's the latter,
I'll make you pay
for what you did and
then we can gossip.
[YUZU]
Heh.
You sure love chit‐chat,
don't you, Kai?
Yeah. You're the only
one I can talk with,
and I can't lose that.
Which is why...
I'm requesting a truce.
If you decide you agree,
let me know.
[YUZU]
Right.
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki! There you are!
I thought I told you
not to wander off
by yourself without telling me!
Wow, you're not very
emotionally stable, are you?
[ZAKURO] I'll show you
emotionally stable!
My mistake.
Bye, Roro. Feel better.
[ZAKURO] Hey, don't push me!
I'll fight you if I have to!
[YUZU]
Thanks. I will.
Tomorrow, then.