[HIMIKO]
No way! I refuse to do it!
I can't abandon
this precious baby.
I promise I can
take care of him myself!
Ohh!
No way in hell! Say what you
want, but I know the rest of us
are gonna end up being
responsible for him, too!
[PUNITSUKI chirps]
That creepy little blob won't
stop hiding in my bike helmet!
[coos]
[ANYA] I wake up to that
thing every morning!
It's enough to traumatize ya!
[HIMIKO] Don't worry,
I've been training him!
See, he can already
hold out his hand!
Come here, Punitsuki,
show him your trick‐‐
[ANYA yelps]
[ANYA]
That's it, now I'm angry!
[HIMIKO]
Sorry, that time was a fluke!
[ANYA]
I'll teach that slug a lesson!
Wow. What an exciting morning.
[ANYA, HIMIKO shouting]
[AKATSUKI]
Definitely!
[HIMIKO] Kudou doesn't
want to let me keep him.
It's not fair!
[YUZU]
Why not?
[ANYA]
Say something to her, would ya?
[AKATSUKI]
Hm? To who?
You know, the tiny one.
I can't get her to listen
to a word I say.
[AKATSUKI] I'm happy you two
have been getting along.
Like hell we have!
Things are worse now!
[ANYA exhales]
[GIRLS chattering]
I'm not sure how I
feel about this idea.
[HIMIKO] You see.
I killed my big brother.
[ANYA] What do you
mean you "killed" him?
[HIMIKO]
I apparently had a sibling.
[ANYA]
Hm?
[HIMIKO]
I was just a baby,
so I don't even remember
his face or his voice.
Then how could you have?
[HIMIKO] They said he was put
up for adoption because of me.
My parents told me that it had
to be done for my protection.
A few years later, I checked
the family registry
and found out my brother went
missing after being adopted.
Whenever a person's been
missing for seven years,
the government sends out a
death certificate for them.
Which means my brother
is officially dead.
Why did they only protect me?
[HIMIKO] It's my fault.
I killed my brother.
Freakin' ridiculous.
That stupid bean sprout.
Huh? Do you not like natto?
[PAKA]
For your seventh challenge,
you will be playing
hide‐and‐seek.
[PLAYERS]
Uhh...
[ANYA]
That's kid stuff!
[ZAKURO] Kind of odd,
at this point in the game.
[PAKA]
Oh dear, it sounds like you have
no idea what you're in for.
All right, then tell us.
[PAKA] Well, it's
basically hide‐and‐seek.
But it's not the innocent
childhood game you remember.
[ALL gasp]
[ALL laughing nervously]
[PAKA]
Meet the Curse‐Stealing Sisters.
Right to left:
Misery, Isabella, and Carrie.
Your objective is to keep
from being detected.
You may only hide here
on the sixth floor.
However, the hallway and any
of your personal quarters
are fair game.
[whimpering]
[PAKA]
Now, as you can see.
These three young ladies
are quite well‐mannered,
so they will generally
wander the area quietly
and keep to themselves.
But when I produce a sound
above a certain frequency...
...they've been known to
become awfully rambunctious.
[laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[PAKA]
No need to be alarmed,
they'll only give you
a silly little curse.
[ALL gasping]
[PAKA] The first time,
they'll take away your sight.
Get caught a second time,
and your eyeballs
will be ripped clean
out of their sockets.
I'm sure you won't die, though.
[PAKA] As of this moment,
floor six is sealed off.
And, naturally,
the locks on all eight
of your bedroom doors are
no longer functional.
[PAKA] After the game begins,
it will be up to you
to choose a room for your hiding
place and successfully evade
the three weird sisters
and their curse
for an entire 60 minutes.
Every quarter hour,
I'll ring the bell,
which will cue the girls
to begin their search
of whatever room is in closest
proximity at that moment.
It's almost like we're
playing Russian roulette
with a three‐in‐eight
chance of losing,
and we have to survive
four rounds in total.
[PAKA] Yes, you're exactly
right. Additionally...
In order to be victorious
in this challenge,
there mustn't be a
single one of you
marked by the curse
when the clock runs out.
That is to say,
all players must be
perfectly healthy.
Now then, I hope you're
ready to begin
this game of cat‐and‐mouse.
[YUZU] This is a problem.
What should I do?
My panties are drying
in my room!
What a humiliating predicament!
How can you even worry
about that right now?
In seven minutes,
the Trio of Psychos
is gonna come in
and murder us all!
You sure that's what
they were called?
Look, if you're really that
terrified, you should
hide better. The first part is
a game of luck anyway, so.
[HIMIKO]
Luck? What do you mean?
[YUZU] Hm? Well, as soon as one
of them walks into the room,
we'll be one level of cursed.
What makes this difficult is
that we can't get cursed
a second time,
no matter what happens.
[KARIN whimpers]
And in order to achieve
such a thing...
[PAKA]
I know what you're thinking.
It's a tall order
for all eight of you
to make it through
this trial unscathed.
So, allow me to explain
the rescue rule.
[ALL]
Huh?
[ZAKURO] If you find a player
who's managed to avoid
being cursed, touching them
will remove your curse.
[ZAKURO] But will I be able
to touch those three girls?
Of course. If it comes
down to it, I can!
Still, though!
Practicing your grope?
[ZAKURO gasps] No! I'm mentally
preparing myself for this game!
[sighs] Yeah,
that's totally normal.
Any reason you're in my room?
[ZAKURO]
Why not?
We're allowed to hide in any
room we want, aren't we?
Yeah, but statistically
speaking,
our chances will be better
if we all separate.
[PAKA] The top contender
for the White Room
is currently Mr. Onigasaki.
[ZAKURO gasps]
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki.
[KAIKOKU]
Hm?
[ZAKURO] Try not to be alone
if you can help it.
Why not?
[ZAKURO]
Just because.
Ah. Scared to be
by yourself, huh?
[ZAKURO]
It's not about me!
[MAKINO]
What a pain.
[ANYA] So we're s'posed
to meet in your room
for the last 15 minutes, right?
Yup. If we have a designated
place that's safe,
then we can fix everyone's
curses at once.
[YUZU] The bell should
ring every 15 minutes.
We can pass two,
but round three is key.
We'll be fine as long
as at least one of us is
curse‐free going
into the final bit.
When the bell rings for
the fourth time‐‐
that's the biggest gamble,
'cause we'll all be together.
So it's a three‐in‐eight chance,
three times. Can we do it?
[AKATSUKI]
I dunno.
I'm just glad you
took your medicine.
It'd be bad if you passed
out during this one.
[ANYA]
True.
Wow, this takes me back.
I haven't played hide‐and‐seek
in like two months!
What are you, six years old?
[AKATSUKI]
Just 30 more seconds.
[bell rings]
[hisses]
[whimpers]
[slurping]
[snoring]
[PAKA]
How unfortunate.
Talk about a rocky start.
[laughing]
[CARRIE laughs]
[KARIN screams]
[ZAKURO]
That's Sarayashiki!
That means all the
girls have been cursed.
Things are looking bleak now.
[ZAKURO gasps]
Oh, no!
Peekaboo, I found you!
[KAIKOKU grunts]
[PAKA]
That won't help you at all.
[KAIKOKU gasps]
[laughing]
[ISABELLA laughs]
[HIMIKO]
It's so dark.
Karin? Yuzu?
Are you guys in here?
I can't see a thing!
[YUZU] Don't worry.
I'm right next to you.
[HIMIKO]
Hm? Yuzu! Thank goodness!
[YUZU] It appears you and I
were cursed right off the bat.
[HIMIKO]
Huh?
[YUZU] Plunged into
an endless darkness.
I guess this is the fate of
those who are discovered.
You know, it might
be my imagination,
but my head kinda feels
heavier than normal.
What a coincidence. Mine too.
It must be a side
effect of the curse.
Side effect?
[gasps] Okay, we should
find Karirin!
Oh, yeah, you're right!
She's been so quiet,
it worries me! Come on!
[YUZU]
Uh?
Hm...?
Oh my god.
What is this softness?
Karirin, is that you?
Dammit, what happened to you?
Answer me!
Ooh, you're so irresistibly
squishy! Karirin!
[ANYA laughing]
Aw man, I wish you could see
how goofy you look right now!
‐‐Two masks!
‐‐[ZAKURO] Shut your mouth.
Talk about a relief.
I was hoping you'd be
able to help us out.
Take the curse off.
[AKATSUKI]
Uh, that's just a Pakamera.
Let's see. All I do
is touch it, right?
Oh, hey, I'm as good as new.
That rescue rule's a lifesaver.
Heh! Anya, did you see
that? He talked to a‐‐
[ANYA laughing]
Dude, how do you even breathe
with all that crap on your face?
Ahh. Whoo, I'm about
to die laughin'.
[ZAKURO] Oh, you'll die,
but you won't be laughing.
[KAIKOKU laughs]
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki!
I'm concerned.
That three‐in‐eight chance
is worse than we thought.
If we don't keep
everyone's curses lifted,
then we'll be wiped
out in no time.
So it is better if we split up.
You two should go find
somewhere to hide.
[ZAKURO]
Wait a second.
Somebody's overprotective.
I'm fine.
Huh?
[door slams]
[bell rings]
[footsteps]
[KAIKOKU]
All clear.
Roro sure is disorganized.
[KAIKOKU]
Judging by the angles,
these photos were
taken by Pakameras.
[KAIKOKU] This is a picture
of Roro and Iride.
But why?
Uh! Whoops.
[ANYA grunts]
Dammit!
Shit, it won't come off!
I knew we shouldn't
have switched rooms!
[AKATSUKI]
I know, right?
Now we need to find
somebody who can lift the‐‐
Uh. Ahh! Ow...
Bet that hurt.
Anyway. If I'm not mistaken.
I'm pretty sure I heard
that occult chick scream
the first time, so that must
mean all the girls are out.
If Onigasaki found a way to get
Oshigiri to go lift the curse,
it should be all right.
I wonder, though.
[ANYA]
I ain't goin'.
Huh?!
Whatever happens, I can't let
mask‐boy see me like this.
[AKATSUKI] That's kinda what
you get for making fun of him
before though. Guess that means
I'll have to be the one
to go call for help then.
[gasps]
Now what's up?
[AKATSUKI]
Anya, she's here.
Huh?
[AKATSUKI whispers] She's right
in front of the door.
[thunk]
Let me in, please!
I really want to see you.
We're in trouble.
If she figures out
where we are this time,
she's gonna gouge
out our eyeballs.
We're screwed!
[bell ringing]
[BOTH gasp]
[MISERY]
Come play with me, hurry!
I've been waiting so long!
[MISERY]
Come out.
[AKATSUKI, ANYA whimper]
[BOTH gasp]
[MISERY grunts]
I think she's leaving now.
Don't you move a muscle.
Ah... Ah... Achoo!
[MISERY grunts]
[AKATSUKI]
She's coming!
[ANYA]
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Akatsuki.
[AKATSUKI]
Yeah?
[ANYA]
You couldn't'a held that in?
[AKATSUKI]
I'm sorry
[bell rings]
[YUZU]
Everyone all right?
We ran into some trouble,
so if you could un‐curse us,
that'd be great.
Wish I could, but they
discovered me and Anya too.
Same here. I apologize for
letting you guys down.
[ZAKURO]
Me, too.
[ANYA]
They caught you again?
[ZAKURO]
Excuse me?
How many times are you
gonna let 'em curse ya?
[ZAKURO]
You're one to talk, idiot!
What, me?!
They found us once, we
dodged 'em in two rounds!
[ZAKURO] Once, twice,
there's no difference!
[ANYA] Are you kidding me?
You're crazy!
[ZAKURO]
No way, you're crazy!
Wait. So is there nobody left
who can lift the curse, then?
[ALL]
Uhh...
There's no way
they got all of us!
[ZAKURO]
Hang on. What about Aikawa?
Right, of course.
I can't believe we almost
forgot sweet MakiMaki!
[screams] Okay, who touched me?
Ahh! Hey, let go of my hair!
Whoever's hand that was,
you are freakin' dead!
[ZAKURO]
Ouch! That's my, uh, stop!
[PLAYERS shouting]
Um. Please stop fighting
before somebody gets hurt, okay?
[whimpering]
Ah! Oh my gosh, who
is that, leave me alone!
Himiko.
[HIMIKO gasps]
Aikawa!
[MAKINO]
Are you okay?
Uh‐huh!
[AKATSUKI]
Gosh. I hope that piece of hair
doesn't stop sticking up now.
At least it didn't get
pulled out, though.
Uh?!
Aw, thanks, but can you
tell me who you are?
Hey there, Makino!
So you didn't get cursed!
MakiMaki's here?
[AKATSUKI]
Where did you end up hiding?
In my room.
Sleeping, but I got stuck.
[AKATSUKI]
What does that mean?!
You're our hero, MakiMaki!
Hurry up! Gimme a big
hug so I can see ya!
[KAIKOKU] Ugh, don't scare
the poor guy off.
[ZAKURO]
Glad you're safe, Aikawa.
Yeah, it sure took ya
long enough, Makino.
[ANYA, ZAKURO grunt]
[ZAKURO]
Not you!
The feeling's mutual, pal!
[AKATSUKI] This next round
is the last one, right?
[KARIN] No matter what we do,
the whole thing's based on luck.
[ANYA] Feels like
it's the riskiest game
we've played so far.
[AKATSUKI]
I'm sure we'll be okay.
[PLAYERS]
Hm?
Don't worry.
They won't find us here.
Huh? And how do you know that?
I just kind of... know.
Huh?!
The final round of hide‐and‐seek
begins in one minute.
Uh?!
[YUZU]
Thirty seconds to go.
Ten more seconds.
Nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
[PAKA]
♪ Ding, dong, ding, neigh! ♪
You've reached the end of the
game with zero cursed players,
which means Stage
Seven is cleared.
Please send a representative
to the first floor
so that you may
receive Chromosome Zero‐Six.
[PAKA]
Both their view count
and their progress through
challenges are commendable.
What's most impressive
is that, so far,
no player on the team
has been left behind.
In which case...
I believe it's about time.