[PAKA] They've progressed
this far and so smoothly!
Most impressive.
There's quite a lot to be said
for the talent of this group.
How about that?
I suppose it's time for
the fun to begin in earnest.
Random question. D'you think
Makino has a girlfriend?
[ALL]
Uh?
Hey, stop it, that's hot!
Ooh, what makes you
ask that question?
Well, this could be nothing,
but when Himiko and I went in
to wake him up this morning.
[AKATSUKI]
Makino!
Makino! Rise and shine!
Your breakfast is
waiting for you, kay?
It's bonito flake rice!
Huh?!
Thank you so much, Sumire.
Oh, man.
It was way too
adorable for words.
Is that why Himi's been as red
as a lobster all morning long?
Sumire, huh? That could
be his pet's name.
Nah. He has a cat, but I
think its name is Moshika.
He's the irresistible MakiMaki.
I bet he has five or
six lovers at least!
[HIMIKO] You don't think
he's a player, do you?
All girls talk about is romance.
[ZAKURO]
Iride's there, too.
Potato, potahto.
Come to think of it, are
any of us in a relationship?
[GROUP]
Uhh...
'Kay. I'll take that as a no.
What even is a girlfriend?
A food, maybe?
Can you purchase
one at the store?
And will they
microwave it for you?
[KAIKOKU]
We get it, you're clueless.
Just stop.
Actually, I go to
an all‐girls school.
[KARIN]
Doesn't stop some people.
[ZAKURO]
My school is all boys.
[ZAKURO] And it doesn't
stop some people.
[gasps] You mean,
indulging in carnal desires
before taking the sacred
blood oath of marriage?
That's disgusting!
Did you say "blood oath"?
Buncha morons.
[ZAKURO]
You're awfully quiet over here.
What about you?
Me? No way, I'm not
interested in girls!
[ZAKURO] You sound like
a middle‐schooler!
Yeah, well, you're an
elementary‐schooler!
[ZAKURO]
Toddler!
[ANYA]
Yeah, whatever, fetus!
[ZAKURO]
Why go straight to "fetus"?
[YUZU] Ooh, speak of the devil!
Go on, ask him!
Hey there, buddy,
who's Sumire?
[BOTH gasp]
[KARIN]
Looks like a girlfriend!
[AKATSUKI]
Saw that coming!
[ALL]
Hm?
[HIMIKO]
Uhh...
Huh?
I wonder what kind of person
Makimaki's girlfriend could be?
If he confused her with Himiko,
I guess she must be younger.
Doubt it.
[PLAYERS]
Huh?
The expression on his
face was the kind people
have when they've got an older
girlfriend who spoils them.
Mm‐hm!
Well, I suggest that we settle
this debate with a vote!
You do know that voting
on someone's age
doesn't actually change it,
right, Yuzu?
Who thinks her age...
...is lower than his?
And, higher?
I do!
High!
[PAKA]
♪ Ding, dong, ding, neigh! ♪
[PAKA] As always, I appreciate
everyone gathering so quickly.
[AKATSUKI] Is it time
for the tenth game?
[PAKA] That's certainly
on the agenda, Mr. Iride.
But first, I have prepared a
special treat for you to enjoy.
A special treat?
Calm down. You know
it'll be something twisted.
Happens every time.
I'm sure "special treat"
is the wrong phrase for it.
[PAKA] Well then.
I won't keep you waiting.
[PAKA] Welcome, friends,
to Paka's Island!
As a reward for your miraculous
achievements thus far,
I am proud to invite
you to participate
in this exhilarating
bonus stage!
[ALL gasp]
[ZAKURO] Something tells
me this won't be fun.
[PAKA] Don't be silly! What
classic RPG would be complete
without a relaxing
mini‐game area like this one?
That explains the new outfits.
[PAKA]
In a moment, I will distribute
a number of gold coins
to each of you.
Use them to play any game of
your choosing and try to win
as many additional coins
as possible before
the clock runs out.
Yes, come to Paka!
Subsequently, your
winnings will be tallied up,
at which time you may redeem
them for a selection
of wonderful prizes
at the Coin Exchange!
Coin Exchange?
What kind of prizes are they?
[gasping] Paka Headband, Paka
PJs, Paka Parka, Canned Paka!
[PAKA] Collectors, rejoice!
The rarest of Paka treasures!
Some out of print, some fully
remastered for a new generation!
The idiot loves it,
but it makes the rest of
us wanna blow chunks.
[PAKA] You can't be serious!
Why, this is a lineup
fit for even the most
dedicated of Paka fans!
[HIMIKO]
Hey, what's that thing?
[KARIN "Make Any Request
Come True Ticket"?
[PAKA] I thought the name
was self‐explanatory.
Anyway, if you earn that ticket,
you're entitled to have any
single request granted to you.
[PLAYERS gasping]
[PAKA] Obviously, your
wish must be confined to
The Ones Within and anything,
well, within it, but otherwise,
the sky's the limit!
[ALL grunt]
Sounds great! And seeing
as it's a bonus stage,
we can just relax
and have fun with it!
[PAKA] The duration of this
challenge is 120 minutes,
and there's no restriction
on how many coins
you can accumulate.
Now, go forth, and may luck
and prosperity bless you!
[KARIN]
Low.
[KARIN grunts]
I did it!
Wow it looks like you're
doing pretty well, Karin!
How many coins have you won?
What? I play it safe!
Is that bad?
No, not at all.
What game is this?
Have you never played High‐Lo?
It's a simple game where you're
dealt a card face‐down
and you have to guess
if it's higher or lower
than the dealer's card.
[AKATSUKI] If you're right,
you get double what you bet
and then choose whether
to keep going.
Do what you want,
but unless you start putting up
more than one coin at a time,
you're never gonna get anywhere
with those little bets.
Leave me alone.
It's the way I play!
[HIMIKO laughs]
[ZAKURO]
Already lost a coin.
[ANYA] If you're too chicken to
bet more than one at a time,
then you're not cut
out for gambling.
[ZAKURO] The ones who
really shouldn't gamble
are people like you
who go all in
without considering
the consequences.
[ANYA]
You don't get it.
Gambling's about high stakes.
You win the pot or go
home with nothing.
Leaving everything up to chance
is what makes it so much fun.
[ZAKURO] We're too young
to admire gambling.
My brother said different.
[ZAKURO]
He was wrong!
What's that? You wanna go?
[ZAKURO] Bring it! We'll settle
this before time's up!
[ANYA growls]
[YUZU] I do get where Anboy's
coming from, though.
I'm not interested in
paltry victories, either.
If you ask me, we'd
better go big or go home.
[exhales]
[roars]
[ANYA] You should bet
on your gut instinct.
All in on A!
[YUZU]
I'm all in on Punitsuki.
You, MakiMaki?
It's always smart
to bet on black.
All right, let's get to it!
[ANYA] What the hell? Wait
a sec, I wanna change my bet!
[yells]
Ohh!
[groaning]
[groans, screams]
Why are they all
ganging up on me?
Come on! Go, Mimicry Man‐Eater
B! Fight! Knock 'em dead!
[YUZU] That's odd. I could've
sworn you just bet everything
you had on Mimicry
Man‐Eater A.
[grunting]
[wails]
[PUNITSUKI groaning]
That's my boy!
[YUZU] Anboy. You know
the rules, right?
[ANYA laughs] See that?
I was like "ha!" And "hi‐yah!"
[ZAKURO]
Yeah, I saw.
Saw you throw away
all your coins, that is.
Let him enjoy his
victory cheer, Zak.
We both know he lost in the end.
You're right, Anboy, gambling's
about big wins and big losses.
There's only one option left.
I'll give that furball
a shakedown!
[ANYA] Cough up the coins or
I'll knock your lights out!
[PAKA]
Neigh.
That works.
We shouldn't resort to violence.
Yeah, says the girl with
the flash bomb.
Uh? You've got a hefty sum
of coins there, Himi.
What game have you been playing?
None of them.
These are the coins I
started the game with.
I'm not good at gambling,
so I've just been
watching you guys.
[ANYA]
Ah...
Here! They're all yours
if you want them!
Otherwise, they'll probably
just go to waste.
Whoa! Awesome!
[YUZU]
Oh cool. Himi's an enabler.
[ZAKURO] Most of these
minigames are standard fare
for an RPG, but...
[BOTH grunt, exhale]
[KAIKOKU]
Pipes?
[ZAKURO]
That's from a different game.
‐‐[KAIKOKU] Up and over.
‐‐[ZAKURO] Wait, don't!
You can't dive in without
knowing how the game works!
Oshigiri. Are you one
of those people?
The ones who read the whole
manual before playing?
[ZAKURO]
Yeah, I study it on the toilet.
Well, I'm the type who learns
things through experience.
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki!
Where am I?
It's been a long time since
Kai vanished, hasn't it?
[ZAKURO]
This is why I said to wait.
[YUZU] Knowing him,
he'll pop up again soon.
Uh?!
[AKATSUKI gasping]
[ZAKURO, HIMIKO gasp]
[YUZU]
That was quick!
[AKATSUKI]
You came back huge!
And you have a sweet moustache
for some reason!
You're like, Super Kai!
[KAIKOKU]
It's‐a me!
[roars]
[growling]
[PUNITSUKI grunting]
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[gasps] It's a board game.
[HIMIKO] I wonder how many
people can play it at once?
Sweet! I think I'll
give it a shot.
[AKATSUKI]
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
[PANDA grunts]
It's my old buddy Pandarou!
Long time, no see!
[AKATSUKI]
What a great start for me!
One, two, three.
What's it mean "battlefield"?
[ANYA] Those three steps threw
him right into a battle.
[KARIN]
Is that good or bad?
[ANYA] Must be weird
fighting yourself, huh?
[PUNITSUKI]
Puni!
[PUNITSUKI B]
[PUNITSUKI C]
Puni!
[PUNITSUKI D]
‐‐[PUNITSUKI E] Puni!
‐‐[PUNITSUKI F] Puni!
[KARIN]
Looks like it called for backup!
[PUNITSUKI G]
Puni!
Uh, Puni!
[ANYA]
He can do the same thing?
[PUNITSUKI H]
Puni!
[ANYA] T
hat one's bad too?
What is this, a friggin'
family reunion?
[KING PUNITSUKI]
Puni!
[PLAYERS]
Uhh...
[ANYA, KARIN]
Don't make friends with it!
Holy crap.
What's with this game?
Can't crack a joke.
I'm too tired.
[ANYA]
There's a drink machine, right?
[YUZU] Yeah, but all
it has is Paka Juice.
[ANYA]
Of course.
King Punitsuki was
such a sweet baby.
[AKATSUKI] 'Kay, let's
keep up the good work!
[AKATSUKI]
One, two, three... Four!
[gasps]
[AKATSUKI screams]
[YUZU]
How about you, Zak?
[ZAKURO]
Fresh out.
Onigasaki was on a
winning streak, though.
I can't wait to see
what he's got!
[KAIKOKU]
Feast your eyes, everyone.
[KARIN]
He cashed them in?
[ANYA]
Canned seafood?
I knew he liked sushi, but damn.
[ZAKURO]
What kind of fish is in there?
[PAKA]
Neigh.
[HIMIKO]
Big trouble!
[PLAYERS grunt]
[panting]
Help! It's Iride!
Oh gosh, that hurt. Did I
land on a trap space or...?
[gasps]
Akki?
[ANYA]
Where the hell did he go?
[PAKA] If you mean Mr. Iride,
he's quite safe.
Oh, that's a relief.
He'll be back, won't he?
[PAKA]
Yes, naturally. Although...
As I mentioned before,
this bonus stage
has a set time limit.
And the pitfall trap that
has just claimed our dear
Mr. Iride was designed to be
extremely difficult to escape.
[AKATSUKI]
Uhh...
[PAKA] But as long
as he's able to return
before the clock runs out,
he'll be perfectly fine.
Okay, so what happens if
he doesn't get back in time?
[PAKA]
Don't be alarmed.
I didn't mean to insinuate that
his life would be in danger.
All I'm saying is that
he won't get a chance
to play with
you ever again.
[ZAKURO]
So, he'll be a dropout?
[ANYA growls]
Bastard!
Stop it, Anboy. Every second we
stand here asking questions,
the clock continues to tick.
We should be thinking
about how to save Akki.
[ANYA grunts]
I wonder what would
happen if somebody else
played the dice game and fell
into the same trap that he did?
Or we win the request
ticket and wish him back.
[ZAKURO]
Which of us has the most coins?
[gasps]
I do?
[KARIN groans]
Sorry. I'm just
not good at RPGs.
Or fighting pandas.
[coins clinking]
[ALL gasp]
[MAKINO]
I won.
[gasps] It seems even
Lady Luck can be seduced
by our sweet MakiMaki!
Amazing!
This guy's got the magic touch!
That's gotta be enough coins.
[MAKINO]
I'm drowning.
[ZAKURO]
Uh, we should probably help him!
[KAIKOKU]
After all that,
we still only collected half
of the cost of the ticket.
Hey, I know! If we go
double‐or‐nothing one time,
then we'll have just enough!
That's true.
And getting our hands
on that request ticket
is a sure‐fire way
to rescue Akki.
But that's not our call.
Is that okay?
They're your coins, after all.
Yeah, use them to help Akatsuki.
[sighs] If he's good with it,
then what are we waiting for?
There's not much
of a choice left.
[ZAKURO]
Yeah. No complaints here.
Let's save our friend!
All yeses. What now, Roro?
Doubling our total coins
may sound easy enough,
but it's kind of a massive risk.
I know it's a bit dicey,
but the convenient thing
about going all in
is that you only have
to gamble one time.
Of course, we should
pick the game
that gives us the best odds.
That would be High‐Low.
[YUZU]
Mm‐hm.
Two is the lowest,
and ace is the highest.
If it's one of those two,
then we win on the spot.
Outside of those cards,
the odds get worse as
you approach the middle,
but it's still 50/50.
So I think it's the
perfect game for us.
‐‐[YUZU] Hm?
‐‐[ZAKURO, KAIKOKU sigh]
Well, here goes.
[PLAYERS grunt]
[YUZU] That's the card
I least wanted to see.
Which one? Higher?
Or lower?
[YUZU]
Higher? Or lower?
High!
[PLAYERS]
That's it, then.
The card is...
...higher!
[KARIN, HIMIKO laugh]
[YUZU]
Good to have you back, Akki.
[laughs]
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
Why?
I always worry you.
But I swear,
I'm really doing
much better these days.
Anyway.
Take care, Ichiya.
It's hard to believe, but
we're well past halfway there.
And it's been pretty
easy lately.
I know! We've been
doing so great!
We are, but for how long?
[ZAKURO]
He's in charge. So...
We're bound to run into our fair
share of traps up ahead too.
Let's try hard.
Don't worry. It'll all work out!
[PAKA]
♪ Ding, dong, ding, neigh. ♪
Greetings, Let's Players.
Without further ado,
I would like to commence
with Game Number Ten.