[PAKA]
Uhh...
Stage Three is a dating‐slash‐
nurturing simulation game
called Throbbing Egg
~ Lady Murasaki.
Oh, dear. It's such a lovely day
and yet everyone
looks so glum.
[ANYA grunts]
Hey, don't move!
[PAKAMERA A gasping]
[PAKA]
Ah, yes.
This contraption is a Pakamera.
[ANYA]
"Pakamera"?
[PAKA]
Surveillance robots
that travel around
13th Avenue filming
you all, of course. Notice
they have lenses for eyes.
They act as a kind of supplement
to the city's
stationery cameras.
Not only can they record
outdoors, but their ability
to follow their subject
allows for your audience
to have more complete and
immersive viewing experience.
And in case I forgot
to mention this,
you are completely free to use
any and all of the facilities
in Genome Tower and
the surrounding city.
Except...
[PLAYERS]
Hm?
[PAKA] The tower's
51st floor and above
are strictly forbidden.
Violators will be
severely punished,
so please do take care.
[PAKA] Allow me to explain
the rules of the game.
Your objective is
to care for the girl
who hatches from this egg
and help her build a
successful relationship
with the most popular man
in school, Hikaru Genji.
[ZAKURO] So it's basically
a nurturing game
and a dating sim put together?
[BOTH gasping]
[AKATSUKI] It's huge!
Almost like a dinosaur egg!
[YUZU] Hey, you wouldn't happen
to have a power drill, would ya?
I need to crack this baby open!
[PAKA] Please refrain,
we wouldn't want
the girl ingredients
to spill out everywhere.
[YUZU, AKATSUKI]
"Girl ingredients"?
[PAKA] By the way, this
stage requires a minimum
of four Let's Players.
There's no maximum,
so nominate whomever
you feel is best,
but I do suggest giving
yourselves ample time
to consider your decision.
Aren't these games
your specialty?
I pick Tiny.
[HIMIKO]
Uh...
[HIMIKO whimpers]
I'm guessing by "Tiny"
you mean me?
[ANYA]
Uh, no.
[AKATSUKI] And since it's
part dating sim... Aikawa!
[AIKAWA snores]
[KARIN]
Is he awake?
[YUZU] Aw, don't sleep with
your eyes open, Makimaki.
They're going to dry out.
If no one else wants
to participate,
then can I volunteer
myself again?
What, did you not learn
your lesson last time?
You should play
with us too, Anya.
Oh, that ain't happenin'!
I'll pass, too.
I don't want to put myself
through that again.
Aw, come on.
Based on the genre,
I don't think it'll be scary.
What are you trying to say?!
It's not like the first
one was scary either!
You should go, Oshigiri.
You seem like you'd be good
at dealing with girls.
[ZAKURO]
Huh? Uh, no, I don't think I...
Believe it or not,
Zak's embarrassingly
terrible with the ladies.
[ZAKURO] I mean. I wouldn't
say I'm terrible, but...
[ZAKURO yelps]
[laughing] Oh, I get it now,
you're just scared
of 'em, aren't ya?
Aw, that's precious!
[ZAKURO] How dare you insult me,
you angsty bastard?
You got a bone to pick
with me or something?!
Huh?!
What's this about bones,
I wanna smash your face!
[ZAKURO]
Wow, you are stupid!
Talkin' to yourself, punk?!
[YUZU laughs]
Hey. I think I'd prefer
to sit this one out.
Maybe I'll play the next one.
What are you gonna do then?
Go exploring.
[YUZU sighs] Kai really marches
to his own drum, doesn't he?
[ZAKURO]
Paka left that way, too.
[HIMIKO]
It says in here,
"the girl's looks and
personality will be determined
according to the
breeder's preferences.
The egg should hatch about
an hour after it's warmed up.
[AKATSUKI] It needs warming?
I think I can do that!
[AKATSUKI grunting]
[HIMIKO] Um. That kind of heat
probably won't be enough.
Think about how small
chicken eggs are.
Even those need to be
at 38 degrees celsius!
What kinda girl hatches
out of a freakin' egg?
That Paka's got
some weird hobbies.
[AKATSUKI] Okay! I found
a heater, will this work?
[HIMIKO] Yeah, we'll use
that and the fireplace.
Humidity is important,
so we'll put the boiling
water around it, too.
Oh, and don't forget to roll
it once in a while, guys.
[ANYA]
Man, what a pain in the ass.
Let's just toss it in the bath.
Soft.
Eh?
Huh?
A soft‐boiled egg.
Hang on. That's the first
thing you're saying?
Ding, ding.
Does that mean it's ready?!
[MAKINO]
Microwave it.
[AKATSUKI] I don't know,
what if it's too much heat
and she explodes?
[ANYA] Yeah, what if
her head blows off?
An afro.
[HIMIKO]
Stop it!
[ALL]
Uh?
You can't take the character
creation lightly.
If you make foolish choices at
the beginning just for a laugh,
then you're sure to regret it
whenever a serious scene
comes up later on.
[ANYA]
Oh, sorry.
Doing things like naming
your character A‐A‐A‐A
or making them run around naked
is an insult to
the nurturing genre.
If you don't give them
your time, money,
and love every single day,
there'll be a world of
difference in your final score.
In fact, the massive amount of
effort it requires to succeed is
what makes this kind of game so
fulfilling in the first place!
So whether it's girls,
cows, or vegetables,
each one of them is
my perfect baby!
And we have to give the
babies everything we've got!
To the death!
[ANYA]
Wow...
[HIMIKO]
All right, everyone.
Now let us pray.
Oh, sweet egg baby,
please hatch very soon.
Though if we mess up, we'll just
cook you with crab and ham.
[ANYA]
Huh?
We could make an egg custard
or a mayonnaise omelet,
or maybe an oyakodon carbonara.
Then again, eggs and
crab do sound good.
[ANYA]
Huh?!
[AKATSUKI, HIMIKO] Eggs and
crab. What a tasty meal.
I thought we wanted it to hatch!
Hurry, Kudou, we
need you to tell us
what kind of girl
you like, right now!
What, why me?
[HIMIKO] The manual says
the attributes are defined
by the breeder's preferences!
If all of you shout out
what your ideal type is,
then I'm sure she'll turn out
to be a lovely young lady!
It's like talking about our
crushes at a sleepover!
The egg is about to hatch any
second, so it's now or never!
[ANYA] Who gives a damn
about preference?!
Uh. I guess I'll say a girl
in a school uniform!
[HIMIKO] I'll pray for the baby
to be born as a kind, honest,
and healthy young lady!
[AKATSUKI]
You know...
I miss Pandarou.
[MAKINO]
Afro.
So, this is her.
[YUZU]
Karirin!
Uh? I get a lame
nickname too, huh?
I wish you would cut that out.
[YUZU] Be nice. I'm here to
share a wonderful discovery
with you. You see,
I've just found a sprawling
outdoor bath on Floor 30.
Outdoor bath? That's bizarre.
Very. Anyway, it must be fate
that I ran into you, as I
wanted to get to know you.
Oh.
[YUZU]
And besides...
I'd like to talk
to you about Akki.
[AKATSUKI] The egg has finally
hatched, and with that,
all of our best ideas have
converged into one being.
[AKATSUKI, HIMIKO]
What... have we done?
You must be Mama,
Papa, Papa, and Papa!
Hewwo dere, my name's Murasaki.
[AKATSUKI, HIMIKO]
Why does she talk like that?
Akatsuki. Are you
why she's a panda?
Sorry, when I thought about
someone I liked, I guess that's
the first thought that
popped into my head.
Do you have any idea
how bad you screwed up?
How are we supposed to win
over the school heartthrob
with a giant teddy bear?
Don't talk about
my baby like that.
She's a perfect cinnamon roll,
too good for this world!
You're looking at her like
a mom looks at her child!
Stop being biased!
It's true!
In a girl‐raising game,
the uglier the character starts
out, the cuter they get!
By slowly raising their stats
or even spending all
your real‐world money,
you can make a face
that anyone would love!
I know in my heart
Murasaki has what it
takes to be a knockout!
It's okay, Mama,
don't be sad for me.
Huh?
[MURASAKI] You don't have
to lie, I know I'm ugly,
and too fluffy.
Nobody would love me.
That's nice of you to say,
but the world's not
so black and white.
Damn, what a downer!
And you're making a mess!
You're wrong, Murasaki!
I'm your mom, and I love
you with all my heart!
[AKATSUKI] Papa loves you
too, Pandar‐‐ Uh, ahem!
The world may not
be black and white,
but you are, and
you're gorgeous!
Do you weally think I can
be pwetty, if I twy hawd?
[AKATSUKI] I know you can.
I believe in you!
This is givin' me a headache.
Aren't you gonna say something?
Huh?
[gasping]
Huh?!
Oh. So you and Akki
weren't acquainted before you
ended up in this place together.
You seemed so close, I assumed
there must be more between you.
No way. I'm not
into that weirdo.
I should have mentioned.
I'm what they call
a "completionist."
If I like someone, then I
want to know everything.
And I'm quite taken with you.
Hey. I don't know
if I'm comfortable
being this close
to you in the bath.
I mean, we're girls, but...
Heh. I'm sorry, but I don't
recall specifying I was a girl.
[KARIN gasps]
[KARIN]
Wait, what?
I mean, you have those things...
Uh. And I don't... see a...
[laughing] Oh my god, relax.
I'm joking!
[YUZU laughs]
[YUZU]
Check it out.
The views started rolling
in when I did that!
[gasps] You mean they can
see us in here, too?
Well, I'm not positive, but I
think that's a Pakamera there.
[PAKAMERA yelp]
That was a pretty good shot.
Uh. If that stupid alpaca
doesn't leave me alone,
I'm gonna skin him alive!
Well, we did just get
a little bit closer
to a hundred million views.
So now we know that the counter
keeps climbing for all of us,
even when we're not playing.
No matter where we are
or what we're doing,
the eight of us are
always in a Let's Play.
[KARIN gasping]
We're in this together, Karin.
That's all the more reason
to get acquainted, right?
[MURASAKI]
He woves me, he woves me not,
he woves me, he woves me not.
[MURASAKI sighs]
Papa Bear.
I'm not feewing vewy good.
Huh?
My heart hurts so bad,
I think I'm gonna be sick!
[AKATSUKI]
Mama Bear!
Yes?
Sounds like Murasaki's
got an illness!
A cold, maybe?
[gasps] Ow, my chest!
My heart's breakin'
into little pieces!
[AKATSUKI] Murasaki!
Quick, somebody call a doctor!
[ANYA]
I'm staying outta this.
[MURASAKI snores]
Oh, I understand.
She has a crush on Makino, huh?
Just when I thought
this situation
couldn't get any dumber.
Anyways, I say we head
out to the school
first thing in the morning.
I'm ready to get this
shitty game over with.
[gasps] What did you say?
Every nurturing game
is a treasure,
and I'll prove it to you.
Whoa, put that away, would ya?!
Not till you take that back.
That horrible thing you just
said is a slap in the face
to all the pure and beautiful
babies in the universe!
So then. I should die?
Whether you enjoy
this game or not,
you're still one of
Murasaki's Papa Bears!
I am not!
I am not responsible
for that abomination!
If you don't support your child,
you're an absentee father!
Not to mention your
temper is too short,
just like your eyebrows!
My eyebrows ain't got a
damn thing to do with this!
Hey! Wait!
If Anya is Murasaki's father,
what does that make me?
Can I be her stepdad,
or favorite uncle?
You're just a moron!
No, please don't
touch the hair!
I've got no choice.
[AKATSUKI, ANYA]
Huh?
[ANYA]
Shit!
What the hell is that
chick's problem anyway?
Ugh, my eyes are puffy.
Guess this means we'll be
sleeping in here tonight.
[MAKINO snores]
[AKATSUKI]
You should get some rest, too.
[ANYA] I can't sleep
in a place like this!
Besides, I'm outta medicine.
[AKATSUKI]
Medicine?
[ANYA] Forget it, it's
none of your business.
[MAKINO snores]
[ANYA]
Makino, shut up!
[bell chimes]
Wow, check out the new
hottie on campus!
I'm very happy to meet you,
my name is Murasaki!
[YUZU]
Mm‐hm! What a good girl!
What brings you here?
We're moral support.
You could use more girl power if
you're gonna play a dating sim.
Good grief. Let's go.
[GUARD A] This is
St. Shikibu Girl's Academy!
[GUARD B] Suspicious people
will be banished!
[ANYA] Huh? And what's
so suspicious about her?
Back off!
[GUARD A]
This is a school for girls.
[GUARD B] As such, men are
not permitted to enter!
Gah! Get your hands offa me,
or you're both dead!
Anya, no!
Um, please give him back!
Put him down, right now!
Oh, this is bad.
Anya!
[bell tolls]
[GIRL A]
Mr. Genji!
[GIRL B]
Eat my lunch!
[HIKARU]
My pleasure.
[GIRL C]
Please eat mine too!
[HIKARU]
Of course.
[GIRLS chattering]
Heh. You're just too kind to me!
As if this wasn't complicated
enough already,
the school idol is a teacher.
At least she'll be
with an educated man
who has a steady job.
[YUZU] So, Muramura, how do you
feel about Mr. Genji there?
He seems like a pretty wonderful
guy, and all da girls around him
are really cute too.
Unlike me, cuz I'm just
a big, ugly, stupid loser.
Uh!
No! Don't be mean to yourself,
Murasaki, you're cute!
If you like somebody,
you're supposed to be
honest about your feelings!
We'll work together to figure
out what you need to do.
I know you can win his heart!
Mama Bear.
Would you stop?
[MURASAKI "Somebody I like."
I'll make him very happy!
[HIMIKO] You should sift
the flour a few times.
It'll get the clumps out
so it bakes nice and evenly.
[sneezes]
[MAKINO snores]
You guys aren't helping at all.
Get out!
[AKATSUKI] Maybe we should
see what Mr. Genji's up to.
[MAKINO]
Mm‐hm.
[HIKARU sighs] It's such a pain
being the hottest guy in school.
Those girls are clueless.
Can't they get me something
I really want?
I'm beautiful.
I deserve a present
that reflects that!
Like, for example...
...Dom Perignon!
Yeah, nice shot, me!
I'm gorgeous and a great
athlete! I'm the best ever!
Woohoo! [laughs]
[AKATSUKI] Well, this was
definitely informative.
We need to hurry up
and tell the others.
[MURASAKI]
Sorry to bother you, sir.
[HIKARU]
Mm?
[coughing]
[MURASAKI]
Um, are you okay?
Of course, never better!
What can I do for you?
Well, uh... I'm here to give you
a homemade present from
the bottom of my heart!
[HIKARU]
Uh. Oh, that's so thoughtful!
Heh, heh, heh...
Looks pretty good!
Thanks so much.
Okay then, I guess I
better be on my way.
[HIKARU]
What was that?!
How dare that monstrosity
make a bigger impression
than yours truly!
I simply won't have it!
My name means that I'm
destined to shine brighter
than anyone else!
If I don't stop this, they'll
say I don't live up to it.
I'll be damned if
I let that happen!
I thought I heard someone
crying, Mr. Genji.
I wanted to make sure
everything was okay‐‐
[HIKARU]
You saw it.
The embarrassing side of me
that no one should ever know.
We can't have that. After all,
I'm supposed to sparkle at
all times, no matter what!
I am the illustrious Mr. Genji!
No!
Ma‐Makino!
[HIKARU]
You can't assault a teacher!
How dare you?
What's wrong with you?
Why would y‐‐
Oh, do forgive me, please!
You must be a transfer student.
I would've remembered seeing
you around here before. Wou‐‐
Uh!
[AKATSUKI]
Makino is awesome!
[YUZU]
Yeah, who knew Makimaki could
seduce a person in five seconds?
[AKATSUKI]
Awesome and creepy!
Wait, don't eat that,
it's been on the floor
and it's probably
got dirt all over it!
[AKATSUKI]
Makino is awesome!
[YUZU]
Perfect execution, Makimaki!
[MURASAKI] Dese are for you.
I wanted everybody to have one.
That's why I made
this batch secretwly.
Could you please give one
to my other Papa Bear,
the one that looks
so mean and scawy?
[AKATSUKI]
Right, Anya.
I wonder if he's doing okay.
Outta the way, slowpoke!
Where the hell am I?
[KARIN] Why don't you forget
about this jerk teacher?
Because I can't.
I know he wasn't
very nice to me,
but there's something
I wanna say to him.
I'll tell him that in
spite of everything,
he's a great teacher,
and he lives up to
his name just fine.
That's really sweet.
[KARIN] I'll punch him a few
times on your behalf, then.
[HIKARU sneezes]
[AKATSUKI] I don't know why,
but I feel like Mr. Genji
isn't gonna wake up
for a while.
[inaudible]
[MURASAKI]
You know,
I feel really happy.
What is this?
[MURASAKI]
I think it's time.
[gasping]
Listen...
Mama Bear.
And Papa Bear.
Um, if you don't mind...
...would you please
give me one last hug?
What is this?
Murasaki wanted you
to have that treat.
[door slides]
[YUZU]
Hey. Where'd you two go?
As you guys can see,
we cleared the third stage.
[ZAKURO]
Did something happen?
Yeah, you could say that.
It's a long story.
[YUZU]
Good night.