[YUZU]
Hmph.
[AKATSUKI]
Whoa.
What's that 'sposed to mean?
[grunting, sneezing]
What?
Uh?
Okay?
[AKATSUKI] Should you
find a collapsed person
first, call out to them.
Uh, miss? Hello?
Can you hear me?
[AKATSUKI]
Second,
check for a pulse and to
see if they're breathing.
[AKATSUKI] I'm gonna check
your neck for a pulse now.
Oh! Thank goodness, you're‐‐
[AKATSUKI groans]
[KARIN]
What are you doing? Pervert!
[AKATSUKI]
What? Hey, no, no, calm down.
Let's start over.
My name's Akatsuki Iride.
I swear I'm just a
harmless, regular guy.
[KARIN]
Oh, sure, that's convincing!
Boy, it sure would be nice
to know where we are.
[AKATSUKI] Yeah, I've definitely
been wondering that, too.
There's only one possibility
that makes much sense.
You are a pervert.
One who knocked me out
and brought me here.
Can you stop with
the speculation?
We're in the same boat.
The thing is, I've heard
your voice before.
I'm sure of it.
I have total and absolute
confidence in my memory.
Once I take something in,
I never forget it.
Well, still, let's find
a phone to call the police.
We don't wanna be here
when it gets dark.
There could be bears nearby‐‐
[thud]
[AKATSUKI gasps]
[KARIN gasps]
[KARIN]
Uh. Wha‐‐ Is that real?
Shh! I don't think
it's noticed us yet.
Let's just wait for it to pass.
[KARIN] We don't stand a chance
if that thing finds us.
[AKATSUKI]
Achoo!
[AKATSUKI, KARIN groan]
You idiot! Could you
seriously not hold that in?
I'm sorry, okay?
It's a little embarrassing,
but I'm pretty much allergic
to every type of pollen
there is in Japan.
Yeah, you're right! You should
be embarrassed by that!
[KARIN]
What the...?
[KAIKOKU grunts]
[KARIN, AKATSUKI]
Uh!
[KARIN]
That's... a huge rat.
[KAIKOKU]
Greetings, travelers.
Feel free to provide
a helping hand.
All you need to do
is smash its eyes.
[KARIN]
Huh?
[KAIKOKU]
Go for the eyes.
Stab or gouge them out.
It's a surprisingly obvious
fatal weakness.
Here, you're welcome
to use this.
[KARIN grunts]
What?
Why're you asking me to do this?
Because the boy should be able
to do it without a weapon.
[KARIN grunts] Why the hell are
you running off on your own
and leaving me behind?
[AKATSUKI] No! This is all
just a misunderstanding!
Hi there, big guy.
[sniffing]
[AKATSUKI]
Wow. Your face is enormous.
[KAIKOKU]
Hey! What are you doing?!
Oh! I can't help it,
I've gotta hug your paw!
Seriously, can you please
explain what you're doing?
[AKATSUKI]
It's a panda!
C'mon, haven't you always
wanted to pet one?
His fur is so soft!
It's just like a
comforting blanket!
That's comforting?!
[PANDA roars]
‐‐[KARIN] Uh?
‐‐[KAIKOKU gasps]
[PANDA roars]
See?! Idiot!
[PANDA roaring]
[KARIN, KAIKOKU gasping]
[PANDA]
Hm, hm, hm.
[AKATSUKI] Aw, buddy,
do you have allergies, too?
There's honestly nothin'
to be afraid of!
Did you notice his eyes earlier?
That whole time we were running?
He didn't look down
at us, not even once.
He's probably just out on an
afternoon stroll or something.
He was never actually chasing
after the two of us.
Isn't that right, Pantarou?
Well, I'm impressed.
That was highly observant
for such a frantic moment.
[PAKA]
How excellent. Truly splendid.
I wasn't expecting you to clear
the first stage so quickly.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I officially supervise
the 13th Avenue
of "The Ones Within ‐‐ Genome."
I'm known by the name Paka.
Stage One was "Animal Battle."
Although, the traditional
method of clearing the level
and moving on is to defeat the
gigantic creatures pursuing you.
Mr. Iride, the escape game
Let's Player, surprised us.
I've never seen anyone attempt
to befriend the panda.
It's intriguing,
to say the least.
[PAKA] Untested methods
and new styles of play
have proven to draw in
and fascinate the hearts
of our audience, resulting in
a large surge of total views.
I'm expecting great
things from you.
Now then, everyone.
Please take a moment to
look at your left wrist.
[KARIN]
Huh?
Ew, what is this?
It won't rub off.
[PAKA] Those are epidermal
counter implants. We embedded
all of you with nanochips while
you were still unconscious.
They're directly linked with
the main server in the tower.
So the view count you're seeing
is displayed in real time.
[AKATSUKI] Wait, view count?
What do you mean?
[PAKA]
Come now.
Let's not pretend you're
unfamiliar with the term.
That goes for you two as well.
Sengoku Let's Player,
Mr. Onigasaki.
And horror Let's Player,
Ms. Sarayashiki.
Hey. I never told
any of you my name.
Who the hell are you?
Take off that mask
and show your face.
[PAKA] Oh, no thank you!
It's far too embarrassing!
[PAKA] I swear, you 13th Avenue
people are always so impatient.
Why don't I go ahead and
get straight to the point.
You're only required to
accomplish a single goal
while you're here: Make that
counter on your wrist
tick all the way
up to 100 million.
To be perfectly clear,
it's imperative that you
reach 100‐million views
during this live stream of
"The Ones Within ‐‐ Genome."
Furthermore, you have
an infinite amount of time
to reach this goal.
I urge each one of you
to play as if your very
life depends on it.
[PAKA]
Now that we're all comfy,
you might wanna go ahead
and introduce yourselves
to your fellow colleagues
in forced game play.
Starting at the first
desk by the window,
say your name and game specialty
in a nice, lively voice.
Okay! Hey, everyone!
I'm Akatsuki Iride!
I specialize in escape games!
I like nature, vacations, and
find animal paws adorable!
You're too happy!
[AKATSUKI] But the teacher
told us to be lively.
[KARIN] Yeah, he's also
the guy who abducted us!
Did you forget that we're
all in mortal danger, here?
[PAKA]
All right, next seat please.
Um. I'm Himiko Inaba.
I like farming and
nurturing games.
[PAKA]
I'm trying not to geek out,
but I'm actually a very loyal
follower of your entrancing,
soft‐spoken streams
and videos. As a fan,
it's a true honor and delight
to hear your voice in person.
Do you think you could possibly
whisper breathily into my ear?
Maybe something like "I love Mr.
Paka," y'know, nothing weird.
[PAKA] Sorry, but it's not
your turn yet, Mr. Kudou.
Screw your stupid introductions.
Just let us go free already.
[PAKA] I've already informed
you that any willful acts of
violence toward me are against
the official rules, Mr. Kudou.
If you keep this up,
you will be punished.
Go on and do your worst.
I wanna see you try it.
[PAKA] Starting tonight,
I would advise you
to be very cautious when
eating your meals.
I'm gonna load 'em up with
a ton of bell peppers.
[ANYA]
Is that all you got?
[PAKA] Right, and that utterly
charming fellow is Anya Kudou.
He's a Let's Player specializing
in fighting games.
I guess that makes me
the next one up.
Name's Yuzu Roromori.
I'm big into puzzle games.
Same with mazes and speed runs.
I like to spend my free time
researching tropical plants.
[AKATSUKI]
Yuzu? This is crazy.
You're the Yuzu from Rororo's
Speedrun Stream, aren't you?
It's me! Akki!
From the Hay Fever Stream.
[YUZU]
Whoa, hey, Akki!
Ha, ha! Oh, man, so you
got abducted too, huh?
Hang on, you know her?
Yeah! We hit it off last year
during a "Bury myself in leaves
at a park stream" I conducted.
[KARIN]
Okay, I've heard enough.
[sighs]
My turn.
Karin Sarayashiki.
My specialty is
horror Let's Plays.
If you don't like
that, get bent.
[PAKA laughs] You can't get much
cooler than Ms. Sarayashiki.
Thus, it should
come as no surprise
that a ton of people
want her to step on them.
I mean, you have such‐‐
[KARIN] Shut your snout or
I'll turn you into a fur coat.
[PAKA]
Next row, please.
[ZAKURO]
Zakuro Oshigiri.
I play stealth games.
Can we hurry and get this
dumb stunt over with?
[PAKA] Well, now, that
depends on how hard
you're each willing to work.
[ZAKURO] I've already figured
out that we're all streamers
who happened to Let's Play
"The Ones Within."
But I don't get
why you chose us.
And what comes after
a hundred million views?
What's your true objective?
[PAKA]
Uhh...
[ZAKURO]
Huh?
[PAKA]
Uhh...
[ZAKURO] So you're not gonna
spill your secrets so easily.
Uh, y'know, Zak.
I've got a feeling he's
just screwing with you.
I'm Kaikoku Onigasaki.
I tend to mostly play Sengoku
and Japanese history games.
Nice to meet you.
[PAKA] Thank you,
Mr. Onigasaki. Very lively.
[YUZU]
Hmph.
[PAKA] And last but not least,
we have Mr. Aikawa.
[AKATSUKI, HIMIKO, YUZU]
Hmm?
[MAKINO snoring]
[PAKA]
Wake up, Mr. Aikawa!
Fine. I guess
I'll introduce you.
His name is Makino Aikawa.
He's a dating‐sim player
who relies on his eyes to
conquer rather than his words.
However, as he is known
for his rather reserved
and tight‐lipped streams,
it's exceedingly rare for him
to speak at length.
[ANYA]
I wouldn't call that a stream!
[PAKA]
All right, well done.
You have all been
formally introduced.
Which means we can begin
the election for Stage 2.
Huh? Hold on.
You haven't explained.
[PAKA] Oh, Paka, Paka.
Stage 2. "Ouija Exchange."
Four players are needed.
You'll be drawing
from a set of straws
I stayed up rather
late making for you.
The people who happen
to draw the Paka straws‐‐
Screw your straws! Why don't
you shove 'em up your‐‐
[PAKA] What's that? Are you
saying that you wish to retire?
In that case,
you'd be disqualified.
Which means I'd have no
choice but to imprison you
in the "White Room" on the
lowest floor of Genome Tower.
You would remain alone until
the others finally reach
100 million views.
So you might spend eternity
waiting in that hidden,
silent, cramped room.
This is a young man from a
previous group of players who,
just like you,
complained too much.
The poor fool doesn't even
know that his friends failed,
and so he sits there.
Awaiting a rescue
that will never come.
Waiting and waiting and waiting.
[KAIKOKU grunts]
Too far. That was in
excessively poor taste.
Wouldn't you agree?
[PAKA]
One word of advice.
You would all do
well to comprehend
and respect the reality
of the situation
in which you're
currently involved.
Injury and death are
actual possibilities
because you're taking part
in a real‐life Let's Play.
You're familiar with how
the offline world works.
You know there aren't any
resets or save points.
[PAKA] Now then, let's get back
to the imperative process
of deciding the
players for Stage 2.
[AKATSUKI]
Paka?
Before you start, are we
allowed to volunteer to play?
Y'know. You're an
absolute idiot.
[ANYA] Really? I think
he's more of a dumb ass.
[AKATSUKI]
I just can't help my curiosity.
[KARIN]
Akatsuki Iridiot.
[ANYA]
Ya white‐haired whack job.
[AKATSUKI] Looks like we're
teamed up together again, Karin.
[KARIN] We were never on a team.
Gah, I've got the worst luck.
[ZAKURO] In any case,
we've got no choice now.
Yeah, let's get to it!
[ZAKURO]
Hey, what are you doing?
[ANYA sighs]
You think I'm gonna play along?
You're all idiots. I'm not doing
what that jerk tells me to do.
And who the hell plays
with Ouija boards?
Do I look like a
grade‐school brat?
[ZAKURO] No, but you
certainly act like one.
Huh?
Is it really that big of a deal?
‐‐[ANYA] Mmm?
‐‐[ZAKURO] Hm?
How about this?
You don't have to play with us,
just put your fingertip on it.
Please, we'd owe you big.
Hell no, dude.
Okay, what if I promise to eat
all of your peppers in exchange?
[ANYA gasping]
It's actually moving
on its own! So cool!
[ZAKURO] Do‐‐ Do any of
you know how this works?
Fess up. Come on, which
one of you's pushing it?
[KARIN]
Will you all shut up?
The spirit's trying
to tell us their wish.
[AKATSUKI, ANYA, KARIN, ZAKURO]
Wa...
...ter... Please.
Water?
[ZAKURO] Pretty sure I saw a
fountain in the hallway earlier.
[KARIN]
No, don't!
You can't just
remove your finger!
We have to do everything
in the proper order
or the spirit won't leave
and it'll possess you!
[ZAKURO gasping]
Oh.
Um, that vase is
within arm's reach.
[AKATSUKI] Yes. Heh!
Cool, I think that worked.
[KARIN] Huh. Wow. This is
easier than I expected.
[ZAKURO]
It's moving again.
[ALL]
It wants a friend?
[KARIN] Did this just suddenly
turn into life counseling?
[AKATSUKI] So it doesn't have
any friends?
[ZAKURO] Friends aren't
something you can just get.
You have to make them.
Spoken like someone
who doesn't have any.
[BOTH growling]
[KARIN growls] Enough already,
cut it out, you two.
[ANYA]
Shuddap, get off my case.
[KARIN]
Can you just chill? Seriously...
Well, I'll be your friend.
How's that sound?
My name's Akatsuki Iride.
[ZAKURO]
Leave her alone.
Whoa! What the hell
are you doing?
[AKATSUKI]
Cool, it said okay!
[KARIN growls]
Idiot! Dumb‐dumb!
Moron! Dumoron!
[ZAKURO]
One wish to go.
A...
[ANYA]
...ka...
[KARIN]
...tsu...
[AKATSUKI]
...ki...
[KARIN]
What does it want us to do?
[AKATSUKI]
Uh.
[KARIN]
Hey. What's going on now?
Um. I'm, uh...
I feel like I'm being
pulled by something.
Uh! U‐Uh! I'm not doing this!
Okay, what do we do now?
Hey! Spooky occult girl!
[whimpers]
[growls] You're useless.
[groaning]
You listen! Just 'cause a
person likes horror games
doesn't mean they're
good with ghosts!
Some people enjoy
horror as a genre
but not when it happens to them!
But don't get me wrong,
I'm totally not scared!
[ANYA]
Uh. Right.
[AKATSUKI gasps]
[ANYA] Hey. Anybody know
what floor we're on?
Akatsuki!
[AKATSUKI] Behind you.
There's somebody there.
[ALL gasping]
[ALL whimper]
[KARIN screams]
[ZAKURO]
Wait. What? What's happening?
His ghost! He's already come
back from the dead to haunt us!
[AKATSUKI]
Oh, no, sorry. I'm still alive.
[ALL gasping]
[AKATSUKI sighs] Wow, that was
pretty intense, wasn't it?
I don't think my stomach's
ever dropped like that before!
[KARIN, ANYA]
Fall again!
[AKATSUKI gasps]
[ZAKURO]
Hm? What's up?
[AKATSUKI] Um, there's still
someone behind you.
[ALL gasp]
[ANYA] What the hell?
How'd you get in here?
Hello there.
[AKATSUKI]
You must be the spirit.
Well then,
it's nice to meet you.
What's your name? I hope you
don't mind me asking that.
Thank you for the water.
Of course, it was no problem.
Did you mean it?
You'll be my friend?
[AKATSUKI]
Sure I will.
[FEMALE SPIRIT]
I'm so glad.
Now, you have to come with me.
We can burn up together.
Won't you come with me?
All you have to do is die.
[FEMALE SPIRIT]
See?
You'll forget me
before too long.
[FEMALE SPIRIT]
You liar.
She's gonna burn
this place down!
[ZAKURO] Get away from her!
Iride! Snap out of it!
[FEMALE SPIRIT cries]
[AKATSUKI]
Mm?
[crying continues]
[AKATSUKI]
We really can be friends.
[FEMALE SPIRIT gasps]
[AKATSUKI]
I mean it.
But I just can't go
with you right now.
[AKATSUKI] I've never
broken a single promise
that I've made in
my life, though.
As soon as everything's over,
I promise you.
Hey, good morning, Kudou.
Ya sleep well?
Look, don't be weird.
Just call me Anya, all right?
Uh. Himiko!
Uh?
[AKATSUKI] So the rest
of you were on standby
in the theater while we played?
Yeah. I'm really glad
you all made it out okay.
[HIMIKO]
Uhh...
Quit staring,
or you can eat them.
[HIMIKO]
Uh...
Doesn't this seem
kinda strange to you?
Clearing it was so simple.
I swear, you better
not lose that.
I am not going
through that again.
And also, I guess
I should apologize.
Really? For what?
Y'know, for punching you
when we first met.
[AKATSUKI]
Oh. Don't worry about it.
You mean you're not mad?
[AKATSUKI]
Not the slightest bit.
I would be.
Honestly. It's pretty rare
that I let anything
actually upset me.
[KARIN]
Are you serious? I knew it.
You're a freakin'
weirdo after all.