[PAKA grunting]
[PAKA] The next game
will be exceedingly simple.
[PAKA sighs]
[PAKA] The challenge will take
place here, in the remote ruins
of Thirteenth Avenue's
Dry Dry Desert.
You are to venture into the
deepest depths of this structure
and obtain Chromosome Zero‐Five
from the guard waiting inside.
That is all.
Um. Seriously?
[PAKA] However, only two
Let's Players may participate
this time. One male
and one female.
[ZAKURO gasps]
[KAIKOKU]
Heh.
[PAKA] Now, get ready
for a heart‐throbbing,
couple‐making adventure!
Heh, heh, heh!
[HIMIKO whimpers]
[ANYA]
Dang, don't cry about it!
And why are you only
afraid of me, huh?
Quit teasing poor Himiko,
you big jerk!
"Teasing her"?! I should
be the one crying here!
[PAKA] I am a reasonable man,
Mr. Kudou. And as such,
I wouldn't dream of flying
into a fit of jealousy
and killing you over this.
But tomorrow, you will get
an extra helping of peppers!
[ANYA]
Don't you dare!
[AKATSUKI]
Uh, guys?
If you want me to, I could‐‐
[YUZU]
Forget it.
You've still got a
broken bone, remember?
Heh...
[YUZU]
You need to take it easy.
[AKATSUKI] Oh, it's fine.
I'm ambidextrous, so‐‐
Nope, take it easy.
[AKATSUKI]
But I had perfect attendance.
Take it easy.
[HIMIKO]
Hmm...
[AKATSUKI]
It'll be okay, Himiko.
Anya can be a little
hotheaded sometimes,
but he's actually pretty kind.
[gasps]
This one time,
he spent like an hour helping
a beetle find its way outside.
I was watching him!
[growls] Did you really waste a
whole hour watching that crap?!
[ZAKURO] We already drew for it,
so let's just move on.
[ANYA]
Shut up!
We all know that if you
were in my shoes,
you'd be squealing and
crying like a baby!
[ZAKURO] Trust me, I do not
squeal, and I don't cry.
Yeah? You want me to
make you cry right now?
[PAKA]
Gentlemen!
Please, hold your excitement
until I've explained.
This next stage may appear easy,
but there's one rule you
absolutely can't break.
What's that?
[PAKA]
Under no circumstances
will you be permitted
to tell a lie.
[HIMIKO, ANYA grunt, exhale]
[footsteps]
I‐Is it me, or is the
hallway getting narrower?
Ugh. Just hurry.
Stop falling behind. Tch.
[HIMIKO]
He clicked his tongue at me!
What do I do?
I don't want to make him mad!
[ANYA] Whoa! I know I
said not to fall behind,
but now she's walking
way too close!
Come on, me, say something!
Uh?
[ANYA]
Hey, you gonna talk, or what?
Kudou, have you been
sleeping properly?
Are you taking your medicine?
Huh? What the‐‐?
[HIMIKO]
When we passed by the light,
I noticed the bags under your
eyes are darker than usual.
[ANYA grunts]
[ANYA]
I'm fine.
[HIMIKO]
I'm sorry, but I can't tell
if you're being
honest with me.
[ANYA] I sleep like a log,
now drop it, already!
[HIMIKO gasps]
[MUMMIES moaning]
What was that? Sounds bad!
Yeah. Stand back. Let's see.
[MUMMIES moaning]
[ANYA gasping]
[HIMIKO gasps]
[MUMMIES moaning]
[KARIN] Is it really okay for us
to lounge around like this?
[sighs] Well, what
else can we do?
It's so dark down there,
even the Pakameras
didn't want to
follow them inside.
[PAKA] Indeed, even I'm worried
about Ms. Inaba's well‐being.
All alone with a young man
in a place like that.
The brute had better
not get any saucy ideas.
[PAKA growls]
[KARIN] Hold on, why are you
here kicking back with us?!
Get out of here!
And bring me another pudding!
Aren't you burning up
in that suit, Paka?
I hope you aren't
getting dehydrated.
[PAKA]
It's quite all right.
In the past, I suffered
burns to my entire body.
So, unfortunately, I can no
longer expose my skin.
[AKATSUKI]
Oh, I didn't know.
[ZAKURO]
Need a drink?
[KAIKOKU]
Thanks.
[ZAKURO]
I'm sorry about the other day.
What for?
[ZAKURO]
Back at the demon hideout.
[ZAKURO] I lost my cool
because of my sister.
I couldn't stay calm.
I'm not sure what you mean.
[KAIKOKU] So, are you any
closer to finding her?
[ZAKURO] No. I asked Paka
about it later on,
but he insisted he
didn't know anything.
[KAIKOKU]
That sounds about right.
Oshigiri.
What do you think about Iride?
[ZAKURO]
I dunno.
I guess he's what a little
brother would be like.
[KAIKOKU]
No, not like that.
[ZAKURO]
Huh?
I'm saying that I'm
suspicious of him.
[MUMMIES moaning]
[ANYA]
Whoa, what the hell are these?
I get it. Maybe one
of us told a lie,
and now we're getting
our punishment
for not following the rules.
Wait! That must mean
that you haven't been getting
enough sleep after all!
Is that what you're
worried about right now?!
[MUMMIES moan]
[ANYA] Okay. Do we go back,
or try to break through?
[HIMIKO]
We should break through.
[ANYA gasps]
[HIMIKO] We can wait for an
opening and slip right past.
Smart.
You're tiny enough that you
can squeeze through 'em!
Yeah. Here goes!
[ANYA yells]
[MUMMIES groaning]
[HIMIKO gasps]
The path!
Let's just run for it!
[gasps] Kudou!
That's it! You're dead!
[ANYA]
Hey!
[HIMIKO gasps]
[screams]
[ANYA]
Moron!
[ANYA grunting]
You're so frikkin' heavy!
Heavy...?
[BOTH scream]
[KENYA]
Quit following me!
Cheapskate! Go ahead
and leave already then!
I hope your dad gets
sick with hypothermia,
you big dumb stupidhead!
He's your dad, too.
[ANYA grunts, cries]
Thanks, Ken.
Now I have to console him.
Yeah, sorry, Shinya.
I'll bring some ice cream
when I come back.
What flavor you want?
Anything's fine.
[KENYA]
You want chocolate, little man?
No. Mint chocolate.
Heh. Sure!
[ANYA gasps]
[exhales]
[HIMIKO]
Uhh...
Stay back!
You are way too close!
And quit making that face!
I didn't mean to!
I just thought you might
be hurt or something.
Uh!
[HIMIKO]
Uhh...
[ANYA]
Did I... say anything?
Huh? Oh, no, I'm pretty
sure you didn't.
[ANYA]
Is that the truth?
Um. I think so.
Look in my eyes.
Fine, all you said was "mint
chocolate," I promise!
[ANYA]
Uh! So, I did talk!
Forget it!
[KARIN]
Hmm...
Huh?
Ugh...
[YUZU]
♪ Karirin! ♪
[screams]
Yuzu! Would you please
cut that out!
[YUZU]
Mm... You're so jumpy.
Just relax, you're with me.
Why don't you drop
the act already?
It's obviously him you like.
There's no reason
to use me to hide it.
[YUZU] Aw, what's wrong?
Are you jealous?
[KARIN]
Of course I'm not!
All I'm saying is that
you don't have to act
like such a clown all the time!
A clown?
Thank you.
I'm taking that as a compliment.
You'll all be like this soon.
Since you've already
been chosen.
That said...
Do you think you could
give me some saliva?
Hate to barge in.
You need to learn
some manners, Kai.
Something happen?
Not really.
It's just that Kudo and Inaba
still aren't finished yet.
Iride's at the ruins looking
all depressed‐like.
You're kidding!
I bet he's holding his knees
like a little wet puppy!
[AKATSUKI whimpers]
Maybe you should go over
there and comfort him.
Leave it to me!
Thanks for the heads up!
Bad timing?
No, not at all.
What's her deal?
Yuzu can be so weird
when it involves him.
Iride?
[KARIN]
Yeah.
They said they've never
met before, but...
[KAIKOKU grunting]
[KARIN]
I swear, it's like they've
known each other for ages.
[PAKA]
Hmm...
[HIMIKO]
Look.
There's a ceiling there now.
If it means they can't get to us
anymore, I'm fine with that.
Yeah, but... I'm not seeing
another way out of here.
Huh?
It seems like we're supposed
to put our hands in there.
But how can we be sure
it's not a trap?
I ain't puttin' my hand
in that thing's mouth.
And why'd it have
to be an alpaca?
Why not a damn panda?!
[RUINS GUARD] Fool! Stop kicking
me or you'll regret it.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ANYA]
Hey! Where?
[RUINS GUARD chuckles]
Right here.
Coward.
Come out and fight me!
[RUINS GUARD]
Ouch!
Goodness me!
That smarts, you know?!
[ANYA gasping]
[RUINS GUARD]
Welcome, you simpletons.
It is time for your judgment.
[RUINS GUARD]
Are you ready to be judged?
Lies beget punishment.
Truth begets reward.
So, ye who are lost within me,
your honesty shall be explored.
In doing so‐‐
[RUINS GUARD] Agh.
I told you, that's painful!
Deal with it!
You sure do talk a big game
for bein' a frickin' wall!
Tell us where the exit is.
And cough up the Chromosome
while you're at it.
I ain't got all day, y'know!
[HIMIKO]
This feels like a shakedown.
[RUINS GUARD]
I see.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[HIMIKO]
The ceiling!
Hey! Quit it!
[RUINS GUARD]
Farewell, you eyebrow‐less dolt.
I do hope you enjoy
being crushed flat.
[ANYA] You leave my eyebrows
out of this, dammit!
[HIMIKO]
We're sorry!
We'll listen to everything
you have to say!
[ANYA]
...I swear, I'll kill you!
[MAKINO snoring]
[HIMIKO, ANYA panting]
[RUINS GUARD] You must answer
three simple questions.
[ANYA]
Huh?!
[RUINS GUARD]
Then, you will be rewarded.
Question One.
Memories.
[RUINS GUARD]
Tell me about your first love.
Go on, let the truth lay bare.
[ANYA grunts]
Stop, Kudou!
Don't make him mad!
Yeah, well, this guy's
making me mad!
That face and that smug attitude
are way too familiar!
[RUINS GUARD]
There's no reason to be rude.
[ANYA]
Stop breaking the roof!
Fine, I don't have one!
Hey. We're not supposed
to lie, remember?
[RUINS GUARD]
Hmm.
What you're saying is true.
[HIMIKO]
Uh?
What? You got a
problem with that?
Uh, no.
[HIMIKO]
No one?
[RUINS GUARD]
And now for you, miniscule one.
[HIMIKO]
Me? Uh, let me think.
[RUINS GUARD]
Go on, don't be shy.
Tell me the truth.
[HIMIKO] Okay. He lived
across the street.
Um. His name was Gotanda‐‐
from our school's Whale Club!
[ANYA]
Don't! Gah!
[RUINS GUARD]
Oh? Is that your way of saying
that there were fireworks
between you two?
[HIMIKO]
No, it was just normal!
[ANYA] I really have to stay
on this girl's good side.
[RUINS GUARD]
Question Two.
Personal.
[ANYA]
Ugh, gross!
[RUINS GUARD]
Well, that's insulting.
This is a personification figure
called Kapakapa Slime.
It becomes that which
supports you.
[BOTH gasping]
[BOTH scream]
[door opens, bells chime]
[PAKA]
Ah, if it isn't Mr. Oshigiri.
How can I help you?
[PAKA] If it's about what we
discussed the other day,
I'm afraid I still don't know a
thing about your dear sister.
[ZAKURO]
Not that.
What did you do to Roromori
and the others?
[PAKA] Why, I merely treated
them to some desserts.
[ZAKURO]
Don't play dumb. You were‐‐
[PAKA] Oh, I forgot
to mention something.
The cleaning of the White
Room is finally complete.
So perhaps one of you can
experience it soon.
[ZAKURO]
What is that, a threat?
[PAKA] No, you can
think of it as a warning.
The White Room isn't only for
players who are disqualified.
It's also a depository
for anyone
who severely disturbs
the harmony of the game.
But you shouldn't
be too worried.
The top contender
for the White Room
is currently Mr. Onigasaki.
[ZAKURO]
That's it!
Aikawa.
They're calling you.
[ZAKURO]
Huh? Hey, stop!
[PAKA] Well, that was
certainly unexpected.
[ZAKURO] Aikawa,
tell me what's going on.
Who was calling for me?
I lied.
[ZAKURO gasps]
[SLIME hums]
[HIMIKO]
That's weird.
This thing looks
a lot like Iride.
[ANYA]
Why is it him?
[RUINS GUARD] Ah, so you both
see the same person then?
[ANYA, HIMIKO]
Huh?
[RUINS GUARD]
Question Two, Personal.
The two of you are being
confronted by the entity
who is closest to your heart
at this moment in time.
Wait a second!
[RUINS GUARD] You are to list
five of their admirable traits.
[SLIME hums]
Um, hello,
it's nice to meet you.
[ANYA]
Why would you pick it up?!
[HIMIKO]
Let's see...
Iride is kind, interesting,
attentive, sincere, and
being around him is just like
having a lovable big brother!
[RUINS GUARD] Oh my.
All that in five seconds!
I've got more, too.
[RUINS GUARD]
What about you?
[ANYA] Hm?! Yeah,
everything she just said.
Would you please stop
the ceiling thing?!
Ugh.
You only have to name
five things, Kudou.
I know you can do it!
Of course I can. Here goes.
[SLIME hums]
Argh, fine!
Uh...
I mean, I think he's kinda
interesting, I guess.
[ANYA]
What's wrong with that?!
[RUINS GUARD] I dislike
wishy‐washy people.
I prefer decisiveness.
Lemme think! Blockhead.
Don't cheer me up‐‐
it's distracting!
[SLIME cooing]
[ANYA]
Ah, shit. Four more.
Uh.
Well...
[gasps]
[ANYA]
He wakes me up every day.
He always eats all of my bell
peppers, and when I can't sleep,
he hangs out and plays
games with me.
[ANYA]
And, um...
He...
He doesn't treat me differently
because I'm sick.
[RUINS GUARD]
Very well.
That was pleasantly decisive.
[RUINS GUARD]
One final question.
[AKATSUKI]
It's beautiful.
I hope I can collect
the rest of them soon.
[YUZU]
Akki.
[AKATSUKI]
Uh?
Hey, Yuzu!
So, I was talking with Paka.
He said that if
nothing went wrong,
they'd be back in about an hour.
[YUZU]
Yeah.
[AKATSUKI] Do you think
if I went in there, too,
he would be angry at me?
[YUZU]
Probably. I sure would be.
Uh?
Today's mission.
It isn't for you.
[KARIN] Sheesh. They're
both holding their knees.
[KAIKOKU] So much for
Roro cheering him up.
[AKATSUKI]
Hey, everybody's here.
[ZAKURO]
Don't worry.
Even if something
were to happen,
Paka would make sure
they didn't die.
Besides, Kudou's hard
to kill, like a cockroach.
Hey, who are you callin'
a cockroach?!
I'll teach ya to talk
smack, punk ass!
We made it, guys!
[laughs]
Himiko's back!
And Anya!
Anya! [laughs]
[RUINS GUARD]
Final Question: Confessional.
Speak your sin aloud.
[HIMIKO]
Well...
...you see.
I killed my big brother.