[KAIKOKU'S GRANDPA]
Get out of my sight!
Do not set foot within the
Onigasaki estate ever again!
If those are your wishes.
Damn geezer.
[MAID A]
I'm afraid that Master
doesn't seem to have
much time left.
[MAID B] I suppose that
would explain why
he's been so frantic to
train young Master Kai.
[KAIKOKU]
Like I care.
I'm not that geezer's
prize show dog.
[KAIKOKU] I refuse to become
some ornament for the family.
[ZAKURO] Looks like the target's
finally stopped moving.
About time. Let's hurry up
and finish this.
Kudou will smack us
if we take too long.
I'm going with them! Let go!
Get your hands off me, dammit!
You have to stay with us!
[YUZU] And that's all it takes
to use the transmitter.
Please bring them back safely.
We're counting on you.
We can't fail.
Roro will probably
drug us if we do.
[ZAKURO] We made the right move
leaving Kudou behind.
He lets his emotions
control him.
You should be careful
of that, as well.
Yeah, yeah.
[ZAKURO] In stealth games,
the most important objective
is to complete the mission
and return safely.
They're not about
dispatching enemies.
As soon as we free the captives,
we go straight back
to the village.
Don't even think
about the demons.
That's what Paka
said was our goal.
The bad guys don't matter.
You want me to run
from the enemy, huh?
Well that should
properly shame my family.
[ZAKURO]
Living is the top priority.
If your family name gets
in the way, abandon it.
Good lord, you're extreme.
[ZAKURO]
I'm here for a reason,
and I'm not gonna
let my search end.
I'm gonna guess you mean the
thing with your twin sister?
By the way, what drove you to
talk to me about that stuff?
[ZAKURO] All the others
are playing the game
like mindless sheep.
But not you.
You're the only one looking
for the quickest escape.
Basically, you're the most
determined about getting home,
and that's what I need.
[AKATSUKI]
Ooh!
This room's pretty dang swanky
compared to all the others.
Do you think this
could be Kikka's room?
[KARIN]
What's with you?
How can you stay calm
no matter what happens?
It's freakin' bizarre.
To you, sure,
but it's normal for me.
Uh? Karin, look!
Is that a dollhouse
outside the window?
Except it's so big, it might
as well be a real house.
You're so carefree.
Especially considering we
might end up being murdered.
They'll eat us.
It could happen.
We could be their
main ingredients.
Akatsuki guts mashed
up into terrine!
Slowly‐simmered Akatsuki stew
with tasteful garnish!
Baked and roasted Akatsuki
served as the main dish!
And for dessert,
a bowl of Akatsuki Iride
topped with loads
of whipped cream!
No! Anything but dessert!
[AKATSUKI] Good to see Karin
hasn't lost her cool.
Uh?
Huh? Check it out! Looks like
this bar's a little bent.
[KARIN]
Yeah, you're right.
Although, it's still too
tight to fit through.
[AKATSUKI]
Maybe. I'll give it a shot.
[grunting]
See, I slipped right out!
C'mon, let's beat it!
Uh?
Go ahead. Laugh all ya want!
[AKATSUKI]
What? I'm not laughing.
[lock clicks]
[KARIN]
Hide somewhere, hurry!
Huh? Where's the other guy?
Don't tell me he
slipped through the bars.
Uh, listen, you have no
right to treat us this‐‐
Well, you're the one I wanted,
so it makes no difference.
Who cares where he went?
Ooh, so soft. Just angelic.
Now what am I gonna
do with you...
[footsteps]
[ZAKURO]
It's a big place.
Lucky for us,
there aren't any guards.
[KAIKOKU]
Oshigiri, take a look.
Isn't that idyllic?
[AKATSUKI]
Achoo!
Aw, crap!
Was that...?
[ZAKURO]
Iride? That you?
You guys made it!
You found us!
[AKATSUKI coughs]
[AKATSUKI]
I had to climb through the attic
to get out of that place.
[ZAKURO]
Well, I'm glad you're safe.
What about her?
[AKATSUKI] Oh, yeah!
She's still back there.
If we're not quick enough,
something might happen to her.
[AKATSUKI] Hurry, c'mon!
This way! Right through here!
[ZAKURO]
Huh?
[KAIKOKU]
The hell are we looking at?
Long story short,
it's the dreaded
Onibania family.
[ZAKURO]
Sorry, come again?
The Onibania family.
It's crazy, but all the girls
she abducts, she treats them
like life‐size dolls
to play house with.
She stripped Karin down
in the blink of an eye,
and transformed her into
her new maid, Veronica.
And you just sat there and
watched all this happen?
[AKATSUKI]
Yes, reluctantly.
Meaning you saw her
without any clothes on?
[AKATSUKI]
Yes, reluctantly.
[ZAKURO] Really? Couldn't you
have closed your eyes?
Well. All right, Veronica.
Why don't you pour me some tea?
You know what I'm
in the mood for?
I could go for some
nice Earl Grey.
[KARIN exhales]
Are you listening
to me, Veronica,
do you want me to fire you?!
[KARIN] Do it!
I wish you would fire me!
[MAID C] Hey, whoa!
I'm guessing you're a newbie?
[MAID D] You really don't
want to defy her.
As long as you do what she says,
they won't have any
reason to hurt you.
Just because of some stupid tea?
[MAID C]
Worse, they'll dispose of you!
Yeah! You better play along
and do what I want,
or I'll have my grandpa
smush you into goo.
[PAKA] The enemies on this stage
are quite overpowered.
[KIKKA]
I only need to call for him
and my grandpa will
come wherever I am.
Unlike your supposed
friends who ditched you
and ran away on their own.
[KARIN grumbles]
So go and make me a delicious
four‐course meal.
Veronica.
[AKATSUKI]
It's awful, right?
[KAIKOKU]
So very awful.
[ZAKURO]
Uh...
At least her life doesn't seem
to be in immediate danger.
Iride, were they holding you
in the dungeon with
the other captives?
Can you show us how
to get down there?
Well, um...
The first place they had us
locked up is located over there.
The turtle‐shell‐bondage‐tied
Momotaro tower.
[KAIKOKU]
That's freakin' creepy.
I haven't had the
chance to search any
of the pheasant, dog, or
monkey bondage towers.
Could be any of 'em.
So this whole place is basically
a fortress of perversion.
Who even designed this place?
[KIKKA]
Achoo!
[KAIKOKU]
Shall we split up?
[ZAKURO] If you find the
dungeon, confirm they're
all safe and then come
straight back here.
We'll rescue her first,
and then we'll release
everyone else.
Meet back here in 30.
Got it!
[ZAKURO]
Iride, your foot.
[AKATSUKI]
Huh? What the‐‐?
When did that happen?
Whatever, I'm still
totally fine‐‐
[groaning]
[KAIKOKU]
Here, wrap up both your feet.
Oh, cool, thanks!
All right! I'm off for real now!
[KAIKOKU]
Yeah, just be careful.
I almost let his stupid
face get the best of me.
That was close.
[ZAKURO]
Pheasant tower was a bust.
So he left. That's not good.
A bracelet?
[ZAKURO gasps]
[thuds]
[MAIDS]
Huh?!
‐‐Hey, there you are!
‐‐[MAIDS screaming]
You know where they keep
the key to get in here?
[MAID E]
Uh, yeah, the demon girl
with four long braids
always holds onto it.
[AKATSUKI]
Right, that's gotta be Kikka.
Huh, y'know.
I wonder if she left
it in that first room.
I don't want your food.
But there aren't
any peppers in it.
It's just got some fish flakes.
That's not the problem.
Ohh...
You know what?
Um, what's that?
[ANYA]
I noticed it a while back now.
But ya kinda remind me of him.
Dimwitsuki.
[HIMIKO]
Huh? Do you mean that?
[ANYA]
Yeah. I don't know, it's...
It's like your aura
or something.
Forget I said that.
[HIMIKO sighs]
[ANYA]
Where's Yuzu?
[HIMIKO] Oh, she went
back to Genome Tower.
She wanted to watch their
progress with a Pakamera.
[ZAKURO grunts]
Iride, your foot.
[AKATSUKI] What the...?
When did that happen?
[AKATSUKI] Found it! The key
to the dollhouse dungeon!
I don't know what
else this could be.
All I gotta do now
is stay outta sight.
[AKATSUKI grunts]
[coughs]
You brought this upon
yourself by refusing
to be my granddaughter's
plaything.
[PAKA] I believe you're
going a little too far,
Lord Kihachi.
So you're here.
What do you want?
Kakuriyo's well outside
your area of supervision.
[PAKA] You're welcome to indulge
in that delusion if you like,
but we both know the
entirety of 13th Avenue
is under my jurisdiction.
Now hand over Mr. Iride.
[KIHACHI] Do you really think
I'll give him to you?
You remember the lad's own
words on the matter?
To dispose of him if necessary.
[PAKA] You need to understand
that I consider him
someone indispensable
to my needs.
You sure you want to play
this out, Lord Kihachi?
Humans are such extremely
fragile and delicate creatures.
You can break them
without even trying to.
If you risk that by treating
him any more harshly,
I will employ a full reset.
[PAKA] I am the supervisor
of this realm.
The balance of 13th Avenue
is entirely under my control.
I'm happy to look the other
way if you wish to behave
like you're the king
of the mountain.
However, don't forget
for a single second
that you're nothing more
than a character in a game.
And this act you're currently
so bent on committing.
If you follow through,
it would be equivalent to
breaking the game system itself.
A rather troubling notion,
and I'm afraid that
it just won't do.
[PAKA] I do hope you're
capable of making
a wise decision, Lord Kihachi.
[PAKA] Don't you wish to
spend as much time
with your granddaughter
as you possibly can?
[KIHACHI] You're a buffoon.
Hurry up and get lost.
[AKATSUKI]
Thank you, Paka. Sincerely.
[PAKA] Oh. I didn't realize
you were awake.
Mr. Onigasaki will be
arriving here shortly.
I genuinely wish you
the very best of luck.
Hey, Paka.
Do you think the two
of us could be friends?
I mean, you‐‐
Have you always been
entirely on your own here?
Doesn't it get lonely for you?
You know, my specialty,
well, I'm really good
at escape games.
So can't we escape
this place together?
[PAKA]
I cannot leave.
But why?
[PAKA] I can't leave,
because a promise was made.
[AKATSUKI]
But why?
Hey. Have any luck?
Huh?
[ZAKURO]
My sister...
She was here.
They kept her here.
[ZAKURO]
Two years ago, a beta version
of The Ones Within made
the rounds on the net.
My little sister
really took to it,
but she disappeared
right before she beat it.
Into thin air. I spent
the next two years
following every
single potential lead,
but I couldn't find her.
The police were ready
to give up the search,
and even my parents
agreed with them.
Which led me to make
one last desperate gamble.
I intentionally
got myself abducted
in the hopes of
finding my sister.
[ZAKURO]
And this. It's my sister's.
Her name's engraved on it.
[KAIKOKU]
She was here?
[ZAKURO]
I can't be sure, but that's her.
It's her name.
What if Sakura's still here?
In the dungeons?
Try to stay calm.
Where'd you even find that?
[ZAKURO]
In the pheasant tower.
It was lying in the
corner of the hall.
[KAIKOKU] Where's Iride?
It's been over 30 minutes now.
Oshigiri.
[ZAKURO]
Huh?
[KAIKOKU] You stay put. Just try
to clear your head for a minute.
I'll take a look around.
[KAIKOKU] Why's the signal
coming from the Momotaro tower?
Is that where he went?
Iride!
[AKATSUKI grunts]
I'm really sorry.
I kind of had a run‐in
with Elder Kihachi.
[KAIKOKU]
Come on, we better keep moving.
[AKATSUKI] I know where it is.
I found the dungeon.
It's in the dog tower.
In the very back,
at the bottom of the stairs.
And I've got the key‐‐ Uh.
What's wrong?
[AKATSUKI]
Um, I uh... It's my right arm.
I can't move it.
[PAKA] I can't leave,
because a promise was made.
[YUZU] Well, now that's strange.
What could Akki be crying about?
[door slams]
[MAIDS gasp]
Hey, sorry for the wait.
[KARIN gasps]
You came to save me!
[KAIKOKU]
I'll get this open.
Please!
[MAIDS sigh]
Don't put any strain on it.
It looks broken.
Let's get to the other side
of the pheasant tower.
We should be able to
see the smoke signal
from the village from there.
Smoke signal?
Yeah, to guide us back.
Roro's keepin' it lit for us.
[KAIKOKU]
Everyone get out? Let's go.
[ZAKURO]
Sorry, but go on without me.
I need to confirm
something first.
You two, go on ahead of us.
If you say so.
[KIKKA] Hey! Don't you
people have manners?
You can't just invite
yourselves in!
Ah! Where did all
of my dolls go?
This is appalling!
You thieves are gonna
pay dearly for this!
Afraid you're just
gonna have to play
with this from now on.
[KIKKA gasps]
[chirps]
[KIKKA] I don't want
that little monster!
I only like pretty things and
cute things and elegant things!
For example... Huh?
Hang on. Why do you...?
Your face looks really
familiar for some reason.
[ZAKURO gasps]
Answer me.
Two years back, did you abduct
a girl with a face like mine?
Huh? Two years ago?
Jeez, I forget.
[ZAKURO]
Well remember!
[KIKKA gasps, growls]
Who knows? I probably did.
But she isn't here now, is she?
I'm sure I got bored
and tossed her out.
[ZAKURO gasping]
[ZAKURO]
What the hell?!
[KAIKOKU]
Oshigiri. Listen.
You need to go catch up
with the others.
[ZAKURO]
But!
People who let their
emotions control them
only get in the way.
[ZAKURO]
All right.
[KIKKA] Has he got some
kind of death wish?
That was hilarious! Ha, ha, ha!
Did little Mr. Vengeance think
his fury made him invincible?
[laughing]
Yeah, well, he's
serious to a fault.
So I'd appreciate it if
you stopped teasing him.
Oh! So you knew I was
lying about that stuff?
I mean, I was just
giving him grief
because he was acting
like such a dummy.
And with as many
dolls as I've had,
I can't remember
all their faces.
[KAIKOKU]
You don't say.
Sounds to me like you're
just begging to punished.
[KIKKA]
You're really irritating.
I didn't like you from
the moment I saw you.
A garbage doll like you
deserves to be crushed.
[KIKKA]
Grandpa! Can you hear me?!
I've got one I don't want! Hurry
down! He needs you to stomp him!
Where is he?
Why isn't he coming
down to help me?
[whimpers] Grandpa!
Grandpa!
I'm sorry, my dear Kikka.
The only thing I want
is to be with you.
[KAIKOKU] You really ought to
stop relying on him, y'know.
If you don't learn how
to curb your selfishness,
he'll grow disgusted with you.
That'd never happen!
My grandpa loves me
more than anything!
Are you stupid or something?
There's no grandpa in the world
who resents their grandkids!
[KAIKOKU]
That's where you're wrong.
Not all families get
along with each other.
You choose your own path,
you get cast out.
It's only natural.
[KIKKA gasping]
[KAIKOKU]
Tell me the truth.
Do you really not
remember her face?
[whimpers]
Heh.
Now I get it;
your family hates you.
[KIKKA]
You're just jealous, I bet.
Of how much me and my
grandpa love each other.
[laughs]
You poor thing.
[KIKKA] Oh, you poor,
little, broken doll.
[KAIKOKU]
Hmph.
Man, you really don't
trust me, do you?
[ZAKURO]
Onigasaki.
Let's go home.