[GIRLS]
Hey everyone, we're home.
[ALL]
It's good to have you back.
Hey, Laim, Lapis, Cecil.
How ya been?
[CECILE] Well, with all
of you on the road,
we've been rather lonely, sir.
[chuckles]
Thanks again for allowing
us to return with Gate
before you and the others did.
Well, you could hardly be
keeping an eye on Yumina
if you were still stuck
back in Mismede.
[YUMINA] We brought back
lots of treats and souvenirs!
[LINZE]
Please, help yourselves!
Thank you very much.
On the pride of my family, I vow
to cherish these gifts forever.
Ya wanna see
what they are first?
[TOUYA sighs]
I am beat.
We really need to stop
doing so much.
Yeah.
You're right.
No more adventuring, okay?
Let's just be farmers.
[KOHAKU]
Huh?
[TOUYA]
Guess I'd better take a bath.
[ALL gasp]
Hey, there.
[GIRLS screaming]
[TOUYA]
Sorry!
[ELZE]
Look, I'll admit
that we probably should've
locked the door,
but I still think you could
stand to be more careful.
If you had the decency to knock
this wouldn't have happened.
I know, but I figured that you
girls would've been done by now.
[LINZE]
Touya!
You'll knock, right?
Huh? Oh.
Sure thing.
I have to say, if you'd simply
taken the proper steps first,
then this wouldn't be an issue.
[TOUYA chuckles]
[YAE] If you've truly learned
your lesson, apologize!
Sorry!
[TOUYA] Modeling!
Master Touya.
His Grace, Duke Ortlinde
has come for a visit, sir.
[TOUYA]
Good afternoon.
Hail. What do we have there?
Rubber and steel, I'm tryin'
to make a few bicycles.
They're kinda like
mechanical horses.
Ah. I think I see.
Anything I can do for ya?
[ALFRED] For once, no.
I just wanted to thank you again
for your help with Mismede.
But this "bicycle" of
yours intrigues me.
How long will it take
you to make me one?
Well, I'm still figuring it out.
So, I'd guess at
least 30 minutes.
[ALFRED]
I can wait.
[ALFRED laughing]
[crash]
[ALFRED laughs]
--Allow me to help, Your Grace!
--[ALFRED] This is my mount!
And by God I shall break it.
I'd rather you didn't.
[ALFRED] I shall not be
bested by this "bike."
[ALFRED grunts, laughs]
[YUMINA]
Is that my Uncle?
It sure is.
What's he riding?
Not sure, but he's bad at it.
--[ELZE yelps]
--[crash]
[ELZE] Ow... This is
actually kind of hard.
[YAE]
I believe it's my turn now.
[TOUYA]
Kay, now start pedaling.
[LINZE]
Yeah... Ah!
[TOUYA] It'll take time.
[YUMINA]
What do you think, Touya?
How am I doing?
I can ride around
the whole garden now!
Way to go, Yumina.
You're a fast learner.
I just wasn't focusing, ya know?
It really isn't all that hard.
[TOUYA]
Ahh...
Wait, what are you doing?
Fine, but let me get down.
Hey, you caught up!
These things are surprisingly
easy to ride, don't'cha think?
Way to go, Elze!
I knew you'd catch on.
You're a natural athlete!
I know I am!
[LINZE]
Well, I'm faster!
[TOUYA] They both got really
good all of a sudden.
[YUMINA]
I'm not sure if I should say
that this is thanks to you,
or that this is your fault.
[TOUYA]
Uh?
Wait, I see what
those two are doing!
Hurry up and get
back here, Elze!
It was meant to be my
turn ten minutes ago!
[ALFRED]
Ladies.
It would appear that
I have taken the lead.
[ALFRED laughs]
The duke's certainly having fun.
[LINZE, ELZE scream]
[crash]
[ELZE]
Ow. You okay?
Yeah. What about you, sis?
[ELZE]
I think I'll live.
I'd like to ask a favor
after all, Touya.
Could you make a
small bike for Sushi?
Oh. I'll pay you for
the materials of course.
[TOUYA] Heh. No problem.
I'll get right on it.
[YAE whines]
But if you're busy working
then how will you see
my new biking skills?
[ELZE]
Who's in the lead now, old man?!
[YAE] Hey, wait up!
Well, that definitely explains
where Sue got her intense
personality from.
[MAN 8A]
Keep walkin'.
Or else.
[MAN 8A]
Stupid brat!
[groans]
Damn guards are breathin' down
our necks now, thanks to you.
We told you what would happen
if we caught you workin'
our turf again.
Wait, I'm sorry!
Lemme go and I'll never come
down here again, okay?
Too late for that, kiddo.
[screams]
[TOUYA]
That's enough.
This is a private party,
so butt the hell out.
If it takes two of you and
a knife to beat one kid,
then I'm not really intimidated.
Damn, fellas. So much
for honor among thieves.
You don't know squat about us!
Sure I do.
I know that you can't
outrun a bullet.
That's a good start.
Shame they're just rubber.
[MEN groaning]
[TOUYA]
You all right?
[gasps]
Bye, then.
[RENNE]
Hey, wait!
I just wanted to say
thanks for helping me.
You're lucky I overheard
what was going on in time.
If ya keep on stealing,
ya might not--
[stomach growling]
[TOUYA]
Did ya miss lunch?
Yeah, for about three days.
Tell ya what.
Lemme know what's good
here, and I'll buy ya some.
You got a deal!
[TOUYA gasps] I didn't
realize you were a girl.
Most people don't.
Hi, my name is Renne.
So what, do you live
around here, Renne?
[RENNE]
I stay here sometimes,
but there's a pretty cozy alley
on the other side of town
that I like more.
And your parents?
My dad's gone.
He went to hunt a magic
beast around a year ago,
and nobody's seen him since.
And my momma...
She died just a little
bit after I was born.
I'm sorry.
Renne, would you like
to come work for me?
Huh?!
You'd never have to worry about
food or a place to sleep.
Now, you would have to
do proper work there.
But I'd pay you for it.
So? Whaddaya say?
You'd really let me work
for you? At your house?
On the condition that
you give me your word
you'll never go
back to stealing.
That sound fair?
[RENNE]
Yeah! I-- I won't let you down!
Hey. You clean up good, kid.
Yeah? Ya think so?
From this day forward,
you shall work as a
servant of this household.
Whenever guests are present,
be sure to address Touya
as "sir." Understand?
Yup! I gotcha.
Hi, I'm Cecile.
Come along with me,
and I'll get you started.
I'm off to work, sir.
See you around.
Get to it then.
Have a good time.
[RENNE]
Thanks!
[door slams]
Such an unusual girl.
You think?
By the way, Touya.
Where are the bicycle materials?
[gasps] I totally forgot.
[SUSHI]
So, this is Mismede?
I love it.
It was very kind
of you to do this.
I know how badly Sue
wanted to come here.
Well, thanks to Gate
it's really no trouble.
Touya, let's go home real quick
and grab my new bicycle okay?
I wanna ride it through
town as fast as I can!
That's how you cause accidents.
[YUMINA]
Hey, look.
I think I see Arma there.
What's up, Arma?
[gasps] Hi, Touya!
Hey. How ya been?
[ARMA]
Good!
I didn't know you two
were visiting Mismede.
We're taking my
cousin out shopping.
Oh. I was shopping as well.
[YUMINA]
Oh, right.
Sue, this is our friend Arma.
And Arma, this is Sushi.
It's a pleasure to
meet you, Sushi.
[SUSHI]
Hi! Your ears are super cute.
Can I say that?
[TOUYA gasps]
What's the matter?
See something?
[TOUYA]
Yeah. Look.
Olga's here?
Looks to me like
she's on a date.
So it would seem.
[ARMA]
So, let's follow her!
Wait. We shouldn't impose.
That's why we'll be sneaky.
Wait for me!
Sue, wait! Crap.
[OLGA]
So, at this point,
there was no one left except
the tortoise and the hare.
[OLGA laughs] Do you know
what they were doing?
No, but I'd like to.
That is so adorable!
[SUSHI] Why does the guy
look so awkward?
He wants to hold her hand,
but he isn't sure if that
would be too forward of him.
If he really wants to hold her
hand he should just go for it.
[YUMINA]
Hear, hear.
It's a simple way of
showing affection,
men shouldn't be
so afraid of it.
Don't you agree?
I, for one, think it's
a complicated issue.
[ARMA gasps]
Look, they're going inside!
Ahh.
They're partial to
bananas, you see.
Yeah.
[YUMINA] We can't follow them
in without risking exposure.
[SUSHI] Say, Touya.
Can't you help us out somehow?
Well, I have an idea
that might do the trick,
but I don't really wanna
invade their privacy more.
This is my sister
we're talking about,
and it could be a big
part of her life.
Forget her privacy, I need to
know how this date's going.
[TOUYA sighs]
Long Sense.
[OLGA]
Yes, but enough about that.
I hear that you'll be returning
to Belfist in a few days.
Is that right?
Yes. I'm afraid I must, but...
Once the alliance is formal,
I plan to visit Mismede
as often as possible.
Or... As much as my friends
here would like my company.
[OLGA laughs]
I for one, quite enjoy it.
Sis likes him. I can tell.
I think those two have excellent
chemistry, don't you?
It's so cute!
I need to start going on dates
myself one of these days.
You're much too young
to think of such things.
Even I haven't been on
a proper date yet,
and I'm already engaged.
Heh! Well if neither of
us have been on a date,
and both of us want to,
let's just go on one together!
[YUMINA] Sorry, cousin.
I don't think that would count.
[TOUYA]
Kinda heavy...
[door opens]
[ARMA yelps]
Excuse me.
My apologies. Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay. I didn't see you.
Arma. Are you okay? [gasps]
[gasps]
[LYON, OLGA laughing]
[JAMUKHA]
I see now.
It seems Olga's taken a
liking to this Sir Lyon.
Hope the boy's up for the task.
She's quite a woman.
He'll certainly try.
By the way, why are you running
around wearing a hood?
I sometimes visit the town
in secret to clear my mind.
I bet your ministers are
gonna be furious with you.
Then the flower
bloomed in my hand!
[laughs nervously]
[JAMUKHA]
Ugh, pathetic.
When a man sought a
woman's heart in my day,
he was bold about it!
[THUG 8B]
Piss off! And don't get up.
[THUG 8D]
That'll teach ya.
Leave him be!
Are you gonna make us?
I said to let him go.
All of you should be
ashamed of yourselves.
Ganging up, four on one.
--[YUMINA sighs]
--He's so gallant!
That timid manner he had
with Olga just disappeared!
[ALL gasp]
Cocky bastard. Step up then.
[LYON grunts]
Oh, no!
Let's go!
[TOUYA] But if we go out there,
they'll know we were--
[TOUYA]
Uh?
[THUG 8D yells]
Wait, who the hell are you?
[groans]
[JAMUKHA laughs]
Someone inspired by
this brave young man.
[whack]
You don't think we went
overboard, do you?
Course not. They had it coming.
Um, pardon. That is
Touya, isn't it?
[TOUYA]
Huh?
Sorry, you're the only
person I've ever seen
wear a coat like that.
Plus, there's your voice.
[TOUYA]
Well, shoot.
Lyon, you won!
You're not hurt, are you?
King Jamukha...?
Accel!
You coward! Wait,
I can do that! Acce--
Why don't you stay a while?
Have a little chat with us?
[TOUYA sighs]
Then let's chat about
why you haven't made
a move on Olga!
It's almost as if you aren't
that serious about her!
[gasps] I am very
serious about her!
But, it's hard.
So you earnestly wanna date her,
is that what you're
trying to say?
Of course I do!
Cool. 'Cause she definitely
heard ya just now.
Uh!
[OLGA]
Lyon, I...
[gasps]
I feel the same way.
So, does that mean...
you'll be my girlfriend?
Think so.
[gasps] Yahoo!
[ARMA]
Congratulations, sis!
[OLGA]
Arma? What are you doing here?
--[YUMINA] They're together now!
--[SUSHI] All thanks to us!
[BOTH]
What's going on?
Why were you hiding
in the woods?
[ALL laugh nervously]
[LYON] By the way, Olga.
How old are you?
[OLGA laughs]
Hey, we're home.
I hope we didn't miss anything.
Nothing of great importance.
Although, you did have
another guest arrive.
Who is it?
[squeaking]
[TOUYA]
Paula?!
That's crazy.
You didn't walk here from
Mismede by yourself, did ya?
[LEEN]
Sharp as ever, aren't you?
No Touya, she naturally
made the trip with me.
Hey, Leen. What's goin' on?
I see you found where I live.
Charlotte assisted me in that.
She seemed rather sure
that you wouldn't mind.
What's going on? Is this
woman someone you know?
Oh yeah.
I don't suppose you
would've met her yet.
This is the elder of the fairy
folk back in Mismede.
She just goes by Leen.
Despite her looks, she's
actually way older than us.
You're one of the fairy folk?
But, wait...
[LEEN]
Oh, that?
I'm concealing my wings
with Light magic is all.
They attract more
attention than I like.
Goodness. I can understand why.
Anyway, what brings you here?
[LEEN]
I heard a rumor about you.
Another one of your exploits.
If you truly defeated
a crystalline beast
a few months ago, then I'll
have questions for you.
Huh?
Hey. What's with
our dinner guest?
Yumina says that she's a fairy.
That creepy looking witch girl?
There's no way, the fairy folk
are supposed to be
cute, remember?
[LEEN clears throat]
[BOTH laugh]
So, Leen. What do you
know about these things?
A runner came to the
palace from Lairesse.
That's a smaller village
in western Mismede.
They claimed to have
discovered a crack in the sky
just a few days ago.
The sky cracked?
[LEEN]
It piqued my interest as well.
Enough for me to assemble
a platoon of soldiers
and investigate. However...
Then, just as I was starting
to research the creature,
I was surprised to hear that you
had managed to defeat one.
So, of course I went and
asked Charlotte about it.
And she tells me that you
can use every Null magic
known in this world.
I can't believe you blabbed.
I'm sorry Touya! But I can't
go against my teacher!
Your what now?
Charlotte counts herself very
fortunate to be my apprentice.
I did have to punish her
for keeping secrets once,
but she learned.
That's right.
It was a good lesson.
[LEEN] Here's a sketch of the
magic beast of Lairesse.
Apparently, it squirmed out
of that crack in the sky.
It has a completely
different shape
than the one that we destroyed.
Any clue what these things are?
Just one...
Legend claims that long ago the
world was all but destroyed
by demons. Ancient texts
refer to them as Fraze.
They're said to have red eyes
and translucent bodies.
So does that mean you believe
that these crystal
things are Fraze?
[LEEN]
That I cannot say.
Well, then.
Sitting around pondering
won't get us anywhere fast.
A fair point. By the way, Touya.
I'm moving to Belfast soon.
I have been appointed the
ambassador of Mismede.
Needless to say, I'll
be visiting often.
Oh, and one more thing,
I've been told that you're
proficient with Gate.
[TOUYA]
Yeah, but the catch is,
I can only go to places
I've been to before.
[LEEN] There's another Null
spell called "Recollect."
It allows the user to read
someone else's mind.
Use it in conjunction with Gate
and you can jump to places
from the memories you see.
Whoa. That sounds amazing.
There's a distant place I
need to reach quickly.
Would you mind using those
spells to take me there?
I guess that depends on
where you wanna go.
[LEEN]
East.
As far east as one can get.
The land of Eashen.
Eashen?! Uh?
[LEEN] There's an ancient
ruin in that nation
that I'd like to investigate.
[TOUYA] Do you think it has
something to do with the Fraze?
No, it's nothing like that.
I've always just
wanted to see it.
[TOUYA]
Wait, that's it?!
My master cares for
nothing so much
as indulging her own curiosity.
Th-That was just a joke, okay?
[LEEN] Anyway, this one's
from Eashen, right?
If you were to read her mind,
then we could be there
in five minutes time.
Hey, don't I get a say in this?
My mind is extremely private.
Reading it is not an option!
No need to worry, dear.
Recollect is only capable
of showing memories
you wish to share.
Yeah? But, even so...
The spell also requires
physical contact
between caster and subject.
I hear that the ideal form
of contact is a kiss.
Wait, a kiss?!!
I'm only teasing you.
[TOUYA, YAE groan]
[LEEN]
Yes, good.
Stand here, facing each other.
And clasp hands like so.
[BOTH gasp]
[LEEN] Perfect. Now press
your foreheads together.
You should start picturing the
sights of Eashen now, Yae.
Now, Touya. Cast the spell.
Recollect.
I see it.
[LEEN clears throat]
[BOTH gasp]
I'd really like you to
open up that Gate.
Would you mind?
Yeah! I know, I'm gonna.
Well. Much as I
would like to stay,
I really should get
back to the palace.
Sure. Good work, as always.
[TOUYA]
She ran...
And Gate!
It's exactly like I saw.
So, we're here?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
This is my homeland.
We're in Eashen.