Say.
Since we're in
the capital anyway,
why don't we get
some shopping in?
[YAE]
A fine idea.
[LINZE]
Mm!
[TOUYA]
Hey.
I didn't notice anyone who
looked like that in Reflet.
Is there a name for that race?
They're called demi-humans.
Those are beastmen
you're looking at,
but we use that word to
describe elves, dwarves,
and fairies as well.
You don't say.
[TOUYA] This world is more
different than I thought.
[ELZE] Hey, Touya? What's
going on with that girl?
[TOUYA]
Hey. Is everything all right?
[ARMA shrieks]
Why? What do you want from me?
Well, uh. You just looked...
It seemed like something
might be troubling you.
Actually, I got separated
from my sister in the crowd!
We had agreed on a place
to meet if this happened,
but I have no idea how
to get there from here.
I'll help you find it.
How?
[ARMA]
Olga!
[gasps] Arma!
[OLGA]
You had me worried.
Sorry about that.
[OLGA]
I'm 17!
[AUDIENCE]
Yeah right!
I appreciate you taking
care of my sister.
No problem. We're
always happy to help.
See you around.
Thanks so much!
Now then. There's still
time to go shopping.
It might be difficult to go
everywhere as a group.
Let's split up for a bit
and meet back at the inn.
Sounds good.
I have no objections.
Sure.
I wonder if he was mugged
in some dark alley.
That's the only
excuse I'll take.
I'm sure he just
lost track of time.
Oh, there's the delinquent.
Hey, you're late!
Yeah, sorry!
I lost track of time.
[pants]
[TOUYA]
Dang, it's 5:25 already?
That device keeps track
of the time for you?
Yeah.
A smartphone's like a
Null magic multi-tool.
I see you've equipped yourself
with a rather stylish coat.
Huh? Oh. Thank you.
It's enchanted to make me
resistant to any magic
that I have an affinity for.
The downside would be that
it doubles any damage
from affinities I
don't have, but...
Nice find. It's almost
like that coat
was specially made for you.
And you cut a handsome
figure with it.
[TOUYA] Uh! Well. I guess we'd
better head back to Reflet.
[GIRLS chuckle]
You're still playing shogi?
That's right!
You've been playing non-stop
for almost a week now.
Nobodies gonna be
comin' to the shop
with all this rain.
And there's nothing
you could possibly
be repairing or cleaning
in the meantime, right?
[TOUYA]
Modeling.
A spell that lets me
reshape objects
made of minerals or wood.
[TOUYA]
Let's try it.
Modeling!
[DOLAN, MICAH gasp]
Huh. Cool, it works.
What the heck did you just make?
What about your shop, Barral?
Will it be okay without you?
Yeah, my wife is taking
care of things there.
But listen, Touya.
Would you mind making me
another one of these boards
so I can play at home?
Huh?
[BARRAL]
I'd be awfully grateful.
Well they aren't that hard
for me to make, but--
[BARRAL]
Thanks, you're the best!
Check!
Damn! You stubborn bastard.
[BOTH growling]
Hey. Calm it down, will you?
Huh? It's just a
friendly game, dear.
Whatever.
By the way, Micah,
have you seen
anyone else around?
I'm pretty sure that Linze's
in her room right now.
But Elze took Yae down
to Parent's Café
to try that new dessert
they came out with.
I hear you're the one
who invented it.
Nah, I just showed it to them.
They went out in all this rain?
[ELZE]
We're back!
And we're soaked.
[YAE]
Yes, but we came bearing gifts.
Welcome back. How'd it go?
We got it.
Yup.
The line was a lot shorter
thanks to the rain.
This treat is quite delicious.
They ate there and
brought some back?
[ELZE]
Here. This one's for you, Micah.
[MICAH]
Thanks.
So here's one for Linze.
This one is for me and Yae.
And that one's for the duke.
Be a doll and
deliver it, would you?
Why me?
Why wouldn't you wanna
share a treat with the duke?
He's a nice guy.
[TOUYA]
In that case,
why don't you come
deliver it with me?
I have to polish my gauntlets.
Uh...
[SUSHIE]
It tastes like a cloud of sugar!
[ELLEN] Mind your manners
if front of our guest.
Truly though. This
treat is exquisite.
What did you say it was called?
A roll cake?
[ALFRED]
I envy the people of Reflet,
for they can enjoy this
whenever they please.
If I could use Gate like you,
I'd purchase it daily.
If you'd like me to,
I could give the recipe
to your chef so he can
make it for you here.
That's great!
We can eat it every day
for the rest of our lives!
Now, Sue. That would
be too much.
We shall limit ourselves
to every other day.
[TOUYA] Yeah, that's
probably still too much.
All right, Touya.
You say this game
is called shogi?
Yeah. It's a two-player
strategy game
where you try to capture
the enemy king.
Wanna try it out?
That I do.
No fair, I wanna play, too!
[ALFRED]
Well then, be patient.
You can play as
soon as I'm done.
Fascinating.
So if my pieces advance
across the board.
I can "promote" them.
Right. I like to think
of it as my troops
getting hardened from battle.
Hurry up and stop hogging
the new game, Father!
[TOUYA] You're gonna
knock the board over.
About that, Sue.
This may take a while,
why don't you go play outside?
Because it's raining outside!
Touya! Make him give me
a turn, this isn't fair!
[laughing]
That tickles!
Yeah, it's fun for now,
but eventually, you'll
break. They all do.
'Kay! You can stop now!
I'm serious!
Agh, I can't take it!
I-I think she has a point, sir!
Please let her play!
[ALFRED]
I quite enjoy this game.
I'll have to show it
to my brother sometime.
One more.
I'm sure we can
make it a quick one.
[sighs] Goodness.
So much shogi.
I might start dreaming about it.
[YAE]
Ah.
The royal capital's guildhall
makes Reflet's look small.
[LINZE]
They have more quests here, too.
I'm glad we decided
to check it out.
[ELZE] Hopefully Touya
hasn't lost his touch
from all that shogi
he's been playing.
[TOUYA] It's not like
I wanted to play that much.
Anyway, look at this.
The megaslime quest
is posted here, too.
It must be destiny.
[LINZE, ELZE, YAE]
Any job but that one!
There is no fouler union than
that of sticky and gooey!
[LINZE, ELZE]
Mm-hm!
Doesn't look like
I'm winnin' this one.
[YAE]
Oh, no!
What were you
just thinking about?
Who, me? Whaddaya mean?
Why don't we do this one?
[TOUYA] It's just around
the corner, Yae!
[YAE]
Understood!
Nicely done!
How'd it go with
the horned wolves?
I finished 'em all off.
It wasn't easy though--
there were almost 20
of the stupid beasts.
[YAE]
Elze! Look out!
[ELZE yelps]
Hey, Linze!
I need you to try and
freeze his legs with ice.
'Kay! I'll do my best!
[YAE]
Want your head?
[ELZE yells]
Grasping Ice, come forth!
Frozen Curse: Icebind!
Ha!
Multiple! Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance!
Shining Javelin!
[HEADLESS KNIGHT groans]
Guess that's the end of that.
I am utterly exhausted.
[TOUYA] So these are the ruins
of the old royal capital.
Sure would be cool
if there were a vault
of hidden treasure somewhere.
That it would.
But the capital wasn't
destroyed, it was moved.
I doubt they would've left
anything valuable behind.
Well, yeah, I'm aware of that.
It's just a wistful thought.
Search For Treasure!
[ELZE] How'd it go?
Did you find anything?
We can at least be sure
there's no treasure
near this spot.
Aw, boo. Least we tried.
Hold on.
That just means
there's nothing Touya
would see as treasure here.
Try broadening your search
and something might
come up still.
That's a pretty
good idea, Linze.
Search For Historical Relics!
I found something!
Well? Where do you
think it is then?
It's pretty much
straight ahead of us.
And it's big. Whatever it is.
Interesting.
[TOUYA]
It's underneath all this rubble.
I'm not sure how
we could get to it.
I can take care of this.
Burst forth, Raging Flame.
Great Crimson Inferno. Eruption!
[LINZE]
That should do it.
You might've told us
to take a step back first,
but thanks.
Huh?
[TOUYA grunts]
There we go.
We ready for a dungeon crawl?
[LINZE]
Come forth, Light.
Tiny illumination. Light!
[LINZE]
This place is certainly creepy.
I wonder if it might be haunted.
[YAE]
What?
That is absolute nonsense
and you know it, Linze!
No way is an army of tortured
souls plotting our demise!
How could you think that?
[ELZE]
Yae's right! Ghosts don't exist.
What's up?
The ghosts're just as likely
to attack from behind.
Shut up and walk!
Take a look at that.
Linze.
D'you know what language
it's written in?
I don't. I've never seen this.
I'm familiar with most
ancient magic scripts,
but this is completely foreign.
No sweat. I'll just take
a picture of it for now.
[ELZE, YAE yelp]
Everyone get back,
the ghosts want blood!
Oh. Sorry.
Just how many odd things
is that smartphone
of yours capable of?
[BOTH sigh]
[TOUYA] Slowly but surely,
they're getting used to it.
[ELZE]
Hey. Come check this out.
Do you guys see that
red rock in the wall?
Oh, yeah.
I'm pretty sure that's
an Earth spell stone.
It's probably designed to
activate a powerful spell
whenever mana's
passed through it.
[TOUYA]
What kinda spell? Like a trap?
Well, I wouldn't rule
that out as a possibility,
but who knows?
[ELZE] It'll be fine! Pass some
mana through it, Touya.
Hold on, why me?
'Cause you're the only one here
with an affinity
for Earth magic.
Oh. Yeah, I guess that's fair.
Hey!
If "it'll be fine" then
why'd you back away?
Well. Just in case.
To be on the safe side.
Aye. Never hurts to be careful.
[ALL chuckle nervously]
Heh...
[gasps]
Uh oh!
[YAE, LINZE, ELZE coughing]
Someone went through
a lot of trouble
to impress us.
[TOUYA]
Anyone care to guess what it is?
[ELZE] Nope, but it
looks pretty magical.
[YAE]
It kind of looks like a statue.
Clear glass, but there's
not enough light
for me to see inside.
[TOUYA]
Not to be rude, Linze.
But just how short
is the duration
of that light spell you cast?
What? I mean, Light
magic is admittedly
one of my weaker affinities.
But I can keep a spell like
this up for at least two hours.
Strange. It hasn't
been half that long
and yet the light
is definitely fading.
Yeah, it's petering
out pretty fast.
[gasps] Hey, look in there.
That glass thing couldn't be
absorbing your magic, could it?
[gasps] Whoa,
I think it's alive.
[YAE, TOUYA grunt]
[ALL yelp]
What the--?
Screw this! Let's run!
Gate!
Hurry!
What the heck was that thing?
A magic beast?
I've never seen one
like it though.
Hopefully, it's trapped
under all that rubble.
[TOUYA]
I jinxed it.
Burst forth, Fire!
Crimson Bolero. Flaming Arrows!
I may have just
made it stronger.
Fine. My turn!
That shell will be
hard to cut through.
[ELZE]
Taste my fist!
Maybe we should try diplomacy.
Fat chance. Slip!
[TOUYA]
Good. Hey, Linze!
It's only able to absorb magic
that's thrown directly
at it, okay?
[LINZE]
Got it! I have an idea.
Now, come forth, Ice.
O' Grand Frozen Mass.
Ice Rock, Fall!
Let's try a full power Boost!
We did it!
You're kidding.
That thing can regenerate?
[yelps]
Elze, no!
[TOUYA]
Yae! Linze! Keep it busy!
[YAE]
We're on it.
[LINZE]
You help Elze!
[ELZE grunts]
Hold still for a sec.
[ELZE]
Thanks. I'm all right now.
You lost blood, so take it easy.
It absorbs magic attacks,
and its shell's crazy tough.
But it has to
have some weakness.
[ELZE] I bet its using
our magic to regenerate.
Then the longer we battle it,
the stronger it'll get.
Heh. Just like a shogi piece.
[TOUYA gasps]
[TOUYA]
That's it! We capture the king.
Hey Elze, listen up.
[gasps] Can you really do that?
I can't be sure,
but it's still the
best chance we have.
I'm with you.
[inhales, exhales]
Aports!
Elze!
[ELZE]
Boost!
You dead now, or what?
[TOUYA sighs]
I think that's a yes.
[TOUYA]
Uh-huh. Thank you, God
How did you figure out
that the red sphere
was important?
It started glowing
when that thing
stole Linze's magic.
So I figured that's where
the magic was stored.
Breaking its body wasn't
working, so I went for the core.
[YAE] You're a perceptive
individual, aren't you, Touya?
Where do we go from here?
I suppose we should
report this to the guild.
[LINZE] Considering that we
found it in the old capital.
I think we'd better report
it to the kingdom.
[ELZE]
Agreed.
Maybe we should talk
to the duke about it.
[ALFRED]
A magic beast,
in the ruins beneath
the old capital no less.
[TOUYA]
Weird, right?
I'll have to send out
an expedition.
See what they find.
Yes. I'll send one at once.
[TOUYA] Uh... The thing is,
that dungeon I mentioned--
the whole thing's collapsed now.
[ALFRED]
I see.
[TOUYA] Hold on. I did
take some pictures of it.
[ALFRED]
Pictures?
[TOUYA]
See here?
[ALFRED]
My. What is this device?
[TOUYA] I-It's a type of
Null magic that I use
to record images.
[ALFRED] Hmph. You never
cease to impress me.
It'll take me a little time,
but I can make a copy
for you to keep.
[ALFRED]
Please do.
I think this may
provide us some insight
into the mystery of why
the capital was moved.
That's a pretty big part
of your kingdom's history
to be left blank.
Aren't there records?
I'm sure there were once,
but none remain.
[TOUYA]
That's too bad.
Forgive me, but I
may need to request
your assistance in
this matter once more.
Would you be willing?
Of course.
If your men run into danger,
we'll be happy to help them.
That's most reassuring to hear.
[ELZE] Why do our jobs
never go smoothly?
[LINZE] I'd feel better about it
if we'd found some treasure.
We can go treasure
hunting another time.
I, for one, am beat.
[YAE]
Same.
Let's go somewhere with
better lighting next time.
Gate!
[ALL yelling]
[TOUYA]
Whew. Drawing magic.
I thought it might
come in handy.
[yawns]
[portal opens]
[yelps]
Hi, fellas.
Oh, no. Looks like he's leaving.
Well met as always, Touya.
It's more than fortune
that you'd arrive
at a time like this.
An act of God, perhaps.
For I am in desperate
need of your aide.
I'll be glad to give it.
What happened?
It's my brother.
He's been poisoned.
What?