[TOUYA] So... Where are these
ruins you wanted to visit, Leen?
I don't actually know that much.
Only that they're called the
Niruya ruins.
Niruya?
My father may be able
to tell you more.
That's perfect! Let's pay
him a visit. Lead the way.
[YAE]
I don't feel like I'm leading.
When did that girl
become the boss of us?
She is kind of assertive,
isn't she?
[ALL gasping]
[YAE]
This is it everyone.
My hometown, Oedo.
I was wondering,
is your country ruled
by a king, or what?
Well, Eashen does have a king.
But in practice, the lords
are essentially free
to govern their own
regions as they see fit.
You don't say.
And which lord controls Oedo?
His name's Tokugawa Ieyasu.
Ieyasu?
[TOUYA] It's like God got lazy
and just copy-pasted Japan here.
[YAE]
Is something wrong, Touya?
Na. I'm good.
Oh, wow. Look at that.
What are those men doing?
Those're kagoya .
And that thing they're
carrying's called a palanquin.
They get paid to take
people around in it.
[gasps]
[LINZE]
Huh...
Touya, look. Those poor men.
Their shoes are made of wood!
What was the name...?
Oh! Geta shoes.
That's correct.
You're rather well-versed in
Eashen culture for a foreigner.
Uh? Yeah?
Thank you.
[YAE]
I must say...
Something doesn't feel right.
Is anyone home?
[AYANE]
One moment!
Yae! You're really back!
Ayane! It's been too long.
It certainly has! Lady Nanae!
Your daughter's come back home.
Hello mom.
Oh, Yae. It's so
good to see you.
Missed you.
So, who have you
brought with you, Yae?
Oh. These are my comrades
from the far west.
They've aided me a great
deal in my travels.
Well, in that case,
you have my thanks.
Where's Father right now?
Still up at the castle,
I suppose?
He does love to train.
I'm afraid your father
had to leave us.
You see, he was called to
battle by Lord Tokugawa.
Called to battle?
Well? Who's our foe?
The Takedas.
They attacked out of nowhere
several days ago.
When your father heard the news,
he and Jutaro went to help
defend Kawagoe Fortress.
I thought the city
felt off before.
Guess this explains why.
[LEEN]
Any news from the battlefield?
We heard a rumor, that the
battle is all but over now.
The fortress will fall
in a matter of time.
Then, Father and Jutaro will...
It can't be.
Take me there, please! Use
Recall and I'll show you where!
Yeah. Of course.
I'm in your debt yet again.
[LEEN]
If I'd known there'd be a battle
I'd've brought darker socks.
I'll join you anyway.
The ruins can wait.
Don't worry, if your husband
and son are out there,
we'll bring them back Nanae.
That's a promise.
Thanks, um. Who are you again?
Oh, right. Uh. [laughs]
--[YAE] Hey, hey! Hoo! I say!
--[OTHERS] Hey! Hey! Hoo!
[YAE]
I say!
We made it.
I don't have enough details
to look up your dad,
but your brother's
definitely safe.
Thank you, that's good to know.
[gasps] We need to
help them right now!
Don't be a fool.
Even if you made it
past that army,
the Fortress gates are closed.
Then how can-- Wait.
Couldn't you fly right over them
using those wings
of yours, Leen?
I could've once, but they're
weak from lack of use.
These days, I can
barely even hover.
So what do we do?
[TOUYA]
Here's a plan.
I'll use Long Sense to find safe
spots between here and there.
Then jump in with Gate
till I reach the fort.
That would be safer
than the direct approach.
I need to be sneaky about this.
So for now, I'll go in alone.
Once I've gotten in though,
I'll jump straight back here.
That's a decent plan. I'm
pleasantly surprised, Touya.
Thanks. Be back soon.
[ENEMY SOLDIERS growl]
Are they... dead?
[SOLDIER 9A]
Jutado.
We kill and we kill,
but they just get back up.
They'll breach
the walls by night.
What dark magic is this,
that staves off death?
I've heard rumor that they die
when their masks are broken.
But I can't confirm it.
[gasps]
How'd you get in?
[TOUYA]
Magic! Please don't stab me.
I'm on your side. You're
Kokonoe Jutaro, right?
You have a sister named Yae
who's been training out west.
That's right, my name is Jutaro.
But how do you know my sister?
I'm actually a good
friend of hers.
My name is Mochizuki Touya.
You're a friend of hers?
Yeah, and she asked me to try
and give you guys a hand here.
Want me to grab her real quick?
So, Yae's back in Eashen.
You can bring her?
Yeah, one sec.
Gate!
Brother!
Yae?
Is that actually you?
Yes!
Wait, who are all
of these people?
These are my companions
from the west.
They've each stood beside
me in many a battle.
But more importantly,
is Father safe?
He hasn't been hurt, right?
No. The old man's
healthy as ever.
He's here in the fort, standing
with Lord Ieyasu's guard.
I'm relieved to hear that.
[TOUYA]
Uh?
Begin Programming.
Begin when more than one entity
is selected on the phone's map.
On this condition, set all as
spell targets using Multiple.
End programming.
[ALL gasp]
Come forth, Light.
Give your soothing comfort.
Cure Heal!
What the...?
I don't hurt anymore.
It's like I'm good as new.
Yae? Any idea what happened?
My friend Touya used
a healing spell.
I see.
[TOUYA]
By the way.
D'ya know what's going on with
those Oni mask guys outside?
No, I don't.
By all rights, most of them
should've already fallen.
I'm told that those masks might
be their sole weakness.
[LEEN]
Perhaps they're magic artifacts.
[TOUYA]
Say what?
You know, objects of power.
Lost relics from
ancient civilizations.
That thing you're holding
is an artifact, right?
Anyway.
I got a pretty zombie-ish
vibe from those guys.
Which should mean that I have
a way to take 'em all out.
You don't mean single-handedly.
[TOUYA]
Sure I do.
Woo. There are quite
a few of these guys.
Oh well. Okay, Multiple.
[INJURED SOLDIER 9G]
What are those?
Touya. How are you--?
Strike true, Oh Light.
Sparkling Holy Lance:
Shining Javelin!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[SOLDIERS cheer]
All defeated.
That was your doing?
[TOUYA]
Yeah.
Who saw that coming?
Only all of us that know him.
As impressive as always, Touya!
[TOUYA]
Thank you, thank you!
The name's Mochizuki Touya.
You're too kind. Really.
First off, please allow me
to express my gratitude
for your assistance today.
I'm Tokugawa Ieyasu,
leader of the Tokugawa clan.
Oh. We were happy
to lend our aid, sir.
My daughter. In a princess'
personal guard.
This is quite a surprise.
I told you I was training hard.
Which of you cast the spell?
The one that saved our fortress
in the blink of an eye.
That would be Touya.
Mochizuki Touya's his full name.
He guards me as well.
But, also, we're engaged
to be married soon.
[gasps]
[JUBEI, IEYASHU]
Oh...
[TOUYA]
Hold on, we're not--!
Er-- Uh. I guess it's
kind of in the air.
Things are complicated.
[YUMINA giggles]
[TOUYA coughs]
Moving on. About Takeda.
Do you think they'll
back down after today?
No, if I had to guess, I'd
say they'll attack us again.
You see, between those
undying soldiers,
and the suddenness
of this invasion,
I'm forced to believe
that the rumors are true.
Rumors?
[JUBEI] That the head of the
Takeda clan, Sheengen, is dead.
That his name is being used by
the dark mage Yamamoto Kansukay,
who commands an
army of the dead.
That requires lots of power.
My guess, is that he's using
a strong magic artifact.
[TOUYA] So, what if we captured
this Yamamoto Kansukay guy,
think things would settle down?
I think so.
But he's likely holed up in
some fortress of his own.
And we've yet to
determine which one.
[TSUBAKI] I know where he is.
Allow me to show you.
Who's there?!
[TSUBAKI] I come with a message
for Lord Tokugawa Ieyasu.
I'm Tsubaki, sent by
Kousaka Masanohbu.
He, of course, is one of
the four great generals
of the Takeda clan.
[JUBEI]
You're with Kousaka?
Yes. This letter confirms
our suspicions.
And what else?
[IEYASHU] It seems that
every Takeda general
aside from Kousaka has been
thrown into a dungeon.
He asks that we stop Kansukay
and save what's
left of his clan.
He's with Kansukay now.
Obeying him, yet
striving against him.
But he won't prevail
without allies.
We owe nothing to the Takeda!
But, if things continue like
this, we'll be done for as well.
Have anything to suggest, Touya?
We can help you
deal with this guy.
I thank you.
Do you plan to waltz into the
enemy's camp by yourselves?
Probably. But even
though I have Gate,
it'd be a pain to get noticed
too early. Hey, Leen.
You said you used light magic
to make the wings on your
back invisible, right?
Do you think you could, uh--
But of course. I can make the
whole body unseen if needed.
Sweet. That said,
it's probably a bad idea to
sneak in there as a big group.
Let's keep it small.
Me, Leen, and Tsubaki.
Paula's gonna have to stay.
That all right Leen?
[LEEN]
Yes.
I'll come back, Paula.
Cool, let's get to it.
[ELZE]
Hold on a second.
You're planning to sneak
around in broad daylight?
Yeah, maybe not.
Well in that case, I'd like
to return home for a time.
I need to let Mother know
that everyone's okay.
On a similar note,
if we aren't going home tonight,
I think we should tell Laim.
These men have been
under siege for days.
They need food as
quickly as possible.
You make excellent
points, all of you.
All the undeserved power in the
world won't make you any wiser.
I find it endearing,
you know that.
Well, then. I'll go ready
some horses for you.
[TOUYA]
Thanks but there's no need to.
I've got this...
Tsubaki, can you picture
Kansukay's hideout in your mind?
Yes, but why?
Well, if you'd allow me
to read your thoughts,
I could get us all
there a lot faster.
Then by all means.
[gasps]
[ALL chattering]
[TOUYA]
You're embarrassing me!
Leen. Can ya make
us invisible now?
It's technically more of a
camouflage spell, but whatever.
Come forth for me, Light.
Bend and distort. Invisible.
[TSUBAKI]
You vanished!
[TOUYA] Weird that I can
still see you, Leen.
It's more convenient that way.
I can hear your
voices, at least.
You two ready?
Then, Gate!
Uh! What the...?
We're blocked out.
It would seem our foe has
erected a magical barrier.
[TOUYA]
That's a thing?
Kansukay is a capable mage.
Wait a sec.
Could this barrier cancel
your invisibility spell?
We should be fine.
The barrier's only
meant to negate spells
that target the premises.
I can get inside the complex
without raising any suspicion.
Shall I destroy it for you?
I'd rather you didn't.
If the barrier were destroyed,
it would put our foes on alert.
Good point.
'Kay. Guess we'll just slip
in behind Tsubaki, then.
Long as this spell holds,
we'll get away with it.
Does that work for you, Lee--?
[LEEN laughs]
Goodness Touya,
how can you take advantage of
your invisibility like that?
That's Touya?
Huh?! No way, that's
Leen behind you!
She's the perv. I've been
here this whole time.
No. Hey. Not like that. Ah!
A fine bosom. So ample.
More than expected.
You conceal it with
those clothes.
[sighs] Wait a minute.
We have a mission to do--!
Huh? Sorry, Touya,
what did you suggest?
"Be more direct about it,"
well, if you say so!
[TOUYA]
I didn't say that!
Stop it, ya lecherous fairy.
Sorry ya had to endure that.
I'll smack her faster
if she tries it again.
--Smack me where?
--Shut up and behave!
Touya, you're so mean.
Wha--? But, it wasn't me!
What the hell, Leen?!
We're in the middle of
an operation right now.
Aw, man. I really hope
we make it there.
[LEEN]
May I?
[TOUYA]
Hey. Stop that. Seriously.
Who's there?
Lord Baba. It's Tsubaki.
General Kousaka sent me
here to help you escape.
[BABA]
Kousaka?
In my company, are two
friends of the Tokugawa.
Touya and Leen here are
both capable mages.
They're here to help.
Do you know where Yato's
cell is? Yamagata's?
One level down.
We'll grab them after.
First thing's first.
Modeling.
You're a good deal more
capable than you appear,
young man.
Oh, yeah? Thanks.
[door creaks]
Baba. How goes it?
Nice day for a stroll, eh?
Ah. I take it this means
that my boredom's
gonna come to an
end soon, right?
[BABA]
Young man. If you would.
[TOUYA]
Right.
Many thanks. What're
we planning from here?
Step one is just getting you
guys out of this dungeon.
Step two is to find the guy who
put you here and kick his butt.
I like that plan.
I'll have to come with you.
I've been planning a little
reunion over the past few days.
You're welcome to join us.
Speaking of, do you
know where he is?
[TSUBAKI] He's usually in the
central quarter right now.
I can't find him.
That dumb barrier.
Leen, what would we need
to do to destroy it?
Find the magic talisman
and it's bound to--
[YAMAGATA] Hey, I saw
a magic thing up there.
We can pick up some
weapons on the way.
There'll be fighting
after, am I right?
That's the relic, all right.
Destroy it and the
barrier should shatter.
'Kay. Everyone ready?
[gunshot]
[YAMAGATA]
Hey, look.
What are those things?
Twice in one day, Touya?
I really don't wanna teleport
into a horde of those guys.
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance:
Shining Javelin!
Hold on. Did all of
that come from you?
Well, yeah.
Very impressive.
I wonder if that could've
taken out Kansukay as well.
No. I only targeted the
Oni mask Soldiers.
Ah. I suppose that I
have you four to thank
for the sudden
spaciousness of my camp.
How did you pull it off?
We didn't come here
to chat, Kansukay!
We came here to kill you!
[BABA]
Oyakata, no.
Oyakata?
Baba called him master. So
that must be Takeda Schingen.
You worthless snake!
Release him or else!
[KANSUKAY chuckles]
Oyakata. Please move.
You can't avenge your lord
without first cutting him down.
It's quite the conundrum,
isn't it?
You vile bastard. [gasps]
Please stop, sir.
I can't fight you!
Well, Touya, what'll you do now?
I can't bear it!
To see him like this...
[NAITO] Even if he isn't
in there, we can't.
I knew that you fools would
choose honor over logic
when presented with this choice.
--Now flee like the dogs you--
--[gunshot]
[gasps]
Young man. You just--
[TOUYA] I mean. It's not
like I owe him anything.
Well, I guess that works out.
[KANSUKAY laughs]
I must admit, I didn't
see that one coming.
No matter. For you'll never
beat me while I have this!
He who possesses the
Gem of Immortality
can never be vanquished!
I imagine that it's also
what gave you the ability
to make your masked
soldiers undying.
[KANSUKAY]
Precisely, my dear.
This wondrous artifact gives
me vast amounts of mana,
and incredible power--
[TOUYA]
Aports.
Uh? My gem! How did you--?
Such sticky fingers.
Seems like the fastest
way to end this.
Aw. Well, that's a problem.
This would be a fine toy
if it wasn't cursed to
corrupt its owner's heart.
I'm surprised you can tell.
Live another 500 years and
maybe you'll get there.
No. My gem! Give it back!
An artifact of such power
must be incredibly valuable.
A shame that we'll
have to destroy it.
What?! No, you can't!
[LEEN]
No?
[KANSUKAY groans]
[TSUBAKI]
Oyakata.
[SOLDIERS chattering]
I see. You're not the first
to seek the Niruya ruins.
Thing is, they're at
the bottom of the ocean.
Bottom?
Also, I've been to an island
that was supposed
to be near them.
And it was pretty far from here.
That's no problem.
We can just use Recall
and Gate again, right?
What's wrong? Don't you like
doing it with old men?
[YAMAGATA]
Baba!
How can you touch
him when you have me?
It was good to see
you all. I'm sorry.
I'll try to stay longer
next time, but until then.
Take care, Yae.
And Touya, we're in your debt.
And I'll not soon forget it.
You're good. It was
no trouble at all.
Gate!
So cute!
[gasps]