[ALFRED] Our own nobles
may have done this.
There's a powerful faction
which opposes trade
with the kingdom of Mismede.
Wait, another kingdom?
[ALFRED] It's newly founded.
The king there is a beastman.
And my brother has
recently been considering
an alliance with this land.
Should he fall,
the crown shall be passed
to his eldest daughter,
Princess Yumina.
If the culprit is of our court,
he could use her
youth to his gain,
assuming power as an advisor.
Or even as a husband.
I get it.
So, how can I help out?
You can foil the
assassin's efforts.
Use your Recovery spell
to save the king.
Count Balsa.
It's an honor, Your Grace.
You've come at the perfect time.
Our guards have just captured
the treacherous demon
behind the attempt
on his majesty's life.
What? And who was it?
It was the esteemed
ambassador from Mismede.
Let's cut off her
head and return it.
Quiet!
My brother will be the one
to make that decision.
You think so?
I admire your fair spirit,
but its wasted on that beast.
And Slip.
[BALSA yelps]
[KING grunting, panting]
Stay with us.
He's trying.
That he is.
[door opens]
Brother!
[gasps]
It's good to see you.
But, who is this?
We'll speak later. Go, Touya.
With haste.
Recovery!
Wait. Recovery?
That Null magic can heal
any abnormal condition.
I didn't think anyone
still living could use it.
[grunting]
[ALL gasp]
You're healed.
I was so worried!
I suddenly feel as though
all that suffering
were but a dream.
Oh, thank goodness.
Do tell me, Alfred.
Who's this young man?
Allow me to introduce
the young Mochizuki Touya.
He gave Ellen her sight back.
And now, he's healed you.
I see. You saved me.
Many thanks.
No prob.
Mochizuki Touya, is it?
You did an excellent
job, young man.
Very impressive! [laughs]
That's kinda painful, sir. I--
[CHARLOTTE]
Please, General Leon. Calm down.
Though it is exciting to
see Recovery used again.
Makes me wonder what other
secrets you're hiding.
H-Huh?
The name's Charlotte,
by the way.
Official mage of
the royal family.
Tell me, young man,
you don't possess any other
affinities for magic, do you?
Well, uh. Yeah,
I can use a good few.
I bet you can.
I'd love to get you alone
and talk shop sometime.
Yeah. I'll look at my schedule.
[YUMINA] Excuse me. You saved
my father's life, sir.
Our family is in your debt.
Oh. Yeah, of course.
There's no need to thank me.
I'm just glad he's okay now.
[TOUYA]
Uh... Is there anything else?
Do you dislike those
younger than you?
What?
[KING]
I fail to see what Mismede
would gain from my death.
No, this was far more likely
the act of a solitary traitor.
That was my suspicion as well.
But there's proof.
What kind of proof?
Sir.
You collapsed almost
immediately after drinking wine
you received from
the ambassador.
Who else could've poisoned it?
[TOUYA] So he was poisoned
with wine. Interesting.
[KING]
Hm.
Let's speak with this
ambassador. Hear her defense.
[LEON]
At once.
Hail, Your Majesty.
Olga Strand, at your service.
You're Arma's sister!
[OLGA]
You're here?
Oh?
Are you a friend of the
ambassador's, young Touya?
Yeah. Kinda.
I ran into her sister,
Arma, and helped her
find her way home, one time.
By the way...
No one's messed with the room
where the king collapsed
since it happened, right?
Oh. Right. I ordered
none to touch it.
In that case, I bet
I can sort this out.
[ALL but TOUYA gasp]
[LEON]
Here. The wine the king drank.
I might not need it.
Search. Poison.
I think I understand
now. General?
Could you invite the
king's party to join us?
Oh, and also, see if
Count Balsa can come.
[TOUYA]
Elementary, my dear.
[YUMINA]
Uh...
[BALSA]
What's the meaning of this?!
Why have I been
called back here?
Your Majesty!
Fear not, good Count.
I have recovered.
Indeed.
I'm pleased to see
you well, Your Grace.
Well, that's all of us.
I assume you found something
since you called us here.
[TOUYA]
We'll get to that.
Now, everyone who was present
when the king collapsed
is currently in this room.
Is that correct?
That's right. All of
us were present.
And therefore...
[ALL gasp]
The culprit is in this room!
[TOUYA] Nailed it! I always
wanted to say that line!
[ALL gasp]
Speak, Touya.
Tell us your meaning.
Yeah. Sorry.
Sure, the culprit's here.
She's standing right next to me.
As each of you observed,
this is the wine his
majesty took a drink of
before his collapse.
He gave a toast,
took a sip, and fell.
Yes. That much is certain.
[BALSA]
Yes.
Which means,
as I've been saying,
this wench gave the
king poison wine.
The wine wasn't poi--
[BALSA]
Be silent, you lowly beastwoman!
[TOUYA]
Now then.
I'd like to verify a
certain suspicion I have.
Verify?
Yeah. First of all,
I've prepared a bottle of wine
that surely isn't poisoned.
I'm afraid that
I'm still a minor,
so I won't be able
to test it myself.
I'll have to ask one
of you to assist me.
General Leon. Would you mind?
What's a "minor"?
I'm not sure what you're trying
to prove here, but sure.
A fine vintage.
Now that we can all
agree beyond a doubt
that this wine is poison free.
I'll pour it into
his majesty's glass,
using the same tray his was on.
[BALSA]
Hm.
Since his majesty
isn't feeling well,
he'll need a substitute.
Now who's regal enough
to fully recreate the scene?
Ah! Count Balsa, please.
That doesn't seem safe.
'Course it is!
I mean, it's not like
there's a way to poison wine
after it leaves the bottle.
Balsa. What's the matter?
It's just--
You see--
[TOUYA]
What's up?
Does the thought
of portraying the king
give ya stage fright?
I'm sure you'll do fine.
[BALSA]
Release me!
Please! Somebody help me!
Ah! It burns.
I'm dying, damn it.
That's all in your head.
I already washed the
poison out of the glass.
What?!
I wonder.
What made you think
there was poison in here?
[BALSA grunts]
Explain yourself.
Well, it definitely wasn't
the wine from Olga
that was poisoned.
As the count clearly knew,
it's the king's glass
that was poisoned.
I see.
He framed me!
[TOUYA] I discovered this
by using my search null magic
to detect it.
[TOUYA] Actually, it seems
all of his highness'
glasses were poisoned.
I shudder at the thought.
Are ya gonna confess now?
[BALSA grunts]
The perfect man.
[TOUYA]
Uh. What?
You good over there?
It seems that you're
both talented and wise.
[TOUYA]
Huh?
I won't let it end here!
Don't Slip.
[BALSA yelps]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[YUMINA]
I love you.
[TOUYA]
Okay...
[KING] You've done this kingdom
a great service today.
Among several other things,
I owe you a debt of honor
for saving my life.
[TOUYA] Please, think
nothing of it, sir.
My visit to the duke
was more exciting
than expected, that's all.
Uh--
I have an announcement.
A big one.
May I speak?
Of course, Yumina.
Well,
I've been staring
at Touya all day.
So, I--
I think I'll take
him as my husband.
[TOUYA coughs]
[TOUYA]
Yeah?
This handsome suitor would
make me a happy bride
if you'd give your blessing.
Will you, Father?
I might.
But first, I must ask
why you have chosen him.
He's intelligent and he
lives to bring happiness
to those around him.
And, I should mention,
he's quite pleasing to look at.
He's the first person
I've ever felt like
I could spend the
rest of my life with.
Ah, I see.
Well, if that's how you feel,
I shan't oppose you.
I wish you a happy
life together.
[YUMINA]
Yeah?
Well, this is wonderful.
It calls for celebration.
[TOUYA]
Hey! Hold on a second!
What, is something the matter?
No, I mean, yeah, well--
Aren't'cha bein' kinda
quick to accept this?
You met me like two
hours ago, remember?
Normally, I'd be more cautious.
But Yumina's judged you
to be a good man.
And that tells me
all I need to know.
[TOUYA]
Seriously? How?!
It's quite simple.
Our daughter has
mystic eyes, see.
[KING] The Mystic Eyes of
Intuition, they're called.
With them, Yumina can see
one's true character.
Yeah, well that's
not the only issue.
I mean, first of all,
how friggin' old is she?
[KING]
She's 12.
[groans] Well, there.
Wouldn't that make her a little
too young to get married?
It's common for us
in the royal family
to settle on a partner
before age 15.
I was betrothed to Yuel at 14.
I only wish we'd
done it sooner. Right?
Yes, I was hoping
that our Yumina
would find someone special soon.
[sighs]
If you dislike me,
it's okay to say so, Touya.
[TOUYA]
I'm...
It isn't that.
[TOUYA]
...screwed.
Well then, there isn't
a problem, is there?
Men can't get married until
they're adults in my country.
So, marriage isn't an option
for me until I turn 18.
And how old are you now, Touya?
[TOUYA]
I'm about to turn 16.
Well, in that case,
why don't you two spend
the next couple of years
getting to know one another?
[TOUYA]
Huh?
[KING] If, after spending
that much time with her,
you're still unable
to consider marriage,
we'll accept your decision,
of course. Will that work?
Sure.
[TOUYA]
Two measly years?
She'll only be 14 by then.
It's settled, then.
That'll give you two years
to win over Touya's heart, okay?
[YUMINA]
And win it I shall!
[TOUYA]
Uh...
I certainly hope you'll
treat me well, darling.
[laughs nervously]
[TOUYA groans] Maybe I'm
just having a bad dream.
[phone rings]
[TOUYA]
'Sup, God.
[GOD]
Hey, congrats on the engagement!
You've seriously
been watching this?
[GOD laughs] Seems like things
are getting interesting!
[TOUYA]
Please don't laugh at my pain.
I don't even wanna
think about marriage.
Let alone with a 12 year old.
And we wouldn't want that.
Just like we wouldn't
want you to go
to a special place
in hell, amiright?
Say, did you know that
polygamy's a thing
in that world?
[TOUYA] Are you sure you
aren't secretly the devil?
[GOD] 'Course not! I'd hate
to do his job. Too hot.
Anyway, I'm rootin'
for ya. Later.
[TOUYA sighs]
What the hell, God?
[YUMINA]
Sweet dreams, Touya.
[TOUYA groans]
You've been gone six hours
and you got engaged?
This is quite the surprise.
What were you thinking, Touya?
It's not an official
engagement yet.
My name's Yumina
Airina Bellfest,
and I look forward
to staying with you.
When was it decided
that you'd stay with us?
Well, my father ordered me to.
But you're a princess.
You sure you'll
be okay--? My lady.
Yes, and there's no
need for formalities.
We'll be companions, after all.
I'm a little inexperienced,
but I'll definitely do my best.
So how do I get a guild card?
I'd like to start working
as soon as possible.
[YAE, LINZE, ELZE, TOUYA]
Huh?
Yeah, look, Princess.
Guild jobs are too dangerous.
I can't let you come.
I'll be fine.
Also, please stop
calling me princess.
From now on, it's either
Yumina, or darling.
[YAE, LINZE, ELZE]
Wait. Did she say "darling"?
Darling's not gonna work for me.
Well. Yumina, then. Right?
[TOUYA]
Right. Yumina.
Well done.
Wait a sec. If you two
actually do get married,
does that mean that
you'll be the next king?
[TOUYA]
Uh, me? A king?
No, no, no, no, no.
I-I don't think so.
That's crazy talk, Elze.
In the event that Touya
and I should conceive,
the child born between us
will succeed the throne.
Wha--?
[TOUYA]
All five together!
[ELZE, LINZE, YAE, YUMINA]
Huh?
[TOUYA]
Eh...
You sure you wanna start
with hunting King Apes?
I only wish to
showcase my abilities.
So, a mission like
this should suffice.
Well, if you do get in trouble,
I'm sure your fiancé
will protect you.
[groans]
Don't worry.
I may look fragile,
but I've been trained
in archery and magic.
And I'd like to think
myself capable in both.
Let's get started.
Come forth, Dark.
I seek the proud beasts
wrapped in silver.
Silver Wolf Pack!
Sounds like a summoning spell.
Well. Happy hunting.
They should lure the
apes back to us soon.
Wow.
Summoning magic seems
pretty convenient.
I'd be happy to teach
you how it works later!
[TOUYA] Thanks. Let's do it
after this mission, okay?
Sure!
[WOLVES howl]
Move in!
[roars]
Whirling Spiral.
Please come forth. Fire Storm!
[KING APES roar]
Big Slip!
Let's Boost!
Come forth, Lightning.
Pure Sparking Javelin.
Burning Javelin. Crimson Spear.
Thunder Spear!
Fire Spear!
[roars]
[TOUYA sighs]
Good work.
So, uh. Did I do okay?
Great. That was some
impressive archery.
And you're a skilled
mage, too, so. Yeah.
It's always good to have
support from the rear!
[TOUYA sighs]
If we add her,
that'll make four girls on this
team. And still no guys but me.
And what's so wrong with that?
You might not have noticed,
but we stand out at the guild.
Everyone's always staring at me.
And not in a good way either.
It gets super awkward.
Why do people stare?
Well, they're
jealous, obviously.
Just think about it.
A single guy. With three
super-cute girls.
[GIRLS gasp]
Come on, what're you
tryin' to say, Touya?
You're such a joker!
Calling us cute.
Hey, Touya. What about me?
Am I as cute as
your friends are?
Yeah, I think
you're pretty cute.
[giggles]
[TOUYA]
Uh... Yeah. They're cute.
[BEAST]
Was it you who summoned me?
Cool. Guess I pulled it off.
That was just the first step.
The hard part is forming
a pact with the summon beast.
Wanna make a deal?
[BEAST] You seek to
tame me? How amusing.
I hope you have
flesh on your bones.
[gasps] A white tiger.
I've heard of this.
The White Monarch!
Is that a good one?
It's the highest class of beast
that can be summoned.
Not a magic beast,
but a heavenly beast.
Heavenly? 'Kay.
So, how exactly do I form a
pact with something like that?
Show me the class of
magic energy you possess.
Should I find it lacking,
I'll devour you.
Could you not?
[sniffs]
Strange.
I sense a spirit, or perhaps
an even higher power.
Now, come. Let your
magic flow into me.
If you promise not to bite,
I'll give it a shot.
What are you?
So strong.
No, it's too much!
Touya, stop!
Huh?
[thud]
[TOUYA]
Wow.
[BEAST]
Mochizuki Touya.
I've deemed you worthy
to become my master.
Pact with me, and
I'll serve you well.
How do I do that?
Give me a name.
That shall be the
proof of our bond.
Lemme think. Um...
Kohaku?
How does Kohaku sound?
[TOUYA] That's "Ko" for "tiger."
And "Haku" means white.
And the symbol I put beside each
of them stands for "king."
The white tiger beside the king.
Yes, this name fits me well.
I can't believe you pacted
with the White Monarch.
The White Monarch
is my name no longer.
I am now Kohaku.
Understood... Kohaku.
Master. With your permission,
I would like to stand
by your side at all times.
[TOUYA]
Uh. Sorry, but I don't think
I can walk around town
with a giant tiger.
I believe that this form
will be far less conspicuous.
Yeah. That oughtta work.
You're so cute!
Get your grubby hands off me.
Just who do you think you are?
Oh! My name's Yumina.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am your master's betrothed.
How did you pull that off?
She keeps on pushing
this wife thing.
What's the fuss?
[YUMINA]
I could just cuddle you all day.
Such a cute kitty!
He's so fluffy!
This is the most adorable
kitten I've ever squeezed!
[KOHAKU]
I'm a tiger!
Please, Master, you have
to make them stop it!
Bear it. They'll calm in time.
[KOHAKU]
No!