Wow! It's so pretty.
I haven't been to
the beach in ages.
You're right,
it has been a while.
I'll join as well.
[ALL laughing]
[YAE]
This sand is hot!
[TOUYA]
Huh? Ah...
The ruins are near?
Yeah. They are submerged,
but I bet I could swim to 'em.
[GIRLS laughing]
The water here feels
fantastic. Too bad.
I'd say we should swim, but I
don't own a suit right now.
Wait a second.
Swimsuits exist here?
We could go back to
Belfast. Buy some.
That's a great idea!
Mind taking us back to Belfast
for a quick shopping
trip, Touya?
We're here to investigate
some ruins, remember?
I don't mind, as long as they're
still willing to help us.
It's but a short delay.
Yeah, as long as we're here,
why not enjoy ourselves?
[gasps] Even bigger
than my bathtub!
Thank you for your kind
invitation, young Touya.
I'm glad we accepted it.
[TOUYA] Well, we were in the
area, so I thought I'd offer.
It was an offer I
couldn't refuse.
[TOUYA] I don't think
she wants to be here.
[CECILE]
Oh! It's just lovely!
So, is this the ocean?
I always wanted to see it.
Wait. Where's the other shore?
[MICAH]
We're here! Sorry we're late.
Took us a bit to
close up our shops.
It's good to see you.
Thank you for inviting us.
We should get changed
into our swimsuits
while the sun's still out.
Hold on. I don't see anywhere
for us to change.
Oh! I'll just make us
some tents with modeling.
[ELZE gasps]
[TOUYA] I went ahead and made
a couple pool toys for us, too.
[ELZE]
I call first one in!
And, no peeping, Touya.
[TOUYA]
I would never!
My, it looks like Linze
must be the older sister.
You're one to talk!
Girls like us are supposed
to stick together!
[ELZE]
Touya!
[wheezes]
Well, do you like our swimsuits?
[TOUYA] Yeah. All three
of you look super cute.
[YAE]
That's wonderful to hear!
Although, I have to confess.
I still feel a bit
strange in this outfit.
[TOUYA]
Elze? What's wrong?
Huh? Nothing! I am
perfectly happy.
Hey, good for you, big sis.
Why are we talking
about me right now?
Let's go swim already.
Okay! I'm good to go!
Well, I suppose we had
better follow the leader!
See you in the water!
[GIRLS laughing]
There!
You've done it this time!
And now for my revenge!
Hey Linze, get in here!
[YAE] You shouldn't
let your guard down!
[TOUYA]
Oh, boy.
You okay?
Weren't you planning
to swim today?!
No. It's kind of embarrassing,
but I was never too
good at swimming.
Ah, I gotcha.
Well, then make sure you
don't get a heatstroke.
Right.
[SUSHI]
Touya!
[RENNE]
How's it going Touya?
Let's hear it! Do you think
our swimsuits are cute?
Sure. You both look great.
Just you wait, Touya!
We're gonna make a
huge sand castle!
This beach is awesome!
I guess this is your first
time to visit one, isn't it?
Sure is! I'm gonna take
a bunch of sand back home
with me so I don't forget.
Good idea.
I think this'll help you
to remember it, too.
Oh, hey look, it's us!
Amazing! What is this thing?
It's a tool for
recording things we see.
So cool, so cool, so cool!
I kinda feel like you
can do anything, Touya!
Ha, ha! Of course he can!
I would never settle for
a second-rate fiancé.
Whoa! So you're engaged?
Don't make things up, Sushi.
Shoo. Go play.
[SUSHI]
Right! Let's go Renne!
[RENNE]
Right behind you!
[GIRLS laughing]
They seem to get along well.
[gasps] Cecile, you
kinda startled me.
[CECILE laughs] Sorry, it's
a habit from my job.
Guess I should expect that.
I've been tasked with keeping an
eye on Lady Sue and young Renne.
But it took me longer than
I thought to get changed.
[TOUYA] Yeah, that must've
been a challenge.
The store we went to didn't
have any swimsuits in my size,
so I had to make do with
what they did have.
This one's a bit on the tight
side, as you can see.
I don't really need that
kind of information.
Oh, Lady Sue! Young Renne?
Would you mind if I joined you?
I wonder. Do they really
float at that size?
Enjoying the view?
[screams] Seriously, you two
gotta stop with the sneaking.
My apologies, sir. So,
does what float at that size?
I was referring to
the water donuts!
Just tryin' to make sure
I made 'em right.
[LAPIS] They seem to
be functioning fine.
That's good.
Uh. Say, what do you have there?
Even here, I still
have work to do.
I've been serving
drinks to the ladies.
I hope you two will
get to take a break.
[LAPIS] Yes. Cecile and I
have agreed to take turns.
So don't worry.
[KING, ALFRED, LEON grunting]
[ALFRED]
Don't expect me to yield
just because you're the king!
[KING] Of course you
won't, little brother.
You'll lose because
I'm stronger!
[LEON laughs]
This is nothing!
Well, those three are
as energetic as ever.
[LINZE] Here ya go! Though
you're perfect the way you are.
All right. 'Bout
time I got to it.
[YUMINA]
Touya!
What do you think?
[TOUYA]
It looks great. Very cute.
[laughs] I'm glad you like it.
After all, I did choose
it with you in mind.
Well. Shall we go swimming now?
Uh. Sorry, but I was just about
to go look for those ruins.
I'll join you as
soon as I finish.
Very well, but come and get
me as soon as you're ready.
I'll be waiting for you.
Oh, and same for the marriage.
[TOUYA]
U-Uh!
The engagement. I keep
forgetting about that.
[LEEN]
Hello Touya. Why the long face?
[TOUYA]
What? Oh, it's nothing.
[squeaking]
Does Paula plan to go swimming?
I used my Protection
spell to keep her dry.
We wouldn't want
her to get moldy.
Ah. I guess I should
use that, too.
That way I can bring it with me.
Protection!
[TOUYA]
Hey, Kohaku.
I'm assuming that you
aren't gonna swim?
You do know that just
because I'm feline
doesn't mean I'm
afraid of water.
[TOUYA]
What's wrong?
[LEEN]
Hm... That one girl isn't here.
What girl do you mean?
[LEEN] You know. The one whose
chest you groped a few days ago.
Oh, yeah, Tsubaki!
Wait, for the last time,
that was you!
But you wanted to see it, right?
To see her in a swimsuit.
[TOUYA]
There's nothing wrong with this.
I'm a healthy young man.
Curiosity is perfectly natural.
You just imagined it.
What?! No I didn't, you
can't prove anything!
It seems that you're
a red-blooded man
after all, Touya.
You're one to talk, ya big perv.
Moving along.
I think it's time for us to
start making some progress.
Yeah, what with?
The cop-out you used
on your bride.
We're scouting out those ruins.
[TOUYA]
Oh...
There's nothing for it
but to swim, right?
Yes, I'll be cheering
you on from here.
I have no intention of swimming.
I'd risk getting a sunburn.
Then why bother putting
on a swimsuit?
You threatened me into it.
Just what kinda freak show
am I in your mind?
[groaning]
Are you alive?
Somehow. I was able to
find the entrance, at least,
but when I tried to get
inside, I ran out of air.
Who could've guessed that
you would run out of air
while underwater. All right.
So, how should we proceed?
[TOUYA]
Are there any spells
that let people
breathe underwater?
I've heard of a few,
but I didn't care enough
to memorize them.
Maybe you should've
before we came here.
[LEEN]
Oh, Charlotte. Come down here.
Uh! Of course.
Tell me.
Do you know of a spell that lets
one function underwater?
If... I recall...
[LEEN]
It doesn't look like you recall.
Honestly. It's a shame
that your brain
didn't mature with
that body of yours.
[yelps] What are
you doing, Master?!
You're wearing that suit for the
rest of the day, as punishment.
And, also, you're not permitted
to return to the
palace till I do.
What? But you only asked me
because you don't
remember either, right?
[TOUYA]
That girl is a tyrant.
[KOHAKU] Master. You wish to
function underwater, do you?
Yeah. Do you know
of a good way to?
[KOHAKU]
I'm acquainted with an entity
that has dominion over water.
I believe that they could solve
your problem quite easily.
Who?
Just as I was once known
as the White Monarch,
they are the black.
[GIRLS chattering]
Typically, this spell
would be incapable
of specifying what
spirit it might summon.
But if we infuse my spiritual
energy with master's magic
then he can call them
wherever they might be,
and they'll be too
intrigued to ignore it.
Watch and learn, fairy.
Do as you will, but this
seems a fool's errand.
The Black Emperor's no
force to be trifled with.
I'm still astounded that you're
the White Monarch.
I'm surprised that
you're so worried.
It's not any crazier than
you creating Paula.
Hey, Master. I don't actually
know what they'll ask
you to do before they
agree to forge a pact.
So be careful, just in case.
Wait a second.
You keep saying "they,"
like there's a lot of them.
Did I miss something?
[KOHAKU] The Black Emperor
is two beings in one.
Don't worry. You'll understand
once you meet them.
Black Emperor.
You who rules not just
water but winter,
and the great northern
mountains. I call upon you.
Answer my summons and
appear before me.
It looks like they heard you.
[BLACK EMPEROR A] Mm? Ooh!
Well if it isn't good old White!
It's been too long.
How ya doin'?
[KOHAKU] It's good to see you,
Black Emperor.
Ah... I told you,
just call me Black.
I thought we were friends!
Anyway. What are ya
doin' with that human?
This is my master, his
name's Mochizuki Touya.
Speaking of, you can
call me Kohaku now.
Your master?
You took a mere human
as your master? My.
Just how far have you fallen?
[KOHAKU]
Say what you will, old friends.
He'll be your master
too, soon. You'll see.
Nonsense.
[KOHAKU grunts]
[BLACK EMPEROR B chuckles]
[BLACK EMPEROR A]
Hmm...
Very well. Touya, was it?
I suppose we can test
to see if you're worthy.
Just to humor our friend.
I'm down. What do
you want from me?
Meet us in battle.
In the unlikely event that you
remain standing with your limbs
intact by sunset, you
shall get your pact.
Sounds good. Wanna start now?
Touya. Don't get careless and
let them pull one over on you.
Don't worry. I'll manage okay.
You're surprisingly calm.
At the very least,
I commend your courage.
Let us begin.
Then, Slip!
[BLACK EMPEROR A groans]
Enchant with Slip.
Initiate Program.
Begin as soon as the effect
of Slip starts to fade away.
On this condition, cast Slip.
Terminate this cycle upon
the caster's command.
End of Program.
This is crazy! What is
that boy doing to us?
[BLACK EMPEROR B groaning]
You programmed a bullet
to continuously cast slip.
Saving yourself the trouble.
How ruthlessly efficient.
[BLACK EMPERORS yelp]
Reminds me of the time
me and the girls
had to fight some slimes.
Well. Guess we'll just wait
for them to give up.
[BLACK EMPERORS groan]
[KOHAKU]
Hey! Don't slip!
Oh wait, you can't help it.
[TOUYA] They really seem
determined, huh?
Get ready.
There!
[yells]
I've got this!
Well done.
Way to go!
[LINZE]
Ah!
[ELZE] Lay down, sis!
We'll hide them with sand!
[YAE] Oh no, where's
Touya? Touya help!
[LINZE]
Don't call him over!
We're lucky that is was
just us girls here.
[ELZE] Yeah, Touya hasn't
been around much at all.
[YAE] For that matter,
neither has Leen.
[YUMINA] They said they were
off to investigate the ruins.
So perhaps they're
both out diving.
[LINZE]
Maybe. I hope that's all it is.
[BLACK EMPEROR A groaning]
So much spinning!
The entire world is spinning!
[BLACK EMPEROR B] Please,
no more! We've had enough.
Don't make us fall again.
[TOUYA] Yeah, sorry.
Guess I went overboard.
[BLACK EMPEROR A]
I can see why the White Monarch
acknowledged you as her master.
Mochizuki Touya.
You have proved yourself worthy.
Please forge a pact with us.
Yeah, sure.
If I remember correctly,
that means I need to
give you new names?
[BLACK EMPEROR A] Yes. Please
endow us with worthy names.
[TOUYA]
Hm... 'Kay.
Well, what do you guys think
of Kokuyou and Sango?
Kokuyou?
Sango?
You like 'em?
[KOKUYOU] I will gladly take
the name Kokuyou as mine!
[SANGO]
From this day forth,
I shall be known
by all as Sango.
As you've willed.
Hold it you two. You'll
cause our master trouble
if you lumber around
in that form.
Make yourselves smaller.
Really?
We need to make
ourselves all tiny
like the White-- uh,
like Kohaku here.
We can do that. Watch!
I didn't know you could fly.
We can manage it when
we're at this size.
Although we can't move
all that fast now.
Kokuyou. Sango. Hi.
I, Sango, shall prove
to be very useful.
I'll be just as
useful as her, sir.
[BOTH laughing]
[SANGO] So, you need us
to help you to breathe
while you're exploring
underwater, is that right?
Yeah. Can ya do it?
Yeah, piece of cake.
Cool, let's do it now.
Or, I'd like to do that,
but I can't yet.
Why can't you?
I need to take a quick break.
[LEEN]
Hm. Yes, I agree.
I can't keep you to
myself any longer.
Think I've earned
enough envy as it is.
Say what?
--[TOUYA] Oh.
--[LEEN] Go on.
Play with your friends.
Master.
In that case, Sango, Kokuyou,
and I have catching up to do.
Okay. Have fun.
It's about time
that you joined us.
Sorry, 'bout that.
What were you two talking about?
[TOUYA]
You know. The ruins.
And nothing else? Really?
[TOUYA]
What? You think I'm lying?
[ALL]
Mm-hm.
[TOUYA]
Come on. Where's the trust?
Were you blown away by
Leen in her swimsuit.
Is that why you abandoned
us for so long?
[TOUYA]
Of course not, we were working.
This begs the question.
If not hers, then whose swimsuit
do you think looks best?
Oh yeah. Let's hear it, Touya.
Say... what?
How did we get to this point?
[RENNE] I think we should
make a bunch'a turrets.
Sue's. Yup.
[ALL]
Huh?
Do you mean that? Am I too old?
--[TOUYA] Wha--?!
--Touya, that is not okay.
No! I didn't mean it like that.
I'm a normal, healthy guy. I
like my own age group, I swear.
Listen, I--
[YUMINA]
Is that...?
[YAE]
He never took our picture.
Come to think of it,
you haven't!
This is too much for me.
No. You've got it wrong.
I only took this to help them
preserve the memory, okay?
The memory. Sure.
[TOUYA]
I told you, it's not like that.
It's okay Touya. If you say
it's not, I believe you.
That said,
I think you had better start
making memories with us now.
Sure. I'd love to.
I know! Let's swim. Follow me!
Hey! Are you coming?
We're right behind you!
[ELZE]
Hey, Touya, think fast!
[TOUYA grunts]
[TOUYA]
Ah!
[GIRLS laugh]
[SUSHI]
My suit got best in show!
[RENNE]
Way to go, Sue!
[TOUYA]
I couldn't decide, okay?
Well, those ruins aren't
gonna explore themselves.
Think I'd better go
solo at first.
If anything happens, come
right back with Gate, okay?
Sure. All right guys. Go for it.
Just leave it to us!
[KOKUYOU] You'll be able
to breath fine now.
Cool.
Awesome.
Not only can I breathe down
here, I can walk normally.
It's almost like I'm on land.
We're able to bend water
to our will with great ease.
I look forward to showing
you our real power.
[TOUYA laughs]
Me, too.
Wonder what's making that light.
Guess we're gonna find out.
What is this thing?
[SANGO] Try passing
some magic through it.
[TOUYA grunts]
[gasps]
[TOUYA]
Think it worked.
What the heck?!
[gasps]
[TOUYA]
Whoa.
Excuse me, master. Do you
know where you've taken us?
No.
Uh.
Who is that?
Hm?
[TOUYA grunts]
Greetings, traveler.
I am the terminal that
controls this place:
the Aerial Garden of Babylon.
You may call me Francesca.
'Kay, but uh...
You have queries?
Yeah. Why are you...
...naked down there?