[TOUYA]
So, God killed me on accident.
And then reincarnated me
in this mysterious new world.
It's a world of fantasy.
Home to strange magic
and mystical creatures.
Luckily, God gave me a lot of
cool new powers for this life.
And he let me keep
my smartphone.
[TOUYA chuckles]
[TOUYA] Guess we should
find an inn for the night.
We're still a good distance
from the royal capital.
I wonder. Was this
letter delivery
really the best quest
we could've taken today?
If we had gone after
that megaslime instead,
we could already be back home.
[BOTH]
No way!
Why not?
Because slimes are squishy,
and wet, and flabby,
and moist, and I hate them!
It's instinctive!
[LINZE]
Mm-hm!
And worst of all,
some slimes can melt
peoples clothes off.
I'm not risking it!
[ELZE whimpering]
[TOUYA]
Yeah. That's understandable.
Let's eat before
we look for an inn.
I sure hope we can find
a place like the Silver Moon.
Wait.
Shouldn't we just use my Gate
spell to go back there tonight?
It'd be cheaper and
we wouldn't have to
waste time looking around.
--[BOTH] Of course not!
--[TOUYA] Huh?
If you're in a new place,
you should want to look around.
Exploration is the best
part of questing.
An adventurer should know this.
[LINZE]
Mm-hm!
[MAN 2A]
Hey, hold it!
[CROWD shouting]
What's this?
Those clothes.
I've never seen
anything like them.
She's a samurai.
What's that mean?
Hey, girl!
I hear ya did a real number
on some of my buddies.
Oh. So you're friends
with the drunks
that tried to spar
with me earlier.
In that case,
you should thank me.
I took them to the guards
before they could
hurt themselves.
[MAN 2A]
Shut up! Let's get her!
[MAN 2A grunts]
[MAN 2A groans]
I've never seen that
fighting technique.
Looks like Jiu-jitsu.
[yells]
[stomach growls]
My oldest nemesis strikes again.
Hold on, why'd she stop moving?
Look out, miss, behind you!
[MAN 2D yells]
[TOUYA]
Come forth, Sand!
Obstructing Dust Storm!
Blinding Sand!
[MAN 2D]
My eyes! No!
[TOUYA]
Take this!
We're fighting?
Classic Touya!
Can't just mind your own
business! What a hassle!
[gasps]
[MAN 2H]
The guards are coming!
Hey, Touya? We should
get out of here.
Yeah, right.
C'mon, let's go.
Uh!
[TOUYA] I think we'll
be safe at this distance.
[YAE] I'm grateful
for your assistance.
Greetings, my name
is Kokonoe Yae.
Oh. Kokonoe's just
my family name,
but you can call me Yae.
Well, in that case,
I guess you're from Eashen.
Indeed.
I hail from the
Eashen city of Oedo.
Oedo.
[TOUYA]
That's an old name for Tokyo.
My name's Mochizuki Touya.
My family name's Mochizuki,
so call me Touya.
Oh! It's a pleasure
to meet you, Touya,
are you from Eashen as well?
Uh. No.
I'm just from a country
that's very similar.
[LINZE, ELZE]
Huh?
[TOUYA]
Oh, yeah.
I let them think
I was from Eashen.
So about the fight,
I saw you falter a bit.
What happened?
[YAE] Well, this is
rather embarrassing,
but I misplaced my traveling
funds on the way here so I--
[stomach growls]
[YAE]
I shall gladly partake!
Oh, cool!
So you traveled here to
improve on your martial arts.
Interesting.
My family has produced
generations of great warriors.
And I aim to be one of them,
which means
practicing everywhere.
That makes sense to me.
[YAE] Someday, I shall
become a swordsman
on par with my father
and older brother!
[TOUYA]
She'll eat us to bankruptcy.
[LINZE] So, Yae, where
exactly were you planning
to head after this?
[YAE]
Well, for now,
I'm planning to head
for the royal capital.
It seems like a good place
to put my strength to the test.
How fortunate.
We're actually on our way
to the capital as well.
Say, would you like
to travel with us?
You mean it?
I'd love that.
I mean, after the kindness
you've shown me....
...it'd be...
...rude of me to refuse
your good company.
You'll find me an
honorable comrade
and a capable warrior!
You wouldn't mind if she
joined us, would you?
Huh? Oh. The more
the merrier, I guess.
It's settled then.
[TOUYA]
We really might go broke though.
[TOUYA] Where did you learn
to handle horses, Yae?
The equestrian arts were
part of my earliest training.
It'll be nice to have
a third set of hands.
It was kind of difficult
with just me and Linze.
Yup. I am useless.
[LINZE]
Aw, no you're not.
Touya here is a
very talented mage.
He's learning lots of spells.
And not just elemental stuff.
He can also use a whole
lot of Null magic.
You learned her
Boost spell, right?
So far, it seems like you
can use any spell out there
as long as you know its name.
And what its
effect is, I assume.
[ELZE]
Good grief.
When someone's that all-powerful
it's just exasperating.
[chuckles] So, uh.
I'm a little confused.
Just how many types
of Null magic are there?
[LINZE] Lots. It's mostly
personal magic,
so the theory is that
there are as many spells
as there are users.
[TOUYA]
That's a lot to try and learn.
You're right.
And not many people
have tried it.
So, tomes like
that one are rare.
Some Null spells have
only ever had one user.
Most haven't been seen in years.
So a few hobbyists study them.
But there aren't too many
other people that do.
Yeah, I can certainly understand
why most people wouldn't
bother learning spells
they'll never be able to use.
There's a spell that
curls hair into rolls.
A spell that makes
dogs super friendly.
[YAE]
Ooh. That's a good omen.
[TOUYA] Even a spell that
makes tea stems stand.
There's lots, but the
majority are useless.
[ELZE] Uh... Well, you never
know when one might be useful.
So you might as well learn
as many as you can, right?
[TOUYA] God did boost
my memory, but how much?
I might as well try to memorize
an encyclopedia, sheesh.
[gasps] A spell that draws
distant objects to your hand.
Huh. That sounds useful.
Why don't you see
if you can use it?
Aports.
That's weird.
Wonder why it didn't work.
Well, what did you
try to pick up with it?
[TOUYA] I wanted to see
how Yae would react
if she suddenly lost a katana.
Maybe her katana's
too heavy of a target.
Maybe so. It does
say "small" objects.
And that I should picture
it more carefully.
[inhales]
Aports!
[yelps]
Wait, what happened?
What did you try
to take this time?
Just this.
It's the ribbon that Yae
ties her hair with.
The spell does work!
That could be useful
in any number of ways.
Some of which are terrifying.
Terrifying?
You could pick people's
pockets all day with that spell.
Even if someone
felt it disappear,
they'd have no way of
knowing you took it.
Yeah, fair point.
That would be scary
when ya think of it.
I could take all
the money, gems,
and jewelry a guy could
want, if I felt like it.
Are you planning to try it?
You know stealing's
wrong, right?
[TOUYA]
Calm down, I would never!
That said, I wonder if I could
pull off someone's garments
with a spell like this.
[BOTH yelp]
Relax, I was joking.
[YAE]
Um.
Could I get my ribbon back?
My hair's all over the place.
Here's a spell
that can temporarily
reduce friction in a small
area. It's called Slip.
Huh.
Most of this Null magic seems
like it'd only be useful
in a few specific scenarios.
[TOUYA gasps]
Whoa.
Long Sense.
What did that do?
I can sense things
at a distance now.
It mostly seems to be affecting
my sight and hearing.
Another choice tool
for a pervert.
No way, I wouldn't dare.
[sniffs]
It works on smell, too?
What is that? Iron?
No. Wait, it's blood!
[gasps]
It's straight ahead.
Ha!
[roars]
[SUMMONER 2A chuckles]
Come forth, Fire.
Whirling Spiral: Fire Storm!
[ELZE yells]
[yells]
[yelps]
Dumb rock.
[LIZARD 2B roars]
[TOUYA]
Friction, begone! Slip!
[sighs]
[TOUYA] I guess these spells
are all about how to use them.
Thanks, Touya.
I'm just glad you're safe.
[gasps]
[LIZARDS growl]
[ELZE]
There's still more of them.
[yells]
Wow. Amazing sword work.
[LIZARD 2F growls]
Thanks, Linze.
[LIZARDS growling]
They just keep coming.
How many of these
monsters are there?
Come forth, Darkness.
I seek a scalebound
warrior. Lizardman!
What's that?
It's a dark summoning spell.
They won't stop coming unless
we can take out that mage.
I'm on it. Hey, Slip!
[SUMMONER 2A yelps]
[YAE]
You've been quite the nuisance.
[SUMMONER 2A sobs]
You saved our lives
back there, thank you.
Sure. Was anyone hurt badly?
Seven of my comrades were slain.
If only we'd reacted a
little sooner, we could've--
[SUSHI]
Someone! Anyone, help!
Leim. Leim no!
Help him. He's been shot!
His chest--the arrow
broke off inside.
[TOUYA]
Linze! Can you heal him?
The arrow's stuck,
and my healing magic
can't remove it.
If I were to heal him as he is,
it would extend his
suffering at best.
Please!
I'm sorry, my lady.
Leim. No.
[LEIM]
I fear I must bid you farewell.
I'm grateful for every
moment I spent with you.
[SUSHI]
Leim, stop! You can't talk okay?
So, Linze.
He could be healed if the
arrow wasn't there, right?
Well, yeah, but I can't--
All right then!
Aports!
Whoa. I forgot you
had that spell.
Come forth, Light.
Give your soothing
comfort. Cure Heal!
The pain is disappearing.
[SUSHI]
Leim!
You're okay! Yay!
Thank God.
That was amazing, Touya!
[SUSHI] You have our gratitude,
kind adventurers.
Not only did you
risk your own lives
to save us from danger,
you brought Leim back
from the brink of death.
Forgive the
delayed introduction.
My name is Liem, and I am
honored to call myself a butler
in service to
good Duke Ortlinde.
And the young lady before you--
she is the duke's own daughter.
Lady Sushi Urnea Ortlinde.
[SUSHI] Forgive my dear butler
for being so formal.
Pleased to meet you.
Yeah.
[rustling]
What'cha doin'?
Take a knee.
When you meet the
daughter of a duke,
you're supposed
to hit the ground.
You know what a duke is, right?
A... noble?
[LINZE] Duke is the highest
rank a noble can have.
In order to be given the title,
you must share blood
with the king.
The king?
[gasps]
[SUSHI]
Indeed.
Not to brag or anything,
but my father,
Duke Alfred Urnes Ortlinde,
is actually the younger brother
of his royal highness.
In that case, I guess
you'd be the king's niece.
Sushi, huh? Should I
call you Lady Sushi then?
[SUSHI]
"Sue" will suffice.
I mean, it's not like
we're at court here.
So why act pompous?
And all of that aside,
I would hardly talk down to you
when I owe you my life.
Okay.
So what's a royal
doing out here anyway?
I was on my way back
to the royal capital
after visiting my grandmother.
And then that
mage attacked you.
Do you think he's just a bandit?
That seems unlikely, right?
I had a little talk with him.
And he told me he was hired.
The client never
gave his name though.
I see. That's a shame.
[ELZE] You can still talk
without teeth, right?
[SUMMONER 2A] Please, miss,
I've told you everything!
You need our help?
[LEIM]
Yes, I think we do.
Lady Ortlinde has been targeted,
and we lack the means
to protect her.
We owe you much already,
but I must implore you to
escort us to the capital.
You would be rewarded,
of course.
An escort job.
Let's go for it.
We were headed to
the capital anyway.
We shouldn't just leave them.
I don't imagine they would
slow us down too much.
I'm up for it.
We'll make sure that
you get to the capital.
Very well, then.
Let us be on our way.
So, that's the capital.
[LINZE]
Alephis.
Capital city of the
kingdom of Belfast.
The waterfalls you see feed
the great Lake Palette,
which the city was built around.
Alephis is known to some
as the "city of lakes."
[ALL gasping
Sue!
Hi, Father!
[SUSHI, ALFRED laughing]
Thank God you're safe.
When I heard what happened...
I've never been so
worried in my life.
[gasps] Oh-ho!
You're the adventurers that
saved my daughter's life,
I take it.
I thank you.
Please, there's no need to bow.
We only did what anyone
in that situation
would've, honest.
[ALFRED]
Oh! As humble as you are brave.
Let me introduce
myself properly.
I am Duke Alfred Urnes Ortlinde.
[laughs]
So you found her in your path
as you were heading here
to deliver a letter, then?
That's right.
To think, if you had
not taken that quest,
my daughter would be kidnapped,
or perhaps even the unthinkable.
I'll have to thank
your client, too.
Do you have any idea who
might've been behind this?
[ALFRED]
Hard to say.
I'd be a fool to think
I don't have some foes.
And I'm wealthy.
My daughter could be used
for political leverage
or for ransom.
[SUSHI]
Father.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Have you spoken with Ellen yet?
Yes.
I don't think there's any
need for us to tell her
about the attack though.
It would only make her worry.
Um. Who is this "Ellen"?
Ah. That would be my wife.
My apologies.
I'd love nothing more than
to introduce you to her.
But she doesn't get
out of her room much.
So is she sick, then?
[ALFRED]
Yes and no.
She survived a terrible
illness five years ago,
but it robbed her of her sight.
You tried magic, right?
[ALFRED] Of course, and the
true damage to her body
was healed, but it did
nothing for her blindness.
That, it seems, was
more an aftereffect.
Oh. If only my
grandfather were alive.
My wife's father,
Sue's grandfather,
wielded a very
special healing spell
which enabled him to return
the body to its natural state.
The purpose of Sue's
last journey was to learn
as much as she could about it.
I hoped against hope
that she might
be able to learn that spell.
I'm sorry, Father, I couldn't.
We'll just have to find a
healer and teach it to them.
Sue, your grandfather's healing
was Null magic I'm afraid.
If it wasn't passed to you,
then no one else has it.
At this point, our best hope
is to find someone with
a similar ability.
[LINZE, ELZE, YAE gasp]
Uh...
Recovery.
Hey. What's up?
Sushi. I can see you. My girl.
You're really better.
Oh, Alfred. I see you both!
[SUSHI]
Mother!
Whew.
[ELZE]
I knew you could do it.
Way to go, ya big hero!
[LINZE] You really can use
any kind of Null magic!
Honestly. I'm in awe.
You move fearlessly
to help others
with no thought of failure.
You should know
that you have earned
my undying respect
from this day forward.
'Preciate it.
[ALFRED] Not only have you
saved my daughter's life,
you've also worked
a miracle upon my wife.
Bring it, Liem.
Your first reward.
For rushing to my
daughter's defense,
and for seeing her
brought home safely after.
It's the least I can give.
Ow. How much...?
Inside that pouch, you'll
find 40 platinum coins.
[ALL gasp]
So is platinum a good thing?
It's the denomination
above gold.
Each coin is worth
ten gold ones.
[TOUYA]
Wait.
Just how much would
40 platinum be worth?
And today's final jackpot is...
Forty million yen?
Thanks, but we
couldn't possibly.
If it's truly your wish to
become career adventurers,
you'll want equipment
that can keep you alive.
And for that, you'll need money.
'Kay.
[ALFRED]
These medals bear my crest.
They'll allow you to pass
through any city checkpoint.
Which means you'll have access
to the noble districts.
Furthermore, they show that
you are under the
duchy's protection.
Come back and visit
us sometime, okay?
I'll be waiting for you!
[ELZE]
Well, the letter's delivered.
So I guess our work
is done here.
That certainly was
an eventful mission.
[TOUYA] Mm-hm. We're gonna
head back to our place
in Reflet Village now.
What about you?
Yes, well. I've
been considering.
And I have decided to offer
myself to you, Touya.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[gasps] Wait no, I didn't
mean it in that manner!
Yeah?
Then in what way
did you mean it?
[clears throat] Although
this journey was brief,
I think I understand what
kind of person you are.
You possess great power,
yet you act with humility.
And you constantly strive
to help your fellow man.
To be blunt,
you've impressed me.
I am in training,
body and spirit.
And to that end, I wish
to stay at your side.
Uh... Should I let her?
'Course you should.
Come back to Reflet
with us, Yae.
If you join the guild there,
then we can all start
doing missions as a team.
[TOUYA]
Mm-hm. That sound good to you?
[YAE]
I would be honored.
[LINZE] Good. It would be
a shame for us to part ways
just as we're getting
to know you better.
Welcome to the team
for real this time.
Thank you for having me.
[TOUYA] I might not
deserve these powers.
But if I'm spreading
happiness, who cares?