Wait.
For real?
[TOUYA] They didn't tell me
it was a friggin' palace!
So when you turned
down the knighthood,
the king gave you this instead?
I went to the royal court to
turn him down, like Yumina said,
and he didn't really
seem that surprised.
Instead, he suddenly
offered me a new house.
I wonder,
do you think that he was
planning that from the start?
You bet your spell stones.
[TOUYA]
You caught on, too, eh?
I think it'll make
a lovely home.
[GROUP gasps, laughs]
This place is enormous.
How are we supposed to keep
the whole thing clean?
Especially with just
the five of us.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
What? Something wrong?
[YAE]
No, but, Touya...
...did you just say you'd like
all five of us to live here?
I thought that was assumed.
I don't think that's what
the king had in mind
when he gave it to you.
He probably meant for you
to live in it with Yumina.
This is a fine home,
but if it's meant to be
your place of bonding,
then it wouldn't be fair
for us three to intrude.
A "place of bonding"?
Well, then why shouldn't
the three of you stay here?
I mean, I like you all the same.
Come on.
To me? You're all like family.
Uh!
What's up?
You girls okay?
I'm gonna go and look
around upstairs, okay?
I will also be running upstairs
now to see the attic! That's it.
And I am extremely curious
about the kitchen,
which is why I'm
also running away!
What is all that?
I get it now.
You're not opposed
to starting a family,
your affections
are just divided.
Well, that's a big step forward.
While I do hope you'll share
your life with me, Touya,
I've no intention
of monopolizing you.
I think this arrangement
could work nicely.
And I suspect that
the others might agree.
I'll talk to them and
feel things out for you.
[TOUYA] Huh?! Hold on.
What are you doing?
[KOHAKU sighs]
[TOUYA] Why are they
acting so weird, Kohaku?
[KOHAKU]
Don't ask me. I'm just a cat.
And roll.
This is a pleasant garden.
You like it?
Yeah! We should stay.
[YUMINA]
Oh, Touya.
So, just to be sure,
you're actually asking all
of us to live with you.
[TOUYA]
Pretty much, yeah.
You won't change your mind
later, and kick us all out?
[TOUYA]
Why would I do that?
And Yumina here.
You'll treat all of us exactly
as you would treat her?
Course I will!
[ALL gasping]
It's settled then.
All of us will live
here together.
We'll move forward as
we discussed earlier
once you're all sure you've
made up your minds.
Yeah!
Right!
Everyone's agreed, then.
Made up your minds about what?
I'm lost.
[GIRLS]
It's a secret!
O... kay.
I'm starting to think that your
authority in this household
is rather limited, Master.
My name is Laim, young master.
I'm your new butler.
I've brought on these
ladies of the Maid's Guild
to assist me temporarily.
My name is Lapis, sir.
And my name is Cecile, sir.
We're very pleased to meet you.
These two will handle the
gardens and the kitchens,
and these two shall ensure
the estate's security.
Laim has actually been
my father's chief butler
for as long as I can remember.
Huh? Seriously?
Did he do something
to get demoted?
No, sir.
I've passed that
duty on to my son.
As I have decided to spend
the remainder of my life
serving the man who saved
my younger brother's.
Younger brother?
Yes, his name is Liam.
He's currently in the service
of his grace, Duke Ortlinde.
Oh! That guy I pulled
the arrow out of.
So, Touya. What do you think?
If you recommend him, then sure.
Thanks! Glad to have you.
Thank you very much, sir.
Everyone should
know their duties.
Let's get to work at once.
[STAFF]
Sir!
I can't believe the man
who ran the king's palace
is working for us now.
A talented butler is more
helpful than you'd guess.
This just goes to show how much
promise everyone sees in you.
[LAIM]
Master Touya.
His Grace Duke Ortlinde
and Lady Sushi
request an audience with you.
[SUSHI]
Touya! I came to see you!
[TOUYA]
Uh-oh, the tickler's here.
I was surprised to hear about
you and Touya's
engagement, cousin.
How'd he woo you?
There wasn't any wooing
that I was aware of.
And here I was contemplating a
marriage between you and Sue.
Well played, Yumina.
You beat me to it.
You should've told me you were
thinking about that, Father!
Oh, well!
It's never too late to
show my feminine allure!
Well, that makes one, yes.
How would a double wedding
please you, Touya?
You know, what would
really please me
is some more of this tea.
Fine. I'll stand down
for today at least.
Thanks for understanding, sir.
I should tell you that I'm
actually here to make a request.
Yeah, what's that?
As you recently became aware,
my brother is contemplating
an alliance with the
kingdom of Mismede.
Naturally, the kings would
like to meet in person
so they may discuss
this matter in depth.
And that's our problem.
Normally, one king would visit
the other at his palace.
But now, the journey
seems too perilous.
And so, I--
You'd like to use
Touya's Gate spell.
That's right, Yumina.
You catch on quite quickly.
[TOUYA]
But, I can only use Gate
to travel to places I've
been to-- Oh, I get it.
Yes. I'm asking you
to travel to Mismede.
That's what I figured.
I am Garen of Mismede.
Well met.
And I'm with the First
Knight Squad of Belfast.
My name's Lyon Blitz.
This journey to Mismede
shall mark the first time
our two kingdom's
soldiers act in unison.
Well, we're glad
to be a part of it.
Getting to travel at a native's
side should be a big help, Olga.
I was about to return to
my homeland, regardless.
We're actually just as excited
to be traveling with you.
Our first stop
will be the city of Canaan,
which is in Belfast.
From there, we will cross
the Great Gau River
to enter Mismede.
Fear not. We shall see that
you get home safely, milady.
I'll be counting
on you, Sir Lyon.
Oh, thanks!
[YAE gasps]
It's this one!
[YUMINA]
Sorry.
Now, let's see about this one.
And... pair.
Nicely done!
Seems I've been
bested yet again.
[TOUYA]
Yae! Why don't we switch out?
You can help Olga here
practice her shogi.
I would love that!
Dolan taught me the basics
back at the Silver Moon.
[TOUYA]
Cool.
Hey, Yumina?
Wanna learn blackjack?
[OLGA]
I'm 17!
[TAE]
Yeah, right.
[TOUYA] And so, thanks to
the clever Puss in Boots,
the miller's son was married
to the king's daughter
and they all lived happily.
Yeah, and what happened
after that, Touya?
[gasps]
[GAREN]
What is it?
Armored men approaching.
At least 20.
It's probably a gang of bandits.
Lemme see.
Search for bandits.
8... 12... 20...
I'm counting 28 of 'em total.
Lemme try something real quick.
Enchant Phone: Multiple.
Yeah, this'll work.
Check it out.
I lock on here, and...
Paralyze!
[BANDIT 6A yelps]
[BANDIT 6B groans]
[BANDIT 6C groans]
[BANDIT 6D grunts]
[BANDIT 6E screams]
What was that?
I hit 'em with a
paralysis spell.
They should be easy
to round up now.
Huh?
So, what do we do
with these guys?
I'll send a rider to Canaan.
They can send guards
to pick them up.
Thank you, Lyon.
Sorry for the trouble.
Ah! Not at all!
You need not worry
on my account.
I'm always glad
to be of service.
Pardon, I must make
my men draw straws.
Ah-ha. So that's how it is, eh?
Oh, to be young.
What a feeling it once was.
I almost miss it.
I barely remember it.
And when did we get old?
It's clear to us that Lyon
has feelings for Lady Olga,
but do you think she knows?
Oh yeah, that girl's
flirtin' hard.
Luckily for him, she's not half
as dense as a certain someone.
Uh? Yeah?
Who's that?
He's certainly slow
to pick up on things,
but he does have a
very kind spirit.
He's super nice to everybody.
Yeah. That does make
up for the dimness.
There's a difference
between being nice
and leading people on, though.
Do you still not get it?!
Then sit down and think.
But why?
[GIRLS]
Just do it!
[TOUYA]
'Kay.
Sure.
Hey look, it's Lyon. There.
What's up, Lyon?
Souvenir shopping?
[LYON]
Hm?
Hey, Touya.
No. I'm... just...
shopping for a gift.
Oh! Nothing romantic though.
I promised my mother that
I'd get her something.
Oh?
Heh!
Pick something, Arma.
I'll grab it for you
as a memento of your
time in Belfast.
Whichever I want?
Wow!
Um... This one!
You've got good taste.
[laughs] Thank you
very much, Touya.
Here. Thank you.
[CLERK 6A]
Thanks for your business!
Say, does your sister
likes broaches as well?
[ARMA]
I'm not sure.
It depends.
[gasps] Elius flowers like
this are her favorite!
She'd love that.
Well that works out.
Well, see ya later.
We're gonna go catch up
with the others now.
Right. Bye.
Very subtle. I'm impressed.
You figured me out?
Of course. And I think it's
very sweet what you did,
although I would've
liked a present myself.
Sorry about that.
Well, the only gift
I really need is
the ring you'll put on
my finger someday.
I'm willing to wait until then.
[TOUYA]
Yeah, about that...
--[TOUYA groaning]
--[GIRLS laughing]
Thank you, Touya, and sorry.
Don't be. People get sick
on boats all the time.
[OLGA] We could stay
here for the evening
if you don't feel well
enough to travel on.
I'm good. It's just
a carriage ride.
I felt fine once I
got off the boat.
[ELZE] Strange that you needed
Touya to carry you, then.
Eh, Linze?
Well, yeah, I was tired.
And Touya's arms are
deceptively strong.
Not that I noticed.
Sorry if getting carried
around was embarrassing.
Oh. No, that was
not the problem.
[sighs]
There's no point in trying.
This is Touya
we're talking about.
Stop staring.
Was that for real?
[KOHAKU]
Yes. I felt it, too.
Someone was definitely
observing us,
but they've concealed
their presence for now.
We'll have to keep our
guard up moving forward.
[OLGA]
Are you ready to go, Touya?
Yeah, sure!
[TOUYA]
Oh, ho!
Olga. That's a beautiful
hairpiece you're wearing.
Oh!
Yeah? Do you like it?
I'm flattered to hear that.
It suits you nicely.
I wish the man I care for
would get me such a gift.
Although, honestly, I'd be
even happier if he displayed
his affection by hugging me
close, or holding my hand.
Welp! Time to go!
It doesn't seem likely
that we'll reach Eld
Village before nightfall.
Then we better find a place
to set camp soon, right?
This forest is full
of magical creatures,
but a party this large
should be safe.
That's a bit
frightening, though.
Kohaku's with us.
Those magic beasts
won't even come close.
You're the best, Kohaku.
Yeah!
Hey, are we outta time?
Would you mind if I finished
drying my hair, Touya?
Yeah, but hurry. We don't
wanna make people suspicious.
[ELZE, YAE]
Okay.
--[birds cawing]
--[horse winnies]
Touya!
What did we miss?
No one knows,
but the animals seem to be
running from something.
Something big's
heading towards us.
It's flying!
[GAREN]
A dragon.
But what is it doing out here?
This happen often?
No, the dragons normally
stay within the sacred grounds
at the center of our nation.
If the dragons have
left those grounds,
it may be to retaliate
against a trespasser.
You think someone did that?
There is another option.
It's a fairly rare occurrence,
but young dragons sometimes
rampage without cause.
[gasps] Uh-oh.
Looks like it's heading
straight for Eld Village.
We have to help.
Yumina.
I need you to stay.
Keep everyone here safe.
Right.
Let's get moving.
[ALL gasping]
We need to get the
villagers out of here!
Strike true, Oh Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance:
Shining Javelin!
Kohaku!
Hey, Linze!
[LINZE]
Yeah? [groans]
It's on us.
That's right. Come after us.
[roars]
What?! How dare you
insult my master!
Hold on. Do you think you
could translate for me?
[KOHAKU]
"Though maggots such as you
will surely taste of excrement,
I shall devour you for
distracting me from my play."
Stupid whelp can't even
use the common tongue!
"From his play"?
Sounds like we've got a
selfish brat on our hands.
Linze, I can knock
him out of the sky.
Be ready to take out his wings.
I'm ready. Go!
Multiple!
Strike true, Oh Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance:
Shining Javelin!
Come forth, Water.
Blade both Cold and Clear:
Aqua Cutter!
[gasps]
[LINZE yelps]
[TOUYA]
Boost!
Cut it close there.
Uh... huh...
What now?
[gasps]
[yells]
[DRAGON groans]
Full power... Boost!
Ah... Yeah.
Those scales are like diamonds.
Well. hey, at least this
one doesn't regenerate.
[gasps] It just shoots fire!
[TOUYA yells]
Not good.
[TOUYA]
Slip!
Yae, Elze.
Can you two buy me some time?
Linze, I need you to summon
a giant wall of ice for me.
Kohaku, you keep her covered.
[YAE]
Hey! Over here!
Now come forth, Ice.
Eternal Frozen Ridge:
Grand Wall of Ice!
Modeling!
Multiple!
Strike true, Oh Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance:
Shining Javelin!
[TOUYA]
Modeling!
Play with this!
We got him.
[YAE]
We actually did it!
[LINZE]
That attack was awesome.
[KOHAKU]
Well done, Master.
The whelp is dead.
[ALL gasp]
[TOUYA]
Crap. Another one?
[RED DRAGON] One of my brethren
has caused you great trouble.
My apologies.
You can talk to us.
[RED DRAGON] I am the
sovereign of the sacred ground.
I had come to retrieve the
one who went wild, but...
Red Dragon.
I bid you to warn
the Azure Monarch
to raise his children
with discipline.
It can't be.
The White Monarch is here?
So that's how the black dragon
was made to meet its end.
Don't misunderstand.
My master slayed that dragon.
Rightly so.
The brat failed to pay
him proper respect.
That sealed its fate.
[RED DRAGON] What? A human is
master of the White Monarch?
I apologize for my
brethren's insolence.
[TOUYA] Well, at least
you tried to stop him.
[RED DRAGON]
I beg your mercy.
I'll let you off this time,
but give the young ones
a good talkin' to
so none of 'em pull
somethin' like this again.
That I will, sir.
Glad that's done with.
What a hassle.
[ELZE, LINZE, YAE sigh]
[TOUYA]
Hey, what's the matter?
You're really asking that?
You talked to a dragon.
Aren't you freaking out
at least a little?
[TOUYA]
Eh. I'm all right.
Well, not all of us
have your blessings.
[TOUYA]
It's all good!
[YUMINA]
It went well then?
[OLGA]
What a relief.
[sighs] I'm exhausted.
[YUMINA]
Here.
I brought a blanket for you.
You're good to me.
Thanks, Yumina.
Did you sleep well, my beloved?
Uh...
Uh?!
[ELZE]
About time you woke up.
You slept like a
rock, Touya. Wow.
In fact, I've never seen
you look so relaxed.
Oh, yeah?
Well, did I miss anything big?
[ALL]
No, not really.
Come now, that's
enough sulking, girls.
Rock-Paper-Scissors is sacred.
So respect the outcome
of the match.
We know. We know.
Yeah.
A shameful defeat.
Were you competing
for something?
Nothing worth talking about.
[TOUYA]
Kohaku. What happened?
[KOHAKU]
What does anyone fight for?
Territory.