Starting today, I'll
be joining your staff.
Please treat me with kindness.
Sorry to spring this on ya.
Do you think you could
find a place for her?
[LAIM] Yes, sir.
As you can see,
I made my own outfit.
You'll find that my will
to work is second to none.
Although I will be
taking my breaks.
Okay. Well, it's gotten pretty
late, let's all get some rest.
[FRANCESCA]
So, where's our bed?
Excuse me?
[FRANCESCA]
Service with love!
[LAIM]
Well? A-Am I doing it right?
I love you, and I
want you to know it.
Okay?
[TOUYA muffled]
[knocking]
[gasps]
[YUMINA]
Hey, Touya? It's Yumina.
Good evening, may I come inside?
Yeah. Why not?
So, what's up?
[YUMINA]
Touya...
Yeah?!
[YUMINA]
Do you know why I'm angry?
Because, I was
waiting for a kiss!
Right at the front of the line!
But, you let those two sneak
their way in front of me!
That's why?
Obviously!
So, then you're not upset about
Linze's sudden confession?
There was nothing sudden
about that confession, Touya.
It's plain as day that
she's in love with you.
Was it really?
My bad, I honestly had no idea.
It doesn't matter. So long
as I'm one of them,
I don't care if you
take ten wives,
or even 20 when
you finally marry.
I'd consider it proof
of your masculinity!
However! How... ev... er!
You've been far too careless
letting others kiss
you all willy nilly.
You haven't even kissed
me, so keep your guard up!
You need to take a thorough
look at your defenses!
And get them up to shape!
Wait, but Yumina.
The thing is...
Don't make excuses.
Okay...
[sighs]
Give me a hug and a kiss now,
and all will be forgiven.
Uh. I think you're setting
the difficulty level
a little high here.
[YUMINA laughs]
[laughs] So, correct
me if I'm wrong,
but I'm the first one you
kissed yourself, right?
Huh? Oh.
Well, yeah. I guess you are.
Now be honest with me.
How do you feel about Linze?
Honestly?
I think she's really cute.
When she told me how
she felt, I was excited.
But, I haven't even figured
things out with you yet.
So adding her to the mix...
Touya, do you like her or not?
Yeah, I like her a lot.
I think she's amazing.
Well, Linze, you heard him.
Come on out.
Huh?!
[TOUYA]
What the--? How?!
What's going on here?!
[YUMINA]
I asked Leen to cast
an invisibility spell on
her so we could do this.
'Kay, but how did you
get in the room? Oh.
I guess you walked
in behind Yumina.
[LINZE]
Mm-hm.
You forced us to do this.
It was very rude of you to
shut yourself in your room
without giving her an answer.
I know, but...
She was crying, you know.
No matter what I said, she
was convinced you hated her.
[gasps] I'm sorry, Linze.
[LINZE]
I'm sorry, too.
I should've been more
considerate of your feelings.
I was... selfish.
No way. Don't worry.
Like I said earlier, I was
happy after what you did.
I mean, you're
really cute, and--
Touya!
So, now that you've
both confirmed
your feelings for each other,
why not make this formal
and call it an engagement?
Uh?!
This may seem strange to you,
but it's perfectly common
for more than one person
to get married in Belfast.
And I'm willing to share
as long as you are.
[TOUYA]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Yes. I am. I would like to
get married to you, Touya.
May I?
Yeah, this is all kinda
sudden, is the thing.
Say yes. Won't you, please?
[sighs] All right, sure.
If both of you are okay
with it, then so am I.
Thank you, I'm so happy.
We're in the same spot, Linze.
Both of us are
Touya's fiancés now.
Yeah. Anyway, it's late.
I think you two should
get back to your rooms.
Sure. But first I'd like
a goodnight kiss.
Huh?
Um. I'd like one too.
'Kay. Cool if I just
kiss your foreheads?
I can settle for that.
[YUMINA]
Well, goodnight, darling.
[LINZE]
Goodnight, sweetheart.
G'night. Sleep well.
[sighs] What the heck am
I supposed to do now?
[door opens]
I didn't wake you up,
did I, Touya?
Yes?
[TOUYA] So, um... Next
time, could you knock?
Eh, nevermind, forget
I said anything.
Uh. Yae?
What are you doing out here?
Waiting for Elze to bring you.
We hear you'll be taking
Linze as your wife.
[TOUYA]
Uh, yeah. Looks like it.
I didn't realize how
close you two were.
Do you actually love her?!
Well. I wouldn't quite describe
it as love, just yet.
But, I care about her, as more
than a friend, I think.
[ELZE]
And she accepted that answer?!
Yeah.
Linze is super timid.
'Cept when it comes to
what counts, apparently.
She really is my total opposite.
I still can't believe
how bold she got.
You and I are quite alike
in regards to this.
Without an inciting event
to trigger my emotions,
I can never make up my mind.
What do you...? [gasps]
Touya. We want you to fight us.
If you win, that'll
be the end of it.
[TOUYA]
Huh?!
But, on the other hand, in
the event that we beat you,
well then...
We'll have a request for you,
and you'll have to hear
us out, then answer it.
I've dulled the edge of this
sword so it won't cut,
but it's still heavy enough
to break your bones,
so be careful.
Listen... Couldn't you just
ask the question now?
[ELZE] Take the edge off your
gunblade with modeling, 'kay?
Also, no offensive magic.
In exchange, I'll fight
without my Boost spell.
Look, I'm not agreeing
to any of this
until I know why you
want me to fight you!
People like Elze and I need
something more visceral
to help clear our minds.
Now square up, bucko,
'cause we're comin' for ya.
Why is this happening to me?
[ELZE]
It's now or never.
Fine... Modeling...
It's cool if I use
rubber bullets?
Uh-huh. So, are ya
ready to do this?
Yeah.
Blade Mode!
[yells]
Are you even trying?!
[TOUYA]
Gun Mode!
[YAE gasping]
[ELZE yells]
[TOUYA]
Reload. That's it, you're beat.
[ELZE]
You won't shoot?!
If you're willing to
admit that I win,
then I'd rather not have to.
You're too soft!
How can you protect Linze
when you're so damn nice?
This is who I am.
What can I say?
Yeah, true.
You're just that kind of guy.
It's why Yae and I fell
in love with you.
What the...?
Huh?
That's what she aimed at?
[yells]
We would like you
to put the two of us
in the same position as
Yumina and Linze, okay?
What she's trying to say is that
we would also like to move
this relationsh--
You know what?
Nevermind, you're doing
great Elze, keep going!
You were supposed to
back me up, Yae!
Okay fine, here goes nothing,
the point of order is that
I'm in love with you, too.
I also have feelings
of that sort for you.
You want the same position
that Yumina and Linze have?
Then are you trying to say...?
Yes, it's what you
think. We would...
We would like to become
your wives as well,
if you'd have us, that is.
No, you have to!
You lost the fight, didn't you?
You put yourselves through
all this just to say that?
[YUMINA]
I figured it was the best way
to get their courage up.
[TOUYA]
Yumina?
Wait, are you saying
this was your idea?
Yes, I am.
I proposed quite some time ago
that all of us should marry you.
We hammered out all the
details well in advance.
Wow, that's impressive
and frightening.
[ELZE]
S-So Touya?
What about you?
[TOUYA] Huh?
Hey, did you hear me?
If you have any feelings
for me and Yae,
now's the time to say so.
Well, I like both of
you a lot, of course.
The thing is...
I'm really sorry.
But, could I ask all
of you for some time?
I need to sort out my
thoughts before I decide.
Yes, of course.
We don't want to force
this on you too suddenly.
Thanks, Yumina.
[FRANCESCA]
So, this is where you've been.
Hey, Cesca.
[FRANCESCA] I have a general
grasp of your situation.
What about it do you
need to debate?
I mean, they think I can
make them all happy,
but what if they're wrong?
I'm scared that they'll all
end up dissatisfied.
I assume you mean
while in the bedroom.
The heck got you to that idea?!
I'm just wondering if I can
do my duty as a husband.
Oh, speaking of duties failed,
there was something I forgot
to tell you yesterday.
Is there treasure
here after all?
Someone left a message
for you, Master.
[TOUYA]
Yeah, who?
[FRANCESCA]
Professor Regina Babylon.
[TOUYA]
The professor?
[TOUYA] You mean the professor
who built this place?
[gasps] Uh. Cesca?
What'cha doin'?
[FRANCESCA] No idea.
The professor said that if I
handed this to my new master,
he'd know what to do.
Whoa, it worked!
I see a person.
[FRANCESCA] Yes. That
would be the professor.
Hey there, I'm
Professor Regina Babylon.
A pleasure to meet you,
Mochizuki Touya.
Hold on. You know my name?
What kind of cr--?
[REGINA]
Say no more.
That's an excellent
question, Touya.
It's only natural that you would
wonder about such things.
And I have the answer right
here with me, of course.
Take a good, long look.
This is my very favorite pair.
Like I care!
[laughs] I was kidding around.
Just having a bit of fun.
Try not to let it get to you.
Yup.
You are exactly the person
I thought you were.
Ah... Uh? What's this?
Taking a look at my
aroma pipe, eh?
As I'm sure you've noticed, it's
the same color as my underwear.
How does that make
you feel? Frisky?
Hold on, now! I'll answer
your real question.
I just needed to get that
out of my system, okay?
[TOUYA] One more panty joke and
I'm pullin' this cord for real.
Your question about how
someone from the past
knows so much about you?
It's because I have a tool that
lets me see into the future.
[TOUYA]
Seriously?
[REGINA] Yes, though I
can't choose the era.
That device is what's
allowing me to record
this mock conversation for you.
It's showing me how you'll react
to my words so I can respond.
I've been following
the adventures
of you and the girls
for quite a while now.
Very entertaining.
You mean you've been
watching us this whole time?
No, I was blinded at one point.
The future had been rendered
unstable, you see.
[TOUYA]
Unstable?
Yeah, know what caused it?
The sudden appearance
of the Fraze in our world.
[TOUYA]
"The Fraze"?
[REGINA] I couldn't predict
when they'd appear.
So, despite my
very best efforts.
those monsters brought
the Partheno civilization
to its end.
[TOUYA] Wait. Are you saying
that the Fraze's appearance
caused some kind
of interruption
in the flow of time
between our eras?
[REGINA]
Well put.
At the time, I assumed that
I wasn't seeing a future
because the world
had been destroyed.
Or was going to be,
I should say.
So what ended up saving it?
[REGINA]
Nothing. The Fraze disappeared.
Every bit as suddenly
as they'd arrived.
I've no idea why.
And thanks to that, you can
now see into the future again.
[REGINA] Uh-huh,
and I've jumped right back
into my favorite drama!
Your current ordeal
with the ladies
has been especially
fun to watch.
Would you mind not peeping
in on my private life?
Come now, what's it hurt?
I'm entrusting you with
Babylon in exchange.
I think that's a fairly good
deal, don't you?
Call it a thank you
gift. Enjoy it.
[TOUYA]
Huh?
Listen, you can't just--
Hey, can I ask you
one more question?
You told me that you
were enjoying watching
my current situation,
but is that partly because
you know how this
is gonna end for us?
[REGINA] You want me to
tell you how it shakes out
with those four?
I couldn't possibly.
That would ruin the fun.
It's the most important
question I could ask you.
Stop overthinking it, Touya.
Since when were you the type
to agonize over the future?
Uh.
I fear that this concludes
our little chat.
Fair warning, as soon as this
message finishes playing,
Francesca will be naked.
[screams]
[REGINA]
I'm joking! Later, kid.
Do I strip now?
No ma'am! Absolutely not!
[TOUYA] Ah... That's more
than I can handle.
[LEIM]
Lady Sushi.
You seem to be in rather high
spirits as of late, don't you?
[GOD]
Oh, hi, Touya!
If you'd called I would've
made more snacks.
It's been a while,
God. How are ya?
Honestly, I'm surprised
that this worked.
[GOD]
Oh, yeah.
I imagine your Gate could work
in any realm that has magic.
So? What do you need?
[TOUYA] Yeah. No matter
how much I think,
I can't figure out if this
is the right thing to do.
[GOD] Aw. I'm a bachelor myself,
so frankly, what do I know?
But I feel like you're
overthinking this.
Yeah, you're not the first
person to suggest that to me,
but I can't stop
mulling it over.
[GOD]
Hm... In that case,
why don't I call in
an expert for ya?
[TOUYA]
Huh?
[GOD]
Hey, how've you been?
Good. Good.
Say, could ya stop by for a bit?
Great, see ya soon.
[click]
Sorry for keepin' ya!
[GOD] Wha? Nah, that
was lightning fast!
Sorry, Touya.
[TOUYA]
♪ I can hear my heart pound. ♪
♪ Ready to burst. ♪
[TOUYA]
So, uh...
Who might this be?
[GOD]
It's the Goddess of love.
Who better to advise you, right?
It's nice to finally meet you.
I've been curious about
your situation for a while.
So, yeah, I've looked
in on occasion.
[TOUYA] That makes three
people spying on me.
I gotta ask,
what exactly does being
a goddess of love entail?
A lot of mood setting.
Like, I would never directly
influence someone's emotions.
But I do like to set
up a good cliché.
And that takes work, mind you.
[TOUYA]
Clichés?
[LOVE GOD]
Ya know what I mean?
Check it. When a guy swears
he'll marry his love
after the war, I'll just
make him die tragically
right on her doorstep.
[TOUYA]
So that's you're fault?!
Anyway! What'cha need help with?
Well, ya see...
[LOVE GOD] Hm... That certainly
is a fascinating situation.
Although, I don't really
understand what the problem is.
If you're all in love,
then what's the issue?
[TOUYA] For one thing,
there are four of them.
[LOVE GOD] Forget about
what was common sense
in your original world,
okay? Those girls love you.
If you love them back and
wanna make 'em happy,
then focus on that.
Well, I want to, but I don't
know if I have what it takes
to do that for four people.
While it's plenty important
to cherish your partners,
you still have to balance that
with being true to yourself.
You're saying it's okay
to be selfish sometimes?
Well, yeah, of course!
How can the people
you love be happy
if you aren't happy with them?
Ya figure out what to do yet?
I'm not sure, but I
think I'm getting close.
Great, you can get off my cloud.
Before you go,
what did you think of that
great cliché I hit you with?
What are you talking about?
[LOVE GOD] When you moved
into your new house,
I set up that whole "happened to
walk in on them changing clothes
in the washroom" scene.
Did ya like it?
What?! That was you?
The hell is your problem?!
[GOD] ♪ I'm scared, I'm
frail, but I'm warmin' u--! ♪
[TOUYA]
Kohaku?
What's the matter, Master?
[TOUYA]
Sorry.
Could you ask the
girls to meet me?
So, um... Look.
First off, I won't be
getting married.
[GIRLS]
What?!
What changed your mind, Touya?!
Yes, tell us!
If we did something wrong,
then give us a chance
to make it up to you!
You promised, Touya!
You said we'd marry!
Hold on, it's not that bad!
I'm just talking
about right now.
I really need to give
this time, that's all.
You need time?
So, you do want to marry us
eventually, then, right?
[TOUYA]
I do.
So long as none of
you are against it,
I'll marry all four of you.
That's a promise,
and I plan to keep it.
But, it could be years.
I'm not gonna marry someone
now just to be agreeable
when I know I'm not
ready for it yet.
What do you mean by that?
[TOUYA] I'm not mature
enough to be responsible
for someone else's life.
I have no plans for my future.
So, I'm asking you to wait.
[sighs] That's a selfish
thing to do, you know.
I know that, and if you
lose interest in me while
you're waiting,
I won't blame you.
Well played.
You say that, knowing
it's impossible. Hmph.
I see where that saying
comes from now.
Whoever falls in love
first really does lose.
Even if my sister were
to lose interest,
I'll wait for you as
long as I have to.
Whoa there!
I never said I wasn't
gonna wait for him.
I'm okay with this
course as well.
Seeing as we've all
expressed our feelings now,
all that's left is to wait
and watch them grow.
That sounds nice.
Now that we've all become
Touya's fiancés,
why don't we celebrate?
We can mark the occasion
by having our husband
kiss us each in turn!
[YAE, LINZE, ELZE]
Huh?!
I mean that's all well
and good in theory,
but isn't it too soon?
Yes, it's my opinion that
even if we're engaged now,
we should continue to
have modest relations.
And, what if I told you that
Touya kissed me just yesterday?
[YAE, ELZE gasp]
Um, full disclosure?
He kissed me as well.
Yeah. Just on the
forehead, though.
[TOUYA]
Yeah. Heh, um.
Then you better do
it with us, too!
Just in the interest
of fairness.
Not because we wanna kiss.
I want to! I would
really like to kiss.
It's true.
Well, since you asked.
[gasps] No way!
Too embarrassing!
[groans]
Are you all right?!
That's twice in a day, sis.
Why couldn't you do that
after I took my turn?!
[LEEN laughs] I never grow
bored of watching him.
[FRANCESCA]
According to the professor,
he ends up with a
total of nine wives.
That's a high number.
Hey. I don't recall giving you
permission to enjoy this.
[gasps] Please let me
stay here, Master!
I did all of my chores, I swear!
Say, Leen.
Do you think you could
end up marrying Touya?
[LEEN]
Who knows?
There could be a chance.
[GOD]
All right.
So, you've made a
decision, good for you.
There's no point getting married
until I've become the
man I wanna be, right?
[GOD]
Well, hey.
You're as well-intentioned
as they come.
And you're no coward, either.
Plus, you don't have a big head
about all the powers I gave ya.
[CLERK 12A]
Look, kid.
That might be money somewhere,
but it's no good in this city.
Huh? Sorry sir, but this
is all the cash I have.
[GOD]
What's wrong?!
Is someone in
trouble down there?!
Yeah, sorry I gotta go.
Talk to ya later, okay?
[TOUYA]
S'cuse me.
Would it be okay if I
bought that for him?
[CLERK 12A]
Sure, thanks.
Thanks a million.
That's kind of you.
[TOUYA] Sure, always glad
to help someone in a bind.
That's an interesting
shape for a coin.
[ENDE]
You think?
Honestly, I find the
device in your pocket
to be far more interesting.
My name's Mochizuki Touya.
What's yours?
I'm Ende. A pleasure, Touya.