[GOD] Better rip off
the ol' band-aid.
I'm sorry to say
that you're dead.
I was throwing some
lightning around
and accidentally dropped
a bolt on you.
The guilt is really
tearing me up.
It was a freak accident--
hasn't happened to me in weeks.
Gotcha.
[GOD]
What was it, again? Mochizuki?
Touya. It's Mochizuki Touya.
[GOD]
Mochizuki Touya. Of course.
I have to say.
You're taking the news
surprisingly well.
I was bracing myself to
get chewed out a little.
Well, honestly,
this doesn't quite
feel real to me yet.
I'm still half expecting
to wake up from a dream.
But if I am dead,
then that's that.
No point complaining.
That's a mature perspective.
[TOUYA] Still, I was hoping
to live a bit past 15.
So, is this the part
where you judge me, or?
No, I'm resurrecting you.
You can do that?
[GOD] Yes, but I'm not
allowed to send you back
to the world you were born in,
so I found another for you.
It's kind of like yours.
The air won't choke you,
that's the key.
Oh. Sounds good to me.
Huh? It does?
Looks to me like you're
doing all you can.
I'm just glad I get
to live again at all.
[TOUYA] Grandad always
said to be forgiving
of others' mistakes.
I wonder if he's seeing this.
You've a very kind heart.
Tell me, is there anything else
I can do to make up
for all the trouble?
Anything?
[GOD] Mm. Anything you'd
like in your next life?
Cool. Um. Well...
Could you make it possible
for me to keep on
using this guy?
[GOD]
Your smartphone?
Uh. That's kind of
a dumb idea, isn't it?
I'd have no way to
keep it charged there.
[GOD] Actually,
that won't be a problem.
You should be able to recharge
the battery with magic.
Say what?
You mean you're
sending me to a world
that has actual magic?
[GOD]
Oh, yeah. It's got fireballs,
lizardmen, the works.
I'll endow you
with a natural talent
for using magic, as well.
Still, though. Are you sure
there's nothing else you'd like?
Yeah. Thanks a million.
Oh, I did wanna
ask you one thing.
If I were to bring a
smartphone from my world,
would I be able to
call people from it?
[GOD] Oh. No, I can't let
you communicate directly.
You'll be able to watch or read
anything you'd like, though.
Also, I'll set things up
so you can call me
if ever you need to.
I understand. Let's go
with that, then.
[TOUYA gasps]
So this is my new home.
[TOUYA]
Guess I'll follow this road.
It should lead to
something eventually.
--[phone rings]
--[yelps]
Hey, what's up?
[GOD]
Oh, good, I got through!
Glad you arrived in once piece.
Yeah, me, too.
[GOD] I forgot to mention
something about your phone.
I changed your map
and navigation
to match the world you're
in now. Try using it.
Thanks for letting me know!
That'll be a big help.
I was about to just
pick a random direction.
[GOD]
Yeah, don't do that.
No offense, but I'd rather not
see you again any time soon.
Good luck! I'm out.
[TOUYA] I really have
God's phone number.
[TOUYA]
Heading west.
But even if I reach a city.
What am I supposed to do there?
Should've asked God to let me
convert my money somehow.
Hey! You there!
Hi, how's it goin'?
Hey, we speak the same
language, that's cool.
Wherever did you obtain such
marvelous apparel from?
You must allow me to
purchase it from you!
I'll pay you well.
You won't regret it!
Huh?
Come on down.
We'll find a new set of
clothes to replace yours.
[TOUYA]
Uh, thanks.
I can't read the writing.
Sir, it's nice to see you again!
[ZANAC]
Mm-hm. Get my friend fitted here
for a new outfit, will you?
Something nice.
[TOUYA]
Looks like he owns this shop.
[ZANAC]
Hey! Kid.
I'll pay ya double if ya
sell me those clothes as well.
[TOUYA]
Do I have a choice?
Well, if you find any
other clothes like those,
stop by again, please.
Sure.
By the way, this town
wouldn't happen
to have an inn with rooms
for rent, would it?
I was hoping to find a place
to rest for the night
before it gets dark out.
I know just the place.
Walk down till you
reach the town square
and take a right
at the main road.
There's a fine inn
called the Silver Moon.
Ya can't miss it.
[TOUYA]
Thanks for everything.
[ZANAC chuckles]
[TOUYA]
The Silver Moon Inn, eh?
Look at that.
His shop's called the
"Fashion King Zanac."
[ZANAC moans]
[yelps]
[ELZE]
That wasn't the deal!
You said you'd pay us
one gold coin for it!
[MEN chuckle]
[MAN 1A] That was if the
goods were in better shape.
This antler has a
scratch on it. Here.
That's just one silver coin!
A single scratch
doesn't make the thing
ten times less valuable!
Calm down.
Forget it. I don't
want your money.
Just give the antler back to me.
[MAN 1B]
Don't misread us, sweetheart.
We aren't negotiating.
[TOUYA]
Sorry to interrupt, but,
could you spare a moment?
Who are you?
N' what do you want?
Don't misread me.
My business is actually
with the ladies here.
What business?
I was hoping you might
be willing to part
with that shiny antler
for one gold.
Heck yeah!
[TOUYA]
Sweet.
[MAN 1A]
The hell's wrong with you?
Think I'm allowed to
destroy my own property.
[MAN 1B growls, yells]
[GOD] I'm giving a good boost
to your stamina, reflexes,
memory and so forth.
Long as nothing
too crazy happens,
you'll be pretty
tough to kill now.
[MAN 1B yelling]
[TOUYA] Whoa, it's like
he's moving in slow motion.
[MAN 1B grunts]
[MAN 1A groans]
[LINZE gasps]
[TOUYA]
Here. The gold I owe you.
You sure? I appreciate
the gesture, but--
I'm not about to
break your stuff
without paying you back.
Then I'd be worse
than those guys.
[TOUYA] I only broke it to
try and catch them off guard.
If I'd known that they'd
be so easy to beat,
I could've saved it.
[ELZE]
All right, you convinced me.
Thanks for the assist, stranger.
My name's Elze Silhoueska,
and this is my younger twin.
Her name's Linze Silhoueska.
[LINZE]
Thank you for helping us, sir.
[TOUYA]
Hi, I'm Mochizuki Touya.
Mochizuki? That's
an exotic name.
Well. It's my family name.
You can just call me Touya.
Oh. So you introduce
yourself backwards.
Bet you're from Eashen.
Eashen? Uh. Well.
[ELZE] What are you doing
this far from home?
Yeah. Uh.
For the time being,
I'm just trying to find
the Silver Moon Inn.
I haven't planned any
further than that.
The Silver Moon?
The two of us are actually
staying at that inn.
[TOUYA]
Huh?
[ELZE, LINZE humming]
[ELZE]
Here it is.
Hi there, d'you think
I could book a room
through the next month?
Sure thing.
You finished checking in?
Yeah. All set.
Sorry for the wait.
[MICAH]
Uh, is this a friend of yours?
He helped us out
just a moment ago.
My. Found yourself
a man already, have you?
Shut your gossip mouth, Micah!
[ELZE] The men in that
alley had commissioned us
to bring them the
Crystal Deer Antler.
They seemed a bit dodgy,
but work is work, I figured.
Well, lesson learned.
I was against taking that job
from the beginning, remember?
I really wish you would
listen to me more often.
Yeah, I guess we'd
better quit freelancing
and start taking jobs
from the guild now.
Think there's still
time to register today?
No, they'll be closed by now.
But let's go tomorrow.
Guild jobs are much safer.
[TOUYA] "Guild."
Sounds like a temp agency.
Um.
Not to be a bother,
but could I come with you?
I feel like I should be
looking for work myself.
Of course. Meet you
here tomorrow.
We can show you the way
to thank you for earlier.
Right?
Yeah!
Thanks a bunch.
[TOUYA laughs]
[DOG howls]
[TOUYA]
Whoa, that band's breaking up?
[sighs] I wonder if I'll always
care about news from home.
[TOUYA]
This stuff looks like gibberish.
I need to find a tutor
as soon as possible.
[ELZE] Hey, what do ya
think of this one?
Doesn't seem terribly difficult,
and it has a good reward.
Yeah, it looks promising.
Anything look good
on your side, Touya?
[gasps]
Maybe?
To be perfectly honest, I've
got no clue how to read this.
What? Are you trying to
tell us you're illiterate?
[LINZE]
Uh...
This job is to kill some
horned wolves out east.
And the reward'll be 18 copper.
That could be six copper
for each of us.
Yeah, you seem really strong
from what I've seen.
We'd be happy to form
a party with you.
[TOUYA]
Please.
[ELZE] Of course. Come on,
let's make it official.
Uh--
What's the matter?
I don't have any weapons.
Huh?
[CLERK 1B]
Thanks again!
Cool.
Is everyone ready
to hunt some wolves?
Yup.
Linze here likes to
fight from range,
but I prefer close combat.
Judging from your weapon,
I guess you'll fight with me.
Uh. Sure.
[LINZE]
Say.
That's an Eashen
sword, isn't it?
[TOUYA]
Mm-- Mm-hm.
[ELZE] It's a nice one.
Try not to lose it.
Your guild card either.
It's a serious pain
to get those replaced.
[yells]
[TOUYA grunts]
Hail of Red Stones.
Come forth: Fire of Ignis!
Nice one. So you're
a magic user?
[LINZE]
Mm-hm.
Not bad for our first job.
We were only hired to
kill five horned wolves.
Maybe we'll get bonus
points for the sixth.
[ELZE laughing]
[GUILD CLERK 1A]
All right.
I've confirmed the receipt
of five wolf horns.
Well done, you three.
Uh, what about that horn?
[TOUYA]
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'm keeping it as a memento
of our first mission.
Good idea.
All right, present
your guild cards,
and I'll update your records.
[ALL gasp]
[GUILD CLERK 1A] And the thing
you've been waiting for.
Your reward!
Eighteen copper coins.
Your first mission
is now complete.
We thank you for your service.
[ELZE]
I'm glad we partnered up, Touya.
That job would've
been a lot more
difficult without you.
I think the three of us
make a pretty good party.
There aren't many guys
who can keep up
with sis that easy.
You were quite impressive.
Nah. I was shaking with
nerves the whole time.
Those wolves were
even more ferocious
than I thought they'd be.
By the way, uh.
I have a favor to ask you two.
What is it?
[TOUYA] Well, do you
think you could teach me
how to read and write?
It's a rather inconvenient
skill not to have.
Especially when you can't tell
what job you're taking.
Well, if you wanna learn,
then Linze's the one
to have teach you.
She reads for fun sometimes.
It's a genius thing.
What? That's not true,
I'm not that smart.
But I am willing to try.
That'd be great.
Thanks a million.
And, uh.
While I'm at it,
guess I might as well ask.
Would you mind teaching
me magic as well?
I'd really like to
take a crack at it.
[BOTH]
Huh?
That's a difficult
question to answer.
Do you have an aptitude?
Aptitude?
[LINZE] The type of magic
someone can use is dictated
by the aptitudes that
they're born with.
Those who are born without
any aptitudes can't use magic,
no matter how hard they try.
Interesting.
I mean, I've never done
anything magical before.
But I recently talked
to someone who seemed
very confident that I'd be able
to use magic sometime soon.
And who might that be?
Uh...
Someone old and strong.
[TOUYA clears throat]
So, uh,
what would I need
to do to figure out
what my aptitudes might be?
[LINZE]
These are called spell stones.
They're used to store, release,
and amplify magical energy.
How to do this...
I guess water would be
the easiest to demonstrate.
Come forth, Water.
[TOUYA]
Oh!
Now this is what you
would call active magic.
Watch.
I make a command, channel
energy into the stone,
and it creates this
water in response.
And, by the way...
Come forth, Water.
If you don't have an
aptitude for water magic,
then frankly, you might as well
be talking to a regular pebble.
Wait, so you can't use it
even though your twin can?
It's not something I'm proud of,
so don't be so direct.
On the other hand, Elze can
use fortification magic,
but I never could.
It's not that either one
of us is more magical.
It's just that we have
different aptitudes.
Which is probably a big part of
why we work so well together.
Everyone alive
possesses magical energy.
But aptitudes are what allow us
to channel that
energy into spells.
So if I try to make
water like you did,
we'll know if I
have that aptitude?
[LINZE]
That's right.
You just need to hold the
spell stone in your hand,
focus your mind, and say
"Come forth, Water."
Come forth, Water.
[yelps]
[BOTH]
Uh...
And you had a few more stones?
Yeah, seven total, but--
[ELZE] Maybe we should
go outside first.
[ALL screaming]
Come forth, Fire.
[gasps]
[LINZE gasps]
Come forth, Earth.
Uh...
[BOTH gasp]
[TOUYA]
Come forth, Wind!
Come forth, Light!
Come forth, Dark!
What? Something wrong?
What the heck are you?
This is the first
we've heard of anyone
who can use all six elements.
I have aptitudes
for three of them,
and that's generally
considered pretty rare.
But you can use them all.
That's incredible.
[TOUYA]
Huh? What's that last stone for?
The seventh stone is used
to channel Null magic.
Null magic is unique,
so there isn't any single
incantation for it.
Huh. So then how
do you activate it?
That depends on
whose magic it is
and what it's doing.
Elze just has to say the
word "Boost" to use hers.
I know of a similar
strength enhancing spell
called Power Rise.
There're also spells like Gate,
which lets the user teleport.
That one's extra rare.
Wow.
I can't even start on how
useful that spell would be.
[ELZE]
I'd prefer my boost any day.
Thanks to that single spell,
every man who's ever
underestimated me
because I'm "just"
a girl has paid for it.
It explains why you're so tough.
That is crazy useful.
No doubt.
[TOUYA] So how do you
figure out what kind of
Null magic you can use?
Do you just try everything?
At some point, the name of
the spell just comes to you.
Yeah, that's right.
Null magic is also
known as personal magic
because it's very rare for
any two people to be able
to use the same spell.
So even if I can use Null magic,
I won't be able to
tell for a good while.
[LINZE]
No.
We can figure out if you
have the aptitude at least.
Just pick up the stone
and try casting something.
Even if the spell
doesn't actually work,
the stone should show
a reaction to your power.
Like it'll glow,
or shudder a bit.
Why don't you try casting
that teleport spell?
Just say the word "Gate"
Yeah. Sounds good to me.
Gate!
[LINZE gasps]
[ELZE]
No way.
Did it work?
Looks like it.
Awesome.
It's the forest where
we fought those wolves.
Specifically, the Gate spell
will allow the caster
to travel to places
they've been before.
Wonder why it took us here.
I guess this place was on
your mind when you cast it.
[LINZE, ELZE giggling]
[ELZE sighs]
I still can't believe
that you can use every element.
That's a little
more than unusual.
And with Null magic,
you're like the most
versatile magic user ever.
Wow, Touya. You're amazing.
[TOUYA] I can only do this stuff
because God felt bad for me.
It's kinda weird
getting praised for it.
[MICAH] Hey! Sorry to
interrupt your fun,
but do you have
a second to spare?
[ELZE]
Hey, Micah. What's goin' on?
My friend Aer here
needs some advice.
She's an employee at that café
down the street called "Parent."
I'm hoping to expand
the menu and thought
that adventurers
such as yourselves
might have some ideas.
[MICAH] Or maybe you
tasted something exotic
in your travels that
she could try and steal.
Cool foods? Huh.
Not really.
Nothing comes to mind
at the moment.
What's the food like
in Eashen, Touya?
Anything that'd be
good for a café?
If you had any suggestions,
I'd love to hear them.
I dunno, what kinda food
were you looking for?
Well, we're best
known for serving
a lot of sweets and the like.
Nothing too heavy.
I'd love to come up
with a dessert
that isn't just another cake.
I'm sure I've had
some weird desserts.
All I can come up with
are crepes and ice cream.
Hold on. Frozen cream?
Well, it's not totally frozen.
You serve it kinda soft.
How strange.
[TOUYA] I guess ice cream
isn't a thing here.
[LINZE]
Uh... What's that?
Uh.
It's a magical item that
helps me learn things.
Sorry for the rude request,
but I'd be grateful
if you didn't ask me
too much about it.
'Scuse me.
Could you bring out
a piece of paper
and write down what
I'm about to say?
Sure!
[TOUYA giggles]
So tasty!
[TOUYA]
Three eggs.
Two hundred milliliters of
heavy cream. And between...
[TOUYA] Food ingredients
are the same here, good.
Oh, right.
Hey, Linze, can you
make ice with magic?
Yeah. No problem.
Ice is just another
type of water.
Sweet!
[ELZE]
What do we do next? This is fun!
Delicious!
Incredible. It melts
in your mouth.
So tasty.
I've never had anything like it.
It's a pretty popular
treat in my country.
Think you might want
it for your café?
Yes, thank you for sharing it.
A treat like this could
make our café famous!
I'll have to try
making it again.
I should learn the recipe, too.
Between this and
that device of yours,
you keep getting weirder.
I'm curious about it, too.
It's a secret.
But, I'm glad I got to use it
to repay you a little bit.
Repay us? For what?
[TOUYA] For teaching me
how to use magic.
Thanks, you two.