[LYON] They defeated
a dragon on their own,
and now they're using
healing magic
on all the wounded civilians.
I am beginning to question
their need for an escort.
What's more, they donated
the dragon's usable parts
for the village's recovery.
A single pouch of that thing's
scales could fetch ten gold.
[sighs] They are mighty
and magnanimous.
It's beyond impressive.
[GAREN]
Yeah.
Just who are those people?
[LYON]
Who knows?
I certainly don't.
My name is Solum.
I'm the village elder here.
I wanted to thank you
for saving my people
from that dragon attack.
And for providing us with the
means to rebuild our village.
We shall remember your deeds.
Your words are kind, but...
...we just tried
to do what's right.
What's this?
[SOLUM] There are few
materials in this world
as light and durable as
the fang of a dragon.
Then... you keep it.
I'm told that you damaged
your sword in our defense.
Take this fang to
a master smith,
and he can forge you
a fine new weapon.
Or else, you can sell it and
purchase one with the proceeds.
That's a good idea, sir.
Thanks for suggesting it.
[TOUYA]
It really is light.
[SOLUM] Also, I'd like
to return this to you.
It was found in one
of the dragon's eyes.
I presume it's yours.
[TOUYA]
I wonder...
[TOUYA] Kohaku. Did you sense
whoever threw this knife?
[KOHAKU]
Yes.
In fact, I think I sensed two
people outside of our group
hiding in the trees.
At the time, I assumed
they were villagers.
So this is it.
Berge, The royal
capital of Mismede.
Your Majesty.
I, Olga Strand,
have completed my work
in the kingdom of Belfast.
You have done well.
As have you, Garen.
And you, Knight of Belfast.
I thank you both for
escorting Lady Strand home.
[LYON, GAREN]
Your Grace.
Envoys of Belfast, I'm pleased
to welcome you to Mismede.
I hear that a dragon
attacked Eld village,
and that you defeated it.
Tell me, is this true?
Yes. That's right, Your Majesty.
These four dispatched the dragon
that attacked your village
and can confirm
that it acted alone.
And who are you?
[YUMINA] My apologies for
the delayed introduction,
Your Grace. It's an honor
and a pleasure to meet you.
I am Princess Yumina
Arina Bellfast.
The daughter of King
Tristwyn Urnes Belfast.
Heavens!
And what brings the Princess
of Belfast to my halls?
Please, consider my
presence a sign of
Belfast's earnest hope
for this alliance.
My father penned this
letter in his own hand.
Read it at your pleasure,
Your Grace.
Interesting.
I shall think on the matter,
and respond in the near future.
Until then, please rest.
Enjoy my palace.
A dragon slayer in my halls.
Ha, ha, ha! My blood's
not roiled so in ages!
How 'bout it, young Touya?
Would you care to spar?
[JAMUKHA grunting]
[TOUYA]
Oh, my, what big arms you have.
[JAMUKHA grunting]
[GRATZ]
Sir Touya.
His majesty has
long felt compelled
to fight any strong
warrior he meets.
Frankly, we're all
quite troubled by it.
[TOUYA]
Oh, yeah?
So don't go holding back.
Give him a good sound thrashing.
Do it for all of
us who love him!
[TOUYA] That seems a
little counterintuitive,
but I am in another country.
[JUDGE 7A]
Here are the rules:
the match will end whenever
a combatant admits defeat,
or is put into a position
to receive a fatal wound.
Use of magic is permitted,
provided that it's not
offensive magic which
directly harms a combatant.
Fighters. At the ready.
I think we are.
Give it all you've got, boy.
Think of this as a real battle.
Use any and all means
available to beat me.
Yeah, okay.
Very well. Begin!
[TOUYA]
Slip!
[JAMUKHA screams]
Uh?!
[TOUYA]
Well. Guess that's the match.
What the hell did you just do?!
Hey! Come back.
That's one of my
Null magic spells.
It's called Slip.
He did say it was cool to use
non-damaging spells, right?
[JAMUKHA]
Yeah. Except that one!
A spell like that doesn't
even let a match happen!
Let's go one more time!
Only that Slip spell
is off limits.
No forcing me to trip
this time, ya hear me?
[TOUYA]
Loud and clear.
Begin!
King Jamukha's stronger.
Without magic,
he has the upper hand.
Cast something, Touya.
Come Forth Sand.
Obstructing Dust--
Too slow!
Multiple!
Made the king back
off with a bluff.
Clever.
I would expect no
less from Touya.
Now, Boost!
Accel!
[TOUYA grunts]
You managed to dodge that.
Well done.
Consider me impressed.
So quick!
I could barely see a blur.
It must be his Null magic.
[TOUYA]
That ability ya just used.
I'm guessing it's
your Null magic?
That it is.
You can see why I enjoy a
good scrap now and then.
I almost thought
you'd teleported.
[JAMUKHA]
I've yet to fight a man
who could match my
Accel's speed.
But it burns through
my mana fast, too,
so I prefer to use
it in short bursts.
[TOUYA]
I see.
That's an impressive spell.
I know.
So, thank you.
I'm excited to start using it.
Accel!
[gasps]
Did you...? Impossible!
This spell's surprisingly
difficult to control.
Still, I doubt I'll miss again.
Accel!
Accel.
[ELZE]
Well, this fight took a turn.
[YAE]
I can't see a thing.
You've matched me in speed.
But how will you
match my raw power?
Good question.
Not sure I have an answer,
but here goes.
Accel and Boost!
[JAMUKHA]
Hm? Accel!
[swords clanging]
[JAMUKHA]
Uh...
Looks like Checkmate.
I can't say I understand
what that phrase means.
But, I do concede defeat!
The winner is Mochizuki Touya!
I can't believe he used
two Null magics at once.
Uh?
[JAMUKHA]
I never thought I'd meet someone
who could beat my speed.
Honestly, I think I'd gotten
a little full of myself.
I'll have to take
a lesson from this.
Uh. Yeah? [laughs]
[TOUYA]
And this.
[LYON]
Sir Touya.
Nice outfit. It suits you well.
Thanks.
By the way,
you haven't seen Lady Olga
around, have you?
Not yet, but I just got here.
[PARTYGOERS chattering]
[TOUYA]
He is so into her.
[JAMUKHA]
Welcome, Touya!
You wear our clothes well.
I could almost mistake you
for a nobleman of Mismede.
Yeah? Ya really think so?
[YUMINA] That outfit really
does look nice on you.
So dashing.
Yeah.
That is a good look for you.
[LINZE]
It brings out a different side
of your natural charm.
Your normal outfit is
fine, but this wins!
Yeah, well, all of you
look really cute, too.
Hey! Why don't I take a picture?
[MEN groan]
What did you do?
Uh? Oh, sorry about that.
This is another one of
my Null magic spells.
It allows me to record
an image of any scene
so I can see it later.
Indeed.
It's like you made
an instant painting.
Can you take it out
of that device?
Why, yes I can.
Do you have a canvas or a
piece of paper I could use?
Drawing.
[JAMUKHA]
My word!
That's simply amazing!
Tell me, Touya, do you think
you could paint me as well?
Sure, no problem.
[TOUYA]
Cute, cute, cute, and buff.
[sighs]
Whew. I am beat.
[squeaking]
[TOUYA]
Uh, me?
What's this?
You've brought a strange
guest with you, Paula.
Good evening. Might I
inquire as to your name?
Oh. Yeah, my name's Touya.
Or Mochizuki Touya.
I just go by Touya.
--That will do.
--[door creaks]
So, you're the rumored
dragon slayer.
[TOUYA]
Did that just close itself?
Uh, yeah, that was me.
And you?
Oh, right. Please forgive me.
I'm Leen, an elder
of the fairy folk.
And here,
we have my friend Paula.
Despite appearances, I'm
actually far older than you.
You're older than me?
'Kay, by how much?
Well, it's difficult to say.
Lost track a few centuries in,
but I've seen at least six.
[TOUYA]
Six hundred?!
Older, but it's
a pain to recall,
so let's just go with 612.
[TOUYA]
U-Uh... Uh.
By the way, is your friend here
a summoned beast, or what?
Of course not.
Paula's a teddy bear.
She's filled with bits of fluff.
Must say, I'm surprised
that the sutured limbs
and cute squeaky sounds
didn't give her away.
[TOUYA]
Teddy's don't move.
[LEEN] Now, that's due to
my Null magic, Program.
It allows me to issue
situational commands
to inanimate objects.
For instance...
Initiate Program.
Movement.
Forward, on condition.
Whenever you are sat upon.
End Program.
[grunts]
I forgot to specify a distance.
But you understand.
If I give an object a command,
then it will do as instructed.
Okay, but, like, what if you
commanded Paula to fly?
Would that make her able to?
The spell isn't quite
powerful enough
to allow that level of freedom.
And the object's form matters.
Paula can do far
more than a chair.
But if I wanted to
make a toy fly,
I'd be better off
programming a model bird.
[TOUYA] Hm... Would you mind
if I tried it out a bit?
Huh?!
Initiate Program.
Movement.
Backwards for two meters.
On condition: Whenever
you are sat upon.
End Program.
[gasps, laughing]
Excuse me. How did
you just do that?
[TOUYA]
Use your spell?
I said the words.
That is a truly spectacular
talent you have.
Aside from Null magic,
which elements can you use?
[TOUYA]
All of them, believe it or not.
Sure, makes sense to me.
You know what, fine.
Let's do it. You will
be my new apprentice.
[TOUYA]
Huh?
[LEEN laughs]
Such a reaction.
Relax. I'll not turn you into
a stuffed bear for refusing.
That said, if you should
change your mind--
Sorry, ma'am!
[TOUYA]
I am so out of here!
[LEEN]
Gone, but not forgotten...
Hey, Master.
Are you as tired as
you look right now?
[TOUYA]
Yeah, I'm beat.
A lot happened today.
Wait a second!
What if I used
Program to make it?
[KOHAKU]
Hm?
[YUMINA]
Touya! Are you heading out?
Yeah, what's up?
We just finished
eating breakfast,
so we were thinking about taking
a stroll through the garden.
I'm glad you're getting along.
Seen Yae or Elze?
They're both at a joint
training session
with some of Mismede's soldiers
in the arena right now.
[TOUYA]
Yeah. That sounds like them.
Anyway, what were
you planning for the day?
Just a bit of light shopping.
[YUMINA]
You would look so cute in this!
That's not what I had in mind.
[KOHAKU]
This is so much fun.
[LINZE]
Come forth, Water.
Blade both Cold and Clear.
Aqua Cutter!
Will those pieces
be small enough?
Yeah. Thanks a bunch, Linze.
What are you planning
to make with them?
Something way better than
a sword, if all goes well.
Does that mean
you're inventing it?
[TOUYA]
Modeling.
Well, so far, so good.
Now let's see about bullets.
Modeling.
[TOUYA]
Enchant:
Aports.
Begin Programming.
Three step sequence.
Begin whenever
user says "Reload."
On this condition
expel empty cartridges
at high speed.
Then use Aports to take bullets
of the same type from
the user's person.
Then, place them
into the cylinder.
End Programming.
[LINZE, YUMINA groaning]
How'd I miss?
Oh. I bet it needs rifling.
Modeling.
[sighs]
Reload.
So, is it finished now?
Yeah. Think so.
This type of weapon's
called a gun.
It's like a better, smaller bow.
That sounds great!
Do you think you might
have time to make one
for me as well, Touya?
Yeah, I'd like one, too! Please.
[TOUYA]
Huh?
Okay. Uh.
I'll do an image search.
Take a look at these, and
pick out your favorite ones.
[YUMINA laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
Begin Programming.
Activate when user says
"Gun Mode" or "Blade Mode."
On the former condition,
use Modeling to transform
the blade from a dagger
to a longsword.
On the latter condition,
transform it back into a dagger.
End Programming.
Blade Mode, go!
Now, Gun Mode!
That's brilliant, Touya.
You can use that up
close or at range.
Well, after that fight
with King Jamukha,
I thought I should
prepare for situations
where I can't use all my spells.
You know what?
A weapon like that needs a name.
Yeah, I agree.
What about "Brunhild"?
The show ends when she sings.
That took a little longer
than I thought it would.
Please tell me that you're
as hungry as I am.
Wanna find somewhere
to grab a quick bite?
If you think there's time.
I've heard great things about
Mismede's traditional cuisine.
I have, too.
Apparently they're famous
for a dish called "currae."
I think it's served
at that restaurant.
Well, let's go.
[KOHAKU]
Master!
Someone's watching us.
I can sense them.
[TOUYA]
Okay. Think I'll say hello.
Do you know where they are?
[KOHAKU]
Look to the right.
They're up towards the top
of the highest building.
[TOUYA]
You two go on ahead.
I'll join you in a sec.
What?
You'll meet us there?
Yup. You can order for me, 'kay?
[TOUYA]
You protect them, Kohaku.
[KOHAKU]
Good hunting.
Accel!
Hi.
So, uh.
You can understand me, right?
Mind telling me who you are?
[TOUYA grunting]
Accel and Boost!
[footsteps]
[STRANGERS gasp]
Sorry about that, but they're
just rubber bullets.
You should be fine.
So...
...we ready to talk yet?
I'd like to know why
you're watching us.
[sighs] Well, lemme make sure
you're unarmed, at least.
[STRANGER A gasps]
Uh!
That was unexpected.
Uh. Wait, Lapis?
[LAPIS]
We're with Espion.
A spy network that
answers directly
to his majesty, King Tristwyn.
You're working for the king?
Yes.
Our current mission is to ensure
the safety of Princess Yumina.
So you've been protecting Yumina
from the shadows
all this time, then.
[LAPIS]
Exactly.
Oh, that might explain it.
Is this your knife?
[LAPIS]
Yeah, that was Cecile.
As I guess you saw, she's
a master knife thrower.
That's nice of you,
but I wouldn't call
myself a master.
[TOUYA] So you've been tailing
us since we first left Belfast?
That's when our mission began.
[TOUYA] Wait, then was my
butler in on this as well?
Oh, definitely.
Fair enough.
So, where do we go from here?
[LAPIS]
Our mission's the same.
We'd like to continue guarding
the princess surreptitiously.
But, that can only happen
if you're willing to keep
this secret from her.
Would it be all that
bad if she found out?
It would.
It can't happen.
If she finds out that he sent
her secret bodyguards,
she'll be furious.
[LAPIS]
The truth can never get out.
[TOUYA]
Guess not.
What did I miss?
[YUMINA] Not much. You got
here right after the food.
We ordered you a
pork cutlet currae.
It looks good.
[LINZE] Apparently "currae"
is what they call
the sauce that's poured
over the food.
[TOUYA] So, this is
literally just curry.
[gasps]
Well, it certainly is flavorful.
I feel like I just
swallowed a flaming coal.
[LINZE whines]
Is something the matter, Touya?
I'm good. Just hungry.
[TOUYA]
Spicy!
Gate.
Welcome, King Belfast.
I'm glad you came.
It's an honor, King Mismede.
Thank you so much
for hosting me.
That boy you brought
to see me...
...Mochizuki Touya, was it?
[squeaks]
Charlotte's in Belfast.
Perhaps she knows
something about him.
As my apprentice,
she'll be obliged to help.