(Cicada's cry)
(Door opens)
Hey, Ritchan.
Hey there, Yui.
Ugh, so hot.
Huh? What's that
you looking at?
I found something interesting.
Here, check it out.
Wow, what's with
these pictures?
They were in a cardboard box
that Mio found earlier.
They're pictures of
a past Light Music Club.
Whoa, these are amazing!
They got that look
every band has,
no matter when in
history they played.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Say the word "band,"
and this used to be
the only image that
popped into my head.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
Maybe we can just try
changing this a little bit.
Hmm...
Ow!
What happened?
I scraped the skin
off my finger.
Whoa, that looks painful.
You, too, Mio!
Look at my finger!
Hm?
(Repeating)
I'm not looking,
I'm not listening...
Hehehe...
Ah, my hands!
I've been practicing
drums too much.
The blisters on
my hand broke open!
(Screams)
Hahaha...
Take a look!
It's gross!
(Mio crying)
Disgusting! Boo!
Check it out!
Ritchan, do we have any
adhesive bandages here?
In your face!
It's near you!
(Door opens)
[Ms. Yamanaka]
Don't mind me.
I need to borrow these music
stands for a while. Oh?
(Ritsu scaring Mio)
(Mio crying)
Hehe...
*
[Teacher]
Would the two of you mind
carrying these notebooks for me?
Thank you very much
for all your help.
[Yui]
Ow!
Huh?
Ow...
The antiseptic's
really stinging!
I know. All right, hold your
finger still just like that.
What a tidy desk...
Done. There, that should do it.
Thanks for your help,
Ms. Yamanaka.
Let's see the others.
Um...
Well, you have a ways to go.
The way your skin is right now,
it's going to peel off soon.
Huh?!
Your skin will get tougher
each time this happens,
and you'll become a better
player in the process.
It's a guitarist's
rite of passage.
Oh, it is?
Hey, wait a second!
Did you used to play guitar,
Ms. Yamanaka?
Not me, but I have
some friends who did.
Hmm...
Oh, very good work today.
You, too.
See you later.
U-uh, yes.
Hey, would you like some tea?
[Teacher]
Yeah, thanks.
What a nice teacher...
Hm?
Mugi-chan!
Ah!
Mugi-chan, is
something the matter?
No, I was just thinking
how pretty she was.
Oh, you mean
Ms. Yamanaka?
By the way,
where have you been?
Ah, well you see, I was
asked by Mio to go find out
if the Light Music Club
could use the stage
when we play at
the school festival.
But, I'm afraid they
turned our request down
because they said
we aren't recognized
as a legitimate club yet.
Oh, that's nice...
Hm?
Huh?
We're not recognized
as a legitimate club?!
No, apparently we are not.
I thought in order
to be official,
we just needed to have
four members.
Yeah, Yui.
That's what I thought, too.
(Sighs)
You know, I was thinking,
if we're not recognized
as an official club,
is it okay that we've been
hogging the Music Room
to ourselves?
Look, nobody's said anything
about it to us so far,
so I'm sure it's okay.
I think.
More importantly,
I'd better go and ask them
why we're not recognized.
Yes, you should.
Oh? Hey, what
happened to Mio?
Oh, if you're looking for Mio,
she's still huddled
in terror over there.
Would you come back here?!
Greetings, all!
I'm club president!
[Nodoka]
Oh, Yui?
Nodoka-chan?
Wow, Nodoka-chan,
what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I'm here because
I'm on the student council.
Oh! That's amazing!
That's my Nodoka-chan!
So you two are really
childhood friends?
Well, sorry,
but you don't seem
to be on the list...
Oh, no! You're kidding!
No, don't tell me...
Ritchan! Does this
raise any theories?
Yes, what this
appears to be...
is a sinister plot
by the student council
to drive weak clubs
into being disbanded!
(Gasps)
I know you're really
a pure-hearted person,
Nodoka-chan!
Please, snap out of it!
What are you
talking about?
Maybe you just
didn't submit
a club activities
application form?
Club activities application?
It's the first I've
heard of this form!
No, it's not!
Yes.
That was... back in spring.
I'm club president,
so I'll fill it out!
Are you sure, Ritsu?
[Mugi]
Excuse me, I brought a big
pound cake with me today.
Oooh... Let's dig in!
Ritsu, wait!
I know, I know, Mio!
I'll fill it out just as soon
as we finish eating!
I'll fill it out as soon
[Echoes]
...finish eating...
[Mio]
I knew it, this is
all your fault!
You and your
putting things off.
[Mugi]
Oh, dear. Mio, it's not like
she did it deliberately.
You're too soft
on her, Mugi!
Now, now, now ...
[Nodoka]
How to put this...
I think you're a perfect fit
for the Light Music Club, Yui.
(Mio and Ritsu still arguing)
Oh well, all right, Yui...
I'll see what I can do for you.
Eh?
Wow, you will?!
Name: Light Music Club...
Membership: four.
Who's your advisor?
Advisor?
You don't have one?
[Ritsu]
Sawako Yamanaka.
Our fair school's music teacher.
As a result of her beautiful
features and gentle demeanour,
she is popular with not only
the student body,
but also the school staff.
Plus, her skill
with instruments
and her singing voice
are remarkable.
What?
She is popular enough
to have her own fan club.
What have you
going on about?
Uh, hello, girls...
Teacher!
What is it?
Please agree to be the
Light Music Club's advisor!
Oh, I see. You don't
have an advisor yet...
Ms. Yamanaka, you're the only
teacher that we can turn to.
Oh, please, do it.
I'm so sorry.
I wish that I could be
your advisor, I really do,
but I'm already the
school band's advisor,
so there's no way
I could handle another.
You're kidding...
I'm really am
sorry about this.
She's so desirable,
that she has been
courted by countless men.
Uh, look, flattery isn't
going to change anything!
We won't take up
any of your time!
That's right! Because we always
practice all on our own!
Just write your name here and
give it your official stamp!
Simple, huh?
J-just a sec!
Stare...
Ms. Yamanaka, you graduated
from here, didn't you?
Well, yes...
We were looking through
an old Light Music Club
photo album earlier.
Eh?!
Huh? Hm...
Is something the
matter with you?
Um, so, where is
that album right now?
Uh, well, it's in
our club room.
I see.
Ms. Yamanaka?
Oh!
I would never have suspected
that the last copy
was being kept right here
in the school.
That book contains a
chapter of my bloody past
that must never
come to light.
A spawn of the devil
that must never be awakened!
A forbidden book
never to be seen!
A locked doorway
that must never be opened!
It's...
It's...!
(Panting)
At last, it's over.
Huh?!
[Ritsu]
I knew it!
That was you,
Ms. Yamanaka!
You were this girl,
weren't you?
(Gasp)
Well played,
you found me out.
It's true, I was once a
Light Music Club member!
I never suspected!
Does that mean that
this is you?
I've been waiting for you
people to arrive!
NOW DIE!
Stop it! I'm so ashamed!
(Mio crying)
I'm not listening,
I'm not listening...
You're still dragging
out that shtick?
You were playing
guitar, too?
Hey, right!
Play something!
Huh?!
Don't be shy!
No, I can't! I can't!
Oh, the characteristic
weight of a Les Paul's
mahogany and maple...
This dulcet tone,
full of sweetly
distorted harmonics
from its humbucker pickup...
Ms. Yamanaka?
(Evil laugh)
What the hell...
[Girls]
Her expression's changed!
She's shredding!
She's tapping!
She's Hendrix-ing!
Oh, no! My poor little guitar!
You punks, you've been using the
Music Room like it was yours!
Ah! We're so sorry!
And the first place you four-
Huh?!
Did you all see that?
Uh-huh...
Ugh!
I swore to myself
I'd put on a ladylike front
when I became a teacher...
Yeah, but Ms.-
All of this began
eight long years ago...
Why is she narrating
all of a sudden?!
I was...
*
K-ON!
[Yamanaka]
I was... in love.
I love you!
I'm sorry.
But I like girls with
more of a wild streak in them.
And so I made up my mind.
That I would become
the girl of his dreams.
(Band plays)
(Crowd cheering)
I would be wilder.
Wilder! Wilder!
Ever wilder!
More! More! More!
Wilder! Wilder! Wilder!
I'll go out with
you if you want.
Sawako...
You took it
too far.
I guess that's how it
always ends, huh?
You okay?
Please, spare me
your words of comfort...
Teacher, please,
lift up your eyes.
Oh, Ritchan!
If you don't want
this getting out,
you will be our
club advisor.
Ritchan, you're
so resolute!
Huh?
Oh...
Mugi-chan?
What's wrong?
I dunno, it's Mugi-chan...
Mugi!
Oh! Ah!
Are you feeling okay?
You looked like you were
kind of spacing out.
Oh... Uh...
Hm?
(Band playing)
And that's a brand new original
piece we've been working on.
Hmm...
As our advisor,
what's your opinion?
I have some concerns,
such as the intro and outro,
and the way your rhythm section
is all over the place,
and total lack of
any cohesive hook.
But, don't you guys
have a singer?
Ah!
Wait, you haven't written any
lyrics yet, either, have you?
Well, I guess we just...
You've got a lot of guts,
thinking you could perform
at the school festival
in this state...
We're sorry, ma'am.
What have you been
doing every time
you've been hogging
the music room?!
It's not a place to
sit around and sip tea!
Uh...
We made her mad!
For one thing!
Teacher!
(Growl)
W-would you care for
some yummy cake?
Wah!
Yes, I would!
She would?!
Let's see...
We should have started
with the lyrics first.
(Phone buzzes)
Mugi?
[Mugi]
Now that Ms. Yamanaka
has become our advisor,
my heart is pounding
for some reason.
Good luck with the lyrics.
"My heart is pounding"?
Nah, no way...
They're done?!
Yeah... All done.
Show us, show us!
Already?!
Yes, already!
I would love to see them, too.
B-but I'm embarrassed
to show them to you...
Oh, Mio-chan,
no one is gonna laugh.
[Ritsu]
Yeah, yeah!
[Mio]
But I... Wait a minute!
[Ritsu]
We can't wait!
If you brought them,
that means you're ready
to show them to us, right?!
[Mugi]
Mio, come on, please!
You can give me a little peek!
Just one little peek!
[Ritsu]
No fair! If anybody's
going to see them,
I'm gonna be first!
Why, you?
Why? Because I'm
club president, that's why!
Wha...? Then I'm
Mio-chan's soulmate!
So I get to see them first.
So, there!
[Mugi]
Well then, I'm Mio-chan's
soulmate number two!
And I get to see them next.
[Ritsu]
You got a lot of gall!
I am the place that Mio's
soul calls home, right?!
[Mio]
Since when?
[Yui]
Oh, I wonder how my granny
out in the country is doing?
[Ritsu]
That's got nothing
to do with this.
[Mio]
Did I send mine a
New Year's card last year?
[Ritsu]
Don't change the subject!
Let's see the damn thing!
Ah!
Oh, let me see?
I'm all itchy!
I want to tear this up!
[Mio]
I think that, considering
how fast I did it,
it turned out pretty well...
Huh?
Do you really think
that it's no good?
"No good" might be a
little strong...
Yeah, more like it
doesn't quite fit
the image that we're
trying to create.
C'mon, Yui, you haven't
said anything.
What do you think?
It was awesome...
Seriously?!
I love these lyrics.
I think they're
just wonderful!
Y-you mean it?
Uh...
Hey, What do you think
about the lyrics, Mugi?
She's totally
enchanted!
Mugi, you aren't seriously
telling me that you like them?
I do.
Uh, you think
these lyrics work?
I do.
Seriously?
Really.
For real?
Yes, bring it on.
Uh... S-Sawako!
"Sawako"?
You think that these lyrics
are unworkable, right?
Why, yes!
I suppose they're not.
See, I'm right?
Come on, you three,
let's rethink
our approach, okay?
Let's take a deep breath and...
Wait a minute...
Maybe I can give my
image a boost by saying
I like this
perky, sappy crap.
You're young
at heart, Ms. Yamanaka!
That's our Ms. Yamanaka!
It's Ms. Yamanaka
or no one!
Ya-ma-na-ka! Woo! Ya-ma-na-ka!
Woo! Ya-ma-na-ka! Woo!
You know, now that
I think about it,
I guess I really like
those lyrics, too!
Say what?!
Well, I suppose we're going
with these lyrics, then.
Yay!
Isn't this wonderful, Mio-chan?
Um, yeah...
That means we'll be going
with Mio on vocals.
Huh?
N-no, I couldn't!
Why not?
Well, I...
because I...
Because I can't sing such
embarrassing lyrics, that's why!
Hey, you wrote 'em, lady!
This is gonna be a problem...
Well, I guess that
leaves us with...
Mugi, want to try?
I would, but I already
have my hands full
just managing the keyboard.
Ah, okay, then...
I guess not...
(Yui clears throat)
Ha... Ahh...
Yui, you wanna try?
Wha.. You asking me?!
Well, but I'm not really
a good singer, you know,
so I don't know if I'd be
the best choice for us.
I'm not sure if I should
even try to do it...
Never mind, then.
I'm sorry, I lied!
I'll sing! I want to sing!
You gotta let me try it!
Okay then,
sing something.
Roger!
(Singing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
[Ritsu]
Hold it, hold it!
You'll have to sing while
you're playing guitar!
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I totally forgot.
Oh, geez...
Okay...
(Playing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
This time she's forgetting
to sing while she plays!
(Crying)
I can't sing and play guitar
at the same time! I can't!
I guess I have no choice.
I'll have to give you
special training.
Really!
First thing I'm gonna show you
is how to Hendrix...
Oh, that's all right.
Huh?
(Swooning)
Okay, do your best and
try to keep up with me!
Roger!
Ritsu...
What is it?
You don't think that Mugi
has a thing for
Ms. Yamanaka, do you?
Come again?
Want I'm trying to ask is,
think she's got
a crush on her?
What! Seriously?
Mugi! I was wondering,
do you like Ms. Yamanaka?
Hey, Ritsu!
You moron!
Huh?
(Nervous laugh)
Oh, no, I was just...
I was thinking how nice it is
when it's just girls
hanging out.
What? No way...
Oh, well, good for you.
Wait, so you're
okay with it?
If the people involved
are happy,
that's all that
really matters, right?
Well, um...
Uh... What are we
talking about here?
[Nodoka]
All right then, Yui will
be providing the vocals,
and the set list will be
"Fuwa Fuwa Time."
Okay, I'll get in touch
with you again
once your time slot
has been assigned.
Thank goodness and thank you
for coming in person to tell us.
It's all part of a student
council member's duties.
But are you really sure you want
to go with Yui on the vocals?
She's been getting intensive
lessons from Ms. Yamanaka
after school since last week.
We think that she'll have her
whipped into shape in time.
Ah!
[Ms. Yamanaka]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
She's perfect.
(Gasps)
Now, Yui-girl, show 'em
what you've got!
Oh!
She's awesome!
She's a lot better!
Her face is
full of confidence!
(Husky singing)
Ah!
Wha...?
I made her practice too much!
I threw my voice out!
Knock off the cutesy act!
You're kidding...
Who will do the vocals, then?
All changes must be in
by end of day.
What, you're not serious?
Hm... in that case...
Hm?
Huh?!
You're right, Mio is
the only other person
who knows the lyrics.
Yeah, 'cause she's the one
who came up with them.
[Mugi]
You can do it, Mio!
[Yui]
Do it for Husky-voice Yui!
Ah!
Ugh!
Whoa, Mio!
Mio, what's the matter?
Pull yourself together!
There's only three days
'til we go on!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
Ritsu, don't you think we
should get some practice in
before we go on?
Sorry, but I can't
right now!
Well, you still have a fair
amount of time until then.
Don't you want to use
the time to practice?
She's right! Let's practice!
Pretend that didn't happen.
That didn't happen.
Today's the day of
the performance!
Let's try and practice
as much as we can!
Let's practice!
We're gonna practice, huh?
*