Wow, you sure have thick
eyebrows, Mugi-chan!
Yeah. But they're actually...
...takuan pickles!
Ah!
Whoa! They're delicious!
What's delicious?
Yum...
Takuan...
[Ui]
The priest?
Looks like your fever's
still really high.
Oh, that's right.
I have a bad cold.
(sneeze)
Oh, Ui!
Here. Blow.
Thanks a lot, Ui...
I'll let the school know
that you're sick.
I'm sorry...
You better hurry up,
you're gonna be late.
Oh, there's ice cream
and mandarin orange jelly
in the fridge.
Wow, you left me a feast!
Thanks a lot, Ui.
If you need anything,
call my cell.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
[Azusa]
So her fever still
hasn't come down...
[Ui]
No. She'll probably have to
stay home tomorrow, too.
There's only four days left...
I'd gladly trade places
with her if I could.
By getting her cold
to move to me.
How would you move
her cold to you?
I dunno...
Oral transmission?
She's daring...
Greetings!
Don't spook the underclassmen!
She is?
No excuse!
Getting sick at
a time like this
just shows her
lack of dedication!
You're the one who
gave it to her!
Oh, I did?
Yes, you did! I mean
look at the timing of it!
Um, she probably caught it
the other day...
I want you to pick your
stage outfits from these!
Huh?! You're forcing us to?!
[Mio]
When did she have time
to make all these?
Pick anything you like!
How about this waitress
outfit, isn't it cute?
What can I get for you today?
[Mio]
No way!
That's even worse!
That's... not bad, actually.
Ms. Yamanaka, I think I'm
really starting to enjoy this.
Isn't it fun?
Planet Earth calling!
[Yui]
Guys, look at this!
Hey, how about
we all wear these?
These are so cute!
Oh, they are!
They look easy to move in, too!
I guess these aren't so bad.
C'mon, these are great!
Let's wear these!
Let's wear these...
[Ui]
Sis was crazy about her yukata.
So much so, that she
wore hers all day long,
and that might be the reason
she caught a bad cold.
What is she, two?
Sounds like
Yui-senpai, all right.
Yeah, well, I gotta admit,
that at the time, I was thinking
that those outfits were
pretty awesome, too.
You know, when you think
about them rationally,
they're actually
kind of embarrassing.
You agree, Mio?
Azusa.
Would you mind practicing
all the lead guitar parts
starting today?
Uh?
You think that Yui might not
get better in time?
But I...
Look, it's just so we can be
prepared for the worst.
See you after school.
Later.
I'm sorry...
Seconds, please...
I'm home.
Oh, poor Sis...
Yum!
[Band playing]
Azusa, can you handle it?
Yes, I think so.
All right then,
let's run through it
one more time from the top.
Sure.
Hey there!
Ah! You're here!
Senpai!
Are you over your cold?
Huh? My cold?
(coughing)
That's awfully forced...
Well, I guess that means
you're feeling fine, then.
If you were feeling better,
then you should've come into
school in the morning!
All of us were pretty
worried about you!
Huh? Oh, that! Um... Right!
I suddenly felt better after
classes had already ended!
You just wanted to skip school.
That's not important,
let's just start practicing!
Right?
Yeah, sure, why not.
(band playing)
How's that?
Huh?
What do you think?
I'm not certain, but...
Maybe it was just a fluke.
Maybe you're right.
Let's try it one more time.
I agree.
(band playing)
Yui.
Yes?
Our sound was way too tight!
It's never ever felt
like that before!
All of the sudden your
playing way too on the beat.
What happened?
N-not a thing!
The moon's turned to blood...
Ah!
So, what's the problem?
If our sound is tight,
then that's a good thing!
If you ask me, that's the
best we've ever played.
Yeah, yeah! I think we
should listen to Azusa!
Huh?
Guess you're right.
I suppose we were just
thrown for a loop.
Miss Ritsu, you and Miss Tsumugi
just worry too much.
Huh?
Miss Ritsu?
Miss Tsumugi?
Uh...
It's time to drop
the masquerade... Ui-chan.
When did you...?! Wha...?
Ui-chan?!
You may be able to fool others,
but you can't fool me.
Your boobs are bigger
than Yui-chan's!
Uh. I-I haven't the slightest
idea what you're talking about!
Okay, call me by
my nickname, then.
A-Azusa #2!
An imposter!
I'm so sorry.
[Mio]
Well, I have to admit,
you were a dead ringer for Yui.
I had no idea.
I didn't know that you
could play guitar, Ui-chan.
I can't. But Sis let me
hold it a few times.
Oh, I see.
So that's how you play it!
Yeah, it's written
right here!
[All]
Why am I not surprised?
You know, we might be better off
if Yui just stayed home
and we let Ui play.
Ritsu.
-I should apologize to you, too.
-Huh? Sure.
See, when I saw my sister
lying there in bed,
I couldn't just stand there
and do nothing.
(door opens)
Hey there...
-Serious deja vu!
-Senpai!
Sorry I made you guys
worry about me.
Are you feeling better?
I am! When I woke up
a little while ago,
I was feeling a lot
better than before!
I'd hoped to get
a little practice-
Gross!
Honest, I'm all better!
You liar.
I need a tissue, too.
Ah, Geeta!
So, that's where you've been!
C'mere! Whoa, you're heavy!
Oh, Sis!
Let me make chicken soup
with them next time.
Huh?
Hey, your fever hasn't
gone down at all!
I'm sorry...
I guess I won't make it.
Maybe you'd all be better off
playing without me.
Nonsense!
Azu-nyan, you take lead
guitar for me, okay?
No way.
Azusa...
I said no. If we all
can't play together,
I'd rather just
cancel the show!
Azusa, wait!
Hm...
Yui, don't come to the
club until the show.
-Huh?
-You're kicking me out?
No.
I'm ordering you to
stay home and rest
so you can completely
get over your cold.
And then we'll ALL
play the show together.
Don't you dare give up
until then. Got it?
Mio-chan...
And I want you to practice,
the lead parts too, Azusa.
Not just for when Yui's gone,
but for the future of our band.
Senpai...
For now, let's do
everything we can
to get ourselves
ready for the show.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
I'm gonna sleep a lot.
I'm gonna sleep
as much as I can!
I'm gonna get better
in time for the show!
K-ON!
[Mugi]
Yui still isn't here...
Call her cell?
She sent a message
saying that
she would be here
no matter what.
But it's already 12:30.
(nervous sigh)
[Ritsu]
Do you want to rehearse?
The versions without Yui's part.
Hm...
-I guess we have to.
-No!
Don't you see, we can't do that!
There's no point
in practicing
if Yui-senpai
isn't here with us!
Uh!
What's the matter?
I've pushed back your
set ten minutes,
but please be at the auditorium
at 1 PM as scheduled.
[Mio]
Understood.
I see that all club members
are present?
Uh...
"Light Music Club: All
participants present and ready."
Good.
Nodoka?
One time...
Oh no, buckets all full.
(struggles)
Hm?
Yui-chan?
We'll use this.
Is that really safe?
Ah!
[Mother]
Yui-chan, it's nice to
see you again..
(Yui giggles)
Huh?
(startled)
Eek!
What the heck?
She's been strange
all her life, hasn't she?
But what's the
point of that story?
That when Yui is
focused on something,
she loses sight of
everything else.
I'm sure that she'll
forget about her cold.
That's why I know she...
Huh?
'Sup, girls!
Way to ruin the moment!
More to the point,
where the heck have you
been all this time?
We're having a crisis here!
Well, I can assure you
that I haven't been spending
my time doing nothing.
I factored in the
temperature outside
and made a stylish cold weather
version of those yukata!
[All]
I wish you'd focus that
enthusiasm someplace else.
And so, without further ado!
Huh?
Excuse me for being late...
Yui!
You should have come to
the club room first!
Sorry about that.
Azu-nyan?
That was so mean!
Here we were, worried
about you, and you...
It was mean!
You'd better make amends.
Azusa was more worried
about you than any of us.
Huh? She was?
Azu-nyan!
What you did was terrible!
For one thing, when you
have a cold, you...
Glomp!
I didn't mean to worry you.
Sorry, Azu-nyan.
I'll give it
everything I've got.
Together with
all of you guys. Okay?
We'll make this
the best show ever.
Geez.
Okay, just this once.
Now, come on!
Let's kiss and make up!
Do you think that Azu-nyan
was really worried about me?
I guess...
All right, it's time girls.
Time to get going.
Yeah!
Wait a sec. Where's Geeta?
Huh?
I left him here, didn't I?
I think Ui-chan
took it home with her!
Sis? I'm gonna leave
your guitar right here.
Sure... Thanks a lot, Ui...
Oh my gosh, she did!
What do I do?!
I guess we have no choice...
Ms. Yamanaka?
Here. Use this one.
Oh...
Do you mind playing
a different guitar?
Uh...
Actually, I can't play
any guitar except Geeta!
There's a shock...
Oh!
(running)
Oh! Wow, it's packed already!
I'll just stand.
Hi, Ui-chan?
Huh?
There you are!
And now, get ready for
a performance by
"After-school Teatime"
of the Light Music Club.
(applause)
Oh no, where's Sis?
One, two, three!
(playing "Ballpoint Pen")
Found it!
I have to hurry!
Come to think of it,
I ran down this road
the day of the
entrance ceremony, too.
I was thinking, "I've gotta
do something!" as I ran.
And also "What am I gonna do?"
And "Is this really how
I'm gonna grow up?"
Listen up, me...
The me of that day,
you don't have to worry.
You'll find it soon enough.
You'll find something
that you can do.
Something you can
lose yourself in.
And a place that...
A place that...
A place that means more
than anything to you!
Big Sis!
Oh, Ui!
Peace!
Big Sis, you can do it!
Yeah!
(panting)
Ms. Yamanaka, thanks a lot!
All right ladies,
knock 'em dead.
Ms. Yamanaka, you're awesome!
I really am sorry, you guys.
Now that I think about it...
...I'm always causing
trouble for you...
...And it's always at
important times like this!
You should at least
tie your tie.
We all think you're
the greatest, Yui.
(applause)
You can do it, Yui!
Go get 'em, Yui!
Um, once again, we're
After-school Teatime.
I'm sorry to all of you,
I was so late today because
I left my guitar at home.
Sorry I forgot you, Geeta.
That's why?!
When we started the
Light Music Club we said,
that our slogan was going to
be "Budokan or bust!"
We worked after-school
jobs together
so I could buy Geeta.
We had tea in
the club room together
and talked about everything.
We had training camps at
Mugi-chan's summer homes,
and looked for a new student
who would join the club.
I can't really say that we
devoted ourselves
wholeheartedly to practicing,
but right now, for us standing
here on this stage,
this auditorium is our Budokan!
(cheers)
And we'll sing our hearts out
to the very end!
Fuwa Fuwa Time, guys!
(playing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
One more time!
I love light music!
Ritchan, let's do another one!
You got it!
Yui!
Nodoka-chan!
Your time is up!
What?!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
How about a marshmallow
soy milk hot pot
or a chocolate curry hot pot?
Let's see...
Hmm...
Uh... It's nothing!
Check it! Moustache!
I have to bow out today.
Do you have plans?
Yes, sort of...
Bye!