[Young Yui]
Okay... A little further...
[Young Ui]
S-sis, are you sure
that you can do this?
I can do it!
(struggling)
Uh...
All done!
Gee, I wonder if Santa's
gonna come this year?
I forget to do my homework,
and wouldn't finish
my lunch sometimes.
And I haven't been very good,
so I'm afraid
maybe he won't come.
May I get presents!
Oh, it'll be okay, Sis!
I know it!
Santa will bring you lots
and lots of presents.
You'll see.
I think you should try
making a wish, too, Ui!
Hm...
May there be a
White Christmas this year.
Um, what's a
White Christmas?
It's a Christmas morning
where snow has fallen
and made everything
really pretty and white!
Oh!
Ui! Ui!
Hurry, hurry!
Sis, wait up!
(giggles)
Ta-dah!
Huh?
It's a White Christmas!
Uh? Huh?
Big Sis, what is this?
(giggles)
It's stuffing from a cushion!
Uh!
Uhh...
(giggles)
[Ui]
Our parents scolded Sis
really badly that day.
(giggles)
Uh?
Ui? What's so funny?
(giggles)
I really hope we'll have
another fun Christmas
together this year.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
It sure has gotten cold.
Brr...
Ui, shouldn't you be
wearing your scarf?
Um-hm, but I guess it blew away
when I washed it and
hung it out to dry last year.
(wind blowing)
Brrr...
Oh!
Hm...
Thank you, Big Sis...
Nice 'n warm, nice 'n warm...
Hey, what happened to
your other mitten?
Oh, I lost it somewhere.
Nice 'n warm, nice 'n warm...
(laughing)
*
Check it out!
I made a flyer for
our Christmas party!
[Mio]
Huh? We decided that we're
gonna have a Christmas party?
I did! But I didn't
tell anyone.
You should have!
The date: December 24th,
Christmas Eve.
The place: Mugi's house.
Cover charge: Ten dollars.
Huh?
Sorry, that really isn't
a good day for our house.
Yeah, I was kind of
afraid of that.
The schedule at our house is
always packed this time of year.
You have to make arrangements
at least a full month
in advance.
I'm truly sorry!
R-really, you don't say.
[girls]
That's some house?
Ritsu, what about your house?
No. No, forget that.
Ritsu's place is so messy
there's nowhere
for you to stand.
Excuse me?!
(grunt)
You're one to talk,
your room has dirty clothes
tossed everywhere.
Even panties.
Aah!
Hey! Don't make up
garbage about me!
I have plenty of
pictures as proof.
You big liar!
It's the absolute truth.
"Pan" pastries...
Pan-tease...
Ugh!
More where that came from.
Aah!
Stop it! Please, stop it!
Hey, Yui, how about your house?
I don't see why not.
Yeah! Score!
But are you sure it will
be okay for a big group
to come over on Christmas Eve?
Hm-hm. Mom and Dad are
both going to be away
on vacation that day.
Hey, they were gone when we
where there last time, too.
Yeah, they like to
travel a lot together.
They said they're going
to Germany this year.
Oh!
(laughing)
Whee!
What a lovey-dovey couple!
Is there anything that
the three of us can bring?
Just leave all the food to me!
Are you sure about that?
Yeah! No problem!
'Cause Ui will be
making it all.
Good thing she has
such a mature sister...
Oh, that's right!
There's one more thing!
Let's have a present exchange!
Yeah, let's do it!
Great idea!
Don't bring anything
weird, Mio, okay.
Huh?! That's what you do!
Like that time back in
grade school...
(boing)
Ah!
One trick pony.
Oh! What, you some
kind of comedian?
No. Are you?
[Mugi]
I can't wait!
Christmas party!
(giggles)
Do you want to come to
the Light Music Club
Christmas party, Nodoka?
Uh, are you sure?
I'm not a club member.
Don't worry, it's fine!
I mean, we're all
friends here, after all.
The more people that
come to the party,
the more money
we'll have to spend.
What are you planning
on doing with it?
Can you come, Nodoka-chan?
Yup.
Yay!
So that's the whole deal.
I hope we can count on you.
Of course, I'll be
chipping in to help out.
Just leave everything to me!
But...
If she hurt herself helping me,
that would be terrible!
I'd like you to handle
the decorations, please.
Roger that, ma'am!
What are you gonna do at
your Christmas party, anyway?
Eat cake, trade presents,
you know, all that
Christmassy kind of stuff.
Oh!
Also each of us will
do a party trick!
Huh?
(sigh)
Party tricks, huh?
I wonder what should I do?
Oh, wow, you're really
giving it a lot of thought.
Don't worry, I'm sure
I'll think of something!
Uh... Hm-mm!
And I'm gonna have to go out
and get a present, too!
Oh, you're right,
I'll have to go buy one, too!
[Yui]
What do you think would be good?
-Ah!
-Hm?
This is so cute!
Oh, Nodoka-chan, I really,
really want this!
You know, normally,
you have to go again
if you draw your own name.
Aw...
(sad groan)
Guess I'll go with this, then.
[Nodoka]
Uh...
Ritsu, made up your mind yet?
How's this?
Ah!
A-absolutely not!
How about this, then?
(scream)
Or how about thi-- Ow!
Why do you always try
to get stuff like that?!
Yes! I finally decided!
Oh, hey, you guys!
You came to do a little
gift shopping, too, huh?
So, what did you buy?
Well, if we told you that,
it would spoil all the fun.
Guess you're right.
Oh, hey! Ta-dah!
We're on our way over
to the raffle drawing!
Huh, really? So are we!
Come to Mama!
I won more tissues?
We have a winner! Our top prize!
Here you go! Congratulations!
Mugi-chan?
Oh!
You're all out shopping, too?
Did you just win?!
Uh-hm, a trip to Hawaii,
I think.
[Mio]
What is it with her
amazing luck?!
But I turned
the prize down.
Why?!
I wanted this instead,
so I asked them to exchange it.
We should all play it
together on Christmas!
Uh-hm...
Now then, what should I make?
Hmm...
And what trick should I do?
K-ON!
(loud pop)
Ah!
Big Sis! What happened here?
Oh, Ui...
I thought you were
cleaning the place up.
I couldn't help myself.
Oh! Ooo...
Those look delicious!
(Yui giggles)
Huh?
Hey, don't eat those, Big Sis!
Don't worry, I won't
sneak any bites!
Hehehe...
Huh?
Hm?
I said I wouldn't!
Huh?
It's like we're playing
Red Light, Green Light
or something?!
Come on, Sis,
stop fooling around.
Hehehe...
You haven't done any
decorating at all yet,
so you'd better hurry.
Snip, snip!
You mean, you're just
getting started?!
(door bell)
Merry Christmas!
Come in!
Hey-o! Yui, we're here!
Hey, everybody!
Come on in!
What're you doing?
I couldn't bring myself to
stop, once I got started.
What are you,
a grade schooler?
Oh, here, let me
take your coats.
Oh, right.
Thanks a lot, Ui.
[Mio]
A hardworking little sister
and a goofball big sister...
It's the perfect setup
for a sad soap opera.
[Ritsu]
Wow, this food is amazing!
[Mugi]
You made all this, Ui-chan?
[Yui]
Don't be rude! I made some, too!
Look at this cake!
That's awesome!
I put all the
strawberries on top!
Hey, return the "awesome,"
I just said!
Not right?
Um, well, Big Sis
worked really hard
on all sorts of things today.
For instance, she tried to
clean the house
and tried to put up
the decorations.
And she also... um...
[Mio]
She's really trying to
stand up for her!
We get it. We're sorry.
Nodoka-chan says that
she's gonna be late,
so let's go ahead
and have a toast.
Hm-hm.
The airheaded older sister
and the admirable
little sister...
I suppose that's gotta make
for a pretty good team.
Cheers!
Oh, wow, that's yet
another year done and gone!
Sheesh, you sound like
an old man.
Oh!
Ah! Ms. Yamanaka?!
These are delicious.
Can I have another helping?
When did she get here?!
[Ritsu]
Don't tell me she
climbed in with a rope!
Ha!
[Mio]
And then she snuck in...
[Yui]
...through an open window?!
Now really, who do you
think I am anyway?
Honestly, what sort of club
forgets to invite
their faculty advisor?
Um, well, "forget" isn't
exactly what I'd call it...
We didn't ask you
because we assumed
you had plans with
your boyfriend.
Wha-!
How dare you say that!
Clueless types are scary.
For your punishment, I want
you to change into this, Yui.
Why in the world would you bring
something like that with you?
Hehe!
Ta-dah!
Not working.
You're just not feeling
quite enough shame.
Yes, this calls for...
Ah!
[Yamanaka]
There's no escape!
(Mio screams)
Come back here!
No!
Hello?
Quit your struggling!
(Mio screams)
Oh!
(gasp)
I'm sorry.
I have the wrong house.
It's the right house!
Help me!
No one will ever
want to marry me now...
High schoolers sure lead
amazing lives!
To get this party back on track,
I think we should have
our gift exchange!
Yeah!
High schoolers change moods
at the drop of a hat!
Uh... But what about you, Ma'am?
Oh, don't worry I brought
something, too.
[girls]
Oh!
(giggles)
To be honest, I had planned
to give this present
to my boyfriend today,
if we were still together.
[girls]
Way to drag us down...
All right then,
let's get started, guys!
Uh, sure...
Hm.
The one you have when
the song ends is yours.
Here.
Jingle bells!Here!
Jingle Bells!Here you go!
Jingle all the way!
It's like she's losing it.
Aren't Christmas
gift exchanges
supposed to be
more fun than this?
No one will ever
want to marry me...
Hehe! Jingle bells!
Jingle bells!
Jingle all the way!
I'm getting dizzy...
This may be the most exciting
Christmas I've ever had!
That's all!
Um, this is the one that
I bought to the party.
Oh, no problem,
we'll trade!
Ms. Yamanaka!
Something is telling me
that whatever is inside here
is amazing!
Let's see what we have!
(Boing)
Uh...
(Ms. Yamanaka laughing)
Oh, yeah! This is the best
Christmas I've ever had!
[Ritsu]
She's gone crazy!
[Nodoka]
Stay calm, everyone.
[Ritsu]
I'm sorry,
I'll never do it again!
[Yui]
I'm sure something good
is in store for you!
(Ms. Yamanaka laughing)
[Mugi]
Oh...
That's the present that
I brought to the party.
(giggles)
Ah...
That's from me.
Nodoka, it's Christmas,
not year-end!
Ah!
These look tasty!
You're so lucky.
(evil scream)
(scream)
Oh yes, that's the one
that I brought.
Wait a minute!
You were going to give that
to your boyfriend
for Christmas?
I was! So pardon me
for breathing!
(crying)
[Mio]
Clueless types are scary...
I think, the only ones who
haven't opened their presents
are Yui-chan and Ui-chan, right?
Would you hurry up
and open them!
Y-yes, ma'am!
I got that because you
lost your scarf!
I got that because I remembered
you lost your mitten!
(laughing)
I'm just wondering what
you two would have done
if you hadn't ended up with
each other's presents?
So sweet!
Thank you, Ui!
Hm! And thank you
very much, Big Sis.
Winter will seem almost warm
when I wear it.
Right!
Now it time for each of us
to do a party trick!
Way to ruin a perfectly
good moment, Ritsu...
Hmm?
Hey! You wanna go first, Mio?
Ah!
Wow! She's pretty old school!
Yui, then!
Who, me? I'm not...
Uh...
I'll go!
I'd like to go first!
What? Really?
Hello, everyone!
Merry Christmas!
Is everyone having
a good time?
I'm sorry, this is all
that I can do.
Did you practice?
I did! Big Sis said that
we would be having
a talent contest today.
You thought
I was serious?
You mean you weren't?
I'm sorry, Ui...
Okay, don't worry about it.
Now I'll go!
Air guitar!
Pyoooooow!
Yeah! Then I'll play air drums!
Taka-taka-boom-pow!
Umm...
(scared)
Mio-chan really pushed herself.
I'll do an impression!
[Ritsu]
Wh-what's that?
My impression of a sunfish!
Okay, now I'm going next!
(slap)
A maple leaf!
[Mio]
Who is this woman,
and what did she do with
our sweet Ms. Yamanaka?
[girls]
Thank you for having us over!
Boy, it sure is cold, Ui...
Look! It's snow!
Wow, you're right!
It looks like we are going to
have a White Christmas!
You know, Sis, you once gave me
a White Christmas as a present,
and I loved it, remember?
Huh?
Huh...
Today sure was fun...
(knock on door)
Ui? Ui, can I come in?
Big Sis?
You mind if I sleep with you?
Hm-hm!
Ah!
I'm gonna wear these
to bed tonight!
'Cause they're so warm!
Then maybe I'll wear my
brand new scarf to bed.
'Cause it's warm too.
Ah-choo!
Come on, Big Sis,
I'm freezing!
Hey, I'm gonna start dusting,
Big Sis. You wanna help?
[TV]
The New Year's Countdown
is about to start!
Here's your
New Year's Eve noodles!
Oh!
You said two mochi
with your soup, right?
Uh-huh.
I peeled some
tangerines.
Ahh...
[Yui]
And that's how I spent
my holiday.
Give me Ui-chan!
Those two are quite
a pair, aren't they?
Won't you get fat, doing nothing
but eating and sleeping?
Oh, no. I never, ever
gain weight,
no matter how much I eat.
-No way!
-That can't be!
You too, Mugi-chan?
Mugi, how much weight
did you put on?
...pounds.
I gained... pounds.
(crying)
Just to be safe,
you should apologize.
I'm so sorry!
Mio-chan, you dressed up
really nice today.
Because Ritsu asked me
if I was going to.
[Ritsu]
I was just asking!
Wh-what?!
I guess things won't be
much different this
year, huh, Mio-chan?
I'm gonna go change!
Wait! You should keep them on.
You look cute.
Think so?
I sure do!
Now I've seen something
amazing this year, too!
You haven't changed
one bit, either!
[woman]
Ugh!
[Mugi]
Ms. Yamanaka?!
[girl]
Wow, look at this!
[Ritsu]
Looks like she
hasn't changed, either.
(bells clatter)
(clap, clap)
So, what did you guys pray for?
For my family's
health and safety.
I asked for help
losing weight.
I asked to be able to eat lots
and lots of yummy food!
Hey, we should all pray for
the Light Music Club, too.
May we all get better
at playing our music.
May we all continue to
have lots of fun together.
May we all be able to eat
lots of the great cakes
that Mugi-chan brings to the--
(thump)
May I become more
proficient at the guitar.
Right!
[Yui]
Want to grab something
to eat on the way home?
[Mugi]
Please don't talk about food!
[Mio]
You really never gain
any weight, Yui?
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Mio]
We're the Light Music Club...
If you ever get lonely,
come over to visit
whenever you want!
What am I,
a grade schooler?
Welcome to our club room!
Come in, come in,
it's so good to see you!
Welcome to our club!
Um... First, could you
explain what that was?
You two...
Ui!
In any event, we'll be
performing four songs tomorrow,
so be sure to come.
I'm lonely...