[Yui]
It's summer!
[Ritsu]
It's the beach!
Oh!
[Mio]
It's so pretty...
[Mugi]
It's sparkling!
Ready, let's swim!
Yeah!
You guys, be careful and
don't get carried away, okay!
Bleh!
Yui, the water's all salty!
Because it's saltwater, Ritchan!
Yui, there are waves here!
There are waves, Ritchan!
They're not listening to
a word I said...
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
(Camera clicks)
Hm?
Light Music Club?
Sakura High Festival?
*
(Nervous)
Let's see...
(Strum)
Ow! My finger!
You really did forgot
how to play.
Huh?
(Giggles)
My grandma used to
compliment me all the time.
"Yui," she said, "as soon
as you learn one thing,
everything else seems to
leave your head."
I don't think that
was a compliment.
Oh, Mio!
Where have you been?
Huh?
We're having a training camp!
Training camp?
That's right.
Summer vacation is almost here.
We're going to the beach?
Or maybe to the mountains?!
We're not going out there
to play around!
This will be a
band training camp!
We'll be practicing nonstop
from sunup to sundown!
I'd better buy
new clothes to wear!
Yeah, I need to buy
a swimsuit, too.
Listen!
Pretty soon after the
end of summer vacation,
is the high school festival.
"High School festival."
Yes! In the past, the Light
Music Club was pretty famous
for its live performances
at the Sakura High Festival.
That festival is-
Wow, the school festival!
School festivals at high schools
are pretty elaborate, right?
Concessions!
Yakisoba!
Takoyaki!
(Giggles)
I know! I really want to
have a full-on maid caf¨¦!
A-A haunted house
would be a lot better!
A maid caf¨¦!
A haunted house!
I said, a haunted house!
No! A maid caf¨¦ is
the way to go!
(Whack)
Ah!
Hmph! How come
you only whack me?
We're the Light Music Club,
aren't we?
WE are performing!
Hello, everyone.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh?
Ow... ow...
Would you like
some madeleines?
[Mugi]
Goodness...
[Mio]
What do you think, Mugi?
I know at the beginning
I said we should
take things slowly,
but I mean, come on.
It's been three months now,
and we haven't played
together a single time.
[Mugi]
Now, now, now, now, now, now...
Six times.
What?
Oh! Yeah, definitely!
Let's go!
I've always dreamed of having
a sleepover with you all.
Really, you have?
So, should we go to the beach?
Or how about-
I told you, this is going to be
a training camp for the band!
(Nervous laugh)
Uh, how much is this
training camp going to cost?
You know, she right.
We're on a tight budget?
I hadn't thought of that...
Hey, Mugi?
Yes?
Do you have a summer house?
Yes, of course.
Oh!
Of course she does!
Sis?
Come on, Sis!
(Snoring)
How about getting
out of bed all ready?
And aren't those my pajamas?
(Sleepy groan)
A little longer, please...
You're just hopeless.
Huh?
Um, Big Sister?
What time is it?!
Um... Uh...
(Phone rings)
Hello.
[Mio]
Good morning.
A fine morning
to you, too.
(Train horn)
[Yui] I'm sorry!
(Sigh)
Boy, I can't believe
I made it...
Yeah, and after we warned you
not to oversleep, too.
Sorry, I was way too excited
to get a good night's sleep.
What are you,
a grade-schooler?
(Giggles)
Yeah, well, seems she's
not the only one.
She's asleep.
Well, she did say that
this was her dream.
(Soft giggle)
The gel type will be fine...
Gel!
Hey, I wonder what she's
dreaming about right now?
You know, I think we need to
get a picture of this.
Cut it out,
that'd be really mean!
It's for our memory album!
(Click)
(Waking sounds)
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You see, you woke her up.
I'm sorry about that!
So now that our awake,
you really gotta tell us.
Where's this cool
summer home of yours?
Ah!
Let's see...
Almost there.
Ah!
Wow!
(Seagull cries)
The beach?
Yes, the beach.
Yui!
Ready, and...
Pull!
(Excited)
[Yui]
Smell that salty air!
Swimming! Yeah!
I told you, we didn't
come here to play!
[Yui and Ritsu]
Yeah!
(Mugi giggles)
[Ritsu]
It's huge!
Oh!
To be honest,
I had hoped to stay in one of
our larger vacation houses,
but unfortunately,
I only got permission
to borrow our smallest.
This is your smallest house?
This...
(Excited laugher)
Wow! Look at all this space!
This is amazing!
Huh?
What's this?
Oh my, I'm sorry!
I said they didn't need to
leave anything out for us,
but I guess they did.
Mugi, what's in here?!
Oh!
Oh, it's a princess bed!
Whoa!
Look at that!
I'm so sorry!
I always tell them
I'd like things to be
as normal as possible.
They just don't seem to
understand what that means.
Come in.
It hasn't been used recently,
so I'm worried that the gear
might not work properly.
Well, everything looks okay!
Hey, where are Yui and Ritsu?
I don't know.
They wandered off at some point.
Those two are hopeless.
What's that?
Oh, you mean this?
(Girls singing rock)
It's a past Light Music Club
playing at the school festival.
I found it in
the clubroom earlier.
They're good.
Yeah, they're way, way
better than we are.
Yes.
When I heard this,
it's like I had this sudden urge
not to be outdone by them.
So is that why you suggested
this training camp.
Yeah. But we're...
I don't think we will.
I know we can do this.
Mugi-
Yeah! Time for some fun!
Oh, yeah!
Well, that was fast!
What about practice?!
We're gonna go on ahead,
so you two hurry up
and get changed!
You still sure?
Y-yes, I think.
[Ritsu]
Hey!
[Yui]
Hurry up!
Wait, I'll be right there!
Come on, Mio, shall we?
Wait! You mean you're
gonna go with them?
We may as well enjoy ourselves
a little while we're here.
Right?
Uh...
But I thought we'd...
Mugi, we're going!
Coming!
We'll all be waiting for you.
(Upset grunt)
Wait for me!
I'm going, too!
*
[Yui]
K-ON!
It's been two weeks since we
tragically washed ashore
on this desert island...
Yes, although I thought
we were done for
when we were
cast adrift at sea.
Still, you gotta admit, this is
kinda fun in its own way.
What a grand find...
Seems we're saved...
Tonight we feast-
What kind of crazy scenario
are you acting out?
Mio, you're...
Eat this!
Come on, Yui! Let's swim!
Right!
(Grunt)
(Steps walking away)
That hurt.
Then again...
This sure is a pretty place.
(Laughing)
C'mon, tell me,
what did you draw?
It just grew to this size
before I knew it.
(Laughing)
I'm not scared, I'm not scared,
I'm not scared...
When you go to the doctor,
your kneecaps will be
covered with barnacles.
Ah!
(Laughing)
Ahh!
I swallowed
seawater!
We've made it at last to the
golden island of Zipangu!
The day's not over yet.
Huh? When did you get that?
We're at the beach and all.
And it's a beautiful day.
And if we don't live it up,
what was the point of
coming all this way and...
Wah!
Practice!
What, you forgot
about that?
It's all your fault, Ritsu,
with your going on and on
about goofing off.
Oh, yeah? Well which of us
was having the most fun, huh?
Uh...
[Ritsu] (Full belly groans)
I'm so stuffed!
Ah... The floor feels
wonderfully nice and cool.
When you close your eyes,
it almost feels like you're
being carried far away
out to sea by the
ocean waves, doesn't it?
Hey, you're right it does...
Good night, Ritchan.
Yeah, you, too.
Hey, come on, guys,
we're starting!
You need to
get up, you two!
(Sighs)
Hey, Mugi, stand back
for a minute.
(Heavy bass note)
(Groans)
(Tuning up)
(Ritsu and Yui tired groans)
Oh, c'mon, can't we
just call it a day.
We came here to practice, and
so that's what we're gonna do!
Yeah, but we're tired.
I've been meaning to ask,
have you been putting on
a bit of weight lately?
Oh!
Especially around
your mid-section.
Huh?!
Maybe it's because
you haven't been playing
the drums lately?
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I can't hold this any longer.
Aw, this guitar feels like
it weighs a ton!
That's why I told you
before bought it
that you should
get a lighter one!
Who was it that told me
to buy this guitar?
You did!
The floor's warmed up.
It's not as comfortable.
Yeah...
Roll... roll... roll...
Careful,
you'll get dirty.
Yeah, this spot's
nice and cool...
How do you expect to play
in the school festival
if you don't practice?
[Ritsu]
Oh, come on, I told you that
we should do a maid caf¨¦!
[Yui]
I still think we should
do a haunted house!
Ugh... Yui, you're not
following me at all.
Look closely at Mio.
Wh-what's this
got to do with me?
Let's face it, Mio. There aren't
many people in this world
better suited to the
maid look than you.
Black stockings!
A lily-white apron!
And a maid headband!
The adorable power
of cute compels you!
Love!
And she'd have a
catchphrase like that!
That might be really cute!
Just kidding, relax-
(Thud)
[Yui]
S-Squad Member Ritsu...
When we're done with this,
we're really gonna start
practicing, got it?
We know, we know!
One, two!
And now for our last number!
Let's do it!
*(Soft melody playing)*
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Huh? Wait! It's over already?
Budget issues.
We'll do it again, soon.
Yeah, they'll be
going off like crazy
at our Budokan show, right!
Budokan show?
Huh? That's what we all settled
on as our goal, remember?
Right?
Huh?
[Yui]
In that case, I want
the fireworks to be pink!
[Ritsu]
Are you a grade-schooler?
Oh, but it'd be cute!
We'd look like
a bunch of kids!
[Mugi]
I think pink would be
a little much, too.
Aw, you really think so?
(Nervous laugh)
(Rock music playing)
Huh?
If want we're to do is
try to play at the Budokan,
then we need to get
at least as good as this.
[Ritsu]
Wow, they're good.
[Yui]
Huh? I think I could
play this song...
(Scary girl on tape)
I've been waiting
for you people to arrive...
Uh...?
NOW DIE!
What was that?
The tape must have
switched to side B.
Oh, right...
I'm not listening,
I'm not listening...
Scary ghosts...
in a scary
haunted house.
Stop it, please!
No more!
Please...
(Crying)
Ritsu.
You overdid it.
Hm...
Mio, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
You see, Mio?
Everything's okay, now.
It wasn't a ghost
on the tape.
Really?
Sparkly!
The power of cute compels you!
(Waves washing)
(Sniff)
I'm really sorry.
Hm.
Uh...
Hey, Yui,
did you really mean what
you said about that song...
Yeah, watch this!
Let's see...
(Plays melody from tape)
Oh...
No way.
There! How was it?
Wow, that was perfect!
(Giggles)
Thanks, but not quite,
I don't know how to
make it go "myon"...
"Myon"?
Wait a minute, I think you must
be talking about choking.
This choking?
Guess again.
Choking is when you pull on
the strings to bend them
and change the sound while
a note is being playing.
[strum]
You do it like this...
Oh, wow!
See?
Do this...
and this?
Yeah, that!
(Yui giggles)
(Laughing)
That sounds funny!
Uh, funny how?
Look a spook
afraid of ghosts.
Ghosts!
Ah! I can't believe you
even have an outdoor bath.
I certainly had
a lot of fun toady.
Yeah.
Maybe you were right, Mugi.
Maybe I should just
try to relax a bit
and not worry so much.
Then we should've
had a lot more fun!
Who are you?!
It's Ritsu!
Wow, your bangs are long...
Got a problem with that?
They're long,
but surprisingly cute.
Oh, thanks! Wait, a second.
What do you mean by
"surprisingly"?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Hm...
I think you're
trying for this.
Wow! You can tell?
Amazing!
Now, all you need to do is
stick out your ring finger.
Oh, I get it!
Ugh!
A-are you all right?
Ow, ow...
(Giggles)
Music is a wonderful
thing, isn't it?
It was so much fun
playing together
with everybody,
for the first time today.
Yui...
And I would've missed out on it
if you hadn't suggested
having a training camp.
Thanks, Mio-chan!
Uh...
Uh, well...
It looks like Mio's
all embarrassed!
I am not! I'm red from
the heat, and that's all!
[Ritsu]
You're not fooling anyone.
[Mio]
You're wrong, all right!
So just drop it!
Uh-oh, Mio's mad!
Why, you...!
Come back here, darn it!
Ooo, scary!
(laughing)
Come back here!
[Ritsu]
Is anyone home?
Coming! I'll be right there!
So you said the pictures from
the training camp are ready?
Yep. Right here.
Ah! Wow!
Ah! Hehehe..
Ah!
Haha! That one turned out great.
Actually, I have that shot-
(Choking)
Hand over the negatives, now.
I-it's a digital camera,
there's no negatives...
[Ritsu]
Come on, Mio, we're starting!
Yeah, hang on!
I'll just be a minute!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Nodoka]
Hm, I don't see it
listed anywhere.
Oh, no! You're kidding...
Wait, don't tell me...
Ms. Yamanaka, did you
use to play guitar?
[Yamanaka]
No, but some old friends
of mine did.
[Ritsu]
This was in that cardboard box
you found the other day, Mio.
They look like pictures of
an old Light Music Club.
That's amazing! I knew you
could do it, Nodoka!
Who's your advisor?
Advisor?