[Ui]
Hello, I'm Ui Hirasawa.
My high school
entrance exams are over,
and this spring, I will be
joining my sister Yui at--
[Yui]
Ui!
W-was y-y-your name th-there?
What's the matter with you, Sis?
Why are you so nervous?
B-because!
My name was there.
I passed, Sis.
Really?!
Uh-huh!
Oh...
(crying)
Uh, Sis? I really
can't breathe...
You did so good!
You did great!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
It was thanks to the
kind support of each and
every one of you here today,
that Ui managed to pass
and begin her journey to
a happy and successful life!
(click)
well, it looks like Ui passed.
Looks like Yui is the
happier of the two.
A doting parent?
Or a doting sister,
is more like it.
It sure is shaping up
to be a happy spring.
Congratulations, Ui.
Yeah, way to go!
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
Uh...
There it is.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
[girl]
We're in the same class again!
Mr. Akai's our homeroom teacher?
[girl]
I wonder if I'll be in the
same class as Yoshiko-chan?
[Yui]
And... there I am!
2nd Year, Class 2, huh?
Yeah, so am I!
Oh, look!
So am I! Class 2!
Really! No way! That's great!
How bout you, Mio?
Class 1...
Uh... Um...
Hey! What's with those looks?
If you ever get lonely,
come over to visit
whenever you want!
What am I,
a grade schooler!
Are you gonna be okay
away from me, huh?
I won't be able to
crib off my homework.
Ha! You don't have to
worry about me!
I'll have Mugi with me
to help me out!
Hm!
[Ui]
Hello, everyone!
A very good morning!
Oh! The uniform
looks great on you!
You look so innocent!
Y-you really think so?
Sis, your collar.
You left the tag from
the dry-cleaner on.
Wow, you're right!
And also, you've got
a bad case of bed head.
I didn't have time
to brush it this morning!
Let's try to get up a
little earlier starting
tomorrow, all right?
Uh-huh...
You know, maybe you two
would be much better off
if you switched ages
with each other.
(bell rings)
Well, see you later.
I guess we should
take off, too.
(Yui)
Huh? Class 2 is up on
the second floor?
That's right.
It's like we're literally
upperclassmen now.
See ya around, you Year 2,
Floor 1, Class 1 student you!
Oh yeah! Bite me!
[Mugi]
We'll see you at break!
[Yui]
Where on the second floor is it?
[Ritsu]
I think somewhere around...
(sigh)
I'm lonely...
(classroom chatter)
There isn't a single
girl here that I know.
[Nodoka]
Mio! Glad to see you!
I was worried that
I wouldn't know anyone
when I was put in a
different class than Yui.
(crying)
Here's hoping for
a good year together.
Same here!
*
Want to join
the Basketball Club?
The Tea Ceremony Club
really is a lot of fun!
Consider the
Occult Studies Club!
Are you interested
in ping pong?
Wow, look at this,
the halls are packed already!
Large clubs certainly have
more recruiting options.
Don't ever underestimate
the Light Music Club!
Mio, got the flyers?
Well, I kinda threw
this together.
"Kinda" is right...
Ah!
It lacks any selling points!
What exactly are
our selling points?
Something like, "Come and
join the Light Music Club,
where you get all the
tea and snacks you want,
and get to sleep!"
-That sounds great!
-No it doesn't!
Well, do you have any
better ideas?
'Cause the way it is now,
it's got no impact!
If it doesn't, we'll just
have to give it some!
[Mio]
We're the Light Music Club...
[Mugi]
We're holding a performance
to welcome new students, meow.
Please be sure to come, meow.
[Ritsu]
If you're interested, come to
the Music Room after school!
Woof, woof, woof!
[Yui]
There's also lots of
yummy snacks, cluck!
Uh, Mio-chan...
Wh-what is it?
It's doing the opposite
of what we wanted?
Yeah, that just
occurred to me, too.
[Ui] Oh, really?
[Yui] Huh?
[girl]
Yeah. So, what club do you
think I should join?
It's a tough choice, huh?
M-hm.
(Yui running)
Ui!
Big Sis?
(screams)
(panting)
Ui...
What was that?
Beats me.
Huh? Ah!
We're the Light Music Club.
If you're interested, feel free
to come by the Music Prep Room
on the third floor
after school.
Sure...
What the heck?
[Mio]
You know you shouldn't
run at people like that!
[Yui]
Yeah, I'm sorry...
[Ritsu]
Oh man, these things
are way too hot...
[Mugi]
I think it's fun, like we're
working at a part-time job.
[Yui]
You sure do like
working, Mugi-chan.
Uh...
Come on, Azusa.
Let's go.
Uh-huh.
(girls panting)
[Yui]
After all that sweating,
we hardly had any takers.
[Ritsu]
We'll just have to make up for
it at tomorrow's performance!
[Mugi]
You're right.
(sigh)
Excuse me.
But I made all these
outfits for you, too.
Uh, well, afternoon
classes are starting!
[Ui]
The Light Music Club?
Yeah, all the girls came across
as being pretty cool.
Wanna check them out?
No thanks, I'll pass.
See ya.
What's gotten into her?
You'll come, right?
Sure, I guess.
I'll go with you.
Then let's go!
Uh...
Azusa, Jazz Appreciation
is having a welcome meeting
in their club room
upstairs. Let's go.
Hm.
Here it is.
(knocking)
Excuse us! May we come in?
Welcome to our club room!
Uh, Big Sis?!
Oh, Ui!
You're joining the
Light Music Club?
Wait, you two are
dressed up, too?
-[Mio] Help me!
-[Yamanaka]Step aside, please!
Come in, come in,
it's so good to see you!
Welcome to our club!
Uh...
First, could you explain
what that was?
[girl]
As I recall, it's suppose
to be two doors down
from the Occult Studies club.
(Mio screaming)
Huh? I wonder
what's up there?
I'm not exactly sure, but I
think it's the Music Room.
The Music Room, huh...
[Yui]
Ever since Christmas, it's like
Ms. Yamanaka has gotten
totally addicted to putting
us in different costumes.
Ah, I see.
Oh, I nearly forgot, this is
Yui, she's my big sister.
I'm Yui Hirasawa.
If you wait just a minute, I'll
go get you some nice, tasty tea.
It's okay to take
this one, isn't it?
It's pretty hot,
so be careful, okay.
Ow!
Are you all right?
S-Sis, are you okay?
(nervous)
(panicked)
(sigh)
You have a seat, Big Sis.
I'll take it from here.
Are you sure?
Oh, Yui...
Let me introduce Ritsu-san.
Hi there. I'm the club
president, Ritsu Tainaka.
[Nodoka]
Darn it, Ritsu!
She seems really cool.
You still haven't
submitted your request form
to use the school auditorium!
If you don't, you won't
be able perform tomorrow.
Oh, you're right...
I swear, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Sorry! I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry!
I want you to meet
Tsumugi Kotobuki.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And you, too.
I'm so sorry for
all the drama.
[Ritsu]
Wait, wait!
She seems like
she's really nice.
And what's with these
silly getups, anyway?
Hey, they weren't my idea!
Ah...
Oh my, Ritsu...
Huh?
And last but
not least is... huh?
Her?
Yeah, her name
is Mio Akiyama.
It's just that she gets
embarrassed really easily.
Huh?
What's the deal, Mio?
Quit hiding out there
and come on in
and join the rest of us.
No way! You'll laugh at me!
No, we won't laugh.
It looks great on you.
Y-you really mean it?
She's so cute...
Uh?
Hmm...
Hm...
Um, Ui, who's this lady?
This is Ms. Yamanaka.
She's their faculty advisor.
You two...
Yes?!
Care to try one?
No thank you.
Please consider joining up.
Thank you very much,
we will.
So what did you think?
Well, it didn't quite seem
the same as real jazz,
if you know what I mean.
It didn't, huh?
Uh?
Hey, why did you stop?
That reminds me...
[Yui]
K-ON!
Wow, they look kinda cool!
[Ui]
Now they finally look like
a Light Music Club.
Mio-chan, my strap is
caught on my shoulder.
Yeah, mine is, too.
I can't move in this skirt...
Yeah, these sleeves are...
No, I guess they're fine.
[Ritsu]
Ah! I can't play like this!
[Mio]
Whose bright idea was it
to wear maid outfits?!
We decided to change
into track suits.
Okay, here I come!
Ready!
Yea!
Hahaha!
-You're next, Mugi! Go on!
-Right!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Okay, why don't we
get started then.
Hm.
(strum)
That was awesome!
They're cool, but not
those track suits...
[girl]
You're really going?
They were the ones in those
animal costumes, remember?
I'm just gonna take
a quick peek.
(playing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
[Azusa]
Track suits?
[girl]
Hey, isn't that Ui Hirasawa?
She's in our class.
It's almost like she doesn't
want to be there...
[Azusa]
Maybe they don't take things
seriously in this club.
[Yui]
Um, we're really sorry
we didn't give you
a full-on proper performance.
We normally go all-out
when we play.
-Really, we do that?
-Of course we do!
In any event,
we'll be performing
four songs tomorrow,
so be sure to come.
We'll want to hear your
unvarnished opinion!
Sure, I'll do that...
W-well, I guess we
should get going then.
I'll see you later on
back at home, Big Sis.
Sure thing, Ui.
[Ui]
So, what did you think?
Um, well, they're certainly
incredible in many ways.
You think so?
Oh, and that cake we had
was really good!
Yeah, it was, wasn't it?
(sighs)
Um, listen, I--
I'm sorry, I have to
go to the bathroom!
Go on without me. 'Bye.
Their prospects
are looking grim.
Oh...
Uh...
Uh?
Hmm...
[Yui]
What did she think?
She said she thought
it was incredible.
Wasn't it, though?
She'll come tomorrow,
too, right?
Yeah, probably.
The Light Music Club,
it's really a blast!
Yeah.
(tuning)
Hey, Big Sis?
Yeah?
What do think is
the best thing
about the Light Music Club?
Huh?
Well, let me think a second...
I guess it's
how much fun it is.
Fun in what way?
I don't know. Fun is fun.
Do you wanna join, too, Ui?
Our goal is to
play the Budokan!
I'll think about it.
Now that I think about it,
Sis has been really energetic
ever since she joined the club.
Until a little
while ago, she...
Ui... Ice cream!
Not until after
you've had your dinner!
I want ice cream! Ice cream!
But now, she's really focused
and working hard.
Ui?
Yeah, Sis?
I really wanna have ice cream!
After you've had your dinner!
In some ways she's the
same as ever, though...
Uh...
It's packed out there!
Well, it is suppose to be
the welcome party
for all the new students.
If we play like we always do,
and we'll be fine.
B-b-but we don't...
Your still not over
your stage fright, huh?
Ritchan!
I just found
a one dollar coin!
I wish you would be
more nervous!
[Mio]
The order is: "Fuwa Fuwa Time,"
"Curry, Then Rice,"
"My Love is a Stapler,"
Brush Pen, Ballpoint Pen."
Your taste in song titles
is as unique as ever seen.
Really?
So, do you really want me to
sing all the vocals today?
That's right, we never
decided on that.
I've got it. Since we are lucky
enough to have two singers,
I think that you should do
at least one song today, Mio.
Huh!
C'mon, high five!
-No way! Forget it! I can't!
-Oh, Mio...
But everybody loved your
singing in our last show.
Forget it!
Come on, accidents like that
don't happen twice.
-No! Ah!
-But, Mio...
-Mio-chan...
-No!
(crying)
-You want ramen?
-No!
-So then, no gyoza?
Boy, that's one serious
rejection response.
[Yamanaka]
I guess we have no choice.
We'll have to let Yui
handle everything.
[announcer]
Next up is a club introduction
and performance
by the Light Music Club.
Look like we're on!
[Yamanaka]
Break a leg.
And I have just one last word
for you all before I go...
What is it?
Uniforms as costumes are great!
Would you please
clear off the stage now.
[Ui]
Really? You've decided?
[Jun]
Yeah. The Jazz Appreciation Club
has some cool
upperclassmen in it.
I'm sorry.
Well, if that's the club
you want to be in,
then that's the club
you should join.
It's your decision after all.
See you.
(sigh)
Hm?
Uh...
Uh, excuse me!
(Playing "Curry, Then Rice")
Sorry to drag you
in here like this.
Oh! Wow, it really is
packed in here!
Huh? Whoa...
(audience clapping)
Wow, my sister's
on vocals today!
Hi, we're the Light...
(feedback)
...the Light Music Club.
To all you new students
out there,
congratulations on
getting in to our school!
When I first heard about
the Light Music Club,
I thought all they did was
play "lighthearted" music.
(audience laughs)
Yui's banter is doing a good
job putting everybody at ease.
I signed up without
giving it much thought,
thinking I could
just play castanets
or something simple, like that.
So I hope all of you
think about joining up
with the same
carefree attitude!
But you know, Ms. Yamanaka
told me one day,
that castanets are actually
really hard to play.
Here's our next song.
About time...
Oh, Ms. Yamanaka is our advisor
and the music teacher here--
(drums playing)
What are we, a comedy band?!
Sorry, Ritchan.
Anyway, here's our next song,
"My Love is a Stapler"!
(playing "My Love is a Stapler")
That riff is tough, and she's
pulling it off perfectly!
Except for...
Yui, sing!
Ah! I forgot the lyrics!
Ah! Uh...!
Mio-chan...
Hurry up and sing!
*
(groaning)
[Mugi]
Um, excuse me girls...
You know, no one
is going to come in
with you glaring out
the door like that.
[Yui]
Aw, but the crowd at our show
was so psyched about us!
[Ritsu]
Impossible, not a
single person showed up!
[Yui]
Oh! You don't think it's because
of the way I messed up, do you?
You know, maybe it's because
we have such a low
membership in our club.
(sigh)
Come on now,
the tea is ready!
I suppose we're just gonna
have to go and nab up Ui.
The poor girl isn't a bug.
(door opens)
Pardon me...
Uh, yes?
I'm very interested in
joining your club.
Um, would you mind
repeating that?
I'd like to join the club.
Ah!
[Ritsu]
We got one!
Ahh!
Good for you, Big Sis!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Azusa]
Um, what's this?
[Yamanaka]
It's a pair of cat ears,
obviously.
No, I knew that,
but, uh...
What am I supposed
to do with them?
I wonder if they're testing me
to see how independent I am?
[Yui]
Okay, it's your turn
next, Azusa-chan.
Um, my name's Azusa Nakano,
Year 1, Class 2.
I look forward to
our time together.