(audience clapping)
One, two, three, four!
One, two...
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
(Excited crowds)
Today is the big day...
I wonder if Yui and the others
are here already?
Sorry I'm--
*
[Husky voice]
Step right up, step right up!
It's a bargain, it's a bargain!
Wait, that voice...
Right, serving for one.
Enjoy.
Thanks, young lady.
Thanks!
Geez, Yui!
What are you doing?
Mio! Want some yakisoba?
It'll just be a minute!
Why is this happening?
We perform today!
We don't have time
to mess around.
We have to get together
and practice like crazy!
Sorry. I really want
to practice, too,
but I got put on the morning
shift at my class' booth
and I have to stay.
Uhh...
Thank you very much!
Looks like we
tripped the breaker!
Aw, again?
Hey, it'll be undercooked!
How many times has this
happened today already?
Hey, come on,
your not suppose to have
more than three
hot plates at a time!
You know the rules!
It's not us!
I bet you anything
it's Class 5!
Seems like a rough gig here...
Thank you, come again!
Hey, Mio!
Ritsu, do you want to try
and get in some practice
before our show today?
Oh, now's no good for me!
Just take a look at
the line I've still got
waiting back there.
Well, isn't there anyone here
who can take over for you?
Not really. You see,
I was the one who
suggested doing this
haunted house,
so I have to oversee at least
the first few hours here.
Ah. Well, where's Mugi then?
Hm.
(scream)
(panicked)
Thank you so much!
Hope you enjoyed it!
Right, next
in line, please!
[girl]
It looks scary...
[boy]
It'll be fun! Don't worry!
In here?
Yep.
It's okay for
class members to go in.
It's dark,
so watch your step.
Heh, heh, heh!
(nervous breathing)
M-Mugi, you in here?
(screaming)
M-Mugi! Where are you?
[Mugi]
Mio, it's me.
Mugi!
Ahh!
(Mio screams)
Huh?
Thanks, hope you enjoy it!
Nodoka-chan!
Your voice is still scratchy.
Are you gonna be all right?
It's still a little bit sore
from club practice, that's all.
I'm gonna be just fine.
Isn't today's your
first performance?
-You go on at three, right?
-Yeah.
Well, you still have a fair
amount of time until then.
Don't you want go and
get in some practice?
Yeah. I'm planning to do that
as soon as I get
finished with my shift.
In that case,
go ahead and take off.
I'll ask around and
see if there's someone
who can take over the rest
of your shift for you.
Okay, but...
You just go on ahead.
I'll take care of it.
Yui!
What are you waiting for?
Go practice.
Ah!
Thanks! I'll be back!
Oops! Sorry about that, sonny!
Hm!
Go on in!
Enjoy yourselves!
[Panting]
Ritchan!
Hey!
Where are Mio and Mugi?
Your voice hasn't
back yet, huh?
No, I'm afraid it still
sounds a little raspy.
Try saying something like,
"Thank you for the grub"!
Thank you for the grub!
Ha! You sound like
a sumo wrestler!
Treat a training match
as a tournament,
and a tournament as if
it were a training match!
Sumo is not a national sport,
it is a martial art!
Is this what it means to be
defeated in the ring,
but victorious in technique?
Dosukoi, dosukoi, dosukoi!
Dosukoi, dosukoi!
So where's Mio-chan
and Mugi-chan?
Sorry, I couldn't resist!
Mugi is working inside here,
but Mio might have gone on
up to the club room.
C'mon, we gotta get in
some practice!
You're right, we should.
Mugi and I are
gonna be relieved soon,
so we'll meet you upstairs
just as soon as we can.
Got it.
We're gonna practice, huh?
Hm...
Next in line, step right up!
What're you doing, Yui?
Shhh!
Huh?
(giggles)
[Ritsu]
Wow! I bet she's been
practicing up here all morning.
[Mugi]
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mio!
We're sorry we
left you by yourself.
Yeah, we all want to
practice, too!
You guys...
What kept you?!
(Playing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
Yeah! All right! That didn't
sound too bad at all.
Oh yes, that was perfect!
Do you think you can
do this, Mio-chan?
Uh...
Mm... Mm-hmm...
[Mugi]
We'll play it just like that.
I knew I'd find you here!
Is there a problem,
Ms. Yamanaka?
Hehe... Although it
wasn't voluntary,
I am your club's advisor.
So I thought I ought to do
something to help out.
I made costumes
for each of you!
You're way too into this!
Ms. Yamanaka, we appreciate
the sentiment and all...
Huh?
You expect me to
put that on and sing?
In front of the whole school...
[Ritsu]
But not the best timing.
I don't understand?
Are you telling me
that you don't care for them?
(Mio panics)
If you want, you can always
wear my old costume!
Ah! I suddenly feel like that
last outfit wasn't so bad!
Stop it, Ms. Yamanaka!
Mio isn't the only one who'd be
embarrassed to wear this stuff.
That's right!
Gosh, you really mean that?
But I worked so hard
on making them...
And besides...
Yui-chan and Mugi-chan are only
too happy to wear theirs.
Ugh!
Would you two cut it out!
Why is all of this happening?
You're not still
nervous, are you?
How about I give you
a makeup job
so insane that no one
will know it's you?!
N-no, thank you!
Right! You go and break a leg
out there, girls!
Ah! Oh no! All this craziness
has made me forget
everything I'm suppose to do!
Let's practice then!
It's the only cure!
She's right, let's practice!
Pretend that didn't happen...
That didn't happen.
(nervous laugh)
*
[Yui]
K-ON!
Okay, go ahead and carry this
down to the auditorium.
Okay... Whoa!
It's pretty heavy,
so be careful.
Hey, by the way,
how's Mio-chan doing?
Well, I'm having Mio
focus on something else.
I'm on vocals...
In front of
the whole school...
That's obviously
what will happen.
It's too risky to have her
move any equipment around.
Oh yeah, I see...
(struggling)
(Mugi humming)
(Yui groans)
There's not a
bead of sweat on her!
La de da de da...
Nodoka-chan...
Ah, Yui. The play is just
getting starting now,
so leave that in
the corner, okay?
Gotcha...
Whew...
All right, the
Choir Club is up next,
then the Light Music Club
is up after that.
All of their
equipment is here.
It's almost time!
Ah... We're finally done
moving it all!
Yeah, good work.
Tea's ready!
Come on and get it you two!
Yay! That's our Mugi-chan!
Ritchan, you and Mio are
childhood friends, aren't you?
Yeah, that's right.
For how long would you say?
We've been joined at the hip
since kindergarten!
Huh?
No, wait. Maybe it was
since grade school?
Then you're not really
childhood friends.
Now, has Mio-chan
always been the shy type
ever since she was
just a little girl?
You better believe it.
There was one time...
Oh, my! You've got
really pretty hair!
Ah!
When I said to her...
Oh, wow! You're left-handed!
That's really cool!
Hahaha!
Everybody,
Mio-chan's so awesome!
When I said stuff like that,
she go totally beet-red and get
all flustered and embarrassed!
Well then, it's your fault
the way she is, Ritchan!
Has all the equipment
been carried over?
Mio-chan!
You... got your nerves
under control?
Hm?
Here you are.
Surprising, considering you
were against doing the vocals.
Get real.
I'm not a baby, you know.
I can't let myself freak out
over every little thing forever.
Oh, yeah.
She's totally freaking out!
We're about to go on
in a few minutes!
How are you gonna perform
in your condition?
I can't do it.
Oh, Ritsu, please do
the vocals for me!
If I did that, who would
play the drums then?
I'll play them, please!
Then who's suppose to
play the bass?!
I'll play the bass,
too, please!
Have it your way!
I'd love to see how
you're gonna pull that off!
Ritsu! Ritsu!
Would you please
get off me, Mio!
Ritsu! Ritsu! Ritsu!
[Yui]
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry, Mio-chan.
If I hadn't overdone it
and did this to my voice,
you wouldn't have to go
up on stage and sing today.
Yui...
Hm...
Don't worry, I'll handle
the vocals, okay!
No, no, no, no...
Yui, I'm sorry,
that's not what I wanted!
You know that!
(nervous fidgeting)
Hm... Oh, that's right!
We need to come up
with a spiel!
What is a spiel?
Hm? Intros and stuff!
You know, like when the band
banters with the crowd
between songs at a concert.
Oh, right, right!
Hey, everybody!
How are you doing?!
(crowd applauding)
The Light Music Club would
like to welcome each
and every one of you to our
very first show ever today!
(crowd applauding)
Haha! Woo! Woo!
Hehe...
[Ritsu]
Now, let's introduce
our members!
Guitar! You can always find her
slacking off on her days off,
"If it's sweet, leave it to me!"
she always says,
It's the devil-may-care
fairy, Yui!
(making guitar sounds)
(crowd applauding)
And on keyboards!
She's your girl when it comes
to fine snack goods!
She has the graceful, lively,
natural airhead of a rich girl,
give a big hand to, Mugi!
(making keyboard sounds)
(crowd applauding)
And on bass and vocals!
Scary and gory stories are
most definitely not her thing!
She's the Don of
the Light Music Club,
the dangerous queen, it's Mio!
(thump)
Ow!
Who are you calling
dangerous, huh?!
You proved my point...
(giggles)
And last but not least, me!
Fair of face and figure,
and mind!
She's everybody's idol
with her sunny smile.
Give a big hand to...
me, Ritsu!
(thump)
Ow!
Quit tooting your own horn!
(laughing)
Uh...
(crowd applauding)
[announcer]
Let's hear it for
the Choir Club!
Ah! Look at all those
people out there!
Goodness, you're right.
(deep breath)
Our very first number...
Come on!
Time to get out there and
show them what we practiced!
Yes!
[Mio]
Um, Ritsu...
Do I really have to go out
on stage looking like this?
I think it suits you
really well, Mio.
She's right!
It looks so cute on you!
Oh man!
[announcer]
Next up is a performance by
the Light Music Club!
So get ready for
some great music!
All right now, let's do it!
Yeah!
Whoa!
You can do it, Yui!
(tuning up)
(audience applauding)
What's with the costumes?
They're so cute!
What club are they again?
I nailed it!
(panicking)
I can't do this!
[Yui]
Mio-chan!
Huh?
We all know that you
practiced and practiced
and practiced your heart out
for this, Mio-chan.
*
[Ritsu]
Yeah, Mio!
We know, Mio!
We know you can do this!
So, let's knock 'em dead!
(audience mumbling)
One, two, three, four!
One, two, three!
(Playing "Fuwa Fuwa Time")
(car horn)
Uh? Oh...
(audience applauding)
(audience cheering)
(giggles)
(gasps)
Thank you, everyone!
(audience cheering)
I think maybe this will finally
let Mio get over her shyness.
Uh... Ah!
Oh!
Mio!
Ugh... Ow...
(gasps)
Huh?
Oh...
(camera click)
(gasp)
(Mio screams)
[Ritsu]
That was some great work
yesterday, everyone!
Yeah, really good work!
For your first time
in front of a crowd,
I think you did
pretty good, Yui!
Aw!
As for Mio...
She's apparently got
her own fan club now!
Oh, amazing!
But I'm afraid she's
kind of out of commission
at the moment...
Huh?
P-panties... Panties...
No one will ever want
to marry me now...
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Ritsu]
I made a flyer for
our Christmas party!
Ah!
I wanted this instead, so
asked them to exchange it.
Now then, what should I make?
All done!
[Yui]
Gee, I wonder if Santa's
gonna come this year?
I haven't been very good,
so I'm afraid
maybe he won't come.
May I get presents!