[Yui]
Our long sought-after
new member
has finally arrived to join us
at the Light Music Club!
Welcome to the
Light Music Club!
Hey, don't just stand there!
Come in!
(giggling)
All right, now tell us,
what's your name?
Uh, my name is Azusa.
So, what instrument
do you play?
Well, I play--
So, what's your
favorite food?!
-What's your favorite color?
-Calm down, people.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
Um, I'm Azusa Nakano,
year 1, class 2,
and I play a
little bit of guitar.
Hey, just like Yui does, huh?
I look forward to playing
with you, Yui-senpai.
Oh!
Yui-senpai...
Senpai!
Hey! Come back
to Planet Earth!
*
For starters, try playing
something for us!
I'm still a beginner,
so I'm not very good yet.
No problem!
I'm gonna teach you
everything I know!
Wow, you're starting to act
like a senpai already.
Uh, well, here goes.
(shredding on the guitar)
Sh-she's great!
She's way better than I am!
Uh-oh. What should I do?
They're acting strange
all of a sudden.
I bet it was because
I played so badly.
I'm so sorry!
My playing must have been
awful to listen to.
No, that's not why
we reacted like that!
Y-you have a ways to go!
Huh?!
What's with you?
Yui, how long are you
gonna keep acting cocky?
Uh!
Oh!
Ah!
Yui-senpai, I would
really love to hear
you play the guitar again!
Huh? Uh...
Oh. Um...
Ugh!
I threw my back out
during the show,
so maybe later, okay?
Lame.
Whatever. Just move it.
Well, in any event,
I guess we can assume
that you're going to be
joining the club, right?
Yes!
I was very moved and excited
when I heard you all play
at the welcoming ceremony!
I look forward to
playing with you.
She's so dazzling,
I can't even look at her!
Oh, that's right.
My application form.
Duly received and accepted.
So, we'll see you
here tomorrow, then.
You will. I guess
I better get going now.
Oh, no!
What am I gonna do?!
Go start practicing.
Hello, everyone!
Well, someone's awfully cheery!
Yes, the end of the school day
couldn't come fast enough.
Let's get to it, then!
To practice you mean?
No, have tea.
Eh?!
[Mugi]
Here's a cup for you, Azusa.
Are you sure?
I mean, is it okay
for us to have tea
in the Music Room
like this?
Yeah. Don't sweat it,
it's fine!
Uh...
(nervous)
Um, Ma'am, this isn't--
I'll have milk
with my tea.
Huh?!
I'm Ms. Yamanaka,
your advisor.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
[Azusa]
Wow, she sure is pretty...
[Yamanaka]
I think she'd
look good in cat ears.
Have some sweets, too.
Sure!
They look just as good
as always!
[Yamanaka]
So, you have a new member.
Spring has come,
all right.
[Ritsu]
So, did you get yourself
a boyfriend yet?
Don't bring that up!
It's none of your business!
All right, sorry.
[Azusa]
This is the Light
Music Club, isn't it?
Oh, maybe they're testing me
to see if I have initiative.
(plays guitar)
QUIET!
Ah!
Uh...
(heavy breathing)
Ms. Yamanaka, you moron!
I just, I just wanted to
enjoy my tea in peace.
Maybe, but there's a
right way to say things.
(crying)
Hey, sorry. Ms. Yamanaka's
a little bit strange.
Heard that.
Don't let her get to you.
C'mon, let's eat some cake!
(crying)
Teatime is our main
selling point, after all.
(crying)
Azusa-chan?
It's not supposed to
be like this!
She's flipped out!
I'm don't sense any motivation
from any of you!
Um, well, our welcome show
is over, so--
That has nothing
to do with it!
It's wrong for you to
treat the Music Room
as your personal property!
You should get rid of
all these tea sets!
Ah!
No, please!
Anything but that!
You're a teacher!
How can you say that?!
Look, let's all
calm down, and--
How do you expect me
to be calm, huh?!
Uh?
That's a good girl...
Petting her isn't
going to calm her...
It calmed her down!
I'm so sorry
I lost my composure.
Oh, that's okay,
we don't mind at all.
That's a problem too.
No, Azusa, you have
a very good point.
Uh...
We really ought to show
a little more
motivation around here.
We clear on that?!
Yeah...
Mm-hm.
(sigh)
(screams)
I don't really want to go,
not after that scene
I caused...
Hi, everyone... Huh!
They aren't fazed at all!
Uh...
W-we were all just about
to start band practice!
Honest, we were!
(playing a few notes)
Uh...
That was fast!
I just don't have any energy
if I don't eat cake...
Here. Have a bite.
Hm? Aaah...
Oh!
She's good!
Ah...
Why don't you have some,
Azusa-chan.
It's really good.
Say "Ah"!
Uh...
Go on.
Um...
Aah...
Tasty.
Hm! What did say?
I said "wasty"!
A waste!
Haha...
Oh, I guess she really
didn't like it?
Oh...
Hm...
Try this.
Ah!
Oh...
Try it!
Ah!
Oh...
Interesting...
[girls]
Goodbye, Ms. Yamanaka!
[Yamanaka]
Goodbye, girls!
(sighs)
No more after-school teatime
in the Music Room
after today...
Nevertheless, I must act
like a teacher...!
...once in a while.
Hi, girls!
Are you practicing hard?
Oh come on, you're eating!
Mmm...
Now I can die happy.
Please don't.
So, tell me, why did
you decide against
getting rid of all
the tea sets?
W-well, because...
I thought it was wrong of me
to reject everything,
since I'm new.
-Oh!
-(sigh)
So, when did you start
playing guitar, Azusa-chan?
Let's see, around
4th grade, I guess.
My parents play
in a jazz band,
so I was really
influenced by that.
That means you're not
a beginner at all!
Hehe...
I'm curious what it was
that got you interested in
playing guitar, Yui-senpai?
(gulp)
Who, me?
(Whistling)
I can't say it!
I can't tell her I joined
because I thought the club
played lighthearted music!
Anyway, it sure is great
that a new member has
joined the club!
She dodged it!
Almost forgot!
I brought a welcome to the club
present for you, Azusa-chan!
Ah...
Ta-dah!
So, um, what exactly are those?
They're cat ears,
of course.
I can see that.
That's not what I meant.
What am I supposed
to do with them?
Hehehe...
It's okay, don't worry.
It's kind of a Light
Music Club ritual.
What kind of ritual?!
(grunt)
Goodness, you
embarrass so easily!
Of course I do!
The rest of you think this
is embarrassing, too, right?
So...?
Looks great!
That's our Mugi, all right!
Huh? Am I the
odd one out here?
[Yui]
Here. Now it's your
turn, Azusa-chan.
(nervous)
Um...
Oh!
Ah!
They look awesome on you!
When is comes to this stuff,
I'm never wrong.
The Light Music Club
welcomes you!
This was it!
Mmm...
Oh, Azusa-chan, you're so cute!
You know that?!
Try sounding like a cat,
"nya!" Like that!
N-nya...
(swooning)
I couldn't help it!
That's it! Your nickname
has to be Azu-nyan!
Uh?!
(girls excited)
K-ON!
[Yamanaka]
Next, put on this outfit!
You'll be a cat-eared maid!
No way!
Absolutely not!
But it'll look great!
I won't!
Azusa is so cute...
It's great that the object
of their teasing
is Azusa now instead of me...
...but this loneliness
that I'm feeling?
What is it?
What the heck have you
been talking about?
(Yui stretching)
That was so fun!
[Azusa]
I'm exhausted even though
we didn't practice at all.
Oops, I forgot something
back up in the Music Room.
okay. We'll go on ahead, then.
Yeah, okay.
Oh! There it is!
Hm?
(heart thumping)
(thumping louder)
Mm...
Hehehe...
Ah!
A m-moustache!
That's lame, Mio.
[Yui]
You know, Azu-nyan,
there's a fantastic
ice cream shop
really near where
my house is.
[Mugi]
Why don't we all go there!
Great idea!
It'll be my treat!
Um, okay.
No, no! You have to
answer "Nya!" Okay?
See, "Nya!"
N-nya!
Purr, purr,
purr, purr!
She's being
domesticated?
[Yui]
This is great!
It's delicious,
all right.
You've got some
on your cheek.
Uh...
Are you okay?
Do you think you can
handle our Club?
Yeah, I guess.
It's just to me the relaxed
atmosphere is kinda...
...you know.
Hehe...
It's okay.
You'll get used to it.
(Azusa laughs nervously)
I don't exactly want to.
[Ritsu]
So, what's the
emergency meeting about?
[Mio]
We have a brand new member,
so I think we're
asking for trouble
if we keep goofing off
like this all the time.
Y-you do?
If we keep this up,
Azusa might get
tired of it and quit!
Ah...
I don't want Azu-nyan
to stop coming!
Then have no choice.
We have to find some dirt--
OW!
Maybe we should try coming up
with a proper activities plan.
An activities plan?
She has a point.
For starters...
Oh! Let's throw a
welcome party for Azusa!
Good idea!
Sounds like fun!
Wait a minute!
(kids laughing)
[boy]
Coochie coochie coo!
(Yui laughing)
C'mon, Azu-nyan, eat up!
There's plenty!
We have cake, too.
And I brought this for you!
Cut that out!
Mmm...
Uh...
You like taiyaki?
Um-hm.
Hey! Watch where you're
throwing, you idiot!
You can do it, Ritchan!
(Azusa sighs)
Mio is a great bassist,
so why is she in such
an unmotivated club?
Hm? What is it?
Um, nothing.
Uh, Mio, do you
play in any bands
outside the
Light Music Club?
Oh...
Hm, playing in a band
outside the club
would be fun, all right.
Oh, are you sure you want to
be say things like that?
Oh! Wh-what's that
a picture of?!
Let me see it!
What is it?!
Is she being
blackmailed into staying?
The bunny look works, too.
Ah!
Hi, Ms. Yamanaka!
Sorry I'm late everyone.
I had a few things
to get together first.
Ta-dah!
Oh! It's so sweet!
Yeah.
Awesome as always.
Azu-nyan, if you don't
want to wear them,
we'll be happy to!
Th-that's not the problem...
[Yui]
That was so much fun!
[Ritsu]
So, where should we
go next time?
Why don't we
go to the zoo?
A hot spring
would be nice, too.
[Yui]
Oh! Good idea!
[Mugi]
Yes, it's a wonderful idea!
[Yamanaka]
You think so?
You really want to
go to one next time?
Listen up, everyone!
Oh?
We're the Light Music Club!
Starting tomorrow,
we're going to practice!
Is that clear?!
No ifs, ands, or buts!
You got it!
Mm-hmm!
[Ritsu]
Okay,
we're suppose to be
the Light Music Club,
even though you may
have all forgotten!
Yeah, well,
I remember just fine.
Today, we're gonna practice!
[Yui, Mugi, Yamanaka]
Yeah!
[Mio, Azusa]
Y-yeah...
[Ritsu]
Okay now, since we have
Yui and Azusa on guitar now,
that oughta widen
our range quite a bit.
Who wants to play
lead guitar?
Well, the lead guitarist
should be--
Me! Me!
I want to do it!
Where's this confidence
coming from?
Harumph!
(clears throat)
I suppose it would make
more sense to decide
after we hear you
both play.
(Yui moans)
Um, I guess I'll
go first, then.
(shredding on guitar)
Azusa is terrific.
She's a great player.
Okay, Yui--
I threw out my back!
Give it a rest, already!
Azu-nyan, please teach me
how to play guitar!
Whoa! She's quick on her feet!
(Yui playing)
[Azusa]
Um, I think you should
use muting on that part.
And I think that last phrase
would sound better
with a little vibrato.
Muting? Vibrato?
What are those?
Ah!
Believe it or not,
she's been playing
for a year now.
How can she get by without
knowing muting and vibrato?
(Yui playing)
Hey, wait. She's using
muting just fine.
Oh, that's what you call that?
So that's muting?
"Muting" is a
fingering technique
where you lightly
touch the strings
to dampen the notes
as you play them.
Yui is the type of person
who doesn't read the manual
when she buys a game.
I can see that.
(stretching)
Could you please put some
royal milk tea on for me?
Oh...
I'm sorry, but today we're
only going to practice.
(whining)
I suppose we can take
a little break.
Ah...
What about practice?!
We'll work harder
starting tomorrow.
(sigh)
Azu-nyan!
Now say "Ah"!
[Mugi]
I have a personal cup
for you, Azusa-chan.
[Azusa]
This will ruin me.
If I stay here,
it will ruin me!
*(melancholy music)*
I should play in other bands
outside the Light Music Club.
There have to be other
great bands out there.
I don't get it.
All these other bands
are better than
the Light Music Club.
(audience cheering)
So why?
Azu-nyan hasn't come
in a while.
She might not come back.
Azusa! Why haven't you
come to the club lately?!
We've been practicing every
day since you were here last!
We've been waiting
for you to come back!
Uh... Something wrong?
You didn't just come to
tell us that you're quitting?
No way, please,
anything but that!
(crying)
I don't know anymore...
Huh?
I don't know why I wanted to
join your club anymore.
Or why your show touched me
so much in the way it did.
I thought that I could
figure it out
if I hung around you
for a little while...
...but I just don't
know anymore!
Azu-nyan...
(sobbing)
Right! Let's play a number
for Azusa, then!
Let's make her remember what she
was feeling that day, okay?!
Mm-hm!
(playing music)
Huh?
[Azusa]
Yui-senpai hardly knows
any musical lingo at all.
Ritsu's drumming
is always kind of wild.
So why are their songs so good
when the four of them
play together?
Why?
Azusa.
You asked me the other day
why I don't play in bands
outside the club, remember?
Uh, yeah.
I think it's because
I love being in a band
with these girls.
I bet the others
feel the same.
I think that's why we all
play so well together.
Uh!
C'mon! Play a song
with us, Azusa!
Uh...
All right! I really want to
play music with you guys!
I really do!
Oh, what a relief!
Now, I know there's
gonna be times
when we're gonna slack off
and drink tea or whatever,
but I think that time
is crucial for us.
(gulp)
I'm so burned out...
I don't think
I'm gonna want to play
for at least a whole week...
Are they serious?
Probably.
[Yui]
Azu-nyan, why don't you
try on those cat ears!
[Azusa]
Huh? What? No way!
[Yui]
Please? It'll make me
try harder!
[Azusa]
Oh.
[Yui]
The power of cute compels you!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Ritsu]
It must be rough
to be a teacher
and working during
summer break...
[Yamanaka]
Yeah, we have to go to
seminars and whatnot...
Are you guys practicing?
[Yui] Yeah!
[Yamanaka]
Did you want something?
[Ritsu]
The Light Music Club is
gonna have a training camp.
[Yui]
We were all wondering
if you wanted to come.
A training camp, huh?
[Ritsu]
She doesn't look too thrilled
about it, does she?
[Azusa]
Are we ever gonna get
around to practicing?
[Yui]
Azu-nyan!
[Ritsu]
Gimme the cabbage!