[Nodoka]
Yui.
Oh! Hi, Nodoka!
Wanna walk home with me?
Oh, no, I'm sorry Nodoka.
There's a club meeting
I have to go to today.
Oh, really? I guess I'll
have to walk by myself.
She's finally found
something she can get into.
I'm happy and sad
at the same time.
Ahh...
What's wrong, Yui?
Mugi says
she gonna bring
some tasty
snacks today!
You're not going
to play guitar?
Hm?
Hee, hee.
(Sigh)
[Yui]
It was like this even
in kindergarten...
Hm?
And grade school, too.
Even when we got
into middle school,
Your ice cream.
my life has always
been kinda unfocused.
But now that I finally
made it to high school...
I've joined a club
for the first time!
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
Hey, everyone!
[Yui]
These three are my fellow
Light Music Club members.
Hello.
This is Mio Akiyama,
our bassist.
(playing bass)
She's tall, and pretty,
and gives off a real
"cool grown woman" vibe.
Hey, Mio, how come you decided
to take up playing bass
instead of a regular guitar?
Hmm...
Playing guitar is...
well... embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Ya' know, the guitar is the
core instrument of the band,
and because of that,
you have to play right up
in front of the group.
So the eyes of everyone
in the audience are on you.
Just thinking about being in a
position like that, makes me...
Oh!
Mio!
Mio is kinda delicate.
Mio, are you all right?
This is our
keyboardist,
Tsumugi Kotobuki.
(Plays keyboard)
We call her "Mugi" for short.
She's calm, soothing,
and really, really nice.
Ya' know, you're a terrific
keyboard player, Mugi.
I'll bet you've been
playing for a long time.
I started studying the piano
when I was only four years old.
I've even managed to win a few
awards at some competitions.
Oh, wow! That's amazing!
Why did she join
the Light Music Club?
[Mugi]
All right, dig in everyone.
Oh, I almost forgot, I've been
meaning to ask you something.
This club room is really nice
and very well equipped.
Are all high schools in the
area like this nowadays?
Oh, no, I brought all that
stuff from my house.
It's yours?!
Yes.
Mugi is definitely
one of those
"rich girl" types.
Our drummers name is,
Ritsu Tainaka.
(Playing drums)
She's a cheerful girl
who's just full of energy.
You really seem like someone
who would be a drummer.
What?!
I've got a completely
legitimate reason for that!
A powerful reason that moves
almost everybody that hears it!
What?! Tell me!
Tell me! Come on!
It's because...
Hmm...?
Well, you know, it's...
cause they're cool.
That's it?
Ugh! Oh, come on!
Just imagining having to
wriggling my fingers like crazy
just to play a guitar,
bass, or keyboard...
...makes me wanna scream!
I really hate it!
Wow, I guess your
choice of instruments
reflects your personality?
*
[Mugi]
Would you like another one?
Yes, thank you!
So you first wanted to
join the Choir Club,
but joined ours instead?
That's right.
You see, I wanted to pick a club
where I could make friends with
the sort of fun, pleasant
people that one so rarely meets.
[Both]
We're like rare animals to her?
That reminds me, Miss Hirasawa,
have you bought your guitar yet?
Just call me Yui.
(Gasp)
After all, I already call you by
your first name, right, Mio?
(Nervous gasp)
Y-Yui?
Oh...
That's so cute!
So what about
your guitar, Yui?
Huh?
Guitar?
Oh, yeah, that's right!
I forgot!
I'm supposed to play
guitar, aren't I?
Yeah, well, this is
the Light Music Club.
Eh-hehe...
Do you know how much a guitar's
going to cost? A lot?
Hmm...
Well, the cheap ones start
way down in the low hundreds,
but believe me, you really don't
want one that's TOO cheap.
Something around 500
should be fine.
Whoa, that much?!
500 dollars is
ten months' allowance...
Yeah, well, expensive guitars
can run up into the thousands.
Can I use club funds?
Nothing doing!
(Groans)
Uh...
Here, try one,
they're delicious.
(Sighs)
Mmm... Ah!
Anyway, we can't do anything
if you don't have an instrument.
Right, then! Let's go check out
guitars on our next day off!
Go!
(Giggles)
(Change falling)
(Sigh)
'Tis vexing...
(Knocking on door)
Yes?
Hey, come on, Sis,
dinner's ready.
Ui...
What's wrong, Big Sis?
I joined the
Light Music Club.
Really?!
So, I want to buy
a guitar I can use.
Wow, I didn't even know
you could play the guitar!
I can't!
(Gasp)
So anyway,
do you think maybe you
could lend me some money?
I'll pay you back.
I'm sorry, but I don't have
a whole lot of money either.
Yeah, I figured...
Hey, why don't you
just ask Mom
for an advance
on your allowance?
Huh?
I'll even go with you
if you want me too,
to back you up.
Little Sis, I can
always count on you!
Hehehe...
Oh, Yui! Hey!
Over here! Over here!
Hm? Oh! Hey, guys!
Ugh!
Ow! Sorry!
Huh? Hehe....
[Mio]
She's got like ten feet away.
[Ritsu]
She can't make it
the rest of the way?
Who's a good boy?
Who's a good doggie?
[Ritsu]
Did the money situation
work out?
[Yui]
I begged my mom and
I got her to give me
a 500 dollar advance
on my allowance.
I have to be real careful with
my spending from now on...
And make sure I
don't waste money...
I can buy this now!
Come on, Yui!
Oh, I'm just looking!
Uh...
*
Boy, I'm exhausted!
I stocked up!
Wow, this was fun, wasn't it?
So where do you guys
want to go next?
Wait a sec...
Are we forgetting something?
Your instrument, dummy!
Whoa! Jeez, I forget!
Oh, wow!
Look at all the guitars!
Oh...
Huh?
Hmm?
Hey, hey!
[Mio]
Yui! See anything that you like?
Huh?
Hmm...
Are there guidelines or
something to choose by?
Of course there are.
There's the tone of the guitar,
but there's also its weight,
composition,
and the shape and
thickness of the neck.
So for girls, one with
a slender neck would be-
Ah! This guitar
here is cute!
[Mio]
She never listens...
(Giggles)
That guitar costs
2,500 dollars.
Huh?
Wow, it does!
Oh, but that's way, way more
than I can afford.
Do you have your heart
set on this one?
Uh-huh.
Oh...
Uh, there's some
cheap ones over there.
Huh?
(Sighs)
I really want this one,
though...
This reminds me of how badly
I wanted my current bass.
I agonized over it.
I-I'd like this one!
And I haggled like crazy when
I bought my used drum set.
You can do better!
Now, try again!
You made the salesman cry.
Yeah, well, I wasn't leaving
the store without those drums.
Um, what is "haggling"?
It's when you use grit
and determination
to force someone to lower
the price on something
you really want!
That is amazing!
It's almost admirable!
What's so admirable about it?
Uh...
Yui...
Ah! Got it!
Let's all get a temp job!
Temp job?
Um-hm! So we can help
Yui buy her guitar!
Huh?! No, I can't
let you do that!
Don't sweat it, this will be
a "club activity"!
Oh, Ritchan...
I'll try it. It could be fun.
Mugi-chan?
All right! Let's get to it!
Go!
[Ritsu] Gooo!
[Mugi] Gooo!
[Mio]
What kind of job are
we talking about?
[Yui]
K-ON!
[Nodoka]
A job?
Yeah, so I can buy a guitar!
When did she become
so self-sufficient?
I'm happy and sad
at the same time.
The rest of the Light Music Club
has offered to help me get it.
What? You got
the others involved?
Yeah!
(School bells)
So, what kind of job
should we get?
We could hand out
packs of tissues?
(Sighs)
Uh...
I-I can't...
[Mugi]
What about a fast food job?
W-welcome, can I take
your order?!
That's a problem.
Oh, right. That might be kind
of a tough hurdle for you, Mio.
I couldn't push the button
if I thought somebody scary
would answer.
I can't go and take orders!
Oh!
Ah! Miss Mio!
[Yui]
Oh, please, don't push
yourself on my account!
(Sighs)
I keep telling myself I can't
do it before I even try.
This is so Yui
can buy a guitar!
So it's for the greater good
of the Light Music Club!
I have to overcome
my limitations!
Oh...
Name the job!
I'll do anything!
Oh!
Wh-what?
What is it?!
How about this?
[All]
"Traffic Volume Survey"?
We have to count the number of
people and cars that pass by us.
We do it using a counter.
Like the Wild Bird Society!
This is a job
even Mio can do!
[Mugi]
Yes, you're right!
Hm!
[Yui]
See you later!
[Ui]
Wait, Sis!
Don't forget your lunch!
Whoa, why so much?
I made lunch for everyone else
in the Light Music Club, too.
I mean, after all they took
this job to help you, right?
Yeah, thanks, Ui!
[Ritsu]
Here.
Now, we'll work in pairs
and trade off every hour.
Oh!
(Clicking)
Goodness, you're nimble.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, looks like a challenge!
Whoa, you're really
fast, Ritchan!
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ow!
Ugh! Finger cramp!
That's what happens when
you get worked up.
You know, we have a bit of time
before the survey starts.
I think we should all
go have some tea.
Yeah, let's go have a picnic!
You guys really
worry me sometimes.
(Click)
This weather sure feels nice
today, doesn't it, Mugi?
Yes, it does.
(Breeze blowing)
Oh!
Ah...
[Yui]
She's like a
highlands princess!
Huh?
A magazine giveaway?
One of the prizes
is a guitar.
That might just be the fastest
way to get it, all right.
Could be?
Mugi, you aren't tired at all?
No, I feel fine.
And your thumb
doesn't hurt either?
Uh-uh.
(Click)
You aren't sleepy?
Oh!
Hm?
I just pressed the
button on the counter
instead of
answering you!
Hehe...
(Click)
(Clicking)
Uh?
She's playing a four beat.
And that's an eight beat.
Keep your mind
on the job!
Mugi, these sweets are
really great and all,
but is it okay
for us to keep
eating this fancy
food all the time?
[Mugi]
Oh, it's fine.
All sorts of people give
me these all the time.
If I left them at home,
it would only go to waste.
[Yui]
People bring your family
enough sweets to go to waste?
What kind of family are you?!
[Ritsu]
I'm counting the clouds!
[Mio]
Is this an
occupational sickness?
[Ritsu]
That's a wrap for day one!
Well, I'll be off for
the station, then.
Mio and I are
going by bus.
You said you're
walking home, right, Yui?
Hm-mh!
Tomorrow, let's--
Yeah! Let's eat some more
of those great sweets!
Hm?!
I was going to say,
"Tomorrow, let's all
work hard again."
You better watch it.
But if they'll just
go to waste, then...
Watch it. Watch it.
Watch it.
It is an occupational sickness.
Bye! See ya!
[Ritsu] Sure.
[Mio] Bye!
[Mugi] See you tomorrow.
Oh!
[Yui]
Hey, guys!
Thanks for everything,
I mean it!
I promise, when I
finally get my guitar,
I'm gonna practice every day!
(Giggles)
*
(Traffic passing)
(Clicking)
(Yawn)
(Groans)
[Woman]
Thank you for two days
of hard work.
Ma'am, the pleasure
was all ours!
[Mugi]
Here.
So, eighty dollars
per day, huh?
Even with the 500 dollar
advance your mother gave you,
that's still
nowhere near enough.
Guess we'll have to work
a few more jobs, then.
You're right, Miss Mio.
[Mio]
Okay, guess I'll hit
the want ads again.
[Ritsu]
Right.
I just can't take
this money from you.
Please, I want you to spend
the money that you earned
on yourselves.
But, Yui?
I'll buy myself a guitar
all on my own.
[Ritsu] Yui...
I want to get the guitar and
start practicing right away,
so I can play with you guys.
Would you mind going out
to the music store
with me again tomorrow?
Hm-mh!
Thanks for everything, guys!
I better go home now.
See you tomorrow, Yui.
Goodbye.
'Bye, guys!
I have to get good fast,
for me and them.
Well, I'd best be
heading home, too.
Hm-hm.
Oh?
Huh?
[Ritsu]
Oh, man.
I think Yui's losing it.
(Guitars playing in background)
Huh?
(Yui sighs)
Oh!
Eh-heh...
She really wants that badly.
Okay! Then let's get
another job!
Oh!
Wait right here, okay?
Hi, excuse me.
Yes?
Would you mind terribly
if I haggled?
Huh...?
Could you see your way to
lowering a price on a guitar?
Uh...
Ah!
Y-you're the company
president's daughter?!
Ah! Uh...! Hm...!
Perhaps...
I could go this low?
Hm.
No, try again!
He says he will sell you
this guitar for 500 dollars.
Serious?!
What?! What did you do?!
The thing is, this store
is in my family's
business consortium.
(Gasps)
Really, is that so? Wow!
Mugi, I don't know
how to thank you!
I'll pay you back
the rest, I promise!
Hehehe...
Oh, it's so cute!
(Laughs and giggles)
Twaaaaang!
Oh! I look like a rocker!
Hehe...
Oh! I gotta practice
signing my autograph!
(Door opens)
Huh?
Big Sis, could you
keep it down...
Hey, Sis, if you
don't get up soon,
you'll be late for school!
Big Sister?
Uh...?
She slept with it...
Hm!
Oh, yeah!
Awesome!
Wow, that guitar looks like
it belongs on you.
Try playing something!
Uh...
(Playing scales)
(Groans)
You really haven't practiced
at all yet, have you?
Well, the guitar is all
bright and shiny and new
and everything,
And I guess, I'm just a
little scared to touch it.
Yeah, I can totally
relate to that.
I posed in front of
the mirror with it,
and then took a lot
of pictures of it,
and slept all night
with it though.
So play it.
You haven't even taken
the film off of it yet.
Ahh....
HIYAAA!
(Traumatized)
I couldn't help myself.
Ritsu, apologize!
I'm sorry!
I acted on impulse!
Please, forgive me!
Here, why don't you
have a snack.
Oh, something like that won't--
It made her feel better!
No, you're right.
The purpose of a guitar
is to be played by someone.
And so, it's not right to just
admire it and never use it.
Ah!
Thanks for that, Ritsu!
I really needed
that motivation!
It was?!
Well, I was kinda hoping
it would give you
the urge to practice.
Boy, I'm goo-- OW!
So, shall we practice, then?
How do I get the guitar to
sound like they do in a concert?
You've just got to
hook it up to an amp.
Ready!
(Loud strum)
Heh!
That was awesome!
It's finally started...
We've got our
Light Music Club.
Indeed.
All right Budokan,
here we come!
(Crowd cheers)
By the time we graduate!
[Mio and Mugi]
Uh...?
(Playing scales)
I'm sorry. That's all
I can play right now.
I guess I should
learn a lot more
before I try playing
with an amp.
Ah! Be careful!
Huh?!
(Loud feedback)
That's what happens when you
pull out the guitar cord
before you turn the amp
all the way down...
You could've said
something sooner...
(Sighs)
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
Ah! We've got
midterm exams?!
Is that a
chord, too?
I don't get it, Yui.
Why didn't you study?
Well I really had
planned to, but I...
Come on, when you
study for a test,
don't you ever end up fixating
on everything BUT studying?
Oh, look at that!
It's sweet bean jelly!
*