Let's see...
Hmm...
(typing)
(train pulling up)
Hm?
(sigh)
(cat meows)
(hiss)
Uh...
(yawn)
(humming)
It sure is cold
today, huh, Ui?
Yeah.
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
(door opens)
I'm freezing!
[Mugi]
Hm?
(Yui shivers)
It's so cold!
Ritchan, aren't you cold?
Oh, yes!
It is most frigid, indeed!
Yes, indeed it is!
Huh?
Ritchan...
Hm?
Whack!
Wow, your cheeks are
really warm, Ritchan!
What's the big idea?!
All right, then!
Cold! Cold!
(laughing)
(strum)
It's so cold
I can't play Geeta!
I've got a great idea!
I'll try playing
with my gloves on!
Yeah, that's gonna work...
I'm ready!
Here we go...
Let's see...
Ah! I can't hold the pick!
Oh! They're catching on
the strings!
You're bad gloves!
Wasn't it obvious?
Right, Ritsu?
Ritsu?
Ritsu, is something the matter?
Ritchan?
Huh?
What's the matter?
Mm... Uh, it's nothing!
Check it! Moustache!
Ah! Ritchan, that's sneaky!
I'll try, too! Moustache!
Wrong! That looks nothing
like a moustache!
Like this, Senpai?
(laughing)
Waaa...
Handy! I'm sorry
I got mad at you!
You named your gloves, too?
You know, I think this is
all winter's fault.
Oh, come on.
You shouldn't blame winter.
You know what?
I think you're right!
There's lots of fun things for
us to do on cold winter days!
I know! Come over to my place
on Sunday for a hot pot party!
[Girls]
Uh...
Huh?
I'm sorry, but I already
have plans that day.
[Ritsu]
Me, too.
I told my kid brother
that I'd take him out
to the movies on Sunday.
And I don't think
that I'll be able to
leave the house at all
this weekend.
Aww...
What about you, Mio-chan?
I can't come, either.
I want to write some
new lyrics this weekend.
Aw...
Sorry, but you and Ritsu
are always bothering me,
so I can never concentrate
when I'm here.
See?
Oh!
(nervous giggle)
We apologize for
being insensitive.
Oh, well then.
I guess it'll just be me, Ui,
and Geeta for the party.
Try not to get your
guitar dirty, okay?
Don't forget, you just
had it worked on recently.
That won't be a problem!
I'm gonna put a bib on him
before he eats!
Guess that's all right, then.
You gotta have a hot pot
party in the winter.
Ooo.. It's full-on winter
now, huh, Ritchan?
These gloves that I got from
Ui are all nice 'n warm!
That kid sure has
her act together.
[Ritsu]
I wish I had a
sister like her.
(Yui giggles)
[Ritsu]
I'm green with
jealousy, you know!
Um... Wait!
Huh?
Yeah, what's up, Mugi-chan?
I have to bow out today.
Do you have plans?
Um, sort of... Bye!
I wonder what's up
with Mugi-chan?
Think she's going to
meet up with someone?
With a boyfriend, maybe?
Oh! I can see how Mugi-chan
would be popular with the boys!
Yeah!
[Ritsu]
Later!
[Yui]
See you next week!
[Azusa]
I'm off.
Senpai?
Yes, what?
Sorry, but I have to
go buy something
by the station
on the way home.
Oh, what'cha gonna buy?
Um. Just some toys.
Nothing special.
Oh, some toys?
Maybe I'll tag along...
No, it's fine!
You don't have to go!
I'll just see you later.
Bye, Azusa!
(stomach growling)
Huh?
[Mio]
Ritsu, about that thing
the other day.
Mm...
Ritsu?
Huh? You say something?
What's the matter?
Nothing at all!
Gosh, it sure is cold, isn't it?
Hehe...
I'm starving, Mio!
Hm?
[Clerk]
Thank you, come again!
Nothing beats a piping hot
meat bun! Hehe...
Oh! Freezing!
(sigh)
Ooo... So cold...
[Jun]
Azusa!
Could you please look after
my family's cat this weekend?
Huh?
My aunt was supposed
to watch her,
but she came down with a cold
and has to stay in bed.
She's still just a kitten,
so I'm worried about
leaving her alone.
But I've never
taken care of a cat.
Oh. I should have known...
But if there's no one else
that you can ask...
Really?!
Wanna play?
(meow)
Ah! Uh...
Go ahead.
A-alright!
Ah...
I did it!
Okay, let's start off
with the cleaning.
Right! I'm eager to learn!
(music playing)
Hey, Sis!
C'mon, get out of bed!
(groan)
Sis!
"On winter days, I am happy
no matter how cold it is."
"When I see you
running towards me,
panting out white
puffs of breath,"
"your neatly trimmed hair
suits you well."
"But then again,
I'd also like to see you
with your bangs hanging down."
Hm...
Looks goofy...
Hey, Sis, you ready yet?!
Uh... I'll be
right there! Geez!
Oh!
(door closes)
Uh...
(yawn)
(stretching)
Uh...
(meow)
You're Azu-nyan #2.
Allow me to read
your order back to you.
You ordered one cheeseburger
with everything
and two medium colas,
is that right, sir?
Don't forget to smile!
And sir, would you be wanting
fries with that order?
Sure, I'll take some fries, too.
Thank you very much, sir!
(giggles)
Just like that.
Right!
Right... I'll get some
killer lyrics here!
Oh, no one's coming?
No.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah. I know.
Why don't we invent some
new hot pot recipes today,
for the next time
everybody comes over!
That's awfully
forward-thinking of you, Sis!
How about a marshmallow
soy milk hot pot
or a chocolate curry hot pot?
Maybe we shouldn't fly too high
too fast, okay, sis?
Huh?
Who knows, they
might taste good!
Sis, why don't we buy some
strawberry milk today?
Ah! Ui, you're so generous!
(giggles)
K-ON!
It's cold!
Lyrics aren't
coming to me at all.
Maybe I should've gone to
Yui's hot pot party.
But it sounded like everybody
else already had plans...
I wonder what everyone's up to?
It's freezing!
I thought we were having a
global warming crisis!
Dummy, it's supposed to
be cold in the winter.
You know, you're such a wimp.
I wish the girls in your
class could see you now.
Come on, cut me
some slack, Sis...
Oh, wait...
What?
Hmm...
-Whack!
-Ah!
Nice 'n warm!
[Boy]
Hey, Tainaka!
Huh?
How's it going?
Oh, hello.
Cold, isn't it?
I'm on my way over to
Suzuki's house. Wanna come?
Yeah, sure!
Can I? Please, Sis?
Hmm...
Yeah. Just don't
stay out too late.
(laughing)
[Boy]
See ya' later!
Where did you go?
[Satoshi]
To see a movie.
[Boy]
How was it?
[Satoshi]
It was pretty good, I guess.
Uh...
[Mugi]
Thank you for waiting, Miss!
I'm sorry, but I ordered a hot
coffee, not a big soft drink.
Uh... Eh...
I'm sorry,
I'll exchange it right away!
Ah! Oh!
Oh, sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It's okay, don't worry.
What drink did you need?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
What's the matter?
What is it?!
Azu-nyan #2!
Was that...
Was that really...
a love letter?
(phone rings)
Hm?
Maybe I should go home...
(phone rings)
Hm?
I messed up...
I thought I could do it,
but I messed up!
(phone rings)
What should I do?
What should I do?!
(phone rings)
Eh?
[Yui]
Which hot pot would you
rather try,
marshmallow soy milk
or chocolate curry?
Huh?
That's a hot pot?
Strange!
Boy that's weird,
nobody's answering...
(phone rings)
Oh, it's Azu-nyan!
Hello there! Azu-nyan?
[Azusa]
Please don't send out weird
texts at a time like this!
At a time like what?
It's a kitten!
It's this cat that a friend
asked me to look after!
What's wrong with it?
I really have no idea,
but something seems to
be wrong with her.
And nobody's at home
right now...
and I... and I...
I don't know what to do!
Understood! Try to stay calm,
Azu-nyan, we'll be right there!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to cause such a fuss.
I'm just glad that nothing's
wrong with Azu-nyan #2.
I had no idea that cats
threw up hairballs all the time.
Open wide!
For you, Azu-nyan!
Hmm...
I guess they might taste better
when you eat them as they are.
Of course they do!
Oh, look! I've got texts
from the rest of the guys!
Ah! Mugi-chan has a job?!
Oh! Mio-chan went all the way
out to the beach!
Ritchan wants to know
where we are.
"We're at Azu-nyan's place."
How can I help you?
What a surprise! Mugi-chan
started work at a real job!
Our Mugi sure is growing up!
Yep!
Azusa!
Did Jun come over
and get her cat
from you already?
Mm-hm.
That's really good news.
So, I gather you spend
your day cat-sitting?
(giggle)
Oh, Mio-chan, welcome back!
Write anything good?
Looks like that's a no, huh?.
But that's kinda cool, though,
jetting off to a windswept
winter beach like that!
You guys are so awesome!
Don't grow up and
leave me behind, okay?
You haven't changed at all,
right, Ritchan?
I've too changed!
Huh? What?
What did you change?
Just forget about it.
It's nothing.
Oh, that reminds me, Ritsu...
Reminds you?
What did you think
of those lyrics
that I left in your mailbox?
Did you like them?
Huh? Lyrics?
Yeah. I tried writing them all
out on my computer this time.
Then... you were
the one who left them...
Huh? Yeah.
Uh...
Aaahhh!
You wrote that stuff?!
That was you?!
I TOLD you I was going to
leave it in your mailbox!
Don't do old fashioned stuff
like that in this day and age!
Aw, come on, Ritchan,
let's eat our hamburgers
before they get cold.
'Kay?
Thank you very much
for coming miss!
Oh...
[Mio]
Huh?!
Oh! Hey, what's the
matter, Mio-chan?
Well, my bass is
still really cold,
and when it touched
my thigh, I just...
Oh! Do it again!
It was really cute!
Forget it.
You never seem
to have any problems
playing your keyboard,
do you, Mugi?
Huh?
Don't your hands get
numb from the cold?
Well, no,
they're just fine.
They're so warm!
Let me see!
Wow, you're right!
I've always had a
high body temperature.
You're so lucky!
I wish we could install
one of you at our house!
Azu-nyan, you should come
here and feel this!
Uh...
No thanks, I'll pass.
She really is warm!
Here!
Oh, I suppose if you insist...
Wow, you're right,
they're really warm!
You know, your hands are
so tiny and cute, Azu-nyan!
And I'm just a simple girl with
man hands and a cold heart...
Ugh! Are you still
hung up on that!
They say people with cold hands
have warm hearts, Mio-chan.
Mugi, what are you doing?
Uh...
Mugi-chan, your hands and
heart are both really warm!
Ah...
[Yui]
This is so warm!
Yeah, this is nice and warm...
Winter's not so bad.
Mugi-senpai, how long do you
plan to keep working?
At least until New Year's.
We'll visit you
at work again, okay?
Mio, we're never using those
lyrics you gave me, got it?
What? Why not?!
Hey, do you think it costs lots
of money to rent the Budokan?
Wait a minute!
You want to rent it?!
Well if we don't, we can't
play a big show there, right?
It's best to have
big dreams.
We'll stand on
that stage some day!
[Mio]
Well, we better practice
a lot more, then.
[Azusa]
That's right!
We have to practice!
And we'll never play there
if we don't go pro.
[Ritsu]
You two are hardcore
realists, aren't you?
[Yui]
I, for one, am gonna
work hard, Ritchan!
[Mugi]
Let's work hard!
[All]
Yeah!
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
A live house?
Yeah! Yeah! An old friend of
mine from middle school
invited us to come
and play a show there.
But this says here that the
show is on New Year's Eve.
That's only ten days from now.
But we really don't
have anything ready.
Aw, but it sounds like fun!
I'd really love to
give it a shot!
Me too!
Geeta, let's do our best
together tomorrow, okay?
I just know this is
gonna be a lot of fun!