[Ui]
Hello, Ui Hirasawa here.
I'm hanging out with Azusa-chan
for the first time today.
[Azusa]
Hey!
Azusa!
Sorry!
What a cute outfit!
(giggles)
Oh, you're going to that
training camp
with the Light Music
Club, aren't you?
I am. It's three days
and four nights.
My sister said that the one
they all went to last year
turned out to be
a lot of fun.
A lot of fun?
Ah...
I bet she meant they practiced
the whole time, doesn't she?
Hm? Uh... yeah.
I think so.
Huh? Ui! Isn't this cute?!
Mmhm.
[Azusa]
Oh, I see.
After all, the four of them
play so amazing well together.
They must practice
a lot there...
Right?
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
What's my sister like when
she's at the Light Music Club?
Well, I guess she's kinda...
Tell me!
She really doesn't
practice at all,
and she gave me a
pretty weird nickname...
Azu-nyan!
and she's all touchy-feely
all the time.
Yeah, my sister really is
warm and sweet, isn't she?
Um, that wasn't exactly
what I meant.
Huh?
So, what is Yui-senpai
doing today?
She's at home.
Sis doesn't handle
heat very well.
She hates air-conditioning, too.
I can picture her
sprawled out on the floor.
She's been lying around
the house all day lately.
Talk about lazy...
But she's so cute when
she's lying around!
She's adorable!
Ui! Ui!
Uiuiuiuiui, Ui!
Why do Ui and I see
her sister so differently?
You know, lately
I've been wishing
I had a big sister
who was a lot like Mio.
Yeah, I think she's
really nice, and cool, too.
What about Ritsu?
Hmm...
Well, she's awfully
irresponsible
and completely unfocused.
I'll pass.
Oh... who's unfocused?
Ah!
-Hello, Ritsu. Nice to see you.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
[Ritsu]
Hey. I saw you two from outside
and decided to come in.
- So, you're by yourself today?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Mmhm, Mio's off taking
some summer classes.
You mean you don't have to
go to any, Ritsu-senpai?
What? Who, me?
Summer classes? What for?
What was I thinking?
Oh, that reminds me.
I've been meaning to
ask you something.
Mugi-senpai brings her own
tea sets to the club room
and fancy cakes and
has vacation homes.
Does she come from
a really rich family?
That's for sure!
She even has a butler at home,
and her family even leaves
the country sometimes
to go on long vacations!
They really do that?
It'd sure be cool
if they did, huh?
So you don't know for sure.
Hey, why don't we
give her a call
and go hang out over at
her place for a while!
Wait. Are you sure?
It's kind of short notice.
(phone ringing)
That's weird, she's not
answering her cell.
I guess I'll try
her home number.
(dialing)
Hmmm...
(phone ringing)
(male voice)
Yes, hello?
Somebody picked up.
Hi! Is this Tsumugi's dad
I'm speaking to?
No, I am in the employ of the
Kotobuki family as their butler.
Whoa! They really have a butler!
Um, well, um, would Tsumugi
happen to be at home right now?
Senpai, just calm down!
I've very sorry,
but I'm afraid Miss Tsumugi
is summering in Finland
at the moment.
Oh, she is?
Thank you very much then!
Sorry to have bothered you!
See! Told you!
It's just exactly like I said.
Oh!
(Ritsu groans)
I'm exhausted for some reason...
Want to come over to my house?
We have a nice watermelon.
Count me in!
I'm home!
You here Sis?
Watermelon...
Ritsu and Azusa-chan
decided to come over.
Welcome home, Ui...
[Ritsu]
It's strangely soothing...
[Azusa]
It's just like she said...
Hello! Excuse us!
[Yui]
There she is!
[Ritsu]
It must be rough
to be a teacher,
and working during
summer break...
[Yamanaka]
Yeah, we have to go to
seminars and whatnot...
Are you guys practicing?
[Yui]
Yeah!
Did you want something?
[Ritsu]
The Light Music Club is gonna
have a training camp...
[Yui]
...and we were all wondering
if you wanted to come.
A training camp, huh?
[Ritsu]
She doesn't look too thrilled
about it, does she...
Well, fine, I guess,
we'll just go by ourselves.
She gets mad when
we don't ask her,
and when we do,
this is her response!
Too bad, she could've gone
swimming and had a barbecue.
Huh?!
I can't wait for
this training camp!
All right!
This is our first time
together for a while,
so why don't we go buy stuff
for the training camp?
Hey, by the way, what are we
all here to buy today?
Some brand new gear
for the band?
Well, uh...
Cute swimsuits!
They're ready to goof off!
I had a feeling something
like this would happen.
Hey, we're not gonna play
around the whole time.
I can't trust you guys!
How come?!
Hey, we'll have to take
some breaks, too. Right?
Hm? Oh, yeah.
I hadn't thought of that.
(giggles)
[Ritsu]
What's this loneliness
I'm feeling?
Oh!
[Ritsu]
This one's even more awesome
than the last one!
This is the vacation home
you said you couldn't
borrow for us last year?
No, I'm sorry.
That home wasn't available
for us this year, either.
I find this one
rather cramped,
but we'll just have to
put up with it.
You have an even
bigger one?!
Oh, yeah,
let's have some fun!
Yeah!
Hey!
No playing until
after we practice!
Aw...
We wanna have fun!
All right, majority rules, then.
I vote that we
practice first.
Play first!
I want to practice.
I vote for playing.
[Mio]
An unexpected betrayal!
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
[Azusa]
When Mugi-senpai
says "playing,"
I wonder if she means...
I'm flying!
Yes, yes, yes!
Naw, that could never happen...
Huh?
[Mugi]
I told you I didn't need
this stuff, didn't I!
You are to get rid of everything
on the beach this instant!
I don't want the yacht, either!
Mugi...
Senpai...
Catch!
(laughing)
(sighs)
Back and forth,
back and forth!
Are we ever gonna get
around to practicing?
Azu-nyan!
Why don;t you come and
play with us, Azu-nyan!
No, thank you.
I see. You must be pretty
bad at sports, huh?
Uh! I am not!
Bring it on and
you'll see what I can do.
(camera clicks)
Azusa has fit in with the club,
just fine, hasn't she?
I suppose.
[Yui]
Dr. Ritchan, you should
look at this right away!
[Ritsu]
A star-sharped extraterrestrial!
[Azusa] Hey, Mio.
You know that old story about
corn barnacles, don't you?
A long time ago, a boy cut
his foot on a corn barnacle-
(Mio screams)
Uh, Mio...
What's the matter?
Mio?
Hehe!
(giggling)
[Yui]
You gotta move up some more!
(laughing)
Wo-hoo!
(clapping)
Ah!
- [Yui] Gimme!
- [Azusa] No!
(scared)
[Ritsu]
Mio!
(laughing)
I don't know what got into me-
Mm...
[Yui]
Where am I?
A desert island?
(groaning)
Wake up, Ritchan!
Yui...
Oh!
Y-Yui!
Ritchan!
We did it! We made it!
We got to the new world!
-Zipangu! The land of gold!
-What the heck are they doing?
We're all played out...
Let's all go eat and
then call it a night.
What about
band practice?
I knew it!
I knew we should've practiced
instead of playing
around out here!
But you played more
than anybody, Azusa.
You're all sunburnt.
Well, I'm gonna go
practice, too!
All night long?
I will!
K-ON!
[Ritsu]
I'm beat. And I'm starving too.
[Mio]
Suck it up.
This is awesome!
It's awesome, all right...
I've never used an amp
like that before!
Mio, let's hurry up
and practice!
These snares are brand new!
Talk about
self-serving.
(tuning up)
Azu-nyan, what's that thing?
What? Oh, this?
It's just an electronic tuner.
Really.
What do you use a tuner for?
You use it to
tune your guitar.
Wait a minute. You've never
seen a tuner before?
Nope, this is
the first one.
How do you tune
your guitar, then?
Huh? I do it by ear...
See?
Sh-she has perfect pitch!
I have no idea if she's
amazing or not!
Right! Here goes!
One, two, three, and four!
(ending a song)
Hey! That sounded really
great, didn't it?
Yes, it was perfect.
You were great, Yui-chan!
I wonder when they
had time to practice?
You set a perfect tempo
for the song, too, Ritsu.
Did you do some
cram practicing?
I'm so hungry that I've got
absolutely no energy left...
I guess the hunger made her
loose her extra energy
and play better than usual.
Oh... C'mon, let's eat!
Please feed me!
Yes, me too!
[Yui]
We're back!
[Ritsu]
Welcome back!
[Mugi]
Oh, thanks, Ritsu.
Ritchan! We bring you meat!
And veggies!
Yeah!
A whole head of cabbage!
I'm so hungry, I'll eat it raw!
Show a little patience,
all right?
They goof off all the time,
but for some reason they
manage to play really well.
Let go! The cabbages!
The god of cabbages is angry!
If we split up the cooking work,
it'll be ready in no time.
I'll light the grill and start
getting everything heated up.
See, our new member is taking
the initiative and working hard.
All right, all right...
(crying)
My eyes are burning!
Yui, sure you can handle it?
Ritchan!
Yui!
When we die,
we die together!
Yes!
Ready!
So, why don't we
make some onigiri?
Right!
They're so different!
Hm?
I guess it's just that
you have man hands, Mio.
Shut up!
*
Ah! That was delicious!
It was terrific!
That was awesome all right!
Hey!
Who's for fireworks?
Uh... Oh...
Aw, I burned out.
You know, when a firework
almost burned completely out,
it sort of makes you want
to cheer it on, doesn't it?
You can do it! You can do it!
You can do it!
All right, one more time!
(fizzing out)
Ah!
It broke off again.
[Yui]
Ritchan, look, it's going out!
[Ritsu]
Right! At times like this,
we have to combine
and get bigger!
[Both]
Combine! Form Sparklerman!
[Mugi]
Hey! No fair!
[Mio]
Morons.
Is that too heavy?
No, I'm fine.
Let's test our bravery!
Oh!
If it's not one thing,
it's another...
Why not?!
We have to have to have
a bravery contest,
it's a camp tradition.
Yeah, well I'm not doing it.
Oh, you won't?
You do have a problem
with scary stuff...
I can handle it just fine!
So, bring it on, Ritsu!
Hehe...
Now you're going to pay dearly
for making me wait
so long to eat!
(owl hooting)
(bird cries out)
Huh?!
S-seriously, Azusa,
who still has bravery
contests in high school?
Um, you're kind of
hurting my hand.
(moaning)
I wonder what that is?
I-I bet it's R-Ritsu
up to her usual tricks!
(moaning)
Mio-chan...
(screaming)
Mio! Senpai!
Pull it together!
(moaning)
Ms. Yamanaka!
What are you doing here?!
I-I finally found you...
Huh? Ms. Yamanaka?
What's wrong and
what are you doing here?
well, my plan was to
catch up with you
and then surprise you all
by my sudden arrival.
But I got lost.
It looks like you succeeded
in surprising us, anyway.
Regardless of how lost you got.
Mio-chan! Everything's
all right! Mio-chan!
I had no idea Mio got
frightened so easily.
(hooting)
Nobody's coming...
That was total hell...
Now, now...
Oh, Mio! Mio!
Azusa, don't you
like hot water?
Huh? No, that's not it.
Azu-nyan, at times like this,
it's best to just
get it over with!
Ow!
Oh, was it because
you are sunburned, huh?
[Mugi]
Yui-chan, have you
lost weight?
[Yui]
Huh? No.
Didn't I tell you before?
I can eat all I want, and I
never gain any weight at all.
[Others]
I'm so jealous!
[Yui]
What? You, too, Ms. Yamanaka?!
You know what, it's strange,
but I really can't tell
the two of you apart
without my glasses on.
I guess I'll have to tell you
apart based on bust size!
(thud)
(crickets chirping)
(sleeping grumbles)
Gimme the cabbage...!
(flushing)
Uh?
(guitar notes)
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
make you practice with me.
Don't worry about it, Yui.
It's all right.
I've been hoping that I
might get a chance sometime
to practice with you anyway.
Aw. Thanks a lot!
Let's see...
(playing notes)
Ah...
Azu-nyan, you're really good!
Huh? Oh, no, not at all!
Now it's my turn
to give it a try.
(playing notes)
Wow, this part is
really tough.
Maybe you should playing it
at a slower tempo at first.
Like this?
I did it!
Azu-nyan, I'm so glad I met you!
Azu-nyan!
Thank you so much, Azu-nyan!
(giggles)
*
Hello, Ui Hirasawa here.
I'm hanging out with
Azusa-chan again today.
Hey!
Hi, Ui! Sorry I'm late!
Hi! What kept you?
Wait, who are you?
Ah!
So I guess you didn't get
in much practicing, huh?
We did practice some,
but I was expecting more
intensive training or something.
We basically goofed off
most of the time,
swimming and
stuff like that.
Hm...
But I wanted to
practice a lot more!
I see.
Wait a minute, that's weird,
my sister wasn't tan at all.
How did you get so sunburned?
Oh, um...
Because I played around
more than anyone else.
(giggle)
Still, though...
I'm really happy I went.
I learned lots of things
about the others in the club.
Yeah? what kind of things?
Well, like Mio is more of
a scaredy-cat than you'd expect.
Oh, she is?
What about Ritsu?
Well, she is
unfocused and all,
but she and Mio
are great together.
And what about Mugi?
Let's see, Mugi is
sweet and generous
and is always
thinking about others,
and she's got a
childlike side to her
that's fun and really cute.
Oh...
Okay, what about my sister?
Well, Yui is...
She buckled down
and practiced!
I knew it!
But...
Ah...
She still stays glommed
onto me all the time.
She's warm and sweet,
isn't she?
Hehe...
You know, she is.
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
These strings are all corroded!
When was the last time
you changed them out
for new ones, Yui?
Huh? You mean you're supposed
to change the strings?
What?
Is this a vintage guitar?
No, we're sorry. It's just
kind of dirty, that's all.
It's been a year since
I bought it!
What if she decides not to come
back to the club anymore...
What will happen to our concert
at the school festival?