[Azusa]
I never suspected that
the Light Music Club
would face a crisis of
these proportions
so soon before
the School Festival.
(Azusa humming)
[Ritsu]
You sure are in
a good mood, Azusa.
Huh?
I get happy when I think about
actually playing a
live show at the festival.
Aw. That's really cute!
I wish I could have seen you
play at last year's festival.
(Mio spits)
Yeah. Guess you put on
a pretty big show last year,
-didn't you, Mio?
-Huh?
She tripped while she was
up on stage, and-
Ah!
[Yamanaka]
Hey! I just happen to
have a recording
of their last year's show.
Ah! I wanna see!
I wanna see!
Are you sure you won't
reconsider, Azusa?
Yui, Ritsu...
(snap)
Wait! No! Let me go!
Now, let's start with
the primo scene.
[Mio]
Don't look, Azusa!
It's too dangerous!
You'll be cursed!
I can't unsee it.
I was too late...
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
(music playing)
[Azusa]
It's pretty weird.
You guys seem to only play
incredibly well
during live performances.
Oh, look at you, offering up
opinions and everything!
Head lock!
Noogie! Noogie!
(Yui giggles)
What is it, Yui?
This is bringing back
a lot of fun memories.
As I recall,
you blew out your voice
just before we did this show.
Yeah! My voice was all scratchy
when I woke up that morning.
That's right!
So Mio took over vocals...
This will be your first show
as member of
the Light Music Club.
Yeah!
I'm gonna give it
all I've got!
[Nodoka]
I'm sorry to interrupt when
you're having such a good time.
Oh, Nodoka!
What's going on?
Don't act like you don't know.
This.
[Ritsu]
Auditorium Use Application...
[Nodoka]
Right. You haven't submitted one
for the School Festival.
Oh, I completely forgot.
Don't be so nonchalant!
Things have been kinda hectic,
so it slipped my mind.
[Mio]
The same thing
happened last year.
Actually, that was the
Club Application...
Ow!
[Ritsu]
Okay, Azusa,
you be the secretary.
[Azusa]
Me? Well, I guess I don't mind.
Let's see, "Applicant"
is Light Music Club...
So, what do I put down
for "Name"?
[Ritsu]
The band name, I guess.
[Azusa]
Right.
Now that you mention it,
what is the band's name?
-Sweets Smile! -Girl Gang!
-Chocolate Melody!
They're all different!
We never settled on one.
Then it's the perfect time
to pick a name!
[Yui]
I got it! How about...
"Yui Hirasawa and
the Bumbling Sisters"?
[Ritsu]
What are we, chopped liver?
[Mio]
How about something
like "Pure Pure"?
[Ritsu]
Enough with the jokes,
let's be serious about this.
But I was being serious...
You really meant that?!
Well, everyone has
different tastes.
It doesn't make them wrong.
[Yamanaka]
All right, then!
Huh?
I'll choose the band name!
I think we should all give it
a little more thought!
They pulled together...
[Nodoka]
Just bring the paperwork
to the Student Council Office
when you're done.
I'm sorry that we made you
wait for nothing.
It's all right.
Nodoka-chan, why don't you and I
stop and grab some tea
on the way home!
Sure, Yui,
I'll text you later.
Okay, why don't we all just
sleep on the band name tonight
and get to practicing our set
for the show now?
I agree!
The Festival's soon, so we
have to give it 110 percent.
I will!
[Yui]
Oh, sound!
My guitar hasn't really been
sounding quite right lately.
Huh? You want me to take
a quick look at it?
Eh?!
These strings are all corroded!
When was the last time
you changed them out
for new ones, Yui?
Huh? You mean supposed to
change the strings?
Wh-what?
Plus, the neck is warped!
Didn't you know that
a warped guitar neck
can completely throw off
the octave tuning!
Uh... Neck? Octa?
[Mio]
Calm down, Azusa!
This is way too much
for Yui to digest.
Basically...
you have to take really good
care of your instrument.
This is a beautiful guitar!
Oh! But I do take
good care of it!
I sleep with it every night.
I dress it up nice.
That's not what I mean by
"taking care of it"!
In that case,
is there anything
you can do to fix it,
Ms. Yamanaka?
Huh?!
I think you'd be better off
taking it to the
music store, don't you?
[Ritsu]
You just can't be bothered.
(laughing)
You and I better just go
to the music store, then.
What? It isn't
that serious, is it?
The festival's coming up,
and we can't practice with your
guitar in the shape it's in!
Oh...
Ritchan, you don't do any
upkeep on your drums, do you?
Yes, I do!
Oh...
And even if I didn't,
don't make it sound like
a foregone conclusion
that I don't.
It IS you we're talking about...
[Yui]
Ow!
[Ritsu]
Okay, here we are.
Hey, I'll wait for
you guys out here, okay?
But, why aren't you
coming inside?
You see, the thing is
I'm a lefty,
so looking at all those
right-handed instruments
would only make me sad.
Ah.
[Ritsu]
Hey, Mio, check this out!
It says here that they're
having a Lefty Fair today.
Huh?!
Oh!
Have I died and
gone to Heaven?
Clerk! I want you to give me
everything you have
on display here!
Hey, Mio, get a grip girl.
Boy, Mio-chan sure looks happy.
That's cause there's not a lot
of models made for lefties.
So, you want to just
go on without them?
Mmhm.
-Excuse us!
-How can I help you?
We were wondering if you
could make some adjustments
on a guitar for us.
Yeah, sure thing.
On which guitar?
This one.
Ah. Well, why don't we
have a look at it
and see what we've got.
Um, is this a vintage guitar?
No. We're sorry. It's just
kind of dirty, that's all.
It's been a year
since I bought it!
I-I see...
Well, feel free to wait
in the store until I'm done.
Thank you very much.
(sigh)
Well, let's browse around
the store until he's done.
Hey. What's the matter, Yui?
Uhh...
My poor guitar is being
stripped naked bit by bit!
What are you talking about?
I'm curious about
something, Yui?
Why did you buy that
guitar in the first place?
I mean, look at it. It's heavy,
and it's got a thick neck.
It's got all sorts of quirks.
Huh? I got it
because it's cute!
Because it's cute?
Yeah, that's right.
Huh? You do think it's cute?
Don't you, Azu-nyan?
I don't get
Yui-senpai's tastes.
Sorry we kept you waiting!
We dropped it off to have
them do some maintenance.
Right. Good deal.
Wait a minute.
Where did Mio-senpai go?
Oh, Mio is still
over there checking out-
[Clerk]
Miss Kotobuki!
Huh?
It's so good to
see you again, Miss!
Oh, hello.
Hey! If it isn't Miss Kotobuki!
It's been too long!
Mugi says that this shop
is part of her family's
business consortium.
Uh!
It's always a shock to hear
someone call her that, isn't it?
[Clerk]
Thank you for waiting.
Ah!
[Ritsu]
It's all clean again!
Make sure you keep it
maintained from now on.
Geeta!
[Ritsu]
She named the thing...
Oh, thank you so much, sir!
D-don't mention it.
So, the bill
comes to 50 dollars.
Huh?
You charge for this?
U-um, yes.
Well, of course
they charge for it!
I have no money.
-Huh?!
-What do I do?
What's the matter?
Well, it looks like Yui-senpai
didn't know that music stores
charge for maintenance work.
Oh, she didn't, huh?
Oh, goodness.
Did I bring any pocket money?
O-oh, M-Miss, no...
Perish the thought!
Consider it on the house!
Huh?!
No, I couldn't possibly!
Please, think nothing of it!
We're constantly in
your father's debt!
-But, I...
-I insist!
Well, it looks like you
just lucked out.
That's that, then!
What do you say we
all get going?
Yeah!
Um...
Hm?
Aren't we forgetting Mio-senpai?
Yeah. I'll go call her.
Mio!
C'mon, it's time to go!
Don't wanna.
Are you a grade schooler?
Look, everybody's waiting for
you and we have to get back.
Don't wanna.
Sheesh! C'mon, Mio, let's go!
Hey, Ritsu!
Let's go home now, Mio.
I know one person
who actually likes to string
his guitar in reverse order.
[Mio]
Hey, wait! Watch it!
Huh?
Uh...
Hey, what'cha doing
down there, Mio?
Enough, already!
You jerk.
(Bells chime)
Thank goodness,
Geeta is all pretty again!
You gave your guitar
a name, huh? That's nice.
What do you want to do now?
Hmm, good question...
Hey! How about going for tea?!
Tea again? Really?
Sorry, guys!
But I'm supposed to get together
with Nodoka-chan right now.
Uh...
[Mio]
You're going to see Nodoka?
Can I tag along?
Huh?
Oh, that's right!
You and Nodoka-chan are in the
same class together, aren't you?
-Sure.
-Really?
I'm gonna give her a call and
let her know your coming.
Great, thanks!
Mm...
K-ON!
(Yui giggles)
Oh, I've always wanted
to try out this place!
But you have no money?
Oh, it's okay.
I'll pay for Yui's share.
When I get next
month's allowance,
we'll all go out and it will
all be on me. How's that?
I'll hold you to that.
So, is Yui really
doing all right
at the Light Music Club,
like she says?
Yeah, but whenever she
learns one thing,
she has the tendency to
forget something else.
I know how it is.
But when she's
focused on something,
she can do
amazing things.
That's for sure!
She can be a real
handful, can't she?
Huh? What'cha
talking about?
Feh. Those two sure seem to be
having a good time together.
More to the point, why are we
sneaking around like this?
Hehe. It's like we're private
investigators, isn't it?
That's it, I'm going in.
And then the teacher
came up to me and-
Well, you two sure seem
really friendly!
Huh?!
Ritsu? What are
you doing here?
Oh, I just happened
to be here.
Did you come here
all by yourself?
Nope, Mugi and Azusa
are sitting over there.
Huh? Oh, hey, they are!
Oh gosh, thank you for
taking such good care
of our little Mio!
Uh, Ritsu?
Hm? What?
You want me to leave?
Um... Well, no I don't, but...
[Ritsu]
Then what's the problem?
What's that?! What did you get?
What's she doing?
Her ice cream is melting...
[Mio]
Wow, that's a gorgeous
boxed lunch!
No, it's not.
I just threw together
whatever I had lying around.
Huh? You mean you make your own?
That's amazing!
Oh, come on, it's
no big deal. Really.
No, mine are always-
[Ritsu]
Okay, lunchtime is over!
Ritsu? Sorry, but I
just started eating.
We're practicing through
every lunch break
from now until the
school festival!
Uh...
[Ritsu]
Gee, I wonder what Mio's
gonna do to liven things up
at this year's big school
festival concert?
She gave the crowd that
panty shot last year,
so maybe she'll show her
belly button this time?
Ooo... Or maybe...
I thought we were
gonna practice!
Uh?
And we will!
Then why are you-
Haha! Takoyaki!
Huh?
-Ponytail!
-Hey!
Braids!
Come on, cut it out!
What's gotten into you?
Oh, guess what I brought?
A great horror movie!
So scary, it will make
your hair stand up!
This is stupid!
I'm going back to my classroom.
All right.
Suit yourself.
Uh...
Gosh, I'm so sorry
I interrupted your
wonderfully pleasant
lunchtime with Nodoka,
your brand new best friend.
Huh?
Who said anything about that?!
I don't get it.
Why are they fighting?
Uh...
How about some tea?
Let's have tea! All right?
I brought some
lovely tarts today.
Wh-what should I do?
I have to do something!
Anything!
Let's all be friends
and practice together
like we planned!
I-it didn't work!
[Ritsu]
Yeah, I guess we
should practice.
Let's get started.
S-sure! All right!
One, two!
(playing music)
Uh...
Huh?
Ritsu?
What gives?
I'm glad that your drumming
isn't as wild as usual,
but don't you think
it's a little weak?
Ritsu?
Ritsu, what is it?
Aw, sorry.
I'm just not
feeling it right now.
Let's try it again
after school.
R-Ritchan...!
Let her go, Yui.
But she...
Twerp.
I guess Ritsu isn't coming...
(sigh)
She didn't come after
school yesterday, either.
[Yui]
I wonder what's wrong?
I'd say it was because Mio
has been so cold to her.
Huh?
For the sake of the
Light Music Club,
you need to be Ritsu's plaything
for at least a day!
If you don't,
Ritsu's heart...
...will grow harden.
Hey mister! A jumbo!
And she'll order
a jumbo beef bowl
she knows she can't finish.
What am I doing?
She'll be driven to despair.
And she'll go so far down
the path of heavy metal...
she'll never find her way back!
That's what happened to you
when you got dumped
by your boyfriend, isn't it?
Pardon?
What if she decides not to
come back to the club anymore...
Huh?
What'll happen to our concert
at the school festival?
Come on, let's practice.
You mean without Ritchan?
What else can we do?
Aww...
But, shouldn't we go ask
her to join us first?
Um...
(sigh)
[Yamanaka]
You could also start
looking for a replacement.
Now, I'm just saying
that it's always a
good idea to be prepared.
But...
There's no replacing Ritchan!
Mugi-chan...
Let's just wait.
Let's wait for Ritsu
to come back to us.
I know she'll come.
I know it.
(sigh)
Ah, Mio!
Uh...
Mugi-chan you were right!
Oh, good morning.
Listen, Mio,
about Ritchan, she's...
Look, I didn't come here to
check up on Ritsu. I, uh...
She's been staying home
from school.
Huh?
(giggles)
(kids chatter)
(noises outside)
(sigh)
(footsteps)
[Ritsu]
Mio...
So now you have ESP?
I think I can recognize
your footsteps.
(sigh)
How's the cold?
I still have
a bit of a fever.
I guess that explains why your
drumming sounded so weak.
Heck of a time to get sick,
right before the festival...
You just get better quick, okay?
We're all waiting
for you to come back.
They're not mad?
They're not.
Are you?
Of course not.
How could I be mad at you?
It's just...
Just what?
Without you there drumming,
I guess it's kinda lonely.
Even though you're pretty wild,
I really like how your
drumming is always so
full of energy and powerful.
Uh?
(giggles)
Ritsu! Were you...
Hooray, I'm cured!
(sneeze)
Oh, Ritsu, you are not!
Come on now, lie down.
You still have a fever.
(groans)
I'm going home, okay?
Aw! C'mon, don't go yet!
Stay until I fall asleep!
Please!
Oh, good grief.
(laugh)
(knocking)
Excuse us. Can we come in?
-Ritchan, how are-
-Shhh...
I was finally able to
get her to go to sleep.
Ahh...
Um, why did Yui
fall asleep, too?
Oh, good grief...
I'm back!
Now, let's bust our butts to
get ready for the festival!
Yeah!
Hey!
You guys didn't submit your
auditorium use permission form?!
Huh?
Ah!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
A deadline is a
deadline, you know.
Couldn't you bend the rules?
I'd like to appeal
on their behalf.
They missed the
submission deadline
because the club president
was home sick with a cold.
Please make an exception.
Well, if you feel this
strongly, Miss Manabe...
You have until
the end of the day.
Ah!
Oh! Oh, you!
You're a good egg, ain't cha!
Please look after Mio!
And please, while your at it,
you can look after me
from now on, too, right?
Hey!
[Mio]
What's wrong with "Pure Pure"?
[Ritsu]
Rejected.
[Yui]
How about "Clenched Fist"?
[Ritsu]
Too balladie.
[Yui]
How about "Gum On the
Sole of My Shoe"?
[Ritsu]
You stepped in some, didn't you?
[Yui]
Oh! How did you know?
[Ritsu]
Mugi, don't you have
any good ones?
Hm... How about something
like "Recharging Time"?
[Ritsu]
Sounds like bad luck!
[Mio]
How about "Popcorn Honeymoon"?
[Ritsu]
Oh, come on guys, what's with
all these silly, cutesy names?
What do you think of
"Rocket Pencil"?
[Ritsu]
Would you hush!
God, this is annoying!
I can't even enjoy a
nice cup of tea!
For stuff like this,
just pick something at random!
All done!
Ah!
She decided it on her own!
Aww...
What the heck.
Hm.
Mmhm!
(laughing)
All right!
We've settled on a band name!
[Azusa]
All that's left now
is to practice hard for
the School Festival concert.
(sneeze)
Oh...
Maybe not...
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
So, her fever hasn't
gone down yet...
No. If this keeps up
tomorrow's show is in danger.
Getting sick at
a time like this
just shows her
lack of dedication!
You're the one who
gave it to her!
Oh! I did?
Oh, Big Sis...
You may have fooled the others,
but you can't fool me.
(nervous sigh)
*