(Clock ticking)
(Clock alarm ringing)
(Groan)
(Alarm stops)
(Exhales)
[Ui]
Sis, come on.
You'd better get out of bed.
Sis--!
Huh?!
(Panicking)
Ah! I-it's eight!
I'm late! Oh!
Hey, why the rush?
Hm?
(Rushing happy music)
Whoa!
Ugh!
(Panicking)
See you later!
Oh, good morning, Yui...
[Yui]
Good morning!
Uh?
(Crossing bell)
(Panting)
What...?
I read the clock wrong!
(Music continues)
Starting today...
I'm a high schooler!
("Cagayake! Girls" plays)
[Girls]
Congratulations on
starting school here!
Please join the Tennis Club!
The Judo Club's better!
Please join the
Tea Ceremony Club!
Please join
the Abacus Club!
Please, please!
Uh...
Hm...
Hm?
Hmmm...
Uh...
[Nodoka]
What are you
groaning about, Yui?
Hm?
Oh, hello, Nodoka.
I'm not sure which club
I should join-
What?! You haven't
decided on one?
It's already been two weeks
since school started!
You have to choose!
B-but I'm absolutely
terrible at every sports,
and I don't really get
any of the literary clubs.
(Exhales)
This is how people
end up becoming NEETs.
You're pegged as a NEET just
because you don't join a club?
You know, looking back on it,
for as long as
I've know you,
you've never joined
a single club, have you?
Crud!
I really do feel
like I ought to at least
try to do something.
But what the heck
should I be doing?
[Ritsu]
Mio!
(Ritsu laughing)
Ritsu?
Let's go check out
the club!
Which club
do you mean?
The Light Music Club,
what do ya' think?!
But I was planning on
joining the Literature Club.
Ah!
I've already filled out
the application form.
(Groan)
Rip.
Ah! What do you think
you're doing?
[Ritsu]
C'mon, let's go!
Move it, move it!
[Mio]
Cut it out!
(School bells)
[Ritsu]
Huh? It's been disbanded?!
Well, on the verge of
being disbanded.
All the students who were
in the club last year
have now graduated,
so the club will be disbanded
unless four students
join this month.
Oh, so that's why there wasn't
anyone in the Music Room.
(Door opens)
[Yui] Ms. Yamanaka!
Hi, Yui. I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, I have a music class
to teach in a few minutes.
Light Music Club, good luck.
She sure was pretty, wasn't she?
That is not the issue here.
Um...
Oh...
Uh...
Please hand out these syllabus
sheets to all the students.
Syllabus sheets?
Oh, right!
So sorry about that!
(Nervous giggles)
Hm? They're staring at me!
[Ritsu]
Bad tempo.
Oh, no!
[Ritsu]
She's useless.
I-I'm so sorry!
[Yamanaka]
Are you all right?
Ah!
And clumsy.
(Yui nervous crying)
It's being disbanded,
so that's that.
I'm gonna go join
the Literature Club...
If I join and there
aren't any members,
does that make me...
the club president
Ah! Doesn't sound bad at all!
[Yui]
Um, what was that club
you were talking about
with those girls?
[Yamanaka]
The Light Music Club?
[Yui]
Yea. What is it?
[Yamanaka]
The Light Music Club is about
playing light-hearted music.
Light... Music Club?
[Yamanaka]
That's right.
The Light Music Club.
(Girls exercising outside)
So, what's your plan, Ritsu?
We wait for
prospective members!
We just wait?
Wait!
Hm.
(Girls exercising outside)
Come on, let's go home.
(Door opens)
Hello. I wanted to find out
about joining your club.
Ah!
The Light Music Club?
No, I meant the Choir Club.
But why not join the
Light Music Club instead?
But... the Choir Clu--
We need more members like you!
Please! I'm begging you!
You won't regret it! I promise!
Don't try to force her
to join, like that.
It's really rude!
(Ritsu crying)
I'm going now. I'm sorry.
[Ritsu]
Mio!
What about that promise we made?
Was that just a big lie?!
That I would play drums and
that you would play the bass!
Our band!
We've been saying forever
that we would start one! Huh?
We promised each other,
remember?!
That night we went to see
that concert together!
This is it.
This is, isn't it?
Were those sweet words
nothing but a big lie?!
No, your flashback is.
Oh, really it is?
(Ritsu excited)
Mio, this is it!
You and I are going to
play in a band together!
Isn't that exciting!
You forced the idea on me.
Yea, but you said
you wanted to!
Yes, I did, but...
And if we went pro, we said we'd
split all the proceeds 70/30!
Don't make stuff up.
(Tsumugi giggles)
Uh... Eh...
This will be a
great deal of fun.
The only instrument I can play
is the keyboard,
but I'd like to join your club
if you will have me.
Ah!
Thank you so much!
Now we only need one more
person to join us!
Well, I suppose that means
I'm already a member?
Um, you're...
Tsumugi Kotobuki.
I'm Ritsu Tainaka, drums.
This is Mio Akiyama,
she's on bass.
Let's see...
Now we need a guitar player!
Oh...
Yui?
My high school years
are very important.
I wanna do something...
Well, then do it.
Ugh... But I have absolutely
no idea what it is I should do!
Oh, good grief...
(Yui whines)
Would you like any
french fries with that, Miss?
Ah, yes! I would love some,
thank you!
Thank you.
(Tsumugi giggles)
What is it?
This is my first time eating
in a fast food restaurant!
How can that be?!
I know it's silly,
but I've always dreamed of
having someone ask me
if I wanted french fries.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Please begin the meeting.
Okay, this planning
meeting is now underway!
Our goal is to recruit
one more member by
the end of the month!
[Tsumugi]
How in the world
do we do that?
[Ritsu]
That's why we're meeting,
to think of a way right now.
For instance, offering people
an amazing prize if they
decide to join!
[Mio]
Amazing prize?
Yeah! Like some kind of
gift or something.
Like a car, or a plane,
or a boat?
[Mio]
Amazing, but impractical.
More along the lines of ice
cream or help with homework.
Who would join up for
something like that?
What should we do, then?
[Girls]
Hmm...
(Yui whines)
Plop.
The president shouldn't
lose interest!
Come up with something
to keep me interested!
Uh, I want to go home.
Um, for now, why don't we...
[Girls]
One, two!
(Giggling)
(School bells)
There's... There's just one more
week remaining in April.
No one has answered our ads yet.
Disbanded before we're a band.
[Ritsu]
I won't let that happen!
Ah!
Huh?
Uh?
Hm...
Wait, Light Music, huh?
(Music and clapping)
(Yui laughing)
You're very good at that, Yui.
(Yui excited)
I'm gonna do it!
[Yui]
K-ON!
For the time being, I've decided
to join the Light Music Club!
Oh, yeah? So what is it
that they do at this club?
Dunno.
Huh?
But since the name of
the club is "Light Music",
I figure they only do
really easy stuff.
You know, like whistling.
Sounds like they don't
have much ambition.
You see? It looks like
they're some kind of band.
What? But I don't know
how to play the guitar!
Well then,
what can you play?
Umm... Umm...
I can play castanets?
(Playing castanets and humming)
That's a perfect
fit for you.
[Mio]
See? Look at this here...
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
A prospective member
has come forward.
Oh!
Here. Isn't that
wonderful news?
Also, that's a lovely tea set,
but make sure you clean up
after yourselves once
you're done, all right?
All right!
Hm.
Yes! Now we won't
be disbanded!
[Mio]
Yui Hirasawa...
[Ritsu]
Just her name makes her
sound really awesome.
[Mio]
She's got to be a guitarist.
[Tsumugi]
I can't wait to meet her.
Yeah! A real powerhouse
has joined us!
[Yui]
Light Music Club...
(Nervous moaning)
I-if I don't get down
this hallway,
I won't reach the
Light Music Club!
(Gasp)
[Yamanaka]
Oh, hello!
The Light Music Club,
is up in the Music Room.
This is the place?
It won't be an easy thing
to say right after joining,
but I've got to quit.
I wonder what kind of
people would join
the Light Music Club?
[Scary Guy]
Oh, you want to quit, do you?
Did you think you could walk
away without any consequences?!
(Yui screams)
I'll murder you!
(Nervous moaning)
What am I gonna do?!
(Yui whimpers)
Wah!
You've got it all wrong!
[Ritsu]
Hmm... Huh?
It's the useless, clumsy,
bad tempo girl!
What is it your doing?
Huh?
You startled me!
Uh... You aren't Yui Hirasawa
by any chance?
Y-yes.
The girl who wants to join us?
Y-yes!
Aah!
I'm so sorry I misjudged you!
I'm sure you must be
totally awesome on guitar!
We've all been waiting
for you to get here!
[Yui]
It seems like somebody's been
embellishing things about me...
Hey, guys!
Our brand new member
has arrived!
Is that her?!
Ah!
Welcome to the Light Music Club!
It's so good to have you here!
Right! Mugi, go get
the tea ready!
[Tsumugi]
Okay!
Wh-what should I do?
Go ahead! It's quite delicious!
(Nervous)
(Sipping)
Ah! Wow, this is great!
(Yui bites)
This is so good!
Mmm... Maybe I should
give up on trying to quit.
[Ritsu]
What kind of music
do you want to play?
[Yui]
Huh?
Whose your all-time
favorite band?
Uh...
Which guitarists do you like?
Oh my, I have to tell them.
I can't really play
the guitar at all!
Je-je-je...
Oh, are you trying to say
Jimi Hendrix?!
Whoa!
No, it's not,
I mean I don't...
Jimmy Paige, then?!
No! No, I je-je-
Jeff Beck?!
I didn't really list
many guitarists
whose names start with "J"?!
Oh wow, Jeff Beck,
that's cool!
Who is he?
[Mio]
In the music world,
they say that there's only
two kinds of rock guitarists:
Jeff Beck, and everyone else.
He's a brilliant and
challenging guitarist
who's always searching
for new sounds.
[Tsumugi]
My goodness!
[Ritsu]
You're so hardcore,
Miss Hirasawa!
(Yui nervous crying)
I gotta say,
I'm so glad
that someone like her
joined the club!
We were at the point where the
club would have been disbanded
if we hadn't gotten another
member within the next week.
Thank you so much
for joining!
[Yui]
They keep making it harder!
But I'm... I'm just gonna
have to spit it out!
Um, I'm really sorry,
I don't know how to say it,
but I made a mistake
joining this club,
and I only came here
to beg you to let me quit!
Wha...?
I can't play the guitar.
I thought you would be playing
a different kind of instrument.
What instrument
can you play, then?
Casta-
Er, the harmonica.
Oh, I have a harmonica
right here.
Ah!
Try playing someth-
I'm sorry, I can't play it!
But, Miss Hirasawa, if you
wanted to join this club,
that means that you're at least
interested in music, right?
Is there another club
you'd rather join?
Uh, no, none in particular...
(gasp)
We can't let this mark leave
this room, no matter what.
To keep the club
from being disbanded...
...we have to keep
her here somehow!
I'm sorry.
I really mean it. Bye.
[Ritsu]
Wait just a minute!
[Tsumugi]
How about another cup of tea?
But I-
We have cookies and
madeleines, as well.
Mhm!
[Mio]
They're baiting the hook!
So good!
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
come here and gorge myself.
Hey, don't sweat it!
I think we should start
eating snacks like this
every day from now on.
Aren't we drifting
off topic here- OW!
Miss Hirasawa, what other
sorts of things do you like?
Uh...
Oh, I like anything
that tastes good.
Geez, just food?
Mhm. On your days off,
do you spend your time at home
doing anything
in particular?
Just sitting around,
I guess.
What kinds of things
do you like?
Um, I like cute things,
I guess.
Have any weaknesses?
I'm not very good with
extreme heat or cold.
I spend winter under
the table where it's warm,
and in the summer,
I spend my time on the floor
where it's cool.
[Mio]
She's a tough one.
[Ritsu]
What the heck do we do?
[Tsumugi]
I don't know.
Um, I should go.
Don't go, I'm begging you!
You can just hang out and
do nothing if you want!
I'll try to bring even
tastier snacks, okay?!
I-I'm really sorry.
I didn't take things seriously
when I applied to join...(sniff)
I got all your hopes up.
How can I ever apologize?
(sighs)
We're the ones
who should apologize.
We shouldn't have tried
to force you to stay.
So please! At least
hang around for a while
and listen to us play a song!
Oh!
You'll play a song for me?!
[Ritsu]
She's swallowed the bait!
(Instrumental warm up)
Oh...
(Tuning bass)
Hm.
Mm.
One, two, three, four!
(Playing "Love Me")
(Applause)
Hehehe...
What did you think?
[Yui]
I don't know what to say...
It's really hard
to put into words!
Hmhm!
You guys aren't
very good, are you?
[Ritsu]
Talk about blunt!
But it seems like it would be
a whole lot of fun to do!
I'm decided that I'm
going to join this club!
(Gasps)
Uh...
Eh...
(Excited)
Banzai!
Excuse me.
Okay, let's commemorate the
start of the Light Music Club!
(Giggling)
Hey, that's my camera!
Here we go, guys!
[Yui]
But the problem is
that I can't play
any instruments at all.
Can I be a manager
or something?
[Mio]
Um... well, we aren't
a sports club.
I know! Why don't you
take this opportunity
to begin learning the guitar?
But it looks really complicated!
I don't think I could.
Don't worry about it!
Between the three of us,
we'll teach you everything
you need to know.
Um... I guess you're right.
Listening to you play
just now made me feel like
I could do at least that well,
if not a lot better!
(Mio sighs)
We're so glad
we could help.
What?! You went ahead
and joined anyway?
Um-hm! They practically
begged me to join!
Seriously?
Oh, as a manager
or something, right?
When someone else says it,
it sounds insulting.
I joined as a full-fledged
member of the band!
And they say that they'll
teach me to play guitar!
Huh...
Oh, that means you're
gonna have to go out
and buy yourself
a new guitar.
Hmm...
I wonder if they will
let me borrow one?
Probably not.
Uh...
You can buy them for about
fifty dollars, right?
(Nervous gulp)
[Nodoka]
Oh, boy.
I wonder if the
Light Music Club knows
what they're getting themselves
into with this girl...
(Yui hums and giggles)
("Don't say 'lazy'" plays)
[Yui]
Hey, everyone!
These three are my fellow
Light Music Club members.
I wanted to pick a club
where I could make friends
with the sort of fun, pleasant
people that one so rarely meets.
Y-Yui?
All right! Let's get to it!
Go!
Hm? Oh. Hey, guys!
(Giggles)
Ow!
But now that I finally
made it to high school...
I've joined a club
for the first time!