[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
Lindo!
Lindo! You're finally back!
It'll be okay now. I'm home.
Oh, right. This is my
older brother, Lindo.
And Lindo, this is the Student
Council president, Rem Kaginuki.
Pleasure to meet you.
[LINDO]
We're leaving.
[RITSUKA]
But, Lindo, why? Wait!
Sorry, Rem. I gotta go,
but thank you so much.
Jeez, you didn't
have to be rude.
And will you let go? That hurts!
[ALL]
Hm?
[MAGE] Well, someone got up
on the wrong side of bed.
[URIE] After the trip to Nagano,
who could blame him?
All that way and still no closer
to finding the grimoire.
I can't tell you how
much I would've loved
to watch that house burn.
Such a pretty picture
that must have been.
[MAGE] I freakin' told you to
hurry up and get your hands
on that grimoire before
someone else stole it.
But you let it get away.
[URIE]
This isn't like you at all Rem.
As the Arlond heir,
it should've been a breeze.
I hate to say it, but maybe
you're losing your touch.
Perhaps I should
take it from here.
Rem, how about we play a game
to compare strategies.
What do you say?
This piece can be her...
Uh.
Watch yourself, Urie.
Heh. Yes, of course.
It's too early.
[RITSUKA]
What do you want?
[LINDO]
I dunno. You to get up?
[RITSUKA]
Lindo!
[sighs]
You can't just waltz in here
without knocking, y'know!
Your snoring drowned
out my knocking.
Uh! I don't snore.
Now come on. Your breakfast
is getting cold.
[RITSUKA]
Get out of my room!
[gasps]
Smells amazing!
[LINDO]
It's royal milk tea.
You've always been
a good cook.
But I gotta say, since
you moved to England,
you've become a five star chef.
Change out of your uniform
when you're finished.
What, why would I do that?
[LINDO] I think it's best
that you stay at home.
Take some time off.
Huh?!
[LINDO] And as I've said
over and over again:
stay away from Rem Kaginuki.
[RITSUKA] And as I've said over
and over again, why should I?
It's for the best.
You don't get how
much he's done.
Rem's been the only one to
help since mom disappeared.
And now I have to apologize for
you being so rude last night.
Uh! Hey! What is this?
Holy Water from Fatima.
Are you serious?
Why would we need it?
Hey, answer me!
You are not to leave this house.
Okay. But why?
[door clicks, slams]
[inaudible]
Lindo?
[RITSUKA] I mean, isn't that
a little ridiculous?
He hasn't always been this
protective of me, has he?
[AZUNA]
I don't really remember.
But with everything going on,
maybe he's right.
He just wants to keep
you safe, you know.
[RITSUKA]
I guess.
[AZUNA] We should have
a sleep over tonight.
My mom won't mind at all.
After school, I'll grab
some clothes and stuff
and head your way.
We haven't exactly had a
chance to talk in a while.
You're the best! I think
that's exactly what I need.
I've got so much
to update you on.
[AZUNA] Should I bring over
some of those cream puffs?
Wait, you mean the
ones from Aspiration?
Those are so good!
[AZUNA] I know, right!
All right, bye, girl!
Can't wait! See ya!
[knocking]
[RITSUKA]
Come in!
Hey. Guess what!
Azuna's gonna come over
later to spend the night.
[gasps] What a great idea.
So, did you want to
tell me something?
[LINDO] Oh. Yeah.
I'm heading out for a bit.
Uh? For what?
Oh, nothing you need
to worry about.
Gotta handle something.
But no matter what,
do not leave this house.
Well, that was pretty cryptic.
I will keep her safe.
♪♪♪
♪ Chatting with my friends,
cream puffs, and tea ♪
♪ I like all those things
'cause they make me happy ♪
♪ Today is the same
as yesterday ♪
♪ I'm just like every
high school girl ♪
[RITSUKA]
Oh, Mom. Please be okay.
[tires screeching]
[WOMAN screams]
[RITSUKA gasps]
[gasps]
Hi.
You're Urie Sogami.
So you do remember me.
Well, yeah, I mean,
you're kinda famous.
[URIE laughs]
[RITSUKA] Uh, what are
you doing at my house?
You weren't at school today.
Rem was very
concerned about you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just, I can't
leave right now.
My brother wants
me to stay at home
where he knows I won't
be in danger.
So you're stuck here?
I guess.
And I feel so bad since
you came all this way.
Oh. I can get you a
cup of tea if you want.
Sorry, it's a bit messy.
No thanks. But I do have news.
About your mother, in fact.
Rem wanted to tell you.
Really, what did he find out?
Since it's not official,
I'm not sure I should say.
Let me go get ready!
I wonder why Rem
wanted to meet here.
Voila. After you.
Pretty.
[VOICES] ♪ Come, let us all,
happily sing ♪
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
[VOICES]
♪ Come, let's sing ♪
♪ For this enchanting party ♪
♪ The beauty of this night
Will never end ♪
♪ This party is for all time ♪
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
[VOICES] ♪ Come, let
us all, happily sing ♪
Um, hello.
You're here!
We missed you!
[gasps]
Oh, okay?
[GIRLS laugh]
[RITSUKA]
Uh.
[GIRLS chattering]
Who's that?
[GIRL 3B]
Why is that girl here?
[GIRL 3C]
Who does she think she is?
[RITSUKA] Oh, great.
Here we go again.
Urie, is Rem here yet?
[URIE] Shh! Don't worry.
We're in my Eden, now.
♪♪♪
♪ I welcome you to paradise
It's my own Eden of amour ♪
♪ "Amour's" my favorite
word for love ♪
♪ Isn't it so... wonderful? ♪
♪ It's true. ♪
♪ Don't worry if
you feel a chill ♪
♪ I'll warm you
in my arms, my dear ♪
♪ So don't you fret
No, don't be troubled ♪
♪ Feel free to flap your wings,
My butterfly ♪
♪ Take a look at
the sky above, ♪
♪ the moon and stars ♪
♪ Their twinkling is a
blessing from afar ♪
♪ Our night together
will be oh so sweet ♪
♪ We'll be free, from any bond ♪
♪ Let us dance, let us dance
Feel the beat and take my hand ♪
♪ Taste of the forbidden nectar
Of our own sinful play ♪
♪ We will whirl, and we'll twirl
Faster than ever before ♪
♪ Spinning higher till our mind
and body have merged into one ♪
♪ More and more that you
give me Of your amour ♪
♪ The more amour lures us! ♪
♪ I can't help but love you ♪
♪ With drama
Is how I will kiss you ♪
[RITSUKA gasps]
[URIE gasps]
Sorry. I, um...
[RITSUKA] Uh, It's just...
I need to talk with Rem.
It's important.
I want to know what he
found out about my mom.
[GIRLS laughing]
[AZUNA] Two cream puffs, please.
Better make that four.
I wonder how many
Ritsuka can eat.
Wait, what?
How did I miss a call?
Oh right, it was on silent
all day because of class.
[VOICEMAIL 3A]
One message.
[RITSUKA] Hey, Azuna, Rem
found out something about Mom,
so I'm heading out. Sorry.
[CLERK 3A]
Wait! Miss?
[RITSUKA panting]
[GIRLS laughing]
[RITSUKA]
This place is like a big maze.
I'm so lost. How do I get out?
What is happening here?
[GIRLS laughing, chattering]
[gasps]
[GIRLS laughing]
[panting]
♪♪♪
[GIRL 3G]
Look! There she is!
[GIRL 3H]
Quick! Stop her!
[REM]
Tell me right now, who did this?
I wonder...
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
[sighs]
[GIRLS laughing]
[RITSUKA gasping]
Give us that pendant,
and we'll let you go!
No, please!
My mom gave it to me!
Please, stop it! Just let me go!
Why are you doing this to me?
[URIE]
Follow me!
[gasps]
[GIRLS laughing]
You should be safe here.
Yeah. Thanks for saving
me back there.
[RITSUKA gasps]
Stay close,
and I'll protect you.
I don't get it.
Who're those girls?
And where exactly am I?
I'm sorry.
They were out of line.
I know how scared you were.
It's just that my butterflies
are a little protective of me.
Can you please tell me
where to find Rem?
I've been gone a while. I don't
wanna upset my brother.
I forgot to tell him
where I was going.
I'm not sure.
What do mean, "Not sure?"
Didn't you bring me here to
talk with Rem about my mom?
[URIE chuckles]
You lied to me.
Never. But there is
someone being untrue.
Like your brother, choosing a
school, far away in England.
Why do you think he did that?
What? Because...
...his school has one of
the best folklore programs.
Uh!
Wait a second, how do you know
where my brother goes to school?
I know a lot of things
about your family.
Even some secrets.
Ones they never bothered
to tell you about.
Poor thing.
Maybe you should ask your
brother what he's hiding.
What for?
My brother doesn't lie!
Listen up kid: Lindo isn't
majoring in folklore.
He's an exorcist.
[gasps]
You're right when you say
he chose the school
with the best program,
but it's not what you think
because where he trains,
demons are fact, not fiction.
There's no way.
[inaudible]
This can't be true.
[URIE]
Face it, my darling butterfly.
I'm not the one
who's lying to you.
[RITSUKA]
Well my brother isn't either.
[URIE]
I really don't understand
why you're so quick
to defend him.
Especially after he's
kept so much from you.
[RITSUKA]
Huh...?
[URIE]
Think about it.
Why wouldn't he just tell you
he was going to Europe
to become an exorcist?
Maybe the answer to that
has to do with your mother.
My mother? What are
you talking about?
Are you saying you know
something about her
that I don't?
Why don't you ask that
brother of yours?
The one you love
and trust so much.
Though I wouldn't be
surprised if he didn't tell you.
I... don't believe it.
Poor Ritsuka.
So sweet and naïve.
Come here.
Let me make it all better.
Yes. My butterfly.
You smell better than
the sweetest rose.
Urie...
Tell me about the grimoire.
I really need to find it, and
you're the key that can help me.
[RITSUKA]
The... grimoire.
That pendant is in the way
of us being together.
Why don't you
take it off for me?
[RITSUKA]
Mm...
[gasps]
Of course.
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
Uh! Oh, Rem!
[REM] I told you to
watch yourself, Urie.
Now, come on, let's go.
Not so fast, we're in the
middle of a discussion.
You wanna know, right?
[REM]
Come with me.
[URIE]
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
Ritsuka!
[REM]
Uh!
Almost seems like you care.
Well. Isn't that sweet?
And a little odd,
since people are usually nothing
more than pawns to you.
What is it about her? I wonder.
Why's she so special?
What?
Too personal to share
with your oldest friend?
This is none of your business.
[URIE]
I'm not so sure.
I think you're
starting to question
the nature of my loyalty to you.
Is it because you're afraid
I'm gonna get my hands on
the grimoire before you do?
I mean, let's be honest,
we're not really all that
different, are we, Rem?
In fact, strength-wise, there've
been times I've had you beat.
I guess I'd be uneasy, as well.
I don't have to listen to this.
There you are!
[RITSUKA] Lindo! These weird
people were chasing me...
Over there... at that
amusement park...?
Maybe you were just dreaming.
You've been through a lot.
You must be tired.
It was there!
I'm glad I came to get you.
Let's go home.
[RITSUKA]
U-Uh...
[RITSUKA] How did he know
exactly where I was?
Is Urie right about Lindo?
Lindo isn't majoring in
folklore. He's an exorcist.
[gasps]
[URIE humming]
I love all of my butterflies.
But Ritsuka...
You're the special one.
Who smells like roses.
Soon the day will come when
I get to watch you dance.
My beautiful and perfect
little butterfly.
Mine and mine alone.
[URIE]
I'll hold you close.
Until you fall apart.
[LINDO]
I have to protect you, Ritsuka.
Please try to understand.
Ritsuka, I just wanna
keep you safe.
I'll protect Ritsuka,
no matter what the cost.
Act 4: "Bolero of Solitude
and Melancholy."