[LINDO groaning]
Lindo?
Ritsuka, stay with me.
Hey, I'm here. Just relax.
[LINDO exhales]
Come on, kitty. I'll catch you!
[meows]
[RITSUKA]
Kitty!
What's going on? Need help?
There's a little kitty
stuck up in the tree.
Poor thing. She must be scared.
Hold this.
Uh?
[LINDO]
I've got an idea.
What is it?
[LINDO grunting]
It's really high! Be careful!
Over here.
I'm trying to help you.
[CAT 10A whimpers]
Come on!
[yelps]
[LINDO grunts]
Lindo! No!
[crash]
--[LINDO groaning]
--[footsteps]
You okay?
[CAT 10A meows]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[RITSUKA] If I really am
the forbidden grimoire,
shouldn't I be able
to heal Lindo?
I wish I could do something
after all he's done for me.
[LINDO]
Ritsuka, go inside!
I have to protect the
flowers from the storm.
I'll handle it.
They'll be safe when
I build an enclosure.
[RITSUKA]
I can help you!
No! It's way too dangerous!
Uh... But...
Hey, Ritsuka. What is it?
You got sick.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
That's not true.
This happened because
I'm still too weak.
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
But I'm going to get stronger.
That way I'll always be
able to protect you.
Because, Ritsuka, I've been in
love with you for a long time.
[gasps]
Oh, I forgot!
I bet you'll be hungry
when you wake up.
I'll go get something.
You're gonna be okay, right?
I promise I'll be right back.
[RITSUKA]
Hello? Is there anybody in here?
Uh?
[RITSUKA] I hope no one
minds if I take some.
It all looks so different now.
Everyone's gone.
Kinda sad.
I guess the school
festival really is over.
[inaudible]
Here's the truth.
The grimoire is the great power.
And whoever holds that
power within their grasp
will have the ability to
conquer the entire world.
Power...
[window opens, wind howls]
I should go. I don't want
Lindo to get worried.
[footsteps]
[REM]
Hm?
[SHIKI]
Well, look who we found.
Hey, catch!
A souvenir from Vienna.
[REM]
What about the exorcists?
[MAGE]
We crushed 'em, of course.
[URIE]
Did you expect anything less?
[SHIKI] It wasn't as thrilling
as I had anticipated.
[REM]
I see.
Are you kidding me right now?!
Not at all. What's up?
I want an explanation
for why you lied to us
and treated us like idiots!
Idiots?
Cut the crap.
First you make up
stuff about Vienna
and then we end up
doing your dirty work?
It's enough to make
us start to wonder
what exactly we are to you.
[URIE] But don't worry we're
not gonna hold our breath
and expect to hear
you call us friends.
You're all being ridiculous.
We respect status and
tradition. Is that clear?
I don't have time
to be manipulated
by these silly
emotions of yours.
So glad you brought that up.
'Cause it reminds me to
ask what your plan was.
What are you talking about?
Rem. Let's not play these games,
we all know the grimoire
was never in Vienna.
You just didn't want it to end
up in our hands, am I right?
Or should I say for her
to end up in our hands.
Our dear, sweet Ritsuka.
That's some theory.
[URIE]
Are you calling me a liar?
[REM]
This is absurd.
So then, you won't
mind if I take her?
[MAGE growls]
[SHIKI] The grimoire belongs
to the Arlond family.
That's fine with me.
I only care about
keeping the girl.
There's no way in hell,
you creep!
Ritsuka's gonna be
with me, got it?
[REM growls]
I want her laughter and I want
her tears. I want it all.
Sorry, but you can't
have my butterfly.
[MAGE growls]
[URIE] I won't let you.
She's my little pet.
[REM growls]
None of you will
touch the grimoire!
[URIE] Hmph. Well then. Guess
she's important to you, too.
So do you love her?
Gonna fight for her?
Have you lost your minds?
What is up with this
obsession with feelings?
What are you guys, humans?
It is quite a nuisance,
but you should know,
not even a devil can hide
from his emotions.
So what's the deal, Rem?
[REM] Nothing. We're talking
about the grimoire.
[SHIKI] We're also talking
about Ritsuka.
That's all she is!
[inaudible]
[REM grunts]
[URIE] If you're going
to insist on lying to us
about things like this,
we're not going to be able
to trust you anymore.
♪♪♪
♪ Quit hiding from
your desires ♪
♪ We've all grown tired
of all your lies ♪
♪ Just accept
what you feel inside ♪
♪ Don't try to pretend
like it's nothing ♪
♪ We see the truth ♪
Feelings? You have
got to be kidding me.
I have no need for those.
♪ Just cut the crap! ♪
♪ You look like a fool
Tryin' to play it cool ♪
♪ No more excuses now,
just say it ♪
♪ You want her so badly ♪
♪ You're consumed
by your feelings ♪
That's enough.
She's the forbidden grimoire.
She means nothing more to me.
[SHIKI]
♪ You know you're wrong ♪
♪ She's so much more
than just the grimoire ♪
♪ She's a girl,
an oh-so-fragile human ♪
♪ Surely you have
seen her charm ♪
♪ There's no way
you could ignore ♪
♪ It's unequaled ♪
Heh. You must be kidding!
♪ Why won't you hurry
and spit it out ♪
[MAGE]
♪ Don't be a chicken! ♪
♪ Speak up, can't hear you ♪
[ALL]
♪ You can't hide any longer ♪
♪ We see the real you:
emo liar ♪
♪ Seriously, these lies
have been such a pain ♪
[URIE] ♪ She is the light that
can brighten your gloomy days ♪
♪ What you need to get you
through the darkness ♪
[MAGE]
♪ When you feel cold and alone ♪
♪ She's the one who
brings you warmth ♪
[SHIKI]
♪ She has the power to turn ♪
♪ All the world with
just her touch ♪
[ALL] ♪ Let's set the stage,
the battle begins ♪
♪ We will fight for her love
Who will win in the end? ♪
♪ Anyone could be a contender ♪
♪ Play dirty,
or you could play fairly ♪
[URIE]
♪ Make your intentions clear ♪
[MAGE]
♪ You're so annoying ♪
[SHIKI]
♪ No lies, it's getting rude ♪
[ALL] ♪ Just be frank about your
own emotions now: emo liar ♪
♪ Don't be an idiot
We're all tired of it ♪
♪ The time have come for
the truth We need to know ♪
♪ Tell us honestly the way
you feel about her ♪
♪ Spit it out ♪
♪ Come on, spit it out! ♪
[RITSUKA panting]
No!
Uh.
We meet again,
Miss Tachibana.
Daughter of man,
keeper of the grimoire.
[gasps]
Won't you come with me, my dear?
For the sake of
your sweet mother,
and for that brave and
foolish knight of yours.
Where are they? Tell me.
[JEK] Heh. We were once
human ourselves, you know.
We experienced love.
We were parents, and
children, and siblings.
[RITSUKA]
What?
That's why we've been taking
such good care of her.
Your mother is safe with us.
How can you say that?
You kidnapped her!
It was like she vanished.
[JEK]
Well, I suppose that is true.
[RITSUKA]
You're lying to me!
You don't know where
my mom is, do you?
[JEK]
Honestly.
Why in the world would I need to
make up something like that?
Oh, I see.
You're used to associating
yourself with the devils.
Unlike them,
I don't need to trick you.
If I wanted to, I could get rid
of you easier than this apple.
[gasps]
It's quite sweet.
Makes me wonder...
...will your blood
be just as tasty?
Wait. You're a vampire?
[JEK laughs]
[sighs] I'll be back soon.
Don't worry.
[RITSUKA]
Thank you for everything.
Done already? My, that was
certainly a very quick goodbye.
Well, the sooner we leave,
the sooner my family
will be back together.
[JEK chuckles]
[RITSUKA]
Ahh! Oh, I'm so sorry!
You should be!
Why don't you watch
where you're goin'?!
Huh?
Oh, uh. Lord Jek,
is this girl with you?
And if she is?
Forgive me. I had no idea.
You remind me why I hate humans.
Always so fickle, they can
never make up their minds.
[MAN 10A whimpers]
[MAN 10A]
No! [whimpers, screams]
[RITSUKA] You promise
my mother's all right?
[JEK]
Of course.
A vampire would never tell a
lie, because it's beneath us.
A devil is a different story.
[RITSUKA]
What do you mean?
[JEK]
What do I mean?
Only that devils are truly
the lowest of the low.
[gasping]
[gasps]
[gasps] Mom, I'm here!
Careful now. You don't
want to wake her.
Huh?
She's so peaceful
when she's dreaming.
It must be quite a happy one.
Uh? What did you do?!
It's nothing for you to
get all upset about.
She's strong enough
to handle a feeding.
Stop worrying. We wouldn't turn
just anyone into a vampire.
[RITSUKA]
Mom...
Uh! Ritsuka!
This is futile.
Why are we fighting?
We don't have the grimoire.
[MAGE] Yeah. Guess we
should find her first.
And with that traitor,
Roen, in the picture,
our first priority should be to
get to her before Maksis does.
I never liked that dog.
I'd love to get
my hands on his neck
and remind him who
he's messing with.
He's gonna regret the day
he chose to play us.
We've got enough
trouble on our hands.
Confronting Roen is a
problem for some other time.
Like I said, we need to focus
on tracking down Ritsuka.
[URIE]
Look, Rem.
We haven't forgotten that
you're the Arlond heir.
We respect that.
And I think we can all
agree that it's imperative
to keep the grimoire
away from Maksis.
We want to trust you.
But until you decide to be
completely honest with the
three of us, don't think that
we're going to hand her over.
[SHIKI, MAGE]
Mm.
What's the matter,
do you think it's poisoned?
What do you want from me?
Let's see... Maybe a
fairy tale will help.
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
Once upon a time
there was a professor.
A man who was intent
on finding answers
to all the great mysteries of
the world in which we live.
What fascinated the
professor most of all
was the magic of
the forbidden grimoire.
But soon, the devils found out.
Once the professor
possessed that grimoire
and its mysterious power,
those devils knew they
needed it for themselves.
And one devil made
it his mission
to trick the man and get
what he wanted most.
You see, the professor
had a daughter,
both beautiful and wise.
This devil thought if he could
get close to the man,
he could not only take the
grimoire but, also the daughter.
From their union,
a child was born.
She was the first human
born of royal devil blood
in over 615 years.
Within this child lay the power
to rule the entire world.
This was the forbidden grimoire.
The devil was overjoyed.
His daughter contained
the strength to rule
not only the demon realm,
but heaven and earth, as well.
Legend has it the
devil king, Maksis,
and his lover, Maria
named their daughter...
...Ritsuka.
[RITSUKA gasping]
That's right. Maksis, the
devil king, is your father.
[MARIA]
Ritsuka...
[RITSUKA gasping]
Mom?
I'm here!
Ritsuka. I'm sorry
about all of this.
It's okay.
[MARIA]
This is my fault.
[RITSUKA] Mm-mm.
Don't say things like that.
It's such... such a
terrible burden for you.
So unfair for a human child to
hold such a superhuman power.
But you were never really
fully human, Ritsuka.
Not when the devil's
blood runs through you.
[gasps]
[JEK]
It's a power you didn't ask for,
but it claimed you anyway.
You had no choice in the
matter. You poor thing.
[RITSUKA]
I'm glad.
[JEK]
Mm? What'd you say?
[RITSUKA]
All this time,
I never understood why
this was happening to me.
I mean, I'm supposed to be
a normal high school girl.
But all these crazy
things kept occurring.
The people I loved got hurt.
And I couldn't help but wonder
why I had to go
through all of it.
But now, now I know it's because
I'm the devil king's daughter.
It was me.
I made everyone suffer.
I wish... I wish I
had never been born.
None of this would've happened.
Uh?
If you trust me, I can
make everything better.
Really? How in the world
could you possibly do that?
It's a secret. One I think
the vampire king himself
would like to tell
you the details of.
Vampire king? What?
The ruler of destruction
and confusion. Lord Nesta.
When the devils started
to oppress the vampires,
he gave us refuge.
But our oppression ends now
and a new day is dawning.
Because the time has
come for Lord Nesta
to defeat the devils
once and for all.
He will release you from
the burden of the grimoire
and use its power to punish
those devils for their crimes.
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
Once he possesses it,
he will be unstoppable,
no one will be his equal!
Even the devil king,
Maksis, will live in fear.
But wait. How exactly would
he remove the grimoire?
Beats me. Our king
wouldn't divulge
something that sacred
to underlings.
But you, my dear,
are running out of options.
And the clock is ticking.
I've told you all
you need to know,
and it's up to you do decide.
Either you choose to
surrender the grimoire,
or it's the end of the road.
Both for you and your mother.
Come along now, Ritsuka.
Lord Nesta is waiting.
[RITSUKA]
Mm...
[RITSUKA grunting]
Please. Ladies first.
[RITSUKA]
What about my mom?
We'll take good care of her.
And I've told you a vampire
would never tell a lie.
All right. I've made
my decision.
Take me to this "Vampire King".
[BOAT MAN 10A laughs]
[JEK] Once Lord Nesta removes
the devils from this world,
he'll claim the demon
realm for us vampires.
When that time comes,
we won't care about the humans.
You will be free to live
your lives as you please.
It will be your very own
happily ever after.
You know. Just like
out of a fairy tale.
Oh, no.
[REM]
Ritsuka.
[panting] Ritsuka.
Where are you?
[gasps]
[VAMPIRES]
Ritsuka.
[NESTA] It's time to
fulfill your destiny,
daughter of the devil king.
[NESTA laughs]
[DEVILS] Act 11:
"Samba of Jet and Crimson."