[VOICE laughing]
[VOICES laughing]
[RITSUKA panting]
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
[URIE]
I'll hold you close.
[gasps]
[URIE]
Until you fall apart.
I'll hold you close.
[RITSUKA gasping]
Lindo!
You planning to sleep
the day away?
That's a shame since
it's so pretty out.
[RITSUKA exhales]
[RITSUKA gasps]
I'm doing laundry.
Where're your dirty clothes?
[LINDO gasping]
Are you sick?
I'm okay, just feeling
a bit tired I guess.
Well, I'll take
good care of you.
Try to take it easy.
Just like old times,
you remember?
[LINDO] Ritsuka!
Oh, c'mon don't cry, sis.
If you want me to I can
talk to mom for you, okay?
[RITSUKA]
Really?
[LINDO]
It'll be fine.
'Cause I'll take
good care of you.
'Kay!
[RITSUKA]
You were just like a prince,
the way you were constantly
watching out for me.
And I'd think,
"Wow I have the coolest
brother in the whole world!"
But now look at you.
I'm not cool? That it?
Heh! Hey, you said it, not me!
I'm still cool!
[RITSUKA grunting]
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
What on earth?
Why is it locked?
Uh!
Lindo? Did you do this?
I did. I have to protect
you, Ritsuka.
Please try to understand.
But...
Tell me.
There's a rumor you're
an exorcist. Is it true?
Huh?!
[LINDO] I'm sure you
remember that grandpa
used to study folklores
and demonology.
[RITSUKA]
Yeah.
[LINDO] He was the top
researcher in his field.
Unfortunately, being the
best attracted grandpa
unwanted attention from some
rather nasty creatures.
What kind of nasty creatures?
Well. Honestly. They were
vampires and devils.
In the end, they
murdered grandpa.
But wait, I thought he
got sick and passed away.
Only because he was stricken
with a fatal curse.
What?
Now you know.
That's the reason we kept
you away when he died.
I was there with him
in his final moments.
Afflicted by the curse,
he was no longer human.
Grandpa was unbelievably
worried about you and mom.
Before he died,
he made me promise
that I would keep our
family safe. No matter what.
[RITSUKA]
I see. But why? Why you, Lindo?
[LINDO]
All this devil and vampire stuff
has been hammered into
me since I was a kid.
The folklore, the
demonology, all of it.
Protecting you,
and mom... our family,
that has been my job for years.
So you became an exorcist.
Did Mom know about everything?
She did.
And that's why she nagged
you to wear your pendant.
[LINDO] Potpourri repels evil.
I don't get it.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
We were planning to soon.
Mom and I were going to tell you
everything before your birthday.
But then, those guys came along.
No way! There's no
way this is true!
But... Uh...
Where is the forbidden
grimoire? Tell me. Now.
Red eyes.
[LINDO]
Red eyes means vampire.
Whoever took mom
was probably one.
For real? But then...
...why'd they take her and why
on earth are they after me?
[LINDO] Grandpa had a
pretty good theory.
He believed that the devils'
power is starting to fade.
And so, the vampires are just
capitalizing on the opportunity.
And that's where the
grimoire comes into play.
[gasps]
[LINDO]
Do you know what it is?
Only the name.
[LINDO] The grimoire is
extremely powerful.
Whoever possesses it
could potentially control
the entire world.
[gasps]
[LINDO] These creatures believe
that the Tachibana family
is the key to the grimoire's
whereabouts.
That's why they
targeted you and mom.
But what for?!
I don't know anything!
And I definitely don't
know where it is!
Tell me about the grimoire.
I really need to find it, and
you're the key that can help me.
Hold on.
Back when I was at the
amusement park with Urie,
he knew about the book.
All of the student
council know.
Urie Sogami,
Mage Nanashiro,
Shiki Natsumezaka,
and Rem Kaginuki.
They know because
they're devils.
Devils? You've gotta
be joking, right?
Rem has done nothing but go
out of his way constantly.
He even saved my life
twice already!
Oh, and he also said that
it was the devil worshippers
who probably took mom.
You cannot trust him!
Yeah, so anyway.
Do you have any idea
where the grimoire is?
No, I don't.
Here's what I do know.
Vampires, and yes
the devils too.
They're looking everywhere
for the grimoire.
You need to understand
that they'll stop at nothing
to get it. They killed
grandpa and took mom.
Ritsuka, I just wanna
keep you safe.
Believe me. Everything's
going to be fine.
I promise to protect you.
There are devils and vampires.
So was that the power
of a devil? But then...
You're all right!
Oh Rem, I was so
worried about you!
♪ ♪
♪ I want to believe ♪
♪ That he cares enough to not
do something to hurt me ♪
♪ Why won't you believe? ♪
♪ I'm the only one who'll
always keep your smile safe ♪
Ritsuka...
♪ I can hear a voice inside ♪
♪ Proclaiming this
is your destiny ♪
♪ All this love is for
no one else but you ♪
♪ I told myself that you were
Just my beloved sister ♪
♪ Younger than me,
helpless and sweet ♪
♪ Only siblings, nothing more ♪
♪ Yet there are feelings that I
Can't seem to put to the side ♪
♪ So then I
Chose to become one ♪
♪ An exorcist so I'm
always protecting you ♪
♪ I bear the mark
of an eternal sin ♪
♪ Through my whole body
it flows ♪
♪ So I'll give everything I have
within For I know I must atone ♪
♪ Can you hear
the voice of love ♪
♪ Although I may
never be forgiven ♪
♪ True love, so powerful
It'll soon tear me apart ♪
♪ I am yours, I am yours alone
Your personal exorcist ♪
♪ Sworn to be yours
for all eternity ♪
♪ I would gladly give
my life for you ♪
No matter what it takes,
I'll keep her safe.
[RITSUKA grunting]
Nailed it!
'Kay. Here goes.
[RITSUKA] Sorry Lindo, but
I've gotta learn the truth.
Uh!
Oh, hi, uh... Is Rem here?
Are you on the student
council, too?
[chuckles]
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
[footsteps]
[RITSUKA]
There you are!
[REM]
Uh.
Do you need something?
Well, you see,
you've been so nice
about all the stuff going on
with my mom, although...
I just wonder if you're doing
it because of the grimoire.
You keep rescuing me, and I feel
so safe when I'm with you.
I need to know that
it's genuine.
[REM] Your brother hates me.
That complicates things.
[gasps]
You shouldn't spend time
with me anymore.
I'm sorry, but I can't continue
to offer you my help.
[RITSUKA]
Hold up!
[STUDENT 4A]
It's "the Great Rem!"
Hello, I'm looking
for Miss Tachibana.
[STUDENT 4A]
Ritsuka?
[STUDENT 4B]
I haven't seen her.
[STUDENT 4C]
But why her?
Oh sorry, but Ritsuka's
not at school today,
is everything all right?
Are you sure?
She was just at
the third library.
[AZUNA]
Huh?
Oh, well.
Aw, crap.
May the ancient blessing
rest upon you.
Accept this sacred power,
for once in your hands it
shall serve you forevermore.
[RITSUKA]
Well, Rem.
I'm no closer to the truth
than I was at home.
[STUDENT 4D]
The president?
[STUDENT 4E]
That's what I heard!
Let's get on it!
[RITSUKA]
Hold up.
Did you just mention something
about the student
council president?
Yeah, he's been asking
around for some girl.
[RITSUKA]
Who is it?
Something like... Tachibana?
Right. I think it's Rika...?
[STUDENT 4E] That's it!
She was in trouble recently.
[STUDENT 4D]
If we bring her to the president
we'll be his new favorites!
Hey, are you in?
Uh! Nah.
[STUDENT 4D]
Your loss!
Yeah!
That's odd. What could
he want from me?
[gasps] Oh, Rem!
What a surprise.
Whoa, you're smiling.
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka? Ritsuka!
[RITSUKA]
Azuna?
[RITSUKA gasps]
Let's go.
[RITSUKA]
Uh, okay, where?
[LINDO]
Anything?
[AZUNA]
No.
[AZUNA] Don't worry,
I'll keep looking around.
Show me the way.
What once was lost
must now be found.
[RITSUKA panting]
Wait up!
I needed to ask you something.
About the council.
Is it true? Rem, are you
all really devils?
[LINDO]
Ritsuka!
[RITSUKA]
Uh. Lindo?
[chuckles]
Wait a sec. You're not...
[RITSUKA]
Stop! Get off me!
[FAKE REM chuckles]
[gasps]
[FAKE REMS chuckle]
[RITSUKA] What's going on?
How're you doing this?
You are a devil!
Someone. Help me!
[LINDO grunts]
[gasps]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
He didn't hurt you at all?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Would you look at that?
They actually fell for it.
My plan is working perfectly.
What will you do?
Time to show me your true
power, Mister Exorcist.
[FAKE REMS growling]
Lindo, please! Stop this!
Someone help!
You can't...
[FAKE REM chuckles]
Stop it.
[laughs]
I said stop!
[LINDO gasps]
Ritsuka!
I don't care you're all human,
screw this nice guy stuff.
By the sacred name, you
will obey my command.
Those hidden in shadows.
I renounce you.
Be gone!
[FAKE REMS groan]
[RITSUKA]
Rem!
[REM]
What is this?
[LINDO]
Hey! Stay away from my sister!
Oh, that smell. It's faint
but still enticing.
I think I've seen
enough for one day.
This proved to be
very enlightening.
Where have you been all day?
[RITSUKA] You protected me,
like you promised.
It was really cool. I didn't
know you had it in you.
Thanks for the vote
of confidence.
Well I hope now
you believe me.
The council is
made up of devils.
Maybe. I don't know.
I just don't think that Rem
could really be bad.
It's so hard to believe.
Ritsuka you seriously
don't get it, do you?
No, I don't get it at all.
That's why I've decided to go
back to school tomorrow.
What for?
I'm sick and tired of
not knowing stuff!
I'm going to find some answers.
If you try to stop me,
I'll just break out.
Heh. I was starting to think
that my little sister
had finally grown up
a bit this year.
Yet I see you're still
as stubborn as ever.
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
[LINDO] Take this.
It's a ring of the Sacred Lux.
As long as you wear it,
you'll be safe.
Wow, the Sacred Lux.
Listen, if you really
wanna go back to school,
I won't stop you.
For real?
However, starting tomorrow,
I'll be going to school, too.
Uh! Seriously?
Like my school?
Your school.
Huh?!
Things are finally
falling into place.
Although, I still have
to find the grimoire
before anyone else does.
I want the grimoire, but then...
♪ ♪
♪ Do you still believe ♪
♪ Deep down in your heart? ♪
♪ So kind and
sensitive you are ♪
♪ What if that pure heart
Should be torn apart? ♪
♪ How will you
feel about it then? ♪
[LINDO] By the sacred name
you will obey my command.
Those hidden in shadows.
I renounce your presence.
Now be gone!
[ALL screaming]
[LINDO] I'll protect Ritsuka,
no matter what the cost.
[JEK]
Strange.
Why would you target us?
[MAGE] Guess you really
want to see what happens
when you defy a devil.
We don't got all day.
Get ready.
Cause this is amazing.
Act 5: "B-Boying of
Vainglory and Impulse."