[REM] But I think all
these events are related.
Your house being attacked,
your mother disappearing,
and there're the incidents we
are dealing with at the Academy.
It would seem that
Shinko Academy
is housing a group
of devil worshippers.
Where is the forbidden
grimoire? Tell me.
[RITSUKA] Maybe now the
police will believe me.
[REM]
I'll call them on your behalf.
They'll listen to me.
The authorities greatly
respect the Kaginuki name.
Are you sure I can't
change your mind?
[gasping]
Yes.
My brother's coming back
from England tonight,
so I'll just hang out
with my friend Azuna
until his flight gets in.
You'd be safer if you
stayed at my house.
There's still a possibility
something might happen.
That's true.
I'll be fine, though!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 2A]
Oh, Rem is here!
[STUDENT 2B]
He's beyond gorgeous!
[RITSUKA gasps]
What is it?
Nothing!
So, um, thank you for
putting me up for the night.
Uh... See you later!
--[RITSUKA panting]
--[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 2C] Whoa! Did she just
say what I think she said?
[STUDENT 2AA] She's the one
that got in trouble, right?
[STUDENT 2D] I think her
name's Ritsuka Tachibana.
[STUDENT 2BB]
What'd that girl even do?
[STUDENT 2E]
Who does she think she is,
staying at the
Great Rem's house?
[RITSUKA groans] No, it's so
not what they're thinking!
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka!
Uh!
Azuna!
Oh, thank goodness!
[AZUNA]
I was I was so worried!
Oh, sorry about that. I'm okay.
Silly, there's nothing
to apologize for.
[AZUNA] Wow that's crazy.
Um, any news on your mom?
[RITSUKA]
No news.
[AZUNA]
Sorry.
[RITSUKA]
Rem said he'd call the police,
so I should hear something soon.
He's pretty influential.
Must be a Kaginuki thing.
Yeah. I was wrong about him.
Huh?
You know, what I said yesterday.
About how the president
acted like such a jerk?
Well, last night,
he was really great.
Oh.
He tried to deny it, though.
Said he was just helping
the school. But still...
He saved me from those bad guys.
I'm so glad.
[TEACHER 2A] "If it's for
everyone's happiness,
I'm ready to have my body
burned like that Scorpion.
Even a hundred times."
[RITSUKA]
This is the same old classroom.
These are the same old lessons.
But, everything seems
so different, now.
Oh, Mom...
[bell tolls]
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka.
Uh?
Let's go get some food.
Sorry. I'm not very hungry.
[AZUNA] It's important to
make sure you eat properly,
especially at times like these.
[STUDENT 1C]
Hey Ritsuka! You're needed.
Hello, Miss Tachibana.
The president has
requested your presence.
Did the police find out
where those guys took my mom?
Don't know
Hold on. You want
me to come, too?
[STUDENT 2CC]
No.
You weren't asked for.
Only Miss Tachibana.
'Scuse me?
Don't worry, Azuna.
I'll be fine.
[gasping]
Okay.
[RITSUKA]
You came to school, huh?
[dog growls]
It's such a pleasure to see you
again my sweet little butterfly.
[dog barks]
You are...?
My name's Urie Sogami.
Enchanté.
Y'know, you can always
ask me for help.
Forget "the Great Rem."
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
It would be my honor to help
such a beautiful lady like you.
[RITSUKA gasping]
[dog barks]
[gasps] I'm good.
[URIE]
Aw, you're blushing.
[SHIKI]
Enough Urie, leave her alone.
Ignore him. Hi there,
I'm Shiki Natsumezaka.
Rem told us about your woes.
You poor thing!
Please let me know if you
need anything, okay?
[SHIKI]
Such a defenseless little girl.
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
When I think of all
the horrible things
that could've possibly happened.
The thought makes me shudder.
[MAGE] Dude, can you stop being
such a creeper all the time?
Hey, I'm here if
you ever need me.
Just ask for Mage
Nanashiro, babe.
Hands off, pal!
Come on!
You're totally safe with me,
so don't even worry about it.
[RITSUKA]
Thanks, but no thanks!
[SHIKI laughs]
Call the wambulance,
Mage just got burned!
[MAGE] Why don't you
shut your pie hole?
[SHIKI laughing]
[URIE] Here my butterfly,
won't you enjoy this rose?
[MAGE] She doesn't want
your stinky flower.
[URIE] Says the guy who
smells like a jockstrap!
[MAGE] Least I smell
like a man, pansy picker!
[BOTH growling]
[SHIKI] Wow, they're pretty
ridiculous aren't they?
But I, on the other hand...
--[SHIKI yelps]
--[dog growls]
Dumb rat! That hurt!
Do you want me to turn you
into a pair of fuzzy slippers?
Please stop.
[REM]
What's going on in here?
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
Oh, Rem, it's you!
[SHIKI]
Uh!
Ritsuka, I just
got off the phone
with the police department.
So, uh, any news?
Yes, there is something.
They tracked your mom's last
location using her phone's GPS.
[RITSUKA]
Where is she?
In Nagano. Not too far
from Karuizawa.
Nagano?
[REM]
So you're familiar with it?
My grandpa's house is there.
[REM]
That's interesting.
I recall you saying
that he studied demons
and vampires, correct?
[RITSUKA] Yeah, his research
materials might still be around.
[REM]
Then let's go.
I think it's likely
we'll find a clue
to your mother's whereabouts.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[phone rings]
Uh!
Be careful.
[MAGE grunts]
Man, why did Rem have to go
and take that chick
with him to Nagano.
Seriously, a real man would
have just gone alone.
[URIE chuckles] I wouldn't
risk underestimating him
if I were you.
If anything he took her
along because Rem knew
the girl might end
up being useful.
[MAGE]
Hm?
[URIE] It's possible our
sweet Miss Tachibana
could be hiding a clue
of which she is unaware.
More like he took her
because the "Arlond heir"
gets to do whatever he wants.
Quiet.
You know he's known as
the "Kaginuki" heir here.
[MAGE]
Whatever, man. I know.
Did you get a chance
to eat lunch?
No, but I'm not that hungry.
You should make sure
you eat properly,
especially at times like these.
What is it?
Oh, sorry, it's just my friend
told me the same thing earlier.
Are you going to eat it or not?
[RITSUKA]
Uh, sure.
It's delicious!
You've done so much for me.
Thank you. You know,
like "again."
I haven't done anything
that deserves your gratitude.
[RITSUKA]
But because of me you had to go
out of your way yesterday.
And then today as well.
I'm unbelievably grateful.
So, um, you must be, like,
a serious dog lover.
Huh?
That Pomeranian at the library.
I also saw him
back at your house.
Oh, Roen just likes to follow
me around everywhere.
[RITSUKA]
Aw, his name is Roen?
[REM]
Do you always talk this much?
[RITSUKA]
Sorry.
You don't like shitake
mushrooms?
I don't exactly hate them.
Okay.
But you can't really
call mushrooms food.
When you think about it,
they're just a gross fungus
that grows on trees.
Gross fungus?
[gasps] It's over there!
[RITSUKA gasps]
Oh, no.
[REM] Careful, the culprits
could still be inside.
So sad...
[gasps] My mom!
Hey, mom?!
My mom... She's not here.
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
This is her phone!
That means she's
been in the house!
Oh, Mom.
[gasps]
It'll be okay. I know
we're going to find her.
I think it's safe to assume
those devil worshippers
are behind this, too.
My best guess? They're
most likely still looking
for the forbidden
grimoire they were
asking you
about last night.
Could your grandfather
have kept it here?
Maybe. I'm not sure.
Is this grimoire really
important or something?
To them, apparently.
[RITSUKA]
Well grandpa kept
a lot of important
books and papers.
I suppose he could've had it.
Is there anywhere else
where he may have put
his more valuable possessions?
I honestly have no clue.
When we were little,
we'd come visit him.
I always looked forward
to spending holidays here.
Mom, Grandpa, Lindo and I,
we always had so
much fun together.
[REM] Is this your
mom and grandfather?
[RITSUKA] Uh. Yeah. The picture
next to them is my mom's sister.
Interesting.
Do you think your aunt
might know anything
about the grimoire?
[RITSUKA]
I wish that we could ask her,
but she died when I was a baby.
[REM]
I'm... sorry.
[REM] There's no time
to clean up right now.
But I can't just leave it.
Tell you what, I'll send some
of my servants over later.
You're welcome to
come with them.
That way you can have some help.
Okay, yeah, thanks.
[RITSUKA]
I'll find you.
[gasps, grunts]
What's wrong?
The door is stuck!
Meaning they trapped us in.
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
Isn't there another
exit in the kitchen?
[RITSUKA]
Yeah.
[crackling]
[REM]
Watch out.
[gasps] I'll go get
the fire extinguisher!
[REM]
No, wait!
[gasps] No!
[VAMPIRE 2A laughs]
[RITSUKA grunts]
[REM]
Get out of here.
Fast as you can.
Right...
[chuckles]
Don't tell me that's
what you call a fire.
♪♪♪
So we meet again.
♪ All of you vulgar fellows,
hear me and begone ♪
♪ I must warn you to not
block the path I tread ♪
♪ My heart of ice ensures there
is no mercy to be shown ♪
♪ Your time is up. ♪
♪ You're nothing but
a pitiful marionette ♪
♪ Go on and dance for me
in the palm of my hand ♪
♪ Dance till the hour
of your doom ♪
♪ I have laid claim
to this enchanting girl ♪
♪ She will be,
mine completely ♪
♪ Keep your filthy
hands off of her ♪
♪ Behold! I'm the one
and only Rem Arlond ♪
♪ Even the darkness bows
before the Prince of Despair! ♪
♪ Now, this is where this
silly game comes to an end ♪
♪ For I have declared
a checkmate ♪
♪ It's finally here ♪
♪ The end of the
dark-side game ♪
I let him get away again.
[VAMPIRE 2A groans]
Did you happen to
find the grimoire?
[groans]
[REM chuckels]
I'll take that as a "no."
We begin and end as dust.
We'll call this checkmate.
[VAMPIRE 2A yelps]
He's still not out.
Please be okay!
[REM]
I'm fine.
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
You're all right!
Oh, Rem, I was so
worried about you!
[RITSUKA cries]
No need to cry. I'm fine.
[EMERGENCY PERSONNEL chattering]
Why, Rem?
Why is this happening
to my family? Oh, mom.
[REM]
Drive us home.
As you wish, Master.
[RITSUKA]
Lindo!
Lindo! You're finally back!
It'll be okay now. I'm home.
[URIE] I know a lot of things
about your family.
Maybe you should ask your
brother what he's hiding.
[RITSUKA]
There's no way...
[URIE] Don't worry.
We're in my Eden now.
Act 3: "Tango of Passion
and Seduction."