[RITSUKA] The school
festival's almost here,
and I've been really busy
getting ready for it.
So many crazy things
have happened.
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
It's like my heart is
telling me one thing
and my head is
telling me another.
I know it may not be
the safest place for me,
but I want to go to school.
When I'm here, I feel like
I'm closer to finding my mom.
But more than anything,
I can't be afraid of them.
[RITSUKA]
I haven't seen Rem.
Not since that day.
The day that everything changed.
[LINDO] Ye evil ones,
ye who lurk in darkness.
Ye sinister ones.
May the sacred power of
light banish and repel ye.
Now listen to me. Be careful.
The festival will be
full of outsiders.
Which means there will
probably be vampires
as well as devils there.
'Kay.
[gasps]
Good. The scratches have healed.
They looked much
worse than they were.
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine, really.
[doorbell chimes]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[AZUNA]
Morning, Ritsuka!
[RITSUKA]
Morning!
[nervous laughter]
Here's the deal.
You are not to go anywhere
without Azuna or me, understood?
There'll be no
exceptions this time.
Okay, okay.
I promise you guys. No one will
find out until after I turn 17.
I know how important this is.
Good.
We're all gonna make it
through this together.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[RITSUKA]
Wow! It's all so pretty!
This is nothing like the
festivals we used to have
back in middle school.
Yeah!
Oh right, I forgot
it's your first one.
Our school's festival is pretty
over the top awesome.
And just wait until tonight.
The dance is gorgeous.
Cool.
[SHIKI] Where could he be
hiding? Maybe down here?
[URIE]
All right, Fallen Angel,
that's enough creeping
around from you.
Just give it a rest.
Yeah, who cares where he is?
Rem can take care of himself.
Not him. I meant Roen.
I have to find that
yappy little fluff ball.
[REM] You won't be seeing
him around here.
He's abused our trust
and betrayed us.
What does that mean?
[REM] He manipulated us to think
he was an innocent, loyal puppy.
But it was simply a ploy
to help his previous master.
The fallen king, Maksis?
He's still around?
Yeah, cause I coulda sworn
your Dad defeated that dude
and sealed his ass away.
Ah yes, but the forbidden
grimoire could change that.
I guess that means
Roen was after it, too.
But, he wanted to use its
powers to revive Maksis.
[REM] Yes.
[URIE] What a shocking
turn of events.
[MAGE] Good thing he didn't
find the grimoire first.
No, I did. Recent information
has helped me locate it.
[ALL gasp]
So you got her to come clean?
Not quite.
You see the Tachibana Family
never had the grimoire
to begin with.
Before his death,
Professor Tachibana had made
arrangements to hide it.
But where?
[REM]
Vienna.
Vienna?
In an old church,
outside the city.
My men are on their way
to retrieve it as we speak.
[ALL grunt]
[REM]
Checkmate.
May the darkest of blessings
be upon this ill-fated world.
Destined for the Arlond family.
So this world's really gonna be
at the mercy of Rem's dad?
Yep. Even if we swear our
loyalty to that family,
we'll be lucky if we end up
with the dregs when it's over.
You're not thinking this
through. It's perfect.
All we have to do is let Rem
lead us to the grimoire.
And then we snatch it away
from him at the last moment.
[URIE] Let me tell you who's
not thinking things through.
[SHIKI groans]
[SHIKI]
Uh?
What kinda low lives
do you think
would go for that plan anyway?
Definitely not us!
Yes. I thought as much.
[MAGE, URIE laugh]
[REM] The grimoire
is keeping her alive.
[REM]
If I remove it, she'll die.
Thank you! Enjoy the festival!
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
[AZUNA]
Uh?
[RITSUKA]
Awkward.
[GIRL 8A]
Stalker alert!
[GIRL 8B]
Totes creepy!
Yeah that's unsettling.
I'll make him move.
[RITSUKA sighs]
Thank you, Azuna.
Uh?
Someone came by to see you.
[laughs]
Well, hello my little butterfly.
Aren't you just as
radiant as ever?
Did you want something?
Why yes, I need a date
for tonight's dance.
So whaddya say to that?
[RITSUKA]
Huh?
There's no need to
fight it. Trust me.
Just give in to
your true feelings,
and let me show you
what I can do.
Get away from me!
Please hear me out.
I know you think I manipulated
you to get to the grimoire.
[RITSUKA]
Mm...
I'm sorry.
Turns out you honestly didn't
know anything about it.
But--
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
I don't normally go around
romantically abducting girls.
We found out today that
the forbidden grimoire
is actually in Vienna.
[gasps] Wait... What?
[MAGE]
That's what Rem told us.
He said that?
Be my date at the party tonight.
I mean, dancing's
not really my thing.
But if you're a girl who likes
to move, I'll make an exception.
Uh! Stop!
[MAGE gasping]
Move it, Mage.
You're in my way.
Ah, shut up! She's not
gonna go with you!
[BOTH growl]
[SHIKI]
Guess who.
[yelps]
Oh my.
Even though you run,
it makes me want you more.
Please say you'll
accompany me this evening.
We'll follow where
temptation leads us.
As the romantic swaying
seduces us deeper.
To places we've
never seen before.
Hold on.
Your intoxicating aroma
seems weaker today.
[RITSUKA grunts]
[MAGE] Yeah, I know!
What's up with that?
[URIE] It's true. I miss
that enchanting scent as well.
[ALL sniffing]
[gasps]
Back off, you sick pervs!
[ALL grunt]
Who the hell invited
this chick?
I've had enough of you butting
in where you don't belong.
Why don't you just
get out of here.
No way in hell!
This is my best friend.
I'm not gonna let you hurt her!
Hey, wait, no one's
tryin' to hurt her.
[LINDO]
Leave! All of you!
By the sacred name, obey me!
O ye who lurk in darkness.
Begone from here!
I said, begone!
Look! It's the Student Council!
OMG. They're so close!
[MAGE, SHIKI, URIE]
Huh?
[FEMALE STUDENTS scream]
[ALL]
Uh...
[URIE] Oh! My sweet butterflies!
This is too much!
[MAGE] Hey! Wait!
Respect the Boss Man!
[SHIKI] Oh Claustrophobia!
You terrible mistress!
[AZUNA] Geez! They really
just don't get it.
That was so weird.
The stuff about Rem,
and him saying the
grimoire was in Vienna.
He definitely just made that up.
[RITSUKA]
You really think he did?
Yeah! To get them off his back.
'Cause he wants to keep
the grimoire all to himself.
Devils lie.
They'll do whatever they have
to, to get what they want.
Right.
[CROWD chattering]
[STUDENT 8E]
Thank you for coming!
Don't forget to take a glass!
[MAN 8A] Grape for the Gentlemen
and Orange for the Ladies.
Whoever gets the crowns will
be our lucky king and queen.
I'm lost.
What is this king and queen
stuff they're talking about?
Oh right, forgot to tell you.
In one of the women's
glasses there's a crown.
And the same goes
for one of the men's.
[STUDENT 8F]
Ohh! Nothing!
[STUDENT 8G]
Bummer! I wanted to be Queen.
[STUDENT 8AA]
There's always next year!
If your glass has the crown,
you become the queen.
The star of the entire evening.
Even sharing a romantic
dance in front of everyone.
[RITSUKA] But what if they
don't know each other?
Tough. It's a really old
festival tradition.
Uh...
Chill. No way you'll get
it your first year.
[clinking]
Uh!
--[RITSUKA gasps]
--[STUDENTS chatter]
[ALL]
Mm?
[gluping]
[growl]
Oh thank God!
[MAGE, SHIKI, URIE growl]
[RITSUKA] I wonder who
the king is gonna be.
[STUDENT 8G screams]
The Great Rem is here!
[GIRLS chattering]
Glad you're here.
We saved a glass for you.
Thank you so much.
[clinking]
[REM]
Huh?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[gasps]
[ALL grunt]
[STUDENT 8I] The Great Rem
is this year's King!
[STUDENT 8J]
It's not fair!
I don't want him dancing
with some other girl!
[STUDENTS chattering]
You can't!
Ritsuka! You have to switch!
[STUDENTS shouting]
[STUDENTS] Our Happy King! Our
Happy Queen! Congratulations!
[applause]
[RITSUKA] I can't believe
this is really happening.
What an odd coincidence.
Who would've thought you
and I would get the crowns?
Strange, don't you think?
[RITSUKA]
I guess so.
[SHIKI]
Well this sucks.
Isn't that convenient.
Do you guys think Rem cheated?
No. He's just lucky.
I didn't pick up on
anyone using any magic.
In my opinion,
that's even worse.
Ritsuka.
Don't worry.
She's safe right now.
There's no way they'd try
anything with a crowd like this.
[tapping]
[orchestral music plays]
[STUDENTS]
Our happy king! Our happy queen!
[gasps]
[gasping]
Wait. Rem, please!
I don't know how!
[REM]
Just follow my lead.
[gulps] 'Kay.
[music continues]
[RITSUKA]
Um. I wanted to thank you.
What precisely did I do
to deserve thanks?
[RITSUKA]
You helped my brother, remember?
[REM]
I was just protecting myself.
[RITSUKA]
Say what you want Rem.
You're not as selfish as
you'd like people to believe.
I know you're protecting me.
I just don't understand why.
[RITSUKA] Our hands.
They're so warm and tingly.
Like my body is
whispering to me.
Like trees swaying in the wind.
♪ ♪
[RITSUKA] ♪ When I look
in your eyes I see ♪
♪ A reflection of me ♪
[REM] ♪ When I look
in your eyes, too ♪
♪ I can see me in you ♪
[RITSUKA] ♪ My hand in yours;
a rush of warmth ♪
♪ A moment to last
for all time ♪
[BOTH]
♪ This emotion we share ♪
[REM]
♪ Could it be love? ♪
[BOTH]
♪ This emotion we share ♪
[RITSUKA]
♪ Must be love ♪
[BOTH] ♪ I want to go on
just like this ♪
--♪ To a place ♪
--♪ that I've seen ♪
♪ In my wildest dreams ♪
[REM]
♪ No tomorrows or yesterdays ♪
♪ No more names
or destinies ♪
[RITSUKA] ♪ Flowers will shower
in cascades of white ♪
♪ As stars shoot across the sky
both day and night ♪
--♪ To a place ♪
--♪ that I've seen ♪
[BOTH]
♪ In my wildest dreams ♪
[STUDENT 8K]
Wow! They're so beautiful!
[STUDENT 8BB] Let's check
'em out on the balcony!
[fireworks popping]
No way.
[BOTH gasp]
Um. Rem, I...
[RITSUKA gasps]
[LINDO grunts]
[RITSUKA] That song is still
running through my head.
I just wish I could know
if what I'm feeling is real.
[AZUNA grunts]
[LINDO grunts]
They're vampires!
We came to get
the sacred tome.
It's known that you've
been protecting it.
[VAMPIRES grunt]
Azuna! Get her home!
On it!
By the sacred name,
you will obey me,
o ye who lurk in darkness!
Begone from here, forevermore!
[VAMPIRES grunt]
[VAMPIRE 8E yelps]
[LINDO]
By the sacred name, obey me!
[VAMPIRES groan]
O ye who lurk in darkness,
begone from here forevermore!
[VAMPIRE 8A screams]
Ritsuka, we're gonna
keep you safe.
Be careful.
[LINDO] Become thou dust in
sacred light and vanish!
Lindo...
Ye who lurk in darkness, begone!
Now!
[LINDO panting]
[footsteps]
[LINDO groans]
[LINDO yells]
[gasps]
Lindo!
[LINDO grunts]
[LINDO growling, yelling]
[RITSUKA whimpers]
[JEK chuckles]
[RITSUKA screams]
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka!
[RITSUKA whimpers]
She goes with me.
No way! Let her go!
[RITSUKA gasps]
[AZUNA]
Are you okay?
[AZUNA gasps]
[JEK]
You'll pay for that.
[RITSUKA gasps]
No!
[ALL grunt]
[RITSUKA whimpering]
Please don't cry.
[RITSUKA]
Azuna? Azuna, please!
Stay with me!
Azuna, please! I need you!
Please don't go!
Azuna, you can't die!
I won't let you! Azuna!
[RITSUKA cries]
[JEK laughing]
We found it!
The grimoire is ours Lord Nesta!
Don't worry, dear.
I'll be back to get you soon.
When the light begins to fade.
[REM]
Give it up.
You cannot protect
her in this state.
[LINDO] I would rather die
than let you take her!
[REM] If that's what you really
want, consider it done.
[LINDO, REM] Act 9: "War Cry
of Secrets and Contrariness."