[AZUNA] Hey! Where's that
brother of yours?
Did he stay home?
[RITSUKA]
Lindo had to run an errand.
But look at this.
He gave me this huge lunch.
[AZUNA]
Whoa!
He put it in a nice
basket and everything!
If that's a normal lunch then
your birthday meal will rock!
Yeah.
Ooh, maybe it'll be expensive!
Maybe.
We're still going to hang out
on my birthday, right?
Are you sure?
Of course I am, silly!
[bell tolls]
Uh-oh. Enough chit chat.
We're gonna be late! Come on.
[RITSUKA]
Right.
Uh?
What's a bird doing in here?
All right, be free!
[gasps]
In order to prove my strength
and keep my power someone
must be the pawn.
And that's the part
you play in all this.
[RITSUKA whimpers]
[RITSUKA]
U-Uh...
Have I not been clear?
You will stop going
behind my back.
I am the Arlond heir.
Everything pertaining to
the grimoire is in my hands.
Do all of you understand?
Sorry, Mister Heir. Have I
missed part of your genius plan?
What do you mean by that?
You've done nothing.
There's no progress.
Meanwhile, the clock's ticking.
Did you forget about
the damn vampires?
They're not gonna go away.
We need to move now if we want
to beat them to the grimoire.
[REM] Those leeches
aren't worth our concern.
[MAGE]
Heh.
[REM] If anything, blame
yourselves for this set back.
Thanks to your foolishness,
the girl won't give me
the information we need.
Whatever, she's like
totally hot for me.
Next time that chick
will explain everything,
even if it's by force.
My, what a dismal thought.
Want me to show you
how it's done?
That's enough!
There will be no more
acting out of turn!
Anyway, that little
pawn is essential
if we're going to
find the grimoire.
I won't risk destroying
that chance.
That almost sounded tender.
Yeah it sure did.
[REM]
Watch yourselves.
Very scary! I'm getting
goosebumps.
It seems there are too
many snakes in one room,
I wonder which one
will come out on top?
There can be only one, you know.
What the hell, man?
You're not making sense.
If only one can survive...
...who will it be? Ah!
[MAGE] How 'bout I take
those scissors of yours
and lop off your stupid wings?
[SHIKI] What? Mage, you're
always so mean to me!
[REM] Both of you just
knock it off already.
[SHIKI]
Aw, don't be upset, Rem!
If you guys kick me out, heaven
only knows where I would go.
[URIE] With such wonderful
wings on your back,
the possibilities are endless.
[SHIKI]
Et tu, Urie?
Hey, Roen.
They're being bullies.
Will you play with me?
[ROEN barks]
What is your deal? Stupid rat!
Shiki, calm down.
Leave me alone!
[MAGE] Forget him.
He's just acting like a baby.
Moving along.
Tell me, Rem, what is your next
step towards the grimoire?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[AZUNA] Aw man, I forgot my
notebook! Back in a flash!
[RITSUKA]
Okay!
[SHIKI grunting]
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
[SHIKI grunting]
[RITSUKA]
Um, hey. What're you doing?
Quit that! You're ruining them!
[SHIKI] It's none of
your business! Go away!
[RITSUKA gasps]
Oh, it's you.
What's your name again?
Shiki.
Look, Shiki.
I'm not going to just stand by
while you destroy these flowers.
It's so childish.
So you like flowers?
Huh?
Let me see.
[SHIKI]
Hm...
[RITSUKA gasping]
[SHIKI] Don't leave!
What about the flowers?
You asked me to go away,
so wish granted!
[SHIKI]
I was joking. To be honest,
I was hoping to catch your
attention, Miss Tachibana.
[RITSUKA] Make sure you
get all the thorns out.
Your hankie.
Uh?
May I?
Sure, just go ahead
and keep it, though.
Seriously, get all
the thorns out,
you don't wanna
get an infection.
An infection? How perfect.
Uh?
The pain would be grand.
Each throbbing moment
would remind me of you.
Please stop that.
Why, are you worried about me?
Well maybe a little bit.
You're hurt after all.
[gasping]
[SHIKI]
Your smell is so lovely.
Uh.
[SHIKI] The rest of the student
council always teases me,
but you're different,
Miss Tachibana.
Tease you?
[SHIKI] Yes, they always make
fun of me because I'm an angel.
Angel?
[SHIKI] Indeed. A poor
helpless fallen angel.
Unwanted by Heaven.
You and I aren't so different.
[RITSUKA]
I'm nothing like you.
[SHIKI] We both have a lot
of questions, though.
"Where should I go next?"
"What should I do now?
"Who am I really?"
[SHIKI]
Tell me about your maman.
I bet your mother was
a fan of flowers, too.
What?
She used them in
decorating, correct?
Well, yeah.
I knew it!
I might have figured out
where those vamps took her!
You think so?
[SHIKI]
Mm. I do. C'mon let's go.
[RITSUKA]
U-Uh...
Is something wrong?
What, you don't trust me?
[RITSUKA]
Mm...
I'm not like the rest
of the council.
They're all liars.
Or maybe... you prefer
them over poor little me?
Uh.
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka! Thanks for waiting!
Who's this?
Bring your friend,
the more the merrier!
Okay.
This way.
[AZUNA] Do you trust him?
He kinda creeps me out.
I know it's a risk,
but if he's right then
we can save my mom!
It's too weird. We should go.
[SHIKI]
You can leave alone.
[AZUNA]
Excuse me?
[SHIKI]
We don't really need you here.
No way, if she goes, I go.
[SHIKI]
Mm.
[PRIEST 4A] Perhaps you have
noticed the frequent activity
of the dark ones as of late.
[LINDO]
Yes sir, I've been hunting them.
[PRIEST 6A]
Lindo,
we have heard you recently
used a forbidden power.
[PRIEST 6B] Be careful,
do not succumb to darkness.
Thank you for your concern.
Moving on.
A year has passed since we first
knew the grimoire was close by.
Yet its exact location
continues to evade us.
The dark ones are growing
even more restless.
No doubt because
of the grimoire.
[LINDO grunts]
Remain vigilant and be sure to
report back with your findings.
Right.
[PRIEST 6A]
Blessings upon you, Brother.
[PRIEST 6B]
Stay safe.
I never knew that there was a
museum this close to our school.
I thought you said Ritsuka's
mom would be here.
Unless this is
some kind of set up.
Ritsuka, does this
art look familiar?
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
Yeah, who painted these?
[SHIKI]
You know I'm not really sure.
[RITSUKA]
Uh! Hey wait!
Shiki? Shiki!
[SHIKI] This place is especially
for you. It's a maze of sorts.
But also a museum
of your memories.
You'll find the answers here.
The answers?
[SHIKI]
Look at the painting.
What is this is...
There's no way.
[URIE]
Maria. That's the girl's mother?
[REM] Correct. We're tracking
her as we speak.
Yeah well, I'm getting
tired of waiting!
What's that, Mage? You
could help if you're bored.
[MAGE]
Heh!
[URIE] So? Where exactly
is the butterfly's mother?
We found her.
[UNDERLINGS groan]
[gasps] This room?
It's real. I'm at grandpa's.
Uh? Who's out there?
[RITSUKA] Is that mom?
No wait, it's Aunt Marta!
[gasps]
[MARIA]
Happy Birthday, Ritsuka!
[LINDO]
Blow out your candles!
[GRANDFATHER]
Make a wish!
[ALL laughing]
[RITSUKA]
Yay, I did it!
[VOICE 6A]
I can't believe this happened.
[VOICE 6B]
It's so sad.
[VOICE 6A] And Marta leaving
behind her only child.
[VOICE 6B]
Poor Lindo.
[RITSUKA]
They're talking about Lindo?
Mommy...
[LINDO]
Belial. Astaroth. Echidna.
[RITSUKA gasps]
[LINDO] Gusion. Eligos.
Belial. Pazuzu. If...
[GRANDFATHER]
Ifrit.
[LINDO]
Ifrit. Tannin.
Can this be...?
[GRANDFATHER]
Good job, Lindo.
Remember, never trust a devil.
No matter what, we must
keep the grimoire safe.
You have to protect
the Tachibana family.
[RITSUKA]
That's grandpa!
Or not.
Who are you?
[inaudible]
No way. Who is he?
What's going on? I'm scared!
[SHIKI] Maybe it was a memory
from a long time ago?
[gasps] Shiki!
[grunting]
[SHIKI]
Shh. Hush now.
What else did you see?
You should know,
wasn't it your idea?
[SHIKI] Maybe I did help a
little, but you had all the fun.
Guess what? You've seen all
that before in real life.
[RITSUKA gasping]
I should probably go. Sorry.
[SHIKI]
Aw, go where?
[RITSUKA]
Azuna and I are going home!
Is it really your home?
Are you sure about that?
What do you mean?
You poor little thing.
Vampires and devils are ruining
your life, aren't they?
Uh!
♪ ♪
[SHIKI]
♪ So helpless and pathetic ♪
♪ Like a rabbit controlled
by Providence ♪
♪ Those melancholic eyes
Reflect a life so pitiful ♪
♪ I can take you far away
from all of that ♪
♪ Keep you nice and safe ♪
♪ Go to sleep in my arms
And I will never let you go ♪
♪ Don't worry,
I won't do anything ♪
♪ Only want to sleep
nestled against you ♪
♪ It won't be pain
that you'll be feeling ♪
♪ While you close your eyes
And without making a sound ♪
♪ We'll mix and melt
together into one ♪
♪ For this is our lullaby
Holding tight, our lullaby ♪
♪ An ecstatic lullaby ♪
♪ Look at us so thrilled,
so joyful ♪
♪ Don't you see that I am you
And you are clearly me? ♪
♪ So it's natural that
we might feel a sting ♪
♪ What a lovely lullaby
Such a crazy lullaby ♪
♪ Eternal lullaby
It's time that we must go ♪
♪ Oh so pink and so
alluring is the fruit ♪
♪ That I gladly
drive my love into ♪
♪ It'll be over soon
With one blink ♪
♪ Of an eye ♪
[RITSUKA gasps]
No!
Want to play tag?
It's a fun game.
I promise to win, though.
And you get to be my prize.
What?
The fear on your face.
I simply adore it.
We'll be together always.
Don't try to leave.
Because if you do,
I'll kill you.
[SHIKI groans]
Don't touch her,
you filthy creep!
[SHIKI groans]
[exhales]
[AZUNA]
By the sacred Name,
those cloaked in the darkness
will obey my command!
Prostrate thyself before me.
You're hereby banished. Be gone!
[SHIKI panting]
Azuna.
[AZUNA]
We need to get out of here.
Uh!
[AZUNA]
Quickly, Ritsuka!
[AZUNA gasps]
Heh!
[RITSUKA gasps]
[SHIKI] Oops, guess you didn't
know that I'm sort of an angel.
Sorry Miss Exorcist--you'll
have to try again.
Miss Exorcist?
Now it makes sense.
My poor little darling.
Feeling alone?
Let's go. I'll explain later.
Hold on.
Was our friendship only
because of the grimoire?
Please, just tell me the truth!
To be honest it was, but now...
You're after
the grimoire, too?
Listen, Ritsuka!
We have to keep it out of the
hands of those who are evil.
It's like your brother said!
Lindo knew about you?
He knew you were an exorcist
this whole time?
I feel so stupid.
It's to save you!
Oh, you poor little thing.
[RITSUKA, AZUNA grunt]
[SHIKI]
Lying is a sin, y'know.
Looks like I'll
have to punish you!
[RITSUKA, AZUNA yelp]
[AZUNA]
Ritsuka!
So, which punishment
should it be?
By the sacred Name,
you will obey me!
[AZUNA gasping]
[AZUNA screams]
Oh, no!
[AZUNA whimpers]
[SHIKI]
Are you deaf?
I said that wouldn't work on me.
[AZUNA groaning]
No!
[SHIKI]
What should I do to you?
It would be a waste
not to savor your agony.
Stop.
[AZUNA groaning]
How about I peel
off your skin?
Yes, that'd be so much fun!
[AZUNA groaning]
[SHIKI] I wonder if you'll peel
as easily as an orange does.
Oh my.
I bet you'll be deliciously
grotesque.
[AZUNA yelps]
Scream for me, Miss Exorcist!
[RITSUKA]
That's enough!
I won't let you
keep hurting her!
Come on, she's just a filthy
liar. Why protect that?
[RITSUKA]
She's still my friend!
[SHIKI]
Friends don't lie.
Azuna may have lied,
but she did it in order to
protect me! It was necessary!
Ritsuka.
No more, okay?
I hate all this fighting.
I refuse to stand
around and watch.
Please just stop it!
Ritsuka...
That's so boring.
Total buzzkill.
Wait...
Well. See ya girls!
Hang on a second!
What about us finding my mother?
Were you even telling the truth?
Lies could be true.
The truth could be lies.
It's whatever you decide.
[gasps] Rem.
[RITSUKA]
Are you behind all this?
Did you make Shiki lie to me?
Stop!
[REM]
What for?
Why did you even bother to
help me in the first place?
[gasps]
I'm not a pawn in some game.
I'm a real person
with actual feelings.
I know we'll open
that door together.
The door leading to my
beloved Lord Maksis.
I refuse to fail him again.
He's my world.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Act 7: "Pas de Deux of
Fantasy and Innocence."