[LINDO] The grimoire
is extremely powerful.
Whoever possesses it
could potentially control
the entire world.
These creatures believe
that the Tachibana family
is the key to the
grimoire's whereabouts.
That's why they
targeted you and mom.
Take this. It's a ring
of the Sacred Lux.
As long as you wear it,
you'll be safe.
Wow, the Sacred Lux.
Listen, if you really
wanna go back to school,
I won't stop you.
However, starting tomorrow
I'll be going to school, too.
Huh?!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 5AA] You transferred
here from England?
That's so cool!
But you don't have an accent.
Do you only use it
when you're there?
[STUDENT 5BB] Aren't exchange
students the coolest?
Not really.
[AZUNA] Uh... Did you think
he'd be this popular?
Honestly, I didn't think
he'd seriously show up.
Ritsuka!
[STUDENT 5BB]
Wait, you know her?
[STUDENT 5B]
So who is she?
You gotta tell me.
Who's the hottie?
Your ring is so pretty.
Looks expensive.
Oh my gosh did he give it
to you? Is he your boyfriend?
Guys, cut it out!
Lindo is my brother!
[STUDENT 1C]
Oh. Well, is he single?
[TEACHER 5A] In March of
the late Eleventh Century,
the Byzantine Empire requested
assistance from Pope Urban II.
They needed his help to
recapture the Holy Land,
which was being occupied
by the Seljuk dynasty
after their conversion to...
[LINDO] As long as you
wear it, you'll be safe.
They know because
they're devils.
[TEACHER 5A] Now, the
proclamation made by th--
--[crash]
--[STUDENTS gasping, screaming]
What is the meaning of this?!
We are in the middle of class!
Mr. Nanashiro!
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
You're comin' with
me today, babe.
[RITSUKA]
Uh... Hey!
--[RITSUKA screams]
--[STUDENTS chattering]
What're you doing?
I mean it, put me down!
[AZUNA]
She said stop! Let her go!
[RITSUKA screams]
Ritsuka!
[MAGE grunts]
[RITSUKA grunts]
Chill out.
[RITSUKA]
I'm not going anywhere with you!
I mean it! Ahh!
Ritsuka!
What am I gonna do?
[TEACHER 5A]
The Pope's words proved powerful
and inspired the Crusades.
Which we know as the
most famous Holy War
to involve the Catholic Church.
[LINDO]
Ritsuka!
[STUDENTS chattering]
She's gone.
[gasps]
--[door creaks]
--[ROEN barking]
And here returns the exorcist
who believes he's a
knight in shining armor.
These awful pests
must be removed.
Oops!
I guess my hand slipped.
I got a call from
someone overseas
offering information
on the exorcist.
It could be rather useful;
don't you think?
[REM] He's relying on support
from the Exorcist Society.
But soon enough
they'll be too busy
to concern themselves with us.
Ohh.
Until then, you can keep
playing house with the girl.
Don't get distracted.
[REM] I'm just protecting
our investment, that's all.
I suppose someone has to.
And who better than
the Arlond Family heir.
The one who knows
failure isn't an option.
[REM grunts]
[REM]
Mage?
[RITSUKA whimpering]
Aw, what's the big deal,
Ritsuka?
You got a fear of heights?
I can understand that.
I mean, a human would
die if they fell.
[RITSUKA gasps]
[MAGE laughs] Wow, you gotta
learn to relax, sweetheart.
It would take a lot more
than that fall to kill a devil.
A devil?
[MAGE]
Yep. You heard me.
Lindo was right. They're real.
Now, if you don't want me
to devour your soul,
tell me where I can
find the grimoire.
I don't know. I swear I don't.
[MAGE] You got some balls, kid.
Guess you really want
to see what happens
when you defy a devil.
[RITSUKA screams]
[MAGE grunting]
[MAGE growls] I've about
had it with that exorcist.
He thinks he's so damn clever.
[RITSUKA]
Uh!
How 'bout it?
Let's officially make you mine.
[RITSUKA]
Huh?
Then you can stop
playing hard to get,
and tell me the truth
about the grimoire.
I promise I told you
the truth. I don't know.
And also, what do you
mean "make you mine?"
Don't be shy.
You know you're already starting
to fall in love with me.
Trust me,
It happens every time.
A soul can't help but fall hard
when they're around me.
[RITSUKA]
Uh.
Uh. What's that?
[MAGE] We don't get all day. Get
ready. Cause this is amazing.
[RITSUKA screams]
♪♪♪
[MAGE] ♪ Number one
I'm aimin' high and done ♪
♪ If you diss me, you die
You know that's loner style ♪
♪ Anyone that's
gonna try to front ♪
♪ I'm gonna bust them
in the face! ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[MAGE]
♪ Gonna be self-made ♪
♪ That's the plan
Gotta be a man ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[ALL]
♪ Hey, yo, bring it on! ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[MAGE]
♪ I got so much manliness ♪
♪ They all just wanna
be with this ♪
♪ All your dreams are VIP
When you're with me ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[MAGE]
♪ Watch your retinas, girl ♪
♪ My power burns so hot,
it's blinding ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[MAGE]
♪ Call me "Mage the Great!" ♪
[CHORUS]
♪ Vanquish! ♪
[MAGE] ♪ I'm gonna get
the grimoire and the girl ♪
♪ 'Cause that's the way I
play it Don't put up a fight ♪
♪ You know you're
going to be mine ♪
♪ Tell a lie For a devil like me
It's a piece of cake ♪
♪ Soldier time
Frontal attack, yeah ♪
♪ It's OK ♪
♪ Screw those guys
Rem, Urie, Shiki ♪
♪ They're all creeps ♪
♪ I'm gonna take you away
From all of this ♪
♪ A desire
Like a raging fire ♪
♪ That goes on and on forever ♪
♪ Gonna be reckless
Rebellious ♪
♪ Gonna break
their stupid rules ♪
♪ (Yeah, I'm 'a break 'em) ♪
♪ Wanna find the path
One that's going to last ♪
♪ Chasing down
the now that never ends ♪
♪ Fists up in the air
I'll go toe to toe ♪
♪ Ready to rumble
Come on let's go ♪
♪ Nobody is ever gonna
snuff me out ♪
♪ Got a drive that's
ignited me ♪
[MAGE] Disgusting! Human food
always tastes like crap!
Ahh. I'd kill for
a soul right now.
Why aren't you eating?
I've lost my appetite.
I won't act like everything's
okay after what you've done.
Fine, then, suit yourself.
I can see why Rem
can't handle you.
Uh?
[MAGE]
I never liked him anyway.
He's always so smug
and thinks he's so much
better than everyone else.
[RITSUKA] You're wrong.
He's not like that.
[MAGE chuckles]
That guy's got you wrapped
around his little finger.
Which, of course, is exactly
where he wants you.
Don't you see that he lied
so he could get what
he needed from you?
That doesn't make
sense. No way.
I like to be a little
more straightforward
and a lot less manipulative.
The truth is I don't really
need to lie to you,
because I'm so powerful.
So tell me. You in love yet?
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
[MAGE]
Let's face the facts.
Everyone falls for my
charms and good looks,
and they all wanna be with me.
Come on.
It's time to stop being afraid
and just embrace
what you're feeling.
How could I ever have feelings
for someone who kidnapped me?!
You've never even considered
what I might think.
What? Wait a second,
I haven't gone to this
much effort for anyone
and you're totally
not appreciating it.
[sniffs]
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
It is you.
You smell delicious.
Uh...
Mm! I have to go.
Go where?
[RITSUKA]
The bathroom!
[door slams]
What could she be
so upset about?
[RITSUKA exhales]
I've gotta get out
of here, now.
Just gotta find the police.
Then I can get back home.
[RITSUKA whimpers]
Why were you trying to
run away from me?
Well, I--
[MAFIOSO 5A speaking Chinese]
Uh!
What?
[speaking Chinese]
Look man, I'm just trying
to enjoy my dinner.
But, hey, if you wanna fight.
Let's do this.
[speaking Chinese]
[MAFIOSOS grunting]
[MAFIOSO 5A groans]
[MAFIOSOS speaking Chinese]
[MAFIOSO 5B screams]
[MAFIOSO 5A gasping]
Thanks to your dumb ass,
she's run away again.
And your soul won't be
as tasty as I was hoping,
but it's better than duck legs.
[MAFIOSO 5A groans]
[speaking Chinese]
Not as bad as I thought,
but I think you'll be better.
[RITSUKA panting]
[RITSUKA]
Someone, please! Help!
No!
[REM]
Calm down. It's just me.
[RITSUKA gasps]
You're here. How?
Ritsuka, I'll
always protect you.
They'll drop you off
at the airport
then my private plane
will to take you home.
It'll all be okay.
How'd you know where I was?
Be sure to contact your
brother as soon as you can.
I have a feeling that
he's very concerned.
[RITSUKA]
Okay. I will.
You're safe now. That's
what's most important.
What's the matter?
[RITSUKA] I'm safe now
and that's only important
because I'm the key to
the grimoire. Right?
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
I trusted you.
I thought you cared about me.
But now I know the truth.
You're a devil. And a liar.
[REM]
Yes, you're right.
I've been entrusted with a
task that I must complete.
In order to prove my
strength and keep my power,
someone must be the pawn.
And that's the part
you play in all this.
[gasping]
[RITSUKA]
Don't touch me!
[RITSUKA yelps]
Uh?
Hey, Rem.
What're you doing here?
It would appear I need to
remind you who is in charge.
Am I wrong?
The pawn belongs to me,
and I won't be giving her up.
Especially not to you.
[MAGE growls]
[REM]
Everything I've planned,
and everything that I've built
is now ruined because of you.
I have every right to destroy
you for your insubordination.
Oh give it up,
the girl's mine now.
Why don't you just
admit you lost
and go back to
your little games!
[REM grutns]
[RITSUKA gasping]
[RITSUKA]
Rem, plea--!
I will do whatever it
takes to get her back.
Ritsuka's mine.
[footsteps]
[MAGE]
Hm? What's up?
Finally decide to give up
on the screaming?
Well, this is depressing.
Better? I mean, this
is the kind of thing
you humans enjoy
looking at, right?
[RITSUKA grunts]
Ahh. I don't get it.
So Rem's a devil, big deal.
It's not worth
getting all upset about.
[RITSUKA]
No. It's not that at all.
Are you crying?
So sweet.
Uh...
[gasps]
Hey!
Look, you're not supposed
to put spells on me!
I don't like it. It's weird.
[RITSUKA screams]
[MAGE]
Ritsuka!
[splash]
Hey, I'm sorry.
[gasps]
Damn it. Moment's dead now.
[LINDO] Prostrate thyself before
me, o ye who lurk in darkness.
Though thou wouldst veil
thyself in the shadows.
[BOTH gasp]
Be driven out by my hand!
[RITSUKA]
Lindo, what are you doing here?
Foul devil, you better not
have laid a hand on her.
[LINDO] What have you done?
You vile demon.
Ha! Some exorcist you are.
Hate to break it to ya,
but you're a little late.
This one's all mine.
Man, let me tell ya,
you missed out.
What are you talking about?!
That's not true at all!
Now, let go of me!
[LINDO]
I will kill you.
Don't make the mistake of
thinking you can violate her...
...and walk away!
Lindo?
[LINDO growls]
Interesting. All right then.
[MAGE]
You don't fool me.
Your eyes just told me
everything I need to know.
Silence, devil!
[MAGE grunts]
[RITSUKA]
Please. Stop it!
[LINDO]
O ye who lurk in darkness,
obey my voice and pledge
that thou wouldst utter
before it only the truth...
Go ahead and say
whatever you want.
It's not gonna stand a chance
against the strength
of my power!
Pledge to me now!
[gasps]
Listen carefully, it doesn't
matter who you are,
I'll crush anyone
that gets in my way.
And I'll do it with the
strength of my bare hands.
Nothing personal,
but you don't have a shot.
I'll kill you. You must pay.
I'll kill you.
Lindo...
I'll protect her. Always.
Even if it costs me my life.
Stop it.
[MAGE]
Die!
[LINDO]
Be gone!
[RITSUKA]
No!
[BOTH gasp]
[RITSUKA grunts]
[RITSUKA gasping]
[LINDO]
Ritsuka!
I've got you.
I know. You saved me.
[MAGE] This party
turned out to be a bust.
See ya 'round, Ritsuka!
I'll give you some time to see
what your heart really wants.
Then, you'll be
begging to be mine.
[sighs]
Thank goodness. Are you okay?
I'm fine. It was nothing.
What's wrong?
[LINDO] Forgive me.
I let my anger take over.
[RITSUKA]
It's okay, really.
You always come
to my rescue, Lindo.
Thank you.
[MAGE sighs] I'm sick of all
these posers getting in my way.
[sniffing]
Wow, that scent of hers
just soaked right in.
It tasted so sweet.
[SHIKI laughs]
Uh?
Oh! What the hell, Shiki?
Don't sneak up on me!
[SHIKI chuckles]
Mage. You're blushing.
Is it a good look
for you? I think not.
Uh! I am not blushing!
You are so dead!
Maybe one day you'll
follow through
on these empty threats, but
alas, today's not that day.
Anyway, I have something coming
that will send shivers
up your spine.
[SHIKI] I only hope you
find your way to me quickly.
Then I can lock
you away forever.
[SHIKI] The fear on your face.
I simply adore it.
We'll be together always.
Don't try to leave.
Because if you do,
I'll kill you.
Act 6: "Farandole of
Reminiscence and Labyrinths."