[REM'S FATHER]
My son.
[REM]
I'm here.
[REM'S FATHER] Why have you
not come to me sooner?
Please forgive me, Father.
[REM'S FATHER]
Answer my question.
It's complex.
[REM'S FATHER]
Is the human world preferable
over your devil's pride?
No, the thought is laughable.
[REM'S FATHER] Do not lie to me,
or you shall pay with your life.
I'm not, I would never dream
of betraying you, Father!
I swear it!
[REM'S FATHER]
Silence!
[REM'S FATHER] Actions speak
louder than words, boy.
I do not care for
empty promises.
What I want is the
forbidden grimoire!
[REM grunts]
[REM'S FATHER]
Find a way to make it yours,
or else you will not be around
to carry on the Arlond name!
Well that sounds fun.
This is one of those times
I'm thankful not to
be the Arlond heir.
Yeah, tell me about it.
His old man is known for having
a pretty short temper.
It's not as if being shamed once
in a while is going to kill Rem.
Unless it does, in which case
I can practically imagine
how much pain he must be in
at this very moment. Ahh!
[MAGE] Nobody asked
for an angel's opinion!
Ouchie!
Whatever, you're both enjoying
this as much as I am!
Perhaps we are.
You're the only one
making it creepy, though.
[SHIKI]
Ouchie!
Oh please, you like it.
You're such a crybaby.
[SHIKI]
Leave me alone!
You guys always pick on me,
but you're the ones undermining
Rem at every turn!
Speaking of, why are we
wasting a golden opportunity
when Rem's busy
with the old man?
Don't be silly Mage.
That's my butterfly.
Yeah, in your dreams!
I'm gonna get the girl
and the grimoire.
It'll be such a breeze.
[BOTH]
Mm?
[URIE]
Shiki!
[MAGE] Dammit, how the hell did
that worm get the jump on us?
[RITSUKA] Let's see, two cans
of spray paint, check!
Anything else?
[RITSUKA]
Yeah, duct tape.
Looks like it's over there.
Hold up missy,
there's no way I'm letting you
wander off by yourself.
Chill out! It's five feet away.
[AZUNA]
I will not chill out!
Listen, those devils could
pop up anywhere, anytime.
They're worse than cockroaches.
[sighs] You're like a girly
version of Lindo.
[AZUNA]
Not one boy in our class
has helped with the
school culture festival.
I swear. I mean, how in
the heck are the two of us
even supposed to get all these
decorations and stuff
back to school?
I think this store
might offer deliveries.
It's worth asking.
Good idea. Okay.
I'll go check out and schedule
the delivery for us.
Stay where I can see you.
At all times. Got it?
Yes, ma'am.
[ROEN panting]
Huh? Hey, wait a second.
Isn't that Rem's dog?
What's he doing in this store?
Uh, uh!
[RITSUKA] Azuna, I'm gonna
step outside real quick.
I promise to come right back!
Now I've gotcha!
Yep! Just as I suspected,
you do belong to Rem!
But why were you in the store?
We don't want you
to get lost do we?
[barks]
[RITSUKA laughs]
Aw, silly puppy!
Your widdle paws are so cute!
Okay, time to go back.
[RITSUKA laughs]
Hey, that tickles!
[RITSUKA]
Uh?!
What's going on?
Why, it's a pleasure to see
you again, Miss Tachibana.
Well, as a human.
We met once.
I am Roen, remember?
[RITSUKA screams]
[phone rings]
[RITSUKA gasps]
If you could please ignore
your phone for a minute,
I have some info on the
grimoire. I really want to help.
[RITSUKA] Uh? The grimoire.
Are you a devil?
I am Cerberus.
I'm more of a dog
than say a devil.
Hell's watchdog, to be precise.
My master is Maksis.
I am his most faithful servant
and right hand man.
If it's clarity you're
seeking, then follow me.
The choice is up to you,
Miss Tachibana.
I'll respect your decision no
matter what path you choose.
[RITSUKA]
Azuna? It's me.
I have a quick errand
I need to run.
Don't worry. I'll go
straight home afterwards.
Lying to your friend?
My goodness, you're
such a naughty girl.
[groans]
You again?
[SHIKI]
Shh.
[AZUNA]
Uh?
Shiki! Where the hell does
a stupid angel like you
get off trying to leave
us behind like that?
You got some kinda death wish?
[SHIKI, AZUNA gasp]
[crash]
It seems you're desperate
for the tender caress
of my thorny whip.
[SHIKI laughs]
No, I'll take a raincheck
because what I was
actually trying to do
was help you guys out!
This girl is her best friend!
She'll tell us where
we can find Ritsuka.
Oh, yeah?
Excellent.
For sure.
[REM]
Uh?
[RITSUKA]
Hey, um. I wanted to ask...
...what exactly is
the forbidden grimoire?
I know that it's
a book of magic,
but I don't know how
it's supposed to work.
Is it full of magic
spells or something?
[ROEN]
Magic spells, how cute!
[RITSUKA]
Don't tease me.
We shouldn't linger. Follow me.
[RITSUKA]
No. I'm not budging.
I want to know right now.
Either you tell me about
the grimoire, or I'm leaving!
Well, who knew?
You have a backbone.
You've got courage
Miss Tachibana,
just like your father.
[RITSUKA]
Huh?
My lord Maksis finds
his power failing.
But perhaps you know it as the
war between vampires and devils.
Am I correct?
How it relates is the forbidden
grimoire is essential
in order to restore
this weakened power.
So wait, does the
book have a spell?
What I mean is does it tell you
how to revive the devils?
Not quite. Here's the truth:
The grimoire is the great power.
And whoever holds that
power within their grasp
will have the ability to
conquer the entire world.
[RITSUKA groans]
[ROEN]
Ah, what an enticing smell.
Hold on. What smell?
Uh?
[ROEN] It's enough to make
anyone lose control.
Hey, where'd you go?
Ah yes. This aroma is
impossible to resist.
[RITSUKA yelps]
Stop it!
[ROEN gasps]
[RITSUKA gasps]
You stay back!
[ROEN] Your eyes burn
with such a fiery resolve!
But I think it's your
charm that's alluring.
Perhaps that's what makes
the scent of the grimoire
so attractive.
Ritsuka Tachibana.
The extraordinary
power of the grimoire
slumbers deep inside your body.
My girl, you are the
forbidden gimoire.
That scent is the
irrefutable proof.
What?
[ROEN]
Basically, whoever has you
will be able open
the gates to Gehenna,
or as you humans
like to call it, Hell.
By doing that they will
master this world.
[RITSUKA whimpers]
Want to know something?
I can remove the grimoire,
and all its boundless power,
from inside of you.
Then I will take that power and
deliver it to my beloved master,
my Lord Maksis.
The vicious war between
the devils and vampires
will finally be over.
Your sweet mother will
return home safely to you.
Your family will
be free at last,
and no one will ever
bother you again.
Really? Is that true?
♪♪♪
[ROEN] ♪ The forbidden grimoire
It's the one and only truth ♪
[ROEN]
♪ Humble servant, ♪
♪ giving all I can In His Name,
I give everything I am ♪
♪ I long to obey
my master's will ♪
♪ All of his desires
I swear to fulfill ♪
♪ If my canine body should,
set aflame ♪
♪ And burn to ashes of black ♪
♪ A privilege, it would be
Reveling in my destruction ♪
♪ Filling me with ecstasy ♪
[howls]
[ROEN]
♪ Come now, ♪
♪ Let's open up the door
Let's do it together ♪
♪ The door that leads
us to Lord Maksis ♪
♪ On the other side is a world
Just waiting for you ♪
♪ In your hand,
you hold the key ♪
♪ Do you miss those days,
of innocence? ♪
♪ Are you longing to return? ♪
♪ Then put all your trust
In Cerberus ♪
♪ And devote yourself to me ♪
[ROEN] Lord Maksis means
absolutely everything to me.
He just needs the power
of the grimoire.
After that the devils
won't need you.
Then the Tachibanas
will be free.
[MAGE groans]
[URIE, SHIKI groan]
You're really startin'
to tick me off.
[AZUNA]
I said be gone!
[URIE] What a pity, you seem
to be short on holy water.
Where'd Ritsuka go? Better talk,
or we'll all get mad.
And you're not gonna like the
three of us when we're angry.
[LINDO]
Azuna!
[AZUNA]
Uh?
[LINDO panting]
[MAGE]
Man, here comes the killjoy.
If we cause trouble
outside the school
then it's bound to reflect
poorly upon the student council.
I wouldn't worry.
We can always blame you.
How typical.
[sighs] That was close.
[LINDO]
Azuna! Are you okay?
You were late coming back to
school so I started to worry.
Where's Ritsuka? Tell me.
What?! But she should have
been back home by now!
[gasps]
[RITSUKA]
I just don't believe it!
[ROEN] That's your decision,
but the time is almost upon us.
What do you mean?
The forbidden grimoire and
all of its incredible power
will be unleashed on
your 17th birthday.
The effects will then last until
the night of the next full moon.
Uh.
We were planning
to tell you soon.
Mom and I were going to tell you
everything before your birthday.
That's what Lindo meant.
Interesting, so your
family knew everything.
There's a lot of secrets.
It's like everyone knew about
the grimoire except for you.
Wow, your brother hasn't been
honest at all, has he?
Shut up!
My brother would never
lie to me like that!
[ROEN]
I suppose there is a difference
between lying and omitting.
He simply failed to
mention the grimoire
was hidden deep inside
you all this time.
So I guess that's not
technically a lie.
[RITSUKA]
Uh...
There's no need to be afraid.
I only want the power
you're harboring.
[ROEN]
If you were to go to sleep here
in this room until
your 17th birthday.
Then, when the grimoire
within you begins to stir,
we merely gift that power
to my beloved Lord Maksis.
Follow these simple instructions
and the people you hold dear
will no longer be in any danger.
So, take off the ring,
and we can start.
[gasps]
No, you can't go.
[RITSUKA]
Huh?
Don't do it.
Why Rem?
Why would you stop me?
You're hurt! Who did that?
[REM grunts]
Oh my, what would
dear old dad say?
Those scratches are nothing
compared to what he'll do next.
Why Roen?
I never thought
you'd start working
for that fiend Maksis again.
You owe the Arlond family
after we took you in!
Do I? Ha, ha, ha.
Those are pretty words
coming out of the mouth
of the Arlond heir.
Tell me more about
my obligation
and how I should be grateful
to be your loyal dog.
[REM] Loyal is the
last word I would use
to describe a rat like you!
[RITSUKA screams]
Get your hands off of her!
[ROEN]
And if I don't?
How tough do you think it
would be to dig out her heart?
[ROEN laughs]
[RITSUKA gasps]
[REM growls]
[ROEN] You are the forbidden
grimoire's precious vessel.
I wouldn't dare give such a
treasure away to just anyone.
Please, stop.
[screams]
[ROEN groans]
[REM grunting]
[RITSUKA sighs]
[RITSUKA]
Lindo!
Ritsuka! Are you okay? Tell me!
Uh? Blood...
[growls]
[gasps]
How dare you?
No, wait!
Stop, Lindo! Rem didn't do this!
[LINDO] I'll make you pay.
You'll wish for death!
[REM, RITSUKA gasp]
[LINDO growls]
Lindo? It's okay.
[gasps]
[LINDO yells]
[RITSUKA gasps, groans]
Ritsuka!
[LINDO growls]
[LINDO yells]
[REM grunts]
Leave him alone!
[LINDO growls]
You cut me?
[LINDO yells]
[REM, LINDO grunting]
[yells]
Would you destroy Ritsuka, too?
[LINDO]
Huh?
[LINDO exhales]
Oh, Lindo!
I hurt her. I hurt her.
Thank God! It's all okay now!
Everything will be fine!
Where did he go?
[ROEN] Well, I suppose
there's always next time.
I know we'll open
that door together.
The door leading to my
beloved Lord Maksis.
I refuse to fail him
again. He's my world.
He's my world.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Uh? It smells great.
Ritsuka. I hurt you. I'm sorry.
[RITSUKA] Did you know the truth
this whole time? That it was me?
Tell me the truth.
I deserve answers.
I knew. Grandpa told
me a while back.
I figured. And, mom knew too?
Remember how she'd always
want you to wear your pendant?
And she'd put vervain in it?
[RITSUKA]
Mm-hm.
It was special.
Home grown by mom.
It was magical and holy.
The grimoire's scent was
hidden by the potpourri.
That's why she insisted upon it.
Something must have
changed, then.
Grandpa died.
It was only natural for you
to become devastated.
But that's when the scent
started to be noticeable.
Because the pendant failed.
Though brief, it was long enough
for them to smell the grimoire.
Within the year they
would make their move
and come looking for our family.
That should bring you up to date
about everything
that's happened.
So, then... I'm the
reason mom's missing.
It's my fault.
That isn't true!
But it is!
Ritsuka! Please, listen to me.
All of us just wanted
to keep you safe!
Stop protecting me!
Let it be over. Save yourselves.
[gasps]
If handing over this power
will be the end of all this...
Fine with me!
No, you can't!
And why not?
Because, you...
Because doing that
would be the end of you.
[gasps]
That's it. I can't say more,
but you should know this.
I'll save you.
Even if it costs me my life,
I will protect you, Ritsuka!
Is everyone hiding something?
Lindo was like an entirely
different person.
I don't know who I should trust.
With all these lies,
which one is true?
What do I do? I just
feel so lost.
This time. Checkmate.
No, you can't go.
[REM]
What's wrong with me?
[RITSUKA]
"Waltz of Transience."