Vampires will never beat Devils.
[VAMPIRES yelp]
[VAMPIRE 12C groaning]
How pathetic.
They must really believe
they can take over the world.
[VAMPIRES groan]
[VAMPIRE 12E screams]
All right, that's enough
screwin' around!
[SHIKI laughs] I think it's
time for a little punishment!
[VAMPIRES screaming]
[ROEN laughs, whistles]
[VAMPIRE 12I gasps]
[VAMPIRES scream]
Get out of my way!
[VAMPIRE 12L groans]
[LINDO]
Ritsuka!
Stop! Let go of me!
[NESTA groans]
[JEK]
Lord Nesta!
You'll pay for that!
[RITSUKA screams]
I've had enough of you
and your games.
No!
[JEK]
Lord Nesta.
The moon is high. It's time
to prepare for the rite.
[gasping] Stop!
Get away from me!
[NESTA chuckles]
Now relax and give in
to the sweet ecstasy.
[RITSUKA screams]
[whistles]
[groans]
[ROEN]
I will do what I must
to make the will of
my master a reality.
Damn you, you filthy mongrel!
[RITSUKA gasping]
[JEK]
Get back here!
It's okay. We're going
to keep you safe.
But how?
[JEK]
This isn't any of your business.
She belongs to Lord Nesta now.
[LINDO]
Over my dead body she does.
Oh, is that a threat?
Or are you volunteering,
you pathetic dhampir?
Take her.
Yeah.
Rem. I'm really scared.
[REM] It's okay.
You're out of danger now.
Thank goodness.
Wait, what?
When all this is over, there's
something I need to tell you.
You'll be safe with me.
By the sacred name,
you will obey me.
Oh ye who lurk in darkness,
begone from here--
[JEK grunts]
Keep your filthy
hands off of me!
[LINDO grunts]
You disgust me!
How could you betray the man
whose blood runs
through your veins?
You turned on your own father!
I have no father.
[JEK]
You fool.
It won't be long until
you're on your knees
begging for the mercy
of Lord Nesta.
No one can defy his
overwhelming power.
So just give up.
Stop this ridiculous fight.
Looks like you're
the fool now.
After what you did to Ritsuka,
I will make you all pay.
Ha! Just how stupid
can you be?
A dhampir is no match
for a vampire.
I could destroy you in a second.
[LINDO groans]
[JEK grunts]
[LINDO screams]
[JEK]
Die!
Damn. What've you done?
[LINDO]
Begone from here, forevermore!
[JEK groans]
Lord Nesta...
[JEK]
My everything...
Such a disappointment.
Eat some of this!
[VAMPIRE 12N screams]
[laughs] How about some more?
[VAMPIRES screaming]
[VAMPIRES scream]
[yells]
[gasps]
[NESTA]
My son. My one and only son.
Shut up! You think I care?
[gasps]
[NESTA] Do you have any
idea how long I've waited
to see you here? Don't you know
how important you are to me?
No. I guess you wouldn't.
[NESTA]
The only love I have ever known.
The true love of my life
was your mother, Marta.
[NESTA] My poor, sweet Marta.
So kind and gentle.
But in the end,
it was her kindness
that destroyed her and
broke her son's heart.
I hoped one day we
could be a family.
Just the three of us,
together forever.
[LINDO] The three of us.
Together forever?
Yes.
But I need the grimoire to
make that dream come true.
We will never be free so long
as they are still around.
That's why I need
your help, son.
I need you to get
me the grimoire,
so that I can destroy the
devils once and for all.
[LINDO exhales]
At last, you and I will
control the dark realm.
And we can do as we please.
We could even bring
your mother back.
Come. Take your place
beside me, my son.
Father...
[gasps]
Lindo!
[NESTA]
The day I've waited for is here.
My one and only son has
finally come home to me.
He's lying to you!
Please, stop!
You cannot trust him!
[NESTA] I always knew you
would fight alongside me.
Because you hate the
devils too, don't you?
Now, we can't be stopped.
[NESTA laughs]
[LINDO grunts]
[NESTA groaning]
I'd rather die than fight
alongside you. Dad!
[screams]
[NESTA groaning]
It's done.
[VAMPIRES whimper]
[MAGE, SHIKI, URIE, ROEN gasp]
[RITSUKA]
You're okay!
Ritsuka!
Well, it looks like the exorcist
stole our thunder after all.
I'll allow it this once.
That standoff sent
chills down my spine.
Hey Rem. What's up?
[NESTA chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[NESTA] You couldn't honestly
believe that a dhampir
could kill me. Come, now.
I'm a king, after all.
[NESTA laughs]
No way!
[SHIKI] But the legend
said, if you pierce
the Vampire King's heart
he'll die writhing in agony.
He's hidden it.
[URIE]
His heart?
[ROEN]
If they were that easy to kill
someone would've already
done it by now.
I've heard their ancestors
possessed some sort
of special ability. That must be
the secret of their longevity.
Tell us where it is!
Even if I did,
you devils aren't smart enough
to find a way to stop me.
[REM grunts]
[yells]
[ALL groaning]
[RITSUKA yelps]
[screams]
Ritsuka!
[REM groans]
[LINDO groans]
[REM groaning]
No! You're hurt!
[chuckles] Just give up.
The grimoire is mine.
And with its power,
I will control the world.
Isn't it a pity that you'll
never experience it
because you'll be dead! [laughs]
It's no use. Why are you making
it harder on yourselves?
There is nothing you
can do to stop me.
[RITSUKA] All this pain...
All this fighting...
All because of the grimoire!
[RITSUKA]
My whole life changed.
So many people died.
And for what?
Because of some horrible
power that lies within me?
[RITSUKA]
No. That's not fair.
I won't let this control me.
I'm sick of people I care
about paying the price.
If this is my destiny,
then this is my fight.
And I'm not running
away anymore.
So if the grimoire
lies within me,
then I get to choose
what happens to it.
It's my choice.
[clock chimes]
[REM gasps]
[BOTH gasping]
Ritsuka?
[RITSUKA] And I choose
to use its power myself.
I am going to protect them all!
[NESTA gasping]
[RITSUKA gasps]
[RITSUKA]
Uh?
Azuna...
[gasping]
[NESTA groans]
[NESTA grunts]
[heartbeats]
[RITSUKA]
Even the most feared vampire
who thrives in darkness is
terrified to face his own death.
That's enough.
His reign ends now.
It's time you find
your humanity,
and leave this world behind.
Rest in peace.
[NESTA screams]
[NESTA groaning]
[RITSUKA gasps]
[screams]
Uh! No!
Ritsuka. Come on.
Please, wake up!
Thank you.
I'm here for you.
I won't let go.
I have to be honest. I've
never seen Rem like this.
Yeah.
Aw, man.
I'm quite depressed now
that the grimoire's gone.
[sniffs] Not to mention
the scent's almost gone too.
Patience gentlemen,
we've got time.
Let's see. Only a 615 year wait.
[ROEN]
How unfortunate.
Lord Maksis will be
rather disappointed.
I suppose I'll just have to
search for something else.
[REM]
When we first met,
I didn't know it, but our fate
had already been sealed.
I felt something that I didn't
really know how to explain.
And, I was afraid you
wouldn't feel the same way.
But...
[gasps]
I can't keep it to
myself anymore.
I love you, Ritsuka.
I'm glad.
I love you.
[RITSUKA cries]
[REM]
Now that the grimoire is gone,
there's no reason for me to
continue living in this world.
Come back with me.
[gasps]
We can be together.
We could have a life we've
only dreamed about.
In the demon world.
♪♪♪
[RITSUKA, LINDO, REM]
♪ Dance with destinies ♪
♪ High up in the sky
Enclosed by millions of stars ♪
♪ How our paths ever crossed
Miraculous we're all here ♪
♪ Now I need to tell the truth
What I feel inside my heart ♪
♪ I love you forever and ever ♪
[LINDO] ♪ I can see she's
found her wings ♪
♪ And it's time for her fly ♪
♪ I'll always be there
to protect her ♪
♪ Now I know
I can do so from afar ♪
I'll keep her safe. I swear.
That's how I'll show my love.
[RITSUKA, REM]
♪ Dance in a sweet dream ♪
♪ You and I together
We'll go hand in hand ♪
♪ To the place that we've seen
Only in our wildest dreams ♪
♪ Listening only to the sound
Of our own eternal vows ♪
♪ I love you forever and ever ♪
I promise you.
I will make you happy.
[REM] ♪ You must make a choice
How your life will now unfold ♪
♪ Two dissimilar worlds
Two dissimilar paths ♪
♪ Devil world or human world ♪
♪ Two dissimilar worlds
Two dissimilar paths ♪
♪ Dance with destinies ♪
♪ I don't want to part part from
him The one I truly love ♪
♪ Here where we move as one
Together in his world ♪
♪ Then there are
those so dear to me ♪
♪ I can't stand
to lose them all ♪
♪ It is there we live
Together in my world ♪
My world? His world?
♪ This is my choice
I must decide ♪
♪ For this is my destiny ♪
♪ I will choose
that path that will lead ♪
♪ To a treasure immeasurable ♪
♪ My true self ♪
I've made my choice.
I decide to stay human.
So long, my beautiful butterfly.
Next time we meet, you know
you're gonna be mine.
One day, Ritsuka, we will fall
in love with each other.
I hope we meet again,
if fate would be so kind.
[RITSUKA]
♪ Dance with my devil ♪
♪ You're my only true love ♪
♪ my dear, dear, dear devil ♪
♪ You and I now must part ♪
♪ For now we'll walk
Our own paths ♪
♪ We will surely meet again
In a future far away ♪
♪ I'll love you
forever and ever ♪
[RITSUKA]
Goodbye, my dearest devil.
[inaudible]
[ROEN]
Welcome back, Lord Maksis.