[LOKI laughs]
[LOKI] It seems your
friends are trying to mount
some sort of rescue!
Don't underestimate them.
You have the upper hand now,
but that can change
in an instant.
I'm not worried.
Soon, I'll be showing you
the greatest tragedy
this world has ever seen.
I hope you're looking
forward to it.
Santa's not the kind of person
who backs down from a challenge.
[LOKI]
Maybe not...
But what hope
does one person have
fighting against
a bunch of gods?
What gods?
Don't tell me you forgot.
The gods Oz summoned
are still patrolling the paths
leading to the Divine Gate.
The Scandinavians.
That's right.
The same ones who
completely slaughtered
your beloved Knights of Round.
I hope our friend Santa Clause
had a good Christmas last year,
because he won't even be
able to recognize this world
when my plan is finished.
[AOTO]
What happened?
It's you.
[K giggles]
[K]
You're finally awake, Aoto.
Do you have any idea
where we are?
[AOTO] Some place that's
close to the Divine Gate?
[K]
Yes.
This may look like a tower,
but it's really a path.
So... Let's go!
Those powerful gods will find
us if we keep standing here.
Where are the others?
[AKANE] Man, just when I thought
things couldn't get any weirder.
What is this place?
And what am I supposed
to do now, huh?
Hey, Midori! Or Aoto!
Where the hell is everybody?
Can anyone hear me?
[buzzing noise]
[AKANE]
Holy crap!
You can't be
serious with this!
I hope everyone
else is doing okay.
An explosion?
Is someone fighting back there?
Midori...
Dammit.
[PAVLOV] I'm disappointed
you didn't take 'em out, Akane.
[PAVLOV] Haven't you inherited
your dad's firepower?
[AKANE] I'm not gonna fall for
this again, you fake bastard!
[PAVLOV] Huh?
What are you talking about?
I know I've been
away for a while, kid,
but I assure you that
I'm the real deal...
Here, I'll show you.
One... Two...
Whaddaya say, kid?
They're inside.
[UNDINE]
Yeah. I can sense them, too.
[SYLPH] Guess we know
what to do, huh?
[crashing noise]
What was that?
Bad news, whatever it was.
We gotta find them!
Thank goodness.
You're really okay!
No, you stay back.
You're another imposter,
just like before.
You're not gonna trick me again!
Wait, what are
you talking about?
You better stop before
you make me really angry.
Midori...
I get it.
If fighting with you is the only
way to prove it's really me,
then so be it.
Let's see what you've learned.
If this is some kinda trick,
then I'm gonna destroy you!
You can come at me with
all you've got, Akane...
But I'm not fighting my own son.
If you're really my father,
give me some proof.
All right, kid,
how about the fact that
you were born ass first,
and blue because
you weren't breathing.
It was your mom who
insisted on a natural birth,
even with all the scientific
shortcuts available to her.
It all worked out, though.
You started crying as
soon as I smacked your butt.
That's impossible...
Mom said she never told anyone.
I've put you and your mother
through some really hard times.
Yeah, you have.
Listen to me.
You have to give up on this.
It's not too late.
I'll talk to the Council.
See if I can get
them to pardon you.
Wait. Hold on for
just a damn minute.
You have no idea what
the Council is capable of.
They made the Knights
of Round disappear.
Permanently.
I'm well aware.
Your dear ol' dad played a part
in that massacre as well.
It couldn't be helped.
Blame the Divine Gate for
causing this chaotic world,
leaving us with no options.
A fair many lives have been
lost thanks to the Gate,
because of all the
disasters it caused.
And yet, we still need it there
to maintain the fragile balance
between worlds, or else even
more chaos would rain down.
That's why I've devoted my
life to researching the Gate,
so we can truly understand it.
The Driver you use,
the subspace we call "zones,"
those autonomous machines...
They're all byproducts
of the research we've done
on the Divine Gate.
A silver lining
to all this, I guess.
I don't believe that
there was no other way...
How can you be so calm
about all those deaths?
'Cause it was for
the greater good;
we couldn't allow Arthur
to destroy the Gate.
There were casualties,
yes, but in the end
we saved countless lives.
I don't want you to
become a casualty, too.
Just shut up.
No more excuses.
Our family was already a
casualty of this stupid fight.
[AKANE]
All those lies...
And yet Mom always said
you were a great man.
[AKANE]
Mom, why did Dad leave?
And why isn't he coming back?
Is it because
he doesn't love us?
Akane, you may be too young
to understand this, but...
Your father can't come back
because he's out there
fighting for us.
Yes. It must all be for us.
[crying softly]
You destroyed us!
Screw the greater good if
it means sacrificing the lives
of everyone around you!
I'm not going back!
I'm gonna go find
the Gate again
and fix this!
If this is who you are,
I wish you'd've stayed dead!
[AKANE yelling]
Oh, is that so?
Then show me the
fire in your heart.
Let's see how strong
my selfish kid is.
[LOKI] Conflict is the heart
of every good story.
The closer our main
players get to the Gate,
the more their dreams begin
to fall apart in front of them.
[ARTHUR] And none of them
have even had to face
the Scandinavian gods yet.
[LOKI chuckles]
I know, isn't it wonderful?
Yes, it is.
This is where your arrogance
might begin to cause problems.
[LOKI]
Oh?
[ARTHUR] You plan to have these
kids open the Divine Gate
so you can remake the world from
scratch however you see fit.
You're oversimplifying it.
Though, yes,
that is the endgame.
But none of them will
be able to reach the Gate
without a key,
even if they are Adapters.
Right now only one of them
has the ability to open it.
The other two need
to experience something
in order to obtain
their Gate keys--
True despair.
That's the key?
[laughing]
Oh, and there is another
thing you forgot about, Arthur.
You left yourself
out of my plan.
I'm still going
to make you a king.
One who controls
this whole world.
[ARTHUR]
You're insane.
[LOKI laughing]
[SAINT A (DANTE)]
Ginji...
You knew that Akane,
Aoto, and Midori
were alive this
whole time, didn't you?
Tell the truth.
[SAINT B (AEGIS)] There's
no need to be defensive.
We're not blaming you
for any of this.
Loki was manipulating
everyone, wasn't he?
[SAINT C (JOHANN)] We realize
now that we should never
have trusted Loki.
His scheming has
even destroyed Oz.
So.
What do you want me
to do about it?
[SAINT A (DANTE)] I'll be
completely up front with you.
Powerful agents of Celestia and
Hellistia are now on the move
due to Arthur's selfish actions.
Like it or not, the
Council needs your help.
You still have an important role
to play in all of this madness.
Hang on, what
are you talking about?
I'm just a student.
[SAINT C (JOHANN)]
No, you're more than that.
This may come as
a surprise to you,
but you're the only one
here who can reach the Gate.
So we need your help.
[GINJI]
I'm the only one?
[SAINT A (DANTE)] It seems your
friends were important figures
in Celestia and Hellistia,
and those worlds are
looking to reclaim them.
You don't mean
Hikari and Yukari?
Um... Who's there?
[SERVANT 10A] We've come
to bring you home, Princess.
Princess? What do you mean?
Oh, hello.
Are you from Hellistia?
You don't seem surprised
to see us standing here.
Do you understand that
we've been looking for you?
Yes.
Suddenly everything's
starting to come into focus.
[ARTHUR] You couldn't have
planned a more roundabout way
of doing this.
[LOKI] I'm well aware; this
scheme has too many variables
for my taste, but I'm afraid
your little trick is to blame,
my friend.
Ah. So you know
about that, eh?
I cursed you to ensure
you were mine to control,
body and soul, Arthur.
And yet you put up resistance,
almost as if you
planned for this.
You may think humans
are weak subjects,
but we won't let you destroy
our world without a fight.
Why yes, I see that now...
And I know the reason
you can resist me
is because I only have a
part of you locked up here.
Tell me, my defiant king...
Where have you hidden the
rest of your fractured heart?
So there's still
some hope left.
[HOGNE]
I finally found you.
Come on.
I wanna see how much fun
you are before you die.
Sorry, but I don't
have time to play!
You're gonna have
to do better than that!
[HOGNE]
Where'd he go?
[OZ] That's it. I can't
take it anymore, Dorothy.
We're going to search for
the kids from the Academy
and keep them from
doing anything stupid.
Dorothy?
[MIDORI yells]
I'm not gonna let you tarnish
my memories of Elena anymore!
What are you saying?
[MIDORI]
She's my number one best friend!
I've been looking for her
ever since she disappeared.
Were you really thinking
of me all this time, Midori?
Wow, that means so much to me.
[MIDORI]
No way...
You're really Elena?
Well, yeah.
I've been trying to tell you
that from the beginning.
[MIDORI]
But how?
I've been wanting
to apologize to you.
Can you ever forgive me?
Stop right there.
Everything is fine.
It's been a long time
since the day I left.
Neither of us are the same
person we were back then.
I have comrades, and a place
where I feel like I belong now.
Comrades?
[ELENA]
Yeah...
So don't worry about it.
[MIDORI]
It's just that...
I've been... trying to...
You're the one who said our
friendship was "a little much."
Remember that?
[ELENA] I even go by a
new name these days.
Everyone calls me Dorothy.
But you can still call me Elena.
So much has changed.
Elena... This is crazy!
That's just life.
We grow and we move on.
[chuckles]
Anyway...
The reason I'm here
is to tell you to quit.
Stop risking your life.
Oh! Sorry...
I know I shouldn't
tell you what to do,
but I just want you to be safe!
Elena...
I found you.
[ELENA]
A Scandinavian god!
[K] Looks like we might get
there without being spotted.
[AOTO]
Where are my friends?
Don't worry.
Once they know despair too,
they'll join you at the Gate.
What does that mean?
[UNDINE]
Hey, Aoto!
[AOTO]
Undine!
Oh, good, you're okay!
Just as I suspected.
You're able to see me, too.
Yeah.
I've always been
able to see you.
[DOROTHY yells]
Pathetic humans...
You're so fragile.
[MIDORI]
This isn't your fight, Elena.
Get out of here
before you get hurt.
I'm the one she's after.
Don't worry.
We'll have time
to catch up later!
But... Wait! Midori!
Bet you can't keep up with me.
When it comes to running, I'm
better than anyone, even a god.
Ha! So you wanna have a contest?
Okay. I'll show you who's best.
Don't tell me that weak
punch is all you got.
Oh, I'll show you!
Akane, freeze. Don't move!
[AKANE]
Huh?
Oh, this is bad!
A god from an
outlying region...
Guess he musta gotten bored.
I'd like for you
to meet my sword.
I wonder which of you will
be Laevateinn's first victim.
Watch, kid.
This is the true power
of science and machines.
[AKANE gasps]
What are you doing?
Stop, Dad!
[PAVLOV]
Now listen up.
You follow the path
you think is right
and never stop fightin', okay?
[PAVLOV] I'll be the one
takin' you down.
Excellent...
The father, and then the son.
I feel like you're
underestimatin' me.
Oh?
You can't dodge
that thing forever!
You must not have listened.
I said I'd take you down.
Akane. Take care of your mom.
For me, kid.
[MIDORI yells]
[HODR]
There's nowhere left to run.
Don't worry, I'll make
sure you die quickly.
It's all over now!
No! Why, Elena?
Why would you...?
Best friends...
Until the very end.
Elena!
Forgive me.
[AKANE]
No!
You can't just die
like that, dammit!
We were waiting for
you to come back, Dad!
You can't...
Not again!
[AKANE crying]
No, it can't be...
[MIDORI crying]
[MIDORI]
Why?
Elena!
We were finally reunited.
There were so many things
I wanted to tell you...
Why?
[MIDORI sobbing]
[LOKI laughing]
[LOKI] It sounds like the other
two have obtained their keys
to the Divine Gate.
But the boy who already knew
despair is the closest to it.
It's been such a long time.
I've been waiting
for you, big brother.
What's your life like?
How does it feel to be
falsely accused of the crimes
your little brother committed?
Of course, you're still
playing the martyr.
No brother,
you made me this way!
[ARITON] I've thrown
away all sense of guilt!
Let's go!
[ARITON] Sorry, brother.
This is the only way to free us.