[NARRATOR]
The girl runs swiftly
as if she were
riding the breeze.
She doesn't realize that
the future she runs toward
may not be what she expects.
For who can know which
way the wind will blow?
I'm sorry!
[yelps]
Oh my goodness, are you okay?
Yeah!
Least I think so.
[MIDORI]
Hurry, let's go!
[ELENA]
Whoa!
Not so fast!
[NARRATOR]
The two girls run hand in hand.
They don't understand that the
bond of friendship is fragile--
That it might eventually
fracture beyond repair.
How could they know
in these happy times?
That one day...
[NARRATOR] The only thing left
will be memories and tears
for a friendship that
exists only in the past.
Hiya, Arthur.
It's been quite a while huh?
Well, well,
what do we have here?
The trickster god Loki is
gracing us with his presence?
Always good to see you, Oz.
Summoning both of us at once.
Let me guess,
it's a special occasion?
[ARTHUR]
Yesterday, I obtained the key.
We're going to open
the Divine Gate, gentlemen.
You mark my words.
You can't be serious, Arthur.
There's no way.
Interesting...
[OZ] Even if that's true, the
Council will never approve!
[LOKI chuckles]
So you called us here to get
your impossible mission
started, is that right?
I honestly don't care
whether you believe me or not.
But it's the truth.
Help me and you'll see that.
Sure. I can't say no
to a preposterous challenge.
[OZ] Will you quit fooling
around and be serious for once?
What happens if you do manage
to open that damn Gate?
Then I will do
whatever has to be done.
[LOKI]
Hmm...
Hmph. I'll support you
with all my magic,
but on one condition.
Whatever happens with the Gate,
you have to promise me
that you'll help the weak.
Agreed?
How about you watch from
the sidelines instead, Oz?
I'll make sure to
save you good seats.
[LOKI chuckles]
It seems it's not a
challenge, but an invitation.
I have to admit
that I'm interested.
So tell me, what does the
great and powerful wizard
have to say about
this development?
I just hope he's actually
half as confident
as he's pretending to be.
A foul wind approaches.
Very impressive!
She's able to hold
her own against Ginji.
She's more fired up than
she usually is, that's for sure.
But things don't always end well
whenever she's in
the zone like this.
[MIDORI yelling]
It seems like she moves
as straight as an arrow
through her life.
However...
Her conscious and subconscious
are twisting together.
[MIDORI]
I am not going to lose!
[GIRL 3A]
Whoa! Hey, look at this!
It says that someone
saw the Divine Gate
at Mount Hagakure!
[GIRL 3B]
That's crazy!
I wonder if they got
their wish granted!
Oh, please.
I haven't believed in that
fairytale since kindergarten.
[GIRLS laughing]
[ELENA] Do you think
there really is such a thing
as the Divine Gate?
Oh yeah, definitely!
But you can only see it
if you believe in it.
Okay.
So tell me what
you would wish for
if you managed to find the Gate.
I'd want never-ending cucumbers
so I could eat 'em all day.
You're ridiculous.
[MIDORI]
Well...
Why don't you tell me
what you'd ask for, then?
[ELENA] I'd ask to be
your number one best friend
forever and ever.
That's what I want
most in the world.
[MIDORI] Well, that's dumb.
You're already my best friend.
Yeah, but how do you
know if it'll be forever?
Trust me, I do!
[ELENA]
Then it's a promise.
Number one friends
until the end of time!
For sure!
[EFREET]
Time's up!
I'll be...
...number one!
Stand down!
The match is over!
Did you not hear Efreet
call time a second ago?
[MIDORI]
I'm sorry!
Midori really
killed it out there.
Think so?
She looked pretty
scared, if you ask me.
Wonder why?
Training's the only way
she'll reach the Gate.
Yeah, but remember...
Fear of failure can stop
even the strongest among us.
[NARRATOR] The students know
that the road to their goal
will be paved with setbacks--
That the path is full of curves.
But there's something
they don't yet understand.
The greatest suffering
lies not in failing
to achieve their dreams,
but in seeing the vast
emptiness that lies beyond them.
[HIKARI]
Welcome aboard, Aoto!
[MIDORI] Let us know if you
have any questions, okay?
[HIKARI giggling]
[CHILDREN laughing]
Say cheese!
Hey, Aoto!
Do you want any chicken?
It's still hot!
Um, no thank you.
What, you don't eat meat?
I've just never
had any hot food.
I guess that's
kind of weird, huh?
Just tell her...
About how your heart
rejects anything that's warm.
That's always been
your greatest fear, right?
That if someone shows
you true kindness,
you'll realize what you've
been missing all these years.
[glass shatters]
I'm sorry!
It slipped right outta my hand!
No worries.
Excuse me.
Hey, hey, hey!
Why don't you tell me
how you ended up
looking for the Gate, Aoto?
Well, I'm an Adapter.
Oh, no, no, no.
I already knew that.
What I mean is...
Not really how,
but maybe... Uh...
Um, I dunno how to put it.
Well, you, like, uh...
I know.
She means why are
you looking for the Gate?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
the "why" is what's
important, huh?
What are your goals?
And why seek it out?
I guess...
C'mon, tell us your
number one reason!
After all, number one is the
only thing that matters, right?
Midori?
Ha! Fooled ya!
It doesn't matter since
I'll be the first one
to find the Gate.
Yes, It's a cutthroat world.
But someone has to be
number one, don'tcha think?
Actually, I see you as the type
who'll fall on your face right
in front of the finish line.
[MIDORI]
That's mean.
[ALL laugh]
[MIDORI]
Hey, stop!
Why does everyone
think that's so funny?
[AKANE laughing]
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
It's just that you
were so insistent that
the loser stay behind
and clean everything.
It's not funny!
[AKANE]
Hey!
Don't mix the recycling
with the trash.
Y'know what?
There's no point in
you staying here to help
if you're just gonna
nag the whole time
and make fun of me.
You should've gone home
when everyone else did.
Come on.
[laughing]
Your sad face.
[ALL]
Rock, paper, scissors!
I've never seen anyone
lose so hard before.
[MIDORI growls]
You shut your stupid mouth!
It shoulda been
a foot race instead.
Then I would have
beaten all of you jerks,
and I would've been number one!
You said something
like that earlier.
What's all this about
having to be "number one"?
Is something wrong?
Well, I'm not sure.
Wha--?
[MIDORI]
That may be the problem.
Maybe if I find the Divine Gate,
I'll have the answer.
[MIDORI] Why was it so
important for her to be
my number one friend, anyway?
[NARRATOR] The wish that
her friend shared with her
is a whisper in the
background of every beat
of the girl's heart.
It pulls her closer
to the holy Gate.
Guiding her.
Fueling her as
she stumbles forward.
You're late!
Better hurry!
It'll look bad if we're tardy on
the first day of seventh grade!
Sorry, sorry!
[yelps]
[ELENA] Man, you're
such a mess in the morning.
Thanks for the save.
[ELENA]
You came undone.
There, much better.
[ELENA]
C'mon, let's go.
'Kay!
This is it.
Yeah. No big.
Hey, wait...
Thanks for waiting--
[STUDENT 3B] Hey,
your name's Midori, right?
You're gonna be
late for our lab.
[MIDORI]
Yeah...
Wait a sec.
Nobody wears
their ties like that,
even though we're supposed to.
It's much cuter this way.
[STUDENT 3B]
Walk with us?
Yeah, sure.
[NARRATOR] Even though she
knows the seasons change,
the girl thinks
the bonds of friendship
will withstand
the march of time.
But just as the leaves
of summer yield to autumn,
so too do relationships
turn brittle
and begin to fall apart.
[STUDENT 3B] I heard
they're gonna have fireworks
for this year's summer festival!
I know, I'm excited!
It's because so many
tourists are coming
to visit Mount Hagakure
these days.
I guess we have the
Divine Gate to thank!
Hey, Midori.
You wanna come to
the festival with us?
It's always a ton of fun!
Yeah, sure.
Uh, can I bring
another person with me?
Oh, she means her.
Yeah, we're fine with that.
But I don't think she'd
have a good time.
We've noticed you're the
only person she ever talks to.
No, that's not the case!
You just have to
get to know her,
and then you'll see
she's a really cool person.
She's super nice,
and fun to be around
once she gets
comfortable with you.
[MIDORI] A bigger group
will be so much fun.
Just give them a chance.
This is the perfect way for
you to get to know everyone.
[ELENA] But I don't want to
get to know any of those girls.
Why not?
Because I don't need
a whole bunch of friends.
You're the only one
I need, Midori.
You're my number one
best friend.
Uh...
You know, you say that...
And we're best friends.
But, I--
It's just--
They're my friends, too.
Being number one
friends is the only thing
that matters, though.
You don't need anyone else.
Hey...
That's just... not right.
We can all be friends!
The only thing
that we've ever needed
in this world is each other.
I see no reason for
that to change now.
You remember.
We made a promise back then.
We said we'd be each other's
number one best friends
forever and always.
I'm sorry.
This is a little much for me.
[MIDORI]
No, wait!
"I'm sorry about earlier.
I'd really like to go to this
year's festival with you."
"We've always gone together
ever since we were little kids."
[MIDORI gasps]
[MIDORI]
"Then where are you going?"
[NARRATOR]
So many questions.
And yet, there may
never be answers.
Still, the girl can't help but
reach out and try to grasp them.
Even if they're as fleeting
as the glittering flowers
that bloom in the night's
sky over the festival.
[GIRL 3E]
Did you see this?
It says a girl went missing
up by Mount Hagakure.
[GIRL 3F]
Really?
Maybe she was spirited away.
[GIRL 3G]
That's so freaky.
What the--?
Where did she go?
[MIDORI panting]
[POLICEMAN 3A]
Hey, stop!
Elena...
[MIDORI]
And that was it.
I never saw my
best friend again.
There was a lot of talk about
what happened to her back then.
But I believe she's at the Gate.
She's probably there
waiting for me,
even after so
many years going by.
I know it.
May I ask you what's
brought this on now, Boss?
You were really particular
about choosing the dates
to begin our search
for the Gate.
The time is finally upon us.
Sounds like fun to me.
Am I gonna die on
some wild goose chase?
I will stay by your
side no matter what.
Aw, you don't have to worry.
I'll make sure to keep
you safe, 'kay, Daddy?
That's so kind of you.
Thank you, Bedi.
And you, Gawy.
[LANCELOT]
What a joke...
[KAY]
Here we go...
[LANCELOT]
Hmm?
Oh, sorry.
I guess I'm just dumbfounded
that we're doing this.
Lemme guess...
This is all that Santa Clause
guy's idea, right?
Of course it is!
What good ever came
from an out-of-season
Christmas present, anyway?
None, I bet.
There's a chill
in the air today.
I've just the thing.
Some soup will warm us up.
I'm sure that Lance
will come around soon.
I know.
I need all my Knights of Round.
That's why I was so
selective in choosing them.
[K]
Y'know, it's funny.
You're not even sure
why you're here, are you?
Sure, you have a wish
you want granted.
But part of you doesn't
want for it to come true.
Because you're afraid
of what it would mean
and what it would do to you.
You're wrong. I have no wishes.
Okay, maybe not,
but you do have a big gaping
hole inside of your heart.
You try so hard to hide it,
but you'll never
be able to patch it up
and make it whole on your own;
you're gonna need
some outside help.
I couldn't care less about
reaching that stupid Gate.
That's what you think, but
your heart says otherwise.
Deep down, you want
your wish to be granted.
No, I don't have a wish.
Have you noticed
he spends a lot of time
talking to himself?
[AKANE]
What a weirdo.
Let's move!
Let's what?
Wait for me.
[AKANE] Y'know, we shouldn't
be snooping around like this.
[MIDORI] I just wanna be able
to help out if he's upset.
There's probably a lot
going on in his head.
[AKANE]
I wouldn't be surprised.
I mean, the guy did
murder his parents.
To be honest with you,
I don't think he did it.
It's just way
too crazy to be true.
Or he must have had
a really good reason.
[AKANE] Come on, you've
gotta stop making excuses
for this killer.
Whoa, what did you do?
[MIDORI]
Nothing!
I just entered Aoto's name
in the search bar
and then it kicked me out.
But...
I wonder why...
[AKANE] What did this guy do
to get his files restricted?
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Do you still think of it, Aoto?
I do.
I remember it so vividly--
The night we met each other.
[AKANE]
He might've killed his parents
and caused the Blue Christmas?
That's nuts.
[BREUNOR] You are trying to
find the truth, aren't you?
I'll tell you.