[NARRATOR] When the light shines
bright, it creates shadows.
Just as turmoil
and darkness arise
anytime order starts to
spread across the land.
Those wholive in the darkness
are called "the Defiers."
They are the wretched people
who do not know the light.
[NARRATOR]
Not everyone is aware of this.
The boy still does not realize
that there is a dark world
just beyond the light.
[AKANE] Agh, This
place is so far away.
[MIDORI] Well, it is
in an abandoned section.
[AKANE] Okay, so what
does that mean, exactly?
What? You should know this!
It's where we're doing
our special training.
Of course I know.
Just remind me.
[MIDORI] It's my understanding
that it's some kinda place
where people can't live safely.
Actually, it's an
area the World Council
doesn't manage, bon.
Oh, gotcha.
I get it now.
It's just like I said it was.
Ha! You're as
clueless as me.
[MIDORI laughs]
[METABON] Sometimes I
worry about you two, bon.
Oh, wow!
What a view!
This is totally not what I
expected it to look like at all.
The abandoned section
is gorgeous!
There's probably more
to an area like this
than meets the eye.
What?
There weren't any
advisors on board,
so who's supposed to be in
charge of this special training?
What's the matter, huh?
Are you gettin' scared?
Of course not!
I was thinking out loud is all!
I hate when I feel like I don't
know what's going on, y'know?
[GINJI]
If you got a problem, go home.
[AKANE]
Ginji!
[NARRATOR] The boy can't
find interest in anything.
Because of this, he
searches for the Divine Gate
using a power that
favors nothingness.
His blade heartlessly
slashes everything,
even when he's the
one who gets hurt.
Ha! There's no
way I'm leaving!
Training to reach the Gate
is just a waste of your time.
I'm the one who's
gonna get there first.
Nuh-uh!
Hey!
Would you two
please stop fighting?
[HIKARI]
Yeah, calm down, you guys.
Let's see some smiles, yeah?
[MIDORI]
Hikari!
[NARRATOR] The girl
always seems to be happy.
Her smile never clouds
over or falters.
But a painted-on grin
can never truly cover up
feelings of heartache
and fragileness inside.
Well, hello!
It's good to see ya!
[MIDORI chuckles]
Hey there.
I didn't know you two
were coming along!
[HIKARI]
Yup! Yukari's pumped!
[NARRATOR]
The girl likes the night.
The tranquility.
The purple-hued city.
The deep dark shadows.
Those things all bring
the girl a sense of calm.
The girl is at home
in the night.
She loves darkness
more than anything.
There's darkness within you.
I see it in your eyes.
Is there something you
don't like about this place?
I don't have much
of an opinion.
[YUKARI]
Oh.
[BEDIVERE]
I've been waiting for you!
Wait, where are you going?
You can't just ignore me!
That's so mean!
You guys came from the
Academy for special training,
didn't you?
[BEDIVERE]
I'll be your trainer.
I'm one of Arthur's
Knights of Round.
Codename Bedivere.
Did you not recognize my mask?
[YWAIN] Listen, the kids know
us as the Knights of Round.
Since they call us "Knights,"
they'll instantly get
that you're one of us
if you wear a horse mask.
Y'know, like a...
like a chess piece.
Just trust me on this.
[BEDIVERE]
Yeehaw!
That stupid Ywain
tricked me again!
I've never been so
embarrassed before in my life!
Something tells me that
she's not the brightest.
Yeah, but she seems like a
really nice person at least.
So when are we gonna
start our special training?
Oh! Yeah, that.
Hope you brought your game
faces, 'cause it won't be easy!
[AKANE] All we have to do
is break up into two teams
and find some checkpoints?
Lame.
I was actually kinda worried
that the special training
was gonna be super
tough or something,
but so far it's been
a lot of fun!
[AKANE]
Whatever.
All I care about is
beating Ginji's group.
It took you guys long enough!
Hey, it's Breunor.
That's right! You've
found your first mission.
Yes, you have the high
honor of fighting me,
the Great Palomides.
[MIDORI]
Uh...
[PALOMIDES chuckles]
A duel between real men
is a competition of strength!
[MIDORI]
Uh...
Ha! All right then, old man.
We'll see who's
the strongest here.
Come on! Let's fight!
[BOTH grunting[
Why am I not surprised
he volunteered to do this?
Don't you think this is whole
thing's kinda strange, Aoto?
[PALOMIDES]
What's the matter?
Don't tell me that's
all you've got, kid!
[MORDRED]
True or false?
Arthur's Driver is known as
the great sword, Masamune.
Circle for true, X for false.
Choose the side that is correct.
'Kay, game on.
Time to do this.
[AKANE]
It's gotta be true!
[AOTO]
False.
[AKANE yells]
Wow, I was right.
And the blue-eyed kid
is the winner!
Arthur's Driver is
actually called "Excalibur."
Why am I always
the one who gets dirty?
[AKANE]
This sucks.
I can do better than that.
[NARRATOR] The boy still chases
his father's blazing footsteps.
No matter how much time
passes, that man's image
remains imprinted in the
forefront of the boy's memory,
burning bright.
Never fading out.
[AKANE]
Huh?
[GIRL screams]
--[yells]
--[splash]
Hey, are you okay?
[GIRL laughing]
So you came all
the way out here
for some special training?
Well, that's the story
they told us, at least.
It seems like a waste of time.
Sounds cool to me.
You're a weirdo.
Hey, now...
That charm.
It's pretty.
[AKANE]
Hm?
Oh. You mean this?
So what is it?
Something important to me.
But you wouldn't get it.
How important?
Like, if you had to choose,
would you save a
friend or the necklace?
That's not fair.
You can't compare
things like that.
[GIRL]
Hmm...
Then, will you give it to me?
Say what?
Not a chance.
Okay, fine.
I've just always wanted
something like that.
Something precious to me!
But surely you have a
couple of things in your life
that you consider
special, don't you?
It's funny...
Happy people always
think that way.
Look, forget about it.
I'm happy that you're happy.
And you should be, too.
[GIRL]
Uh-oh, you missed a spot.
Right there.
By your ear.
Where, you mean, here?
[GIRL]
The other side.
[giggles]
You big dummy.
[laughing]
[MIDORI]
Akane!
Where'd you go?
Oh. There you are.
Is something wrong?
Nothing. Sorry.
I was talking to--
[MIDORI]
Hm? To who?
[AKANE]
Um... Never mind.
[LANCELOT] Now is not the
time to be playing games
with these kids, Arthur.
The most important
lessons in life
aren't always learned
on the battlefield.
Battles are the least of my
concerns with these children.
All of our decisions are
made in order to get closer
to the Divine Gate, right, boss?
[ARTHUR]
Don't forget, Lancelot.
A fruitful harvest starts with
a single blooming bud.
You don't forget that
these are your students.
They're not a bunch of crops.
[MIDORI sighs]
We finally made it.
Aw man, I am
completely worn out.
Excellent work, you guys.
You can freshen up
over there if you'd like!
Hey.
[AKANE]
Yeah?
What's up with you?
[AKANE]
Nothing, really.
You have to talk to
get it off your chest.
That's what Midori says.
I met someone earlier.
Back in the woods.
[NARRATOR] The girl had
appeared out of thin air,
and then was gone
just as quickly.
He feared that by
talking about her,
she might disappear
from his memory as well.
Like she'd never existed
in the first place.
[BEDIVERE]
So, everyone,
how did you like your
special training today?
I bet I'd like it more if
I knew what the point was.
Of course.
I've wondered that as well.
What's that supposed to mean?
[BEDIVERE] You're not
the only ones in the dark.
I have no idea why we're
doing this sort of training.
All the boss said was,
"Every choice comes
with a consequence."
So I guess you should keep
that in the back of your mind.
That's enough talk.
Let's move on to
your next mission.
[chuckles]
[MIDORI] Now we're supposed
to go back to the station
in the dark,
without our trainer?
How's this supposed to help us?
[AKANE]
Huh?
[HIKARI]
Whoa... Who are they?
What the hell?!
They're shape-shifting.
This is bad news!
They look strong.
Watch out!
[MIDORI]
What the--?
[YUKARI]
They're Seconds.
Second whats?
[YUKARI] Don't tell me you've
never heard of them before.
They seek out power by
crossing the species barrier,
hoping they'll be able to reach
the Divine Gate by doing so.
The thing is, Seconds
don't normally attack people.
Something strange is going on.
We won't allow anyone to
trespass on our territory.
You're all dead!
We can take these guys!
No, our mission is to return
to the station, Ginji!
You're gonna run away?
I'm following orders!
C'mon, let's go!
'Kay!
Hey, it's you.
[GIRL laughing]
[GIRL yelling]
What the hell?! Agh! Quit it!
No! I'm sorry...
But they saw me with you.
They don't like intruders.
Okay, then...
You're obviously not human,
so just what are you?
That's where you're wrong.
All of us are human.
At least, we were.
But we ended up out here
because we'd be dead
if we stayed in town.
[GIRL]
They called us "Defiers,"
among other much worse things.
Do you get it?
Then they forced us
to live in hiding
because we questioned
the Council.
I've never heard of you before.
[GINJI yelling]
[HIKARI]
They're tough!
And so sad.
[AOTO]
Hold on! Where's Akane?
What?
He was right behind us
just a minute ago!
Let's go find him!
[GARETH] It would appear
some of the Seconds
escaped to the
abandoned section.
I'm unfamiliar
with their Drivers.
I wonder where
they obtained them.
From the Grimoire Cult,
most likely.
So you knew about them?
We could deploy a rescue team.
No.
And tell Bedi not
to help out, either.
But... the kids
don't stand a chance.
[ARTHUR]
Will they cross swords?
Perhaps talk it out?
Or run away
from the entire fight?
I want to see how they choose to
handle this odd turn of events.
[LOKI] You're putting
too much responsibility
on their shoulders.
[OZ] Wouldn't it be much safer
to readjust your plans?
[ARTHUR]
There's no need for that.
[OZ] Just so you know,
you can't get to the Divine Gate
by stacking up dead bodies.
[AKANE grunting]
[AKANE]
Would you cut it out?
I don't wanna fight you!
Why do you keep attacking me?
What did I do ever do to you?
[GIRL]
That necklace.
I'll get it after all.
Hey...
Are there any good movies
coming out these days?
And is that amazing bakery
near the station still open?
[AKANE]
Huh? What are you talking about?
[GIRL] We had to sacrifice
all that in order to survive.
We had no choice but to leave
or we would all be murdered.
Why do you get to be happy
while I live in pure misery?
It's just not fair!
[AKANE]
Aoto!
You stay away from him!
Oh, this is perfect.
Are you happy that your
friends came back for you?
Too bad they're a weakness.
They'll only drag you down.
[AOTO]
Akane! Now's the time!
Hurry and say
what's on your mind!
[AKANE]
Huh?
We're judged on
the actions we take.
But sometimes feelings are
the most important weapon.
[AOTO]
I didn't act when I should have,
and didn't say
what I should have,
and because of that,
I lost something important.
So talk now!
Listen...
I'm sorry about all of this.
I had no clue what was goin' on.
I didn't know there
were other people here
so far from away the city.
I can see now that we
have it much easier than you.
I'm so pathetic!
So...
Is there any way
that I can help you?
Please, just tell me
what I can do.
[GIRL]
You know...
I've never met someone so naïve.
[yells]
No, Akane!
[AKANE grunting]
[GIRL] You don't even
think of us as people,
so how can you understand?
We're "Seconds."
[AOTO]
But he's trying to understand.
That's gotta count
for something!
We know much more than
you blind fools ever will.
And we know it's pointless
to trust your motives.
You just don't get it.
Go away!
But why?
[BEDIVERE]
If I hadn't stopped her,
she would've
killed you just now.
There are other ways...
[BEDIVERE] You're a big
asset to the Academy,
and Arthur doesn't
want to lose you.
Now!
By the order of Bedivere,
your training is complete!
We knights shall
administer justice!
[OZ]
Such brutality.
They're definitely your
subordinates, all right.
[LOKI] But the kids
tried talking things out
instead of fighting.
It's a choice that will allow
them to claim their innocence.
Has the World
Council checked in?
Oh please, you don't
have to pretend you care
what they say.
I mean, you've already made up
your mind, haven't you?
You'll try for the Divine Gate
no matter what or who
stands in your way.
And you know what
responsibilities
fall on your shoulders
because of this choice.
But you've weighed your
losses, codename Arthur.
A successful leader
will guide his people
when they've strayed
from the path.
I chose to take on the name
of a king for a reason.
It's my duty to shepherd my
subjects in any way I see fit.
[AKANE]
I'm sorry.
[GIRL]
Why are you apologizing?
After all, you didn't
do anything wrong.
[AKANE]
But still...
Hey.
[GIRL]
You missed a spot.
Right there.
By your ear.
The other side.
You dummy.
[AKANE crying]
I guess people can be nice.
[GIRL]
Please be happy.
[AKANE crying]
[AKANE]
No...
There must've been another way.
It didn't have to be like this.
Your conscious and
subconscious both agreed.
They wanted to save this girl
and protect her from harm.
But in the end, you didn't
have enough power to do so.
[AKANE]
Dammit!
[SANTA CLAUSE]
Just you wait.
I've got a great
present for you.
[LOKI] Arthur's finally
going to make his big move.
I'm shivering with anticipation.
[ARTHUR]
I'm heading for the Divine Gate,
and I'd like you to join me.