[NARRATOR] The boy was young
when he first felt the flames.
They were born from the warmth
of his father's love,
sparked by the bond
between parent and child.
This fire made him feel safe.
Now those flames guide the boy
as he tries to put
his life to good use.
He strives for
the same salvation
that his father pursued--
Redemption through
a cleansing fire.
The boy's blazing eyes search
the horizon for his father,
even though he knows that
he'll never see him again.
[AKANE yells]
[NARRATOR] He tries to live
up to his father's legacy.
To make him proud.
You're so sweaty.
Do you want me
to hose you off a little?
Yeah, no, thanks.
Fire and water don't mix
together very well, remember?
He seems kinda upset.
It must be because
of what Aoto said.
Save your breath.
I did kill them.
It was my fault.
[MIDORI] It's gotta hurt
since Akane lost his father.
[LOKI]
Ah, good morning, Arthur.
I see you stayed
the night again.
[LOKI]
Enjoy.
I made it just
the way you like it.
Why are you here, Loki?
[LOKI]
Don't sound so cold.
Every king needs a
god looking out for him.
So here I am.
By the way, I heard
you're trying to recruit
another kid with powers
into the Academy.
[chuckles]
[LOKI]
I can't wait to meet him.
What kind of boy have
you found for us this time?
Don't make that ugly face.
If you've taken an
interest in this kid,
then of course
I'm interested, too.
[K]
It's painful, isn't it?
Every time you see dry
bread and milk together?
Then you're reminded
of painful memories.
I try not to think
about those days.
You can try all you like,
but those thoughts
are gonna keep coming.
They're like scars
left on your heart.
You're forced
to relive the pain,
knowing it's impossible
to reach into the past
and change the
things you regret.
[MIDORI]
Hiya, Aoto!
I'm so glad we caught you!
[AOTO]
What are you doing here?
We came to pick you up!
Now we're off to the Academy!
You may think we're a nuisance,
but we're just trying
to be good friends.
Well, a good teacher,
in my case.
I'm not his friend.
Do these little
furry guys belong to you?
[AOTO]
No.
[MIDORI]
Oh, okay.
But you feed them?
Sometimes, when I feel like it.
That's horrible.
They'll grow to depend on you
and think you actually care.
Well, whatever the case,
they do look pretty happy.
[AKANE]
Think for a second, gah!
Imagine how sad they'll
feel when he betrays them.
[MIDORI]
You've got a point.
[UNDINE] Maybe it's a
little early in the day
to be talking about
betrayal, Akane.
You're forgetting
that deep down inside,
we all have a kind heart
and want to make the world
a better place
for everyone else.
Only sometimes our other
emotions get in the way.
I don't believe that.
[MIDORI growls]
I don't.
Anyway, we should
get on to the Academy.
Will it make me a better person?
[AKANE]
Who knows?
That's up to you,
not anybody else.
Besides, with--
[MIDORI] Is there something
you want to work on
specifically, Aoto?
It might help to know that.
You have to say
some things out loud
for them to become true.
What? Don't tell me
you've suddenly gone mute.
We're not mind readers.
[AKANE sighs]
We're getting nowhere.
I knew this was gonna
be a waste of time.
Hey, hold up!
Sorry about that.
He's always been impatient,
but it's like he's been
extra on-edge lately.
Plus, with all the rumors...
[MIDORI] I know we're asking
a lot of questions
about stuff that's
kinda personal.
We're just trying to
get to know you better.
Because, honestly, we feel
connected to you in some way.
[METABON]
That short fuse of yours
is going to get you
in trouble one day, bon.
What?
That was nothing
back there, man.
Then why're you
so frustrated, bon?
Just forget it.
Anyway, where are we right now?
I thought the
Council had fixed up
all of Terrastia's
neighborhoods.
You can repaint a building,
but that doesn't
make it new, bon.
Ugh, it's all so stupid.
That boy's a punk and
the Council only looks like
it's helping out.
[AKANE]
You know, if my dad were here,
he'd actually be
getting stuff done.
He had sway over the Council.
They called him
the Genius of Divine.
I think they needed him
to guide them.
But then...
There was an accident
during one of his experiments,
and he was killed.
At least, that's
what the Council told us.
I don't believe it
for a second, though.
My dad was brilliant.
He wouldn't have made
a fatal mistake.
That's one of the reasons
you're still trying
to find the Divine Gate,
isn't it, bon?
You're not sure what happened,
so you want to know
the whole truth, bon.
Shut up!
[MIDORI] Akane's tried to
follow in his dad's footsteps.
But now that he's gone,
the path isn't so clear.
Explains a lot.
Like why he's so hostile to me,
seeing as I killed
my own parents.
I still can't believe that,
even if you do say it's true.
Unless you had a good
reason for doing it.
Your past isn't the important
thing about you, though.
This is what counts.
Right here.
[MIDORI]
Bye for now.
See ya later!
[K]
Deep down, you know this,
but I'm going to say it anyway.
If you want to know more
about that red-haired boy,
you should go and find him.
If you do, maybe you'll
end up feeling a little better,
but then again, maybe you won't.
One thing's for sure--
Nothing's gonna change
if you stay still.
[AOTO] I shouldn't get
close to anyone ever again.
[K]
That's probably true,
but you can't
control your heart,
as much as you like
to pretend you can.
Gimme whatever you got.
What do you want?
How about all
of your change?
[stomach growling]
Sounds like you're
pretty hungry.
Yeah.
Let's see...
That's horrible.
They'll grow to depend on you
and think you actually care.
[AKANE]
Where are your parents, kid?
Do you have any?
[HIROTO] Mommy and Daddy
are both busy right now.
[AOTO] Are you looking
for food again?
[HIROTO]
Huh?
Oh! Hi, Aoto!
Got any bread?
Not on me, but I can go
and buy some if you're hungry.
Thank you so much!
What's your deal?
Just feel like feeding
the strays again?
[AOTO] You were about to do
the same thing, weren't you?
[AOTO]
He needs someone's help.
Well, why aren't his
parents here, then?
They should be
taking care of him.
He's too young to be on
these streets by himself.
Not all families are perfect.
[AKANE]
That's not an excuse.
Aoto! Let's eat!
[AKANE]
Hold on.
I wanna go talk to his parents.
What for?
They can't feed him.
[PATROL DRIVER] This is an
automated World Council patrol,
dedicated to ensuring
the safety and security
of your neighborhood.
If you witness any
suspicious activity,
please report it to
the Council immediately.
Is that a Driver that's
been designed for patrols?
You see a lot of
them in areas like this.
These machines are so cool!
[PATROL DRIVER] ...ensuring
the safety and security
of your neighborhood.
If you witness any
suspicious activity,
please report it to
the Council immediately.
Thank you for helping us...
[low whirring noise]
What happened?
[LOKI chuckling]
Showtime.
Let's see what you can do.
[AOTO, AKANE gasp]
[WOMAN 2A, MAN 2A yell]
[CROWD screaming]
Why's it doing that?
I'm scared!
Stay close to me.
Can you hear me?
There's a patrol
Driver going nuts!
[OPERATOR]
This is Council Headquarters.
I can't find any malfunctioning
Drivers in your area.
Could you be mistaken?
Why don't you tell me?
Do you see what's happening?
[OPERATOR 1A]
Confirmed.
We'll send the trons
in immediately.
Dammit. The trons?
Huh?
[HIROTO screaming]
[AOTO]
No, wait!
[AKANE]
Hey! Are you all right?
Somebody help!
I can't get down!
[HIROTO whimpering]
[HIROTO'S FATHER]
Hiroto!
Daddy! Please save me!
Hiroto! I'm coming!
[HIROTO'S FATHER screaming]
Daddy!
[coughing]
Help me!
No... No...
I'm sorry. I can't.
Get up and save him,
damnit, he's your child!
It's no use.
And why not?
Because he's trapped as well.
[OPERATOR]
Nontron in position.
We'll now generate the zone.
[AKANE]
Roger that.
[OPERATOR]
Checking the coordinates.
Ready to move on!
Hey, Aoto! Akane!
All right!
Let's take it down.
Hell yeah!
Hey, water-user.
Go put out the fires back there.
No. I don't have the control.
You're the only
chance we've got.
[AKANE]
This was made for you.
You want to save
the kid, don't you?
Let's go!
[MIDORI]
Ha!
[AKANE yelling]
[HIROTO'S FATHER crying]
Look over there!
[AKANE]
Hey!
[MIDORI]
Is he hurt?
He'll be okay.
--[AKANE] You! You're worthless!
--[MIDORI] What are you?
Why didn't you try to save him?!
Tell me!
[AOTO]
He did try.
Not everyone's that strong.
Some are ruled by their
subconscious fears and memories.
[AKANE]
What are you talking about?
This man consciously
wanted to save his son.
That much should be obvious.
But he was too afraid
to act due to something
in his subconscious.
We're not always able to
control that kind of fear.
Trust me on this.
As a kid, I learned
you can't always act
on the things you want to.
You look so sad.
[HIROTO coughing]
[HIROTO'S FATHER]
You're all right, Hiroto.
You're just making
excuses for him.
If you can't protect
the people you love,
then what good are you?
[MIDORI]
No, wait!
I think Aoto's right.
Akane...
[HIROTO'S FATHER]
Hiroto.
Forgive me.
I wanted to come to save you!
Please. I'm sorry!
I really tried!
Hiroto...
My little boy.
Come here.
Do it.
Take your father's hand.
Spend time with him now
while you still have the chance!
Don't regret this.
I think you should
listen to him, you know.
Your father tried
his best to save you.
And that's the truth.
'Kay.
[HIROTO]
Daddy!
[HIROTO'S FATHER]
Hiroto!
[HIROTO]
Daddy!
Finally, things are
getting interesting.
[K] Even if someone
wants to be a good person,
you can never truly know
what's in their hearts.
Painful memories
and fears might keep them
from living the life
they want to lead.
Your conscious
and subconscious
are both as pure
as they come, Aoto.
Still, your actions
have been tainted
by all the terrible betrayals
you've faced in your life.
[K]
You're afraid to let people in
because you're sure
they'll hurt you.
You're not the only one
who has these fears.
Your little brother
was the same way.
But you knew that.
And you always have.
[NARRATOR]
The boy stands motionless
as an unrelenting rain
begins to fall.
It's not water from
the sky that drowns him,
but the crushing tears of
memories he'd rather forget.
[AOTO'S MOTHER]
Aoto, please, no!
[AOTO'S FATHER]
Stop! Don't!
[AOTO'S MOTHER]
You can't!
Don't kill us! Someone help!
Catch ya later, big brother.
Take care.
[AOTO]
Don't go!
Wait...
[AOTO gasps]
[ARITON]
Did you see it?
The Divine Gate?
Behind me?
[AOTO yelps]
Ah! That hurt, big brother!
On second thought,
maybe we shouldn't see
each other ever again.
[AKANE] Even if you're in pain,
don't let it control you.
[ARTHUR sighs]
I'm going to call it a night.
[ARTHUR]
Handle the rest.
[TRISTAN]
You got it, boss.
You know, it's strange...
You go by the name
of Santa Clause,
and yet you show up
with presents
even when it's not
the holiday season.
Yes, but only for you, Arthur.
Merry Christmas.
[ARTHUR] I'm happy you finally
decided to attend the Academy.
They badgered me into it.
Whatever!
You jerk.
You came here on your own.
Hey, watch your mouth.
He's one of us.
Either way, I'm glad.
Now, I've got
important news for you.
Something very special
has come into my possession.
A gift.
Like Christmas came
early this year?
Yesterday, I obtained the key.
[MIDORI]
The what?
[ARTHUR] The key that will
lead us to the Divine Gate.
The key that will make
all our dream come true.
[MIDORI gasps]
You mean it?
The Gate's real?
Seriously?
The Divine Gate.
That's right.
And we're going to open it up.
[NARRATOR] The boy's
conscious and subconscious
both desired to move forward.
I must see him again.
I must grab his hand once again.
[DOROTHY] I'd ask to be
your number one best friend
forever and ever.
That's what I want
most in the world.
[NARRATOR] The wish that
her friend shared with her
is a whisper in the
background of every beat
of the girl's heart.
[MIDORI] Why was it
so important for her
to be my number
one friend, anyway?