[AOTO]
You're early.
Don't you have a
tutoring session today?
No, I have the day off.
For our birthday.
Oh, yeah.
I guess I'd forgotten.
That's probably for the best.
They're only going
to celebrate mine.
And that's just because I
finally became an Adapter.
I don't understand
how you can have
such bright, clear eyes,
big brother.
Our parents have put us through
so many terrible things.
Do you hate me because
I'm their favorite child?
None of this stuff
is your fault, you know.
Of course not.
I'm just the one who has to
deal with all their pressure.
[NARRATOR] After seeing
his little brother's eyes
fill up with sorrow,
the boy found
himself speechless.
Suddenly, he was
filled with regret.
But who could he turn to for
help when they seemed so alone?
Long t
What are you
doing at the Gate?
Fate has guided me
to this spot.
[LOKI] You've caught on to how
this works by now, right?
Only the chosen ones can
go through the Divine Gate--
Those who know true despair.
Those who've lost an
important piece of their heart.
You fell into that
category, didn't you Arthur?
But a god got in my way
before I could step through.
Tell me something, my king...
Do you really believe it's hope
that's waiting beyond the Gate
and not just more sadness?
Hope is a resilient force--
One even a god can't destroy.
Careful, that sounds like a bet.
Now, then...
Why don't we sit back and watch
the future unfold together?
[K chuckling]
[MIDORI]
Who are you?
I was right to put
my faith in you.
I knew you'd make it this far.
Just where... am I?
Looks like you're doing well.
More importantly, what
have you been up to lately?
What's your life like?
How does it feel to be
falsely accused of the crimes
your little brother committed?
Keep a close watch on Aoto.
He's about to experience
a new ocean of despair.
This is important.
His true nature
is about to surface.
Since the day his brother
killed their parents,
Aoto has suppressed himself.
He locked away his feelings
and put up barriers
like his cold demeanor.
He believes it was his fault
that his parents were murdered.
And it constantly
haunts his thoughts.
He carries the crushing
weight of his brother's sins
and crimes as his own.
His broken heart is full
of regret and sadness.
After all you've been through,
your heart's in
the same condition.
So what will you do?
The Divine Gate is
right in front of you.
I see it.
I'm so close.
Get to your feet.
It's almost time for you to
take a step through the Gate.
[ARITON] Do you remember
what it was like, brother?
Our parents didn't
always single you out.
Before I developed any powers,
they doled out their
twisted kind of love
to both of us equally.
They'd tie me to a tree
whenever it rained
and made you stand
across from me, watching.
They said the only way
they'd cut me loose
is if you became an Adapter.
How many nights
did we spend like that,
staring at each other
in the pouring rain?
Brother, please, I'm cold!
I'm sorry...
I'm trying... I am!
[ARITON] You were always
crying and apologizing to me
for your failure.
I didn't understand.
Not until we switched places.
Being tied up
was hard, sure...
But having to watch powerless as
you shivered against that tree
was painful in a different way.
That's when it started.
You'd do anything you could
to try and protect me.
[ARITON] You rebelled against
our parents in full force.
Flunked the aptitude
test on purpose
despite your intelligence.
Anything to turn
our parents' anger
away from your little
brother and towards you.
Not true.
You actually were better
than me at everything.
[ARITON]
Stop lying to me!
I know you saw it then!
The Divine Gate revealed itself
to you before I could see it!
At the time, I wasn't
sure what was happening.
It was only later that
I made sense of it all.
You're... mistaken...
[ARITON]
Use your head!
Most people can't bear the force
of the Divine Gate. Right?
That's why they
lose consciousness
the first time they see it,
just like I did my first time.
But on that night, you proved
to be more powerful than me.
I felt the spark in you myself.
You're right... I guess.
You guess what, that
you kept the truth from me?
You could have told your
brother about your power.
I was afraid.
[ARITON] Our parents were
worthless human beings.
You were scared that
if they found out
you were the strongest,
they'd start abusing me again.
They could've learned a thing
or two about sacrifice from you.
I couldn't bear to
watch them hurt you.
So is that why you took
the blame for me that day?
When I tried to burn our house
down with them inside of it?
[AOTO'S MOTHER screams]
Fire!
[AOTO'S FATHER]
Hurry, get the extinguisher!
[AOTO'S MOTHER]
What happened?
We didn't leave
anything burning, did we?
[AOTO'S FATHER]
Dammit...
[AOTO]
It's my fault.
What are you--
I'm the one who did it.
Are you out of your mind?
How could you?
[AOTO] You deserve it
for what you put us through.
You little brat!
[AOTO'S MOTHER] We're hard
on you so you'll develop
strong abilities.
You'll thank us one day.
You can work for the World
Council if you're an Adapter.
Do you understand
what that means?
You'll be able to work
your way up the ladder
and influence the world...
This isn't some stupid fairytale
like chasing the Divine Gate
for a wish; this is real life
that we're preparing you for!
We do all of this
for you and your future!
Say that all you want...
But how can we care
about the future
when our present is such hell?
And besides... In the end,
this benefits you.
[AOTO'S FATHER] How dare you
talk to your parents like that!
I'll show you what hell is like!
[AOTO'S MOTHER]
No, stop, that's enough!
[AOTO'S FATHER] I'll tell you
when you can come back
in the house.
[ARITON] That incident
made me realize you were
a giant hypocrite.
You may have thought that
you were making things
better for me back then...
But all you did
was bring me more pain
as I watched how
they treated you.
It tore my heart up inside.
So thanks for nothing.
Weird... It's been so long...
I didn't realize I had any
more tears left inside me
after all these years.
[NARRATOR] There's a
conscious and subconscious
living in every person's mind.
Sometimes the
subconscious takes control.
Are you blaming me for
what you did to our parents?
Don't worry, brother.
That scene wasn't enough
to make me pick up a knife
and go at them.
They brought my wrath
down on themselves.
My subconscious
was full of hate.
Eventually I just
couldn't hold back.
[ARITON] Does it really matter
if it was premeditated,
or if it happened in
a moment of bloodlust?
Why make the distinction?
What is intent?
Conscious? Subconscious?
Where does the difference lie?
All the pain that
filled my heart...
All my feelings for you...
Mixed together, they fueled the
overwhelming fury in my soul.
And then one day...
I could barely look at you.
I didn't want to think about
everything you'd gone through
for me.
Your good intentions
were a burden. Worthless.
But do you remember, brother?
Before I killed our parents,
I paid you a visit.
Sorry, brother.
This is the only way to free us.
[ARITON] Even then,
your eyes were clear.
Bright and penetrating.
Watchful.
[ARITON] That was the night
I saw the Divine Gate
for the first time,
and finally became an Adapter.
I tasted true power
before collapsing.
Your eyes had been
calm and clear,
but I could sense
your judgment in them.
You had been looking down on me.
I wasn't judging you, brother.
I was trying to protect you!
[ARITON]
That's why I hated it so much!
You and I are twins!
You're only my big brother
by a few minutes!
I wasn't powerless!
That night...
Why didn't you say anything or
suggest we run away together?
It could've been
just the two of us!
Why did you choose to shoulder
all the pain yourself?
To indulge your ego and
feel like the better person?
You know I wasn't.
Of course! You're still
playing the martyr!
No, brother...
You made me this way!
Ha! Twisted!
[NARRATOR] The boy's demented
subconscious swelled,
plunging his
conscious into darkness.
He became a machine fueled by
hate and the desire to destroy.
His perceptions warped, unable
to see reality any longer.
[ARITON] You must have wanted
to run away from that hell,
to join me and be free somewhere
far away from our parents...
Didn't you?
Our parents were terrible,
but I still held out hope.
Always.
I told myself that
one day we'd go back
to the warm family we'd
been when we were younger.
All of us happy.
I never truly
gave up on them.
Heh. Well... Maybe
I was wrong about you.
You really are as stupid
as they thought you were.
There might have been
some good left in them.
[ARITON]
I don't buy that...
Our parents wouldn't change.
We were just tools for them.
They didn't love us.
And you know what else?
I'm sick of you still taking
the blame for me, big brother.
I've thrown away
all sense of guilt.
As for you, it's over!
I won't be your lesser anymore!
[SYLPH]
We finally found you!
Looks like somethin'
big is going down here, bon.
Undine, are you okay?
Poor Aoto...
He has to fight his brother.
[K]
The time has come.
What choice are
you going to make?
[ARITON] I've thrown away
all sense of guilt.
Let's go!
[ARITON yells]
No, stop it!
I don't want to fight you!
Don't you hurt Aoto!
Leave him alone! Or else!
You can't stop them.
Not anymore.
[ARITON]
Dammit, fight me!
[AOTO]
No! I am not going to hurt you!
[ARITON yells]
I've had enough
of your hypocrisy!
[SYLPH screams]
Look, I'm not a hypocrite.
I was simply trying
to protect my brother!
You're lying to yourself!
Just like all those families
who pretend to be happy.
And those parents who think
they can make up for anything
with a Christmas present!
Blue Christmas was punishment
for all of their failures.
This is bad...
The sins of the past are
starting to turn the present
into a nightmare for Aoto.
This fight doesn't have
to end with these brothers
killing each other.
I don't need you to
protect me from myself
or anything else.
Just like I didn't need our
parents putting me through hell,
using me to make their
own miserable lives better!
Now... Die!
[NARRATOR] Misunderstandings
between family...
Actions with
unexpected consequences...
Hands that refuse to be held...
Even though love is at the
foundation of all these things,
it's an emotion that
can be easily distorted,
morphing into hate,
and taking on an evil form.
[ARITON growling]
This is the end,
my dear brother.
[ARITON yells]
I'm coming!
[K] Aoto has to overcome
his demons on his own.
This is his fight.
[K] You should choose what
you do next very carefully.
What is your future?
[SURTR] Looks like
the humans are under the
Key Spirit's protection.
This might get tricky.
Damn, I hate those
stupid little brats.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But you're hurt.
That explosion was nothing.
Now let's get inside
that Gate Room.
[OZ]
You're not going anywhere!
[OZ] It was foolish
of me to think you gods
would handle things reasonably.
Now there's only one thing an
idiotic, ruined clown like me
can do to make things right...
I'm taking back all the power
I offered up to you gods
in the first place!
[OZ]
Dorothy!
Even if it means
sacrificing myself!
[yelling]
[SURTR]
You can't stop us!
[HOGNE]
You moron... I'll kill you!
No! You can't!
[screams]
Crap, our Drivers!
[ALL scream]
[ARITON yells]
[ARITON]
Brother...
Why won't you let me
set you free from the past?
I won't let you!
No way!
[ARITON yells]
Undine!
It's just as I thought...
I knew... one day...
I'd be able to help you
overcome the things
that were holding you back.
Don't forget the past doesn't
determine who you are at heart.
And that the future
is up to you.
You're gonna be okay,
Undine, I promise.
Hey, you called me by
my name again, Aoto.
That makes me happy.
I'm not done yet!
[AOTO]
No, stop!
[ARITON yells]
I'm coming, Aoto!
[MIDORI]
I'm here!
[ARITON laughing]
The desire to destroy
filling your heart...
The subconscious taking
over your conscious...
You tried to kill me.
We're not so
different after all.
No...
It's okay.
I'm glad I got
to see the real you.
Thanks for that, brother.
But know... only one of us is
gonna survive our next meeting.
[AOTO]
Wait...
[ARITON]
I'm gone.
As long as you continue to
bear my sins, I'll move freely.
See you soon, brother.
[ARITON laughing]
[SYLPH]
Her wound is really deep.
[METABON]
It looks painful, bon.
[AOTO]
Undine!
Are you okay?
I'm so glad I was able
to protect you, Aoto.
I'm like you...
I wanted to keep you
safe like you wanted
to protect your
little brother.
Now, go.
Don't let this stop you.
Yeah, we'll take
good care of her.
You still need
to push onward, bon!
Don't let this be the end, bon.
I'm gonna be fine.
I've got them.
You keep moving on your path.
Let's go!
It's time to enter
the Divine Gate!
You have earned
the right to do so today.
Welcome, everybody.
I hope you're ready to
experience the Divine Gate's
true form.
What...?
That's huge.
[K] It's watching your conscious
and subconscious thoughts,
putting despair
and hope on the scale
and weighing the
balance between the two.
But what does that mean?
See for yourself.
All you need to do
is walk towards it.
Wait... What are you, exactly?
You can't be my
own hallucination
if everyone sees you.
I'm the key.
The guide who shepherds
those who've experienced
true despair towards the Gate.
The key?
[K]
Do you want to change the past?
Or the future, now?
You have the ability to
choose either at the Gate,
but you'll need to
make your decision soon.
You three have
earned the right.
Because your hearts
have been broken to pieces.
[SANTA CLAUSE] You took away
Arthur's ability to choose
for himself.
But I'm here to give
him his freedom back.
[LOKI]
What a dramatic display, Arthur.
Now let's go watch the
remaking of the world together.
[ARTHUR]
It's not that easy, my friend.