[NARRATOR]
The boy knows...
...that sometimes
the moon turns blue.
[NARRATOR] He's aware that
such a moon shines on him,
coloring his world.
That night,
the moon was blue.
[CROWD screaming]
[NARRATOR]
That is why...
...the boy was able
to sink into the night.
That blue, dark, sinful night.
[PAVLOV] This is the fifth
version of the autonomous Driver
that we've developed.
The new model
boasts significant
tactical improvements
thanks to the Elements Heart
we've used as a power source.
Its fighting capabilities
are extraordinary.
Although, we're still
trying to sort out
a few lingering problems
in its operating systems.
Excellent work.
[LANCELOT]
I don't like this one bit.
The Knights of Round
are more than capable
of protecting you
without this thing.
[ARTHUR] Speaking of
my Knights, where's Shorty?
I haven't seen him
for a few days.
If you're talking about
Breunor, he's out sick.
Something wrong?
[ARTHUR]
No.
Let him get some rest
while there's still time.
[AOTO]
Surveillance.
[BREUNOR]
No matter what it takes...
...I will find the
evidence that proves
you're the bastard
who murdered my father.
--See ya!
--Have a good one!
[AKANE]
Hey, I got a question.
So... what's the deal
with you and the Council?
What are you talking about?
Um...
It's nothing, but uh...
We just...
Ugh! I'm gonna
come out and say it.
Please don't.
Here's the thing.
When we tried to find
your files on the server,
it said they were
all restricted.
Totally confidential.
So you were snooping
around in my files.
Well, when you say it
like that it sounds bad.
[AOTO]
Then what were you doing?
Hey, I already told you.
We don't give a crap
what you did in the past.
But look...
If you've got baggage that
needs to be taken care of,
then we wanna help you.
We weren't trying
to spy on you.
[AKANE]
Great. The silent treatment.
I know!
We're all members on this
social media networking site.
Why don't you join it, too?
It's really fun!
There, I just sent you a link.
You can use the site
to post things
that you don't want
to say in person.
Sometimes that's easier!
[AKANE]
A little too easy.
You post way too much
stuff on there.
[MIDORI]
Maybe so...
But it's only because
Undine always replies.
This is excellent!
Not interested.
What? But why not?
[AOTO] I don't have
anything to post about.
See you later.
He doesn't know
what he's missing.
[AKANE] I still don't
understand why the Council
has all his info
classified like that.
[MIDORI] It does kinda
seem like a red flag.
[phone chimes]
[MIDORI]
Hm?
I just got a direct message.
Who the heck's Blue Stray Cat?
No one I've heard of.
It's probably
some kind of scam.
This guy says he
knows how we can access
classified documents.
[AKANE]
Gah! What the hell?!
Was someone listening
to our conversation?!
This is super shady.
Do not respond to him!
It's gotta be a trap!
Did you not hear
a word I just said?!
[AKANE]
A lecturer's access pass?
[MIDORI] Does he mean
we should steal one?
[AKANE]
Terrible idea.
[MIDORI]
Excuse me, is anyone here?
[AKANE]
There. That's it!
[UNDINE]
Is someone in here?
There you go.
Oh! It's you guys!
What's goin' on?
Uh, well, you know,
nothing much.
Actually, Midori has
something to ask you.
Wait what are you--?
I mean, yeah I do.
Oh!
You remember that thing
I posted on Friend Log
about the cucumber cheesecake
that you excellented earlier?
Here, I brought you some!
[UNDINE gasps]
That's the
limited-edition flavor
you have to wait in line
for hours to buy, right?
Yeah!
[MIDORI] And I've been looking
forward to eating it all day.
[UNDINE]
Wah! This is amazing!
Thank you so much!
[laughing]
[MIDORI]
I feel bad tricking her.
But we'll put it back real fast.
[SYSTEM VOICE]
Access granted.
[AKANE]
This is it!
[MIDORI]
All right!
Hm? Why would all these
pages about Blue Christmas
pop up when I'm only
searching for Aoto's name?
That was the incident at
the shopping mall, right?
Remember, there was
that big fire at Christmas
like two years ago,
and a lot of people
got trapped and died?
No accident. But then...
[SYSTEM VOICE] "Blue Christmas"
files have been accessed.
Authorization level three,
Lecturer Undine.
A teacher from the Academy?
[LOKI]
What is the matter?
Must be a real emergency.
You never call me yourself.
[PAVLOV] The researcher
has disappeared from the lab.
He left no clues to
his current whereabouts.
[LOKI]
Schrödinger, huh?
Well, that is quite a problem.
[MIDORI]
Here's the incident report.
That night two years ago,
it says a pair of murderers
killed 666 innocent people.
And the suspects
are still at large. Wow.
So then why was it
called an accident?
[AKANE] The World Council
must have decided
that it was best to cover up
the truth for some reason.
[MIDORI] A girl named Ruri
was the only survivor.
She testified that one of
the murderers was a blonde boy
who used a blade
made out of water
to kill a man
right in front of her.
Whoa.
No... Aoto?
[MIDORI] It looks like he was
investigated as a suspect,
but there wasn't evidence
to actually convict him
of the crimes.
[AKANE] He might've killed
his parents and caused
the Blue Christmas?
That's nuts!
[MIDORI] But if there
were two murderers,
then who was the other one?
[SYSTEM VOICE] Insufficient
authorization level.
Say what? I thought we
were at the highest level!
Then--
[AKANE]
What the--?!
[BREUNOR]
Who do we have here?
Why am I not surprised it's
Aoto's friends causing trouble?
You must be looking up
something pretty important
to have stolen an access pass.
It's a kid.
[BREUNOR]
Hey!
Breunor from Arthur's squad.
The secret military agency
known as the Knights of Round.
[BREUNOR] You're trying to
find the truth, aren't you?
About the "Blue Christmas."
I'll tell you.
[SCHRÖDINGER]
You've been bad, Breunor.
I'm bringing this surveillance
Driver back home.
[phone chimes]
[SCHRÖDINGER] It's been two
long years since Blue Christmas.
[sighs]
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Do you still think of it, Aoto?
I do.
I remember it so vividly--
The night we met each other.
The moon was blue.
It was perfect.
[STAFF 4A] How old did you
say your son was?
[BREUNOR'S FATHER] He's about
to start middle school.
They grow up so fast,
don't they?
This'll probably be
his last gift from Santa.
[SCHRÖDINGER]
In that moment,
the world was cloaked
in the most brilliant hue.
[STAFF 4B]
Everyone, please remain calm.
It's probably just a blackout.
[AOTO]
This world is deeply flawed.
No one realizes
how pointless life is.
Um, Sir?
[screaming]
[WOMAN 4A screams]
[CROWD screaming]
There's so much noise.
But I have a solution.
The world would be
bearable in perfect silence!
[CROWD screaming]
[MAN 4A]
I can't get through the ice!
[WOMAN 4B] Let us out!
Please, I don't want to die!
[SCHRÖDINGER]
It was beautiful.
The world I'd
thought was so gray
finally had some color to it,
thanks to you.
[SCHRÖDINGER laughing]
Oh. Hello.
It appears you're on my side.
[SCHRÖDINGER groaning]
Trust in me.
We can make this
world beautiful again.
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Aoto...!
Everything you said
and did was perfect.
And in that moment...
...something changed.
I fell in love
for the first time.
[BREUNOR]
Two people were behind it.
Aoto was one of them.
I'm watching him to try
and track down the other guy.
The other murderer.
They'll pay!
I'll make sure of that!
They took everything from me.
Those bastards
murdered my father!
[BREUNOR'S FATHER
breathing shakily]
[RURI gasps]
Oh, look.
A little bunny rabbit
seems to think she can hide.
[BREUNOR'S FATHER]
Don't you touch her!
[MIDORI] But Aoto wasn't
arrested because there wasn't
any evidence he
was the murderer.
So?
I know he did it!
My father told me.
I was supposed to meet up
with him that day,
but when I finally got to
the mall, it was too late.
[BREUNOR]
No, Dad!
You're fine!
[BREUNOR'S FATHER]
Breunor...
This is for you.
Don't go. You can't.
Who would ever do this to you?
A boy.
With bright blue eyes.
Oh God, no!
C'mon, wake up!
[explosion]
[BREUNOR]
I managed to escape the blast
because Arthur saved me,
then I came to the Academy.
And now he's here, too.
Aoto, with the bright blue eyes,
blonde hair, and a water blade.
[AKANE]
Hold on a sec.
You're basing this
completely on his eye color?
[BREUNOR]
That's why I have to find proof.
And you're going to help me!
[AKANE] Why would I do
something stupid like that?
[MIDORI]
Okay!
He didn't do it, so this way
we can prove he's innocent.
And we can figure out
who's really to blame.
You're wrong, but okay.
I can track him down.
[BREUNOR] The surveillance
drones are gone?
Damn it! What's going on?
[MIDORI]
I can tell you where Aoto is.
Connected Friend Log members
can always tell
where each other are.
[AKANE]
Where's that?
Those are the ruins
from Blue Christmas!
Who are you?
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Long time no see, Aoto!
I've been looking forward
to this day for so long.
After Blue Christmas,
the Council captured me.
They kept me locked up
inside their lab.
But I never stopped
thinking about you, Aoto.
Do I know you?
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Something's different.
You're not as sure of yourself.
It's almost like you're
not the same person.
But I recognize those blue eyes.
[BREUNOR]
I found you!
[MIDORI]
Aoto. Are you all right?
[AOTO]
Yeah.
[AKANE] You've got a lot
of explaining to do later.
[SCHRÖDINGER] How impolite,
crashing our little tryst.
I recognize you.
Yeah, you're a Genius of Divine!
Schrödinger!
Wait, like Schrödinger's cat?
Is he the Blue Stray Cat
that messaged me?
If you're here...
...you know something!
And you're gonna
tell me everything!
Time for you two
to start talking!
Out with it!
Confess your sins!
I don't like
where this is going.
And who's this other guy?
One of the murderers?
[SCHRÖDINGER] You should know
better than to challenge
a Genius of Divine.
I'm always a few steps
ahead of everyone else.
And I came prepared.
Get it in gear, you two!
Deal with these
small fries for me!
They're after you.
C'mon, let's cover him!
Where is he?
You know where he's
been hiding out, don't you?
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Hm? I don't understand.
Who are you talking about?
The other Aoto who
you've mistaken me for.
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Hmm...
Ah. So that's why
you don't recognize me.
You're Aoto, it's true,
but you're not my Aoto.
[BREUNOR]
Talking time's over!
Watch out!
[BREUNOR]
What the hell is going on?
[SCHRÖDINGER]
You've got the same clear eyes.
But you're not
the one I'm longing for.
I guess the first love
really is hopeless, isn't it?
Where is he?
Aoto...
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Since you're here, imposter,
I'll give you the present
I was going to give my Aoto.
A glorious testament
to my devotion!
[SCHRÖDINGER]
Samidare!
It's time to wake up,
my darling.
Demonstrate your power
by killing them all!
[BREUNOR yells]
Man, we gotta
stop that thing...
[NARRATOR] When he fell
in love for the first time,
the man gave up his boring
life to devote himself
completely to someone else.
As his obsession grew stronger,
a doll was made to stand in
for the object of his affection.
But when he realized that
his first love was hopeless,
suddenly a new,
untroubled love was born.
Right in front of him.
It had been there all along.
[AKANE yells]
[SCHRÖDINGER]
That was wonderful.
Wait! Don't go!
You can't just leave without
telling me where he is!
[SCHRÖDINGER] I'm positive
I'll see you again, other Aoto.
Goodbye for now.
Damn!
There's no way
we'll catch him now.
[BREUNOR]
Who were you trying to find?
I need you to
tell me what you know
about the Blue
Christmas incident.
It was me. I did it.
[BREUNOR]
Don't lie to me, idiot.
One day soon you're gonna
tell me everything you know.
So weird.
What are the odds
it still works?
[AKANE]
Huh? What even is this thing?
[MIDORI, AKANE yell]
Step away!
Hello.
What is your command, Master?
"Master"? What?
Does she mean me?
Yeah, I think so.
Looks like we got
a new teammate.
This would be the perfect
thing to post about, Aoto!
A picture of this
moment will make
for a great first entry
on your Friend Log!
[camera shutter clicks]
[MIDORI]
That looks awesome!
If you say so.
[phone chimes]
This is excellent!
[AKANE] Whoa, did I really
just catch you smiling?
[AOTO]
Uh, no.
[AKANE]
You totally did!
[AOTO]
No, I didn't.
[MIDORI] Ooh!
Are you embarrassed, Aoto?
[ARITON] So you finally made
some friends, big brother.
[ARTHUR] The most
important lessons in life
aren't always learned
on the battlefield.
[AKANE] But surely you have a
couple of things in your life
that you consider
special, don't you?
[GIRL] It's funny--happy
people always think that.