[NARRATOR]
The rain begins to fall...
...slowly, at first.
Low points in
the street fill up,
creating puddles.
But not everything holds water.
A broken heart, for instance,
can't be filled.
Droplets stream down
the boy's face like tears.
It's almost funny, since
he never lets himself cry.
Not anymore.
These days, he tries not
to feel anything at all.
[CHILD laughing]
[NARRATOR]
The girl runs.
Faster than anyone,
racing through the present.
Searching for a past
that's been left behind.
She runs towards the holy Gate,
the Divine Gate.
[NARRATOR]
The boy who lights flames.
The red blazing fire.
It is the warmth he
has always felt close by
since he was little.
He believes it was
handed down to him
by his late father.
Oh my gosh, that episode.
Tell me you watched it.
[GIRL 1A]
Uh, yeah, of course I did.
[GIRL 1B]
It was so good!
[GIRL 1A]
I know!
[PASSENGERS chattering]
[PASSENGER 1A]
What's his problem?
[PASSENGERS gasp]
[MAN]
I can finally see it.
It's time to rebuild.
This whole world is crap!
I'll make a better one.
You'll see!
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[AKANE]
Huh?
What is that?
[MAN laughing]
Little girl...
You believe in the glory
of the Divine Gate, right?
[GIRL whimpering]
[MAN chuckling]
It was once upon a time,
that three worlds
merged into one.
Yes.
As a result, six
incredible abilities
were brought to our people.
Now, the Divine Gate
calls to those of us
who have faith--
Those of us who truly
deserve its powers.
Through the Gate,
all things are possible.
You've probably heard all this.
Maybe as an old bedtime story.
In fact...
I bet you used to fall asleep
dreaming that you'd wield
such magic yourself!
But you forgot about
the Gate, didn't you?
I didn't.
I'm one of the chosen few
worthy of its blessings!
[MAN]
Not so fast!
[GIRL screams]
The Gate is real! You'll see!
And I'm going to use its
power to change this world.
I will become God.
[GIRL 1C]
No! Don't!
Let me go!
[MAN] What the hell
are you looking at?!
[GIRL]
Please, help me!
I see.
You're an Adapter, too.
Mind your own business!
Like that'll stop me.
You're dead!
[MAN yells]
[GIRL screams]
Everyone freeze!
We're the World Council.
Who are you?
[OPERATOR]
Nontron in position.
Generating zone.
Um, we're doing this right now?
[OPERATOR]
Ready to move on.
'Kay, it's time
to start talkin'.
So what happened?
Hey, wait! You violated
Driver possession laws!
How so?
I don't even have a Driver.
Then how did you...?
[MIDORI]
Akane!
This guy's not doing so hot; we
need to get him help right away.
This quest is clear.
We have one suspect in custody;
he's in critical condition.
Please send medical
aid immediately.
[OPERATOR]
Roger that.
ron arrives.
This zone will be maintained
until the rescue
[AKANE]
Stop!
All this rain...
I should have known something
like this would happen.
[NARRATOR]
The rain doesn't fall forever.
Time is the only thing
that's unstoppable.
I've seen you before.
Why're you following me?
The Divine Gate is
almost within your reach,
but you refuse
to seek it out, Aoto.
You think it's
something intangible,
like emotion or
thought, don't you?
You weirdo.
[laughing]
[ANNOUNCER] Several people
were injured this morning
when a deranged man
used a Driver
to attack the passengers of
an inbound central line tramcar.
So far, no motive has been
uncovered for the assault.
Two students from the
World Council Academy
who happened to be
riding the tramcar
at the time of the incident
managed to apprehend
the attacker,
saving many innocent lives.
[CROWD clapping, cheering]
[AKANE]
Oh, thanks. It was nothing!
About the guy who got away...
Can't help wondering who he is.
[MIDORI]
Blue eyes?
They've got people
looking into him.
He's an Adapter, so I'm
sure we'll know soon enough.
[MIDORI]
Race you there!
[AKANE]
No fair! Midori!
He was a water-user.
Do you think it's possible
he didn't have a Driver?
I don't know.
All I could tell is he must
have been crying recently.
Huh? You think so?
Jeez, how do you
have so much stamina?
Don't you ever get tired of
running around all the time?
You're crazy!
[MIDORI]
It's my favorite thing!
I'd run in a
straight line forever,
all the way around the world
if I had the chance to.
The only problem
with running so fast
is that I'm afraid
I might miss something
one of these days.
[MIDORI laughs]
I'm the winner!
You know what would be
the best thing in the world?
If the Divine Gate would
suddenly appear right here
in front of me.
Not this again.
If you'd stop talking
about the Gate,
you'd have more friends.
So?
I've already got a best friend
who understands me. I'm cool.
[BOTH gasp]
I dunno, maybe you
should listen to him, bon.
[MIDORI]
Oh, hi.
[METABON gasps]
Hey pal, where
were you this morning?
Pets are supposed to be loyal!
Watch it or I won't
share my intel, bon.
Now, now.
No fighting.
So, what's the scoop, Metabon?
You ready for this?
According to
surveillance cameras,
this morning's incident was
caused by the fire user, bon.
Fortunately, the water-user
managed to take him down, bon.
[MIDORI]
Interesting... [gasps]
Wow...
Man...
We gotta figure out
who this guy is.
He's got the look of a
cold-blooded killer to me.
You really think so?
It still seems to me
like the poor boy's
about to burst into tears.
Or maybe he looks like that
because he's able
to see the Divine Gate.
Would you please shut up
about that fairytale?
Your wish-granting
magical Gate doesn't exist,
so enough already!
Come on!
Aw! You secretly
believe in it, too!
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm not some stupid kid, okay?
Please. If you don't
believe in the Gate,
then why're you here?
Lemme guess...
It's 'cause you wanna
use the Driver's power.
Or maybe become a hero.
Or both.
[AKANE]
Well, I dunno.
You believe! Told ya!
Sure, ya got me.
[TRISTAN] We have information
regarding the incident
on the tram.
It seems the attacker
came to Terrastia
for a contract job
two years ago.
He's a demon and an Adapter.
How is he doing?
He's severely injured,
but stabilized.
He'll live.
Maybe he couldn't adapt
to the environment here
and it drove him mad.
Actually, we suspect
that he might be suffering
from some form of
psychotic disorder.
Ugh! I hate dealing with
beings from Hellistia.
Those guys are the worst.
[YWAIN] You can't stereotype
an entire world like that.
There are good and evil
humans here on Terrastia.
It's the same thing
for the demons.
And for the fairies, too.
We all have the capacity
to be villains or heroes.
Well, you are
a perfect example
of a totally psychotic human,
so I guess you're right.
What'd you just say?!
Whatever his home world,
we'll punish him the way we
would punish a human criminal.
You got it, boss.
And...?
What about the boy
who was there?
He left the crime scene
before anyone
could talk to him.
I see.
I'd like to have a chat
with him and hear his side.
Then I'll make sure
that that happens.
[LANCELOT] You've taken some
kinda special interest
in this water-using boy,
haven't you, Arthur?
[ARTHUR]
Perhaps.
But with good reason.
It's the same attention I'd
give anyone with his abilities.
[LANCELOT]
Yeah, but you don't know--
[ARTHUR] If he's as
powerful as he seems,
then I will have him
attend our Academy.
That way he won't be a problem.
Something about him
rubs me the wrong way.
Well...
I certainly understand
your reservations.
But you'll have
to trust me on this.
Oh, don't worry.
I know what my place is.
Good. Thank you.
[BOY 1A]
So gross!
[BOY 1B]
Mackerel ramen?
Sounds disgusting.
[BOY 1A] And did you see
him put ice in there, too?
[GIRL 1E] He's got the
strangest eating habits.
[BOY 1B]
Cold, watered-down soup.
Well... He did kill his parents.
He's a psycho. For real.
You mean...
All of the rumors
about him are true?
My parents definitely
think he did it.
Apparently he was
neglected as a child
and went through some seriously
messed up stuff growing up.
[BOY 1B]
For real?
[GIRL 1D]
No way.
If he killed his parents,
then how come he's free
to walk around and go to school?
[NARRATOR] I wish the rain
would fall even harder.
Swallowing everything.
Like a muddy stream.
But even then, a rain
cannot put out a fire.
[BOY 1A] All right,
that's enough for today.
--[BOY 1B] Let's go!
--[GIRL 1B] Hold on!
[AKANE]
Special Advisor.
You called for us, ma'am?
[AKANE yells]
Didn't I tell you never
to call me "ma'am"?
[AKANE] Ugh!
You could've killed me!
[EFREET] I had faith that
you'd dodge the attack.
That's the reason we left the
Heaven World in the first place,
or do you not remember our oath?
It's our duty as Adapters
to use our abilities
to maintain peace
for the greater good.
[AKANE yells]
[EFREET]
Are you being sarcastic?!
So, Master.
What did you want
to talk to us about?
This morning's tram incident.
Or have you foiled
more crimes since then?
We've already heard
the news reports about it.
Agh!
[EFREET] Then this should
be a fairly quick meeting.
We want you to find the
water-user and recruit him
into the Academy.
[MIDORI]
Huh?
You want us to make
him part of our team?
You gotta be kidding.
We're always looking
to recruit more people
with abilities!
[EFREET] I'm told that Arthur
has offered him a place
at the Academy
several times already,
but the boy has
refused him each time.
[MIDORI]
Hmm... I wonder why.
[SYLPH] I dunno, but for a
human with that much power,
the safest place
for him to be is here.
There're probably
plenty of other people
who want to get their
hands on this kid.
So we're leaving it to
you two to persuade him.
Fail and you'll disappoint
everyone at the Academy,
the entire World Council.
[AKANE]
Huh?!
[EFREET] But you're not
the only one on this job.
They sent the water fairy, and
she's got a head start on you.
Darn. Really?
Don't worry. We've got this.
I can be super
persuasive, you know.
[SYLPH laughs]
Now that's the spirit!
Oh, I guess you
should know his name.
It's Aoto?
I feel like I've
heard that name before.
I'm sure you have.
It was all over the
news four years ago
when his parents
were found dead,
seeing as the media
called him the killer.
[AOTO]
Why are you here again?
Oh, you know.
Arthur told me to
talk you into joining us.
But really, I'm here on my own.
I guess I like being
around you or something.
[AOTO]
Another example of my bad luck.
What's so great
about the regular school
you're in now, huh?
At the Academy,
all your classmates
would be Adapters
just like you are.
You'd probably fit in
a little bit better.
I've already turned Arthur down.
I don't know why he thinks
you'll change my mind.
[UNDINE] He says we need your
power to maintain world peace,
but if I'm being honest,
I think you're the one
who needs our help.
Come on, Aoto.
Join the Academy.
And use it as a chance
to finally put the past
far behind you.
[ARTHUR]
Long time no see, Aoto.
Thank you for coming.
[AOTO] Figured I didn't
have much of a choice
when I heard that you
wanted to talk about
this morning's attack.
You know your duty.
[AOTO]
Are you going to arrest me?
Of course not.
Why would I? You could've killed
that criminal for all I care.
He deserved it.
That's not who I am.
I don't have that kind of power.
You're a terrible
liar, aren't you?
Well, anyway...
I have something for you.
Go on, don't be afraid.
Take it.
[ARTHUR] It's a Driver
created just for you.
Regardless of
what you might think,
your abilities can attract
the attention of other people
with strong powers.
Believe me.
Without Drivers,
we gifted humans
are no match for Hellistia's
monstrous demons,
or even the mighty
fairies of Celestia.
[AOTO]
Whatever you say.
But I don't want
this thing, so...
I'll see myself out.
[ARTHUR]
Here is my offer.
The truth.
I'll never lie to you, Aoto.
[ARTHUR] Let me know when
you're ready to face reality.
Until then, I'll be
here waiting for you.
Hey, there he is!
[AKANE]
Yo!
Hey, sorry about this morning.
Me, too.
It was a misunderstanding.
Sure.
[MIDORI]
Anyway, since you're here,
would you like a tour of
the Academy or something?
All the people here are Adapters
who can wield
special powers, like us.
And why should I care?
Oh! Well, uh--
Listen, we were
told to recruit you,
so why not make it easy on us?
Would you shut up?
What? There's no point
keeping it a secret.
Moving on...
There really are a ton of
great reasons to come here.
You would get the chance
to hone your ability.
What would you do
with my power?
You'd use me.
Sorry.
[MIDORI] We can reach
the Divine Gate together!
Our wishes will be granted!
I told you to
cut that stuff out.
You can see
the Gate, can't you?
I'm right, aren't I?
You can!
Even if I could...
I don't have any
wishes to ask for.
Well, I guess we can't
force you to join,
but you should know that we're
serious about what we do!
We're keeping the peace!
Remember that.
Oh. Also...
I don't like secrets, so
I'll go ahead and tell you.
I know what everyone
says about you.
That you killed your parents.
But I don't believe the rumors.
What's important to me
is that you do what--
Save your breath.
I did kill them.
It was my fault.
Come back to mock me some more?
You're a giant liar,
but then again, you're not.
You could've killed them,
but you chose not to.
You act like you feel
nothing, but you do.
Rain won't fall forever,
but after that day,
you refused to let the sun
shine on your heart ever again.
You can't even eat warm food
because everything
they gave you was cold.
Just like their hearts
were to you.
You don't even know who
you really are anymore.
You've begun to believe
all your own lies.
[AOTO]
Who are you?
[K] Just someone who's
been watching all this time.
[AOTO'S MOTHER] You make
Mommy so proud, darling.
[AOTO'S FATHER]
She's not alone.
Because of your ability,
I'm happy to be your father.
Please. Just shut up.
Sorry, Son.
Yes.
We're just so happy
you're our son.
Oh! I know.
Let's go buy that new game
you want next Sunday.
Just the three of us.
We'll make a whole day of it.
How does that sound?
Good idea.
I say we do it. Yeah?
[MOTHER, FATHER laughing]
[AOTO'S MOTHER]
How wonderful.
[laughing continues]
[DOG growling]
[DOG barking]
[ARITON] You've always been
a mystery to me, big brother.
You want to hate them,
but you can't do it.
You want to kill them,
but you refuse to.
I know everything about you.
I've seen the true
color of your heart.
It's blue.
Frozen and shattered,
big brother.
Deep down inside,
you're as cold as ice is.
[ARITON] I could end all your
suffering if I really wanted to,
but I honestly don't care.
You're crying on
the inside, always.
[ARTHUR] The holy Gate
has finally opened.
Time to see what's
on the other side.
[AOTO]
Trust me on this.
As a kid, I learned
you can't always act
on the things you want to.
[ARTHUR] You go by the
name of Santa Clause.
And yet you show up
with presents
even when it's not
the holiday season.
[AKANE] Even if you're in pain,
don't let it control you.