[LOKI] You seem determined
to go, no matter what.
[ARTHUR]
Yes.
At this point, a god
could stand in my way,
and I wouldn't even blink.
Such commitment.
You must have a
really good reason.
After all, only a fool would
dare to challenge a god.
You know I hate it when
you beat around the bush
like this.
Loki, don't tell me you're
going to try and stop me.
You're the one who's avoiding
the real subject here, Arthur.
Let's talk about
what's really at stake.
If you do reach the Divine Gate,
what is it you are actually
going to wish for?
[inaudible]
My Knights.
Let us begin our quest!
[NARRATOR]
Some time ago,
a holy portal known as
the Divine Gate opened,
and in an instant merged three
different worlds into one.
Now, an ambitious king
heads toward the place
where it all began
to do whatever he must
to bring order back to life.
[ARTHUR] There's one thing
I want to say to everyone
before we get started.
I don't care what troubles
may lie ahead of us.
I will finish this mission.
Once I reach that holy place,
I'm going to destroy
the Divine Gate.
He wants to destroy it?
What does that mean?
[ARTHUR] The Gate is the
cause of all our problems.
It brought chaos to our lives
when the three planes merged,
creating a world that's
understood only by
a few elite leaders.
They cover up
our city's dirty secrets.
The peace they maintain
is nothing but an illusion.
That's why I've decided
to return the world
to its original state,
the way it was before
everything changed.
[chiming noise]
[OPERATOR 1A]
The Nontron is in position.
Now preparing to
open the Divine Gate.
[OPERATOR 1A]
Ready to move on!
Is that...?
Where are we?
This path will
lead us to the Gate.
We still have quite
the journey ahead of us.
So the Gate is
inside the zone?
[BREUNOR]
You've got it all twisted.
The zone was just a byproduct
of the research we did
to find the Gate
in the first place.
[GINJI]
It's huge.
Is that the Divine Gate?
Strange.
You think?
Calm down.
We're still a good ways
from our destination.
Yes.
We'll pass through many
Gates before we reach it.
On guard.
For what?
Weapons out!
They're autonomous Drivers!
But how?
Loki. This has
your name all over it.
[LOKI] There's nothing more
boring than an easy quest.
At least, for those
of us watching.
Now, let's dance.
Hold on!
Those are gods.
[OZ]
Arthur...
You have no one but yourself
to blame for this mess.
[NARRATOR]
The gods watch over the world
from a high place of power,
rarely descending
to the dirty streets
where lowly humans dwell.
Sometimes they test them,
but they never help them.
Humans have no choice
but to endure their whims.
Ha! So this is the trouble
you were talking about.
Scandinavian gods, huh?
Huh... What do ya say; do you
think we can beat 'em or what?
No, of course not; they're gods.
But we can certainly fight them
and buy Arthur some time.
Yeah, we'll distract them so
Daddy can go after the big Gate!
That's the spirit.
This mission isn't over yet.
[BREUNOR]
Gods or not,
we're gonna take you
floating losers down!
[LANCELOT]
Go.
Are you sure?
We don't have the
time to stand around
and try to think
of another plan now.
Just go.
We've got this.
I want you six
to come with me.
Uh, right.
Okay, let's take them down!
[LOKI] Don't try to pin
this new obstacle on me.
I wasn't the one who
summoned the Scandinavians.
[AKANE]
What's going on, Arthur?
Are the knights seriously
gonna fight gods?
They're providing
a diversion for us.
But why are the
gods even here?
Against those guys,
even the Knights of Round
don't stand a chance.
They knew the path
to the Divine Gate
would be a dangerous one.
They're making an
honorable sacrifice.
[GINJI] So you're just
throwing them to the dogs?
[yelling]
Ginji!
[SURTR] Did you think
you could get away?
Let's go!
[GAWAIN]
Stop being mean to my daddy!
[GAWAIN gasps]
[PALOMIDES]
Gawain!
Palomides, get over here!
You have to make it, boss.
Do it for us.
No, wait!
Let's see who's the strongest:
You or me.
I'm so sorry.
I broke the treasure
you gave me.
Forgive me, Daddy.
Gawy...
[ARTHUR]
We need to keep moving.
We will honor the fallen.
We won't let them die in vain.
[NARRATOR] Every one of the
Knights was prepared to die
for their mission.
They sacrificed their futures
in order to serve at his side.
They were willing to
give up everything for him.
This is bad! We're
getting creamed out here.
Yeah, but I'm not going down
till I manage to land a hit
on one of those gods.
Look out!
[ALL scream]
I didn't think we'd go out
like this, my friend.
How lame.
Hey. Wake up, man.
I can't... do this alone.
[KAY]
This really blows.
Why don't you just run back home
and make us some soup, old man?
[GARETH] It's an honor
for a man of my years
to die protecting the young.
Now, brace yourself.
Insect. That's enough.
[BREUNOR yelling]
Let go.
Otherwise we're
both gonna fall.
Just take care
of the boss for me.
Breunor, no!
[HERVOR]
What pitiful creatures.
Did you think you could win?
We humans might
surprise you.
And we're nowhere
near finished yet.
Why are you trying
to stand in our way?!
That Gate isn't
something the humans
should be able to get to easily.
Besides, a friend of yours
told us to protect it
and keep you from reaching it.
[LANCELOT yells]
They're crazy.
Why don't they retreat?
Why would they try to
fight against the gods?!
I never meant
for this to happen!
[ARTHUR]
That's enough of that!
Say what?
Just who do you think you are?
[ARTHUR]
I'm a king.
[ARTHUR] Another subject
bows to his leader.
You tryin' to make
a fool outta me?
[ARTHUR]
Consider the natural order.
People rely on kings,
and kings rely on gods.
Just as subjects might mutiny
against their monarch,
a king can rebel
against a god and win.
I will kill a god
and become king.
Eventually my subjects
will revolt.
And you will take up
arms against me.
[chuckles]
I hate people like you...
...who never know
when to shut up.
If that's what you want,
I'd be happy to
kill you right now.
I still have much work to do.
But I promise I won't let
anyone else kill me, only you.
No, I can't die yet.
Not before I've gotten the
chance to kill King Arthur.
[ARTHUR]
Tris!
Where are the others?
[TRISTAN]
I'm not sure.
They're probably dead.
Please, Boss.
Make it to the Gate.
I promise.
[ARTHUR]
Tris!
Why do this?
All of your Knights...
How can you sacrifice so many
people's lives like this?
The terrible weight
of this decision
is mine to bear for
as long as I live.
However...
It was all necessary.
But Arthur...
You must really wish
to change the world
if you were willing
to go this far.
[ARTHUR]
Let's continue.
To bring glory to everyone
who entrusted their
lives to my hands.
I refuse to let
them die in vain!
[NARRATOR]
Hearing this,
they understood the king's
commitment to his mission.
They realized he would
push on no matter what,
even when pain threatened
to overwhelm him.
It looks like
we're finally ready
to test this Replica out.
[LOKI chuckles]
You're going to need a trump
card up your sleeve, Arthur.
What the hell is going on?
It's hard to move!
Almost there.
The Divine Gate
is just up ahead.
[NARRATOR]
The king presses forward,
fighting against the weight
pushing down on him.
One final test
for a human to face
before he's able to
touch the power of a god.
Kay. Gareth.
Percival. Ywain.
Lamorak. Mordred. Bedivere.
Palomides.
Gawain.
And Tristan.
[BREUNOR]
Hey...
Breunor, you look
pretty pathetic.
Didn't think you'd
let them hurt you.
[BREUNOR] Honestly, I don't
even feel the pain anymore.
Man, I can't believe yours is
the last face that I'll see.
You can rest now.
Good work.
Everyone did a fine job
of buying him time.
[LANCELOT]
All right, you bastards.
Who wants to go first?
[SURTR] As much as I'd like
to play around with you
a little more, our
covenant ends right here.
[LANCELOT]
Ha! Is that so?
Is it because our
leader actually managed
to reach the Divine Gate?
I guess that means we beat you.
Don't be a fool.
It's not the Gate
that we were protecting.
You really are just
a clueless animal.
Wait, what?!
[SIGURD laughing]
This is it...
At last, the Divine Gate!
What was that thing?
[ARTHUR]
Why is this Replica here?
[ARTHUR grunting]
[ARTHUR yelling]
\I'm the only one who
should walk the path
they opened.
[ARTHUR]
You shouldn't be here.
They died for me!
It's no good!
Don't stop trying yet!
[AKANE]
Dammit.
[LANCELOT]
Hey.
What the hell's this
ruckus about, kids?
[LOKI] Did you have fun
with the Replica Burst?
It was a special
present for you.
Loki.
I should have realized
you secretly had
the Geniuses of Divine
working on your side.
[LOKI]
You've truly surprised me.
I didn't think you'd pay such a
hefty price to destroy the Gate.
You were so close, too.
But you're finished now.
You don't even have the
strength left to wield a sword,
much less fight me.
I'm afraid that means I win.
For my final proposition,
I'll give you two options.
The first is obvious;
you can die right here.
Or, you can take this sword,
and I'll let you live.
As my personal slave-king.
So what'll it be, Arthur?
Sorry, but I refuse to be
manipulated by you anymore.
Oh, of course you'd say that.
You never have
been afraid of death.
Still, I hoped you'd see reason.
[LOKI] Well, I guess this
is where we say goodbye.
I'll have to replace you
with a different king.
What a pain.
[ARTHUR] I'm not going to let
you have the last laugh, Loki.
So Arthur's just on the
other side of the Gate, right?
Yeah. Hopefully.
Don't worry about him.
He's not the type to die easily.
Told ya.
Are you okay, Arthur?
[LANCELOT]
Good to see ya.
There. You've finally
become my king...
...Arthur.
I should have killed you...
Back in the street--
[MIDORI]
No! Lancelot!
What the--?
[AKANE]
It's closing!
This whole place...
It's falling apart!
[ALL yelling]
[SHAKESPEARE] Do you have
something entertaining
planned for me?
[LOKI]
Oh, I never disappoint.
You're going to love the
disaster I've put into motion.
[SANTA CLAUSE]
I know that it's a lot to ask,
but will you please help me?
[GINJI] I swear you idiots
have gone completely insane.