[NARRATOR]
A long time ago,
an arrogant human
built a tower so tall
that it punctured the sky,
reaching the place
where the gods resided.
The gods were appalled
by this demonstration,
and they doled out
a vicious punishment
to remind all humans
of their inferiority.
Now, another human has reached
the gods' hallowed territory,
fighting his way
to the Divine Gate.
But this man is different.
He's punished himself.
Despite his attempts to
resist a god's mischief,
this man, once known
as the Holy King,
succumbed to darkness in front
of that most sacred of Gates.
Why hello there, Arthur.
I see you still have a bit
of consciousness left.
Loki... What've you done to me?
What is this place
I'm trapped in?
[LOKI]
You sound so angry.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
everything I've done for you.
[ARTHUR]
You really are a monster.
[LOKI] It's such fun
to watch humans get angry
when they realize
they're not in control.
[chuckles]
I'll visit you again soon.
[LOKI] Don't look so sad,
my darling little puppet.
I did make you
a king, after all.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The following
is an announcement from
the World Council.
Due to issues stemming
from yesterday's
large-scale system error,
a special curfew has
been put into place.
Please stay indoors after 8 pm.
In addition,
certain city sections
are completely off limits.
These rules are in effect
until further notice.
Thank you in advance
for your cooperation.
Your safety is
our highest concern.
[SAINT A (DANTE)]
You will answer my question!
Yes, sir!
Um... Like I said before, uh...
It seemed like Arthur was
planning some kind of coup
to make himself our ruler.
I was just trying to do
what was best for the Council;
to stop him by
any means necessary.
[SAINT A (DANTE)] So Arthur
was secretly planning to destroy
the Divine Gate
once he reached it?
[OZ]
Exactly!
[SAINT C (JOHANN)]
And to keep him from doing so,
you took it upon
yourself to summon
the Scandinavian gods
for assistance?
[OZ]
That's right.
I figured it was
our only option.
[SAINT B (AEGIS)]
You don't have the authority
to make that decision.
[OZ]
But Loki...
He made it sound like...
[SAINT A (DANTE)]
Where is Loki?
Why doesn't he
speak for himself?
[OZ]
I have no idea!
[LOKI]
So sorry to keep you waiting.
[OZ]
Loki?
[LOKI] It's an honor to stand
before the Six Saints.
I come with news about
the conspirator Arthur
and his personal army,
the Knights of Round.
You'll be happy to know
that all of them are dead.
[LOKI] Those Saints like to
argue because it makes them
feel important.
They never act on anything.
Hey...
There's no way you were telling
the truth back there, right?
[LOKI] You're going to have
to be a little more specific.
Come on!
About Arthur and the Knights
of Round all being dead--
That must've been a lie!
[LOKI]
Oh, I see.
Tell me, what are you
hoping I'll say right now?
[OZ]
Dammit, would you be serious?!
[LOKI] The truth won't
make you happy.
You and I have
both conspired against
the Six Saints.
We've taken the
first step together.
That means we share
the same fate now.
So I don't understand
why you're acting like
some kind of insolent brat.
You're going to have to
learn to steel yourself, Oz.
All I want is
to know the truth
about what happened to them.
Come on, tell me
they're still alive!
Loki, some of them were
just kids from the Academy.
[LOKI] All killed by the
Scandinavian gods you unleashed.
Every last one of them struck
down with extreme prejudice.
Beneath these white gloves,
your hands are
stained red with blood.
Don't pretend like you didn't
know what was happening.
You are not innocent.
Hey.
I was wondering when you'd show.
[YUKARI]
Why are you three late?
[UNDINE] Just making sure
we weren't followed.
I'm so glad to see
that you're okay!
[SYLPH]
Midori, you're choking me!
Akane was really worried
about you, too, bon.
Shut up!
So what do things look
like in the outside world?
Well, I'm afraid
it's not good news.
The Council's trying
to track you down.
Nothing's being reported
in the news, though;
not the tower,
or the expedition,
or anything like that.
[MIDORI] They're ignoring it
and pretending it didn't happen.
Just like the
Blue Christmas stuff.
It definitely sounds
like we can't trust
the World Council anymore.
On the bright side,
we brought the medicine
and other supplies
you asked for.
[MIDORI]
Awesome!
We used up the last
of our bandages
right before you got here.
[UNDINE] Hikari,
how's your leg healing up?
Pretty good; I'll be fine!
It looks really painful.
[sighs]
We need to get going.
Really? Already?
The Council might get suspicious
if we're gone for too long.
You've got a good point.
Thank you so much!
Be safe out there.
[SYLPH]
We'll come back soon, okay?
[GINJI]
Great. So what do we do now?
Any ideas, Santa?
Well... Probably
not a good idea
to go running back
to the World Council
if we're not certain
what their plans are.
Just think of how
this must look to them.
They'll think of Arthur
as the bad guy,
and honestly, I would agree.
I mean, he killed Lancelot right
in front of you for no reason.
In cold blood.
Yeah, he did.
But it was weird...
Arthur didn't really
seem like himself
after he reached the Gate.
Blame the god.
Loki was standing
right behind him.
At this point,
we're all in the dark.
There's no way to know
what happened at the Gate.
And I suppose
that probably means
you don't trust me, either.
[YUKARI]
We don't.
But if Santa hadn't
come to save us,
I don't think we ever
would've made it outta there.
[HIKARI screaming]
[YUKARI]
Hikari!
[YUKARI] We can't
keep this up much longer.
[HIKARI]
Don't worry about me.
Just save yourselves!
[YUKARI, HIKARI, GINJI yell]
[GINJI]
Who are you?
They call me
the children's ally.
There it is!
[GINJI]
Now, don't get me wrong,
I appreciate you showing up
right in the nick of time.
But why were you there
in the first place?
[SANTA CLAUSE] Because I
made a promise to Arthur
a long time ago.
Made it just in time! Heh!
Hey, guys! Hurry!
You're gonna miss it!
And then you'll be sorry!
[SANTA CLAUSE]
Man, you're impatient today.
[ELISABETH] What's so urgent
this early in the morning?
[ARTHUR]
See for yourselves.
Isn't this view amazing?
[ELISABETH gasps]
It's beautiful.
[SANTA CLAUSE]
Yeah.
Wonderful news,
my Geniuses of Divine.
The prologue has now
come to a conclusion.
It's finally time to
move on to the main event.
Let's begin the
Twilight Judgment.
Oh, and I thought you
might like to know...
I'm going to have your son
join our little play, as well.
Now, then...
I'd like to introduce you
to our show's brilliant writer.
Ta-da!
[SHAKESPEARE]
Surprise!
[LOKI]
Ah! Hello, hello.
It's been too long since I've
had the pleasure, Shakespeare.
Do you have something
entertaining planned for me?
Oh, I never disappoint.
You're gonna love the disaster
I've put into motion.
Great! Tell me
how the story goes!
[LOKI laughs]
Yes, why wait?
You get out your Divine Pen,
and together
we'll write a tragedy.
[SHAKESPEARE]
Okay!
Hey, Oz?
is something bothering you?
I think I may have
gotten some children
from the Academy killed.
They were so young,
probably around your age.
[DOROTHY]
Midori?
[SANTA CLAUSE] On that
fateful Christmas night...
I saw the blue moon
shining overhead.
Wait, you mean
the Blue Christmas?
The Council covered it up;
they never told Arthur the truth
about what happened there
and decided to keep everything
a big secret.
That's how they operate.
The truth about
your father's death.
Your old friend's whereabouts.
The Council has answers.
They're keeping things from
each and every one of you.
[HIKARI]
How is that possible?
[GINJI]
What're you talking about?
[AKANE]
Hold on a sec.
What secret is there about
my father's death, huh?
[MIDORI] Do you know
where my friend is?
I thought she'd be
waiting for me at the Gate.
Sorry, I don't have that info.
The Council has managed
to hide it all, even from me.
You can blame Loki for that.
[GINJI]
Loki?
[inaudible]
[SANTA CLAUSE] After the
Blue Christmas tragedy,
I started following
Loki's movements.
He controls the World
Council thanks to the help
of a group of
researchers and scientists
called the Geniuses of Divine.
[HIKARI] This sounds like some
kind of crazy conspiracy theory.
[YUKARI]
If your story is true,
then what does Loki
stand to gain
from everything
that's happened?
[SANTA CLAUSE] He probably
wants to harness the power
of the Divine Gate.
With it, he'd be able to
build a new world from scratch.
Why would he do that if he's
got so much power already?
I think that's just
the kind of person he is.
He likes watching
people struggle,
and finds entertainment in
humans trying to survive.
[GINJI gasps]
I see. So that's why he
stopped Arthur's operation.
Spot on.
I warned Arthur that Loki was
planning to do something.
That's one of the reasons
he tried to destroy the Gate--
To protect the world
from any more chaos.
I knew he'd try to
do something extreme,
but I never thought...
he'd do that.
What're you going
to do now, Santa?
[SANTA CLAUSE] Whoever reaches
the Gate will have the power
to determine the future
of the entire world.
I'm going to save Arthur.
I know that it's a lot to ask,
but will you please help me?
You're not seriously
asking if we'll go
to the Gate again.
Yeah, that would be suicide.
And why us, anyway?
Because Arthur chose
all of you for a reason.
[K] You spend so much time
in your own head.
And yet, you never
decide on anything.
I'll ask you again.
Is it the past you want to
change, or the future, now?
Maybe neither.
I just don't know.
[K] You're slowly
getting closer, Aoto.
You're discovering your heart.
[GINJI]
Hey, man.
We need to talk.
[door opens]
Okay, so what's up?
[GINJI] We've decided we're
going back to the World Council.
[ALL gasp]
I don't want to be in hiding
for the rest of my life.
And there's no way we can help
the situation from here.
But it's too
dangerous to go back.
Did you forget Loki
tried to kill us?!
[GINJI] True, but we're
still alive, aren't we?
Maybe Arthur was really
in the wrong this time.
You're just gonna turn
your back on Santa Clause
after he saved us?
[GINJI] You're forgetting
that he could be lying to us,
for all we know.
Will the Council
welcome you back?
In their eyes,
we're all traitors
as Arthur's accomplices.
They know that we're students.
We can't be blamed
for following orders.
We hardly even knew
what Arthur wanted to do.
Yeah, that's right.
We got mixed up
in this by accident.
In a way, we're the victims.
So then, you don't think
we'll get in trouble?
Nobody really knows the truth
about what happened at the Gate.
And it's not like we can
get any answers while hiding.
He's right.
Let's all go back
to the Council.
I agree.
You with us?
[AKANE]
There is another option.
[GINJI]
Huh?
We can go to the
Divine Gate again.
Oh yeah!
No way!
Did you not see
what happened to Arthur
and the Knights of Round there?
[AKANE] Yeah, but I'm
still gonna go back.
Arthur was determined
to protect this world
no matter what.
The Knights of Round
gave up their lives
to make sure that his
mission was successful.
I'd much rather see his version
of the world than Loki's.
Hands down.
And I wanna know the truth
about my dad's death!
[MIDORI]
I'm with him.
I've got a friend waiting
on the other side of the Gate.
And I'm not going
to abandon her.
Please don't be
blinded by your emotions.
I swear, you idiots have
gone completely insane.
So Aoto, do you agree
with these two?
Yeah, I do.
I want answers, too.
I need to know what
happened that day.
[inaudible]
Fine, do whatever you want.
But when everything goes bad,
don't forget that
you could've joined us.
This means we might not
be seeing each other again.
Take care of yourselves.
I'm sorry.
You guys be careful.
This isn't right!
[YUKARI]
Don't worry.
We won't tell them that
we know where you're hiding.
[LOKI] Yukari and Hikari both
said they don't know anything
about the others.
But you'll level
with me, right, Ginji?
I know it's hard,
but think of it this way.
Now that martial law
has been imposed,
they're bound to be spotted.
If you talk to me, though,
we can capture them all safely
so that none of them
wind up getting hurt.
I don't like what
you're implying, Loki.
[LOKI] Sorry, I have a weakness
for thinly veiled threats.
What's going on?
Stop! We haven't
done anything wrong!
Impossible... This is
where the hideout was!
[MIDORI]
You replaced their memories?
[SANTA CLAUSE] Sort of, but
it's really not that impressive.
It comes with being Santa.
But it is a useful skill
if a kid ever sees me.
Holy crap.
So this means that one of those
backstabbers betrayed us!
Looks that way.
But who knows what
the Council did to them.
Looks like Santa Clause
pulled a fast one
and scrambled your brains.
What now?
I bet you're pretty angry.
I know how we can find them.
[alarm sounding]
I wonder what's going on.
[GINJI]
Hey! Bad news.
It looks like the Council's
discovered Santa's hideout.
[EFREET, UNDINE, SYLPH]
What?
[GINJI] They're about to
dispatch a raid team.
We have to warn everyone
while there's still time
or else they're toast!
We'll head out now!
[EFREET] Quick!
You have to get out!
Master!
Why, is something happening?
[SYLPH] The Council is
on their way here right now!
They can't be;
that's impossible!
[UNDINE]
But Ginji told us so!
[MIDORI]
Something's up.
[SANTA CLAUSE] Looks like
we fell into his trap.
[OPERATOR 1A]
Zone generation complete.
The building's perimeter
is surrounded
by autonomous Drivers.
Fire when ready.
There's nowhere to run.
Can you hear me?
Give up and come on out already!
Don't fight this
or you could get hurt!
I know you didn't
agree with me,
but if you stay in there,
they'll have no choice
but to drag you out!
Ginji...
Those losers have completely
turned against us!
[METABON] They must mean
business if they're using
generated zones to attack, bon.
I apologize.
This isn't how I wanted
everything to go down.
If you've changed your minds
and want to return
to the Council, go.
I get it.
Nah, it's too late for that.
We're not gonna give up just
because of one little setback.
Thank you.
Then you can leave
these guys to me.
You sure?
Don't worry about a thing.
I've still got a few tricks
hidden up my sleeve.
[OPERATOR 1A]
Initiating attack.
[PATROL DRIVER 2A] This is an
automated World Council patrol,
dedicated to ensuring
the safety and security
of your neighborhood.
They're insane if they
think they can take us on.
[PATROL DRIVER 2A] This is an
automated World Council patrol,
dedicated to ensuring
the safety and security--
[HIKARI screams]
[YUKARI]
What was that?!
[GINJI growls]
You're gonna end up getting
everyone killed, y'know!
[chuckles]
[ALL scream]
I didn't think there were
any underground tunnels
still open.
This is the perfect
escape route!
Yeah, and Santa said
it goes almost all the way
to the Divine Gate.
I wonder how close we'll end up.
[OPERATOR 1A]
Zone deactivation complete.
Maybe they already
headed back
to go and try to save Arthur.
If they did, we may as
well have their funerals.
[SHAKESPEARE]
Oh, hi!
Are you already finished
with your plotting?
[LOKI]
Yes, for the time being...
Now, let's raise the curtain
and get the show started
with that special pen of yours.
[SHAKESPEARE]
Okay!
[ALL yell]
[UNDINE]
Where'd they go?
[SYLPH]
They disappeared into thin air!
[EFREET]
Akane! Where are you?
[UNDINE]
Aoto!
[LOKI]
It's showtime!
[OTHELLO] Please allow me
to introduce you
to your new family.
[SHAKESPEARE]
He's totally got the whole
"tortured soul" look down!
[METABON laughing]
[AKANE]
What's going on?
[SHAKESPEARE] You'll never guess
where the plot's going next!