[NARRATOR] The boy had
always been alone.
He was born and
abandoned in Terrastia,
no one bothering to raise him.
He felt he existed
for no reason,
all by himself in a big,
uncertain world.
Sadness filled the air around
him, saturating his daily life.
Where does that door go?
It can't be any worse
than on this side.
[NARRATOR]
The boy had no reason to stay.
He found himself in a
place of light and beauty.
A world called Celestia.
But this new land did
nothing to lift his spirits.
It was as though every
splendor before his eyes
was nothing but an illusion.
Even the colors dancing through
the bright sky seemed unreal.
[NARRATOR]
Until one day...
He found another boy.
One who was smiling.
Excuse me...
But where is this place?
This is Celestia.
We're near the Holy Night Town.
Celestia?
Wait, hold on a second.
You're a human, aren't you?
What are you doing over here?
Isn't it Christmas Day
back in Terrastia?
Shouldn't you be
there celebrating?
No, I'm all alone.
[BOY]
Are you an orphan or something?
Do you not have anywhere
that you can call home?
[ARTHUR] No. Do you
think I could find one?
[BOY]
Uh...
Well, I don't know why
you're asking me that.
Don't cry. How about
I give you a present?
Like I said...
It is Christmas Day, after all.
Who are you?
Uh... Well, I'm, uh...
Yeah, I guess that
I can tell you.
You see, I'm Santa Clause.
You're Santa Clause?
Yup, that's me.
It may be for
just one day a year,
but it's my job to make the
whole world a happy place.
Are you being serious?
If you don't believe me,
how 'bout some proof?
C'mon, follow me.
[ARTHUR]
Where to?
Well, to my place, naturally.
To show you the truth.
Just you wait.
I've got a great
present for you.
I'm gonna give you a
brand new start at life, kid.
Let's get you cleaned up a bit.
[ARTHUR]
Thank you.
[ELISABETH]
Finally! There you are!
I've been looking everywhere!
Who is this?
Hey, Lisa!
I just met this guy, but he's
gonna be my best friend forever!
Oh, really?
That's wonderful.
[ARTHUR] When the Divine
Gate opened before,
it merged together the
three worlds of Celestia,
Terrastia, and Hellistia.
And the result was utter chaos.
We have selfishness
to blame for this.
Cowardice.
People only cared about
themselves and their own worlds.
[SAINT A] But what can you do to
rectify this situation, Arthur?
I'll do whatever I have to.
Anything to prevent
another incident
like the Blue Christmas
tragedy from happening again.
[SAINT C] And what if you're
unable to succeed in that?
[SAINT B] Isn't this
why the Academy was created?
[ARTHUR] I've gathered
Adapters with great potential
here to help me.
Together we will reach the
Divine Gate on this expedition.
[SAINT B chuckles]
[SAINT C] You're certainly
obsessed with finding
the holy relic, aren't you?
[SAINT A] Whatever our
thoughts are on the matter,
we won't rob you of
the chance to imagine
that your goal is achievable.
You deserve the right to dream.
[LOKI] Arthur's finally going
to make his big move.
I'm shivering with anticipation.
[OZ] I don't understand
what the hell is going on
in Arthur's head!
Or for that matter, in yours.
You want to know what's
going on in my mind?
Let's just say that it's
something very entertaining.
[chuckles]
And I can't wait to
see it all play out.
[ARTHUR]
You can laugh if you want to.
But it's true.
I'm in love with Terrastia.
How touching.
You've got a bright
future as a poet.
Oh, keep talking, Arthur,
I'm falling for you.
You're both just
jealous of how smart he is.
So?
Go on, why have you
summoned us here now?
The time has come, my friends.
Let's find the Gate.
All right! Let's get a move on.
It seems I have more important
things to worry about
than what soup to make tonight.
Are you serious?
Of course he is.
I can tell by that
mischievous smirk.
There's no stopping the boss
when he gets that
look on his face.
Well, serious or not,
you know you can count
on us to follow your lead.
Let's stop yappin'
and get going!
Yeah, what's our first step?
I'll be by your side
throughout this journey.
I won't back down.
Let me ask you
one thing, Arthur.
What's your plan if we
do find the Divine Gate?
It's simple.
I'm going to put the world
back the way it should be.
And what way is that?
[ARTHUR] Those who walk
through the Divine Gate
receive great power--
Enough to remake
the entire world--
To restore it to the
way it once was.
Now I see.
That's why you want to
obtain the Gate's power.
Yes.
I'll do whatever it takes.
And I refuse to stop until I
have completed this mission.
That's why I've
surrounded myself
with people who I can trust.
Those who will follow me
on this difficult journey.
Now then...
Allow me to lead you
as your king.
This isn't going to be
an easy expedition.
I'm asking that each of you
trust me with your lives.
[ALL]
Yes, Your Highness!
[MIDORI]
First place!
[laughs]
[BREUNOR]
You two always lose to her.
[AKANE]
Oh hey, what's up, Breunor?
That's Sir Breunor.
Anyway...
Arthur wants to talk
to you guys right now.
[MIDORI]
Huh? How come?
You can go ask him yourself.
Although...
It probably has to do
with us claiming the Gate.
Once there, Arthur's
gonna use his wish
to make this messed-up world
a better place for everyone.
Is this a joke?
Huh?
No, it's not.
So what does he want with us?
Look, I'm just the messenger.
Ask Arthur yourself!
There. That's all I had to say.
I wonder if he wants us to
go with him on this journey.
I sure hope so.
That's crazy.
Hey, what do you think, Aoto?
I bet... that whether
we go or not is up to us.
It's why we're here.
The reason behind
all of this training.
That makes sense.
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Let's see what he wants.
Sounds good.
How 'bout I race you there?
Let's go!
[K] Have you decided
what your wish is?
Aoto...
Do you really think that finding
the Gate will make it come true?
I'm not sure I believe that.
But going after it must
be better than doing nothing.
You really have changed.
You're moving on.
But aren't you afraid that
pain might be waiting
for you again if you
find the Divine Gate?
I'm used to pain.
That's fine.
Do you want to change the past?
Or the future now?
I find empty fish tanks
to be comforting.
That's cool, but why?
[ARTHUR]
They're so full of potential.
I could put anything in there.
Huh... There are
a lot of possibilities.
What a cool thought!
That's so smart, Arthur.
Ehh...
I dunno, I think I'd rather see
a bunch of awesome fish
swimming around,
if I'm being honest here.
Is that so?
What about you?
The tank reminds me of my home.
Oh, I see.
Your home?
What do you mean?
Let's move on to
why I've brought
the three of you here today.
This world we live in
is so full of discontent.
Akane. Midori. Aoto.
I'm heading for the Divine Gate.
And I'd like you to join me.
You mean you're
seriously offering us
the chance to find it with you?
Yes, I am.
Of course.
Naturally, my Knights of
Round will be coming along.
In addition to you three,
I've asked Ginji, Hikari,
and Yukari from the Academy
to join as well.
[AKANE] But we have no
way of knowing for sure
that we'll find it, right?
[ARTHUR] You'll never get
anywhere if you think like that.
Have faith.
I need people who
believe in the Gate.
Only they will be able
to pass through it.
But what if you're not
even sure you want to find it?
What if you're not certain you
want your wish to be granted?
[ARTHUR] Just as rain
gives way to sunshine,
your doubts will clear.
I only have one wish in life.
And that's to claim the
Divine Gate no matter the cost.
This entire plan is outrageous!
What's the matter?
I actually think he's
being quite smart,
because the more help he has,
the better his chances are.
Yeah, but what's his endgame?
What will the world look
like if Arthur remakes it?
It would be interesting
to see him reshape things.
But you're overlooking
the fact that I don't think
Arthur's telling the truth.
It's a pity.
What is?
Just come out with it.
[LOKI]
Hmm...
I'm just saying that if
we can't trust Arthur's plan,
then I think we should use our
powers to do whatever we like.
Don't you agree?
Well yeah, of course we should.
But I didn't need you
to tell me that, Loki.
Excuse me.
[LOKI chuckling]
Ah. I'm so excited, Arthur.
I've been captivated by you
since the very first day we met.
[LOKI]
What are doing, child?
Who are you?
Oh, me? A god.
What? Are you for real?
Is it true that gods have the
power to do whatever they want?
Why, yes.
I suppose I can do anything.
That must be nice.
[LOKI]
Would you like to be a god?
Mm-mm.
I don't think so.
I think I'd rather be
the king of this world.
A fearless leader.
[LOKI]
Why's that?
The reason we have wars
is because of bad leaders,
but I wouldn't let that happen.
I'd protect this world
and its people.
That's why I want
to become king,
so peace can finally be
restored throughout the land.
And then my best
friend could make sure
everyone was happy forever!
Then it would be my pleasure
to help you achieve
this great dream of peace.
[LOKI] Just like a king is there
to lead and help his people,
a god must be there
to guide a king
and help him on his path.
Thank you!
[LOKI]
Now... Why don't we begin?
Well, everyone.
The day is finally here!
[LOKI] It's time for
the Twilight Judgment!
[OZ]
Hear me, Scandinavian gods.
We offer ourselves up to you.
Turn us dragons into blades!
[OZ] In times when
the weak are oppressed,
use the power of these
weapons to protect them!
[AKANE]
So... what should we do?
Are you seriously
asking whether or not
we should go after
the Divine Gate?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going for sure.
But what you two do
is up to you guys.
Those things
he was talking about...
I will remake the
world and return it
to the way it should be.
And then become its king.
I guess that must be the reason
you want to find the
Divine Gate so badly.
Wait, a king?
Like, with a crown?
That's right.
And I'll be a grand leader.
My subjects will all prosper.
My good friend will ensure
happiness to everyone.
Who is this friend?
'Cause that's nuts.
He's the kind soul you
know as Santa Clause.
One night a year,
he brings joy and presents
to people all
throughout the world.
Oh yeah, I know
all about Santa Clause!
Whoa, is he really
a friend of yours?
Aw man, come on.
Don't tell me that
you think there's a real
Santa Clause, too!
It may be hard to believe,
but I assure you that he exists.
He is just as real
as the Divine Gate.
That's why I'm
going to reach it.
[AOTO] If we go, will our
wishes really come true?
[AKANE]
I don't know.
What happens if I get
to the Divine Gate
before anyone else does?
Then it'll just
grant my wish, right?
Yeah. You think
there's, like, a limit
to the number of
wishes it grants?
[SYLPH]
That's not how things work.
According to legend,
the Divine Gate
will indiscriminately grant
the wishes of everyone
who reaches it.
That's one of the reasons it
has caused so much chaos
throughout the world.
Yeah, Efreet is right.
Not all people have
honorable wishes, bon.
Well, if that's the case,
then we definitely have to
try to find the Gate, right?
Yeah, of course you do!
I'm guessing that you
won't wanna miss out.
Yeah.
I've got questions,
and the Gate's my best chance
of getting real answers.
What about you, Aoto?
[AOTO]
I don't think I could say no.
Alrighty!
Then let's go see Arthur.
[NARRATOR]
The rain begins to fall...
...slowly at first.
The dark clouds roll in,
as if to cover up each
individual's secret wishes.
But the world
is full of desires.
Wishes also known as lust.
[ARTHUR] Welcome to the
Divine Gate expedition.
Before we begin,
some introductions.
It's so nice to
finally meet you all.
My name is Oz.
I come from the realm
known as Dragtia,
and I'm at your service.
The name's Loki.
I'm from Ragnatia.
How exciting!
I'm looking forward to this!
I can't wait to see
what you'll accomplish!
If you're really from Ragnatia,
then that means
you must be a god!
To be honest, I wouldn't've
expected you to be so friendly.
You should never
presume to know how a god
is going to behave, dear.
You may be from Dragtia,
but you don't
look like a dragon.
Then again, I don't know very
much about that place at all.
Just as I don't know
everything there is
to learn about humans.
We can teach each other.
Both these dudes
seem really suspicious.
Yeah.
I understand what you're
trying to get at, okay?
[LOKI]
Thank you, Ginji, my boy.
[NARRATOR] Sometimes the
rain can't be anticipated.
Just as hope can come
without a warning.
However, the rain will
inevitably fall once again,
and hearts will
eventually cloud over.
Everyone knows this,
and yet they still
cling to hope.
As if they've never
been hurt before.
[MIDORI]
I'm gonna find you.
[METABON]
Why so quiet, bon?
What, you got
a problem with it?
If there's something
bothering you,
then get mad and
yell about it, bon!
Isn't that more your style, bon?
Would you shut up?
I'm just annoyed because
there's so much going on,
and I can't wrap my
head around any of it.
But I absolutely will
find out about my dad.
That's one thing
I can be sure of.
[K] I thought you
liked the shadows.
You've always enjoyed
quietly hiding in them,
holding your breath,
because you want to be
as invisible as possible.
But not now.
You're stepping
out of the shadows
and taking some
action for once.
Yeah.
I'm not going to just sit
back and watch anymore.
Because that never
works out well.
I always end up hating
myself even more.
[UNDINE]
Oh, hey, there you are, Aoto!
[UNDINE laughing]
Hey, did you need
something, Undine?
Oh wow!
That's the first time
you said my name!
Uh, yeah, I guess it is.
[UNDINE] That means
you're finally starting
to open up to me.
I knew it would happen
eventually, but I'm so excited!
Do you really think
that we're getting closer?
Just because of that?
[UNDINE]
Yeah, I sure do!
Feels like it.
I'm so happy!
I feel like I can do anything
to help you out now, Aoto!
[laughing]
So what's up?
[UNDINE]
Ah! Right.
Arthur was looking for you.
He said he wants to see you
alone for some reason.
I'm afraid that I lied to you.
[ARTHUR] I said that
I liked empty fish tanks.
[AOTO]
Okay, so you don't like them?
I know how scary it is
to lose something.
We're alike in
that way, aren't we?
That's why I'm always prepared
to lose things that I value now.
[ARTHUR] I want to turn the
world back to how it was
when Santa Clause was able
to give everyone happiness.
He gave me a new start
when I lost everything,
so I want to repay him somehow.
The only way I can.
[AOTO] It sounded like
your wish was for yourself,
but in fact it's selfless...
For someone else entirely.
[ARTHUR] You understand
because you're the same way.
You're always
sacrificing yourself
to keep something
important safe.
You've been protecting
your little brother, Aoto.
You've been his scapegoat.
[AOTO gasps]
[ARTHUR] Caring for other
people or ideals or worlds--
Anything other yourself
makes a person stronger.
That's the blessing and
the curse of being human.
[OZ]
Arthur.
You have no one but yourself
to blame for this mess.
[AKANE]
What's going on, Arthur?
Are the knights seriously
gonna fight gods?
[GAWAIN]
I'm so sorry.
I broke the treasure
you gave me.
Forgive me, Daddy.