Uh, it's a girl, watch out!
Whoa!
No!
Element, lightning, descend!
Oh, thanks a lot, Lee.
Don't take your eyes off it.
Sekura, now!
Right.
Windy card, come to my aid and stop Elle.
Windy!
Stop!
Return to your power, confine!
Arrow card, go!
Lee deserves that Clow card much more than she does.
Wow, looks like you've got a fan club.
Wow, great job, Sekura.
The arrow card really had it in for ya.
Ha, do I know how to pick a card captor or what?
Hmm.
Pie and cupcakes.
Wh, where am I?
Huh?
I'm underwater, but how can I breath?
Water is ever flowing, ever flowing...
What a weird dream.
Jeffrey?
Here.
Kimberly?
You've done much better this term, Kim.
Uh, Harrison.
Here.
Let's try a little harder next semester, okay?
Allie?
Here.
So, how'd you do?
I got a C!
I thought I was going to flunk music for sure.
You weren't that bad.
Madison?
Coming.
Well done, Madison.
Thanks.
So, you're nervous too, huh?
Me? As if.
Spring break, he has to show his mom.
You'd be nervous too if you met her.
Clam up.
Hey Madison, how'd it go?
The same as last semester.
That must mean straight A's again, right?
Lee Shoron.
And Maylin Ray.
Here.
Oh boy, Lee looks like he's gonna be sick.
So, are you going to go anywhere for spring break?
What is this?
Why didn't I get straight A's?
You just need to spend a little bit
more time studying for your tests, Maylin.
I'm sure you'll do better next term.
One B-, I can show her this.
Huh?
No homework for a whole week.
Yeah, spring break's the best.
Want to look inside?
Sure.
Hmm, I can't decide which one.
I see you've finally made up your mind.
This one was my favorite too.
Thanks.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You get to draw one.
The Readington Shopping District
is having a big contest right now.
Everyone who buys something gets to draw one.
Cool, good luck Sekura.
And the grand prize is a trip for four to Hong Kong.
So far, everyone's gotten the consolation prize.
So, what color is it?
Hey, look, it's a gold one,
probably just the consolation prize.
Ah.
Gold is the,
grand...
Grand?
Look!
The grand prize!?
That's amazing, Sekura, a trip over seas.
And just in time for spring break.
Yeah, I know.
I've never even been on a plane before.
I haven't seen Hong Kong in ages.
Kiro, you've been to Hong Kong?
Oh yeah, I used to live there.
While Clow Reed was still around.
So, that must mean the Clow
cards have been to Hong Kong too.
Oh, they haven't just been there,
that's where they were created, Sekura.
I wonder what Hong Kong's like?
Just stick with me.
I'll take you to all the best spots in town.
But, wait a sec,
Hey, what is it?
Didn't you tell me your father was
going away on a business trip this week?
Oh, I forgot.
You should go.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
I just wish I could go with you.
I've never been to Hong Kong before,
but I think it will be okay if Tori takes you.
Huh?
But Tori, what about,
what about your part-time job?
I'd miss five shifts, but I'll do it.
Huh?
You're the best!
And Madison makes three.
Tori, why don't you take Julian along too?
Sure, I think he can make it.
As far as I know, I don't think he has anything planned.
Yeah.
I wonder if that one over there is our plane.
Huh?
Okay Sekura, act natural.
You, you brought your video camera?
Of course, I'm going to videotape everything
and then edit it into a video
scrapbook with my mom's new software.
I think I'll call it Madison
and Sekura's first world tour.
Maybe we can use it for our independent study project.
Sekura, come on.
It's time to board.
Okay.
Sekura, don't forget, you can't wear shoes on the plane.
Really? You can't?
Miss, you may leave your shoes on if you wish.
Huh?
Tori!
That was so not funny.
Fresh air.
Kiro, would you get back in the,
uh,
Kiro, just stay hidden a little longer.
But it's hot.
Hey Sekura.
Julian.
So are you ready for our big trip?
This'll be my first time in Hong Kong too.
Oh, and by the way, thanks for inviting me.
Sure.
You ladies have a nice day.
Wow.
This room's huge!
Sekura.
Kiro!
I'm sorry.
How could you forget that I was stuck in there?
This is not funny!
But since you did bring me back to Hong Kong,
I'll forgive you.
For now anyway.
Has it changed much, Kiro?
Has it changed?
What an amazing view!
Has it ever changed!
Whoa, man!
Hong Kong Island is so close to our hotel.
Yeah, it says right here, it
only takes five minutes by ferry.
Hey, if you keep leaning over
like that, the sharks will get ya.
Huh?
They have sharks here?
Yep, the guidebook says so.
Oh.
Huh?
A shark?
Ah, it's so beautiful.
How much farther is it?
Don't worry, we'll be docking soon.
I've just never been to such a big city before.
Neither have I.
This is going to be the best vacation.
Film me later, okay?
Okay.
Wow, things really changed.
It's been a long time since you've been here, Kiro.
I'll bet hundreds of years.
But it,
it still feels the same.
I can still sense powerful forces,
the traces of ancient magic.
They're as strong as ever.
Not to mention that,
all the food is still great.
Oh Kiro.
What is it?
I was just thinking how Sekura's never been very lucky.
What'd you say?
Oh, hear me out.
I remember Clow Reed used to
say that nothing is accidental.
Well maybe Sekura was supposed to
win the grand prize for a reason.
You never know. Stranger things have happened,
especially in Hong Kong.
Oh come on, Kiro.
This dream again.
Who are you?
The dream again.
It, it was just so strange.
And we'd like four of these, oh, four of that,
oh, a bunch of these and four of this one too.
Is that all, sir?
We'll let you know.
Okay, dig in!
Okay.
Madison, would you like to share one with me?
Sure.
Kiro!
Kiro?
I think I'll try something else.
Yeah.
Okay, what was wrong with that one?
No, nothing.
I just changed my mind.
Well, let me see it then.
Huh, but there's so many to try.
You don't want this one.
Pass it over.
But.
Pass it over now!
Well, speed it up, squirt.
Right.
Changed my mind, we'll eat it.
Doesn't it look delicious, Madison?
Mm, it sure does.
Fine, whatever.
Okay, okay.
After lunch, what do you say we go check out Bird Street?
Did you say Bird street?
Yeah, it's a street packed with birds.
I've never seen so many birds in one place.
They're the most popular pet in Hong Kong.
Look at all the different kinds.
I'll bet some of them can learn to talk too.
That's so cool.
Wow.
Ah, Bird Street.
You've been here?
Mmhmm, and it hasn't changed a bit.
Huh?
Hello.
What's wrong?
It feels like we're being watched.
There's something strange around here.
Kiro, there can't be a Clow card here, can there?
No, this is different.
This feels more evil.
Hey, look at those ones.
Hm, they must have escaped.
Those birds!
Sekura!
We've got to follow her.
Okay.
All right, where's she running off to?
Hurry up.
We'll be right back.
Huh?
Release.
Stop!
There!
I'm sensing something.
Huh?
Wake up!
It's you.
What are you doing here?
Whoa!
Uh, Kiro, where do you think she could have run off to?
I'm sorry, hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Wait a,
Hey Maylin.
Madison Taylor?
What in the world are you doing here?
Sekura won a trip in a raffle.
Yo, little girl.
I see you brought the stuffed toy.
Hey!
They let you through customs?
All right, that's it!
Oh, come on, let me outta here.
Hey Madison, have you seen Lee around?
He said there was a strange aura
and then he took off somewhere.
Well, I've been looking all over for Sekura too.
Huh?
Sekura!
Lee!
Hey Madison.
Are you okay?
Where did you go? I was so worried about you.
Oh, I'm fine.
But you're soaking wet.
You had me so scared.
Sekura!
Oh.
I told you to stay close.
I'm sorry.
I saw,
I didn't mean to worry you, really.
Kids.
Why in the world did you take off on me like that?
Hey, what's up guys?
Hello, how you doing, Julian?
Well hello there.
We need to get you into some dry clothes.
Mmhmm.
I'm kind of glad you got soaked back there.
These outfits are so cute.
You should let me take you.
You look great.
Blue is my favorite color.
So sweet.
Oh, I think it's adorable.
So cute.
So irresistible.
Who are they?
No clue.
Who knew that Lee kid was so rich?
This house is incredible.
Well, speaking of cute.
Hello.
Hey boys.
Hey girls.
I hope we get to eat, don't you?
Hm?
Who are they?
So who are all those girls, Lee?
They're Lee's sisters.
All of them?
Yeah.
Wow.
I like this one.
They're really energetic.
Hey, don't you mean really weird?
Kiro.
Oh, I'm sorry, Lee.
She's so beautiful.
Hello mother.
Pleased to meet you.
How do you do?
That's Lee's mother?
But she looks so young.
Mm hm.
Boy, she looks pretty spooky to me.
Kiro!
I'm okay.
He's standing so still.
Yeah.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Sekura Avalon.
Thank you for the beautiful clothes and I'm really...
I can sense great power.
You possess the Clow cards.
When one has great powers,
it will at times attract grave danger,
but you must know that already.
I insist, you must stay here tonight.
What?
Lee.
I want you to show me your report card.
Ah, what a day.
I can't believe how pretty Lee's mom is.
Yeah.
She's beautiful,
but there's something mysterious about her.
I thought so too.
She holds a great deal of power, more than Lee.
I'm not surprised that Lee's mother
could sense me in the Clow cards.
Remember, everyone in their family
is a direct descendant of Clow Reed.
Was Clow Reed the most powerful
sorcerer in all of Hong Kong?
Yeah, probably in all of Asia.
But word is he certainly wasn't
the most popular man around.
When you have that much influence,
you're bound to make enemies along the way.
Did what his mom say about power
attracting danger freak you out?
I'm sure everything is gonna be just fine.
Yeah.
Tomorrow, we'll go downtown and go shopping.
And eat more Chinese food.
Goodnight Madison.
Night Sekura.
When one has great powers, it
will at times, attract grave danger.
The dream again.
Who are you?
Answer me!
At last, you have finally come back for me.
Huh?
I've been waiting all this time.
I've been waiting all this time,
waiting for you, for you to return!
You've finally come to set me free.
Sekura, what's wrong?
Sekura!
Are you okay?
That dream.
That's no ordinary dream.
Come in.
I call on the power of the celestial spirits divine,
water, wood, metal, wind, and earth,
power of the thunder and lightning abound,
I command thee.
Gather and grant me knowledge, release your light.
The spirits tell me you have
been summoned here to Hong Kong.
Summoned by whom?
By the woman in your dreams.
Be careful.
There are many powerful spirits at work here.
But what should I do?
It is you and you alone that
knows the path that you must follow.
With the magic of the Clow
cards comes great responsibility
and even greater risk.
The evil that seeks you now is very powerful.
But so are the spirits that will guide you.
This evil lures you only in your dreams.
Your dreams are where you will find the answer.
Sekura, you will find your way.
I know you will.
Don't worry.
You will know what to do when the time comes.
It was so nice to meet you.
Bye.
Come back soon.
You really slept over last night?
Yep.
Hm.
Well, I shoulda slept over too.
Thank you so much for everything.
Beware of water.
Hey, come on, let's get going.
Oh.
Coming.
Please take care, Sakura.
Okay.
The one in the back that looks
like a knife is the Bank of China.
And the one with the canon on the
roof is the Hong Kong Shang Hai Bank.
This area is Hong Kong's financial district.
Those banks are fierce competitors.
Hmm.
Hey, who knew the little girl could be such a tour guide?
And when are we gonna eat lunch?
I can't even think about food now.
I can't stop thinking about that woman
in my dreams and what she wants from me.
Was Lee's mother right?
Does this woman have something to do with the Clow cards?
My dreams will be where I find the answer.
Maybe Kiro was right.
I was destined to win this trip.
Why do we have to follow them around all day?
I don't have a choice.
Mother told us to.
What, to be their personal tour guides?
Well no.
Yeah, then what?
She sensed that Sakura might be in some kind of danger.
A barret.
Ah.
Hey, the woman in my dreams
had a barret just like this one.
This is getting weird.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
I'll take this one.
What? No, I, Julian, wait!
Uh.
Really, you don't have to.
Here.
It really suits you.
Oh thank you, Julian.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Huh?
Sekura?
Oh, not again.
That's it.
Huh?
That little.
Kiro, you can come out now.
There's an evil presence and it's growing even stronger.
Come on.
Hey, are those the birds that were in your dream?
Yeah.
Uh oh.
They're not ordinary birds.
They're spirits and I don't mean the good kind either.
Huh?
Should we follow them?
You bet.
Looks like no one's around.
Mmhmm.
What is it?
Do you hear water?
Oh yeah.
It's coming from the book.
That woman.
Huh?
No!
What are you, oh?
Come inside.
Sekura, wake up, hurry up.
Come back to me.
No choice.
Sekura!
Oh!
Hey, we've been looking everywhere for you.
I sense it.
Sekura?
Sekura, what's happening?
What's going on here?
Are you okay?
Kiro?
You're starting to look like yourself again.
Are we in the dream?
This is not a dream.
You created this world with your magic.
What is this? Who are you two?
She's the woman on the book!
You're just a little girl.
How did you get here?
Answer me.
Answer me!
Sekura!
Right.
Fly!
A Clow card?
Tell me, where did you get a Clow card?
Kiro, she seems to know about the Clow cards.
Uh Sekura, watch out!
Freeze.
Another Clow card.
Lee!
You have Clow cards too.
How'd you get here?
I was underwater, then suddenly, I'm here.
What happened to everyone else?
They were right behind me.
We've got to find them now.
There's no need to look.
The ones who came with you are over there.
Tell me, where is Clow Reed?
I am waiting.
I know I've seen her before.
Where is Clow Reed?
Let's split up now.
I'll go and try to distract her
and you go and help out the others, okay Sekura?
Where is Clow Reed?
Go!
Storm!
Sword!
Fly!
Let's go.
Maylin, Tori,
Julian.
I'll be back, I promise.
Sekura, hurry.
Ug, it's not working.
Madison, you're okay.
All right.
Where, where are we?
We'll explain it all later.
Huh?
It is unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
Kiro, stay here.
Sekura!
Lee, Lee, where are you?
Answer me!
Fly away, now.
Quick, get out.
Listen, you guys have to escape, now.
But.
Her powers are weaker above.
You should be able to escape if you fly up.
Silence!
Wait, no!
If Clow Reed won't set me free,
then I will use all of your powers to escape
and then I will finally have my revenge.
Sekura, come on, let's get out of here.
Hurry.
If we don't go now, we'll all be caught.
Sekura.
You will not escape!
There's the way out!
Sekura?
I guess it was all my fault.
Come on, don't say that.
It wasn't you. It was the woman on the book.
Book.
The book.
Speaking of which.
What book?
A magical book that acts as a
gateway to a different dimension.
The dimension we were just in.
So, if we find the book, we can save everyone.
What kind of book was it?
It was an old book with a strange aura.
Huh?
The aura has disappeared.
It's not here.
It's gone.
Sekura.
Lee,
Maylin,
Tori,
and Julian.
Don't lose hope.
We'll find a way back in there and save them.
That woman, I remember her now.
Is someone down there?
I will be right away to you.
Someone's coming.
Let's get outta here.
Yeah.
How can I help you?
Hmm?
Her name was Soo Yung.
She used to read people's
fortunes on the surface of water.
A fortune teller?
Yeah, Clow Reed never spoke about
it, but the story was that one day,
Soo Yung bumped into him on the street and
they fell in love with each other that very moment.
Go on.
At the time,
Clow Reed's magic was growing increasingly powerful.
As he and Soo Yung grew closer,
he taught her how to use magic,
but she began to use her magic for evil instead of good.
Clow Reed was the only one powerful enough
to stop her and as she plotted to destroy him,
he learned of her plans and created
another dimension in which to imprison her.
But that was so long ago.
Shouldn't she be dead by now?
She is. It's her spirit.
Her spirit?
Her world is a different kind of
dimension than the one that we live in.
Somehow, when she died, her spirit
must have become trapped inside.
She may not even realize she's dead.
It's a very complicated spell, Sekura.
Clow Reed must have known that she could have
escaped from a mortal prison using her magic.
So where does the book fit in to this whole thing?
Simple, she needed to lure him
into the dimension to escape.
Maybe that explains why you were drawn to its aura.
You had the Clow cards.
If that's true,
I should be able to get back into that dimension
again, but how can I do it without the book?
Hm. Hard to say. There is usually more
than one doorway into dimensions like that.
But the energy has already disappeared
from the shop we were in today.
And the book isn't around anymore either.
Book.
Kiro, I know the place on the cover of that book!
What?
It's the place where the woman was sitting.
It's the well!
Hey, what?
Did you figure something out?
Yeah, I know where the entrance is.
I was just there yesterday.
Hey, way to go. Now we can go find the others.
Yeah.
All right!
Now that's why I made you the card captor.
Mmhmm.
And I've got the perfect battle costume.
So, this is it?
Yeah.
Hm, there's a really strong energy coming from it.
Sekura, don't!
What is that?
It's the force field.
Force field?
A powerful spiritual boundary
has been created around this well.
But what can we do?
Not much.
Clow Reed created this barrier and he
has much stronger magical powers than we do.
But how do we...
Huh?
What is it, Kiro?
Somebody's coming.
Quick, in here.
Huh?
What's Lee's mom doing here?
Stand back.
But we already tried that.
Lee's presence has disappeared.
I know.
It's my fault.
That is not true.
His powers were no match for her magic.
But yours, maybe.
She is very powerful.
Go, Sekura.
Madison, you stay here.
Are you sure?
Please be careful, Sekura.
Yeah, I will.
And thanks for the battle costume.
It's made of all water resistant materials
so it will keep you dry in the water.
Come back soon.
Where are we?
It's an energy tunnel, a passage way. Take a good look.
This place connects to thousands of different dimensions.
If we get lost in here, we'll never be able to get out.
So where do we go?
Use your thoughts.
Concentrate your energy on the place you
wish to be and your thought will guide you there.
I want to go where my friends are being kept.
That's it.
Where are we?
I don't think we came out in the right place, Kiro.
Wait, this aura, it's,
that way.
Bird Street.
It's like a bunch of different
dimensions have merged together.
Keep going.
Okay.
The aura's growing stronger and stronger. It's close now.
The energy's coming from in there.
You're right.
Ready?
Yeah.
You again, why did you return?
I want my friends back.
If you want me to return them to
you, you must bring Clow Reed to me.
I already told you, we can't do that.
Clow Reed is...
I've been waiting all this time.
Waiting for him to set me free.
Would you just listen to what we're trying to tell you?
Geez.
She won't listen.
Whoa, what's going on?
It's an earthquake!
Huh?
There they are.
I will ask you one last time.
Where is Clow Reed?
That's what we've been trying to tell you.
Clow Reed is dead!
In that case, you shall all perish here!
This place.
Sekura.
Right.
Oh key of Clow, power of magic, power of light,
surrender the wand, the force, ignite.
Release!
Wand!
What's happening?
They're coming.
Where'd she go?
Hey, up there.
What is this place?
What have you done with Clow Reed?
Clow Reed is dead!
We can't just keep running like this. We've gotta hide.
I can't just leave my friends.
Kiro!
Sekura!
Now, tell me, where is Clow Reed?
Clow Reed is already dead.
You are a liar!
No, it's true. He passed away a long time ago.
It can't be!
He can't be dead.
Clow Reed can't.
Huh?
Huh.
He trapped me in there.
I will have my revenge!
I don't even know how long it has been.
All these years, I've used my powers to summon him,
tried to escape.
I trusted him.
Together we could have ruled all the land.
What a fool I was.
Why did you summon me here?
You have disappointed me, Soo Yung.
All that I know, I learned from you.
Join me.
Together we would be invincible.
I taught you magic, yes,
but magic should be used to serve the greater good,
not as a tool of power and destruction.
I'm sorry, but you've left me no choice.
The path you've chosen must end here.
The barret was the third entrance into the dimension.
She's been trapped inside the well ever since.
Water is ever flowing.
Water is ever flowing?
That was Clow Reed's voice!
That's it!
Arrow!
You again.
You felt betrayed by him, didn't you?
I'm sure he never meant to imprison you forever, Soo Yung.
I know he didn't.
But he's gone now.
I'm sorry you've suffered, but
please let my friends go.
Clow Reed, is he really dead?
Mmhmm.
I waited for him to come back to set me free.
I wanted revenge.
Huh?
I was so angry at him
for doing this to me.
But he is gone and I shall go too.
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you or your friends.
All she wanted was to be set
free and have her spirit move on.
She didn't know that Clow Reed had died.
It's over.
Her spirit can find peace now.
Lee,
Maylin,
Julian,
Tori,
you're okay.
What was it that we visited yesterday, Julian?
I don't really remember.
Me neither.
They don't remember a thing, do they?
Nope.
It's probably for the best.
Don't know how we'd ever explain it.
Well, maybe next time.
Huh?
I think we'll be back again soon.
I got a feeling we haven't seen the last of this place.
That sorceress may have seemed evil,
but she just wanted her spirit to be set free.
I'm glad my friends are okay too.
Well, if you do come back to
Hong Kong one day, count me in.
You bet.