[static buzzes]
[ominous music]
[bird tweets]
[wind whistles]
- [Fleia] I wish I could
escape from this gilded cage.
[wings flutter]
[somber music]
Free to fly away like
you, my little friend,
back to the real world
I've all but forgotten.
- [Karon] Fleia?
Fleia?
Are you in the studio?
Fleia.
[gasps] Fleia.
[wind howls]
Fleia!
[gasps]
[sobs]
[upbeat music]
[determined music]
[engine roars]
- Get ready, they're
gonna move out.
- Let's kick ass.
- Terrorists, man, I always
say you gotta be prepared.
[doors slam]
[device beeps]
[gun clicks]
[door bangs]
- Don't move, you're
all under arrest.
- [Cop] Oh, shit.
[gun bangs]
[helicopter blades hum]
- [Dunan] Christ,
here we go again.
Another glorious
day in the city.
- [Bularios] At least it beats
being a damn traffic cop.
- [Dunan] Yeah, I don't
know how I'd manage
without people shooting
at me every day.
[helicopter blades hum]
- [Team Leader]
Team A, ready to go.
- [Team Leader] B
Team, ready to go.
- [Team Leader] C Team, ready.
- This is the police.
We haven't been able to organize
the truck you requested,
but we can guarantee your
safety to the airport.
As a gesture of good will,
we want you to let
the children go.
- If we don't get what we want,
then you can whistle Dixie.
[gun bangs]
[bullets clang]
[concrete clatters]
[cackles] You get us
our fuckin' truck,
or the kids are gonna eat lead.
[helicopter blades hum]
[device hums]
- [Bularios] Go.
[feet pounding]
- Now listen, this'll
be your final briefing.
[helicopter blades roar]
You see down here,
they got heavy armor,
so avoid that route if you can.
Now here they've only got
troopers and Landmade suits,
so this is the way to go now.
Uh, hey, where you goin'?
- The bathroom.
- That stupid asshole.
Thinks he fuckin' knows a lot.
[determined music]
[lines whooshing]
[lighter clicks]
[flames hiss]
[toilet flushes]
[gun clicks]
[AJ grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[feet shuffling]
[headset beeps]
[gun clicks]
[gun bangs]
[glass shatters]
[hostages shout]
[gas hisses]
[hostages cough]
- Hold your breath, it's CS gas.
Oh my God, they'll be comin' in.
[door bangs]
- Don't move.
[hostage gasps]
[guns bang]
[body thuds]
[hostage screams]
[guns bang]
[body thuds]
- Eat it.
[gun bangs]
[gasps]
[body thuds]
[guns bang]
- Damn, you're lucky
you got caught.
If you were still up there,
you'd be toast. [laughs]
[determined music]
[chain clicks]
- Mommy!
- [Mother] Oh, Timomi!
[gun bangs]
- Huh.
Stay in here.
Bularios!
[feet pounding]
[guns click]
Evans, Evans!
[grenade clip clicks]
- Huh?
Grenade!
Hit the deck.
[explosion booms]
- Booby trap.
- [SWAT Commander]
Attention, all units,
one hostile has escaped.
He's armed and dangerous.
Two officers are down
at the rear entrance.
[ominous music]
- This guy's special.
I think he knew we were comin'.
He got himself away
from the others
because he knew they'd had it.
His best chance of escape
was while we were
busy with his friends.
I guess he's part cyborg from
the way he broke those cuffs.
- [Dunan] He's all bastard!
[Karon moans]
[Karon gasps]
- Huh?
Freeze.
[ominous music]
- That's not a very
friendly gesture.
- I've told you
not to come here.
- Things didn't go
too well for us today.
In fact, everyone
except me is dead.
I'm going to need more people.
- You need Landmates.
- If I could get that
kind of hardware,
I'm sure I could
put it to good use.
- Go and see this man here.
- Oh, yes, and
what's this guy do?
- [Karon] He's an arms dealer.
- An arms dealer, wow, I didn't
know that they still exist.
- Well, I'm a cop,
you're a terrorist,
it's just a matter
of supply and demand.
Just good old fashioned
commerce, that's all.
It always was and always
will be the way of the world.
[computer keys click]
[reception buzzes]
- Okay, Bully, I
got it here now.
The image in the data
bank is an exact match
for the guy you
and Dunan caught coming
out of the john yesterday.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
So who is the mystery man?
- He goes by the
name of AJ Sebastian.
He's a kind of career terrorist,
a real hard case with a
string of convictions.
It says here he even got caught
in an attempt to bust into Gaia.
That's how he lost
his eye and his ear.
He's one determined asshole.
That's all the info
I've got on him here.
You want anything else,
then you'll have to
go direct to the SSSP.
- Hmm.
[elevator dings]
[workers murmur]
[phone rings]
[keys click]
Hey, Dunan.
- Ah, Bularios, how's
it been going with you?
- Well, okay.
I've been checkin' out
our suspect's file.
His name's AJ Sebastian,
he's quite a boy.
The SSSP have taken
over the case.
- I knew that guy
was big trouble,
[printer beeps]
especially if Central
Admin want to get involved.
So why are the SSSP
interested in this man?
- All I know is
he was once caught
trying to sneak into Gaia.
I can only guess, but I'd reckon
this guy's not a terrorist
because he wants money, he's
out to change the world.
That's why the SSSP are
holding all information on him.
- And that's why I'm
putting in this application
for a secondment.
- What, and leave SWAT?
I don't believe it.
You'll miss all the excitement.
Anyway, so where are
you gonna transfer to?
- I'm going to investigation.
- Huh, you can't be serious.
What for?
- [Dunan] Because I want
to find that son of a bitch
and kill him.
[soft upbeat music]
[helicopter blades hum]
[Hitomi yawns]
[Hitomi giggles]
[helicopter blades roar]
- [Athena] She
hasn't brought anyone
back with her this time.
- Thank God for that,
every human she brings in
here has to be rehabilitated.
The cost to Olympion
Social Services,
not to mention the police,
is getting extortionate.
- Well, that can't be helped.
The General Management
Control Office are aiming
for total integration
to Olumpos.
- Hmm.
[fax beeps]
Huh?
Excuse me a moment.
[ominous music]
- Well-meaning idiots.
The outside world doesn't
breed human beings.
It's full of psychopaths
and lunatics.
Experimenting with them
will only destabilize
Olympion society.
They'll never integrate.
How can they after
living in that hell?
Poor devils.
That reminds me.
What happened to the last pair
Hitomi brought back to Olumpos?
They were put in a SWAT team.
- As police officers,
they've been excellent,
but as people, they're
pretty goddamn weird.
- Excuse me.
Inspector General,
we've had confirmation
that it was AJ Sebastian.
- Again?
Goddamn him.
This man has got to be
stopped at all costs.
Nike, what were their names?
The couple we were
talking about.
- She's Knute Dunan and
he's Bularios Hecatonchires,
both in SWAT.
- [Athena] Are they
good enough for the job?
- [Nike] You mean AJ Sebastian?
[soft upbeat music]
[customers murmuring]
- If everyone's glass is full,
I would like to propose a
toast to the girl responsible
for saving us all from the
ruins of the world outside,
and indeed to all of us.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- [Friends] Cheers!
[customers murmuring]
- [Dunan] Everyone in
this room has been rescued
from the ruins beyond Olumpos.
We owe an enormous debt
of gratitude to Hitomi.
When I think how Bularios
had been crippled
and blinded by the war and how
they managed to rebuild him,
give him a life
again, it's marvelous.
And when she comes back
from her expeditions,
she finds the time
to do casework
for the people she has saved
and helps them
settle into Olumpos.
But for her, we'd all
still be lost out there
in that wasteland.
[car engines hums]
[can clatters]
[coffee gurgles]
[gun bangs]
[man grunts]
[body thuds]
[man gasps]
[switches click]
[door hums]
[feet shuffling]
[motor hums]
[armor clanks]
[Hitomi hums]
[ice clatters]
[Hitomi gasps]
[lively music]
[customers murmur]
- Hello, I think
you're very handsome.
[lips smacking]
Hey, you haven't had a drink.
- I'd like to,
but I'm going on duty
at nine o'clock tonight.
- What?
No, no, you can't,
it's not fair.
- Hey, Hitomi,
what are you doing?
You're only being an
embarrassment to this poor guy.
- Hands off.
[shouts]
Handsome, come on back
to my place later on.
[engine roars]
- Now then, take this.
Huh?
Come on, wake up.
You can't go to sleep here.
Is she all right?
[Hitomi sighs]
[explosion booms]
[glass clatters]
[ominous music]
[customers gasp]
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- [Customer] Oh
my god, it's gone.
- What's that-
- Hey!
Look at the sky.
[customers gasp]
It must have been one
hell of an explosion.
- [Customer] Look at it.
[Hitomi hiccups]
[customers murmur]
- Oh, no, that's
gotta be Tartarus.
What am I going to do?
[engine roars]
[tires screech]
[crowd shouts]
[car horns honk]
[frantic music]
- There goes Karon.
- Just our luck to
be off duty tonight.
[explosion booms]
[dramatic music]
[feet pounding]
- [AJ] Come on,
move it, you guys.
[sirens wail]
[guns bang]
[suspenseful music]
[gun bangs]
[helicopter blades roar]
[guns bang]
[explosion booms]
[suit clangs]
[frantic music]
[gun clicks]
[helicopter blades roar]
[suit clangs]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
[guns bang]
- [Cop] It's no
good, he's had it.
- [Cop] Shit, that son of
a bitch can't be far away.
[water roars]
[suits clang]
It's okay, he's one of us.
Okay, the coast's clear.
- [Cop] You okay?
- [Karon] Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just the suit got
fucked in the firefight.
One of the bastards got
away onto the upper level.
- [Cop] Leave him to us.
- [Cop] See ya.
[suits clang]
[water roars]
[door bangs]
[computer beeps]
[keys click]
[computer hums]
[phone rings]
- Hello, Olumpos
Television news room.
Hey, it's that terrorist.
I'm sorry, go ahead, caller.
- Today, we in the
Human Liberation Union,
attacked the Tartarus block,
the headquarters
of the biodroids.
This action is intended
as a warning to them.
We would like to remind them
that they were created to serve
mankind, not to govern it.
They have risen to power
out of the chaos
caused by the last war.
They have no moral or
legal claim to government,
and we refuse to
recognize them as such.
We will continue to oppose them.
We have also recently come
by certain information
which tells us
that the biodroids
are going to deploy robot police
and heavily-armed
Multi-ped Cannons
in areas that they
consider to be volatile.
This is not the act
of a benign servant.
It is the act of a
dictator and oppressor.
It is clear to us the biodroids
intend to retain
their grasp on power
by every means available.
However, it is
still not too late.
We call on the human
population here to rise up
and shake off the
shackles of tyranny.
Freedom to humanity.
[gun bangs]
[explosion booms]
[somber music]
- Anything else?
- Un-uh.
- Well, that's just the
usual sort of stupid bullshit
we've come to expect from
these crazy lunatics.
If only they were crazy.
That Sebastian is
up to something.
What the hell was he doing
in the Tartarus block?
[dramatic orchestral music]
[engine hums]
[suspenseful music]
Was anything taken during the
raid on Tartarus last night?
- [Nike] Quite a lot.
Information retrieval, mainly.
Files on two
biodroids are missing.
Unfortunately, we're not sure
who they relate
to at the moment,
but the SSSP are investigating.
- [Athena] When do you
expect their report?
- [Nike] In three days.
On the plus side, the
incubation units were undamaged
and all current
fetuses remained valid.
The program's continuing
at full capacity.
[determined music]
[helicopter blades hum]
[guns bang]
[ammunition clangs]
[metal clatters]
- Whoa.
- Oh.
- [Cop] Golly.
[officer laughs]
- Holy shit, that thing
really kicks ass, huh?
- Look, Bularios,
about that attack on the
Tartarus block last night.
- Yeah, I know,
Sebastian was there.
If only we'd been on duty.
- Yeah.
- [Bularios] By the way,
I applied for transfer
to investigation as well.
- Oh, brilliant.
- And I figured if we
can't get a transfer,
then we'll take leave
and look for the bastard.
[Dunan hums]
[soft music]
[engine hums]
- [Newsman] This prototype
version of the Multi-ped Cannon
has to be operated by
a technician on board.
But thanks to scientists
at the Olumpos Institute,
all that is set to become
a thing of the past.
Future production models
will be controlled by Gaia,
Olumpos' central supercomputer.
This means that no matter
where a Multi-ped
Cannon is located,
it'll be able to react as
part of a coordinated response
to terrorism wherever it occurs.
Now, as we've seen in the film,
that response is selective,
depending on the threat.
It ranges from heavy artillery
down to .50 millimeter,
laser-guided,
water-cooled machine guns.
Kieran.
- [Kieran] Well, I wouldn't
want to be on the receiving end
of that lot.
- [Newsman] Well, that's
all we've time for
from \"Tomorrow Today.\"
Next week-
- The prototype Multi-ped
is going to be moved
to the central magazine
at seven tomorrow,
so phase one is tonight.
[phone rings]
[employees murmur]
- Dunan, Bularios,
this report stinks.
You got all, huh?
Oh.
So what the fuck
do they call this?
The Merry friggin' Celeste,
I shouldn't wonder.
Absent and this report
wants them in Central Admin,
my fucking life.
[phone rings]
Now what?
Yeah, this is Lieutenant
Bronx of the Olumpos SWAT.
Everyone's gone out the office,
Bularios, yeah, this is
his phone, but he's out.
[reception hums]
Well, the best I can suggest
is that you leave a message.
[reception beeps]
Jesus, yesterday, I
can't get rid of him,
today I can't find him.
[feet shuffling]
- See you guys later.
- Yeah, take it easy.
[feet shuffling]
- It's three days since we put
in our transfer applications
and we've heard nothing.
And nothing from the
terrorists either.
- Well as far as the transfers
are concerned, God knows.
But the Multi-ped Cannons are
due to be deployed shortly,
so the terrorists will
have to move soon.
There's no way they can
allow their deployment
to go unchecked.
- Yeah.
Hey.
- What's up?
- [Dunan] Karon.
- [Karon] Oh, hi there.
- I heard you got
injured the other night.
- That's right, just one
of those things, I suppose.
- Yeah, it was bad luck.
For Evans' grave?
- No, I've brought the
flowers from my wife.
She's also in this cemetery.
[somber music]
Thank you for coming.
She was always pleased
to get visitors.
You know, my wife's death
was the greatest tragedy
to have happened in my life.
- Did your wife
die in an accident?
- I'm afraid not.
She couldn't adapt to
her new life in Olumpos,
and so she became neurotic and
finally she killed herself.
- Oh.
- [Karon] Mind you,
I sometimes think
she had no real choice.
The city's organized
environment suffocated her.
In a way it was murder.
- How can you say that?
This city is the
most perfect place.
- I used to think that,
too, when I first came here.
Everything's provided for,
there's no unemployment,
there's proper healthcare,
housing, you name it,
we've got it, but
that's the problem.
We no longer live,
we just exist.
Living means fighting,
struggling for advancement.
It's a fundamental part
of the human condition.
You deny it, you
deny life itself.
That's what happened
to poor Fleia.
She had everything, but in
reality, she had nothing.
There was nothing
for her to live for,
nothing to strive for,
so she decided she couldn't
stand it any longer
and threw herself from
our apartment window.
I mean let's face it, we're
just living in a human zoo
with the Administration
as the keeper.
- That's not true.
You've got to admit most
people are happy here.
- That's because 80% of
the people in this city
are biodroids,
designed for life here.
They're programmed
to operate in this
environment from birth.
So it's no surprise,
they're happy.
[birds singing]
[car engines hum]
- [Teacher] Come
on now, children.
[children giggle]
- [Child] Oh, yeah.
Come on, let's go, hurry up.
- [Karon] 80% of the
people in this city
are biodroids designed
for life here.
[soft music]
[children giggle]
- [Child] Come on, come on.
- [Karon] They're
programmed to operate
in this environment from birth.
- He's 'round the back.
[solder gun hisses]
- [Yoshi] Hi.
- Hi.
Is it ready yet?
- [sighs] Yeah, sure it's ready.
Just as you requested, right?
There.
As you said, I've made the
armor half-thickness all around.
- [Karon] Excellent.
- [Yoshi] I don't
want to tell you
your business or anything,
but you won't get much
protection from it now.
- [Karon] Yeah, I know.
- Well, okay, it's your funeral.
And believe me, it will be
if anybody uses armor
piercing bullets on you.
- Hey, let me worry
about gettin' blown away
by some asshole out there.
If I can get top speed
out of this suit,
I'll be too fast for anyone
to get a shot off at me.
- Oh, well, you know,
if your chief finds out,
you'll be in trouble.
This is completely
against all regulations.
- Just you forget
about the regulations.
Remember, I paid you cash
in hand for that job.
So just think about
how you'll spend it.
- Yeah.
- And anyway, it's like you
said, if I die, it's my funeral.
What's that?
- Huh?
You mean that one?
That's Dunan's new Guges.
She trashed her Landmate.
She's pretty hard on Landmates,
so I persuaded her to
buy this Guges model.
It's much more
expensive, of course,
but it's a lot tougher
and better made.
But then again, I bet she wrecks
it within a week. [laughs]
- I see.
She'll be a strong opponent.
- Don't you mean rival?
- Oh, sure I do.
[upbeat music]
[hangers clatter]
[coin clatters]
[steam hisses]
[Dunan sighs]
- [Cop] Hey, Dunan, where
you goin' in such a hurry?
- So what kept ya?
- I was having a
shower, all right?
- Why, you're not seeing a guy?
- Exactly.
Come on, now let's move it.
[tires screech]
[soft music]
- Ah, please do come in.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Oh, stand easy and go
take a seat over there
and listen up.
Now I'll come straight to the
point as my time is precious.
You will find this
terrorist, Sebastian,
and then I want you to kill him.
I want you to understand that
this man's not to be arrested.
- But, ma'am, that
contravenes section 38
of the Olympion Freedom Charter.
- That's true, but
Sebastian is a special case
and we must employ special
measures if we are to stop him.
I have chosen you
two for the task,
'cause I know you have
taken a particular interest
in the case.
All the state files on
Sebastian will be made available
for you to inspect.
You will give this case
the highest priority.
All leaves to be canceled
until Sebastian is dead.
Well, that's it, good afternoon.
Oh, and one more thing.
The best of luck to you both.
[Dunan gulps]
- It was a hologram.
- Sure was, a pretty
crap one, too.
- It really gets on my tits
that she wouldn't
see us face-to-face.
- Yeah, too good to come into
close contact with us humans.
- [Dunan] So I suppose
we follow her orders,
just like she said.
- [Bularios] Sure,
no turning back now.
[determined music]
[tires screeching]
[crook shouts]
- Whoa.
Ah.
[tail light cracks]
[shouts]
Whoa.
[gun clicks]
[gun bangs]
[crook shouts]
[doors clangs]
- [Crook] You fuckers, give
me my fuckin' phone call.
- [Cop] Hey look, Dunan
and Bularios are here.
- [Cop] Christ, I thought
you guys had gone on leave.
What brings you back here?
- [Cop] Leave my ass,
they've been on their
goddamn honeymoon.
- Hey, Dunan, if
it didn't work out,
I'll be your new boyfriend.
- Bang.
[cops exclaim]
Bang, bang, bang,
bang, bang.
- Hey.
- [Cop] Don't shoot. [laughs]
- Hey, Bularios, there are
some messages on your phone.
Most of them from women.
- Thanks.
Huh?
[car engines hums]
- [AJ] You're sure you'll
be all right on your own?
- I'll be fine.
Besides there's no
time to arrange help,
and it'll be much easier
for me to break in
and make the snatch on my own.
- Excellent, after tonight,
I'll have the Multi-ped Cannon
and you'll have the girl.
You know where to take her?
- Yes.
- [AJ] Good.
It's unfortunate
these two cops live
in the same block as Hitomi.
You'll take care of them.
- Don't worry, I
won't let Bularios
and Dunan get in the way.
I'll take them out
of the picture first.
[bird tweets]
- [AJ] Well, good luck then.
- And the same to
you, my friend.
- [AJ] Thanks.
[ominous music]
[shelf swishes]
[keys tapping]
[computer beeps]
- This is Olumpos Police
Department, how can I help you?
[armor clicks]
- [AJ] Sorry to
keep you waiting.
[armor clanks]
[suspenseful music]
- Okay, let's go.
- I have to do something first.
- I need to speak
to Bularios Hecatonchires
and Dunan Knute, and quick.
What do you mean
they're on vacation?
I've got important information.
[door crashes]
[grunts]
Oh, oh.
- Hello, hello.
- Ow, ah, ooh.
[grunts]
[skull creaks]
[groans]
[skull cracks]
[bottles crash]
- That stupid old man was
double dealing with the cops
behind our backs,
which is a great pity when
you consider all the effort
that we put in.
- Yeah, I think you can probably
relax safe in the knowledge
that he's not gonna tell
anyone anything anymore.
Running this bar on the
huge profits he made
obviously wasn't enough for him.
I guess he needed the extra
thrill of being a spy.
[soft music]
Well, this is it then,
[sighs] time we split up.
I don't even know your name.
- [AJ] After today, it won't
matter what I'm called,
but for the record
I'm Sebastian.
- I'm Karon, Karon Mausoros.
[wings fluter]
[bird tweets]
[metal clicks]
[computer hums]
[Bularios laughs]
- Huh?
[Dunan grunts]
Humph.
[computer clicks]
[computer beeps]
- [Nereus] Hello, Bularios,
how have you been?
Sorry I'm not transmitting
picture, but I wouldn't-
- Nereus!
- [Nereus] Into the wrong hands.
Listen, I've got some really
hot information for you,
but it'll cost ya. [cackles]
- What the hell does he want?
- But then when doesn't it?
- Who is it?
- It's Nereus, my
old tip-off man,
but he's been out
of crime too long
to hear anything
about anyone now.
- [Nereus] I think you'll
find it's worth hearing.
I'll wait for you at my
place, the Bar Nereus.
Just in case you can't remember,
it's located downtown
near the river,
one block down
from the hospital.
See you soon.
[computer whooshes]
- [Bularios] Look, there's
another one coming up now.
[computer beeps]
- [Nereus] Bularios, I still
haven't heard from you.
It's most unlike you to let
an opportunity like this
slip through your fingers.
Perhaps you think
I'm bullshitting you.
I tell you something.
This case involves a policeman.
- Huh?
- Wow.
- [Nereus] And
furthermore, I know who.
So if you want to find out who
the traitor in your midst is,
you'd better get
yourself down here now.
The longer you leave it, the
higher, the price will rise.
See you soon.
[computer whooshes]
[computer beeps]
- Hello, it's me, Hitomi.
I'm sorry to bother you guys,
but I've been
having some trouble
with the auto-lock
on my front door.
Could one of you take a look
at it before I go to bed, huh?
[water splashes]
[cover clangs]
[metal bangs]
[machines hum]
- Haven't you finished sifting
through all that data yet?
- It's taking me forever,
but when I finish, do you fancy
downing a few beers with me?
- Okay, I'll see you later.
- Hmm.
[machine beeps]
[machine whooshes]
[gasps]
Oh, deep shit.
Deep shit.
[phone beeps]
- Yes, this is Athena.
What?
The biodroid data related
to Hitomi was removed
from the central files
before the raid on Tartarus?
Okay, thank you.
This is Athena, get
me the SSSP now.
[gas hisses]
[suit clangs]
[dramatic music]
[door bangs]
[door clangs]
[feet pounding]
- That's far enough.
Do what I say and
this won't go off.
Now drop the gun.
[suspenseful music]
- Don't even think about it.
Move a muscle and I'll blow
your fuckin' head clean off.
[gun bangs]
[fist thuds]
[Bularios groans]
Hey, Bularios.
[gun clicks]
[gun bangs]
- Huh?
- Bullseye!
[feet pounding]
- That's far enough,
now hit the deck.
- Get out of my fuckin' way.
Huh?
- Shut it, bitch.
[foot pounds]
[gun clicks]
- All right, hot
shot, drop the girl
or I'll fill ya
so full of holes,
you'll be winning the next
Mr. Swiss Cheese contest.
You're really beginning
to piss me off.
Now drop the fuckin' girl.
[feet pounding]
Huh?
[dramatic music]
What the fuck?
[frantic music]
[armor clangs]
[grunts]
[feet pounding]
Bastard.
Get off.
Don't shoot, you idiots,
you might hit Hitomi.
[fist thuds]
[grunts]
- [Officer] Let's move.
[feet pounding]
[water splashes]
[explosion booms]
- Hitomi.
[suit bangs]
[Karon sighs]
- The engineer,
calling the driver,
the engineer,
calling the driver.
- [Driver] This is
the driver, over.
- [Karon] I got the tag.
I repeat, I got the tag.
Engineer out.
[engines hum]
[keys clicking]
- [AJ] Oh, and before you go,
make sure that all the
weapons systems are online.
Listen, Buster, you're
wasting your time.
Gaia, the Central computer'll
abort your commands.
- Well, thank you.
And speaking of abortions.
[tech shouts]
[body thuds]
[door clicks]
- As you know, Gaia, the
Central Integration Computer,
controls every
aspect of the city,
power, water,
weapons, everything.
What you probably don't know
is that there is
an override key.
It's built into Hitomi's DNA.
That key is now in the
hands of the terrorists.
You realize they
now have the power
to shut down the entire city.
Now you don't have
to be a genius
to see what the
consequences might be.
We've got to get her back.
- [Bularios] We understand
the situation is serious,
but why were we arrested?
- You've been arrested on
suspicion of being spies.
- No way.
[Dunan huffs]
- We have, for some time,
been aware that there's a
security leak within the police.
Unfortunately, we
have been unsuccessful
in positively identifying
the guilty parties,
however, we suspect you both.
Let us not forget that the
Sebastian was able to escape
from your custody without
any apparent problem
during the Tower block siege.
Now either he's very clever,
or else he didn't so much escape
from you as walk scot-free,
which can only mean one thing.
You are terrorist sympathizers,
and as you were not
born in Olumpos-
- Why you, you, you
know, that's not true.
We've always served the city.
- Yes, that's true.
It will be the perfect
cover for your subterfuge.
In addition, when
Hitomi was kidnapped,
you two were on the scene
and the terrorist escaped.
- That's because your
men had us arrested.
They were obeying their orders
and you prevented them
firing on the suspect.
- But Hitomi could easily have
been killed in their fire.
- We can make Hitomi's
replica any time.
It would be better if she were
dead, then let them have her.
- But that's worse than murder.
- Don't be ridiculous.
She's a biodroid,
a factory-made,
synthetically produced
human product,
built to fulfill
certain specific needs.
So don't give me any shit
about the sanctity
of all human life.
[ominous music]
[chain rattles]
- Well, Hitomi still
counts as our friend.
- It's just as well the girl's
your friend and not mine
because Hitomi's still in the
clutches of those terrorists,
and dead or alive, we need her.
- Pardon me, ma'am,
we've recently received
some information
from an old informant of mine.
If you'll just give us a
chance to follow it up,
you'll see your trust
in us is justified.
[crowd gasps]
- [Bystander] Oh,
Jesus, what happened?
Do you see what I see?
- Wait a minute-
- Where'd he go?
- Is it in there?
- Yes.
- [Bystander] Where, I can't?
- Oh, boy.
- Christ.
- [Bystander] Does
anyone know who it was?
- Dead men can't talk.
- True, but he's already told
us the most important thing,
that they're being assisted
by a member of the police.
- What do you suppose
they're going to do?
- I ain't got a clue,
but I'm prepared to bet
good odds it's gonna be big,
and there's gonna be one hell
of a lot of shootin' involved.
We really ought to
buy some new guns.
[helicopter blades hum]
- Okay, everyone,
now pay attention.
We will be arriving
at Olumpos City
in approximately 12 hours.
I would remind you we
are being brought in
to defend the city against an
unspecified terrorist attack.
The emphasis being on defense,
so make sure you don't blow
the shit out of the place
in a fit of over enthusiasm.
Over and out.
[helicopter blades hum]
[explosion booms]
[ominous music]
- Computer access
one is destroyed.
[explosion booms]
- [Cop] Computer
access two destroyed.
[explosion booms]
- [Cop] Access three destroyed.
- Ma'am, three of the four
computer access terminals
have now been
entirely destroyed.
- Good.
Excellent, now
there's only one place
they could possibly
gain access to Gaia,
and we have it
completely surrounded.
So come on you fuckers,
let's see you try it
[suspenseful music]
[map rustles]
- [Karon] Time to get going.
[shoes tapping]
[motor hums]
[somber music]
- [Doctor] Karon Mausoros,
we're from the Olympion
Mental Institute.
We'd like to ask some
questions about your late wife.
- As you will be aware,
your wife made frequent
trips to the Institute
before her death.
- Undoubtedly, her sanity
had been disturbed.
We would like you to tell us
what caused that disturbance.
- Anything might help us,
whatever you can remember.
We must help you then.
- Huh?
What, what?
Hey, get off me.
You have no right.
- Quiet, Mr. Mausoros.
- Where are you taking me?
Answer me, damn you.
You can't just take
me from my home.
It's not right.
[lights click]
[soft somber music]
Dang. [gasps]
What do you want of me?
You have to tell me.
Huh?
What are you
looking at in there?
[doctors laugh]
- Karon, hello, Karon.
- Fleia. [laughs]
Oh, no, it can't be.
It's my memories.
[grunts] You have no right
to access that information.
You can't treat me like
this, you bastards.
This is like being
a laboratory rat.
I'm a human being.
Oh.
[elevator dings]
[lock clangs]
[door hums]
It's time for us to get going.
- No way will I
ever help terrorists
to destroy the city
of Olumpos. [gasps]
Stay away from me.
Remember, I'm a biodroid
and we can't do anything
that could possibly harm
our beautiful environment.
- Hitomi, I'm not asking
you as a biodroid,
I'm asking you as a human being.
[feet pounding]
[armor clanging]
- Time to change.
[engine roars]
- [Cop] Hold it,
hold it there, buddy.
[tires screech]
- Huh?
Look, there's Karon.
- Hi, I've got an extra
Landmate to deliver.
Here are the papers.
- [Dunan] Hi, Karon.
[Hitomi gasps]
- Dunan.
- [Cop] Yeah,
that's all in order.
[engine hums]
[van rattles]
[Hitomi shouts]
[eye clicks]
[ominous music]
- What's wrong?
- [Nereus] This case
involves a policeman.
[engine roars]
- Shit!
Come on.
- What?
[suspenseful music]
[metal creaks]
[tires screech]
- All right, get movin'.
- [Cop] You, contact
headquarters.
- [Dunan] What the
hell's goin' on?
- I heard, Hitomi in that truck.
- [Dunan] What?
- Remember, we're lookin'
for a crooked cop.
- What?
You can't mean Karon.
I don't believe it.
- We know he thinks
Olumpos murdered his wife.
[engine roars]
[guns click]
- So we've got you now.
Or is it possible you've got us?
[tires screech]
[suspenseful music]
[engine roars]
Fire!
[guns bang]
[glass shatters]
[ammunition bangs]
[tires screech]
[metal clangs]
[glass shatters]
[brakes squeal]
[feet pounding]
Make sure that the driver
is well and truly dead.
[armor hums]
[fist thuds]
[gasps]
[soft dreamy music]
[glass shatters]
- [Cop] Bastard.
[electricity sizzles]
[armor bangs]
[suits whoosh]
- [Dunan] Give it up,
Karon, you're finished.
[feet pounding]
[soft dreamy music]
[metal screeches]
[air whooshes]
- [Cop] Catch.
[helicopter blades hum]
- [Dunan] Karon.
- Listen, you have
to get out of my way.
- We can't do that.
- [Karon] You have to.
Don't you realize
if the remote-control
Multi-ped Cannons come online,
they can only be
operated by Gaia?
That means the entire planet
will be under its control.
Humans will no longer
control their destiny.
- Where are the gunships?
- [Officer] We'll be with
you as soon as we can.
- What can we expect
if he succeeds
in taking Gaia out of service?
- It'd be a total fuck up.
Everything would go offline.
Shit.
- What is it?
- I think I know what
the bastards are up to.
When Gaia goes offline,
the only thing that would
still be operational
is the prototype
Multi-ped Cannon.
And if that were to fall
into the wrong hands,
we would be
defenseless against it.
- [Dunan] Surrender now, Karon.
- [Karon] Never.
I won't tell you two again.
You'll have to
kill me to stop me.
- Huh?
- I can't let Olumpos survive.
It treats us like
laboratory rats
[gun bangs]
[explosion booms]
[metal clangs]
[suit bangs]
[Hitomi gasps]
[somber music]
[door hums]
- [Bularios] Hitomi,
get out of the way.
[guidance lock beeps]
No, you don't, you fuckers.
[gun bangs]
- [Dunan] Don't go
in there, Hitomi.
- Oh, please.
You must go in, go in now.
[door hums]
[power hums]
- Huh?
- What?
[water splashes]
- Oh?
[gas hisses]
- Hey.
- Get out of there!
- I don't know.
- Go, go!
[power hums]
- [laughs] It's all mine now.
[engine hums]
[metal clangs]
- [Athena] Attention all units,
proceed to the Multi-ped Cannon
maintenance bays immediately.
[explosion booms]
[dramatic music]
[glass clatters]
- [Cop] Attention, attention,
this is a red alert.
This is a red alert.
All citizens should
make their way
to the city's communal
complex as soon as possible.
This is a red alert.
[engine hums]
[tires squeal]
- Too fuckin' late.
Quick, call out the air team.
- Right, well do what you can.
We'll go to Gaia and
get its functions back.
- Gaia, ma'am?
- As fast as you can.
- Right.
- [Athena] It's our only hope.
[helicopter blades roar]
- [AJ] Hmm.
[gun bangs]
[engine roars]
- Our only hope is to get
Gaia switched back on again.
- I just hope we
make it in time.
[engine roars]
- You can't just walk in there.
Gaia has defensive systems
designed to prevent
unauthorized access.
It'll kill you.
We have to disconnect
the DNA log first,
but that could take days.
Hey, come back here.
- [Athena] We haven't got
days, we've got minutes,
and the only thing that can stop
that Multi-ped Cannon is Gaia.
So somehow we have to find
a way of getting it back on.
[engine roars]
[tires squeal]
[motorcycle bangs]
[guns click]
What the hell are you doing?
- We've come to reconnect Gaia.
[guns bang]
[metal bangs]
[glass clatters]
[motors hum]
- I love it, this is my
kind of machine. [cackles]
[frantic music]
[guns bang]
Nothing and no one
is gonna stop me now,
and you boys are in
deep shit for trying.
[gun hums]
[gun bangs]
- [Cop] Get us some backup,
we're getting trashed.
[machine beeps]
- [Dunan] Is this it?
- [Athena] No, these are just
some of Gaia's data banks.
We need to get to the ROM drive
at the center of this lot.
It's the bit that uses all
the information stored here.
We'll have to be careful though,
because it's defended by
remote security systems.
[camera hums]
[elevator dings]
Okay, let's move it.
Our best chance
is to keep moving.
It makes us a harder target
for the security systems.
- It's a piece of piss so far.
[lasers snap]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
- Have you been hurt?
- [Dunan] Oh, Bularios!
[Bularios groans]
[building rumbles]
- [Control Operator] Hello,
D Flight, this is Control.
We need ya here
and we need ya now.
- [Pilot] This is D Flight,
we're still about
20 minutes away.
- [Bularios] There's about
200 meters of passage to go.
- [Dunan] Yes, and how
many more booby traps?
- Look, you two are gonna
have to run it alone.
I'll cover you from back here.
Now get moving.
- Bularios!
- Look, don't argue,
just get on with it.
My leg's completely fucked.
There's no way I'd ever make it.
Look, I'll tell you what.
When this is over, you can
take me shopping for a new leg.
- Uh-huh.
- [Bularios] Now don't stop.
Just keep going straight
and don't even look, okay?
Go!
[suspenseful music]
[feet pounding]
[camera hums]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
[camera hums]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
[camera hums]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
[women gasp]
[gun bangs]
[glass clatters]
- Hey, tough guy, good shooting.
- [Athena] This way
- [groans] What a fucking day.
[tense music]
[pages rustle]
- God, it's hopeless.
We'll never find out which
is the DNA circuit lock.
Useless.
[snorts] Sorry. [laughs]
[ominous music]
[helicopter blades hum]
- [Cop] If those reinforcements
don't get here soon,
we're fucked.
- It's here.
- Yes, brilliant.
Hurry.
- [Dunan] So what's it
look like I'm doing?
[feet pounding]
[suspenseful music]
[ominous music]
- [Cop] It's useless, we
can't even slow it down.
- [AJ] Olumpos, you're finished.
- There it is.
That circuit is responsible
for the DNA lock.
All we have to do is break it.
And that's going to be your job.
- But my right hand's hurt.
- Then you'll use your left.
Remember, you're a trained shot.
You have a better
chance than me.
[gun bangs]
You're at one o'clock,
come down left.
[gun bangs]
Now you're too far down left.
Just keep calm.
[gun bangs]
Right a bit.
Down a bit.
[gun bangs]
We've only got two rounds left.
- Remember,
concentration is the key.
[gun bangs]
- [Dunan] Shit.
- Squeeze the trigger,
don't yank at it.
[gun bangs]
[motor hums]
[ominous music]
- What the fuckin' hell?
Oh, Christ.
[metal bangs]
[Multi-ped bangs]
Fuckin' cocksucker.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Huh?
[gun bangs]
[shouts]
[armor bangs]
- [Nike] This is mission
control to all units,
the Multi-ped Cannon
has been neutralized.
All units are to return
to base immediately.
The threat to
Olumpos is now over.
- The doctors say I'll be up
and about in a week or two.
- Well, it'd take more
than a couple of bullets
to put you down.
- I'm the one you
should blame, I'm sorry.
- That's nonsense.
- You mean that?
- Of course.
If someone as handsome as
Karon asked me to do something,
I would.
- Huh?
- Hah, you're just
jealous, aren't you?
- No, no, no, not
at all. [huffs]
[friends laugh]
[somber music]
[bird tweets]
- [Karon] In a cage
you're protected
from the real world outside,
but that's not living.
Sooner or later,
you have to escape.
[engine hums]
[car honks]
[engine roars]
[upbeat music]
[singing in foreign language]