[Radu] Are you
alright, tovarish?
[Ion] Yes. I'll be
fine... Radu...
We must hurry.
Almost there... I'll scout
ahead and prepare the vessel...
You wait here, tovarish,
and rest... Take care.
No, wait...
Don't worry...
Just relax...
Madame... I leave
Ion in your hands.
Oh... Yes!
Okay... Lean on me. We need
to relieve the pressure...
Get away!
I don't need the aid
of a filthy Terran!
Terran or not, you
need help now...
So stubborn...
But what can I do?
Fresh blood. The wound
on your shoulder
has undoubtedly
been reopened...
Please, you need to
remove your shirt...
Our options
are limited...
I don't possess the tools
to clean it down here,
but a new bandage
couldn't hurt.
Unless you'd like to lose
that hand- back off!!
I'm in enough
pain already...
I won't suffer the touch
of a lowly Terran.
Lowly?
Now get this straight!
You may not like me,
but at the moment no one else
is offering you any help...
So stop whining
like a child...
Injured, you're
nothing but a burden!
I- I wasn't whining...
And I am not a child!
How dare you call
me a burden!?
You're honestly going to
sit there and tell me
you're not
slowing us down?!
You needed your friend's help
just to hobble this far!
From my
viewpoint,
you're inability to
walk is a burden...
Then again, perhaps
you're right
and I owe you an apology...
Go ahead, prove me wrong.
Stand on your
own two feet.
You'll pay
for that!
Hey...
Easy...
I apologize... I shouldn't
have let my emotions
get the better of me...
That was childish.
You need to conserve
your strength.
I will make an exception this
time. You may redress my wound.
But, you must do it
carefully, Terran.
I'll do
my best.
I'm so
stupid.
What's wrong...? Why
are you staring at me?
This wound
is serious.
Just now...
I- I shook you.
Don't be too hard
on yourself...
Truth be told, I fully intended
to kill you earlier...
It was quite prudent of you
not to hold anything back.
I have far less sympathy for
the Terran that attacked me!
Not one word
from my mouth...
And he decides to shoot
me! It's Atrocious!
Maybe... Though Father Tres
had no choice but to use force.
It's true.
Prior to you showing up,
the embassy was bombed...
Good people died...
I think anyone would
question Father's loyalty
if he hadn't attacked
a Methuselah
in Cardinal Sforza's
chambers...
I'm not saying it
wasn't unfortunate.
There...
Much better...
It was odd timing...
Other than me and Radu...
No one else knew
of the meeting.
Radu!
I was starting to get
worried about you...
Radu, what
are you doing?
A pity, tovarish...
I didn't want to have to
be the one to kill you.
What?! This doesn't
make any sense!
The Terran knows what
you refuse to see.
Radu... How
could you?
Liar! Liar!
You can't possibly
expect me to believe
you'd jeopardize
this mission!
Not me... What are you
hiding?! Answer me!
[Radu] Ion...
Listen to me.
These are dangerous times...
It was I who sabotaged
your meeting with Cardinal
Sforza last night.
You!? Of all
people...
What reason could you have
for doing such a thing?
Why, for our future,
of course...
There is no
better reason.
The day when Methuselah
and Terrans can coexist
will never
come... And yet...
Our Augusta desires
this in vain...
But, these talks must
not occur, my friend...
A viper will always
strike... Do you understand?
I don't... If you truly believe
that... Talk to Her Majesty!
Share with her
your wisdom...
It's better than hiding in
the shadows of dissent!
This plot of yours
isn't going to work!
Such frankness is an
endearing trait...
But you forget your place,
Ion Fortuna... Fate...
Especially ours...
Is to serve the Empire,
in life or death.
However, unlike you, I am not
a favorite of our Empress...
I am not afforded the chance
a favored retainer has,
of being chosen as a
secret messenger...
What advice could someone of
my low station possibly give
that might echo to the
ears of Her Majesty?
No... The shadows provide my
best vantage point for now.
I am powerless in the
Empire, and as such,
am but a token among
many on the board.
My only shot at playing in this
game is to change the rules.
Founded on actions,
not words...
And inscribed
in blood.
Rules to change
the world?
No...
Rules... Which
shall renew it...
Igne Natura
Renovatur Integra.
Better late
than never, eh?!
Sorry to keep
you waiting!
Father
Nightroad!
I would've been here
sooner but trouble called.
Hopefully this boat will
make up for my tardiness...
Huh...?
Oh, my!
Stay away!
Father
Nightroad!
Don't move!
You'll both join
him shortly.
Radu...
Listen...
Farewell...
tovar-
[Esther] The
Inquisitorial Department!
Found you!
Foul beasts! Your
judgment is at hand!
Damn you!
Radu!
Radu...
No!
Radu!
Owwww.
Father Abel! ...Glad
to see you're alright!
Quickly, get onboard!
We have to leave!
Come on... Let's go,
Your Excellency...
Here...
This way.
Nightroad! I'm not sure how
you managed to survive...
But no matter. Hand
over the demon now!
Nightroad!
Petro!
Haha! There's
no escape!
Hahah!! The sinful
may turn and run...
But they can't hide... Devine
punishment is your reward!
Prepare yourself,
Deputy Enforcer!
Ahh!! My
Screamer!
You'll
pay dearly!
Would you
please be quiet!
Esther!
There's a blanket beneath your
feet... Use it to cover him!
Oh! Right!
Protect the vampire?! Does
your blasphemy have no end?!
Does your cruelty?! This one
must meet with Her Eminence!
That is
a lie!
[Nightroad] No, Chief!
She tells the truth.
Please, give us a
little more time!
This messenger brings
important news.
He must be allowed to speak!
Alright... He'll
talk. But to what end?
[Paula] I need an
explanation, Your Eminence.
You are protecting
a vampire... Why?
Does the Ministry
of Holy Affairs
think it can tame this
one? It tried to kill you.
His protection
is for our own.
I'm afraid you must
do better than that.
You won't drop this despite an
impeding official inquisition?
No.
Oh, Really?
You may arrest
me if you wish.
A tempting idea given
the circumstances.
However, my orders are to take
corrective measures only.
The annihilation
of all vampires...
That is our first mandate...
You're in direct violation.
Thus, until evidence is
proven to the contrary...
The inquisitorial department
will run Cartago.
Evidence... How shrewd...
So now what? Tea?
Later.
We must first mount a rescue
on behalf of Brother Petro...
He was captured by the vampires
and their human sympathizers...
Upon his safe return,
those vampires will die.
As for the traitors, no
leniency will be tolerated.
They too will
be executed.
One other
thing...
Be aware these events
will be reported
to Cardinal Francesco...
And per protocol...
Until such time operations
are complete...
I, Vice Chief, assume
custody of Your Eminence.
Cartago is under
martial law.
My sister has
made her move.
Does that hurt? Forgive me.
I'll loosen your bandage.
No... leave it
alone... Let me be.
But, I...
I'm fine.
Try to keep movement in your
left shoulder to a minimum
until it completely
heals...
I've managed to
stop the bleeding,
but, there's a chance you
could tear the muscle again
if you're
not careful...
But I must say, from this
Terran's point-of-view,
your body has shown
remarkable resilience...
You're very lucky
I might add...
An inch further
to the left
and that bullet would've
hit your heart.
I don't feel
very lucky.
I'd have been better off had
you let me die back there.
At least then
I'd be spared
knowing the betrayal
of my best friend.
Oh, why couldn't
I have just died!
I'll never forget that
look in Radu's eyes!
Stop it! That's an
awful thing to say!
You should rest... I'll go,
but if you need anything,
I'll be right
outside.
You...
I need you.
Keep me
company.
I don't want
to be alone.
All right.
Radu was more than a friend.
He was my foster-brother.
We've been at each
other's side since birth.
He was my only true
friend... Why, tovarish...?
Why did you turn
that gun on me?
Liar!
Radu was right!
I'm a blind fool!
You're not.
I would've willingly
given my own life for his!
No, you...
And yet...
It Turns out that I didn't
really know him at all!
I hate him now- For his
betrayal. For the deceit...
But most of all,
for dying before me!
Oh, Radu... How did I not see
the trouble you were facing?
He must've been
so desperate.
He wouldn't have shot
me. I know that...
He just wanted me
to listen to him.
But I didn't.
Instead I killed him!
If only I'd paid
closer attention.
I know he wanted to
tell me the truth.
We always told each
other everything.
But not anymore. My
tovarish is gone, forever...
I'm all
alone.
That isn't true.
I'm not going
anywhere.
Don't worry... I'm here,
Your Excellency...
For that, I am
most grateful.
[Esther] In a way, you've
brought me one step closer
to realizing
my dream.
A world free
from conflict...
Where vampires and humans
coexist in harmony.
Like many of my kind...
I once believed the myth
that all vampires
were the enemy.
It's very warm...
Your hand, I mean.
Forgive me!
You are
most unusual.
Pardon?!
Well, what I mean is... You're
a very interesting Terran...
Uplifted... That's how I
feel when I'm around you.
Strange sensation...
I like it.
I'm glad... Well,
uh... I know!
Why don't I open the
curtains for you?!
I believe you
mentioned earlier
that you enjoyed the
night view from here.
It reminds of
the Empire...
Although it's not nearly
as beautiful... Or bright...
I miss my home. I wonder
if I'll ever see it again?
I doubt it... And even if I
do, it won't be the same...
Not without
Radu there.
I'm sure you'll make it
back... Your Excellency.
Attempts to locate
Father Abel and his group
have been
unsuccessful.
There've been no
communications?
None.
And... considering Your
Eminence's circumstances...
I will wait.
[Nightroad] Will
he survive?
He'll pull through, Father.
The wound is stabilized.
However, he's too weak
to walk on his own.
Good enough. We'll
leave in the morning.
Our travel may
inconvenience the good earl,
but it beats getting caught.
Don't worry.
I won't slow us down.
Uh... What? Did I
miss something?
Who's
there?!
You should be more mindful of
your surroundings, Flamberk.
Never know who
might wander in.
Puppet Master...
Always a pleasure.
Next- Episode 14.
The Ibelis, Part III.
A Mark of Sinner.
Avert not thine eyes.