Air ships from the
Inquisitorial Department
have begun a
city-wide bombardment
for no apparent reason.
Attempts to make contact...
have all failed.
Why? What can they possibly
think this will achieve?
Lady Caterina... you should
move to safety at once.
This is madness.
Paula and the others
wouldn't take action
against innocent civilians.
I suspect there's more to
this than meets the eye.
I've got to go back.
I've made a decision...
if we're going to move,
now is the time.
You can't! It's
too dangerous!
Don't worry... We have an ally
who can help us get through.
Brother Petro...
if you would?
This task will be difficult.
Not only would you
be our shield...
You would act as our
weapon. Our halberd...
Fighting your
way through...
leading all of us
to the embassy.
Are you out of your mind...?
You're asking me...
God's soldier, to
help a vampire?
I'll make a
deal with you...
After my mission
is completed...
I'll offer up my head as
payment for your service...
I swear.
Your Excellency!
You can't do it!
You can't bargain
with your life!
It's just one
life, Esther.
If my assignment
is successful...
millions of lives
might be saved.
I'm willing to
pay that price.
As Chief of the
Inquisition...
my duty
is clear.
Protect the Church... protect
the citizens of Cartago...
and protect the
lives of the troops
that are under
my command.
Please!
You must...
I haven't
finished yet!
It appears... in order for me
to be able to do my duty...
I have to help
you do yours.
A truce until your
mission is done.
Then your life
is forfeit...
and you A.X. agents...
are under arrest.
My body will be your
shield and your halberd.
Father?
Why are you here...
Puppet Master?
You seemed to be having
a little difficulty,
so I came to
offer backup.
That is, of course,
if you don't mind,
Adept Major...
Flamberk.
Take that... You might
find it very helpful...
these codes will let you
control those toys in the sky.
Oh, yes... one
more little thing.
You failed to kill
the Earl of Memphis
because he was your
friend... didn't you?
You got
sentimental...
and that made
you sloppy.
Damn you...
I'm no toy!
I really rather like that
little show of yours...
What an intriguing
ability...
Of all the unique powers
possessed by vampires...
yours are
especially impressive.
A living
flame thrower...
And you were so eager to
put that power to use...
weren't you?
We did everything humanly...
and inhumanly possible
to get assassins near
the Imperial emissary
and Cardinal Sforza... But
after our cover was blown...
by your crude attack...
we heard nothing from you.
Assuming this wasn't a complete
failure on your part...
why didn't you
activate the Ibelis
when the assassination
attempt went to pieces?
If we had used
the Ibelis...
their deaths would have
looked like accidents.
It has to look like a vampire
killed Cardinal Sforza...
and a human killed the
Earl of Memphis...
otherwise the Empire and
the Vatican won't fight...
and the Order's
plan will fail.
Aren't you exaggerating?
The critical thing is that
the meeting of the emissary
and the Cardinal be prevented..
The Order will be very
displeased with failure.
I haven't failed
yet, Puppet Master.
Do you think you can
clean up your mess...?
I still wonder if
you're capable
of killing the
Empress's envoy...
If you'd skipped the
fancy pyrotechnics
and done that in
the first place...
we could have counted
on the fanatics
in the Empire and the Vatican
to fan the flames of war...
but no, the Empress chose
your childhood friend
as her messenger... and you
just didn't have the guts
to do what needed
to be done.
My personal history
with Ion won't stop me
from carrying
out my mission!
The Fates can certainly
play cruel little tricks
on us sometimes,
can't they?
Very well... I'll trust
you to take care of Ion...
while my new toys take
care of the Cardinal.
More.
[Puppet Master]
I'm rather proud
of my lovely new
Death Hunters...
each one contains a
re-animated corpse...
and not just any corpse,
a vampire corpse...
they have all the
abilities of vampires,
and they're under
my control...
Oh, no!
May I ask you a
question... Esther?
Is it very
important?
Oh, no... I was just wondering
if you've ever driven before?
For God's sake! You can talk
later, for now just drive!
Keep your eyes peeled for a
narrow road on the right!
On the right
you say?!
That's left! Left! Keep
your eyes on the rooooad!
Stop!
That's far
enough... Monster.
Paula...
you saved us.
Clear.
First the airships attack
the city for no reason...
Then these masked creatures
attack the embassy...
What's
going on?
Eminence... we have to
use the Iron Maiden
to counter-attack... it's the
only way to stop the fleet.
No, Sister... an air battle
over the city is too risky...
the civilian casualties
and destruction
would be
staggering.
We've got to
do something!
All the diplomatic
progress you've made
so far on
this trip...
it's all going up in
flames out there!
I've no doubt that's
one of their goals...
to sow the seeds of
suspicion and unrest
among the people
of the world...
by destroying the Vatican
and everything it stands for.
Your Eminence...
tactical analysis
dictates a swift retreat.
The Rosen Kreuz Order...
What are they trying
to do in Cartago?
Everybody hang on!
We've almost reached
the main road!
I'm sorry... you all
right, Excellency?
Yeah.
Radu! Radu, you're alive!
Why?! Why are you doing
this? We were friends!
[Radu] I'll never
accept dialogue
or negoiate anything
with the Terrans...
Ion! Your death must appear
to be caused by human hands...
The sacrifice of your life
will inflame the hatred and
distrust between our races...
Be careful...
Wait... You mean... you're
one of the extremists?
Ugh... he's taken over one of
our Goliath electric tanks...
Yes, I'm afraid I
am... my tovarish.
I'm sorry... I had hoped
I wouldn't have to be
the one who had
to do this...
Look out!
I gave you my
promise, didn't I...
to be your shield
and your halberd...
Don't stand
there... run!
Brother Petro,
you musn't!
Brother Petro!
Excellency!
Excellency...
Oh, no...
Forgive me...
tovarish.
We failed you... how
could this happen...?
Father Nightroad...?
Now Die!
What?!
My god, what's
happening?
It can't be! He's drinking
the blood of a Methuselah!
What...
what is he?
Nooooo!
Did I
get him?
You are food... nourishment...
I will hunt you...
and then I will
devour you...
What kind of
madness is this?
This can't be real,
it can't be...
What are
you doing?
What kind of
thing are you?
No... it's
impossible!
Where
are you?
Coward!
Ha! Found you!
Monster...
Excellency... tell me
you're all right...
Nooo!!!
No, Father...
please don't...
Esther... it's all
right... listen...
Keep away from us!
Keep away! I beg you!
Esther...
God forgive me...
Forgive me...!
We still haven't been able to
locate Baron Luxor's corpse...
of course... in
that inferno...
it's possible that
any trace of him
was completely
incinerated...
we're still in the process
analyzing the debris.
It appears the Order
has extended its reach
into the Empire as
well... I had no idea...
So it seems we have
a common enemy...
we have no choice
but to work together
to destroy this contra mundi,
as you call it, at once...
Before they succeed in
destroying all hope
of a lasting
peace between us.
Agreed...
when you return to the Empire
to make your report...
please relay that message
to her Imperial Majesty
and assure her
of my support.
Your Eminence...
regarding the envoy
you will choose to accompany
me back to Byzantium...
will you consider the
suggestion I made earlier?
She's an excellent choice.
I'm sorry, Esther...
Sorry you had to see that...
Now you know...
how my sins...
...have marked me.
I don't believe that.
Next- Episode 15.
The Night Lords: Part One.
The Return of the Envoy.
Avert not thine eyes.