[Ion] Please, Esther!
You must kill me! Quickly!
This thirst...
it's so strong!
I might drain every drop
of blood from your body...
Before that happens...
Before I kill you...
No! I can't!
You've got to!
Now, Esther!
I can't restrain
myself any longer!
Please!
I don't... I don't want
to hurt you! You must!
Excellency...
It's all right.
You can have my blood.
There's no need to cry.
You can't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
Esther... You can't...
Here... Please...
Esther...
I...
No... I can't! I won't!
Thank you, Esther...
I'll always remember you...
And your kindness...
Excellency!
Stay back!
I'm glad to have met you...
I'll never forget you...
Farewell, Sister Esther!
Don't! Nooo!
It would appear that
I've arrived just in time!
Sorry it took so long... These
corridors all look the same,
so I got a little
lost on the way down...
Father Nightroad!
I knew you'd find us!
Suleyman!
Impossible! This Palace
is under tight security!
Ah! The Duchess of
Kiev! What's wrong?
I'm here to expose you
for what you've done...
Your treasonous acts
against the Empire!
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
The Earl of Memphis and the
Terran you have imprisoned
will be my witnesses... Once
they make a formal report
of what they have seen
first hand, you'll-
Unfortunately, that
will be impossible.
I was handed a report
just before you arrived.
It said they'd been found
dead in their cell.
What?!
Apparently, there was a dispute
and they killed one another.
If you doubt this
to be the truth,
I'm sure we can arrange for
you to examine the bodies.
[Ion] There's
no need.
She can examine our
bodies right now.
Earl of
Memphis! Esther!
As you can see,
we're still alive.
[Ion] I know all
about your plan,
and the heinous crimes
you've committed.
Your guilt and involvement
in killing my grandmother
and assassinating the
Empress is undeniable!
Surrender now and
accept your punishment.
You're the one who needs to
surrender, Earl of Memphis.
For treason against
your own people!
Enough!
No! She
can't be!
How?!
How can she
still be alive?!
It's impossible!
You do not seem
pleased to see
that I am alive,
Duke of Tigris.
What do you mean? Don't
tell me you believe them?!
Why would I want to
kill you, my Empress?
I'm not speaking of the
incident that took place
at the Moldova
mausoleum...
After all, I wasn't
the one who was there.
Let me reveal the
face behind the veil.
The Duchess
of Moldova!
Indeed.
Mirka Fortuna,
Head of the Imperial Secret
Council Duchess of Moldova.
Grand.. mother...
What's going on?
I thought they
had killed you!
I knew that when The
Earl of Memphis returned,
the traitors would
begin to move.
I appointed The Duchess of
Moldova to be my stand in,
and robotic dolls were
placed in the palace.
Suleyman... I never
thought that you
would concoct such a devious
plan... Among my many children,
you were the one in
which I had placed
my highest hopes
for the future.
Just a moment,
my Empress!
I ask again, what
makes you think
I would do something
as treacherous as this...?
I would never conspire
against you or the empire!
I swear it!
Suleyman...
Do you not
remember this face?
It can't be!
When The Ring of Solomon
was aimed against me...
I must admit that
even I trembled.
You can't! You can't
be the Empress!
Esther, isn't that...
It's Seth!
Now, is there still
something that you wish to say?
Yes, there is...
Just a moment ago,
you said that you had placed
your highest hopes in me.
That is true...
Which is why this has
sorrowed me so greatly.
Has it, now?
Such an
outrageous lie.
You... You've never
put your faith in me!
You've never
trusted anyone!
I was devoted and
loyal to your majesty...
But in all the years I've
spent as your humble servant,
you've never... you've never
believed in any of us!
Suleyman! No!
Tell me... Why
did you miss?
Because no matter
how hard I try...
A child can't help but
to love his mother.
Suleyman.
For over 300 years... I
was your humble servant...
And in all of the
time I served you...
Not once did I ever
understand you.
Who are you...? Why do
you do these things?
Why do you hope for
what can never be?
If I knew the answers
to those questions...
I would be
much happier.
Well done. All of you!
You have my gratitude.
Empress!
And Esther...
Uh, yes, what is it,
Seth? OH! I mean Empress!
Seth will do
just fine...
You aren't one of my
subjects. You are my friend.
All right, Seth it
is! You were saying?
Where is the other Vatican
messenger that came with you?
Father Abel? He
went on his own...
Right after we told him all
about The Baron of Luxor...
Radu.
Radu? He's
still alive?
No, he's dead-
But his body is being
manipulated as a disguise...
By a man named Dietrich
Von Lohengrin,
an agent of the
Order of Rosen Kreuz.
What...?!
The self-restoration
function... This is it.
[Nightroad] Step
away from there...
So, you
did come...
I can't allow you to
repair that device.
It will only
cause destruction.
But your people have
used it once before.
Let's make a deal. If you'll
forget this little matter,
I'll take my leave.
Sorry, but I
can't do that.
Kindly leave the Data Cube
behind and step away.
You have an observant eye,
Father... But I must decline..
You see, there's
nothing I hate more
than being ordered around
by someone as lowly as you!
It's useless!
Interesting, isn't it?
I gave this vessel's
blood the ability
to burst into
flame at will.
Hehehe- What
will you do now?
Nanomachine: Crusnik 02.
Power Output 80%, Acti--
What is this?
What's happening to me?!
How interesting...
A vampire that drains the
blood of other vampires...
But it would appear that
you have refused to do so.
And this is the
result of your denial.
How...? How did you
know about that?
How, you
ask...?
Oh, I've heard quite a
few things about you...
Including that
you were once
the enemy of the
world yourself.
Farewell,
Father.
[Seth] Don't you think
you've done enough?
Who are you? What
do you want?
Who me...? I'm
just a simple,
pretty girl who happened
to be passing by.
Seth... Is
that you?
It's been a long time,
Abel... Have you been well?
I'm sorry... But
would you mind...
getting the hell...
out of here?!
You're a...
What is this? What's
happening to me?
It's the power
of Crusnik 03...
Highly focused ultrasonic
energy... The Fire of Sound!
I'm feeling generous,
so I will release you...
But... next time
there'll be no mercy.
For you and the others
who have committed
unforgivable crimes
against my children...
You will know the
wrath of my vengeance!
Sister...
It's been a long 900
years, my dear brother.
[Esther] Thank you, all
of you, for everything.
Be careful and have
a safe journey home.
We will.
Excellency... Take
care of yourself.
Right... You
do the same.
I'll try... Well, I
guess this is goodbye.
I wish you well.
If there's something
you wish to say to her,
then say it... Her kind
age and die so quickly...
There's no guarantee that
you'll ever meet again.
But what should
I say to her?!
Just tell her about
whatever's on your mind.
About whatever it is that
you're feeling... Am I wrong?
Esther!
Excellency!
Let's meet again...
Someday... without fail.
Yes, sir...
Excellency.
So, Abel... Why don't
you stay here with me?
We could live together
as brother and sister,
the way we used to.
[Nightroad]
I am a sinner.
That was 900 years ago!
I'm sure she's forgiven you.
I cannot forgive myself.
I'll never be able to
forgive myself... Ever.
Whatever...
Some things work out
better for both of us
by you living in
the outside world.
Better? What are
you talking about?
I'm saying that he's
still alive, Abel.
I was naive.
He had been fused
100% as a Crusnik.
Dropping him to the Earth
through the atmosphere
wouldn't have been
nearly enough to kill him.
I know that he's...
Where are you going?!
I'm going to destroy him...
...once and for all.
Next- Episode 20.
The Throne Of Roses. Part 1:
Kingdom Of The North.
Avert not thine eyes.