[Mary] We will no longer endure
the tyranny imposed upon us
by the government of Albion.
For centuries we have
labored in silence as slaves,
but no more.
Today we declare
our independence
from your
despotic government.
The following conditions
are to be met immediately
if you wish to
avoid bloodshed...
one... the safety
of every Methuselah
living in the Ghetto must be
unconditionally guaranteed...
two... the government
will offer assistance
in our emigration to
the New Human Empire...
three... the government
will publicly acknowledge
the Methuselan contribution
to Albion's prosperity
and technological power.
If this should become
general knowledge...
Albion will be
at the center of
an international
firestorm of criticism.
Our prosperity was a
house built on sand...
surely you, of all people,
must have known that
without the Queen to hold the
Methuselah's passions in check,
this crisis was
inevitable.
I don't need
a lecture.
The only bright spot in
this whole affair is that
they still haven't succeeded
in capturing the Pope.
If we can get to
him before they do,
we have a chance to
salvage the situation.
I admit I didn't
realize the effect
the Queen's death
would have...
I was unable to
hold the dissidents
back the way
she could.
It's true that the Queen
was a remarkable person.
Still- it's a new age, and the
time when people's obedience
can be dictated by royal
decree is passing...
the tighter you hold the
leash, the sooner it snaps.
Until this star of
hope you've spoken of
inaugurates
this new age,
it remains my duty
to protect Albion...
contact the dissidents at
once and begin negotiations.
As you wish,
my lady.
Impossible... that passage
hasn't been used for centuries!
No one even knows
that it's there...
except for
privileged members
of the house of
Manchester like myself.
Unless... It
couldn't be!
I thank you for
bringing us this far...
but we can proceed without
your assistance from here.
Holiness!!
Your knight is
coming for yoooou!!
Not very subtle
is he...?
Please tell me that we're
not gonna go after them.
Frankly, I think it's
nothing short of a miracle
they stayed with us
this far... besides...
We can probably cover more
ground if we split up.
Right... good
hunting, gentlemen,
and watch
your backs!
Be careful.
[Vanessa] Where the
hell is the Pope...?
How hard can it be to
track down one scared kid?
We've got
intruders!
Looks like Vatican
operatives...
Damn! If they should find
the Pope before we do,
there goes our
bargaining chip!
Search the entire city if
you have to, just find him!
Yes,
ma'am!
We've received a
message from Virgil
requesting a truce and
offering formal negotiations.
Tell him to
go to hell.
We're getting out of this
hole no matter what it takes!
Hello...? Hello?
I have no idea
where I am...
Those people
with the guns...
...were
so angry.
What did I ever
do to them?
It's...
it's a city!
Hey, big kid!
Who are you?
Big kid!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Hey, big kid! Help
me! Somebody help me!
Yay, you're awake!
Angelica!
What are you
doing? Stop it!
I'm sorry... she didn't
mean to scare you,
she was worried
about you.
I'm sure she's very sorry if
she caused you any distress...
Angelica...?
What do we say?
I didn't
mean it...
You're the Pope... Alessandro
is your name, isn't it...?
From the
Vatican?
Uhhh... yes... and you
people... you're all...
Vampires?
Vampires? I suppose you
could put it that way.
You Terrans
call us that,
but we'd as soon you
didn't use that term.
This is our home... the
city of the Methuselah...
where we manufacture
advanced technology
for the kingdom
of Albion.
Oh...
Oh, I see.
Looks like you got
caught in the middle
of our internal
problems... sorry.
Then you're not
part of the...?
You needn't
worry...
we're not members of the
dissident faction here...
we didn't capture you
and you're not a prisoner.
Well, that's good.
So just relax!
Angelica!
That's enough!
Sorry...
We sympathize with
Vanessa's goals.
What gives them
the right...
to keep us locked up down here
in the Ghetto like animals...?
It isn't fair.
I had no idea...
how long...?
Generations...
centuries.
We're the source of
Albion's riches...
and this is how they
choose to reward us.
We're not allowed to leave
this underground world...
From the moment we're
born... our destiny is sealed.
It's wrong... but
what can we do?
But I don't suppose...
you'd understand that.
Please... drink your
tea and rest awhile.
Are you
afraid?
I understand...
so're we.
It's only a
matter of time
before the Terrans stage
a massive attack...
There are so few of us,
we'll be wiped out in no time.
Even if we could
strike back...
they'd just strike
back harder...
and then we
retaliate again...
And so it goes... an
endless cycle of violence...
it just goes on and on
until either they are
destroyed... or we are.
It's great!
Holiness!? Can
you hear me?
Now what?
It was my job to protect the
Pope, and I've lost him...
Wha... what's
this? My hands...
Well, well, well...
I wasn't expecting to
catch such a pretty girl...
Who's there?
Dietrich?!
What are you doing here?
You just can't keep
yourself out of trouble,
can you...
dear Esther?
Just one of the many amusing
things I love about you...
What are you
planning to do?
Me? Why I'm going
to end the world.
I assure you it's no joke...
I couldn't be more serious...
very soon an angel of
death will descend...
to render punishment unto this
stifling, and ugly world.
I've been sent
here to make sure
everything is ready
for the party...
All of the invitations
have been delivered...
now it's up to me to
get things under way.
So goodbye... dear
Esther... hang in there.
Wait!
Dietrich!
Come and get me if you think
you can stop me... who knows?
Maybe you're destined to be
this world's Star of Hope.
Star of
Hope...?
Your name... in the old
language of this land...
it means star.
[Esther] Dietrich!
Dietrich!!!
His name is
Pierrot...
But... he's kinda
sick right now.
So I want you
to bless him...
that way I know he's sure
to get better really quick.
Uhh... but
I can't...
Sure
you can!
You're the most important
man in the world,
right Mr. Pope...?
I'm sure that even
God listens to you,
especially if you remember
to ask nicely and say please.
Important...? Me?
No... I'm
not...
There's nothing...
important... about me at all.
What do
you mean?
I'm nothing... I don't
matter... Everyone...
scolds me and looks
down on me and...
...Says
I'm useless.
You mean there are bullies
picking on you, Mr. Pope...?
I'll give them a spanking
if they don't stop!
Huh?
I think
they're jealous
because you were chosen
by God and not them!
If they give you any trouble...
I'll take care of them, okay?
Chosen by God... you
really think so?
Dear Lord... please bless this
rabbit and make him strong...
Amen.
Oh, thank you!
Thank you, Mr. Pope!
Don't worry, I'll give it some
medicine later, it'll be fine!
Hey,
Mr. Pope!
To thank you... I'm gonna
take you and show you
my special secret place
no one knows about!
Huh...? Ah!
Ho...
hold on!
Angelica! Slow
down! Please!
Hurry up,
slowpoke! This way!
Wait up!
Here
we go!
Huh...? Hold on!
What's this...?
Where
are we?
My secret place!
Come on! Look!
What... What is
this place...?
You like it?
Incredible huh...? I
found it when I was playing!
Ohh, Mr. Virgil knows
about the secret place too,
but he said it
would be all right
if I knew if I
didn't tell anyone!
But I think it's okay
if you know, Mr. Pope!
Is that...
a rocket?
[Vanessa] You sure are a pain
in the ass, Your Holiness.
I could hardly believe
the security alert
when I saw it come in.
What are you doing in here?
Let's go!
What are you doing to
Mr. Pope, you bully!?
Be silent, child! ...This
is none of your concern!
No! Stop it!
Let go! Get off of
me! Get out of here!
I don't care if
you are a child,
if you don't-
Stop it!
Please... stop it, I'll
go... just... don't yell...
I can't stand
yelling...
I get so frightened...
when there's yelling...
I'm always
frightened...
no matter
what...
Don't go,
Mr. Pope!
Oh... I'll be all right...
I promise... don't worry.
I'll pray
for you.
Come on.
I'm sorry I
yelled at you.
Did you hear?
We got the Pope!
Hmm?
Good! Now we have to get those
Vatican spies... Move out!
Yes, sir!
Over this way, sir!
Peter?
The rebels are holed up
in the Security Control
Room in block 2 B.
Now we're even... we
always pay our debts.
So you did all
right here?
Oh, yes... everyone
here accepted us
like we were family.
I really thought we were gonna
be all right in this place...
and then all this
had to happen.
They're not really
bad people!
But when they saw
everybody suffering,
they had to stand up
for what was right!
So please, please sir,
don't hurt them, okay?
I told you, don't
call me sir!
This is too big to
handle alone...
I'm just one man
with a gun...
There's a limit to what
I can do on my own.
But sir...
First, I have to get
the Pope back safely...
after that, I'll see if
I can think of a way
to set things
straight.
Thanks for everything-
you've been a big help.
See ya...
Kate, do you copy...? I've got
the location of the rebel nest.
It's likely the Pope is
probably there too... yes...
Tell the Professor
and have him...
(distant scream)
Look out!
My God...
what are they?
Sir, watch out!
I told you before,
don't call me sir!
Peter!
Stay back!
You kids keep quiet...
you let me handle this...
If can't do
that much...
Then I'll never be able to
face my daughter again.
What's that?
Help me, somebody!
Father Nightroad!
[Nightroad] This will take
you directly to the Palace.
[Esther] But wait...
Father... The Pope is still...
Everyone from A.X. is
here looking for him...
You have to get
back above ground.
Understood?
Next- episode 22.
The Throne of Roses:
Part III... Lord of Abyss.
Avert not thine eyes...