[Kate] Would you like
me to make some tea?
[Caterina] No, thank
you, I'm fine.
The Cardinal Assembly
has concluded
that the Barcelona incident was
committed by James Barrie...
and that he was
acting alone.
[Havel] So that's the
official opinion, is it?
[Kate] They're saying
one man was responsible
for the destruction
of an entire city?
And they expect
people to believe that?
[Wordsworth] It's the
same every time.
Rosen Kreuz always manages to
stay hidden in the shadows.
You seem to be handling all
this very calmly, Professor.
My tears aren't going to
bring back the dead,
but... I miss Noelle
too, she was a...
[Wordsworth] They're still
searching... for Noelle's body.
[Caterina] Tell them
to hurry.
Yes, milady.
Some good has come of this...
since the Barcelona incident,
my brother has realized that
Rome could be the next target.
He'll blame the
vampires, but at least
he's taking steps to
protect the city from attack.
That would explain all the cops
I saw on my way over here.
Wasn't this much
security back in prison.
It's not just about the
terrorist threat... remember.
Archbishop Alphonso D'este will
be arriving from Cologne today.
The first time
in five years.
Oh, yeah...
I remember, the guy who lost
the last Papal election...
Speaking of people with too
much starch in their shorts,
where's Father
Four-Eyes?
[Havel] I wish I
could tell you.
Are you saying
he's missing?!
I'm certain that Abel
is in Rome somewhere.
In his last
communication,
he relayed the details
on The Silent Noise,
and told me that The Rosen
Kreuz would strike here next...
He didn't say where
he was headed... but...
Rosen Kreuz
killed Noelle,
and if Rome really is
their destination...
then it must
Abel's as well...
we've got to find
him, and quickly.
Let's go!
Gunslinger!
Positive.
Damn it... this
is all my fault.
Your Eminence...
you mustn't blame yourself
for what happened to Noelle.
There's no way you could have
known the Order was involved.
Listen, if you
need to cry...
well, isn't that what
old friends are for?
It is... you're one of the few
I've been able to count on
these last ten years... Dear
Havel... I Thank you...
[Esther] Father
Wordsworth!
Hm?
Um... I heard about...
Sister Noelle...
And I- I was
just wondering,
if there'a anything
that I can do?
Of course... with
things as they are now,
I'd say we need all
the help we can get.
Thank you!
It's been a very long
time, Your Holiness.
It's, it's good to see
you again, Uncle Alphonso.
I, Alphonso D'este,
apologize formally
for my extended absence
from the Holy Presence.
And now that I see what a
strong and resolute leader
Your Holiness has
become, I can only say
that it was no mistake
that God moved the cardinals
to grant you His
authority on Earth.
Uncle, please don't...
I'm still just a...
Don't be so modest... It was
in the people's best interests
that you
defeated me...
We also serve those who
only stand and wait,
you know... Francesco, my
boy... Caterina, my dear...
It's good to see
you both again.
Has it really
been five years?
It's been...
a long time.
I'm glad... to
see you so healthy.
As your uncle, I can't tell
you how proud it makes me
whenever I hear about
all your achievements.
You're a credit
to our family.
You're very
kind, sir, uncle.
I'm truly sorry
about our last meeting.
We're all very...
glad you came...
Your compassion
and forgiveness
are more than I
deserve... Holiness.
To express my gratitude, I
am donating two gifts
for the greater
glory of the Church,
gifts that will
impress the people
with the majesty
and power of Rome.
The first is an obelisk,
symbolizing Rome's position as
the keystone of
the faith...
The second, offered in the
hope of perpetual peace,
is a new
bell...
May its resonant tones spread
God's blessings and grace over
this great city and
all it's people.
You did
come back!
Cardinal Caterina
said you would.
Thank heaven I've found you!
Everyone's been so worried...
Come on, let's go tell
them all you're all right.
Father Nightroad?
Father, you mustn't despair...
Thanks to your information,
we're checking
every bell in Rome...
We're making every effort
to protect the city.
What happened in Barcelona,
you can help us make sure
that nothing like
that happens again.
Isn't that why
you came back?
I'm sorry
father...
[Caterina] I can't tell
you how grateful I am.
[D'este] And I can't tell you
how impressed I am...
When the Papal
Election Council
elected Alessandro Pope five
years ago, instead of me,
a man who'd worked side by
side with them for years...
I have to admit,
it was a heavy blow.
I was bitter
toward all of you.
But five years
is a long time.
Too long for a man my
age to hold a grudge,
and more than enough time
to wash away bad blood.
When I said the cardinals
weren't mistaken, I meant it...
I'm glad that I
lost the election.
God has other
plans for me.
Francesco seems
as fiery as ever.
Are you having
difficulty controlling him,
my dear Caterina?
Well, I... that is...
Your brother's zeal tends
to outstrip his judgment.
If he gets carried away
with the Inquisition squad,
he could draw us into an
all-out war with the vampires.
We've agreed that his
department is more effective
when it's used with restraint
and kept in the background.
Perhaps that's
worked up until now,
but it may soon
become necessary
to use them more
forcefully in the future.
What do
you mean?
I understand there is
another power in the world
besides the vampires that
is moving secretly against us.
You know
about that?
The enemy of the
world... correct?
I also know that
one of your people
is dead because of this
group... Very unfortunate.
Please accept my
deepest sympathy.
How do you
know all this?
Just because I've been away
from Rome for so many years,
doesn't mean my feelings
for it have changed.
I try to
stay informed.
I've just received word
from the city police
that they've finished
their investigation.
Every bell within the
city limits, big or small,
has been examined
and tested,
including the ones owned
by private citizens.
They found
nothing
All the bells were
perfectly normal.
[Havel] What do
you think, William?
Uh... Professor?
Huh?
I'm sorry, you
were saying?
What is it, William?
Did you think of something?
We checked every
bell in the city...
But did we check every
bell in the Vatican?
William, I understand the
importance of being thorough.
but you can't mean-
[Havel] The bell donated
by Archbishop Alfonso...
it was just
brought in today...
[Caterina] Good
evening, Abel.
[Abel] I'm sorry...
You have nothing to apologize
to me for... or to Noelle.
You were both just
doing your job.
What do you
think you're doing?
Abel... do you really
intend to quit the A.X.?
How will this make up
for not saving Noelle?
Didn't you come back to
Rome to find her killers?
Did you come
just to give up?
And what about
the promise
you made to me ten
years ago? What of that?
I haven't forgotten
what you said.
Abel, wait!
None of us are guiltless,
but God understands...
and if it's the
killing, remember...
that I've had
to kill too...
Is this really
what you want?
Your Eminence!
Is that Abel?
It's all right,
Professor.
Leave him
alone for now.
[Caterina] So, is it
time for vespers already?
[Wordsworth] Yes, but we can't
allow them to ring that bell.
You mean...
[Wordsworth] Of course,
we have no proof...
But with so much at stake,
we can't afford the risk...
we've got to examine
it before the service.
So who's
on it?
Father Leon has gone on
ahead to try to warn them...
but we must hurry,
your Eminence...
His Holiness and the Cardinals
are already gathering,
if they won't listen to
Leon, they might listen to you.
If this is really your
decision, my friend...
you can still
count on me.
[Caterina] I assume you
two know who it was
that donated
that bell...
This situation
could get very ugly.
[Wordsworth] We understand,
Your Eminence...
but that's
exactly the point...
Out of deference to
Archbishop Alfonso's position,
that bell was allowed
to pass through
all of the security
checkpoints unexamined...
Every other bell in the city
has been sought out,
searched, and inspected.
All those bells are clean...
this is the only one left.
[D'este] I understand that
you received information
about an impending crime,
but sending an inquisitorial
squad to examine belfries?
Don't you think
that's a bit much?
Not at all...
Right now there's no such
thing as too much security.
I think everyone's here except
sister... should we wait?
That Caterina!
She has no respect for
your Holiness's time!
We can't wait
any longer...
Vespers should begin on time,
not at Caterina's convenience.
Well... I guess
you're right...
Your respected Eminences,
in a moment we will begin
the evening's vespers!
We are honored to inaugurate
this evening's service
with the tolling
of a new bell...
...the generous gift of
Archbishop Alphonso D'Este.
Wait!!
Get out of my
way, you idiots!
I have to speak
to his Holiness!
Silence!
How dare you interrupt
the service!
I don't have
time for this!
You've got to let me
examine that bell!
Get out of
here now!!
What do we do,
what we do?!
You there!
You're one of Caterina's
A.X. agents, correct?
[Caterina] Correct.
Your Eminence!
Thank heaven!
I beg your pardon for
this interruption,
but we must
postpone vespers.
I hope you have good reason
for this, dear Caterina.
I assure you, my reasons are
of the greatest urgency.
We need to examine
that bell Uncle's donated
before you ring it.
Are you insane?! How dare you!
Are you suggesting Uncle's bell
is somehow connected
with those terrorists!?
Do you expect
me to believe
that ringing this bell is
going to destroy Rome?!
I'm saying the
possibility exists
and we'd be fools
to ignore it.
What's your proof?
A simple process
of elimination!
Because of our faith in
uncle, this bell
is the only one in the city
that hasn't been examined yet!
This is
utterly absurd!
This is a gift from a
revered Prince of the Church!
Are you trying to imply
that Archbishop D'este,
your own uncle, is
conspiring with terrorists?
I'm implying
nothing of the sort!
It's just that, for the
love of heaven, Francesco,
these people have
destroyed one city.
We dare not
underestimate them!
Please, uncle.
Let go of the rope
and step away
from the bell...
These people are more
cunning than you can imagine,
they may have manipulated you
into doing their work for them!
Come now, you really think I'm
the pawn of some conspiracy?
All of this because of
a harmless bell. Ha!
I'll stop him!
I promise, you're wasting time
and accomplishing nothing...
There! Does that
satisfy your suspicions...
...my dear niece?
Uh... She
didn't mean...
Your actions have
insulted the Holy Presence!
This is blasphemous!
Next- Episode 10. Overcount,
Part II: Lucifer's Choice.
Avert not thine eyes...