[Abel]
Gruesome scene...
[Tres] Fifteen bodies
total. All vampires.
Yes, so it
would appear.
Brain stem,
cervical vertebrae,
and heart- only vital
points were targeted.
All Precisely and
mutually destroyed.
So these vampires just suddenly
decided to kill each other...?
Unable to verify.
Insufficient data.
Confirmed traces of
approximately eight members,
escaped
on foot.
Sister Kate.
[Kate] Stand by.
Assessing the situation...
Requesting permission
to pursue.
[Kate] Affirmative.
Evidence suggests a number
of Fleurs du Mal still
in the vicinity...
Proceed
with caution.
Stop, Tres!
Don't shoot her!
I'm sorry, are
you all right?
You poor,
child.
Were you kidnapped and
brought here by the vampires?
Well, you don't have to
worry about them anymore.
You'll be
safe with us.
Answer: what have you
done to Father Nightroad?
Silence is not an accepted
response. Answer: what are you?
What are
you doing?
I will ask you again. What have
you done to Father Nightroad?
Hello, Abel...
You're late.
Take heart, you have
cause to rejoice...
I've removed all of
the negative elements.
(Abel's scream)
Good. You've
come around...
Professor! Wha- What
happened to me...?
Sounded like you
were dreaming.
Yes...
well...
That little girl's ability
can be quite potent...
Enough so, that Duchess Milan
felt it necessary to send me.
So... What is
it with you...?
Why didn't
you fall?
Fine, don't
talk to me.
Her name is
Elise Wasmeyer...
wanted by the Inquisitorial
Department on charges
of being
a witch...
A witch...? But how?
She's just a child.
The ability she
demonstrated today
is known as
contact telepathy.
She's a mutant-a byproduct of
gene manipulation experiments
carried out
pre-Armageddon.
With a
simple touch
she can manipulate a
person's consciousness,
in many instances
to lethal effect.
The first occurred
two years ago.
Her father shot his
wife, and then himself.
After that, she was
placed in an institution,
where they immediately
began to experience
a rash of
bizarre deaths...
So, you're saying... that
little girl is responsible
for the members of
the Fleur du Mal
turning on each other
the way they did?
Precisely.
And before we turn her over to
the Inquisitorial Department,
it is my job to determine,
among other things,
what she was doing with those
vampires in the first place.
Well, that was certainly
uncalled for...
As I was saying, a sister
of the St. Raquel Convent
will be here shortly
to take you to Rome.
In the
meantime,
why don't you tell us a little
more about your abilities.
Perhaps it would be best
if I spoke to her alone...
Would you mind leaving
us, Professor?
Well, I can't see
what it would hurt.
Besides, I should
probably be there
to meet the sister
when she arrives.
Now behave yourself,
young lady.
No throwing things at Father
Nightroad, understood?
And no throwing things at me,
either! I mean it, young lady!
[Abel] So... You
like cats, I take it.
We used to have
a lot of them...
...back when Mommy and
Daddy were still alive...
I could tell. You sounded
like a real one just now.
Yeah, sure, just like the
dirty old stray that I am?
Now why would
you say that...?
That's not what I
meant at all...
I hate
people...
When people find out about
me... bad things happen...
They always want
to try to kill me,
or lock me way
in a cage...
That's what my Mommy
and Daddy did...
They decided they
didn't want me anymore,
because they thought
I was a freak...
The vampires tried to kidnap
me for the same reason...
In the end, everyone
hates me...
I don't have a friend
in the world...
No, Elise..
that's not true...
Trust me, you
don't want to make
the whole world
your enemy...
Besides, at the very least,
you do have one friend in me...
That doesn't matter.
Just leave me alone.
I'm afraid I
can't do that...
I almost wish I'd never been
born in the first place...
There's no point in my
even being alive...
We are all God's
children, Elise.
Every life has
value in His eyes...
It will be all
right, I promise.
I don't get it, why do
you care so much about me?
Because you remind
me of someone.
Really? Who?
[Kate] Iron Maiden,
calling Gunslinger...
Cardinal Caterina has issued
the following order...
Where are
you going?
The Bathroom. Is
That a problem?
Hold on. I told you,
I'll show you the way.
You're coming
with me? Pervert!
Huh? P-Pervert...?! How could
you even suggest such a thing!
I wouldn't-...
Forget it. I'll
find it myself.
Well, just, come
right back, okay...!
Have you succeeded in obtaining
the girl's deposition?
No, not yet,
unfortunately...
I can't seem to gain
her confidence.
But the goal is to gain
information, is it not?
I fail to understand how
the two are related.
Yes, well... I guess I
shouldn't be surprised...
Stop there.
Any further
attempt to escape
and I will be forced
to terminate you.
[Abel]
Tres, stop!
Father...?
But...
I have my
orders...
Should Elise Wasmeyer make
any attempt at escape,
I have been instructed
to terminate her
without
hesitation...
The girl is a
living weapon,
and cannot be allowed
to remain at large...
She poses far too
great a threat.
These orders...
From Caterina?
Positive... If the Fleurs du
Mal is making continued efforts
to capture
contact telepaths,
we cannot expect this to
be an isolated incident.
So, then in order
to prevent her
from falling into
enemy hands...
Positive.
I'm sorry. But I
can't let you do that.
No, Father! Say
out of his way!
I don't want anyone else
to die because of me!
Whenever I'm around, people
always start killing each other
whether I touch
them or not...
Just let him shoot me! It's
better if I'm dead, anyway!
No, Elise! You can't
think like that!
Krusnik... Your intention
is to fight me?
I cannot
comply.
Good, I was hoping
you'd see things my way.
Positive... therefore, I have
but one course of action...
Erasing Deputy
Enforcer,
Abel Nightroad's enemy/ally
identification signal.
In violation of Canon
Law Article 188
and ministry duty
regulations- Abel Nightroad,
you are hereby subject
to termination.
Father...!
Point-four-three
too slow.
You're wasting
time, Nightroad.
Based on your specs,
you cannot escape me.
What now...?!
Don't
worry.
I'm sorry, but you
left me no choice.
Father...!
It's all
right now.
So, he- he's
a machine...?
Yes... He's all circuits and
wires underneath... An android:
Deputy Enforcer,
HC Tres Iques.
Code Name,
Gunslinger...
That's why your touch
didn't affect him.
I'm sorry... It's
all because of me...
Don't worry, he's equipped
with an auto-repair system...
He'll be up and
running in no time.
He will...?
Excuse me...
Father...?
What happened
here...?
Oh, it's nothing, Sister...
We were just, uh-
We were rehearsing our parts
for the Easter pageant.. Right?
That's okay,
Father.
I'm Sister Louise of
the St. Raquel Convent.
I've come to pick up
Elise, if she's ready...
Thank you, Father.
For everything...
Oh, Hello
Professor...
Care to tell me
what happened?
Well... it's a
long story...
Alright then-
where's Elise
What do you mean? Sister Louise
has already picked her up...
Impossible. Sister
Louise is right here.
We have to hurry! Elise
is in terrible danger!
Fortunately, I
have insurance
against just this
sort of thing...
Thank you, Professor.
I'll put this to good use.
Oh, Father Tres!
Systems restored to
60-percent operational levels.
Search mode
activated...
Pursuit and termination
of hostile elements,
highest
priority.
Heh! Those AX fools
should know better
than to be
so trusting...
So, here we are
again... Welcome back.
Vampire...
You think you're in any
position to judge me?
Do you, you
little monster?
Oh no, you're not
getting close this time.
It wouldn't do well to
have you touching anyone
with that
power of yours.
Let's avoid a repeat of
our last encounter...
We'll make sure you're
safely incapacitated
before we turn you over
to the Rosen Kreuz...
Wha-? Who-?
Rosen Kreuz...?
I can see how they'd find
you a valuable asset.
They just have to
turn you loose
and watch the bodies
start piling up...
Really, a
killer like you
makes the rest of us seem
like gentle little lambs...
That's not true...
I'm not like you.
I never wanted to
kill anybody...
You think that makes
a any difference?
You're still a
murderer, all the same!
But do you know what you really
are? A freak! An abomination!
Neither Terran nor vampire!
No race to call your own.
Not a single friend
in this world!
Trust me... you
don't want to make
the whole world
your enemy...
Besides, at the very least,
you do have one friend in me.
If you're out there
somewhere, help me!
Father, help
me!! Save me!
Dammit... How did
he find us...?
[Tres]
Clear.
No way!
Father
Nightroad.
Go, Tres. Find Elise and
do everything you can
to keep
her safe...
I believe that I feel
a rampage coming on.
Positive.
Dammit, no! What the hell is
happening here?! What are you?!
I am one of God's
many children.
The same as you,
and Elise...
Nano-machine, Krusnik 02...
Power output, 40%. Activate.
You're one of us!
You're a vampire too!
More precisely, I
am a Krusnik...
A vampire that feeds on
the blood of vampires!
No! What are you doing...?!
Make it stop...!
I knew
you'd come!
Careful, you'll
get dirty...
I don't care, I
just wanna hug you!
Everything's going to be
all right now, Elise...
She is a threat... My orders
are to terminate on sight.
Tres, no!
However, my ammunition was
exhausted during the battle...
I am presently unable
to carry out my orders.
Thank you, Father Tres...
At least Until the next time...
Negative... There
won't be a next time.
Mission objective
complete... Returning to base.
He was never out of
ammunition at all, was he...
Next- Episode 3. The
Star of Sorrow, Part 1:
City of Blood...
Avert not thine eyes.