Assassination...
Are you certain?
For some time,
a group of vampires
has been conspiring
to assassinate you
during one of
your travels abroad.
Your upcoming
visit to Cartago,
has provided a
tempting strike-point
in that it's close
to the Empire,
and in an area where
this group is most active.
I strongly advise you to
end your foreign tour
immediately and return home.
I appreciate the
warning, Brother.
However, I cannot
follow it...
The incident which our
uncle instigated in Rome...
It has made the
princes extremely anxious,
which in turn has fostered
unrest among the masses.
This foreign tour, in
place of His Holiness,
is meant to ease that anxiety
and instill confidence...
You know as well as I,
were this visit undermined,
the repercussions would
be devastating...
Your Eminence!
A fire has started
within the bounds of
the Vatican walls.
Sister Esther
is on her way.
A fire? How bad?
At this point,
we're uncertain.
Don't move!
Who are you?!
I told you not
to move, Terran!
Disobey me again,
and you'll suffer.
A vampire?!
You will hold your
tongue until I say speak!
Or I will see you
silenced ever more!
How dare you
defy a messenger
of the
Imperial will!
You said the
Imperial will? Wait!
Does that mean you
were sent by the-
You filthy
Terran!
Damn it! I knew this was
a mistake! I knew it!
Just as I thought!
We should've never
trusted the Vatican!
Wait! No! Come back!
Stop shooting!
Target is lost... Order to
cease fire acknowledged.
Hold it!
Lady Caterina!
Are you injured?!
No.
Ion...
Radu...
There you are...
You're wounded!
What happened?
Did you meet
the Terran?!
Of course not.
You know how they are!
The stupid
Terran started
shooting silver
bullets at me.
Silver?!
This is going
to be painful.
Bear with the
pain, Tovarish
Be still.
A fire erupted
just as I arrived...
So, naturally the
Terrans assumed...
Don't talk.
If not for Her
Majesty's mandate,
I would have
killed them all.
I appreciate
your efforts
regarding the
incident in Venice.
A fruitful
collaboration,
and One that
has established
a valuable tie
with the Empire.
That's not all.
It seems there may be another
window of opportunity
opening within
the Empire.
Someone tried to deliver
a message last night...
Perhaps an
Imperial command.
As in...
From the Empress?
There are numerous
dummy corporations
tied to the
Empire in Cartago.
They own a
zone of buildings
which we suspect
serves as a base-point...
The guise of business
has always offered
a safe haven for
one's evil deeds.
There is little doubt that
last night's intruder
is hiding somewhere
within this zone.
Yes, at any rate, Sister Kate
seems to think so, right?
Well, as far as
you're concerned,
that's beside
the point...
Esther, I need you to remain
alert and ever vigilant.
Please
be patient.
But, why can't
I go with you?
Lady Caterina has you here as
a liaison, not a field agent.
You're going to arrest
the vampire, aren't you?
No, I'm not going
to arrest him.
Then, what on earth
are you going for?
I'm sorry, until I'm certain,
I can't reveal anything...
You'll just
have to trust me.
Father, it's a vampire
you're going after!
There's sure to
be a battle...
Isn't this exactly what
I've been training for
these last five months?
I know how to handle myself!
Let me come!
You need m-
Esther!
All of this is beside
the point. Stay here.
If we need
anything else,
I'll contact you...
Understand?
Cartago
Control Tower...
This is air
battleship, Raguel,
of the Inquisitorial
Department
of the Vatican Ministry
of Saintly Doctrine...
We will be landing at
your airport shortly.
It's not festering.
It looks like the
bacillus in your blood
has started
to reactivate.
Never thought I'd be laid up
over such a minor wound...
I'm as Helpless
as a Terran.
To Methuselah like us,
silver is poison...
You should resign
yourself and rest.
What next, Ion? The
interview was a failure.
I don't see
many options...
You should return
to the Empire
after your
wound has healed.
We are Imperial
aristocracy...
The Empress's
command is absolute.
Therefore, It is my
duty to try again, Radu.
If that's your decision,
then I must warn you.
What is it?
The fire... It's possible
that It may have been set
by hardliners
from the Empire.
Hardliners?
Every regime gets infested
with dissenters...
There is a faction
that doesn't agree
with the current
Imperial mandate...
It's very likely that the
fire was deliberately timed
to when you made
contact with the Cardinal.
In that case, it's more
imperative than ever
Her Majesty's
will is respected.
Nevertheless,
these hardliners
despise the Terrans every
bit as much as you.
Surely you can empathize with
what it is they're feeling.
We serve the Empire,
which deals in absolutes.
It's not in my purview
to disobey a mandate...
This very discussion
borders on treason.
Then I won't
say any more...
By the way,
are you thirsty?
Yes... very much so.
I'll get
it ready.
Greetings... We were ordered
here by Cardinal Medici
to deal with the
attack on your life.
This is the first time
we're meeting face-to-face,
your Eminence... My
name is Brother Petro,
and I am proudly
serving as chief
for the inquisitorial
department...
Accompanying me
is Sister Paula.
Her designation is to
serve as vice chief.
Perfect... graced by the
Knight of Annihilation
and the
Lady of Death...
Dear Brother is being
very cautious, isn't he?
I'm impressed.
Understandable...
Three air battleships;
Even as a show of might,
this is going overboard.
[Petro] I fear the attack
on Your Eminence was
a serious defiance
towards the Vatican.
I believe we
should use the
Inquisitorial Department's
total force
to resolve the
situation.
[Paula] We've pinpointed
a likely location
for the
vampires' hideout.
We will mobilize our
strategy immediately.
[Caterina] Where did you
get this information?
[Paula] Forgive me, but
I cannot answer.
[Petro] Lady Caterina,
your safety
is our
greatest priority.
Please wait at the
Embassy for a short while.
That was
quick, Radu...
Did you remember
the sugar this time?
No offense, but your...
You're a--
Terran!
Enough.
Ion, are you hurt?
Don't worry about me...
This is useless!
We're breaking
off negotiations
with the Vatican...
Their response is clear!
Yes, apparently so.
Kindly lower your blade.
Father!
Terran... Are you
here to arrest us?
You shouldn't jump
to conclusions...
Things aren't always as they
appear... Join your friend.
Thank you!
You deliberately
defied my order.
I- I'm sorry,
Father.
I thought you might
need some assistance...
I was only
trying to help.
No. You were selfish and
exercised poor judgment.
Next time, listen.
Yes, Father.
I beg
your pardon...
Unless I'm mistaken, you are
both Imperial aristocrats...
I am Abel Nightroad,
Special Duty Division,
Ministry of
Holy Affairs.
By orders of my superior,
Cardinal Caterina Sforza,
I have come to offer
you gentlemen shelter.
What?!
I am Ion Fortuna,
nobleman of Moldova,
Earl of Memphis, Empire
of the True Race...
I have been charged
with relaying to you
the Imperial will.
I am Baron Luxor, Radu
Barvon, Imperial Inspector..
We desire an audience
with your superiors.
I see... Since the
purpose of your arrival
is to convey
sentiments of the Empire,
may we consider last
night's visit
a declaration
of intent
to lead the Vatican to
the negotiation table?
Yes... Initially...
However, we've since learned
you are not to be trusted!
Last night my words were
silenced by gunfire,
and today, you barge
into our mansion
uninvited
and hostile!
True, true...
That was a most regrettable
mistake on our part! Hear me.
Everybody! Get down!
What is the meaning
of this attack?!
The Inquisitorial
Department!
What do they think
they're doing?!
Esther, come back! Stop!
It's broad daylight outside!
The windows are
shielded from light!
You needn't worry!
Here we can stare into
the sun's blinding light
without fear
of reprisal.
Of course if either of us
took one step outside,
we'd burn to death in
a matter of moments.
Is there
another way out?
A route shielded
from the sun?
There is an
underground aqueduct
which leads to a small
cave at the coast.
We have a boat
waiting there for us,
prepared for
our escape.
No Radu! You know
we can't trust them!
Your Excellency Earl, I
promise, you are safe with-
Shut up!
You pacify
your prey...
you subdue them with
fake smiles and lies
until you expose
a weakness.
Then you attack
without mercy!
That is the Terran way.
Don't try to deny it!
Ion!
We don't have
time for this...
I believe that we
can trust them.
So, that means all you have
to do is believe in me.
I do. I always do.
Uh, not to rush
you gentleman,
but we are on a
tight schedule...
I believe you should
be leaving now...
Sister Esther will escort
you to Cardinal Sforza.
Me? But, Father...
What about you?!
I shall remain here
and hold off the army.
You can't do that
all by yourself.
Sister, please obey
my order this time.
Protect them well. Their
lives are in your hands.
I understand... Please Be
safe, Father Nightroad!
Father... What is your
reason for being here?
It's a beautiful day,
don't you think?!
I couldn't resist
going for a little swim!
Would you care
to join me?
So... Am I to assume that
you stepped onto that ledge
attempting to
stall our attack?
Even God's soldiers
need exercise, Madame.
Most physicians agree
swimming does wonders
for the cardiovascular system.
I'd lose the armor though!
Restrain him!
[Soldiers] Right!
[Petro]
Vice Chief, halt!
Sir!
He may not
look like it,
but this man is
a Deputy Enforcer.
I'll take
care of him.
Your time would
be better spent
investigating the
mansion. Now, go.
Right.
Tell me your name.
Since you
asked nicely.
I am Abel Nightroad of the
Ministry of Holy Affairs.
So... Are you going to
reveal your name,
or do I have
to guess?
I have many titles...
First and foremost,
I am Chief of the
Inquisitorial Department..
Brother Petro, the
Knight of Annihiliation.
At present, I am searching
for the perpetrator
responsible for last night's
attack on Cardinal Sforza...
If you are a loyal
member of the Vatican,
you should stand
down immediately
and help us with
our holy duty.
[Abel] You and I
share the same goal,
but we have very
different agendas...
Thus, I implore you to leave
the premises so that I may
continue my search
without further hostilities.
Allies must battle so
their foe meets defeat.
So be it.
God will guide me.
My sword will
strike true,
for it is the right
hand of the almighty,
our Lord and savior!
Triumph is mine, for I am
Heaven's flawless soldier!
God's will be done!
As his enemy is mine,
all who oppose me
shall be vanquished
by his righteous aim!
Hell's pit awaits
you, Infidel!
I owe you a debt of
thanks, Nightroad!
I've always wanted to
face a deputy enforcer
on the battlefield.
You've made that dream...
Come true!
Hold him down!
He's mine!
Stand down!
This is a holy duel
between the two of us no one
spills his blood but me!
Interfere, you die.
It's that simple!
Petro... I admire
your tenacity,
but I think we
should stop...
What can we possibly
gain by all of this?
I can tell you're a sensible
man. Let's call a truce.
No one will
think less of you.
Are you that
afraid, Nightroad?
I'm coming for you... Now!
Wait!
Feel God's wrath!
Stop running
and fight me!
Maybe we should take
a break, Petro;
Discuss this
over lunch?!
You've enjoyed
your last meal!
Time to meet your
maker, Nightroad!
Tovarish... Is your
wound bothering you?
I'm alright...
Let's keep going.
What happened to Father
Abel? Did he make it out?
Hold on! Can't we
talk about this?
Petro!
Nice work, sir!
He's dead for sure!
Yeah. From this height, no
one could survive the fall.
He got what
he deserved.
What an idiot!
Silence!
The next man to speak
ill of Father Nightroad
will soon be joining
him in a watery grave.
He was a man who devoted his
life to God and the church.
However inappropriate
his conduct
on the battlefield was,
he deserves our respect.
We will forgive
our fallen comrade
and pray he finds
happiness in Heaven...
But first, we must
hunt down and kill
the cursed vampire who
threatened the Cardinal!
Next-Episode 13.
The Ibelis II.
Betrayal Blaze.
Avert not thine eyes.