Wow!
[Abel] Yes. Beautiful,
isn't it? Simply breathtaking.
And it
should be.
After all, this is the
center of the modern world.
The height of
human existence...
Father
Nightroad...
Do you... Do you think
I'll be able to find my way
in a place
like this?
Oh, you'll be
fine! Trust me!
I'll tell you everything
you need to know!
After all,
this is Rome!
I know this place like
it was my own backyard!
Sorry. No unauthorized
personnel may enter.
Unauthorized? What
are you talking about?
I'm not
unauthorized...
What's
going on?
Oh! Sorry, Esther... Just
a little misunderstanding.
Don't worry about it...
Now look here, Mr. Guard...
I assure you that I
am part of the staff.
Alright, then show me
some identification.
Ah, yes! My I.D.
Just a moment...
Let me get that for you...
Heh... It's uh... Huh...
Now where did I put that
silly thing... Uhh...
I know it's here
somewhere...
Father...
Wait! Don't tell me that you're
starting to doubt me, too!
I'm telling the truth, Esther!
I honestly do work here!
Sometimes I feel
I never stop...
Fine! Whatever! Just
find it quickly, okay?
Everybody's starting
to stare at us...
[Noelle] You never
change, do you, Abel?
Miss Noelle!
I thought it might be
something like this...
I'm sorry if he's
caused you any trouble.
Uhhh...
Right...
You're good...
Thanks,
Noelle...
It's nice to
meet you...
You're Sister Esther
Blanchett, I presume?
Uh, yes
ma'am!
I'm Sister Noelle Bor... A
colleague of Father Abel's.
You're in
the AX?
Don't let her
appearance fool you.
Miss Noelle is
quite powerful!
People say that her
special Heel-Drop Attack
can bring
down a bull!
Abel!
It was a joke! I'm
kidding! I'm kidding!
Come on... Lady Caterina
is waiting for us.
Right!
Hey! Hold on a
minute! Wait up!
[Catarina]
Admirable work on your
latest mission,
Father Nightroad.
I'm looking forward to
reading another one
of your
interesting reports...
[Abel] Uh, yes!
Of course!
And Sister
Esther...
Yes,
ma'am!
Excellent job. Thanks
to your involvement,
the matter in Ishtvan
has been settled...
You have my
gratitude.
Thank you,
ma'am...
but, honestly I don't think
I did much of anything.
Well, that's true. But I
was there to cover for you,
so everything
worked out fine.
Working with Father Nightroad
can be quite challenging,
to say the least. The Ministry
of Holy Affairs welcomes you.
Be strong in your endeavors
for the sake of the world.
Yes. I will do
my very best.
Pardon me,
Miss Caterina...
What did you mean
by challenging.
You make it sound like
I'm a useless burden.
Well, of course
you're a burden...
Surely you've realized
that for yourself by now...
But... You've got
it all wrong!
That's a terrible
thing to say!
It's the circumstances
that I'm placed in
that are to blame for all the
trouble. It's not my fault!
So, by that
rationale,
you're saying that we are the
ones getting you into trouble?
[Abel] Miss Caterina!
Please! Don't say that!
Father Nightroad!
You shouldn't speak to Her
Eminence in that manner!
It's all
right...
[Catarina] Doing your
best, you say?
Does doing your best
include losing your ID?
[Abel] Who told
you that?
[Catarina] Security
made an inquiry...
Please Abel,
you're an adult.
Let's try a
little harder
to keep our things
in order, shall we?
[Abel] Uh...
Yes, ma'am...
Your Eminence.
With your permission,
I'd like to give Sister
Esther a tour of our facility.
Very good... Father
Havel? Join them.
Inform the Professor on
the matter we discussed.
As you wish,
Your Eminence.
[Esther] Do you think
it was all right
to leave Father Nightroad
behind like that?
[Havel] They haven't seen
each other in quite a while,
so I'm sure they have
a lot to talk about...
If we had
more time,
I would have taken you
on a tour of Rome.
It's really a beautiful
city. But I apologize...
Oh, no! That's
not necessary!
I really want to focus
and learn my job quickly
so I can do
my part!
That's great!
Excellent!
I just thought
that I...
that I should
devote myself
so I could help make
a difference...
The training you'll go
through is quite rigorous...
We're going to push you hard,
so don't fall behind, okay?
Right!
[Noelle] The Ministry
of Holy Affairs
governs the Vatican's
foreign diplomacy...
Simply put, it's The
Dept. of Foreign Affairs...
Our task is
difficult,
with the current world
condition being so unstable...
When a situation cannot
be resolved by words,
The Special Operations
Department of The Ministry
of Holy Affairs is
called into action.
More commonly known as
The AX. In other words, us.
Professor? Professor,
are you here?
Again...
Same as always...
[Havel] William, we're
letting ourselves in...
You've made quite a mess of
this place, haven't you...?
Are you all
right, Professor?
This place is...
it's so...
I- I'm sorry, you...
you startled me!
There, there...
quite all right.
William Walter Wordsworth
at your service...
or simply Professor,
if you like...
I actually do have
teaching credentials
at the University of Rome,
for what they're worth...
but I find the students
there to be so bothersome,
that I generally-
Uh, William...
Ah, more guests!
Vaclav! Sister Noelle!
You haven't changed
one bit, Professor...
It's been a long time.
Good to see you.
And who is this you've
brought with you?
I don't believe I've
seen your face before...
Of course... how rude of me.
Sister Esther Blanchet...
I'm new here. I've only
just been accepted
into the Ministry of
Holy Affairs.. So I, uh...
Ah! A newcomer! Welcome!
I am William Walter...
Wait... I just said
that, didn't I?
If I may... I need
to speak to you...
We seem to have a problem
concerning Father Watteau...
Hugue is making
trouble again?
The opposite... Actually,
he's been far too quiet...
It's been almost four months
since we last had any contact.
Well, I think
we all know,
once he sets his
sights on something...
that boy becomes blind
to everything else.
Sorry. Father
Hugue de Watteau...
One of our fellow
AX members...
I'm sure you'll have a
chance to meet him someday,
but right now...
...well, he seems to have gone
missing for the time being.
Oh, that's awful!
You think... something
bad happened to him?
For his sake... I
certainly hope so.
At any rate, it occurred to
me you might have an invention
of some sort that
could be useful
in a situation
like this...
I know just
the thing.
I- I see, William... but
what in heaven's name is it?
I thought you'd
never ask!
As you may know,
all substances emit
characteristic low
frequency magnetic waves.
This is true of biological
organisms as well.
Every living
thing resonates
at a unique
infrasonic frequency-
a bio-magnetic
signature, if you will...
So... I've created
this simple device
which can analyze and identify
these various signatures,
and thereby determine a
person's exact location.
I'm not quite sure I
understand it... but, okay.
I think it would be best
if we stand back...
Wha -What's
happening?
Well, this is odd... The last
time I tested this machine,
it worked
splendidly!
I was able to catch Father
Abel buying some sweets
while he was
on duty...
Please-for the
love of God!
Enough... silence
that horrible thing!
I thought we were under an
electro magnetic wave attack...
but it seems this was
your doing... Professor.
Well, Hello,
Sister Kate...
It's a lovely
afternoon, isn't it?
How- How have
you been?
Drop the act.
You're not charming your
way out of this one...
What was that
awful noise?
Were you actually trying to
knock out my radar? Is that it?
But that's absurd.
The Iron Maiden's radar
wouldn't be disrupted
by something
like this...
Don't test me,
William! I mean it!
What the?!
That woman!
She's... I can see
right through her!
This sort of thing
seems to happen
far too often
with you.
Ever heard
of reason?!
I would expect a gentleman of
Albion to have more sense!
So, this is
the first time
that you've seen Sister
Kate, I take it?
No need for alarm.
She's also an AX Member...
She serves as captain of
the battleship Iron Maiden.
So is that where
she's from? Albion?
Yes, that's right.
As a matter of fact,
Sister Kate and William both
hail from Albion originally...
They've known each other
for a very long time.
I'm sorry if the
Professor's carelessness
caused you any
trouble today...
Since he refuses to admit
the error of his ways,
I've sent this special tea as
an apology on his behalf...
Signed, Sister
Kate Scott.
Delicious!
One of the few real perks
to being an AX member.
Kate's herbal teas are
simply to die for.
Tell me,
Esther...
Have you ever been to
the Kingdom of Albion?
If I asked something
I shouldn't have,
I apologize But,
that wasn't the impression
I was getting from you...
What I mean...
is that I'm able to see
people's feelings...
You can see
people's feelings?
[Noelle] I see them the way
that most people see colors.
That is my special
skill as an agent...
Albion's where my father's
from. I've heard about it...
But... I'm afraid I've never
actually been there myself...
I've always imagined
what it must be like...
I try to picture
it in my mind,
the way my father
must have seen it...
In the not so
distant future...
you'll see Albion
with your own eyes.
I don't even know
anyone there...
I know it's silly,
selfish even,
but I'd still
like to see it...
I can sense hope in the
blue that surrounds you...
I know... It
will happen.
Did you
say hope?
I don't understand...
Why, father?
You have to
ask? Really?
Well, it's... it's because
I am your friend...
Why was I just thinking
about Father Nightroad?
What's the
matter, Esther?
Nothing! I just... I was just
thinking that Father Nightroad
and Lady Caterina
seem to be very close.
I wonder how long they've
known each other...
Ahhh... I think
they've been acquainted
for quite
some time.
They knew each
other before
the AX was even
established, I believe.
I don't actually know
all of the details...
Oh really?
That's Interesting...
[Noelle] You just can't leave
him on his own, can you?
That Abel...
Sister?
Lady Caterina is very
strong. Very certain.
I don't think she has any
reservations or fears...
Yes... There's
no doubt...
The Rosen Kreuz
were the one's
manipulating the
entire incident...
Contra Mundi.. The
Order of Rosen Kreuz...
Lady Caterina...
It's always the same...
Nothing has changed...
Nothing... and 10
years have passed...
Who are you?
Someone who's come to save
the lives of humans...
I'm here to
protect you...
Sister Noelle! Noelle!
Where am I?
[distant sobbing]
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry!
And just...
who... are you?
A friend! I'm Sister
Esther Blanchett...
I didn't mean
to frighten you.
Are you... A- Are
you all right?
Uh... Yes, ma'am...
I'm all right...
Thanks... I'll be
just fine... Really...
Are you lost? Did
you wander out here
and now you can't
find your way back?
No, not
exactly...
I know! Why don't
you come with me?
Right! Shall
we go then?
We're not going to find
our way out of here
just sitting
around now, are we?
There's got to be
someone around here
that can give
us directions.
But either way... It's nice
to know I'm not alone...
Anyone can get lost in
a big place like this!
I'm sorry...
but... Well- I- uh...
Yes...?
What is it?
It's just... Well, I'm...
I'm not lost... exactly...
I'm sorry... Actually,
I uh... I ran away...
You ran away?
My brother was... yelling
at me... Scolding me...
I was scared...
and sad...
And that's why... you
were hiding and crying?
I'm sorry...
Your brother must be
a pretty scary guy.
He is! But he's a
really good person!
He's respected, and wise...
He's powerful... and strong...
Nothing at all...
like me...
My brother... He just hates
me... I know he does...
I don't think your
brother hates you at all.
In fact, I'll bet
he's worried about you.
You're lucky to
have someone around
to look after
you like that...
He wouldn't do it if he
didn't care about you...
You... You really think
so...? That's why he does it?
I know it.
Sister Esther
Blanchett.
Father Tres!
Thank goodness!
What are you
doing here...?
Sister Noelle Bor has
been searching everywhere
in an attempt
to locate you.
Sorry... I went
to the washroom
and I sorta
got lost on my way back...
Is that why
you're here?
Were you out looking
for me, as well?
Positive. I will guide you
to where Sister Noelle is.
Now Please
accompany me.
Of course! Thank
you very much!
Holiness... I request
an explanation
as to why you are outside
at this location...
According to today's itinerary,
you should be at work.
Uh, well, I was... I'm sorry.
Holiness? But
that means that...
Wait... Oh, no!
Are you The Pope?!
Positive.
Sorry! Sorry
about all that!
I didn't lie to
you or anything!
I can't believe that I was
dragging around The Pope.
Sister Esther... Sister
Noelle is still expecting you,
and may even be searching for
you. Please accompany me.
Oh! Right!
My handkerchief!
Let him keep it.
Noelle! Is it true? Is Esther
really missing? Where was-
Here I am!
Sorry! I got lost
on the way back!
Esther! I was starting
to get worried...
Esther! There you are! I'm
so glad you're all right...
To be quite
honest with you,
I get lost on these
grounds all the time...
The layout here is
just so complicated...
But when we arrived
here earlier,
you told me you knew Rome
like it was your backyard...
Uhhhh... I don't
remember saying that...
Father Abel Nightroad...
Requesting damage report.
Abel and
Sister Esther...
Next, Episode 6:
Sword Dancer.
Avert not
thine eyes...