It deflected the blast
from my main cannon...
like it was nothing!
What just happened?!
It was a barrier...
It seems that those small
devices circling the ship...
can emit some sort
of force field.
That means any attack
we make on that thing
will be completely useless!
Hey, Father Hugue's pretty
good with that thing...
Look at him... Those machines
can't get a lock on him.
I see... They're drawn
to an electrical charge...
The devices aren't programmed
to react to living organisms...
Hold on a second...
Are you saying...
those things don't consider a
human being to be a target?
Yes... That's precisely
what I'm saying.
That just made things
a whole lot easier.
Let's see how
you like this!!
What annoying
little insects...
Hey! What
the hell...?!
They're sending
out reinforcements!
This is looking grim...
How are we supposed to-...
[Radio] This is
Colonel Mary Spencer
of the Kingdom
of Albion...
We will support you from
the ground VIA radio.
That airship
is utilizing
a powerful magnetic
defense system.
It's a Methuselah design.
It's called the Aegis Shield.
Aegis...?
I see... That's why my main
cannon had no effect on it...
So... This shield...
It's designed to be
impenetrable from every angle.
Then I assume it has
to be deactivated
every time the
ship attacks?
That's right.
That's it! We just need to
hit him when he turns it off!
Just before
his next attack!
According to the data... That
window's less than a second...
And the only areas
that are unshielded
appear to be the ship's
front and underside.
[Brother Petro] Leave
that barrier to me.
Those faithless villains
that attack our citizens
will not be forgiven!
God's will be done!
Sister!
What is it?
Sister Esther... Please,
go to him. Right now.
Go to Father
Nightroad.
My dear brother Abel
has been killed...
This was your
doing... Cain...
What now...? What are
we to do, my brother...?
[Caterina] I hope that the
peace treaty between us
will last for
generations to come...
[Asta] That is the hope
of my people, as well...
Aside from
that...
I understand that
one of your priests
was killed in
Londinium...
Yes... The one that aided
you in your investigation...
Father Abel Nightroad...
died last night...
Please tell
me, Duchess.
What has become of the Earl
of Memphis? Where is he?
The Earl...?
He's...
Yes... The Day of
Judgment has come...
This planet's infestation
will be consumed by fire...
Their punishment will make way
for the new world order...
And soon... The all
encompassing power that
we of the Order of Rosen
Kreuz seek to obtain...
Will consume all
life... into the void...
Just as our lord
desires it to be...
Damn! At
this rate,
the next attack could break
through our stronghold...
Report! What's
your status?
Petro and Paula
are standing by
on the Tower Bridge,
awaiting the signal.
[Leon] And I'm
providing support
from the roof near
the riverside!
Right! We're
counting on you...
All right... The
time has come...
[Kate] I have detected
and verified a variation
in the electrical
pulse of the airship.
Iron Maiden,
charging main cannon...
[Mary] The pulse is slowing!
He's getting ready to fire!
The electro-magnetic
wave levels
around the airship
are dropping!
Now!!
What!?! What the
hell's going on?!
No!! Impossible!!
All right!!
...What?
Petro...
0-400... Gunslinger...
Executing the Duchess
of Milan's top order...
Mission commencing.
Mission completed.
Father Tres!
What are you--?
Incoming vital signs confirmed.
Distance: 57.89 meters...
Excuse me...
Father Tres!
Esther... That is
you name, isn't it?
Why are... What are
you doing here?
Can't you leave Father
Nightroad in peace?
Oh, not just yet... Abel and
I are soon to become one.
After all, we two... were
originally one being...
We share the exact
same genetic code...
And now we will become
one once again...
Together, for
all eternity...
Joined, we both benefit.
I get a complete body...
and Abel gets to
enjoy an existence
without suffering or
distress... By becoming one,
he will be able to rest
peacefully within me forever...
I don't understand...
What are you?
I am a Crusnik,
my dear...
A being who is in
need of nothing...
while at the
same time...
a being who is in
need of everything...
Now then...
Abel...
Stay away
from him!
No... leave
him alone!
Father...
Did you two boys get
into another fight?
Why don't you
ignore him, Abel?!
He's just trying
to get to you!
Seth...
So tell me- just what did
you do this time... Abel?
Ashes to ashes...
and dust to dust...
I wish all those annoying
fools down there
would disappear forever!
The Earth would be
better off
without them!
That's a horrible
thing to say! Horrible!
Abel! Those people
down there are humans,
just like us!
No! They're not
like us at all!
We're just experimental
test subjects! Lab rats!
You, me... even Cain and Seth!
We're all expendable goods
created for the Mars
Colonization Project!
So knowing that's who we are...
Tell me what kind of a future
do you think we can
possibly have?!
Abel...
I don't know- but I'm happy...
I'm happy to have been born
into this world
at all, brother.
Cain...
It really doesn't matter
where you're from...
If your will is strong...
you can make the future
whatever you want it to
be... So, tell me...
Just what kind of future
do you want, Abel?
I want...
I want a future... where...
Father, you...
You would continue
this battle
until the end of time,
wouldn't you...?
In the name... of the Father,
Son, and Holy Spirit...
May eternal blessings
be upon you...
Behold, the new
Queen of Ablion.
A prayer for the sake
of a new world...
A new world...
a place where we can all
live together in peace...
Amen.
Do you intend
to accompany me?
I will destroy him...
I'll pursue him until the
end of time if need be...
Are you prepared
to do the same?
The Contra Mundi...
It's him... Now that I
know that he truly exists...
I'll fight against him,
as well... At your side...
No matter what fate
or dangers await me...
Fine... So be it...
Then we will see this battle
through to it's bitter end.