Abel! Please refrain from
speaking with your mouth full!
Okay, here's the plan... The
first thing we should do
is concentrate all our
efforts on devising a way
to clear Earl
Fortuna's good name.
At present, we can't
risk being seen in public,
much less gaining
an audience
with Her Majesty,
The Empress...
Excellency, you should really
try to eat something...
Some fruit, perhaps. Or
maybe something to drink...
Even we Methuselah require
rest and nourishment, Earl...
You need to eat to gain
your strength back.
Just leave me
alone. All of you...
My strength is none
of your concern.
It's none of my
concern, you say?!
Asta, what are
you doing...?
Now listen to
me... You brat!
Duchess!
I took you in because The
Empress ordered me to!
Don't pretend for a second that
I actually care in the least
about you or your health!
Do You understand me?!
Little
Dobitoc!
Excellency!
An imperial noble crying
in front of others...
It's pathetic
and disgraceful.
It makes me wonder
just what exactly
the Duchess of Moldova has been
teaching you all this time...
How dare you speak ill of
my grandmother like that?!
No one will insult
her in my presence!
Understand me? No
one! Not even you!
Tell me something... What
do you think she would say
if she saw you behaving in the
manner that you are right now?
You're right. I
apologize, Countess.
Your Highness...
No more... I'm
done crying.
Now then... It's about time
for us to get going... Father?
Huh? Going?
Going where?
The Imperial Council meets at
the palace in the morning...
I assume they will make
an official announcement
regarding the assassination
of The Duchess of Moldova.
When the opportunity
presents itself,
we'll file an appeal to
declare The Earl's innocence
and clear his
name immediately.
Ahh, I see. So I'll be joining
you as a witness, then?
Father? Should
I come, too?
Esther...
I was hoping that you
would accompany me...
I have an errand that I
need to run in the city.
Well...
Of course.
Watch yourselves out there.
Be careful. That reminds me...
I understand that
you've broken your sword.
I've informed Chandall
of the situation.
He'll supply you
with one of mine.
Oh- That's very kind
of you, Countess.
[Asta] Father! Let's go!
Oh! Alright- Okay! Wait, Asta-
I'm not finished yet! Waiit!!
My goodness! Look at this
city! It's breathtaking!
Tell me... Which one of
these colossal structures
does she live in?
It's not she,
it's The Empress!
We'll meet with
Her Majesty there...
Inside the
royal palace.
Really?!
That's magnificent!
What an amazing building!
A palace like that one
must've cost her a fortune!
Keep it down! Someone's
going to hear you!
Oh, stop being so
nervous, will you...?
With your beauty and
my eloquent tongue,
nothing could possibly go
wrong! We're unstoppable!
The false accusations
against The Earl of Memphis
will be withdrawn
immediately.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
I'm starting to think
I'd be better off if
I'd left you back home.
Well, without me, your
story about the messenger
from the Outer World would
lack credibility, wouldn't it?
And besides... With
the two of us here,
Sister Esther will get
the chance to watch over
The Earl of Memphis
for a bit longer.
You're the same as ever.
Huh?
You just wanted those two to
be far away from any situation
that might possibly become
dangerous, didn't you?
What's that? What are
you talking about?
Don't try to
deny it...
Just remember, you can't
keep trying to shoulder
all of the responsibility
yourself. You'll never last.
You're right... I'll
bear that in mind.
But I understand
your concerns...
That girl reminds
me of myself...
The way I
was before.
Her passions cloud
her sense of duty...
If left alone, she may
do something reckless.
It's been a long
time, Lady Astaroche.
About four years,
I believe.
Lord Suleyman!
Hey... who's
this guy?
Lord Suleyman,
Duke of Tigris...
Deputy, Imperial
Secret Council.
My Lord! It's good
to see you again!
You can just call me
Suleyman, my Princess...
Or perhaps you can
call me Uncle,
like you did in
the old days.
All right.
Wow! I don't think I've seen
you blush before, Asta!
You must
be nervous!
Who's this? A
new servant?
Your taste in them
seems to have changed.
Yes, you're right! I just
hired him this past month...
But he doesn't listen
and has difficulty
attending to his duties.
What?! How rude!
When have I ever-
I'm incredibly
embarrassed.
Don't be... By the
way, Princess...
Do you know the agenda
for today's meeting?
I've heard there will
be an announcement...
concerning The
Duchess of Moldova.
It seems that she was
attacked and murdered
in her own mansion by
unknown assailants.
I've also heard
that her grandson,
The Earl Count of Memphis,
was there, as well.
Yes, that's right.
Several eyewitnesses can
place him at the scene...
And it was said... that he
was accompanied by two Terrans:
one male, and
one female.
Terrans?
Yes. Further
investigation has revealed
more pressing
information on these Terrans.
It seems that they are
from the Outer World,
and that they
have ties
with high-ranking
members of the Vatican.
We're in a very delicate
and serious situation.
Someone from the Vatican
has assassinated the head
of the Imperial
Secret Council.
This news will most
certainly develop into
an international incident.
Before the conclusion
of today's meeting,
I expect to be called on to
head a full investigation.
With that authority,
I may soon require
your assistance in
this matter, Princess.
My assistance...?
You are one of the few among
us that have had experience
dealing with the
Outer World...
The Empress knows
of your expertise,
and has great expectations
for you regarding this matter.
Wait a minute, I don't...
I couldn't possibly...
It's just about
time to begin.
I must be going... Until
next time, my lady...
It's time for us
to get going, too!
Right!
Announcing Her
Majesty, The Empress!
Greetings, representatives! My
beloved children of the night!
Excellency...?
Uh... to be honest...
this is the first time
I've ever actually been to
this part of the capital.
We Methuselah only reside on
the west side of the city..
Whenever the Terrans need
to conduct any business,
they always come
to see us...
There's never a need to go to
the east side... Understand?
I see... Don't you
think it would be better
if we went back
to the Duchess'?
No... We're close. We
have to be... Come on.
Excellency!
Do you really think Minmarl
had something to do
with what happened
at the mansion?
The timing of the murders and
our return was too precise...
They must have had some
inside information
to plan something
like that.
I just... It's so
hard to believe...
Minmarl was a servant
of my grandmother...
He works for himself now...
But he would still show
his loyalty and
respect to my family.
Then why would
you suspect him?
Well, because...
Because we live in a world
of lies and deception...
Am I wrong?
Sir, I...
If you don't wish to
accompany me any longer,
you're free to go
back to the mansion.
No! I can't just
leave you alone!
I need to be
here for you.
It's not like you're my
servant or anything...
You have no obligation
or duty to obey me.
That's why you think
I'm here...? My duty?
Here. Let
me see that.
Esther! What
are you doing?
Now you just leave
everything to me...
I'm probably much more
accustomed to reading maps
than you are, anyway,
Your Highness...
Esther...? Do you
know how to read
the written language
of the Empire?
No. Not
really...
Hey! You there!
You two
look thirsty!
Would you like some
tea? It's really good!
So... The tea is 20
akuche per cup...
But I'll give you a deal.
Two cups for thirty!
What do
you say?
No thank you... We're
actually very busy right now.
Oh, come on! I just
know you'll love it!
I bet your date
would appreciate it!
Wait! You think
we're on a date?!
Well of course you are!
You look great together!
I'm actually
kinda jealous!
What an uncouth and
insolent little girl.
Wait... How
much was it?
Two cups for
30 akuche!
Here. And I don't need
the change. Keep it.
Thank you!
Here you
go, Esther.
Thank you
very much!
By the way, would you
happen to know where we are?
We're looking for the shop of
an apothecary named Minmarl.
It's supposed to be in
this area somewhere...
Do you mean Mr.
Minmarl, the merchant?
His shop's
just ahead.
Would you like me
to show you the way?
Yes! That would
be wonderful!
Did you hear? This
girl's going to help us!
This girl?! What a
rude way to address me!
I have a proper name,
you know... It's Seth!
Now that you know it, stop
calling me this girl!
[Seth] Come on!
It's this way!
Through here!
It's a shortcut!
This is it!
Excellent.
Thanks for all of your
help, little girl...
You can go
home now.
What?! Are you
always this rude?
I told you, my
name is Seth!
Why do you keep
calling me girl?!
You know, it must be
really hard for you
to date someone
like him!
Let me give you
some advice...
Choose your boyfriends
very carefully!
You've got some nerve
speaking to us like that!
Go on now! Get
out of here!
Okay!
Goodbye!
I can't believe her! Who does
she think she is, anyway?
That scent!
Is it...
Excellency?
Hold on tight,
Esther.
Oh, no!
Minmarl...
Excellency!
Look! He's
still alive!
Minmarl!
Just hang in there, Minmarl!
Can you hear me?
Say something!
Stay with
us, Minmarl!
Who did this to you...?
Tell me, please!
Forgive me... my
young... master...
I never dreamed
that... that he...
Was planning...
planning to murder her...
Or I... never
would have told him.
Who are you
talking about?
Who was it? Tell me!
My Lord, please!
Tell me who killed
my grandmother!
The Baron of Luxor...
Radu... Barvon.
Minmarl!
That's impossible....
Radu is dead... It can't be!
I saw him die! No!
There's just no way!
He's lying... Why
would he tell me that?
Excellency!
Esther...? What's wrong?
Are you feeling alright...?
What happened
to you?
You're wounded...
Just hang in there...
I'll take you
to the hospital!
No! You musn't!
You can't! It's
too dangerous...
I don't care! I have to
save you! Esther! Esther!
Looks like you're
in a little trouble.
Can I lend you a hand?
How did you...
What are you doing here?
Esther, no!
Oh, no! Quick!
We've got to hurry!
We need to stop the bleeding
first... Hold her up for me.
Medicine...?
Who are you?
Who, me...? I thought
I already told you.
I'm Seth.
Just a simple,
pretty little girl.
Next: Episode 17.
The Night Lords: Part Three.
The Island of Her
Darling Children.
Avert not thine eyes.