Don't worry...
I'm here, Your Excellency.
[Radu] Has she told
you a Methuselah...
was the killer of
her adopted mother?
Strange, isn't it...? That
she would choose to withhold
such a very important part
of her past from you...
[Esther] No! When
I look at you,
I don't see some
blood-crazed monster.
I've never once thought
any less of you
for being
who you are.
She's here!
On our way!
We must hurry to the
Moldova Mausoleum!
Where?!
From where will
you attack?
What should I do...?
What should I do?!
Wait! What's he
saying...? "The Empress...
...will die!"
Radu!!
The Earl
of Memphis!
You traitor!
How far you have
fallen, Ion.
Once revered. Now nothing
more than common, rebel filth.
No! I'm...
An incompetent traitor!
You will die on this spot.
Remembered only for
being the inept fool
who tried to assassinate
the Empress...
And I, the hero
who killed you.
You... You're
despicable!
Farewell...
My tovarish!
Ion...
Get away.
You must Stop...
the Empress...
This
is...
...a
trap!
It's... The...
O... The
Order...
[Dietrich] That's
enough talk, Flamberg.
Oh, you're such the
sentimental one.
I kept you waiting,
Earl of Memphis...
Radu?
Excellency!
Esther!
Run! Get
out of here!
Esther!!
This is hardly the time to
be worrying about others.
Enough!
These two have
information that I require...
Place them
under custody
and take them to the
Palace for questioning.
I'll deal with this
matter personally.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Empress, please wait.
Is there a problem,
Baron Luxor?
No, Majesty.
Forgive my outburst.
No! You don't understand!
Release me... Now!
You're wrong...
This is a conspiracy!
Empress, someone's
trying to kill you!
Silence! You rebel scourge!
No! Esther!
Stay put!
You mean we should
abandon them!?
No. The Empress
needs them to talk,
so they won't be
executed right away...
Calm yourself, Father.
Only our patience can
save those two now.
The Moldova mausoleum
should be visible soon.
It can't be...
Empress!
She's dead...
All is lost now!
Our Empress is no
longer of this world...
How could this
have happened...?!
What will become of the
Empire in her absence?
Feels strange, yes?
When something that has
existed since one's birth
suddenly disappears,
it can overwhelm.
However, we have long since
crossed the point of no return.
It is my sworn duty to
guide this nation onward
for the preservation
of all Methuselah.
Where do we stand?
The Palace is now
under strict guard...
The whereabouts of The
Duchess of Kiev are unknown.
Though I am certain
there is no way
she can possibly intervene.
What of The Earl of
Memphis and the Terran?
They are being held
in the dungeon,
which is heavily patrolled...
The inquest has not yet begun.
It could prove
quite troublesome
if they are
allowed to talk...
You know we cannot
afford to have the nobles
become suspicious
of us in any way.
Not to worry. Dead
men do not speak.
They mustn't die...
at least not yet.
Killing them
inside the Palace
would only arouse
suspicion of murder.
Of course... Still,
death isn't the only way
to eliminate
this problem.
You have
an idea?
Leave everything to me.
In the meantime,
you need only focus
on seizing control of the
throne... Your Majesty.
It's
useless...
Take heart... We will get
out of this. I promise you.
This is all
my fault...
If only I hadn't
been such a fool...
I couldn't save the
Empress... Nor you.
I've told you
I'm on your side.
This is a minor setback...
I've faith in your abilities...
And so
should you.
Esther... After all
you've been through...
why are you
so kind to me?
Your family... They were
murdered by the Methuselah.
There was a time when
I hated all Methuselah.
I walked the same path
that has led our two kinds
to an endless cycle of
hatred and violence...
The truth is I allowed
my pain to blind me
from seeing the Methuselah for
what they are... Individuals.
Ion, I... I'm fond
of you, Excellency!
Honest- You and
The Duchess of Kiev,
and even your grandmother!
I mean, if we'd met,
I'm sure I would
have liked her.
Maybe... I guess
you might've.
I believe that
there's still time
to turn this
conflict around...
Fear can give way to reason,
mistrust to friendship...
We can change, and I'm
rambling aren't I...?
Thank you. And no,
you make perfect sense.
I feel the
same way.
Comfy...?
Cozy...? Good.
Don't be so naive. The Empress
would never succumb so easily.
Word of her demise is
propaganda, nothing more.
She is
the shield
which will protect the
Empire in perpetuity.
So... You
have water?
What?
There is
water everywhere.
Thank you for sharing the
obvious, but I'm not a rat.
I seriously doubt sewer water
would quench my thirst!
It's not like I brought
a flask or anything!
Forget it! We'll
dehydrate together!
Asta!
Be careful.
We're surrounded.
An ambush...
Very astute of you...
That's right...
We're being shadowed. They
know every move we make.
Look out!!
I will draw their fire...
You go to the Palace.
But... But,
Asta! You-
There's no time
for a debate.
You are the only one who
can rescue the captives!
Be careful.
I'm Astharoshe Asran,
Duchess of Kiev! Die!!
Scum!
You have the audacity to
stand before me?! You traitor!
Ah... Temper, temper.
Do you have any idea
the damage you've done?!
The Empress's
infatuation with peace
has forced her to step
down. Her dream of a world
where humans and vampires
coexist is ludicrous!
Radu, why are you
so against it?
Haven't you
realized yet...?
I am
not Radu.
What?!
It's true! Listen to
the way he's talking...
Radu is a Noble of
the Empire, right?
Well, Nobles never refer
to themselves as vampires!
What is
your name?
Fragile, yet astute
and defiant as ever.
That's what I've always
loved about you, Esther.
Is that you, Dietrich?!
You remember...
I'm flattered.
What is the meaning of
this?! Where's the real Radu?
Radu, Radu... Wake up...
Your friend is occupied.
Allow me to introduce myself,
Dietrich Von Lohengrin...
Or, if you prefer,
The Puppet Master of
the Rosen Kreuz Order...
Your friend, Radu has
long since expired...
Fortunately for me,
he was a perfect fit.
And the perfect ruse.
I pulled his strings
like a marionette.
You used him...
He was helpless.
I'll kill you!!
I swear it! I'll rip you to
pieces with my bare hands!
You'll pay for what
you did to him!
Excellency, please!
Ion!!!
Hold on!
I'll help you!
Save your tears,
Esther. He's a vampire.
A wound like that may
sting, but it isn't fatal.
[Ion] M- My
blood...
What's
wrong?!
Easy... Easy!
That's the
thirst kicking in.
My gift to
you, Tovarish.
Esther!
You...
You must...
Kill me!!
What are
you saying?!
There's no time... Hurry,
while I'm still myself!
But, I...
The bullet I shot him with
was specifically designed
to act as a catalyst...
To excite the bacillus-
Bacteria found in
vampire blood.
These bacilli trigger an
uncontrollable bloodlust
which will transform him
into a ravenous beast.
Fight it.
Be strong.
Don't despair, my dear.
I would never walk away
and leave you to
such a grisly fate.
This silver sword can
still the beast's heart.
Die by your hand or this
monster's. It's your choice.
The only monster
here is you!
Tick tock... Normally,
I'd stay to watch
this drama play out, but
alas, I have a busy schedule..
But if you want my advice...
Just aim high Esther...
Come back!
Dietrich!
Esther... Kill... me!
Never!
Easy...
Kill me now!
Ion... No!
Listen to me...
You must do this!
Please... N-Now...
We're running
out of time!
I can't control
it... End this...
Stop it.
I can't! I won't do it.
[Ion]
Kill me.
Next- Episode 19.
The Night Lords: Part 5.
A Start of Pilgrimage.
Avert not thine eyes.