My sister is taking
responsibility
for her misconduct
last night.
She is currently
under house arrest.
Lady Caterina has a strong
sense of responsibility.
I ask that she be
treated with leniency.
I will relay your
kind words to her.
However, I can make no promises
regarding her punishment.
The choices she
made were her own
She must be held accountable
for her actions.
I also believe that
her privately operated
AX team should
be disbanded.
That's a harsh
punishment.
No harsher than the crimes
that she has committed.
Disgraceful.
Under constant surveillance,
never a moment alone.
This is just like being
back in that damn cell!
We have to stay
put for now...
If we move too soon,
it would not bode well
for Her Eminence.
We can't just sit here!
In the worst-case scenario,
she could lose her title
as Duchess of Milan.
They wouldn't!
They can and, most
probably, will..
Cardinal Francesco will
use this as an opportunity
to change the balance of
power in the Vatican.
Ah... The Silent Noise could
be operational any time,
and we're stuck
here like prisoners
with our hands tied.
Oh! Sister Kate!
Pardon the intrusion. I
apologize if I startled you.
But I'm glad you're here.
I've been looking for you.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Has anyone seen or heard
from Father Nightroad?
I'm worried.
You mean... So they're
still trying to cover up
last night's incident?
Please sister Esther...
I need you to lend
me your strength.
You're the only one
I feel I can turn to.
You there! Halt!
No one is allowed
past this point
without presenting the
proper identification!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't it time for
the combined mass?
It would be
considered rude
to His Holiness
if you were late.
It matters not. Soon, this
city will meet its demise.
Everything has been
arranged according to plan.
Preparing the decoy
seems to have been a
good idea after all.
And because of that,
the greatest threat
to your grace's plan
has been dealt with.
The time is
almost upon us.
May the grudge that
has consumed you
for the past five years
be unleashed on them
like the wrath of God.
It's the layout
of the Vatican.
Where did
you get this?
Sister Noelle was clutching
it to her last breath.
You mean... you
were in Barcelona?
I'm glad that you've
returned, Hugue...
I'm sure Her Eminence
will be pleased, as well.
Heh. Professor,
what do you think?
Even in death, Sister Noelle
is still a member of the AX.
She found it...
The Silent Noise.
You mean that?!
But, it was a present
from Archbishop D'Este!
The Duchess of Milan
has fallen into a trap,
it appears that the one who
set it is the Archbishop.
Father Nightroad!
Thank goodness!
I finally found you!
I've been looking
for you everywhere!
I couldn't think of where
you might have run off to,
but then I remembered
this church.
Sister Noelle. This is the
place, isn't it Father?
This is where you and
Sister Noelle first met.
When someone dear
to us is lost,
the only things that
can offer us
comfort are memories of the
better times we shared.
I did the exact same thing
when Bishop Laura died.
So that's why I figured--
Father, wait!
Please! Her Eminence!
Lady Caterina and the others
are all in terrible danger!
The previous Pope,
your father,
was a great and
brilliant man.
Uncle, I apologize...
My actions last night
were disrespectful.
I understand.
You have a duty.
You did what you
felt you had to...
I'm sorry to have summoned
you to this place
during your
house arrest...
But there are some
important matters
I wanted to discuss with
you concerning your future.
My future? What are
you talking about?
Cardinal Francesco is planning
to use the opportunity
created by this situation
to overthrow you
and remove
your title.
However, it
won't matter.
Soon, everything around
you will be destroyed.
What?
When that time comes,
who will the people
turn to for guidance?
Lady Caterina...
It would be a shame
to let someone
with your wit
and intelligence
go to waste.
What do you
mean, destroyed?
What are you... Wait a
minute! No! You couldn't-
I will be the one to lead
the world into a new era.
The Enemy of
the World...
is truly only the
enemy of the Vatican.
The Contra Mundi
are the only ones
who can sympathize
with my feelings.
What exactly are
you saying, Uncle?
What is so glorious
about this city
that would make someone of
your knowledge and wisdom
willingly give her life
in order to protect it?
I summoned you here
to protect you
from being caught in the wave
of destruction and chaos
that will soon
take place.
I'm afraid you've
made a mistake, Uncle.
And If I make it
out of this alive...
I will continue to fight all
of you to my last breath!
I thought you would say
something foolish like that.
Abel!
Nano-machine:
Crusnik, 02..
Power output,
40 percent Activate.
Show me what
you really are!
I'm just a messenger for
the Archbishop... Father.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance...
Lady Caterina.
Allow me to
introduce myself.
Isaak Fernando
von Kampfer...
The Order of Rosen Kreuz.
Court rank: Magus.
My Title: Panzer Magiel
I am here before you
as a humble servant
of the honorable
Archbishop D'Este.
Brother, what is it?
Where is the Archbishop?
The combined mass
is about to begin.
He should have
been here by now!
Just before 6
It's almost time...
Look! The Archbishop!
I was right! That obelisk
is the Silent Noise system!
We've got
to stop him!
Leave everything
to me, Professor!
Behold the power!
What the...
What's that?!
Now that's an
interesting creature.
Gunslinger! Nice of
you to join us! Alright!
Time to bust in and
crash this party!
That bastard's trying
to make a run for it!
We can't allow him to
activate it! Come on!
Whoa! It's huge!
Way to go!
Thanks, Hugue!
That's just
pissing him off!
We'll need a bazooka
to stop this thing!
These were my
instructions
from the Archbishop
concerning you,
Cardinal Sforza I am
to try to convince you
to join our cause.
If that cannot be done...
Then I am to kill you.
I summon thee...
Of thine own free will...
Arise, O Lord
of Darkness...
Lend me thine
power of the flame!
Come forth!
Arrow of Belial!
And now it's time for you to
die Lady Caterina Sforza.
No! Stop!
Abel!
Well done.
You're still alive.
I will...
protect the humans.
Abel! No! Stop!
You've done enough!
You've done
enough for me!
Careful, I wouldn't
try to move him
if I were
you, my lady.
He was struck by the
Arrow of Belial...
an electro-magnetically
accelerated cannon...
I'm surprised he's even able
to sustain his current form.
Get out of here!
Run, Caterina!
Oh, give it a
rest, will you?!
You can't protect anyone!
You've already proven that!
You stood by while
countless numbers of people
were slaughtered
in Barcelona,
including
that Sister
who was one of your
closest comrades.
You've failed time and
again at protecting
the ones who are
important to you
and this time won't
be any different.
Nanomachine:
Crusnik 02
Power Output Level
80 percent. Activate.
What a surprise.
I'm impressed.
It appears you've been
holding back on me.
So this is it..
The true form of the mighty
and powerful Crusnik.
What are you
looking at?
I'm honored to make
your acquaintance.
The true face of a Crusnik
At last, we finally meet.
A mega-volt-level
generator,
powered by your own
body... Impressive...
However Even in this form,
you're still no match for me.
Kampfer!
No!
What... What
was that?!
How were you able to
penetrate my shield?
Ah, yes There is one way.
You cut the current.
Let me guess...
That was the Spark-Gap
attack, wasn't it?
You continue to amaze me.
The true form of
the Crusnik...
Such a powerful being...
What in the
hell was that?!
Hear me! Hear
the sound of hate!
The bells have
begun to ring...
You've got to kill
me now, Crusnik...
or the city of Rome
will be destroyed.
That's it... Now..
Strike me down and kill me.
Take your vengeance for the
Sister you lost in Barcelona.
Long ago, I made a promise.
One that I intend to keep.
A promise to
never kill anyone.
A promise?
A promise you say?
That's right... An oath to
never kill anyone...
Nor allow anyone to die...
As atonement for my sins.
So I will not kill you,
or anyone, ever again!
Now tell me! How do
I stop that thing!
Tell me! I'm
begging you! Please!
Alright, I'll tell you
what you want to know.
There is only one way to
stop the Silent Noise.
You must destroy its
master control chip.
Which I have, right
here... Inside me..
Inside my body.
The chip continuously
monitors my vital signs.
As long as my heart still
beats, it continues to operate.
Kill me, and it
ceases to function...
You'll be able to save this
city and everyone in it.
Simple, isn't it?
Tell me, can you hear
the cries of death
of the people of Rome over
the sound of that bell?
You must act quickly, Abel.
What will you do?
I can't! But I must!
Behold! Rome is finished!
You're the only
one who's finished!
No! How did you-?!
It's all over. Archbishop...
Quick! Shut it down!
Heh, heh, heh...
With pleasure...
Can't bring yourself
to do it, can you?
All because of
that silly promise...
It makes you hesitate.
Keeps you from soiling
your hands with blood.
The bells. They've
stopped ringing...
That means the
Archbishop's been seized
and the plan has
ended in failure...
And since my client
has been captured,
there's really no reason
to go on like this...
It would seem
we'll have to
continue this
discussion another time.
I'll be leaving now. Farewell,
Abel, until we meet again.
Abel...
Abel!
Abel! Talk to me!
Say something!
Abel! Don't die
on me! Abel!
It's been awhile...
02... Abel.
Next - Episode 11:
From The Empire.
Avert not thine eyes.