-That does it! If he doesn't make it
back here in time,
I'll never forgive that jerk!
I'll blacklist him from my cafe,
then I'll burn up
every figure in his collection!
[ Laughs evilly ]
-What's gotten into you?
You sound so evil.
-You've shown yourself,
Darth Jiro.
I wish you'd cool it
with that evil laugh, though.
Believe me, I have enough
depressing company as it is.
-S-Staz!
W-What took you so long?!
-Hmm. What's that stuff?
-It's a magical-essence formula,
but this is the last one!
[ Screams ]
-Man, that hit the spot.
-I can't believe
you just did that!
What the hell
were you thinking?!
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-Well, that's all Wolf's fault.
-Are you kidding me?
It's all your fault!
You're the reason
we're in this mess!
-Come on -- he didn't tell me
you guys were keeping
Fuyumi alive with that formula.
Anybody would have done that,
right?
-I think if it were me,
I would've asked
if I could have a drink
before just gulping it all down.
-Is there some manner
of disagreement occurring here?
-That's none of your business.
Now go on and look
for some panties or something.
-As the young lady and I
haven't met before,
without a proper introduction,
she might actually believe
I'm that sort of person.
Isn't that right, my dear?
-I-It's so nice to meet you.
-Call me "Braz."
I insist.
And might I inquire
as to your name?
-Uh, I'm Fuyumi.
-What a beautiful name you have.
My brother's told me
so much about you.
I'm aware of your condition,
my sweet,
and I can easily remedy it
for you.
-Hey. Don't go overstepping
your bounds.
-You did tell me
this was urgent, didn't you?
-Stop trying to make it look
like you're doing me
some gigantic favor.
I can handle this all by myself.
[ Snap! Crack! ]
[ Both gasp ]
-Very well.
Again, I bend to your will.
How do you plan
to save this girl's life
without the generous assistance
of your older brother?
-Shut up, and I'll show you.
[ Chomps ]
I made a promise before
that I'd be her blood bank
until the day
that I can bring her back.
-What? Uh...
Right here?
-Yeah, that's right.
Now, hurry up.
-But everybody's watching me.
And if I drink that,
then I'll...
-So you gonna drink this or not?
Come on.
-Okay. But at least
let me do it over there.
-Just drink!
-Mmph!
-How's that?
More magic than last time,
isn't there?
-[ Sighs ]
[ Thinking ] I can't resist.
Staz, once I've tasted this,
I can't go back.
[ Sighs ]
-[ Whimpers ]
-I don't approve of this at all.
She seems fine now,
but who knows what could happen
if you continue?
-Well, I don't plan
on keeping this up.
She'll be turned human again
soon.
Wasn't that the deal
we agreed on?
-Indeed it was.
Shall we go and have a look
at her original body, then?
To East Demon World.
Yes, back to your own territory,
where you and Fuyumi first met,
and the place
where she lost her life.
-Well, well.
Looks like
another slow day, huh?
[ Both gasp ]
-Boss!
-Ugh! Is that me?
-It's Yoshida!
Did you forget?!
-Oh. Right.
So, what happened to you, Dek?
-Uh, things have been
a little crazy here.
-Don't you have any clothes
of your own, Tsuboi?
-Uh, he's only doing it
'cause you told him to.
-And my name is Yoshida, Sir.
-[ Clears throat ]
-Tell you what -- Let's not
worry about the details.
Hey, Saty, grab me a beer.
-Sounds good.
Huh?
Hey, who's the kid?
She a new recruit?
-Her? That's my sister.
-Huh?
-Honestly,
I can't conceal my disgust.
To think you've actually chosen
to spend your time
with these uncouth characters.
[ Both shuddering ]
-What -- Can't you go
to the restroom by yourself?
-Something doesn't smell right.
-Duh.
Look where we are.
-Come on.
I'm trying to be serious.
So, how much do you think
your brother really knows?
-I'm not too sure.
It's possible
he could know about everything.
Or it could just be an act.
But one thing I do know --
My brother is
always up to something.
-What is this thing?
Is it edible?
-Trust me --
If he told you anything...
-Aah!
-...you can be positive
there's a catch.
-He said something earlier
that's bugging me.
-Now that Liz's job
is completed,
I'd like to do
a little sightseeing
down here in the demon world.
-Oh. I see. Would you like me
to help you out?
-There's no cause for alarm,
my dear.
But I must say
I'm rather surprised.
Why would a professional,
such as yourself,
assist the others
in resurrecting that young lady?
-Oh. Well, I just...
-She must be
of great importance to you --
perhaps even more than
the others could ever imagine.
-Huh?
-You sure looked pathetic
in there
with all that sucking up
you were doing.
-Hey! Shut up, all right?!
It's not like I had a choice!
Anyway, that's not the point!
-Well, if I were you,
I wouldn't start worrying
about any of that stuff.
I know from personal experience
that if he suggests
you do something,
it'll always benefit him
in the long run.
-[ Sighs ]
Yeah, well, anyway,
when Fuyumi wakes up,
give her this.
-What is it?
-It's a bell,
and if she rings it three times,
then I'll come to her.
Tell Fuyumi to call me
if anything happens, okay?
Later!
-Hey!
[ Bell jingles ]
Guess she doesn't come
when I ring it.
Hmm.
-[ Sniffs ]
-Sorry to keep you waiting,
boss.
-That was fast.
-We should be taking off.
-Call us if you need anything!
-Sure.
-All right,
let's have a look now.
-Hey! Hold on!
What the hell's that thing?!
-A little instrument
that I've developed.
-Oh, great. And who are
you gonna torture with it?
-There isn't anything
to be concerned about.
-Come on!
Answer my question, damn it!
-Her clothes are getting in
the way. Let's strip her down.
-You must be out of
your sick, perverted mind!
We can't do that!
-I cannot understand why
you're getting so frustrated.
You really believe
I'm that untrustworthy?
-Well, pretty much, yeah.
And if I see you try to pull any
crap pretending to save Fuyumi,
then don't expect me
to ever forgive you.
-All this instrument does
is take a sample of her magic.
Resurrection is accomplished
by converting magic
into what humans refer to
as the soul,
then carefully placing it
into a newly replicated body.
To carry this out,
I need to examine her essence.
Do you understand now?
-Fine. Do it.
-Mm. Where...am I?
-Talk about perfect timing.
Now lift up your arms.
-Huh?
-Ready, and...say "Ahh!"
-[ Screams ]
-Stop struggling!
Hurry up
and get it over with, Braz!
-Staz! What are you doing?!
-Stop whining!
-Yeah, you shouldn't watch this.
The sight of what's about to
happen will scar you for life.
[ Gun clicking ]
-All done.
-You sure didn't make it easy
for me, did you?
Calm down. He's the one
that told me to do it.
-Please, Staz.
You're making it sound like
I'm that sort of person again.
-Hey, if the shoe fits...
-I'm going home to prepare
for her resurrection.
Liz told me she'd quite enjoy
seeing more of this place.
Would you mind
showing her around?
-Yeah.
-Seriously?
-Goodbye, Staz.
-Wait. You didn't get
a clean sample before.
Isn't my magic
mixed in with hers?
-Relax.
The task of removing your magic
is, for me,
an extremely simple matter.
You must continue to act
as her private blood bank
until the day
I can bring her back to life.
Promises are meant for keeping,
right, brother?
And I assure you
my vow will be kept.
-Aah!
-Brother is so cool.
-Think so?
He's carrying a man purse.
-Don't worry, Staz.
I'll happily remove it for you.
And then I'll possess
a perfect sample
of your renewed vampire magic.
[ Chuckles ]
And I'll put it to good use.
I promise you that.
[ Laughs evilly ]
-Aww.
-Whatcha lookin' at?
-Uh, n-n-nothing!
Nothing at all!
-Really?
[ Door opens, bell jingles ]
-Oh. Welcome back.
-Uhh...
So, how much they gonna pay you
to work here?
-I felt kind of bad
just waiting around,
so I decided to help out.
Oh, look.
You got such a cute one, Liz!
-It's not that great.
-Oh, is that right?
Well, I'm glad you allowed me
to buy it for you.
Hey, what are you guys eating?
Looks good.
-You want to try some, boss?
-Yeah, Fuyumi made us
a little human-world food.
-Are you sure it's safe?
I mean...
-What kind of cook
do you take me for, anyway?
I may not look it,
but when I was alive,
I was in the kitchen every day.
-Oh, yeah, I forgot --
You don't have a mom.
I'll let Liz try it first.
Then I'll eat it.
-Hey, come on!
That's not fair!
My cooking's not that bad!
-It looks...like a Tsuchinoko.
-It's a Tsuchinoko omurice.
-Enough talk. Let's eat.
[ Squeak! Squeak! Pop! ]
[ Clank! ]
Hey.
No masks at the table.
-[ Gasps ]
[ Sobbing ]
-Come on.
Are you homesick already?
-No!
-You just started crying
out of nowhere.
Bring back memories hearing
Fuyumi didn't have a mom?
Our parents are long gone,
and they're not coming back.
So just get over it already.
-No, that's not it.
-It's a little sweet.
Eh, you know.
-[ Thinking ] This is
so incredibly awkward!
I wish he'd just tell me
it tastes delicious,
even if he doesn't mean it.
-Thanks for the meal.
-So...how was it?
-It kind of reminded me of you.
It was a little bland.
-Oh, really?
[ Thinking ]
What kind of review is that?
-I liked it.
-[ Gasps ]
You really did?
Then I'll make it again!
-Why are you getting
so excited, anyway?
-What do you care?
You think my food's bland.
-Hey, what are you
upset about now?
Ugh! I told you --
No masks at the table!
-Shut up! Let go of me!
-Not until
you take that thing off!
-Hey, come on, you guys.
-The Acropolis Ticket?
-Once I acquire what I'm after,
I'll return,
and then you'll have
an extremely important job
to perform.
It is crucial
that you not return here
until I give you permission.
-Huh?
But I don't understand!
Why?!
-I'll be quite busy
doing some research at my lab.
And I'm going to need you
to keep an eye on Staz
to make sure he doesn't
interfere with my work.
Can you do that?
-[ Whimpers ]
-Oh, come on. You're not
gonna cry again, are ya?
If you want to go home,
just leave.
-I'm not crying!
And I'm not going home!
-Oh. Now I get it.
So this is all his idea.
Braz told you to do something
for him, didn't he?
You mean...I'm right?
-Braz told me
not to come home for a while
because I would only
get in the way of his work.
-That's it? Really?
-Uh-huh.
[ Thinking ] It's a lie,
but it's probably the truth.
Brother has never
asked me to help
with any
of his research projects.
-Good girl, Liz.
- I'm not a cute little sister
to him,
so I have to be a good girl.
Bad girls have no place.
-You're a bad girl, Liz.
-What do you mean, "bad girl"?!
-Take a look at my library.
See all those?
You're gonna get to enjoy
all of them from scratch.
-Ohh.
-Let's see.
How about this one?
No -- this one.
It's a story
where a girl falls from the sky.
You're gonna love it.
-What's gotten into you?
-Listen, kiddo,
if the only reason you're here
is 'cause you've got
noplace else to go, it's cool.
Hey, both of us are
being neglected by our brother,
aren't we?
So I say just ignore everything
and have some fun.
-But that's something
a bad girl would do.
-Yeah, well, you see,
in the demon world,
it's good to be bad.
The real winners are the ones
who have the most fun
doing anything
and everything they want.
Remember that.
[ Soft music plays ]
-Oh.
Ohh.
Hmm.
Ahh!
[ Both chuckle ]
-You see, Liz?
It's a whole lot better
than the crap TV
we get in the demon world.
-Play it again.
-Huh?
There's no need
to watch it twice.
I got plenty of classics
you'll like.
-This one!
-Is she for real?
-[ Giggles ]
You're the one who said
the ones who have the most fun
doing whatever they want
are the winners.
I might have misjudged you.
-Huh?
-You're being
such a good brother to her.
-[ Groans ]
Gimme a break, will ya?
-You're really a nice person.
-Huh?
-I mean...you swore
that you'd bring me back,
and you've kept your word,
doing everything you can
to make it happen.
Thank you very much.
-Yeah, but you haven't been
resurrected yet.
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot.
-What's that?
-It's from Bell.
-Huh?
-She wanted me to make sure
that you got this.
Bell said she'd come to you
if you ring it three times.
-Okay.
-[ Chuckles ]
-Are you kidding me?!
This bastard ruined
the properties I bought!
-Oh, yeah. He's pretty nasty,
isn't he, boss?
-Shut up!
You passed it on to me!
-[ Laughs ]
-Damn that bastard!
I can't believe this!
You don't feel like
playing with the guys, Liz?
-Huh? I'm okay.
It's my bath time.
-Oh, the bath's right over here.
[ Wood clacks ]
It's very Japanese, isn't it?
I remember being surprised
when I saw it
for the first time, too.
-Why'd you take off
your clothes?!
-Huh? We're taking a bath,
aren't we?
-Y-You're coming in with me?
-Well, yeah.
What's the matter?
Are you shy?
You've never taken baths
with your brothers?
-This is ridiculous!
I can take a bath all by myself,
thank you very much!
[ Wood clacks ]
-Okay, close your eyes.
I'll rinse your hair.
-Okay.
-After this,
I'll wash your back, okay?
-Mm-hmm.
You really helped me out
back there.
I usually get soap in my eyes.
-I'm just happy we finally got
to spend some time together.
-Are you trying
to make me like you now?
-Excuse me?
What made you think of that?
-It's what everybody does.
They fear brother and me,
so they try
everything they can think of
to be liked by us.
-None of the people
who hang around with Staz
are that way at all.
Didn't you hear them
laughing in there
while they were beating him
at a video game?
-Because they're bad kids?
-[ Giggles ]
I guess so.
See? I'm a bad kid, too.
I was thinking how lucky Staz is
to have such a cute sister.
If you were my sister,
we'd take lots of baths.
Know what I mean?
-Huh?
You've been
a very insolent girl,
but I'll excuse your crimes.
-I appreciate it.
-[ Laughs ]
-No, boss! Oh, please!
Not that card!
Anything but that card!
-What? I can't hear you.
-Let's leave them alone.
-Okay.
I'm going to sleep now.
-Sounds good.
-There's another bed
right over there.
-Oh, yeah, I know there is.
But we both know
that I'm insolent,
and I've always wanted
to do this.
-You're kind of creepy.
-Good night.
-Your big boobs
don't leave me any room.
Can't believe
how busy today was.
-But it was fun, though,
wasn't it?
-Mm.
Your food was yummy.
-I'll cook for you again.
-And the anime was fun.
-Yes, it was.
-I've always...
always...been lonely.
[ Crying ]
-I'll be here for you, Liz,
if that's okay with you.
-Huh?
[ Groans softly ]
Huh?
Hey, Staz!
-[ Snoring ]
-Come on! Get up!
-[ Groans ]
What is it?
-Look! See?!
-Huh? Aah?!
-That went a lot faster
than I expected.
Guess I'll go
grab some breakfast.
-Fuyumi didn't go anywhere.
She was in the room with me
the whole time.
I didn't see her leave the bed.
And I never heard the sound
of a door opening, either.
-Maybe the reason
you didn't notice it
is because
you were sound asleep, Liz.
-Well, I don't sleep
the way you do.
Besides, she said...
-I'll be here for you, Liz,
if that's okay with you.
-Yeah, I know.
This was done against her will.
She knows that without me,
she'll disappear,
so there's no way she'd ever
leave a stupid note like that
and then go sneaking off.
-Are you saying
that Fuyumi's been abducted?!
-Yeah.
Or even worse.
Damn it.
This is all my fault.
It's always the same.
When she was eaten alive
by that plant
or when she almost faded away,
I was never there to help
when she needed me.
I was focused on myself
and not on the things
that really mattered most.
-Man, I haven't seen you
like this.
-It's always your fault.
But, hey, the Staz I know
would never admit he's wrong.
So stop beating yourself up!
-He's right, boss.
-Come on, we don't know for sure
if she faded away
and disappeared.
Show us the old Staz
and give us some stupid order!
-[ Grunts softly ]
-You know, something like,
"Search every single inch
of the demon world
until you guys find her!"
-[ Chuckles ]
That's not bad,
but I'd say something like...
"You guys go do whatever
it takes to find Fuyumi,
"but...if you still
can't find her,
"I'm gonna go totally psycho
and use every one of my powers
to take it out
on the demon world!"
[ Chuckles ]
-Now, that's more like it!
-We'd better find her.
-Okay! Let's get going!
We don't have any leads,
but that won't stop us!
[ Door opens, bell jingles ]
-What's wrong?
-Brother might know.
-What?
-He might know
where Fuyumi is right now.
-Huh?!
-Because he put
a tracking device in her body.
-When?!
-When he took a sample
with that device.
-Why did you wait
to tell me about this?!
Because brother made me
swear to him
that I would never tell this
to anybody.
-That son of a --
Then he knew
that this was gonna happen!
So, was he the one
that abducted her?!
-What?! No!
Brother would never do that!
-I don't know
what he's up to exactly,
but it's the only lead we've got
to work with.
Take this and go back
to the Acropolis.
Call me when you find out
where Fuyumi is.
-No. I can't do that. He said
I couldn't come home yet.
-Don't worry.
If he says anything to you
at all,
tell him I started going crazy
when Fuyumi went missing
and I threatened you.
You can have it all,
everything I've ever collected
from the human world --
the anime, manga, games, music.
I'll hand over all of them
to you, okay?
Just find Fuyumi for me.
Please, Liz.
-[ Sighs ]
You...gave me this.
He's enough.
That's all I want.
-Are you sure that's it?
-Yeah.
Don't get me wrong --
I'm not doing this for you.
Fuyumi's a bad girl,
but...she was kind of okay.
-Is that right?
-[ Grumbles ]
-You better bring her back,
or I'll never forgive you.
-Got to admit --
you're starting to become
quite the little bad girl
yourself, Liz.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
-Got some info, boss.
Earlier this morning,
a stranger had his breakfast
at a diner here.
-What'd he look like?
-Gimme a second.
Mamejiro and Saty were able
to do a Search Eye on the place.
Yoshida's
morphing into the guy now,
so we'll send you a pic.
-Good work, you guys.
-That looks pretty close.
-Hmm.
-This is the guy, boss.
You seen him before?
-With clothes and hair
like that,
he looks like a guy who'd be in
some kind of British boy band.
Did you see which way he went?
-Uh...
-That way --
toward South Demon World!
-Did you catch that?
-Yeah, I heard.
Thanks.
South, huh?
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-It's not like I don't trust
what Liz says...
...but nobody's
gonna take Fuyumi!
-Give me my panties.
-Sorry. I can't hear you.
-I said give me back my panties!
-What?
-Those panties in your hand --
give them back!
-Next time on "Blood Lad" --
"Two is a Treasure."
-In the demon world,
it's good to be bad.