-Congratulations, Staz.
You are officially free to go.
-Oh, yeah?
-How does it feel?
You're a noble demon again
with completely restored
vampire powers.
-I think it sucks.
Now I have to go out
and destroy that monster.
You're the only one
who's happy my powers are back.
-Indeed.
He's the perfect opponent
on which to test
your full potential.
Now show me
what you're capable of
and prove that unlocking
this talent wasn't a mistake.
It's your destiny.
-So you finally admit
your true intentions --
You manipulate
everyone around you
and force them
into carrying out your demands.
We're just alike.
That's what I hate about you,
brother.
-[ Chuckles ]
And that's the very thing
I love about you,
my dear little brother.
-Don't forget.
-Right.
Stop him, and I'll teach you
the secrets
of human resurrection.
-You'd better.
-[ Chuckles ]
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-[ Exhales sharply ]
-Pretty neat trick, huh?
So, do you want to know
how I did it?
I sent it straight down into
Mister Piggy's wide-open mouth.
And when I expanded it...
Boom!
-Wait. That's...
-Hm! Ta-da!
Bell's back in the house again!
What's with you guys? It's still
like a funeral in here.
-Hi, Bell.
-Oh, joy.
-Shut up, you dust rag!
-So, I, uh...
-Oh, I see.
Looks to me like Franken
couldn't keep his mouth shut.
It's all over your face.
You think you're
causing everyone trouble.
[ Chuckles ] Don't you worry.
Wolf doesn't feel that way.
Not at all.
-[ Growls ]
-Oh! So you want to play around
with me, too.
Is that it?
All right, then.
-I've already
seen this trick once.
[ Chuckles ]
-Huh?
[ Laughs ]
Nice! I mean it!
I like you.
Hmm. I can't decide.
All your parts seem good.
Should I take the legs?
Hmm, yes, it would make sense,
but still...
-You want a piece of me, huh?!
[ Growls ]
But...I just...
-Thought you broke it,
didn't you?
-[ Groans ]
-You happen to be right
about that.
It is broken.
Wild, huh?
But it doesn't bother me at all.
You want to guess why?
-Who cares?
-The answer is simple.
These appendages
are only decoration.
I don't need bones or muscles.
They're so passé.
I control my limbs
a bit differently --
by using magic.
You see, the "me"
that you're seeing right now
isn't really my true form.
The real me
is actually a phantom
who's manipulating
all this dead flesh.
-I've been keeping my magic
in this container,
but now I'm ready to put it
right back where it belongs.
So, here's a quiz
for you, hotshot!
[ Growls ]
What type of creature
changes form
when its magic
is outside its body?
The answer is "me."
-You didn't even allow me
to guess.
You're not really good
at this kind of thing, are you?
But still -- fascinating.
-Three minutes.
See, that's how long
he can maintain his wolf form.
-But he's a werewolf, right?
His transformation
has a time limit?
-Enough about him.
-[ Gasps ]
Hey, we're not finished
talking here!
-Sorry, little guy.
But I need to have a chat
with Franken in private --
just the two of us.
You understand.
-She is such a skank.
-What's the meaning of this?
I won't be able
to help that girl
if you keep me trapped in here.
-Please.
Drop the act already.
You're just hoping that Wolf
loses as soon as possible.
'Cause then you can tinker
with your toy, Fuyumi,
without interference.
So just cut the crap.
This Akim uses spatial magic.
And you've had this information
all along, haven't you?
-Have you been
snooping around my lab?
-[ Chuckles ] I told you --
You can't hide from me.
So I suggest you fess up
and start telling me
everything you know --
for your sake.
-Now, which way is north?
Man, what I wouldn't give for
a cape and bodysuit right now.
Or maybe
a glowing stone pendant.
That might do the trick, too.
But I guess
that's more of a chick thing.
Guess I'll just
be a trouper and...
fly using the power of the atom!
[ Grunts ]
♪ Soaring high in the sky ♪
-Nice! Very nice!
This is so much better
than when you were
swinging that pole before!
That speed! That power!
And that clean, precise attack!
Beautiful!
And yet, somehow...
frail.
-[ Growls ]
-But that frailty...
might be your true beauty.
-[ Thinking ] I'm starting
to run out of time here.
Soon, the magic I released will
be pulled back into my body.
It's the part of me
that's not a werewolf
that causes it to happen.
[ Roars ]
That "frail" quality
you talked about earlier.
Later, you patchwork freak.
-[ Groaning ]
Ohh! That hurt.
Damn.
Forgot I couldn't fly.
Huh?
Wolf?
-Cherry Blood? What the hell
are you doing out here?
-Do we have a new visitor
joining us?
-You got to be kidding me.
How the hell are you doing that?
-I told you --
I'm a phantom, remember?
-That's just messed up.
-Oh, yeah! Right there!
-You like the way that feels?
-Yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Boy, you really know how to make
a demon feel good, don't ya?
Ohh!
Hey, what the hell's
wrong with you?!
Haven't you ever
heard of knocking?!
-You're really disgusting,
aren't you?
-No! It's not
what you think it is!
-Yeah, sure.
That's fine. Whatever.
So, it looks like Franken
will be out for a little while.
What do you say we check in
on Wolf and cheer him on...
from a box seat?
-Huh?
Oh! Wolf!
What the hell is that thing?
-So, what do you think
of my little magic trick?
-Damn it.
It's wearing off
faster than I thought.
-Staz is back!
-Hold on!
What's he doing here?!
-You out of time, Wolf?
This must be the first guy
who's survived
your werewolf form, huh?
-Hey, I'm not done with him yet.
-Yeah, right.
So, you gonna introduce me
or what?
This punk rocker
is the so-called monster, right?
-It sounds like
you know about me, too, huh?
How's that?
-What about getting answers
from your brother?
-What about watching Fuyumi?
- I'm the one asking!
Answer!
- I'll answer after you answer.
-Shut up!
I don't have time for this!
-That's not my problem!
-Excuse me.
-If you don't have time,
hurry up and say it!
-I said I don't have time
to tell you!
-What do you mean, you
don't have time to tell
me you don't have time?!
-That's not what I'm saying!
- I'll be doing the asking now.
Answer my question,
or I'll make both disappear.
-[ Thinking ] Damn.
This guy's housing
an insane amount of magic...
[ Sighs ]
...while I'm running on empty.
-Look! He changed back!
-But why?
He should still have more time.
-[ Grunts ]
-[ Chuckles ]
-Finish him!
-Vampire Tetsuzanko!
[ All gasp ]
You're 10 years too early.
-It's not like any vampire magic
I've ever seen.
-No, it wasn't.
Could he have...?
-I knew it.
Listen up, bullet-less.
-Huh?
-I need to step out and recharge
my magic, which means...
-It means if you tried
to fight him now,
he could easily tear you
into little pieces.
-Yeah, that's right.
So I'm out of this.
But I'll bet
you could do some real damage.
Now, why don't we try
saving our argument for later
and start focusing
on what we came here to do?
You know what I'm saying?
-It's my turn.
-Exactly.
Don't get yourself killed
until I recover, vampire.
-What was that all about?
-[ Thinking ] I think I know.
He -- He remembered
the promise that he made to me.
-Just you?
Your friend couldn't make it?
-Yeah.
Wolf Man had to scamper back
and fetch his favorite stick.
And I knocked you
all the way out here
so I could kick your ass.
You ready?
-I see.
This sure is a lonely place
you blasted me to.
-Doesn't seem to bother you
too much.
At least pretend to be scared.
-I've got a little quiz for you.
Why do you think
I waited for you out here
after you so rudely
blasted me to this place?
-Beats me.
Maybe you saw an ants' nest
and got distracted.
You're not real bright.
-[ Chuckles ] Funny.
The correct answer is,
I thought this open space
would be the perfect spot
to fight the two of you
with everything I've got.
-Man, you suck
at giving quizzes.
-Oh, I was looking forward
to this!
Why'd you have to come alone?!
-Isn't that obvious?!
'Cause I'm more than a match
for you.
-That attack
and your last one, too --
I didn't like them.
-Like I care.
-There's no beauty.
-You're so annoying!
Die already!
I've had it with you!
-Staz!
You know, for once,
you're right, Bell.
Staz has definitely
gotten stronger.
This is insane!
-That all you've got?
-Not quite.
I can tell these smaller attacks
don't work
against someone like you.
-What'll you do?
-A single attack.
I'm gonna unleash an attack
that's so big,
it'll blow you away.
Just watch.
-[ Gasps ]
-Huh?
-Ka...me...
-[ Gasping ]
No! Don't say it!
-...me...
Ohhhhh!
-[ Chuckling ]
What was that supposed to be?
-What's wrong, Fuyumi?
You need another drink?
-No. It's not that.
I was just a little surprised
by Staz's last move.
-It's sickening to watch
such waste of talent.
You're comprised
of excellent parts,
yet you have no idea
how to put them to good use.
Your moves are powerful,
but they leave you vulnerable
and lack beauty.
The last one was god-awful.
You attempted to unleash
that attack with such swagger --
like a third-rate fighter.
-[ Grunts ]
Freak.
What did you say?
-[ Gasps, groans ]
-That move comes from the single
greatest hero in the universe.
If he was standing here
and had attacked you with it,
your sorry ass
would be turned into dust.
You understand what I'm saying?
That's how awesome it is.
You're alive
'cause I'm just a poseur.
I was imitating
the greatest move
of the greatest fighter ever!
Of course I'm third-rate.
I'm not worthy
to use such a technique.
Which is why I have to fight
with my own style.
-About time.
Why don't you --
-Just shut up!
I've decided...
I'm gonna kill you
with a new finishing move --
my original
super-finishing move!
So I suggest you get ready.
You're about to be destroyed
with an attack
created by the same guy
you called third-rate!
-[ Chuckles ] I see.
Sounds like you've finally
gotten serious about this.
I think you've definitely
become something
that's worthy for me to eat!
Let's give it
everything we've got!
-[ Chuckles ]
-Everything is turning out
just as I had hoped.
He is what Staz was missing
all along --
an extremely powerful opponent,
worthy of his true potential.
[ Chuckles ]
Now, Liz, pay close attention
to what happens.
Things are about to get
very interesting.
This is what Staz's --
No -- your brother's magic
really look like.
-Let's go.
-[ Snaps fingers ]
-Aah!
Hey! What'd you
close the space for?!
-Must be nice to be a low-level
demon with no worries.
If we keep on watching,
we'll get blown away, too.
Well, I got a few things to do,
so...later, guys.
-Hey! Aww.
She always does this to us,
you know?
I wonder
how the fight turned out.
-So beautiful.
I have the feeling
that I'm finally seeing you
exactly as you were meant to be.
In the blink of an eye,
we met...
then parted.
And this is the outcome.
Truly a beautiful end.
-Get up.
-Unfortunately, I've used up
all my magic fighting you.
I have no desire to continue.
-That's too bad.
See, I don't remember saying
that we could stop this
on your terms,
because this fight
has just begun.
-Can I ask you a question?
For me, raw power
is the essence of beauty.
What is it to you?
-A burden.
-I see.
-I've been thinking
about which move
I should finish you off with.
But it's becoming a real pain
to decide which one is best,
so...I'll use my favorite.
-[ Groaning ]
-So long,
you sick, patchwork freak.
-[ Strained ] Not bad.
It's quite a fitting move
to end this fight.
-[ Grunts ]
Glad you approve.
-You done here?
I know
you just finished fighting,
but I have a favor to ask.
-Huh?
-There's no doubt in my mind.
He's the perfect one
for the job.
-But I don't think
he'd be willing to help you.
-That doesn't matter.
Let's go, Liz.
There's work to be done.
-Oh! Two left!
Aah!
And time's running out!
What the hell's taking
those guys so long, anyway?!
-It's gonna be all right.
-Hey! Come on!
Get serious!
What the hell?
-It'll be okay.
I'm sure the three of them
are doing everything they can.
-I made a promise
to resurrect Fuyumi.
So if what you're saying
is true,
then I'm not gonna hold back.
-It's the truth, all right.
She'll be disappearing
in a few hours --
all because of you.
-Then why do you insist
on wasting our time
by challenging me again
for Fuyumi?
-You know me well enough by now.
I can't rest
until we've settled things.
-Yeah?
Guess our motives aren't
always logical, are they?
Let's do this.
-Hey. Got somethin' for ya.
-Hm?
[ Gasps ]
-But...how did you...?
-I'm a pro at spatial magic.
This was child's play.
Poor guy. He probably thought
he managed to get away.
Come on in.
-Ohh!
Your technique --
It's the same as mine.
-You're wrong.
My skill is the original.
Yours is just a cheap imitation.
Akim couldn't remember
where he learned
to use his magical skill.
Until he met me, he thought
it was something all his own.
So quit beating around the bush,
Franken.
Tell me who the demon was
that you used to make Akim.
-[ Sighs ]
All right.
Back then, my research
seemed to be at a dead end.
No matter how I tried,
it was no good.
I couldn't obtain the one part
that would be the key
to holding him together.
But one night...
[ Telephone rings ]
Hello?
-[ Distorted ] Hello, Franken.
Have you been a good boy?
I have a present for you.
-All right, who is this?
-Why don't you step outside
and have a little peek?
I'm sure it'll jog your memory.
-In that box was the body
of a spatial-magic user,
which became the core
for Akim's current body.
-So that's it, huh?
He's the thief
who stole my spatial magic?
-Most likely.
-So, who was
this "Santa Claus," anyway?
-No clue.
He's never revealed himself.
-Oh, great.
So, just when I think I've
finally found the magic thief,
there's another mystery to be --
-What have we here?
The young girl who brought Staz
to Demon World Acropolis.
-H-H-How'd you know that?!
And h-how come your lordship's
all the way out here?!
I didn't do it!
-Don't be alarmed.
I haven't reported it to anyone.
Actually, I'm here
regarding a different matter.
-Frankenstein and Akim Papradon,
you will both face judgment for
the crimes you have committed
while disturbing the peace
of the demon world.
Death?
-No, Liz. Just take them
into custody for now.
-Please, wait.
I made a promise.
There's a ghost girl
who needs my help.
-I'm afraid you'll no longer
have the opportunity
to keep that promise.
Go on.
-Yes, brother.
-Huh?
-Satisfied?
-Since the day
I took my first breath,
I've never been truly satisfied
with anything.
-Then why do you fight?
It doesn't make any sense.
I don't see the point
in doing this with you again.
Of course you don't.
But you've always been
like that, haven't you?
Even back then,
when you fell from the sky.
What the hell's this?
What's your name, kid?
-Staz.
-Where are you from?
-Above.
-Yeah, I figured that out!
But I want to know
why you fell from up there!
-I ran away -- to go see Japan.
-Huh?
-And to meet Hayao Miyazaki.
-Who's that?
It takes a lot of money
to go out into the human world.
You have any cash on ya?
Well, you're in luck
'cause I can teach you
how to make a bunch real quick.
[ Chuckles ]
Just got to fight me.
You win,
and I'll give you some money.
But if I beat you,
then I'll make you
one of my new henchmen, okay?
-All right.
[ Grunts ]
I give up.
-What the hell
is wrong with you?!
You haven't done anything!
You've just been
my punching bag!
You didn't even fight back!
-Hey! Calm down, Wolf!
-He's just
a spoiled little brat!
-He's not!
He came from above!
I know what that means!
You're one of the noble demons!
Aren't you, you punk?!
Why won't you fight me
like you mean it?!
-Because if I did that,
then I would kill you.
-"Who cares
if he's a noble demon?"
That's what I used to think
back then.
I thought I was so tough
and that being a mongrel
wouldn't really matter much.
But you know what, Staz?
Turns out I was so weak,
you had to take pity on me.
Even with your true power
sealed away,
I wasn't even worthy
of you fighting at your best.
How can I ever be satisfied
knowing all of that?
See ya.
But it's not over between us.
Next time,
I'll make you fight for real.
-I won't -- not against you.
'Cause you're my friend.
-Ah. How touching.
-Braz?!
-It seems that you have acquired
a true friend.
-W-What are you doing out here?!
And how'd you appear
out of nowhere?!
-Liz had work to do,
so we asked her
to bring us down here.
-They say, "If you can't
beat 'em, join 'em."
So I did.
Sorry. [ Giggles ]
-I must say --
this young lady and that
young man from earlier --
You have
remarkably good friends.
Wouldn't you agree, Liz?
-They must like jerks.
-What's the matter
with you guys?
If you're finished,
then just hurry up and leave.
-Oh, but I have some business.
Have you forgotten
the deal we made?
About resurrecting a human?
-[ Scoffs ]
-First, let's go
and meet this young girl
you want to bring back,
shall we?
-[ Gasps ]
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-Which way is west?
-Liz is spending
the night with us?!
That sounds like so much fun!
Let's play cards together!
-Why are you getting so excited?
-Huh? But --
-I'm not exactly thrilled.
I want to go home.
-Next time on "Blood Lad" --
"Liz, For the First Time."
-In the demon world,
it's good to be bad.