-[ GRUNTS ]
-HUH?
-HE GOT US!
-NOT QUITE!
-NUTS!
-SAY HELLO TO MY LOWER HALF!
-HEY!
-WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THAT ZOMBINATION?
-WHAT'S THAT?
YOU WANT TO SEE MORE?
WELL, IF YOU INSIST!
-WELL, IF YOU INSIST!
ONE CAN OF WHUP ASS TO GO.
-COME BACK ANY TIME!
OKAY, BOSS, WHAT DO YOU WANT US
TO DO WITH HIM NOW?
-YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
LOCK HIM UP.
-WILL DO, MA'AM!
ALL RIGHT. YOU TAKE THE LEGS.
-AGAIN?
-[ Thinking ] FUYUMI...
-I ALWAYS GET STUCK
WITH THE LEGS.
-...AT THE RATE
THINGS ARE GOING NOW,
I MIGHT DIE
BEFORE I CAN
BRING YOU BACK TO LIFE.
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-HUH.
FASCINATING.
I'M WELL AWARE OF GHOSTS,
BUT SHE APPEARS
TO BE COMBINED
WITH ANOTHER KIND OF DEMON.
-ANOTHER KIND?
-WAIT, YOU MEAN LIKE...
A VAMPIRE, RIGHT?
-A VAMPIRE, RIGHT?
-IT APPEARS THAT WAY.
-THAT FREAKIN' PERV!
AND AFTER ALL THAT CRAP
ABOUT NOT BEING INTERESTED
IN HER!
-WAIT. YOU MEAN
SHE'S EATING FOR TWO NOW?
GOT A BUN IN THE OVEN?
BAGGAGE IN THE BELLY?
SHE'S KNOCKED UP?!
-QUIT JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT
THE MAGIC INSIDE OF HER.
OUR BODY GENERATES IT
BY ABSORBING THE MAGICAL ESSENCE
THAT FILLS THE AIR
IN THE DEMON WORLD.
EACH SPECIES OF DEMON
ONLY PRODUCES MAGIC
THAT'S SPECIFIC TO THEIR KIND,
AND NO OTHER.
BUT THIS GIRL'S BODY CONTAINS
MAGIC FROM ANOTHER RACE,
MIXED IN WITH HER OWN,
WHICH IS WHY HER LEGS
ARE BEGINNING TO DISAPPEAR.
HER BODY IS OVERLOADED.
A GHOST IS UNABLE TO PROCESS
THE AMOUNT OF MAGICAL ESSENCE
REQUIRED FOR A VAMPIRE'S POWER.
-OKAY, SO, IN OTHER WORDS,
THIS IS ALL STAZ'S FAULT?
-SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO, DOCTOR?
-WITH ALL OF HER POTENTIAL,
SHE MAY BE ABLE TO RIVAL HIM.
-I'M NOT CERTAIN HOW SHE COULD
HAVE ACQUIRED IT, EXACTLY,
BUT IF SHE'S ABLE TO GET ANOTHER
DOSE OF MAGIC FROM A VAMPIRE...
-HMM.
-...THEN SHE COULD TAKE
EVERY LAST OUNCE
AND HAVE ENOUGH MAGIC INSIDE HER
TO TOTALLY SEIZE CONTROL OF ONE.
-HUH?
[ BUZZER ]
-OH, GIVE IT UP, MAN!
-YOU CAN'T WIN!
-IT'LL ALWAYS END THE SAME WAY!
-WAIT.
-SERIOUSLY?
YOU AGAIN?
-AND STAY OUT!
-[ GROWLS ]
-HUH? AAH! A BEAR!
IT'S A BEAR! NO!
-DRINKING COFFEE
WITH YOUR MASK ON?
-[ GASPS ]
-WHY ARE YOU SO SURPRISED
TO SEE ME?
IS MY COMING TO VISIT
REALLY SO UNEXPECTED, LIZ?
-BROTHER.
N-NO. THIS IS HOT COCOA!
-OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU DON'T LIKE
BITTER THINGS, DO YOU?
SORRY. I HAD FORGOTTEN.
BUT LIZ...
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY REASON WHY
YOU LOOK SO NERVOUS, IS IT?
-[ SIGHS ]
-IN YOU GO!
-[ GRUNTS ]
-AND DON'T YOU COME BACK!
-'CAUSE IF YOU DO,
WE'LL KILL YOU, GOT IT?
-YEAH!
I'M GETTING SICK OF THIS.
[ BUZZER ]
-PRISONER NUMBER 1097639
HAS PUSHED
THE "CHALLENGE" BUTTON.
-HUH?
-PLEASE PROCEED
DOWN THE HALL PROMPTLY.
-IF THERE WAS AN INTRUDER,
YOU COULD HAVE EXECUTED HIM
ON THE SPOT.
SO WHY USE YOUR PRIVILEGE
TO INCARCERATE HIM
WITHOUT FIRST SEEKING
MY AUTHORIZATION?
I WON'T GET ANGRY WITH YOU, LIZ.
BUT THERE'S STILL
SOMETHING YOU'RE HIDING FROM ME,
ISN'T THERE?
-[ SIGHS ]
BUT YOU'LL...BE MAD.
-GO ON.
-HEY, BOSS.
CAN I TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT
NEW PRISONER WE'VE GOT WHO --
UH...
OH. UH, SORRY.
DID I COME AT A BAD TIME?
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
-[ SIGHS ]
-A NEW PRISONER? DO TELL.
-WAIT. ARE YOU SAYING
SHE HAS TO KILL STAZ?
-THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
IF A GHOST HAS THE ABILITY
TO COEXIST WITH MAGIC
OF OTHER SPECIES,
THEN THEY CAN ESSENTIALLY
TURN INTO ANY DEMON
BY CONSUMING THEM.
CURRENTLY, THIS GIRL
HAS THE BODY OF A GHOST,
BUT SHE ALSO HAS THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME A VAMPIRE.
AND IF THAT SHOULD EVER HAPPEN,
IT WILL MEAN THE BIRTH
OF A MONSTROUS NEW HYBRID.
-YOU'VE GONE WAY OVER THE LINE!
WHAT'S THE POINT IN DOING THAT,
ANYWAY?
STAZ WOULD STILL DIE FROM HAVING
ALL HIS MAGIC SUCKED OUT!
-NO, HE'D CONTINUE TO LIVE
WITHIN THE GIRL'S BODY --
-SHUT UP.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANY MORE OF THIS.
-BUT IT'S THE ONLY POSSIBLE WAY
WE CAN SAVE HER.
IF LEFT ALONE,
THE GIRL WILL COMPLETELY
DISAPPEAR FROM THIS WORLD.
-THIS IS ALREADY THE 10th TIME
THIS TURKEY'S CHALLENGED US
TO A FIGHT.
-HE'S SUCH A PAIN IN THE ASS.
CAN WE JUST KILL HIM ALREADY?
-BROTHER, WAIT. I CAN EXPLAIN.
[ GUNSHOTS ]
-WHOA!
-HE SHOT HIM RIGHT IN THE CHEST.
WAY TO GO!
-[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
BROTHER.
-YOU'LL BE JUST FINE.
THESE BULLETS WILL ALLOW
YOUR MAGIC TO RECOVER.
-BY MAKING A HOLE IN MY CHEST?
-DON'T WORRY.
YOUR VAMPIRE BLOOD WILL HEAL
THOSE WOUNDS INSTANTLY.
-WAIT. VAMPIRE BLOOD?
AND WHAT'S ALL THIS STUFF
ABOUT "BROTHER"?
-BOSS, IS THAT SCUMBA--
I MEAN,
THAT GENTLEMAN YOUR BROTHER?
-I HAVE MISSED YOU,
LITTLE BROTHER.
-YEAH, WELL, I HOPE YOU DON'T
EXPECT ME TO SAY THE SAME.
-THAT LOOKS LIKE...
-YEAH, IT'S THE BOOK
OF HUMAN RESURRECTION.
YOU WROTE IT, DIDN'T YOU?
-YOU WANT MY AUTOGRAPH?
-NO, DUMBASS.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THE STUPID THING SAYS.
HOW TO BRING HUMANS
BACK TO LIFE --
THAT'S WHAT I'VE COME
ALL THIS WAY TO FIND OUT.
-IF WE DON'T
FIGURE SOMETHING OUT,
SHE'S GONNA DISAPPEAR FOR GOOD!
I DON'T WANT TO PICK
BETWEEN SAVING STAZ OR FUYUMI.
-SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
-WOW! WHAT'S UP, YOU GUYS?
IT'S LIKE A FUNERAL IN HERE.
[ TWINKLE! ]
TA-DA!
I JUST COULDN'T STAND
HIDING FROM YOU GUYS ANYMORE!
BELL'S IN THE HOUSE, YO!
-BEAT IT, MARSHMALLOW!
-YEAH, GET LOST, PUFFY!
-I'M NOT A MARSHMALLOW
RIGHT NOW, GUYS!
-WHAT DO YOU WANT, HYDRA?
-LONG TIME NO SEE, FRANKEN.
-YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
-OF COURSE.
IN FACT, FRANKEN IS ONE
OF MY REGULAR CLIENTS.
BUT I'M NOT HERE
ON BUSINESS THIS TIME.
I CAME 'CAUSE I HEARD WE'RE
ABOUT TO LOSE THIS NICE RACK.
BUT, FRANKEN, YOU'RE NOT BEING
HONEST WITH THEM.
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE WAY
TO SAVE FUYUMI.
-WHICH IS...?
AAH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-IT'S LIKE THIS.
YOU SEE,
I REALLY HATE BEING LIED TO.
IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO GET KILLED RIGHT NOW,
YOU'D BETTER START
TELLING THE TRUTH.
-I REFUSE.
SUPPOSE I DID TRY
TO TEACH YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
WHAT WOULD I POSSIBLY
HAVE TO GAIN?
-GIVE ME A BREAK.
-WHY ARE YOU ASKING ME THIS?
WHAT MANNER OF HUMAN
ARE YOU TRYING TO RESURRECT?
A WOMAN?
-THAT'S NONE
OF YOUR DAMN BUSINESS.
-SO, IT IS A WOMAN.
A VIRGIN?
-SHUT UP! YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
I SAID IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS!
IF I TOLD YOU,
WOULD IT CHANGE YOUR MIND?!
-IT MIGHT MAKE
A DIFFERENCE, YES.
-THAT'S A LIE!
-[ LAUGHS ]
-CHECK OUT LORD BRAZ.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
LAUGH LIKE THAT.
-WELL, THEY ARE BROTHERS,
WORMBRAIN.
THEY MUST GET ALONG.
RIGHT, BOSS?
-QUIET!
-AW, CRAP! HOT, HOT, HOT!
-I GUESS WE WEREN'T
SUPPOSED TO SAY THAT TO HER!
SORRY!
-WHAT'S WRONG, LIZ?
WHY DID YOU BURN THE ZOMBIES
LIKE THAT?
-STAZ COULDN'T DO THAT,
BUT I BEAT THE ZOMBIES EASILY.
I REFUSE TO ACCEPT
THAT STAZ IS A NOBLE DEMON.
HE'S TOO WEAK TO BE ONE OF US.
-YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT, LIZ.
OUR BROTHER, STAZ,
IS BOTH A NOBLE DEMON
AND A PURE-BLOODED VAMPIRE.
NOTHING WILL EVER ALTER THAT.
AND HE WILL ALWAYS
BE YOUR OLDER BROTHER.
-NO!
I'M THE ONE WHO'S USEFUL TO YOU,
NOT HIM!
I'M BETTER THAN HIM
IN EVERY WAY.
-I'M SORRY, LITTLE SISTER,
BUT YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
-WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS LIKE THAT,
BROTHER?
[ Voice breaking ]
YOU'VE ALWAYS DONE IT --
TREATED HIM
SO MUCH BETTER THAN ME.
WHEN YOU RAN AWAY BEFORE,
I HAD HOPED THAT BROTHER
WOULD FINALLY START
PAYING MORE ATTENTION TO ME.
INSTEAD, HE'D SPEND TIME
LOOKING THROUGH
YOUR OLD PHOTO ALBUMS
OR CHECKING UP ON YOU
THROUGH SOME MAIL-ORDER
CRYSTAL BALL.
HE DIDN'T COME TO SEE ME TODAY!
HE ONLY CAME TO SEE YOU, STAZ!
-THAT'S NOT TRUE, LIZ.
I DO CARE.
-STOP LYING TO ME.
WHEN YOU WALKED IN,
YOU COULDN'T EVEN REMEMBER
THAT I DON'T LIKE COFFEE!
-BUT I ALREADY APOLOGIZED
TO YOU.
-YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT, HUH?
YOU USED YOUR AUTHORITY
TO THROW ME IN HERE
FOR A REASON LIKE THAT?
-I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
YOU COULD NEVER UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL.
-AND YOU COULDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE WAY I FEEL, EITHER.
SO, I GUESS WE'RE EVEN, THEN.
WE'RE BOTH DOING THINGS
FOR STUPID REASONS.
YOU'RE DOING THIS
FOR OUR BROTHER
WHILE I HAVE MY OWN REASONS
TO BE DESPERATE.
AND GUESS WHAT?
THE ANSWER
TO BOTH OF OUR PROBLEMS
IS THE GUY SITTING
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
-YOU'VE BECOME
QUITE THE SMOOTH TALKER.
FINE.
-[ SNIFFLES ]
-IF YOU DO A FAVOR FOR ME,
THEN I'LL TELL YOU
EVERYTHING THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT RESURRECTING HUMANS.
-SORRY. I COULDN'T HEAR YOU.
-I SAID THERE'S ANOTHER WAY.
-INSTEAD OF TAKING OVER
THE VAMPIRE, YOU REMOVE IT.
-IN OTHER WORDS, TURN HER
BACK INTO A PLAIN GHOST.
IS THAT IT?
-IF THAT'S POSSIBLE,
WHY DID YOU KEEP QUIET
ALL THIS TIME?
OUR PROBLEM
WOULD HAVE BEEN SOLVED
IF YOU HAD JUST SAID THAT
INSTEAD OF ALL THIS CRAZY TALK
ABOUT CREATING HYBRIDS!
-THAT MAY BE TRUE FOR YOU,
BUT CERTAINLY NOT FOR ME.
THE SITUATION
IS RAPIDLY DETERIORATING.
-HUH?
-I CAN'T AFFORD TO WASTE
ANY MORE TIME.
I CREATED SOMETHING
THAT'S HORRENDOUS,
A TRUE ABOMINATION.
IF I AM UNABLE TO STOP HIM...
-HIS EXISTENCE COULD MEAN
THE EXTINCTION
OF THE ENTIRE DEMON RACE,
DESTROYING DEMON WORLD.
-WHAT?
THE EXTINCTION
OF THE DEMON RACE?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
-JUST THREE DAYS AGO,
IN AN AREA OF DEMON WORLD
THAT I'VE BEEN WATCHING OVER,
HE FIRST APPEARED
AND MADE HIS PRESENCE KNOWN.
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
-ARTIFICIAL DEMON NUMBER 9.
AKIM PAPRADON.
THAT DEMON WAS, WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE GREATEST MASTERPIECE
I'VE EVER CREATED.
-ARTIFICIAL...
-DEMON?
MY ANCESTOR
ONCE STITCHED TOGETHER
DIFFERENT PIECES
OF HUMAN CORPSES
IN ORDER TO CREATE A MONSTER.
AND I STITCHED TOGETHER
PIECES OF DEMONS
TO TRY TO CREATE
AN EVEN GREATER MONSTER.
AT LEAST, THAT WAS THE IDEA.
-NO.
THIS ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
THIS WON'T DO AT ALL, FRANKEN.
I NEED HIGHER-QUALITY PARTS
THAT ARE WORTHY
OF THIS BODY YOU MADE FOR ME.
-BUT THAT'S MUCH TOO DANGEROUS.
WE NEED TO USE PARTS
THAT YOU CAN STILL CONTROL.
-ENOUGH OF YOUR EXCUSES.
-BESIDES,
WHERE WOULD I COME UP WITH --
-ENOUGH!
I'LL GO FIND THEM MYSELF.
-SPATIAL MAGIC?
-I WAS SURPRISED, AS WELL.
I WASN'T AWARE HE HAD
SUCH INCREDIBLE POWERS,
AND I ALLOWED HIM TO ESCAPE
IN AN INCOMPLETE STATE.
-THEN ALL THAT CRAP
ABOUT CREATING HYBRIDS
WAS JUST SO YOU COULD STOP HIM.
MAN, YOU REALLY
DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
-I'M THE BOSS OF THIS AREA NOW.
AND WHENEVER THERE'S TROUBLE
IN MY TERRITORY,
I SQUASH IT LIKE A BUG
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I DO.
-DON'T BE CRAZY!
YOU HAVEN'T ANY IDEA HOW --
-STRONG HE IS?
THAT'S PERFECT.
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR A GUY LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S THE DEAL.
YOU FIX FUYUMI.
-[ SIGHS ] VERY WELL.
PROVIDED, OF COURSE,
THAT YOU'RE ABLE
TO STOP HIM FIRST.
-HEY! COME ON!
YOU GOT TO START ON HER NOW!
IF WE WASTE MORE TIME,
SHE'LL DISAPPEAR!
-NO.
I'M ABLE TO SUSTAIN
THE GIRL'S BODY
FOR HALF A DAY.
STOP HIM BEFORE THAT.
THEN I'LL FIX HER.
SO THAT'S THE DEAL,
AND YOU CAN TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
YOUR CHOICE.
-SO...
WHERE IS THAT STINKIN' HYBRID?
-[ PANTING ] AAH!
AAH!
W-WHAT ARE YOU?!
WHY HAVE
YOU BEEN FOLLOWING ME?!
WHY?!
-YOU'VE GOT FAST LEGS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY? WANT TO TRADE?
-AAH!
AAH!
-THEN HE APPEARED IN THE NORTH.
HE'S SEEKING OUT
NEW PARTS FOR HIS BODY,
WANDERING, PLUNDERING,
AND EVOLVING.
-DOESN'T SOUND VERY GOOD.
-NOT AT ALL.
AND SOMETHING NEEDS TO BE DONE
IMMEDIATELY.
-SO WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU WANT ME TO DO EXACTLY?
-I WON'T ASK FOR THE IMPOSSIBLE.
AND, FRANKLY,
THE SHAPE YOU'RE IN NOW,
I DON'T THINK THAT YOU CAN DO
MUCH AGAINST HIM.
-YOU'RE RIGHT. I CAN'T.
NOW, IF YOU WANTED ME
TO SNAP A FEW PICTURES OF HIM,
I COULD DO THAT, BUT...
-WHAT IF YOU WERE TO REGAIN
YOUR FORMER POWERS?
-WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
-THE BULLET I FIRED INSIDE YOU
LONG AGO.
IT'S STILL RIGHT HERE, ISN'T IT?
SURELY YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN.
-YEAH.
I REMEMBER.
AND HOW YOU TRIED
TO KILL YOUR OWN BROTHER.
[ BONES CRACK ]
-IS THAT REALLY WHAT YOU THOUGHT
MY TRUE OBJECTIVE WAS?
DO YOU RECOGNIZE THIS?
-THAT OLD MAGIC TRICK?
-NO, I'M REFERRING
TO THE OBJECT.
-NOT REALLY.
HEY, DIDN'T I BREAK YOUR WRIST
JUST NOW?
'CAUSE, YOU'RE KIND OF ACTING
LIKE IT NEVER EVEN HAPPENED.
-I MERELY LET YOU THINK
THAT YOU HAD BROKEN IT.
AT THE MOMENT,
YOU'RE SIMPLY TOO WEAK
TO ASCERTAIN THE DIFFERENCE.
BUT THIS IS YOUR TRUE POWER.
YOU MADE THIS.
IT WAS A BOULDER
FIVE METERS ACROSS.
-WHAT?
-[ Thinking ] THIS TASTE.
THIS IS WHAT I WAS CRAVING FOR.
-LOOK! SHE'S DRINKING IT!
IS THIS THAT EMERGENCY STUFF?
-BUT IT TASTES
A LITTLE DIFFERENT TO ME.
THIS ISN'T STAZ'S BLOOD.
-YES, IT'S A CONCENTRATED
MAGICAL ESSENCE FORMULA.
-WHO ARE --
-ARE YOU AWAKE?
-[ GASPS, SCREAMS SOFTLY ]
-WHAT A TINY SCREAM.
-OH!
-HEY, YOU OKAY?
-WHAT HAPPENED?
WAIT. WHERE DID WOLF GO?
I THOUGHT HE WAS HERE.
-AFRAID HE HAD TO STEP OUT.
TO KILL A MO--
I MEAN,
TO KEEP YOU FROM DISAPPEARING.
-SO, ARE YOU READY?
-YEAH.
-YOU MEAN, YOU HAD TO COME BACK
HERE AND CHANGE YOUR CLOTHES
JUST SO YOU COULD
GO KICK SOME ASS?
-THAT'S NOT WHY I'M HERE.
I CAME TO GET THIS.
-A POLE?
-[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
ALL RIGHT.
-WHAT WAS THAT?
-I JUST SEALED MY MAGIC
INSIDE OF THIS.
NOW IT'S LIKE AN EXTENSION
OF MY OWN BODY.
-YEAH, I STILL DON'T GET IT.
-TRUST ME.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
THAT THING'S GONNA FEEL
MY POWDER!
-THAT'S POWER.
-FOR BEAUTIFUL HUMAN LIFE.
-[ Flatly ]
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT.
-UH, YEAH.
-BETTER GET GOING.
THE NEXT STOP --
NORTH DEMON WORLD.
-HOW MUCH TIME DO I HAVE?
-AS MUCH TIME AS IT TAKES
FOR THIS FORMULA TO RUN OUT.
SHE'LL NEED TO DRINK IT
ONCE EVERY HOUR.
THAT WILL LAST HER HALF A DAY.
-THAT SOUNDS KIND OF FISHY.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
YOU WERE GONNA TRY
TO CREATE A HYBRID
WITH ONLY THAT MUCH STUFF.
-DON'T GET THE WRONG IDEA.
IN TERMS OF MY MAGICAL FORMULAS,
I HAVE AN EXTENSIVE ASSORTMENT,
ENOUGH TO LAST HER FOR A WEEK,
BUT IF I WANT
TO KEEP HER A GHOST
WITHOUT MIXING IN ANYTHING ELSE,
THEN I CAN ONLY USE
SOME OF THE DRINKS HERE.
-[ GRUMBLES ]
-SO HURRY.
YOU HAVE LESS THAN ONE DAY.
-AAH!
-NOW, THEN. LEND ME A HAND.
YOU TAKE MINE,
AND I'LL TAKE YOURS.
-AAHHHH!
-CAN I SEE?
-DON'T LOSE IT NOW, OKAY?
-W-WAIT. I, UH -- WHAT?
-DO YOU RECALL MY ATTEMPTS
TO UNLOCK YOUR TRUE POTENTIAL?
WELL, I FINALLY SUCCEEDED.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IT WAS A FAILURE.
[ THUNDER CRACKS ]
WELL, STAZ, WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO SHOW ME?
-OH. BROTHER, WATCH THIS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
DID YOU SEE THAT?
IT'S NEAT, HUH?
-Y-YES.
-YOU CAN HAVE IT.
-STAZ, WAIT.
YOUR NOSE IS BLEEDING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING? STAZ!
-NEXT, I COULD --
HUH?
-YOU ALWAYS COLLAPSED
IMMEDIATELY AFTER USING
YOUR TRUE POWERS.
BUT, IT DIDN'T SEEM AS THOUGH
YOU USED THEM BY CHOICE
IT WAS AS THOUGH
AN INCREDIBLE ENERGY
OVERFLOWED FROM A TINY VESSEL.
-HUH?
-IF THIS CONTINUED,
YOU WOULD HAVE SURELY DIED.
IT WAS FAULT
FOR TRYING TO UNLOCK YOUR POWER
SO PREMATURELY.
-B-BROTHER.
[ GUNSHOT ]
-AND AS A RESULT,
I DECIDED
TO RESTRAIN YOUR POWERS.
THAT'S THE TRUE STORY.
NOW, THREE DAYS
AFTER THAT MONSTER APPEARED,
YOU SHOW UP,
FULLY GROWN INTO A VESSEL
SUITABLE FOR THAT POWER.
I SENSE DESTINY AT WORK.
THE TIME HAS COME.
I WILL REMOVE THE BULLET
FROM YOUR HEART.
THEN YOU CAN SHOW ME
ALL YOUR POWER --
THE FULL VAMPIRE POWER
INSIDE OF YOU.
-THANKS.
I THINK I'M COOL THE WAY I AM.
-UH...
WAIT. WHAT?
-IF YOU TAKE THE BULLET OUT,
THEN I'M JUST GONNA
HAVE TO FIGHT
WITH THAT BIG MONSTER, RIGHT?
FORGET IT.
THAT'S WAY TOO MUCH
RESPONSIBILITY.
LEARNING
ABOUT HUMAN RESURRECTION
IS ENOUGH FOR ME.
I DON'T WANT YOU ADDING IN
EXTRA BONUSES
AND CHANGING AROUND
THE TERMS OF OUR DEAL.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN BONUSES?
YOU'D HAVE YOUR POWERS BACK!
-THAT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE WITHOUT THEM.
SO FORGET ABOUT THAT,
AND LET'S WRAP UP THIS DEAL.
-I SEE.
LIZ!
-YES?!
OH. [ WHIMPERS ]
[ ZING! ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
-BRING OUT THE ZOMBIES.
-HUH?
-DID YOU HEAR ME?
-[ SHOUTS ]
-HEY. WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
-OUR NEGOTIATIONS ARE OFF.
SO, FROM HERE ON,
THERE WILL BE NO MORE DEALS.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-THIS IS AN ORDER.
KILL MY BROTHER.
-HUH?
-YOU SURE?
-UH...
-ROGER!
-WHAT WILL IT BE?
YOU'LL DIE
UNLESS THE BULLET IS REMOVED.
-[ GROWLS ] DAMN YOU!
-OKAY, WE GOT A BLOODY WALL
AND NO SIGN OF THIS GUY
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
HOW WILL YOU FIND HIM?
-BY CHALLENGING
THE TERRITORY BOSS.
-YOU'RE WOLF OF THE WEST?
-THIS LITTLE PUNK?
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
-YOU CAME ALL THE WAY HERE
TO TAKE OVER, HUH?
-WELL, AIN'T THAT NICE.
-BOSS.
AW, DAMN.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE KID.
THOUGHT IT'D BE THAT MONSTER
I'VE BEEN HEARING SO MUCH ABOUT.
-THAT MAKES SENSE.
I GUESS
THIS IS PROBABLY THE PLACE
YOU FIGURED
HE'D BE COMING NEXT, RIGHT?
-HOLD ON.
SO YOU KNOW ABOUT HIM, TOO?
-BUT SINCE THE BOSS IS ALIVE,
MAYBE IT PASSED ON BY.
AFTER ALL,
THE BOSS IS A WEAK-LOOKING PIG.
-HUH?
YOU LITTLE WEAKLING!
I'M NOT A PIG!
AAHHH!
-UH-OH!
-MOVE IT!
-[ SNORTS ]
-YEAH, YOU ARE.
-I'M NOT A PIG!
I'M A BOAR!
-OINK, OINK, PIGGY.
SORRY.
GOT TO BORROW YOUR TERRITORY.
I'M THE BOSS NOW.
-[ SNORTING ]
YOU LITTLE TWERP.
DON'T YOU GET COCKY!
-RELAX.
IT'S NOT LIKE
I WANT TO KILL YOU.
-TOO BAD. 'CAUSE I DO!
M-MY BODY!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
H-HELP ME!
-[ CHUCKLES ]
HI.
-[ LAUGHS ]
-[ GRUNTS, GAGS ]
-AAH!
-YOU JERK!
THIS IS BLACKMAIL!
-SORRY.
I'M AFRAID A REFUSAL IS
NO LONGER ONE OF YOUR OPTIONS,
AND A NEGOTIATION
IS OUT OF THE QUESTION.
YOU SEE, WE WERE NEVER
TRULY ON EQUAL FOOTING.
THAT IS...
...UNTIL THIS MOMENT.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-DID YOU JUST KILL HIM FOR REAL?
-WHAT A LETDOWN.
[ HEART BEATING ]
-NO, HE'S STILL ALIVE FOR NOW.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH HIM.
-DOES THAT MEAN IT'S OKAY
FOR US TO EAT HIM NOW?
-I GOT DIBS ON THE BRAINS!
-LET'S DIG IN!
-AAH!
-WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-[ SIGHS ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
-MY NAME IS AKIM.
HOW ABOUT A RIDDLE?
-OKAY,
WHAT PUNCH NEVER RUNS OUT,
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU DRINK?
-WHAT KIND OF RIDDLE IS THAT?
-MY PUNCH! NOW STOP DODGING!
-N-NEXT TIME ON BLOOD LAD,
"THAT'S FRIENDSHIP."
-IN THE DEMON WORLD,
IT'S GOOD TO BE BAD.