-YOU KNOW WHAT A VAMPIRE IS?
THAT'S RIGHT --
THE ONE WHO WEARS A CAPE
AND GOES AROUND AT NIGHT
SUCKING HUMAN BLOOD...
-[ GROANS ]
-...A MONSTER.
-HUH?
-AND THAT'S ME --
A DESCENDENT OF THE VAMPIRE.
[ VIDEO-GAME MUSIC PLAYS ]
-UGH!
SHIT, I MESSED UP!
STUPID PASSWORDS!
ANYWAY, I LOVE STUFF
MADE BY HUMANS,
ESPECIALLY THE ONES FROM JAPAN.
THEY HAVE MY TOTAL RESPECT.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T IMAGINE
LEAVING THIS PLACE
AND TRAVELING TO THE HUMAN WORLD
TO FEED ON THEM.
HMM?
AND WHERE IS THIS PLACE?
THIS IS THE DEMON WORLD.
FROM WHAT I HEAR,
MY ANCESTORS USED TO GO AROUND
SUCKING HUMAN BLOOD.
BUT IF YOU ASK ME, THAT'S CRAZY.
[ BLOWS ]
I MEAN, I HEAR
THAT THE SUN'S REALLY STRONG
IN THE HUMAN WORLD,
PLUS, YOU NEED MONEY
AND A PASSPORT TO GET THERE.
BESIDES, I MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT I'M REALLY BUSY.
YEAH? STAZ HERE.
-ONE TSUCHINOKO PLEASE!
WHAT THE HELL?!
[ PHONE RINGS ]
YEAH?!
-HEY, BOSS! YOU'RE UP.
THAT'S UNUSUAL.
-AH, DEK. IT'S YOU.
DID YOU GET THAT DVD AND
THE FIGURE I ASKED YOU ABOUT?
UH, NO, I HAVEN'T HAD TIME
TO GRAB THOSE YET.
BUT I GOT
A LITTLE SOMETHIN' SOMETHIN'
YOU MIGHT FIND
EVEN MORE INTERESTING.
-LIKE WHAT?
-YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS.
IT'S A WOMAN, A HUMAN ONE.
-[ GASPS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-A HUMAN...WOMAN?
-I DON'T KNOW THE WHOLE STORY,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S HERE
BY ACCIDENT.
WE'RE NOT REALLY SURE
HOW TO HANDLE THIS,
SO WE FIGURED
WE SHOULD REPORT TO YOU.
I MEAN,
THIS ISN'T THE HUMAN WORLD.
IS IT, UH, OKAY
TO USE OUR DEMON WORLD RULES?
LIKE, ONCE YOU'VE ENTERED
ANOTHER'S TERRITORY,
YOU CAN'T COMPLAIN ABOUT
WHAT'S DONE TO YOU.
UH, BOSS?
ARE YOU LISTENING?
-A HUMAN WOMAN!
A WOMAN IN THE DEMON WORLD!
A HUMAN!
BRING HER HERE NOW!
YOUR TERRITORY BOSS ORDERS IT.
SEE, THE DEMON WORLD IS DIVIDED
INTO SEVERAL TERRITORIES,
AND I'M ONE OF THE TERRITORY
BOSSES WHO'S IN CHARGE OF 'EM.
I TRY TO ACT LIKE A BOSS
BECAUSE OF MY POSITION,
BUT, RIGHT NOW...
[ GROANING ]
A HUMAN?
I'M GETTING TO MEET
A REAL HUMAN WOMAN!
IT'S LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE.
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT DO I TALK ABOUT FIRST?
IF SHE'S JAPANESE,
I WANT TO THANK HER PEOPLE
FOR MY COOL GAME CONSOLE!
ARIGATO! OH, YEAH!
AND FOR CELLPHONES!
MANGA! I HAVE TO KNOW
IF SHE LIKES MANGA!
AND MUSIC!
WONDER WHICH SONG I SHOULD PLAY?
CRAP, WHAT SHOULD I WEAR?
I'VE GOT NOTHING
BUT CHEAP IMITATIONS
OF HUMAN-WORLD STYLES!
THEY DON'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO THE REAL DEAL!
COME ON! THINK! THINK! THINK!
AAAAAAH!
-HMM?
-[ SNIFFING ]
-[ WHIMPERING ]
[ ELEVATOR BELL DINGS ]
-I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE THIS
IS A LITTLE MUCH.
-BOSS!
-HUH? WAIT!
-I'M HERE WITH THE GIRL!
-NO! I-I'M NOT READY...
YET.
OHH.
-YOU, UH, OKAY?
-[ CLEARS THROAT ]
GOOD WORK, DEK. YOU CAN GO NOW.
-HUH?
-JUST GO!
AND DON'T LET ANYBODY IN!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
AS SOON AS OUR EYES MET, I FELT
LIKE I WAS BEING SUCKED IN!
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE MY HEART
IS BEING SQUEEZED!
WHAT IS THIS FEELING?!
-SO? THINK BOSS IS GONNA
EAT HER ALL BY HIMSELF
OR LEAVE SOME FOR US?
-I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE WASN'T ACTING
LIKE HIS USUAL SELF.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-HMM, WAS ALMOST
LIKE HE WAS NERVOUS.
-ALL RIGHT!
STEP RIGHT UP AND DON'T BE SHY.
BE THE FIRST TO GET ONE
OF THESE RARE PLANTS
ONLY FOUND IN SOUTH DEMON WORLD.
THEY MAKE GREAT PETS!
FUN FOR THE WHOLE FAMILY!
HOW 'BOUT IT?
-YOU DON'T LOOK FAMILIAR.
-EH?
-WHO THE HELL GAVE YOU
PERMISSION TO SET UP SHOP HERE?
-I NEED PERMISSION?
-IF YOU WANT TO DO BUSINESS
IN SOMEONE'S TERRITORY,
YOU NEED PERMISSION
FROM ITS BOSS!
THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES
IN THE DEMON WORLD!
-I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T KNOW.
PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO MEET YOUR BOSS, THEN.
-YOU COME BACK ANOTHER TIME.
BOSS IS BUSY NOW.
-OH, I GET IT.
HE'S GOT
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
IN THAT CASE, I'LL JUST HAVE TO
FORCE HIM TO COME OUT.
-SERIOUSLY?!
THE GAME ALREADY HAS
THAT MANY SEQUELS?!
-YES, I BELIEVE SO.
-THERE'S NOTHING "FINAL"
ABOUT IT, THEN!
-NO, I GUESS NOT.
-THIS IS SO AWESOME!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M TALKING
TO A REAL HUMAN LIKE THIS.
-UM, IF IT'S OKAY,
WOULD YOU MIND IF I ASKED YOU
A QUESTION NOW?
[ PHONE RINGING ]
-SORRY. JUST A MINUTE.
YEAH, WHAT?!
A TERRITORY CRASHER?
YEAH?
WAIT, A PLANT DID WHAT?
HUH. SORRY,
I CAN'T GO RIGHT NOW.
NO. NO. I SAID I CAN'T GO!
HUH? YAMADA'S GETTING KILLED?
NEVER HEARD OF HIM!
SORRY, THIS CONNECTION IS BAD.
YOU'RE BREAKING UP,
CAN'T HEAR YOU.
-[ SIGHS ]
-SO, WHERE WERE WE?
-UM, THAT PHONE CALL SOUNDED
LIKE IT WAS IMPORTANT.
-NAH, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT GUYS LIKE THAT.
-BUT...
-IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME DEAL.
THEY CRASH THE TERRITORY
AND TRY TO TAKE THE BOSS'S HEAD.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-I'M THE BOSS NOW, BUT WHOEVER
COMES ALONG AND DEFEATS ME
WILL BE THE NEXT ONE IN CHARGE.
IT'S JUST THE WAY THESE THINGS
WORK AROUND HERE.
PRETTY STUPID, HUH?
-YAMADA! YAMADA!
-I, UH...
-YEAH?
-...TO BE HONEST,
I'M STILL NOT SURE WHERE I AM,
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY
I'M HERE.
I FEEL SO CONFUSED.
-UH-HUH.
-IT'S LIKE BEING AWAKE
INSIDE OF A DREAM.
-I KNOW. FEELS LIKE
I'M DREAMING, TOO.
IMAGINE --
ME MEETING A HUMAN.
-THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
-HUH?
-IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT IS
THAT YOU GO TO YOUR FRIENDS
BECAUSE THEY NEED YOUR HELP.
-IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN...
WHEN SHE STARES AT ME
WITH THOSE EYES.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
I SEE. SO THAT'S IT.
-UM, ARE, UH, YOU ALL RIGHT?
-YOU'RE JUST --
YOU'RE JUST SO CUTE!
-HUH?!
I LIKE YOU!
SO I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU
IN ANY WAY.
IN FACT, WHAT I REALLY WANT TO
DO IS PROTECT YOU!
YEAH, THAT'S IT!
I REALLY WANT TO PROTECT YOU!
I DON'T HAVE ANY URGE TO BITE
INTO THAT WHITE,
SOFT-LOOKING NECK OF YOURS.
I'LL DO ANYTHING
YOU ASK ME TO DO. ANYTHING!
AND THAT'S WHY I'M GONNA GO.
IT SOUNDS LIKE MY BUDDIES ARE
IN SOME KIND OF TROUBLE!
-BUT, WAIT!
THAT WINDOW IS --
-DUN-DUN-DUN DA!
-WHY'D I LIE TO HER LIKE THAT?
WHY DIDN'T
I JUST SUCK HER BLOOD?
I COULD'VE FED ON HER.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
-AH!
BOSS!
-WELL, WELL.
IT APPEARS THAT THE BOSS
HAS FINALLY SHOWN UP --
THE ONE WHOSE NAME IS KNOWN
THROUGHOUT THE EAST DEMON WORLD,
THE VAMPIRE, STAZ.
-VAMPIRE. YUP, THAT'S ME.
-I'VE BEEN TOLD
YOU'RE PRETTY CONCEITED.
-I ALWAYS HATED IT THE THING
ABOUT SUCKING HUMAN BLOOD.
-SO I'VE COME HERE
TO TEACH YOU A LESSON.
-BELONGING TO NOBILITY,
GOING AROUND IN A STUPID CAPE --
ALL OF IT.
-WATCH OUT FOR HAVE THEM VINES.
THOSE THINGS'LL CHOP YOU
TO SHREDS
IF YOU GET TOO CLOSE TO 'EM.
-FINE.
-BOSS?
-[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
COMING STRAIGHT AT ME?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
I'M GONNA RIP YOU TO PIECES!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
-I'M A VAMPIRE,
BUT I CAN EAT GARLIC,
WALK IN THE SUNLIGHT, AND A
CROSS DOESN'T SCARE ME ONE BIT.
-HUH?
-AND YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH I'M
A VAMPIRE, I'M MORE THAN THAT.
I'M MY OWN PERSON!
-AAAAH!
M-MY HEART'S BEING CRUSHED!
-HEART CONSTRICTION! ZIP!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
-WHOA, THAT WAS AMAZING, BOSS.
-YEAH.
-YOU WERE FREAKIN' POWERFUL
TODAY.
LET ME GUESS -- YOU BEEN
SUCKIN' ON THAT HUMAN?
-NO, NOT YET.
GOOD. SHE'S STILL INSIDE.
-HEY, BOSS, WHAT'S UP?
YOU SURE SEEM HAPPY
ABOUT SOMETHING.
-DON'T BE AN IDIOT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO SUCK HER BLOOD
BECAUSE I'M A VAMPIRE.
I WANT TO AS AN INDIVIDUAL.
I'M BACK.
[ GASPS ]
-AAH!
-NO WAY. THIS CAN'T BE!
SAY IT AIN'T SO.
-UH, BOSS?
-[ SQUEALS ]
W-WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
WHY AM I NAKED ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WHERE DID MY CLOTHES GO?
-SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL HERE?
DOES THIS BELONG TO SOMEBODY
ELSE OR SOMETHING?
-DID THAT THING
ONLY SWALLOW HER CLOTHES?
-CAN I PLEASE HAVE SOMETHING
TO COVER MYSELF UP WITH?
-HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S WEIRD.
-WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WEIRD?
-I'M NOT ATTRACTED TO YOU
ANYMORE, LIKE, AT ALL.
WONDER WHY?
-HEY, I THINK I KNOW.
-HUH?
-I HEARD THAT WHEN HUMANS DIE
IN THE DEMON WORLD,
THEY TURN INTO SOMETHING
CALLED "GHOSTS."
SEE THERE? THAT TRIANGULAR
HEADPIECE SHE HAS IS THE MARK.
-A GHOST? I SEE.
THAT MEANS
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO SEE HER
AS A LIVING, BREATHING HUMAN
AGAIN.
NO, I CAN'T GIVE UP SO EASILY.
IF HER BONES AND HER SOUL
ARE INTACT,
THEN I JUST HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT HER FLESH. HMM.
-UH, BOSS?
-ALL RIGHT.
I'M BRINGING HER BACK TO LIFE.
THAT'S MY BLOOD OATH.
-UM...COULD I GET SOME CLOTHES,
PLEASE?
I GUESS THE FACT THAT I'M DEAD
REALLY HASN'T SUNK IN YET.
HOW DID I GET MYSELF
INTO THIS MESS?
HEY! WHY ARE YOU PUTTING
MY SKULL ON TOP OF THAT?!
-IS THERE A PROBLEM?
-IT'LL GET ALL HEATED UP
IN THERE!
UM, DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
LEND ME SOME MORE CLOTHES?
I MEAN, WEARING
JUST A T-SHIRT AND BOXERS
KIND OF MAKES ME FEEL
A LITTLE SKIMPY.
ARE YOU IGNORING ME?
-JUST DEAL WITH IT
UNTIL YOUR CLOTHES DRY, 'KAY?
GREAT, I'M STUCK
WITH A NAGGING GHOST.
-STAZ, THE VAMPIRE.
HE SAYS HE'S THE BOSS
OF THIS TERRITORY,
BUT TO ME, HE JUST LOOKS LIKE
AN UNEMPLOYED, LAZY SLACKER.
OH, I KNOW THIS MANGA.
-HEY, DON'T TOUCH!
-IS IT JUST ME, OR HAS
HIS WHOLE ATTITUDE CHANGED
SINCE I TURNED INTO A GHOST?
-SHUT UP.
BY THE WAY, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
-MY NAME? FUYUMI.
-OH.
-YOU TOLD ME YOU'D DO
EVERYTHING YOU POSSIBLY COULD
TO BRING ME BACK TO LIFE.
ARE YOU STILL SERIOUS
ABOUT THAT?
-THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING NOW.
-BUT YOU'RE READING A MANGA.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
SOME OF THESE HAVE STORIES
ABOUT HOW TO RESURRECT PEOPLE.
SO I'M LOOKING FOR THAT.
-AND YOU'RE RELYING ON MANGA?
WHAT A NIGHTMARE!
AT THIS RATE, HE'LL START SAYING
HE NEEDS TO COLLECT
SEVEN MYSTICAL BALLS
THAT CAN GRANT A WISH.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
SOMETHING MYSELF!
AH!
STAZ, LISTEN!
-YES, I FOUND IT!
-NO, DON'T!
-YOU SEE THIS DRAGON?
-THAT'S ENOUGH! PLEASE STAZ.
YOU'VE GOT TO
PUT THAT MANGA AWAY!
-WHAT?
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU HERE.
-BUT I JUST REMEMBERED
SOMETHING!
-YOU KNOW THE SPELL
OF RESTORATION?
-NO! I JUST REMEMBERED
HOW I CAME TO THE DEMON WORLD.
-HUH?
-I-I'M NOT GONNA FALL
FOR THAT TRICK.
-FINE. THEN I'LL GO ALONE.
-NO. I MEAN WAIT.
I'M OUT OF SHAMPOO.
I BETTER GO WITH YOU.
[ GASPS ]
HOLY CRAP!
IS THAT THING FOR REAL?
-I'M PRETTY SURE THIS IS WHAT
I PASSED THROUGH TO GET HERE.
-THIS IS KNOWN
AS THE BLACK CURTAIN.
IT ENABLES YOU TO TRAVEL
THROUGH SPACE,
AND IT'S THE HIGHEST FORM
OF SPATIAL MAGIC.
IT'S THE FIRST ONE I'VE SEEN.
-WELL, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
GOODBYE.
-HANG ON!
THIS CURTAIN AIN'T SOMETHING
YOU FIND
JUST SITTING AROUND
ON THE STREET!
-BUT IT IS.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
-HUH? OH, YEAH.
IT'S THERE, ALL RIGHT!
HOWEVER, THIS THING ONLY APPEARS
WHEN THE SPELL CASTER
TRAVELS BETWEEN
THE DEMON AND HUMAN WORLD.
THEN IT'S SUPPOSED TO DISAPPEAR.
AND NOW THAT I'VE SEEN
THE BLACK CURTAIN MYSELF,
I KNOW I CAN'T LET YOU GO BACK
ALL ALONE.
-HUH?
-I'M COMING, TOO!
-UH, WHAT ABOUT YOUR SHAMPOO?
-WHAT?! SCREW THE SHAMPOO!
I CAN GO TO THE HUMAN WORLD
FROM HERE! THE HUMAN WORLD!
DO YOU KNOW
HOW IMPORTANT THIS IS?
HOW I DREAMED ABOUT GOING THERE?
THE DVD BOX SETS,
THE LIMITED EDITION FIGURES!
MANGA! GAMES! EVERYTHING!
THEY'RE ALL WAITING FOR ME ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT CURTAIN!
HANG TIGHT, GUYS, I'M ON MY WAY!
-OKAY, I GET IT!
I GET IT ALREADY!
-HEY, YOU THINK I'LL LOOK OKAY
IN THESE CLOTHES?
I DON'T LOOK LIKE A GEEK, DO I?
-NO, YOU LOOK FINE.
JUST FINE.
-YOU SAID "FINE" TWICE.
DON'T PEOPLE DO THAT
WHEN THEY MEAN THE OPPOSITE?
-WILL YOU PLEASE CALM DOWN?
IF WE'RE GONNA GO,
THEN LET'S GET GOING.
-YOU MORON!
IF IT WERE THAT SIMPLE,
I WOULD HAVE DONE IT BY NOW!
-SORRY!
-WE GOT TO GET YOU TESTED FIRST.
-COME ON.
-WAIT, DO WHAT?
[ BELL JINGLES ]
-ANOTHER SLOW DAY?
-HEY, IF YOU'RE GONNA WASTE
MY TIME, BEAT IT.
-FINE. GIVE ME TWO GINGER ALES.
-H-HEY, STAZ, UH, UM --
-YEAH, WHAT?
-YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT COMING TO A CAFé.
HOW COULD YOU BRING ME IN HERE
KNOWING THAT I'M DRESSED
IN THESE CLOTHES?
-WHY?
A SECOND AGO YOU COULDN'T WAIT
TO GO BACK TO THE HUMAN WORLD
DRESSED LIKE THAT,
BUT NOW YOU'RE FEELING
EMBARRASSED?
-W-WELL, I --
-LOOK, I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
ANXIOUS AND WANT TO GO HOME.
BUT, WHEN YOU GO BACK THIS TIME,
IT WON'T BE AS A HUMAN,
YOU'LL BE GOING BACK AS A DEMON.
-SO, DOES THAT MEAN A DEMON
ISN'T SUPPOSED TO WEAR
ANY CLOTHING
WHILE IN THE HUMAN WORLD?
-NO, YOU DITZ.
-HEY, HEY. DID YOU GUYS
COME IN HERE TO ARGUE?
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
COME ON, NOW, GIVE ME A BREAK!
-[ GASPS ]
-HERE.
-THIS ANIMAL'S TALKING,
AND NOT ONLY THAT,
HE JUST POURED SOME SODA
INTO A LITTLE CUP!
H-HOW CUTE!
AND HE'S SO FLUFFY.
-H-HEY STAZ, WHO IS THIS CHICK,
ANYWAY?!
-NOW, THEN YOU ALREADY KNOW
WHY I'M HERE, RIGHT, SATY?
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
LOOK HER OVER FOR ME?
SHE WANTS TO GO
TO THE HUMAN WORLD.
-CUT IT OUT!
-THERE, THERE.
-SO, YOU THINK SHE CAN MAKE IT,
OR WHAT?
-WELL, I THINK WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO TAKE A LOOK FIRST.
OKAY, LET'S GIVE IT A TRY, THEN.
EXPOSING EVERYTHING,
AND SEEING THROUGH EVERYTHING
WITH OUR THIRD EYE.
BEHOLD!
THE ALL-SEEING SEARCH EYES!
-UHHH...
W-WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
THEY'RE BOTH SHINING LIKE CRAZY!
-YEAH, KIND OF TRIPPY, ISN'T IT?
-OKAY, WE GOT IT.
FROM WHAT WE BOTH CAN TELL,
YOU USED TO BE HUMAN, RIGHT?
BUT YOU'VE JUST BECOME A DEMON,
SO YOUR EXISTENCE
IS VERY UNSTABLE.
-A-MAZING.
IT'S LIKE MAGIC!
-OF COURSE IT IS.
-BY THE WAY,
PUTTING ON BOXERS WITHOUT A BRA
MAKES YOU LOOK
LIKE A REAL PERVERT.
-AH!
OH, NO, WAIT, I CAN EXPLAIN.
-AW, MAN, SHUT UP!
SO, CAN SHE GO OR NOT?
-OH, THERE'S NO PROBLEM
WITH HER GOING,
BUT I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND STAYING
OVER THERE TOO LONG.
-YEAH?
WELL, THAT'S ALL I NEED TO KNOW.
-YOU NEED HER TO DO SOMETHING
IN THE HUMAN WORLD, IS THAT IT?
-ACTUALLY, I'LL BE GOING
ALONG WITH HER.
-HUH?
GOING ALONG?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR TERRITORY?!
-SHOULD BE FINE.
-ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
IF WORD GETS OUT
THAT OUR BOSS IS GONE,
ALL HELL WILL BREAK LOOSE
AROUND HERE!
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME, STAZ?
[ BELL JINGLES ]
YO.
-'SUP?
HEY, BOSS, YOU GOT A MINUTE?
WELL, GO ON, TELL HIM YOURSELF!
OH, UH, H-HI,
I'M YOSHIDA THE MIMIC,
AND I'VE ALWAYS HAD GREAT
RESPECT FOR YOU, MR. STAZ.
PLEASE LET ME JOIN YOUR GANG.
-FORGET HIM, DEK.
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE IT!
THIS IDIOT WANTS TO LEAVE US
AND GO OFF TO THE HUMAN WORLD!
-HUH?
-JUST IMAGINE WHEN ALL
THE OTHER TERRITORIES FIND OUT.
THEY'LL START
A MASSIVE DEATH MATCH
AS THEY FIGHT OVER THE POSITION
OF TERRITORY BOSS!
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
WILL HAPPEN
TO THE PUNY LITTLE ANIMALS
LIKE ME?
I'LL TELL YA! WE'LL BE THE FIRST
TO GET CAPTURED AND EATEN!
-OKAY, I GET IT.
-OH, YOU DO?
-YEAH, AND THAT'S WHY
I'VE DECIDED TO RESIGN.
-OH.
-WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
ARE YOU NUTS?
-YEAH! I DON'T GET IT.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
-IT'S NOT GOOD
IF THE BOSS IS GONE,
SO SOMEBODY ELSE SHOULD TAKE
OVER FOR ME.
AM I RIGHT?
-OH, UM, IT'S YOSHIDA.
-OH, OKAY. YOSHIDA,
AS OF NOW YOU'RE THE BOSS.
-WHAT?
-WHOA! THAT'S MY FACE!
WHAT ARE YOU?!
-SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I HAVE A HABIT OF TRANSFORMING
INTO THINGS I'D WANT TO BE.
- OH, SO, YOU'RE
A SHAPE-SHIFTER, HUH? GREAT!
WHILE THE BOSS IS GONE,
YOU CAN STICK WITH US,
TAKE HIS FORM
UNTIL HE COMES BACK.
-GOOD IDEA!
-OH!
-HEY, BOSS, YOU CAN GO
TO THE HUMAN WORLD AFTER ALL!
-SWEET!
MY VERY OWN BODY DOUBLE!
YOSHIDA, YOU'RE IN!
-SO, IT SOUNDS LIKE
EVERYTHING'S BEEN SETTLED, THEN.
-SO, UM, HERE'S TO ME
FINALLY BEING ABLE TO LEAVE
FOR THE HUMAN WORLD.
OH, YEAH, LET'S NOT FORGET
OUR NEWEST MEMBER, YOSHIDA.
SO, I GUESS...
-CHEERS!
-CHEERS, GUYS.
I GOT TO TAKE A LEAK.
-UH...
SO, DEK, DOES STAZ ALWAYS ACT
LIKE THIS WHEREVER HE GOES?
-HMM?
-IT'S JUST, HE SEEMS SO
IRRESPONSIBLE.
-WILL HE REALLY TRY
TO BRING ME BACK TO LIFE,
OR WAS THAT
JUST AN EMPTY PROMISE?
-MM, WELL, ONCE HE FINALLY MAKES
UP HIS MIND TO DO SOMETHING,
HE SEES IT THROUGH TO THE END.
HE'LL GO TO THE HUMAN WORLD
EVEN IF IT MEANS GIVING UP
HIS POSITION AS THE BOSS.
ONCE THAT SWITCH IS ON,
HE CAN'T TURN IT OFF,
AND 'CAUSE OF THAT,
HE'S ALWAYS DRIVIN' US CRAZY
WITH ONE THING AFTER ANOTHER.
THAT MUST BE TOUGH.
-THERE'S ONE THING I CAN TELL
YOU, THOUGH --
REMEMBER WHEN HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT BRINGING YOU BACK TO LIFE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
LOOK SO DETERMINED.
-R-REALLY?
S-SOUNDS LIKE
A PRETTY STRANGE GUY TO ME.
-HUH? HEY, WHO SAID YOU COULD
SIT THERE AND EAT MY TSUCHINOKO?
-TSUCHINOKO!
-I WAS SAVING IT FOR LAST!
HEY, SATY, GRILL ME ANOTHER ONE.
-NO, DON'T!
-WHY NOT?
-SO, THE PARTY CONTINUED WITH
PEOPLE I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW,
DOING THINGS
I DIDN'T ALWAYS UNDERSTAND.
-TSUCHINOKO!
-THE TSCUCHINOKO
WAS ACTUALLY VERY GOOD, THOUGH,
AND THE FOLLOWING DAY,
MY SCHOOL UNIFORM WAS COMPLETELY
DRY AND READY TO GO.
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-ALL RIGHT, THEN.
OFF TO THE HUMAN WORLD!
-HMM.
ALL RIGHT!
THE HUMAN WORLD!
-YOU'D BETTER FIND
A WAY TO REVIVE ME.
-YEAH, SURE -- AFTER I GET
MY PRECIOUS DVDs AND FIGURES!
-THAT'S YOUR PRIORITY?
N-NEXT TIME ON "BLOOD LAD,"
"BACK HOME, BUT NOT REALLY."
-IN THE DEMON WORLD,
IT'S GOOD TO BE BAD.