-HOLY CRAP!
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S REAL!
IT'S THE BLACK CURTAIN...
A PORTAL THAT MAKES TRAVELING
BETWEEN THE DEMON
AND HUMAN WORLDS POSSIBLE.
NOW I CAN FINALLY EXPERIENCE
SOMETHING
I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED ABOUT --
HUMAN CULTURE
IN ALL ITS AWESOMENESS!
THIS MAGICAL CURTAIN
IS MY TICKET
TO MAKING IT ALL COME TRUE!
I'VE WANTED TO GO THERE
FOR SO LONG!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GETTING THE CHANCE TO VISIT!
-I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU WERE
GOING TO BRING ME BACK TO LIFE.
-THAT'S ENOUGH TALKING.
LET'S DO THIS!
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
-UH, I THINK
WE MADE A WRONG TURN.
-IT'S MY ROOM.
LOOKS JUST THE WAY I LEFT IT.
-HOLD ON. YOU MEAN,
YOU ACTUALLY LIVE HERE?
-[ SIGHS ]
-YOU'RE IN PRISON?
-UH, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
-I MEAN, LIKE THE PLACE
IS COMPLETELY EMPTY.
-I JUST PREFER TO KEEP THINGS
NICE AND NEAT, THAT'S ALL!
-SO, WHAT DO YOU
USUALLY DO IN HERE, MEDITATE?
-WELL, I USUALLY SPEND
MOST OF MY TIME AT SCHOOL.
AND EVERYDAY AFTER I COME HOME,
I STUDY.
SO I KEEP MY ROOM TIDY AND FREE
OF ANY DISTRACTIONS.
-MM-HMM.
-BUT, STAZ, WE DIDN'T COME HERE
SO WE CAN TALK ABOUT
MY CLEANING HABITS.
YOU NEED TO FOCUS
ON WHY WE'RE HERE.
-YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GO TO YOUR SCHOOL.
-HUH?
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE,
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS!
YOU'RE REALLY GOING
TO MY SCHOOL?
-YEAH, I WANT TO CHECK IT OUT.
WE'LL MAKE UP A STORY
THAT I'M A TRANSFER STUDENT,
JUST LIKE THEY DO IN MANGA
AND ANIME, ALL RIGHT?
-WAIT, SO NOW YOU WANT TO
ENROLL THERE?
-HUH?
-FUYUMI? THAT YOU?
-UH, HI, D-DADDY.
-WHERE HAVE BEEN, YOUNG LADY?
AND WHO'S THAT BOY WITH YOU?
YOU KNOW THE RULES
OF THIS HOUSE!
-OH, HE'S MY, UH...
-THE SCHOOL CALLED AND TOLD ME
YOU NEVER SHOWED UP YESTERDAY.
DO YOU KNOW HOW WORRIED I WAS?
YOU HAD BETTER HAVE
A GOOD EXPLANATION!
HELLO, STAZ,
SO NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
ARE YOU GETTING READY
FOR SCHOOL?
I NEED TO GET GOING
AND HEAD OFF TO WORK.
DON'T YOU BE TARDY, NOW.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
-DOT, DOT, DOT.
WOULD YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT THE HECK
YOU JUST DID TO MY DAD?
-OH, THAT? SEE,
ONCE A HUMAN IS BITTEN,
HE FALLS UNDER
A VAMPIRE'S TOTAL CONTROL...
-[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
-USING A LIQUID
SECRETED FROM MY FANGS,
I DILUTED IT A LITTLE
WITH WATER AND MADE THIS SPRAY.
BASICALLY, IT'S MY SPIT.
-GET THAT GROSS STUFF
AWAY FROM ME.
-RELAX. IT DOESN'T WORK
ON DEMONS, ANYWAY.
-OH. RIGHT, DEMONS.
-OHHH!
OH, MY GOD!
SO, THIS IS SUNLIGHT?
-I'M NOT THE SAME.
GUESS IT NEVER REALLY
STRUCK ME BEFORE
THAT I'D TURNED INTO
SOMETHING ELSE.
-IT'S LIKE I GOT TINGLIES
ALL OVER MY BODY.
-NOW...I'M NOT EVEN HUMAN
ANYMORE.
-THE SUN DOESN'T BOTHER YOU,
DOES IT?
-HUH? OH, UH, N-NO...
-THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU'VE SPENT YOUR ENTIRE LIFE
HERE IN THIS HUMAN ENVIRONMENT.
BUT YOU'RE NOT
ONE OF 'EM ANYMORE.
SO I SHOULD PROBABLY SHOW YOU
THE WAY DEMONS GET AROUND
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
-UH...
-FIRST OFF,
THE WHOLE "HUMANS FEARING
DEMONS" THING IS OLD NEWS.
IT JUST DOESN'T HAPPEN ANYMORE.
NOT EVEN THE STRONGEST DEMON
STANDS A CHANCE
AGAINST THE SHEER NUMBER
OF HUMANS
AND THEIR ADVANCED TECHNOLOGY.
AND THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO MOVE
MUCH MORE CAREFULLY
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
SO TRY NOT TO DRAW
ANY ATTENTION, OKAY?
-SURE, IF YOU SAY SO.
-AWESOME! JUST LOOK AT ALL
THE CARS ON THE ROAD!
THESE TRAINS ARE AMAZING!
IT'S LIKE A MOVING ROOM!
SO FAST AND COMFORTABLE!
LOOK AT THIS SCHOOL!
CHECK OUT ALL THESE STUDENTS!
-OKAY, SAY "CHEESE," EVERYONE!
-HEY, STOP THAT!
CALM DOWN. EVERYONE'S STARING
AT US LIKE WE'RE NUTS!
-YOU THINK THEY CAN TELL
I'M A DEMON?
-I DON'T REALLY THINK
THAT'S THE ISSUE RIGHT NOW.
-WELL, IN THAT CASE...
-[ GASPS ]
-HEY THERE, HERE YOU GO,
JUST A LITTLE VAMPIRE SPIT.
ANY OF YOU LOSERS WHO EVEN THINK
ABOUT DISTURBING THE PEACE
HERE IN EAST DEMON WORLD
WILL HAVE TO ANSWER TO ME!
-THAT'S GOOD, BUT CAN WE GET YOU
TO SOUND MORE LIKE A SLACKER?
-YEAH, JUST RELAX
AND TRY TO ACT LIKE AN IDIOT.
-YOU KNOW, I'M LIKE, THE BOSS
OF THIS WHOLE TERRITORY
OR WHATEVER. YOU UNDERSTAND?
SO YOU'D BETTER LISTEN TO ME,
OR I'M GONNA HAVE TO MESS YOU UP
OR DO SOMETHIN' PRETTY CRAPPY
RIGHT BACK TO YOU.
HOW WAS THAT?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-I THINK HE'S GOT IT.
-SEEMS LIKE IT ALL HAPPENED
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE.
-THINK I'LL JUST CROP-DUST THE
REST OF THE SCHOOL WITH THIS.
-APPARENTLY, PEOPLE WHO COME
IN CONTACT WITH THE SPRAY
DON'T FIND ANYTHING THE LEAST
BIT STRANGE ABOUT THE TWO OF US.
AND JUST LIKE THAT,
I'M BACK TO MY DAILY LIFE...
AS IF NOTHING HAD HAPPENED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
-ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S GOT THE ANSWER?
YAMADA.
-I'M IN CLASS, BUT I DON'T HAVE
MY NOTEBOOK,
MY PEN,
OR ANY OF MY TEXTBOOKS.
AND NO ONE EVEN NOTICES.
-HEY! WHAT'VE I SAID ABOUT
BRINGING MANGA TO SCHOOL?
-HUH?
-UHH.
-I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS MANGA BEFORE.
WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
OH, MAN,
THE ARTWORK LOOKS AWESOME!
-HUH?
-HMM?
-HEY, FUYUMI.
WHERE WERE YOU YESTERDAY?
WE MISSED YOU!
YOU DIDN'T COME
TO ANY OF YOUR CLASSES.
-OH, I UH...
-OH, COME ON,
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
SHE WAS TOTALLY IN CLASS!
-WHAT? ARE YOU SURE?
-WELL, ACTUALLY, SAKU'S RIGHT.
I WASN'T AT SCHOOL YESTERDAY.
-WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
LISTEN, DON'T FEEL
LIKE YOU HAVE TO SIT THERE
AND GO ALONG WITH
WHAT THIS IDIOT'S SAYING.
YOU REALLY CAN'T REMEMBER?
-WAIT, YOU'RE RIGHT! YEAH.
IT'S ALL COMING BACK TO ME.
OF COURSE SHE DID.
-WHAT?
THEY'RE TALKING AS IF
I WAS REALLY HERE YESTERDAY.
-THE THREE OF US STOPPED OFF
ON OUR WAY HOME.
-IT WAS CRAZY IN THERE,
WASN'T IT?
-YEAH, BUT THE FOOD WAS AMAZING!
WAIT! SAKU! HOLD ON!
THAT'S NOT ME!
IF EVERYBODY HERE HAS MEMORIES
THAT'VE BEEN CREATED,
AND THEY HONESTLY
BELIEVE THEM...
THEN THERE'S A ME
WHO'S NOT ME.
SO, WHAT WILL HAPPEN
TO THE REAL ME?
IT WON'T MATTER
IF I'M HERE OR NOT.
IS THIS WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO BECOME A GHOST?
-SO, ENJOYING YOUR TIME HERE?
-[ GASPS ] BLEH, BLEH.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-WHAT ARE YOU CRYING ABOUT,
FUYUMI?
-HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
-DO WHAT?
-IF I'D JUST TOLD MY DAD
AND EVERYONE THE TRUTH,
THEY MIGHT HAVE UNDERSTOOD.
BUT THEN YOU HAD TO GO
AND SPRAY EVERYONE
WITH THAT VAMPIRE JUICE.
-SO, WHAT WERE YOU
GONNA TELL THEM?
"I DIED AND BECAME A GHOST,
BUT THINGS WILL STILL BE
THE SAME SO DON'T WORRY"?
TEE-HEE! IS THAT IT?
DON'T BE SO NAIVE.
YOU NEED TO GET OVER IT
AND ACCEPT THE
FACT YOU'RE A DEMON.
WHAT YOU SAY MAYBE TRUE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO INVOLVE
THE PEOPLE I CARE ABOUT.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO ACCEPT IT,
BUT IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
PLEASE, JUST MAKE THEM
GO BACK TO NORMAL.
IF IT'S THE SAME TO THEM
WHETHER I'M HERE OR NOT,
I'D RATHER JUST DISAPPEAR
COMPLETELY
AND MAKE THINGS
EASIER FOR EVERYBODY.
-OH, YEAH?
YOU DON'T SAY?
I GUESS GHOSTS REALLY DO
DISAPPEAR FROM THE FEET UP.
-WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU THINK THIS IS A JOKE?
-TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR BODY.
IT'S FADING AWAY.
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! ]
-WHAT'S GOING ON?
-WITHOUT SOME RESILIENCY,
DEMONS AREN'T ABLE TO MAINTAIN
A STABLE EXISTENCE
WHEN THEY'RE HERE
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
THAT'S ESPECIALLY TRUE
OF LOW-LEVEL DEMONS.
-BUT I THOUGHT I PASSED
THE EXAMINATION,
AND HE SAID I'D BE OKAY HERE.
-TO COME HERE, YEAH.
BUT HE DIDN'T RECOMMEND
A LONG-TERM STAY.
-I-I GUESS. BUT WE'VE ONLY BEEN
HERE A LITTLE WHILE.
-YOU WANTED TO DISAPPEAR, RIGHT?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
-I DIDN'T MEAN IT! COME BACK!
IT WAS ONLY A FIGURE OF SPEECH.
YOU DIDN'T THINK
I WAS SERIOUS DID YOU?
[ WHIMPERS ]
-YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE
DISAPPEARING YET, RIGHT?
-UH-HUH.
[ CHOMP! ]
LISTEN...
I WASN'T TRYING
TO BE A JERK TO YOU.
IN FACT,
I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU.
JUST WANTED TO MAKE THINGS
EASIER AFTER YOU'RE RESURRECTED.
EVERYTHING IS GONNA BE
JUST THE WAY IT WAS,
AND NO ONE'LL EVER KNOW
YOU DIED.
-HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
-LICK IT.
-LICK IT?
-YOU DON'T WANT TO DISAPPEAR,
RIGHT?
-BUT YOU'RE THUMB'S BLEEDING.
-YEAH. I KNOW, YOU IDIOT.
-BUT WHY?
-JUST HURRY UP!
I'LL BRING YOU BACK TO LIFE,
I PROMISE.
BUT UNTIL THEN, I'LL BE
YOUR PERSONAL BLOOD BANK.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
-MY BODY FEELS SO HOT INSIDE.
AND I'M GETTING
A LITTLE DIZZY, TOO.
HEY, LOOK I HAVE HANDS AGAIN.
[ SLOOP! ]
[ SIGHS ]
WOW. THIS DESK FEELS SO GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
-GUESS MY BLOOD
WAS TOO STRONG FOR HER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ALL THAT CRAP
I SAID BACK THERE.
AM I REALLY JUST GONNA LET HER
GO BACK TO THE HUMAN WORLD
AFTER SHE'S BROUGHT
BACK TO LIFE?
NO WAY.
I'LL SUCK HER BLOOD
TILL THERE'S NOTHING LEFT!
-I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GOT IT DONE.
-I KNOW. I'M SO GLAD THAT
I DIDN'T JUST GIVE UP ON IT.
-YOU'RE TELLING ME.
-IT'S SO WEIRD.
THIS PLACE IS FILLED
WITH LIVING HUMANS...
-WHAT?
-...BUT I HAVEN'T FELT THAT URGE
LIKE I DID WITH HER.
[ GROANS ]
SHE MUST BE SOMETHING SPECIAL
TO ME, AFTER ALL,
AND I'D BETTER FIND A WAY
TO RESURRECT HER SOON,
OR I'LL BE THE ONE
WHO HAS NO BLOOD LEFT.
BUT BEFORE THAT...
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHY DO YOU WANT US TO GO BACK
TO THE DEMON WORLD ALREADY?
I FEEL PERFECTLY FINE, SEE?
-MAYBE YOU ARE,
BUT I'M LOW ON MAGIC.
I CAN'T WIN A BOSS BATTLE
LIKE THIS.
I NEED TO GO BACK AND RECHARGE.
-W-WAIT A MINUTE.
NOW I'M ALL CONFUSED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"A BOSS BATTLE"?
-WHAT I MEAN IS AKIHABARA!
IT'S THE CYBER-CITY
THAT I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED OF!
AND I'M GONNA NEED TO BE
IN THE BEST CONDITION
TO TAKE THIS PLACE ON!
WHERE'S YOUR MOM?
-SHE'S NOT AROUND.
-IS SHE DEAD?
-DON'T KNOW FOR SURE.
WHEN I WAS OLD ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND THINGS,
SHE WASN'T THERE.
I ASKED MY DAD,
BUT HE WOULDN'T TELL ME
ANYTHING.
[ SPROING! SPROING! ]
[ SPROING! SPROING! SPROING! ]
-OH, HEY. WELCOME BACK.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-OH, MAN.
THIS IS SO COOL!
I KNOW I'M JUST HOUSE-SITTING,
BUT RIGHT NOW, THIS IS MY ROOM.
THE -- THE BOSS'S COLLECTION!
TALK ABOUT GOOD TASTE!
IT'S INCREDIBLE!
-'SUP?
-DEK! MR. DEK!
-LISTEN, MAN, YOU CAN HANG OUT
IN THE BOSS'S ROOM,
BUT REMEMBER TO STAY
TRANSFORMED.
-OH, SORRY.
-YOU NEVER KNOW WHO MIGHT BE
WATCHING AROUND HERE,
SO DON'T EVER
LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
-RIGHT.
-INTERESTING.
SO THAT'S HOW THEIR BOSS
WAS ABLE TO GET HERE.
GOOD TO KNOW.
-WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
-THE NAME'S HYDRA BELL.
I'M THE OWNER
OF THIS BLACK CURTAIN.
AND I'M ALSO A TOP-LEVEL
SPATIAL-MAGIC USER.
OH, BUT YOU CAN CALL ME BELL.
[ GIGGLES ]
-I THOUGHT THINGS WERE GOING
A LITTLE TOO WELL.
YOU LEFT THAT BLACK CURTAIN
OUT THERE ON PURPOSE,
HOPING IT WOULD LURE ME
TO THE HUMAN WORLD
SO YOU COULD TAKE OVER
MY TERRITORY.
YOU PLANNED THIS ALL ALONG.
-OKAY, LET'S DIG IN!
-[ GROANS ]
-SORRY, DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
-OH, SURE.
FEEL FREE TO IGNORE ME.
-I LIKE THAT. THE WORD "FREE"
DESCRIBES ME PERFECTLY.
-OH, YEAH?
-THAT'S RIGHT, BECAUSE I CAN
CREATE SPACE ANYWHERE,
COMING AND GOING AT WILL,
FOR I AM A TRAVELER WHO CAN BE
IN DIFFERENT PLACES AT ONE TIME!
BUT MY HOBBY
IS TREASURE HUNTING,
AND I TRAVEL BETWEEN
THE HUMAN AND DEMON WORLDS
IN SEARCH OF THE FINEST,
MOST VALUABLE RICHES IMAGINABLE!
YES, THERE'S NOBODY
WHO CAN KEEP UP WITH ME!
-LIKE ANYONE WOULD WANT TO.
-PLEASE TAKE OFF YOUR SHOES.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING, KID --
THAT YOU COULD USE THE BLACK
CURTAIN WITHOUT MY PERMISSION?
-YEAH, WHATEVER. YOU'RE THE
GENIUS WHO LEFT IT OUT THERE.
-I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE
I WAS GOING THROUGH IT.
-LOOK, IT'S NOT LIKE
I JUST GO AROUND
LEAVING CURTAINS EVERYWHERE,
ALL RIGHT?
-OKAY, FINE,
I DID USE IT THERE BEFORE,
BUT I'M SURE I PUT IT AWAY
PROPERLY.
I MEAN, I WOULDN'T FORGET THAT.
-SO WHY WAS IT LEFT OUT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
THAT'S THE REAL MYSTERY HERE.
YOU KNOW?
-I THINK IT'S CALLED "FORGETTING
TO PICK UP YOUR CRAP."
-EITHER WAY, THERE'S A CHARGE
FOR USING MY CURTAIN --
30 MILLION YEN IN CASH.
[ CASH REGISTER DINGS ]
-YOU'RE GONNA CHARGE US?!
-ACTUALLY, IT'S 60 MILLION
FOR THE TWO OF YOU.
-COME ON, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WE DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF MONEY.
-IF YOU DON'T GIVE ME
EVERYTHING I WANT,
I WON'T HAVE ANOTHER CHOICE.
I'LL HAVE TO SELL THE INFO
THAT YOU LEFT YOUR TERRITORY.
-[ GROWLS ]
THAT'S ENOUGH!
-THINK FAST!
-[ GASPS ]
-OH, GREAT. WHAT NOW?
-SEE YA.
-WHAT'D YOU JUST DO?
WHERE'D STAZ GO?
-IT'S EASY.
ALL I NEED IS A FRAME,
AND I CAN MAKE PEOPLE DISAPPEAR
WHENEVER I WANT TO.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-AND NOW I'LL MAKE YOU
DISAPPEAR.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
-OKAY.
YOU GOT TO SNAP OUT OF IT.
-WELL IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M STILL IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
WHAT THE HECK'S HER DEAL?
I SUPPOSED HER PLAN
IS TO KEEP ME HERE
SO SHE CAN SELL THE INFO
ABOUT ME BEING AWAY
FROM MY TERRITORY.
-YEAH, RIGHT. I DOUBT I'D GET
ANYTHING FOR THAT CRAP.
-WHY, YOU!
-WHICH...IS...WHY
I'VE DECIDED TO LET YOU WORK OFF
WHAT YOU OWE ME.
-DAMN IT!
-YOO-HOO!
-HA!
-OVER HERE. [ GIGGLES ]
-AAH! [ PANTING ]
[ GUN COCKS ]
-YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
EXACTLY WHAT I SAY.
ARE WE CLEAR ABOUT THAT?
-I'M SORRY, STAZ.
-YOU WANT TO PLAY IT
LIKE THAT, HUH?
-GO DOWN THE STAIRS
OF THAT BUILDING
AND BRING ME BACK
A CERTAIN ITEM.
-A CERTAIN ITEM?
-TRUST ME. YOU'LL KNOW IT
WHEN YOU GET THERE.
[ LAUGHING ]
GUESS HOLDING YOU HOSTAGE
INSTEAD OF TAKING HIS TERRITORY
WAS THE PERFECT MOVE!
-I'M NOT SURE I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE DOING THIS.
-OH, YEAH. I SUPPOSE IT'S OKAY
IF I TELL YOU.
JUST MAKE SURE THAT YOU DON'T
TELL ANYONE ELSE.
OUR LITTLE SECRET.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANS ]
-WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
-WHAT IS THIS JOINT?
-IS THIS YOUR FIRST TIME HERE,
HANDSOME?
YOU MADE IT THROUGH THE DOOR,
SO YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY A DEMON.
-A DEMON? I THOUGHT
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
YOU ARE, SWEET CHEEKS,
BUT RIGHT NOW YOU'RE STANDING
IN A DEMON-WORLD CLOTHING SHOP
CALLED ONIQLO.
-I WAS GIVEN INSTRUCTIONS
TO COME IN HERE
AND PICK UP A CERTAIN ITEM.
-I SEE.
THAT SORT OF CUSTOMER, HUH?
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?
WISH YOU'D TOLD ME SOONER.
WALK THIS WAY.
NOW, THIS ITEM
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR --
THINK THIS IS IT?
-[ GROANS ]
-I CAN'T PUT IT AWAY.
'COURSE, I NEVER PUT IT UP
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THE GUY
WHO STOLE IT FROM ME DID.
AND THAT'S WHY
IT WON'T EVEN BUDGE FOR ME.
-SO, WHO STOLE IT?
-I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I WON'T STOP
UNTIL I FIND HIM.
THIS GUY HAS NO IDEA
WHO HE'S DEALING WITH,
'CAUSE NOBODY
MAKES A FOOL OUT OF ME.
-WHAT'LL HAPPEN WHEN
YOU FIND HIM?
-ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
THE GUY HAD NO PROBLEM
STEALING MY MAGIC,
WHICH MEANS HE MUST BE
INCREDIBLY POWERFUL
TO PULL THAT OFF SO EASILY.
IF A MAN LIKE THAT DOES EXIST,
I'LL SEEK HIM OUT AND...
-HUH?
-[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
...MARRY THE GUY,
AND MAKE HIM MY HUSBAND.
-YOUR HUSBAND?
-WHA...?
-THESE ARE OGRE UNDIES.
WE OGRES HAVE WORN
THESE LEGENDARY UNDERGARMENTS
LITERALLY FOR CENTURIES NOW,
AND THEY NEVER STAIN, RIP,
OR RIDE UP.
-WHOA, I DON'T EVEN
WANT TO THINK
ABOUT WHERE THOSE UNDIES
HAVE BEEN.
-YOU CAN ADMIRE THEM
ALL YOU WANT FOR FREE SWEETIE,
BUT IF YOU'RE LOOKIN' TO BUY,
NOW THAT'S A WHOLE
DIFFERENT STORY.
THESE UNDIES
CHOOSE THEIR WEARER.
-ENH?
[ GROANS ]
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO PROVE TO ME
THAT YOU'RE A REAL MAN
IF YOU WANT TO PURCHASE
THIS UNDERWEAR.
-[ COUGHING ]
-MY, MY. YOU'RE SUCH
A FRAGILE LITTLE THING.
IF YOU WANT TO HIT ME,
THEN YOU BETTER BE READY TO PUT
MORE BEHIND IT THAN THAT
'CAUSE IT FELT
LIKE A SISSY LITTLE OGRE
WHO GUARDS DISGUSTING PANTIES
THROUGH THAT LAST PUNCH.
-DID I JUST HEAR YOU
CALL THEM "DISGUSTING PANTIES"?
YOU HUSSY!
I'M GONNA SCRATCH YOUR EYES OUT!
[ GRUNTS ]
GOODNESS GRACIOUS,
I'VE GONE ALL STIFF.
-YOU'RE NOT MUCH OF A THREAT
IF MY STARE CAN STOP YOU
IN YOUR TRACKS.
THIS GUY IS SUCH A JOKE.
-YOU BIG BRUTE. HOW COULD YOU
HAVE DONE THIS TO MY FACE?
-I'LL BE TAKING THESE NOW.
NOT THAT I REALLY WANTED 'EM.
-OH, THAT'S JUST CRUEL.
-YEAH, WELL,
I NEVER REALLY WANTED
THOSE DISGUSTING THINGS,
EITHER, BUT...
THANKS, ANYWAY!
-WHAT? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
-BELL...WHY'RE YOU HERE?
-I SAID THERE WAS SOMETHING
I WANTED IN THIS STORE.
BUT WHY WERE YOU FIGHTING
WITH THE STORE MANAGER
OVER A PAIR OF UNDERPANTS?
-FUYUMI HASN'T BEEN HARMED
IN ANY WAY, RIGHT?
-OF COURSE.
SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
-I'M FINE, STAZ.
-GOOD. THEN STEP ASIDE.
I'M GONNA SMACK THAT WOMAN.
-NO! WAIT!
THERE'S A REASON FOR THIS.
BELL'S BEEN TRYING
TO FIND SOMEBODY.
THERE'S AN EXTREMELY POWERFUL
MAGIC USER OUT THERE
THAT SHE HAS TO FIND RIGHT AWAY!
THAT'S WHY SHE WAS TESTING YOU,
SO PLEASE FORGIVE HER!
-HUH? ARE YOU NUTS?
I NEARLY KILLED THE STORE
MANAGER 'CAUSE OF HER.
-[ GASPS ] SCARY.
-I SEE. WELL, THAT CERTAINLY
FILLS IN A FEW BLANKS.
-LIKE HOW FUYUMICCHI IS
SUCH A NICE CUTE LITTLE GIRL
AND HOW STAZ IS JUST A BIG
TURD-FACE, ISN'T HE?
TELL HIM!
-SHE'S ONLY KIDDING.
SHE DOESN'T MEAN IT? 'KAY?
-PERFECT. YOU'RE BOTH BEST
FRIENDS NOW, IS THAT IT?
-OH, WELL, IT ALL JUST SEEMED
TO HAPPEN SO FAST.
AFTER I TOLD HER YOU DIDN'T
TAKE THE BLACK CURTAIN,
WE KIND OF BECAME FRIENDS.
-THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A SECRET!
YOU NEED TO BE PUNISHED!
-AND THEN WHEN I TOLD HER
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR A WAY
TO BRING ME BACK TO LIFE,
BELL SAID THAT SHE KNOWS A BOOK
THAT SHOWS YOU HOW.
-HUH?
-I SURE DO. AWHILE BACK,
I RAN INTO A LITTLE BOOK
CALLED
THE BOOK OF HUMAN RESURRECTION.
-REALLY?
WHERE IS IT NOW?
-I HAD TO SELL IT.
-WELL, WHAT DID IT SAY?
-LIKE I CARE.
-YOU LITTLE --
-BUT I CAN STILL TELL YOU
WHERE I SOLD IT.
-AND WHERE'S THAT?
-HMM...
I BELIEVE IT WAS
OVER IN WEST DEMON WORLD.
WOLF'S TERRITORY, I THINK.
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-WOLF? NO WAY.
-YOU KNOW HIM, THEN?
-[ WHIMPERS ]
OH, YEAH.
MORE THAN JUST "KNOW HIM."
HE'S WOLF-BOY THE WEREWOLF,
TERRITORY BOSS
OF WEST DEMON WORLD.
HE HAPPENS TO BE
AN OLD FRIEND OF MINE...
AND MY RIVAL.
-WHAT'S THE BOSS
OF WEST DEMON WORLD LIKE?
-I DON'T KNOW, BUT I'M GUESSING
HE'S A COMPLETE NIMROD,
JUST LIKE STAZ.
MOST DEMONS ARE.
-NEXT TIME ON "BLOOD LAD,"
"YOU HAD IT ALL ALONG."
-IN THE DEMON WORLD,
IT'S GOOD TO BE BAD.