[ Wind howling ]
-You are Liz T. Blood.
Is that correct?
-Yes.
-Records show you departed
the Acropolis
with your older brother.
Is he not with you?
-He went home ahead of me.
-There's nothing in my file
that indicates he's returned.
-Enough! I'm in a hurry!
Now let me pass!
-Let her through.
I'll handle this.
-Officer Beros!
[ Pop! ]
-Let's go.
I'll escort you to your mansion.
-[ Clears throat ]
Excuse me.
You've got a little gum
on your face.
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-As I'm sure you're aware,
I'm with the Acropolis Police,
and my job
is to maintain order here.
-Hmm.
-I've been wanting
to speak with your brother
for a while now,
but he somehow managed
to get past me.
-He had some urgent business
to attend to, so he --
-Coming and going without proper
authorization is a crime.
So, that gives me the authority
to take him into custody
by using
my special dispensation magic.
-Where will you take him?
-To the last person he'd ever
want to see in the Demon World.
-You don't mean...
-That's right.
King of Demon World Acropolis,
Wolf-Daddy, himself.
-Why would you force him
to see that jerk?
-Watch your mouth.
That's our king.
-What does he want
with my brother?
-I'm not allowed
to disclose that information.
It's all classified.
-That guy's no king, not to us.
He's the one who's responsible
for taking mother and father
away from us forever.
-There it is.
[ Doorbell rings ]
-Hmm?
-Seems you have a visitor,
Santa Claus.
-It appears so.
Excuse me for a moment.
Do carry on with your work.
-[ Grumbles ]
[ Door opens ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
-All right,
you four-eyed pervert!
I know you're in there!
You'd better come out now,
or your sweet little sister's
gonna get it, understand?
-I'm not your hostage!
-Either you make him
come out here or get us inside!
-Bite me!
-My, my.
Haven't changed a bit,
have you, Beros?
To what do I owe
this great pleasure?
-Stop playing games with me!
Just shut your mouth
and open this damn gate now!
-No, don't do it, brother!
'Cause she's out here to --
[Muffled]
-Hurry it up!
-Of course.
Please come in, officer.
-After hauling ass to get here,
I hope this is the right place.
-Such nice color and aroma,
isn't it?
I discovered
this wonderful herbal tea
while visiting the lower world.
-You entered
Demon World Acropolis illegally,
and I'm here to arrest you.
-Hmm.
-I'm gonna wipe that smarmy look
right off of your face!
Because my special dispensation,
the Underdog Choker,
is gonna stick to you
wherever you go!
-Underdog Choker!
-[ Roaring ]
-Hmm.
-As long as that collar's
around your neck,
you won't be able to use
any of your magic powers.
And even if you try anything
funny, there'll be spilled blood
mixed with that delicious
herbal tea you're drinking.
-Interesting.
This is your form of discipline,
is it?
If you wanted to keep me
as your pet,
you should have just said so.
So, why don't you take me out
for a walk, then?
-Brother?
I'm really sorry
that I disobeyed your orders.
-It's okay, Liz.
I'm afraid
I'll be detained for a bit.
[ Whispering ] You failed
to buy me some time,
but will you
look after the house?
-Mm-hmm.
-Thanks, Liz.
You be a good girl, now.
-Ohh.
[ Cellphone rings ]
-That you?
-Yeah.
-Did you find Fuyumi?
-[ Sniffles ] Not yet...
-What's going on?
Are you crying again?
-Shut up!
I'm not crying!
-You are crying.
What's Braz doing?
-He got in trouble
because of me and was...
-What?!
He got arrested?!
How we supposed to find Fuyumi
with Braz in custody?!
- I can still look for her,
okay?
It's just hard right now.
'Cause she's stuck in a dark
place where I can't see her.
-What?!
What are you talking about?!
-'Sup, bitch!
You ain't from around here, yo!
So why you just
yappin' on the phone?!
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo, woo, whaaat?!
-Gotta go.
Call me back the minute
you find anything out.
-[ Sniffles ]
-And don't cry.
You didn't
do anything wrong, okay?
-Hey! I'm not crying!
-Whatever.
-Finally quit
that dumb-ass phone call, yo!
I think you should
give me a ring, dude!
"What's up, ya freak?"
-Hey, have you ever seen
this guy before?
I'm lookin' for him.
-Huh?
Yeah, I can't hear you, man!
What's up, baby?
[ Thud! Thud! Thud! ]
Sorry! I've never seen him, sir!
I regret that I couldn't
be of more assistance.
-I see.
-Oh! But the boss
might be able to hook you up!
He, like, knows everything
for realz, my man!
I'll take you to him, bro!
-Fine.
I'll give it a shot.
-Aw, hellz yeah!
Walk this way!
-Just so we're clear, if I think
you're trying to set me up,
I'll kill you.
-Never mind!
Let's go this way!
Hey, Yukki!
-It's freezing in here!
-I got another customer
here for you!
-Huh? Who's he?
-Yeah, I thought the homeboy
could use a little help.
So here he is all nice, right?
Mm-hmm!
-Sure about that?
-Come on, I can't take this!
I'm freezing my ass off!
-Sorry about that.
I'm a snowman,
so everything around me
starts to get kinda chilly.
Sure is cold.
-You're a snowman,
and you're cold?!
-[ Laughs ]
He's a boss man,
a comedian, or what?!
-So why aren't you cold,
Fish Lips?
-A snowman who gets too cold!
You're killin' me!
-So, Sabao here tells me you're
looking for a little help.
-Hey! Sabao's my name,
and awesome's my game!
Pleased to -- Ooh!
-I've been looking for this guy.
-Hey, so, where you from?
Yo, what's your name, anyway?
-Does he look familiar?
-Hmm.
-Hot pot time!
That sounds great
right about now!
Nothing beats a hot pot
in cold weather!
And how about some Jjigae?
Yeah!
Jjigae hot pot, baby!
[ Crash! ]
-Do you know him?
-I've met him, yeah.
Not sure where he is now,
but I know where he lives.
Got his card right here.
-Is it somewhere close by?!
-I, uh, don't think
you'll be able to find him.
-Huh?
-He lives in
the Dimensional Highway,
one of the seven wonders
of the Demon World.
No one's ever traveled there.
In fact,
it's never even been seen.
-So you're saying that once this
guy's home, nothing can be done?
He can't be followed?
-That's right.
There's a chance Knell
might still be around here.
Take his business card.
-He's a transporter.
He's got some strange powers.
-I don't believe it.
-Here's your compromise ramen!
-[ Slurps ]
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
I guess I'd better
give her something to eat, too.
Hey, can I get
another ramen over here?
-Comin' right up!
-'Kay, in the meantime,
let's see how our guest
is doing in my Grid Room.
Hope everything's fine
in there...Fuyumi.
-Here you go!
And I compromised
by giving you some extra eggs!
-Thank you!
Presto!
Now you see the bowl,
and now you don't.
-Huh?
-[ Screams ]
-[ Chuckles ]
Pretty cool trick, huh?
-You made
one of my bowls disappear!
I ain't gonna compromise
on that one!
You're gonna have
to pay for that bowl, got it?!
-[ Chuckles nervously ]
-And if you don't pay me
right now,
then I'm gonna pick up the phone
and call the police!
-Uh, okay, okay, fine.
I'll get your bowl back for you.
-What?! Hey, let go!
It's hot!
You're spilling soup on me!
If you won't let go,
then I'll just have to make you!
Let go?!
-Aah!
[ Bell dings ]
-[ Gasps ]
What's with the bell?
-[ Gasps ] Fuyumi!
-What's up, puddin' pie?
-Fuyumi just rang my bell.
[ Gasps ]
-What's the matter, now?
-Hold on!
Why is he showing up?!
-Girl, you had way too much
to drink last night.
[ Cellphone rings ]
-That you, Liz?
-Staz!
I know where Fuyumi is!
She's with some weird guy!
-Oh, yeah?
Well, I just found out
who our kidnapper is.
Where are they now?
-Time to go!
Pretty sure I just made
a big mistake.
-Aww, shucks.
I thought I had you that time.
-S-Sis?
[ Ding! ]
[ Distorted ] Aaaaaah!
-Long time no see, Knell.
[ Chuckles ]
You haven't changed a bit.
-Back at ya, sis.
Thanks a lot.
Ow!
-All right.
Now tell me who hired you.
'Cause I know all about
the cargo you're hauling around.
[ Bell chimes ]
Fuyumi happens to be
a friend of mine.
I can't just stand by
and watch you take her away.
-Great.
You would say this now.
I tried e-mailing you about it.
-Huh?
-This would've been
a lot easier if you'd responded.
What I'm doing here
isn't even a job.
It's more like running errands.
-Wait!
You mean you're doing this...
for mama?
-She kept trying, but she
couldn't get ahold of you.
Now she's really pissed.
-You're kiddin', right?
Why would mama
care about Fuyumi?
-I finally found you,
you freakin' ghost thief!
-'Sup, Staz?
-Oh, man, That guy
looks really pissed off.
And I don't wanna be the one to
tell mom that we screwed up
and let that girl
slip through our fingers.
-Wait, hold on!
Hmm, better take off, Knell.
-Huh? You sure?
-What the hell?
Were you in
on this thing, too, Bell?
-As of right now, I am.
-Well, you'd better be sure
whose side you're on.
'Cause if you're not on mine,
I'll kick your ass.
-Seriously?!
You have no patience at all.
Can't you give me a little time
to think it over?
-I'm getting tired
of playing these games!
Give me Fuyumi.
-Don't worry, Knell.
I'll handle this.
You'd better get out
while you can.
-Thanks, sis.
-Tell mom I said hi.
-I get it.
Fuyumi's in there, isn't she?
-[ Gasps ]
-Oh, hi.
I'm sorry about the ramen thing.
-N-No problem.
-You just stay where you are.
I'm gonna go
do something over here,
but I don't want
you to peek, okay?
-Uh, okay.
-This spot right here
should do it.
I'll stick out my feet
a little and...
-It's right here.
Come and get it.
-It's a trap, right?
You can bring it over here.
-Forget that.
I don't feel like it.
-Aah! Damn it!
Aah!
-[ Screaming ]
-The hell was that?!
-[ Giggles ]
See ya!
What the...
I guess my aim
is a little off today.
-You can't catch me, Bell.
And I'm not gonna let you
get away from me!
[ Gunshots ]
-At least with this,
I never miss.
-[ Groans ]
Why are you trying to stop me?!
You know
if I don't get to Fuyumi,
she's gonna disappear for good!
-Of course I do.
But then
this has nothing to do with me.
-If that's true,
then why did you think
she needed that bell
for protection?
-That was to protect her
from you.
Wasn't it obvious?
-Yeah, well, my brother
put a tracking device on her.
-So what?
-It proves he already knew
all of this would happen!
And you trying to stop me is
just another part of his plan!
Come on, Bell.
What are you doing?!
You gotta let me go
so I can save Fuyumi's life!
-Ugh.
I don't understand.
Is she that important to you?
-Huh?
You don't think I'm...
good enough?
-Fuyumi's, like, my
one-of-a-kind collector's item!
-Huh?
-There's only one of her
in the whole world,
like a super-rare item
that's only available
for a limited time!
You know what I mean!
You're a treasure hunter!
-Okay, that's it!
Now you've really pissed me off!
If she really means
that much to you,
and you only think of me as some
chick who cares about treasure,
then let's fight.
If you can beat me this time,
I'll deliver you
to Fuyumi myself.
-Where are we?
-Welcome to Hydra!
-This is getting too weird.
This place looks like the anime
I watched yesterday.
-Follow me.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
I think maybe there was
a misunderstanding, Bell.
-Shut the hell up,
you otaku vampire!
You're the freakin' moron
who doesn't get it!
-Why are you so upset
with me, anyway?
I mean, shouldn't it be
the other way around?!
-Then come
and get a piece of me,
you pathetic,
geeky little bloodsucker!
Aren't you the one who promised
to kick my ass
until I begged for mercy?
That was the reason you got
the bullet taken out, wasn't it?
So, let's see if you've got what
it takes to keep up with me.
[ Squish! Squish! Squish! ]
-What the hell's going on?
[ Gun cocks ]
-That answer your question?
-[ Grumbles ]
Aah!
-You're wasting your time.
You'll never beat me
inside this room.
Watch your back.
[ Gun cocks ]
-[ Groans ]
-Wow! Down already?
-That was pretty cool.
Thanks for making my shirt
look like Kenshiro.
-What does that mean?
So, if you lose,
then you'll have to stop
trying to save Fuyumi
and be my slave forever.
I think that sounds fair.
-Not a problem.
I won't lose.
-Kinda hard to win a fight when
you're on your knees, isn't it?
-I've had plenty of chicks
talk smack to me,
but never one who looks like
a fish face floating in wasabi.
-Hmph!
Does this work better for you?
-Yep!
[ Grunts ]
-I told you
you're wasting your time!
Don't you listen to anything?
You really are stupid,
aren't you?
Sometimes you gotta learn
the hard way.
Once you stepped in here,
you never stood a chance
of beating me.
Come on
and admit defeat already.
Say the words "I give up."
You've done it before.
-Sorry to disappoint,
but I'm not the same loser
I was back then.
So, you're able
to materialize magic, huh?
-Well, yeah.
-You know I can, too, right?
-Well, duh.
You've been throwing it around
and missing every time.
Kinda sad, really.
-Were you wondering
where my magic is right now?
-Huh?
-You need to be a little more
careful of your surroundings.
-Hey! What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Let go of me!
-Just admit you're defeated.
'Cause if you don't, you can
kiss your lower half goodbye.
-[ Grunting ]
-Now say it.
-Okay, you got me this time.
But still, I'm not done!
-What the hell?
Oh.
-Hey!
Give those back.
-What's that?
-We're almost there.
-Good.
[ Thinking ]
Staz, I'm so scared!
I've never been up this high!
If I stay here much longer,
I think I'm gonna pee myself
a little!
Come on, Fuyumi.
I know you can do this.
Just don't look down!
-Stop playing around!
Think about the heroes
in those Japanese comics
you like to so much.
How do you think they'd handle
this kind of situation?
-So you're saying...
I should take your panties,
put them over my head,
and take some deep whiffs,
like they would?
You know,
that's an excellent idea!
-That's not what I meant,
you sicko!
What kind of hero is that?!
Just give 'em back!
And stop holding them
like they're filthy!
That's insulting!
You are sick!
-[ Sniffs ]
Ughhhhhhh.
-I'll kill you!
[ Gasps ]
Aah!
-[ Thinking ] I knew it.
Something doesn't feel right.
When I first picked this up,
I figured it'd be
the perfect thing
to try and bargain with.
"Woo-hoo!
If you want this back,
you have to say 'I give up.'
Got it?"
It wouldn't have been
the coolest thing to do,
but I was ready
to give it a shot.
And that's when it hit me.
Why didn't Bell just give me
another one of her dirty looks,
then go back to her room
and squeeze herself
into some new clothes?
I was about
to look like a real dumbass.
Am I glad I didn't do that.
So what's going on?
She could've left me and run
away in a matter of seconds.
Is it 'cause she hasn't
figured that out yet?
Or is there something more
going on that I'm not seeing?
Seriously, what's Bell
still doing here?
She hasn't moved an inch.
And she has that nervous look
on her face
like I'm gonna try and
do something with her stuff.
No doubt about it --
These panties are her treasure!
-[ Thinking ] What am I
supposed to do, now?
In that bag, I keep
all my secret treasure notes!
And I write down everything
that I've ever wanted!
If he gets to the page
that says "Staz,"
I'm gonna set myself on fire!
I'll be lucky
if he just stops there.
What if he keeps reading
and finds
"Operation: Love Me Staz"?
I wrote it when I was buzzed,
and now it's gonna come back
and bite me in the ass!
Oh, my God!
I want to crawl into a hole
and stay there forever!
If he sees that, it's over!
Not only would he know
how I feel about him,
but it would also mean...
-Later, biatch.
-[ Thinking ] I just know it!
[ Gasps ]
-Guess I should
just keep this in here.
It seems pretty important to you
for some reason.
Man, look at all this.
-No! Don't!
-Huh?
-[ Screams ]
-Hmm.
-Hey, what's up?
-'Sup with you?
-I had it first. Let go!
-That's good advice.
But shouldn't you let it go
before I grab you?
[ Gun cocks ]
-Okay, I think
I've got this figured out now.
It was like this at Oniqlo, too.
You're always using underwear
as some kind of decoy.
This is what you really
care about, isn't it?
-If you read it, I'll shoot!
-You already know
that's not gonna work.
When are you gonna learn, Bell?
-Aah!
-Come on, why don't we sit down
and read this thing together?
-I'm sorry, Staz.
-Let's see now.
"Number 163,
found Gourmet Flower"...
-Okay! I'll say it!
I'll say it!
You win! I give up!
-Was that so hard?
[ Gunfire ]
-You just had to do that,
didn't you?!
-Sorry!
Guess it slipped my mind.
-You're disgusting!
-By the way,
do I look all right?
Hope I'm not so gross
that they can't show me on TV.
I know this might be a bad time,
but you've got a nice ass.
[ Gunshot ]
-Feeling better?
-Maybe you didn't see
how much blood I lost.
Thanks for asking
after shooting me.
-I don't understand you at all.
You're the one who went crazy
and wanted to start
a fight with me.
Then, as soon
as I looked at your diary,
you were ready to surrender.
You're acting really weird.
-It's all your fault, anyway.
-Huh?
-Ohh!
Just forget it, okay?!
You wanna save your precious
Fuyumi, don't you?!
Perfect! I'll help you out!
I might as well, since I'm
nothing but a big loser!
[ Thinking ] It's not like
I really have a choice, do I?
You're so desperate
to be around her all the time,
trying so hard
that you don't notice the
person right in front of you.
What an idiot.
You should try
and forget about Fuyumi.
It's not like you can get her
back now, anyway.
You don't even have enough
blood for yourself,
but all you can think about
is giving it all to her,
even though I'm the one who's
been here for you all along.
If I opened my arms
and stood in the way,
begging for you
to finally pay attention,
you'd walk right through me.
I'm such an idiot.
What else can I say
except, "I give up"?
-I don't really understand it,
but I know it's my fault.
-Huh?
-I realize that no matter what,
I'm responsible.
And, in the end,
it all comes back on me.
So whatever you're upset about,
I'm sure it's something I did.
And even if it isn't,
you can blame me, anyway, okay?
-Just get to the point,
will you?
-I've been thinking about this
for a long time,
and I've finally
come to the conclusion
that I'm more of a bad guy
than a hero.
So if you're mad about
something, don't hide it.
You can take it out on me.
Just say, "It's all
your damn fault, Staz!"
Just don't expect an apology
'cause I'm a bad guy.
-Oh, come on.
-What are you waiting for?
Do it.
-[ Singing in Japanese ]
-Fine, you're an ass.
-Hey, I was just
trying to help ya!
-I get it. I get it.
Thanks a bunch.
[ Thinking ] That was
a close call back there.
I almost let him
find out everything.
I have to hide my true
feelings, no matter what.
And, hey, this is all
your fault, dumbass!
-Come on, boss!
Can't you do anything about that
annoying jerk with the glasses?!
-Patience, Officer Beros.
Our orders from the king
are to bring him in alive.
-I know, but I just want to kill
that four-eyed turd!
-Next time on "Blood Lad,"
"Sins of the Eye Glasses."
-In the Demon World,
it's good to be bad.