This is the first chance
I've had to write on a ship,
so I appreciate the opportunity.
And it helped me realize
how to calm myself.
Be like a kid with finger paint.
[thinking]
It's almost like the brush
is moving on its own now.
Just one month to go
until the Narukain exhibit,
but that's all the time
I really need to--
[yelps]
For you. Eat up!
And what is that?
It's pickles.
Pickles.
Do I need this many?
[laughs]
I'll bring ya back s'more
when ya run out.
And now he's just gonna
disappear into the woods.
[sighs]
Seriously.
No human can eat this much.
Oh.
[thinks]
Oh, man.
Okay, I really need to focus.
I can clearly picture it.
A jarring yet tasteful pickle.
Not pickles!
Now write, and then pickles.
Stop thinking that!
[thinks] Only one month
'til the pickles exhibit.
Get out of my head,
you damn pickles!
[whimpers] Pickles!
[cries] Pickles!
Pickles!
[HANDA] More pickles!
Pickles. Pickles.
--Pickles. Pickles.
--[knocks on door]
Pickles?
I'll bring ya back s'more
when ya run out.
[breathes shakily]
More pickles!
Sensei! Teach us to write!
[HANDA] Of course
it's just you girls.
--Huh?
--"You girls"? Real nice hello.
Oh. Sorry.
--[NARU] Here!
--[gasps]
Grandpa told me to bring 'em
to ya 'cause it ain't gonna
do ya no good to run out
and have no more.
[breathes shakily]
Thank you.
So, can you help
with our school project?
[HANDA] First off, hold
the brush with your right hand.
--[NARU] Is this my right hand?
--[HANDA] Yes, it is.
Wait, you've gotta be
right-handed to do calligraphy?
No, but the inkstone
goes on the right,
so it's easier this way.
So, what's the subject?
Um. It's this.
Okay, I'll do a quick example
for you, so watch what I do.
--Move.
--[grunts]
Aw. You're not gonna slap it on
like normal? I like that.
[HANDA] Slap it on?
I'm just trying to teach you
the fundamentals here.
Huh? Yeah, but I wanna learn
how to write like that!
It's more raw!
[HANDA] Uh, I'm still
hammering out that style.
I'll teach it to you after I get
some public recognition for it.
Recognition?
Don't we count as the public?
I guess so,
but I meant winning first place
in next month's exhibit.
Hmm. Really?
You're too good to worry
about getting awards.
Who cares
about that kind of stuff?
I just wanna have fun with it.
[hesitantly]
You wanna have fun?
Oh, man. So young and naive.
--[BOTH gasp]
--Here. Write this one, Naru.
Cat! Okay!
--[HANDA] All right!
--[GIRLS gasp]
As your teacher, I promise
that you'll both get awards.
And once you get a taste for it,
you'll understand
why I'm so hung up
on being recognized
and winning one myself.
[HANDA]
Now, write for the next hour
--like your lives depend on it!
--[GIRLS scream]
--[gasps]
--Keep focusing.
Hmm.
Don't ink your brush
if there's still ink on it.
Does this line
look right to you?
--[whimpers]
--Stop your brush here.
--[snoring]
--Wake up.
[groaning]
--No more! Please!
--[HANDA] Snap to, girls!
Stop being lazy!
You were the ones who asked me
to teach you, remember?
I can turn you into champions.
Fine, but we've been writing
the same dumb thing all day!
Can't you just, like,
teach us the cheat codes?
--[MIWA gasps]
--Are you serious?
Do you think
writing beautiful characters
come easily
to professionals like me?
You have to feel the emotion
behind every stroke
of the brush!
Calligraphers throughout time
have painted
their emotions onto paper
as though
they were spilling their blood!
--Like who?
--Right?
[HANDA] Physical fatigue,
mental breakdowns,
living in a world
of constant solitude!
Yes, the edge, you have
to peer right over it!
[MIWA and TAMA]
The edge of what?
[HANDA]
Just one more step.
Another step closer
to completion,
but an eternal desert stretches
between you and the end,
and you're too tired
to take that next step.
And when you can't write
any further,
that's when you see it.
The god of calligraphy!
But is the god really there
or is it just a mirage
from the desert?
[BOTH] Can calligraphy make
you hallucinate? Or is he nuts?
[MIWA] This is just a dumb
assignment for middle school!
We're not trying to reach
the point of enlightenment!
Go buy some juice
and let us take a break!
[sighs] You girls don't
even care about this, do you?
[straining]
Yes, we do! I promise!
We really do!
We just need a break!
[HANDA] Fine, but you better
be writing when I get back!
[MIWA] All right,
we will, now just go!
[TAMA and MIWA sigh]
Seriously,
he is like totally obsessed.
--Sei!
--At the rate he's going,
he is never gonna get
a girlfriend.
Who knows? Maybe he's
in a long-distance relationship.
[whimpers, thinks]
"Girlfriend"?
Maybe we should nose around
and see what we can find.
Hey, cut it out.
That's just tacky.
--[MIWA] Oh!
--[NARU and TAMA gasp]
"Kawafuji"?
Let's see if it's a girl.
Please.
You're making me uncomfortable.
--Aw. It's just some dude.
--Huh? Let me see!
Why? You told me to stop.
[TAMA]
There's a group photo in here.
[MIWA] Oh, you think he's going
out with one of those girls?
Maybe her?
[TAMA]
She's pretty and all,
but she's not standing next
to him. What about her?
[MIWA] She looks
a little too plain Jane
to be Sensei's girlfriend.
I guess.
Do looks matter though?
I mean, as long as they wanna
talk about calligraphy with him.
How many women out there
could stand listening
--to his delusional rambling?
--[NARU thinks] Got it!
Listening's easy,
even monkeys can do it.
[NARU] This!
[MIWA] What's that
you're holding, Naru?
Sensei told me that this thing
is his special treasure.
-What is it?
-It's a picture stand.
I wonder just how special
the picture inside it is.
--[chuckles]
--[NARU wailing]
Hey, what's wrong?
[NARU] I don't want Sensei
to be someone else's wife.
You should work
on your definition of "wife."
Aw, poor kid. Her little heart's
about to break.
[MIWA] This is a good thing,
Naru. Trust me,
it's a lot weirder for a guy his
age to not have a girlfriend.
You just wait ten years, Naru.
You'll grow up to be so pretty
that you can have your way
with him if you want.
I can have my way?
Well. Let's take a look...
At Sensei's secret girlfriend!
--[BOTH] Uh...
--[door opens]
All right, here's your juice.
What're you doing?
You should be writing!
You have to take this seriously
if you ever wanna
win an award!
Huh?
You're 23 years old, Sensei!
You can't make calligraphy
your whole life!
You can't fall in love with
some stupid dead historic dude!
You need
a real woman in your life!
Just date Naru
if that's what it takes.
[gasps] Ugh.
[gasps]
Yeah! Date me!
--I want my way!
--Do what?
--[grunts] Get off me!
--[NARU grunts]
[MIWA] At the rate you're going,
you're gonna die alone!
[HANDA]
Where is this coming from?
--[NARU] Gimme my way!
--What are you talking about?
Out to the ocean?
Yeah, the kids want
to go swimming,
so I was hoping
you could keep an eye on them.
I asked the head teacher
to watch 'em,
but you know how he is.
[KAZUYUKI]
That'd cut into my fishing time!
Ah. Well, if you only
need me to watch 'em,
and as long
as they all know how to swim--
One more thing.
It looks like Miwa
and Tama are going as well.
Can you also make sure
they don't do anything
dumb or dangerous?
[KIDS laughing]
I'll make Hiroshi tag along
to help ya keep watch on them.
[HANDA thinks] Something
terrible is bound to happen.
Sensei! Come on, let's go!
--[HANDA sighs]
--Hurry up already!
--Hey, wait a second!
-[KENTA] Get movin', Sensei, go!
Yeah, all right,
just let me get ready first.
--[KENTA] Butt!
--[HANDA] No butt stabs!
--[KIDS laughing]
--[HANDA] Hey, stop running.
[NARU]
Look! Miwa and Tama!
[MIWA] What's up, Naru?
Took ya long enough, Sensei.
[TAMA]
Thanks for taking us.
[HANDA] What's with the outfits?
They look like gym suits.
Yeah, that's because
they are gym suits.
Sorry if that's
not sexy enough for you.
What? You wear those to swim?
Well, yeah.
Why wouldn't we?
It seems like it'd be a pain
to swim with your clothes on.
Hmm? If ya care so much,
take yours off.
Well. I don't actually own
a swimsuit.
[TAMA whimpers]
[NARU]
Hey! You're takin' too long!
It's not my fault!
We're still waiting on Hiro!
Well, let's go.
All right, everyone!
Follow me to adventure!
[KIDS] Yay!
[thinks] All right. He's clearly
not gonna be any help.
Let's go, you guys!
I'm gonna become
--a master backstroker!
--[KIDS cheer]
Hey! Don't run on the rocks!
Jeez, quit freakin' out.
They know this beach
backwards and forwards.
Beach? More like jagged,
deadly boulders!
I don't even see
any sand around here!
Only dumb little kids play
on those kinds of beaches.
[HANDA]
Exactly my point!
Man. It's way too slick.
[yells, grunts]
--[TAMA] Sensei, what happened?
--[MIWA] Jeez, Sensei.
Don't they teach you
how to walk in the city?
[group chattering]
[NARU] Sensei? You okay?
[MIWA] Yeah, he's fine. We've
all fallen on the rocks before.
[MIWA]
All right! Jump in!
[GROUP] Yeah!
--Huh?
--[gasps]
[KIDS laughing]
[DAISUKE and YUTAKA]
Whoa, they're super huge!
--[NARU] A sea urchin.
--[HINA] Scary.
[MIWA]
Quit splashing me, Naru!
--[laughter]
--[TAMA] Calm down!
[breathes deeply]
Hina! Ya find any good fish?
Yeah, but my goggles
got all foggy,
so I couldn't really see 'em.
No problem.
Wipe 'em off with this.
Here, that'll do the trick.
I always use mugwort leaves,
'cause the sap stops 'em
from getting all cloudy.
Oh, wow. Naru, you know so much.
You're just like a grandma!
Hmm?
What's that 'sposed t'mean,
I'm like a grandma?
Huh? Sorry. Is that rude?
Well, of course that's rude!
I'm only seven years old!
[HINA yelps]
[HIROSHI]
So young. So foolish.
They just don't know how
to enjoy the sea, do they?
There's one! Take this!
Hiroshi Critical!
[humphs]
[KENTA]
Whoa, an octopus!
Heed my skills!
Awesome! You're so cool, Hiro!
[BOTH gasp]
[HIROSHI yells]
[KENTA] That was
the most uncool thing ever!
[sighs]
Those guys just don't know how
to enjoy the sea, do they?
How sad.
Sorry to bail, Miwa,
but I need to lie down a bit.
--[MIWA] You okay?
--Oh!
You don't look so hot.
I'm just gonna rest with Sensei
for a while and I'll be fine.
[MIWA] Sure.
--[TAMA grunts]
--Ah!
Uh. You sick or something?
Your face is red!
This is normal.
I'm more of an indoors person.
[HANDA] Well, then this is
the last place you should be.
You need to hydrate.
Can you drink some water?
[TAMA] Uh, yeah.
--[KIDS laughing]
--[MIWA] There ya go.
That's how ya do it!
[laughs]
[thinks] What's with her?
Why does she keep staring at me?
Hey, Sensei?
Um, have you ever gotten
so hung up on something
that you can't sleep?
[HANDA] What's bothering you?
You can tell me, y'know.
[TAMA] Its not that--
it's not that
I'm bothered by it.
But to be straightforward,
what are your feelings
towards Hiro?
Uh...
[thinks]
Hiro? I don't get it.
--[HIROSHI] One, two, three!
--[HANDA] He's close to my age,
so I guess he's kinda like
a younger brother.
[thinks] Wait, no.
We're nowhere near that close.
He's more like the guy
that just drops off my food.
--[whimpers]
--Regardless, why is four-eyes
so anxious to hear
what I think about him?
[gasps]
Now I get it! Of course!
She's got a crush on Hiro!
That explains
why she's been acting
so strange around us lately.
And here she is,
finally gotten up the nerve
to ask me
for some grownup advice.
Now, that's just adorable.
Sensei?
[thinks] Say something nice
to support her feelings.
--He's the perfect guy.
--[gasps]
He always listens to you,
and he cooks.
It's not often you find
a great catch like that.
I mean, you really couldn't ask
--for a better guy to go out--
--I can't listen to this!
Just what kind
of perverted thoughts
do you think have been
keeping me up at night?
--What?
--I'm not a fujoshi!
--Quit tempting me! [wails]
--Fujoshi? What is that?
Be careful running on the--
--ah! [thuds]
--[gasps] Um. Sensei?
[TAMA]
Are you for real?
Ta-da! I found
a sea cucumber. Check it out!
--[girls whimper]
--Gross.
I can't believe
you can hold that.
Here, you hold it, Naru.
This is how grown-ups do it!
[GROUP yelps]
[gulps]
I'm not so sure.
--Boo!
--[BOTH scream]
Why are you so mean, Miwa?
You can't make me hold it!
[MIWA]
Sorry, I'm sorry!
I know it looks gross,
but it's not a big deal
[NARU] It's so slimy.
I'm good now.
[MIWA] There!
You got to learn about nature!
--Hiro. Where's Sensei?
--Huh? Um.
[TAMA] Jeez. Are you seriously
this much of a wimp?
[HIROSHI] Looks like
he's still unconscious.
[MIWA] Perfect.
We should be okay then.
--Naru!
--[yelps]
Whad'ya say we go
someplace more fun? Huh?
--More fun than here?
--[chuckles] Yup!
It's so fun,
only grownups get to go there.
[grunts]
Ah, damn it.
How many times
am I gonna pass out?
I guess we better head back.
Last thing I need
is to miss lunch.
[KIDS laugh]
[HANDA] All right, you guys!
Time to pack up!
[KIDS]
What? Already?
--[KIDS grumble]
--Thanks for making this easy.
[HANDA] Hey! Where's Naru?
She was just here
playing with Miwa.
--Over there.
--Huh?
[MIWA]
My turn!
Huh? Miwa?
Stop it, that's dangerous!
[laughs] Awesome!
Hey, Miwa. Looks like
Sensei's yelling somethin'.
Hmm? Oh yeah.
It's probably time to go.
I say we get
one more jump in first.
Mm-hmm.
It's not our turn.
Hey. Naru! Go for it!
[gasps, yelps]
[grunts]
Hey! Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
No, listen to me! Stop! Naru!
Naru!
[laughing]
That was so much fun!
[laughs]
Awesome job!
You handled that just like
full-blown grown-up!
I heard Sensei cheerin' for me
and saying "Naru"
when I jumped off!
That's why
I wasn't scared or nothin'!
He was?
Yeah. Sounded like he was
shouting something at her.
Not again!
Oh, man. Sensei!
[HANDA]
Damn it!
I can't believe you were
all dumb enough to do that!
[NARU]
I'm real sorry, Sensei.
[MIWA]
C'mon, lighten up.
I promise we won't do it again.
--Don't be mad at us.
--[NARU] Sensei?
[whimpers]
[BOTH whimper]
[sighs]
[HANDA] This is
the first time I've ever--
[NARU gasps]
Before I came to this island,
the only thing I needed
to think about was
taking care of myself.
This is the first time
I've ever worried
this much about someone else!
[GROUP gasps]
Forget it.
Just leave me alone!
--Sensei! [crying]
--Uh! Hey.
[HINA] Sorry!
I won't make you worry again!
--Same here!
--Uh, you guys.
I'm sorry!
I'll be careful from now on!
We didn't mean
to make you worry!
[KIDS chanting]
Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei! [laughing]
I guess the outsider's
really managed
to dig his roots in deep.
--[KIDS] Stare.
--[HIROSHI] No, I'm not that big
--on hugging and laughing.
--[KIDS] Aww.
[HIROSHI]
Don't guilt-trip me!
[buzzing]
[KAWAFUJI] It's no good.
He's still not picking up.
What? I lost the signal again?
I'm kind of at a loss here.
It's like this place
was built on inconvenience.
[KANZAKI] I don't know,
I kinda like it here.
It's got its own
miniature model airport.
What more could you want?
[KAWAFUJI] Kanzaki.
Don't start with me.
[laughs] All right.
I'm happy wherever,
just as long
as I get to meet Handa.
[NARU moans]
♪ You held out a small hand ♪
♪ Smiling, like to you
it was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something
I can not do ♪
♪ You touched my hand
without thinking ♪
♪ But it was nice for me ♪
♪ Oh, whoa ♪
♪ All the time we believed ♪
♪ That the world's
in our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe,
I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand ♪
♪ Your warm hand! ♪
--[TAMA] Whoa! Miwa!
--What?
Your hair is
a total train wreck right now.
Ah.
That's what happens
when it gets this humid.
Well, you're hair
was already pretty kinked.
[MIWA] Looks like
I found a colleague.
Oh. Hey.
You girls also come to fish?
Um. Your hair.
Huh? It always gets like this
when I'm in a good mood.
No, it's the humidity.
Come to think of it,
you guys do have similar hair.
Pretty much the same cut.
Don't jack my style, Sensei!
I wasn't trying to.
[MIWA] Why don't you
just buzz it down short?
[HANDA]
No, that's not really me.
[KAZUYUKI]
Hey, busy day over here.
Huh?
Can the ol' head teacher
join ya?
I tell ya', sure is humid today!
[GROUP gasps]
[MIWA thinks]
Is that gonna happen to me?
[TAMA thinks] I'm so glad
I have straight hair.
[HANDA thinks]
Maybe I should buzz it. Maybe.
[NARU thinks] Huh?
Tengusa head!
[KAZUYUKI] Huh?