[HANDA]
Yeah, it's done.
I'll mail it to you ASAP,
so keep a look out.
It took long enough, but I'm
really proud of this one.
I've been overflowing
with inspiration
ever since I came here.
I really gotta hand it
to Mother Nature.
I'm actually enjoying my job,
compared to when
I was in the city.
Hey, Kawafuji,
are you listening to me?
Hey!
Uh, thanks
for stopping by, Director,
you're a bit early,
so you caught me off guard.
So how would you say Handa's
work is progressing?
Well, according to him
everything's going great.
I hope that he can master
a style that's all his own.
The beauty of his calligraphy
is meaningless
if it doesn't
come from the heart.
I want to see his very soul
splashed right across the paper.
Who knows. Personally,
whatever he does,
I'd like to see him
come back and do it here,
but he seems intent
on staying put
until he sees
the results of the exhibit.
Do you think
he's about ready to apologize
for punching me like that?
I couldn't really say.
If you think my forgiveness
will bring him back sooner,
then let me help.
That is, if he finds himself
ready, of course.
[HANDA]
Stupid Kawafuji. After all that,
he doesn't even bother listening
to what I'm saying.
[sighs]
What I said sure sounded
confident enough.
But I don't know if that piece
is any good or not.
I mean, I like it,
but you can tell
it was written
in the heat of the moment.
Is this like, the "new face"
of my calligraphy?
I could only write this
because I came here.
If I was told to reproduce
something like this
once I went back to Tokyo,
I probably couldn't.
[thinks] Damn it. Now I'm
starting to doubt myself.
Should I really be submitting
something I wrote on a whim
to an exhibit
I can't afford to lose?
Positive, stay positive.
No use worrying
about it now.
Inspiration from nature is my
new weapon, not fundamentals.
I cannot afford to have
an identity crisis right now.
Naru, what
do you think about all this?
Huh? 'Bout what?
Actually, who cares?
Let's play!
I was opening up to you,
and you say, "Who cares?"
You expect me to play games
with you after that? No way.
I don't know if I'd say that
if I were you, Sensei.
--Pchoo!
--Tch!
Should've gone with a "free
shoulder massage" instead.
As long as I have this,
you gotta listen to me forever!
It clearly has
"one time" written on it.
Hey!
What's up, Grandpa?
Huh?
Look who it is!
Hmm?
[thinks]
What the heck are they doing?
[KOUSAKU]
Gotta pile them rocks up
into a wall 'fore a typhoon
comes barreling through.
And if you don't stack 'em
just so, it all falls apart.
[HANDA]
Oh. It's like a puzzle.
Bring me the next piece
right over yonder!
[thinks] He's trying
to trick me into helping him!
I'm gonna make Sensei go
frog catching with me today.
--'Cause I got this!
--[thinks] Frog catching?
--[KOUSAKU] Is that so?
--[NARU] Hey!
If I use this magic ticket,
will he help me out?
--[NARU] Huh?
--Only one use, though!
Ohh!
That's my present!
Don't throw a tantrum,
how' bout we make a trade?
Trade me what?
I want my ticket!
--Here.
--Hmm?
It's a rock.
[KOUSAKU]
A rock that'll skip on water!
--[whimpers]
--Now that's a good deal!
I don't want it!
--[groaning]
--Not bad.
C'mon, now,
let's get to work!
[HANDA]
Whoa, heavy.
[KOUSAKU]
Right over yonder.
Phooey.
Let's see,
where's a good spot?
Here. Ha ha!
Feels pretty good
when it fits just right!
It beats frog catchin',
I'll tell you that much.
[groaning]
I'll be darned,
you ain't half bad, Sensei!
I think I'm just good at jobs
that require precision.
I might need a lesson from ya,
seeing how mine are all
whomperjawed in comparison.
Ha! You got no skills,
Grandpa!
[laughs]
That's mighty honest of you.
Naru!
[NARU and KOUSAKU laughing]
[CAT MAN]
Since we got Sensei for the day,
we should have him
go look at the shrine.
Now there's an idea.
Let's go.
"The shrine"?
[KOUSAKU]
Step on in.
[HANDA]
Okay.
And what exactly
am I supposed to do here?
A prayer, or...?
I'd rather
you take a look at this.
Them's the names of the folks
that helped out
when the shine was built.
Actually, that amounts
to everyone
in the whole dang village.
We wanted
to get it rewritten.
Here. The list.
[KOUSAKU]
Same as on the wall.
We were gonna hire
some fancy pants from the city
to rewrite it for us, but
I reckon you're even fancier.
Take it.
Oh, wow, this is amazing.
This must be really old.
Might not be a whole bunch,
but we can pay you, of course.
Oh, no, I'm not worried
about the money.
Don't fancy the work?
It's not that.
[HANDA] This is just
so meticulously ordered.
I'm afraid I'm rusty.
[KOUSAKU] You just write 'em
how you do best.
And here we got space
for one more name.
Why don't you
put your signature there,
since you'll be
a part of this, too.
Are you sure?
I'm not really adding much.
[whispers]
Shh! It'll be our secret.
That's not very convincing.
--[AKKI] Sensei.
--[HANDA] Hm?
There was a call
for you back at the store.
From Mr. Kawafuji.
First he ignores me,
and then he wants to talk.
Take this. Got it?
[NARU]
Uh-huh.
So why'd Kawafuji
call him, anyway?
He said he had something
important to talk about.
And what's
that supposed to mean?
Grownup talk, that's what.
--[NARU whimpers]
--[KENTA and HINA] Huh?
Is something wrong, Naru?
Grandpa stole
my birthday present.
It was an "I'll do anything
you say" ticket
from Sensei, and we were gonna
have so much fun!
Sorry, sounds like
a tough break.
[AKKI]
So, if you had another ticket,
what would you want
to use it for?
[NARU]
Lemme think.
I wanna go to a festival
with Sensei for one,
and then go walk
in the mountains!
Oh, and we could go
to a sports game, too!
And the beach!
Then let's see...
You don't need a ticket.
If you asked, I bet Sensei
would do that stuff for free.
Y' think so? Then I'll ask him
when I get back!
[KENTA] Festival's
right around the corner!
We gotta make plans!
[HINA]
I wanna wear a kimono!
[NARU] Then let's ask Miwa
and Tama to come too!
[AKKI] Are you sure?
They're gonna cause trouble!
[NARU] You wanna cause
some trouble too?
[AKKI]
Sure.
[ALL laughing]
Yeah. I see.
Oh, no, it's fine.
I'll come back.
[MIWA]
Okay!
I think this one's my best.
Here's my favorite.
Good.
Those are both strong pieces.
You've learned a lot from
my lessons, but as your mentor,
there is nothing more
I can teach you.
That gold award is yours,
I guarantee it!
[BOTH]
Okay!
[ALL groan]
I mean, he says that,
but who knows
if our teacher
is gonna like it or not.
After all of that hard work,
what if we don't get any award?
I don't even
wanna turn it in now!
Are you fools?
I trained you, didn't I?
Your calligraphy
will not lose to anyone!
Where does
that confidence come from?
I'm actually
not confident at all.
Not with your work,
I mean, my own.
I have no idea if my latest
piece is worth anything or not.
[BOTH]
Uh-oh!
Sensei!
Let's go!
There's a festival!
[NARU gasps]
There. All done!
Wow! I didn't know
you could tie a yukata sash!
That's awesome.
[laughs]
It's cute!
You think this is awesome?
Yukata are easy.
--I can do kimono sashes, too!
--Wow.
You're going
to the festival, right?
Yeah.
[NARU]
Yay! Let's hurry!
It's gonna be so much fun!
We're meeting up
with some friends first,
but we'll
see you there, 'kay?
--Thanks again for the lessons.
--Sure.
[NARU]
Sensei, what's taking so long?
[HINA]
Let's go!
That's enough!
A festival. Who knows,
maybe a little change
of pace is all that I need.
What'cha smiling 'bout, Sensei?
I wasn't smiling,
I was just deep in thought!
[NARU and HINA screaming]
--Hey...
--[NARU and HINA] Festival!
[HANDA sighs]
Well, it's fine.
This one last time.
[NARU]
Yay! Party time! Party time!
[CROWD chattering]
[NARU and HINA]
Yay!
C'mon, this way!
[HANDA chuckles]
[thinks]
Wow, it's a picture-perfect
small town festival.
Guess I don't
have much experience
with that sort of thing.
There's a festival today, Sei,
would you like to go?
[SEIMEI]
He has an exhibit to attend to.
C'mon, Handa,
let's go to the festival!
[HANDA'S MOTHER] I'm sorry,
Sei has an exhibit to attend to.
Handa, let's go
check out the festival!
He's got an exhibit,
but you can go with me!
[HANDA]
What?
[thinks]
That is super depressing,
especially since I have
an exhibit coming up.
[NARU]
Sensei! Come play this!
You can win a goldfish!
[thinks] I can make up
for the childhood I never had!
[HANDA trembling]
[IWAO] Well, I'll be damned!
If it ain't Sensei!
[HANDA]
If I can't catch a goldfish,
I don't have to cut off
a finger, do I?
[IWAO] You here to support
the community or not?
Uh, yes sir, sorry.
Then pay up!
A pastry shell?
So, I catch it with this?
It'll be easy!
Easy!
You're mine, fishy!
[HANDA]
Huh?
You sure stink
at this, don't you?
This is defective,
gimme a new one!
It's not the game, buddy,
it's the player.
Fine.
One more try.
'Scuse me, Sensei,
move over a bit.
The nurse from before.
Hey, Iku!
[IKU] You have to be gentle,
or it'll break. Watch.
Take notes, 'cause
this gal's the best there is.
[HANDA and NARU]
That's crazy!
[HANDA]
It's like the goldfish
can't wait to leap
into her arms!
[AIKO]
Ah! It's Iku!
What can I say?
Fair's fair.
Girl puts me
in the red every year.
Can't help but wonder what she
does with all of 'em, though.
Good question.
--[AIKO] Iku!
--Last sweep, here we go!
[AIKO laughs]
What are you doing, Aiko?
That's a damn shame, Iku--
better luck next time.
Aww. I almost broke
my old record!
[crowd laughs]
[KAZUYUKI]
Iku tries to make a clean sweep
at the goldfish scoop
every year.
[HANDA]
The head teacher.
I taught her not to be so flashy
back in school,
but I guess she didn't learn!
Oh, yeah?
She was your student?
[HANDA thinks] He wants me
to ask about the balloons,
but I'm not taking the bait.
[NARU] We didn't catch
a single goldfish.
[HANDA]
Taking care of pets is a pain.
I lost on purpose.
They're doin'
somethin' cool over there!
I wonder what.
Actually, it's
a free throw competition.
--[NARU] Hey, Akki.
--Oh, hey there.
I entered, myself.
You make a four-person team,
then shoot for points
to win coupons.
[ALL]
And we're his team!
--[HANDA] You again?
--Oh right, you've already met!
Anyway, I thought
we might actually have
a shot at winning it
this time around,
but the middle school girls
are out for blood.
5,000 yen in coupons!
Let's teach those fools
that the softball club
shows no mercy!
You got it, Miwa.
Girls these days.
[HANDA]
Hey, Tama isn't with you?
Hey, Sensei.
She was supposed to be here,
but she had to go buy
some dumb manga.
We still need a fourth player,
so she better get her butt down
here before it's our turn.
So this is Sensei!
Wow, he's cute.
Nice shot, Akki!
I'm gonna put that little shrimp
in his place, just you wait!
Akki acts all low-key, but he's
actually a superstar, huh?
If Tama doesn't show up pronto,
we're gonna be disqualified!
[scoffs]
What is her deal?
The release date is today!
Why don't you have it?
--[TAMA crying]
--We've been over this before.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Next up,
"Team Softball Club Plus Tama"!
--C'mon, Miwa, do something!
--[MIWA stammers]
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Are you ready, ladies?
I am gonna shove
her glasses up her butt!
--Sensei, help us!
--Huh?
Even you can make
one little shot, right?
That's easy for you to say.
Also, are you
making fun of me?
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Second shot!
Third shot!
You're in the softball club,
why are you so good?
Officially, yeah,
but we practice with
the basketball club too.
None of the clubs have
many members,
so we trade out a lot.
The country life
is breeding superhumans.
Here! You're up!
Better not miss!
Hold on!
[thinks]
Can't back down now.
Don't blow it, Sensei!
[thinks] I never thought
this day would come,
when I show the world
my hidden talent. That's right.
When I was in high school,
I read basketball manga!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
"Team Akki" wins!
Who'd've thought
that grade schoolers
would seize victory
from the jaws of defeat?
C'mon.
It ain't that bad.
I-- I really thought
I could do it.
[MIWA]
Here, Sensei!
It ain't much, but we still got
some coupons for second place...
Even split
for 300 yen a head.
I kind of ruined it
for you, are you sure?
Well, you did better
than Tama, at least.
I can't complain.
[crying] Why did you sell
the book I preordered?
--That was my copy!
--We'll get more in soon.
Curse you!
[HANDA] What do you want to eat?
Your pick, my treat.
Yay! Takoyaki!
--Yakisoba!
--Cotton candy then.
--[BOTH] Huh?
--[HINA] Cheapo!
You said we could have
anything we wanted!
You need to learn that
adults aren't made of money!
Fine, I'll just
buy it myself, then.
Same here.
[HANDA]
You had money all this time?
Then why were so excited?
If you want something, lemme
know, and I can buy it for you!
Even when free food is at stake,
I can't take up a little girl
on that offer.
[HIRO]
Just let her treat you.
[HANDA]
Hiro!
Try some yakisoba.
Proceeds go
to the baseball club!
Hmm... It's not that
I don't have any money, but...
Three cotton candies,
with these coupons.
[NARU, HINA and HIRO think]
How cheap can you get?
[HIRO]
Here. Extra large.
[NARU laughs]
--Yours.
--[HINA] Awesome!
--And yours.
--Oh, wow.
Thanks a bunch, Sensei!
[thinks] I've never
had cotton candy before.
Where am I supposed to start?
Here? Over here?
Do I just bite it?
[thinks]
Why do I feel like
he isn't responsible enough
for cotton candy?
I'm worried he's gonna get it
on someone's clothes,
or poke himself with the stick.
Hiroshi!
We got more yakisoba!
[NARU]
Taiko drums sure are loud!
They sure are!
[drum playing continues]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
The fireworks display will begin
at nine o'clock.
[NARU]
Did she say fireworks?
[HANDA]
Yeah. It's a big crowd.
Don't get lost, okay?
--[HINA and NARU screaming]
--[HANDA] Uh-oh!
[HINA and NARU]
Help us, we're floating away!
That was fast.
Naru! Hina!
Damn, why is it so dark here?
--Sensei.
--[yelps] Tama?
What are you doing?
I was just reading
the manga I bought today.
I don't do very well
with crowds,
so this is
pretty much what I do
when the summer festival
comes around each year.
Not that I have
any room to talk,
but you are throwing away
your youth.
Have you seen Naru or--
Stop it!
They came through here,
so they were
probably headed to the beach.
The fireworks display should
be starting any minute now.
I know
the perfect place to sit.
Hey, it's Sensei!
[MIWA] Tama, where
have you been hiding?
Oh, you know me,
just reading manga.
Where's the rest
of the softball club?
They're gonna watch the
fireworks with their boyfriends.
Maybe they'll get blown up
by the fireworks.
--Tama!
--[KENTA] Cool!
[KENTA] Look!
Naru and Hina are here too!
--[NARU] Hey!
--So where's your girlfriend?
What gives?
You think I'd be cooking
yakisoba if I had a girlfriend?
I know.
Just pullin' yer' leg.
--So, same group as usual, huh?
--Yep!
Can't believe
summer break is ending.
So it's back
to the drudgery of school,
but we had lots of fun and all
good things must come to an end.
Will you be
taking entrance exams?
[HIRO]
Hmm.
I'll probably look for a job.
[MIWA]
Like, a job on the island or...?
--I'm leaving.
--Aww. It's gonna be so sad.
Well, I still
got some time left.
I guess so, and even if you
leave, we still have Sensei.
[HIRO] You think Sensei
can take my place?
--Uh, hey.
--[ALL THREE] Hm?
There's something I needed
to tell you guys before--
--[fireworks squealing]
--[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Fireworks, yay!
[NARU]
They're blasting my eyes!
--[HINA] So pretty!
--[KENTA] Whoa!
--Hey.
--[BOTH] Hm?
Got any idea what Sensei
--was gonna say to us?
--No.
It's obvious
if you look at him.
That back
and those slumped shoulders
tell you everything
you need to know.
[BOTH giggle]
Sensei!
I'm here to play!
It's locked?
Sensei!
Huh?
He's gone.
♪ You held out
your small hand ♪
♪ Smiling like to you ♪
♪ It was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something ♪
♪ I cannot do ♪
♪ You touched my hand ♪
♪ Without thinking ♪
♪ That was nice for me ♪
♪ All the time we believed ♪
♪ That the world's ♪
♪ In our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe,
I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand ♪
♪ Your warm hand. ♪