Ahem!
'Kay, guys.
If you want Sensei to hurry
back, then gimme a "heck yeah!"
[ALL]
Heck yeah!
If I know Sensei, he won't wanna
come home to a messy house.
So let's team up and make
this place sparkling clean!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Miwa's the one who made
most of this mess.
It's a trap, don't listen!
Time to work, you guys!
Sensei's gonna be so happy!
[ALL]
Yay!
You think
we'll see Sensei again soon?
I hope so.
Sensei!
Hurry on home! We miss you!
[HANDA stammers]
What is this?
[HANDA] Would you mind maybe
explaining this to me?
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
I think it's fairly clear.
This is a silent protest.
I don't want you going back
to that island.
How bored are you?
I already submitted my work.
I was planning on going home
to the island today.
Why, you little beast!
This is your home,
you awful, awful boy!
After all the trouble
I went to raising you,
you throw me
under the bus that easily?
--Mom, calm down!
--Not a chance!
I am going to punch you
and punch you and punch you
--until you change your mind!
--Can we try talking first?
You went straight to abuse!
You couldn't save this
for later, could you?
You're being rude to our guest.
Oh. Hi, Kawafuji!
Nice save!
Perfect timing!
I just stopped by
real quick to tell you
that your work
was accepted for the exhibit.
I'll be leaving now.
What're you saying?
Don't go!
Or even better,
take me with you!
Oh, no.
You're staying!
We are having a life-crisis
discussion, right now!
With Kawafuji included!
He's on my side,
so that's only fair!
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
I was against him going
to that island from the start.
But this big dumb jerk
sitting next to me
decided my opinion
wasn't important.
As if that
weren't bad enough,
then I hear you got sick
and were hospitalized?
Without me
to watch out for you,
I bet you weren't careful about
your cat allergies, either!
--I, uh...
--And just like your father,
you won't listen
to a word I say!
Well, fine! Then I won't listen
to you, either!
You're staying here if I have
to break both your legs!
I see where you get your bouts
of violence from.
[HANDA thinking] As long as
she doesn't break my hands.
Well, clearly your mom makes
a strong point about this.
--I'd stay home.
--What?
Don't you care about
my progress as an artist?
Now that I know you can write
just fine in Tokyo,
I'd honestly rather
have you stay close by,
so I can crack my whip.
Democracy at work, I see.
It's hardly
the wilderness, you know.
I dropped
my phone in the ocean
and I still have
cell phone reception.
And! It's right next
to the mainland,
so I can still get something
if I really need it that bad!
Besides, it's not like
I get out that much anyway,
so I'll hardly notice
the difference!
All I need
is my calligraphy.
I mean, it's not like
I've really got friends here.
Ouch, buddy.
Did I do something
to piss you off, or what?
You honestly think it's the
location that has me so worried?
Huh?
[thinking]
I can tell you've been
hanging around
weirdoes, haven't you?
You've picked up these strange
habits and don't even notice!
I can hardly
recognize you anymore!
Am I seriously that bad now?
Ah... I wouldn't say bad
so much, but weird, definitely.
You have to choose
your friends carefully!
Bad company
ruins good morals!
Hm?
[HANDA thinking]
Bad company, huh?
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
What?
What do you mean, "no"?
You've been acting strange
ever since you came back!
You keep
eating pickles for some reason,
and I heard you talking about
catching some "nusano"?
What is that, drugs?
[HANDA] I don't know
what you're talking about.
And I haven't changed, okay?
[KAWAFUJI]
I dunno about that.
[MOTHER]
The Sei I know would never raise
his voice at his mother!
[groaning]
If your only concerns are
the location and the people
who live there, then I'm afraid
I'm with Seishu on this one.
Thanks, but you didn't
have to change your seat.
I lived on the island myself
when I was his age
and I turned out just fine.
It's a perfectly
healthy environment.
Huh?
I never knew that.
Well, I wouldn't
have asked you to leave
if I didn't know it would be
a positive experience.
Yujiro Kido has been
looking after you, correct?
Kido?
--The mayor!
--Sort of.
I'm sure I have some photos
of us in one of my old albums.
Ah! You don't get
to submit physical evidence!
That's not fair!
This is just
a stroll down memory lane.
[HANDA]
Wow.
I didn't know you kept
old photos like this.
That's crazy.
You look just like Handa.
I like to believe
I have a kinder face.
Here!
It's a picture of me
from the island.
[HANDA]
Whoa, you're both so young!
[SEIMEI] I believe
this was 35 years ago.
Kido and I went
fishing for hisanio.
[BOTH]
Hisanio!
There! "Nusano"!
We caught a hisanio
ourselves, didn't we?
That's not quite
how I remember it.
Wait, the local store?
Oh, good to hear
it's still around, then!
[HANDA] Is that the owner?
She's so young!
She was really pretty!
Ah! The river
hasn't changed a bit!
--[HANDA'S MOTHER groans]
--[SEIMEI] The river.
[SEIMEI] I actually
injured myself down there.
[HANDA] Oh yeah, me too.
I have a scar right here.
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
I've had enough!
None of you understand
my feelings one bit!
You're all just talking about
how great the island is!
I'm worried about my son,
is that so wrong?
Can't you
take this seriously, Da?
Our precious child
is heading down
the path of destruction
and you're cheering him along!
[KAWAFUJI]
"Da," huh?
[SEIMEI]
Please dear, calm down.
We should support whatever
is best for his development.
He needs to live his own life.
Yeah?
And he should do that away
from his loving mother?
The dear,
sweet boy that I raised
would show some appreciation
for all the loving care
I showered him with!
Discourtesy,
as high as a mountain!
Boy, your mom
really is a handful.
You! A back-stabber
and disrespectful to mothers!
[KAWAFUJI]
She heard me? Ow!
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
Undutiful, like a cutting wind!
As traitorous
as a raging fire!
[KAWAFUJI]
Ma'am, wait! you may recall...
Rest in peace, Kawafuji.
[HANDA thinking]
If this is how she's gonna be,
I may be stuck
in Tokyo forever.
[SEIMEI]
Seishu...
I know that I was the one
who sent you to the island,
but what you do now
is all your choice.
Whether this is for your work
or for your own well being,
I trust in your decision.
Just remember,
you'll always have a home here.
[HANDA'S MOTHER] Why does
he have to be so cruel?
I just want the best
for him, can't you see? Ah!
[HANDA sighs] I finished
my piece for the exhibit,
and I think I have a firm handle
on my new style now.
Maybe I don't need to rush back
to the island after all.
If you're gonna stay holed up
in your room either way,
I think it's more convenient
to live here in Tokyo.
[HANDA sighs]
Weighing the pros and cons,
Tokyo does come out ahead.
So why can't
I make up my mind?
Hm.
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
Sei?
This package
just arrived for you.
It seems it's from your friends
back on the island.
Wait!
Are these your things
and you're never going back?
[HANDA] I don't think
they want me gone that bad.
Actually, this got here
a little late.
I asked them for some things
to help with my exhibit piece.
[ALL]
Huh?
What's this stuff?
Shoulda figured.
They just tossed in
whatever junk they had.
They're bullying you!
My sweet boy
is being picked on!
It's complicated, okay?
Must be from Naru.
Ha! Naru?
Who is this "Naru"?
-Some hussy?
-She's just a kid!
They sent these, too?
Uh-oh, it looks like Miwa's
upset about her grade.
Sei, what on earth are those?
It's calligraphy written by
these kids I was teaching.
Huh?
Pretty good for a rookie,
if you ask me.
If I'd known they were
gonna get their grades so soon,
I would've stuck around
a little while longer.
Wish I coulda been there
when they got the news.
So I could congratulate them
or encourage them or something.
Sweetie...
Do what you want.
I don't care.
C'mon, Mom,
enough pouting already.
I'm serious, okay?
Ugh!
If someone on that dumb island
needs you,
then you have to go back.
You mean that?
Yes, as long
as you call me
every once in a while,
you awful child!
Okay, does this mean
I can book a flight?
Well, nobody's stopping you.
You're all right with this?
I am.
I don't know
who his friends are,
but it felt like he really
wanted to look out for them.
If I put my foot down now,
it would just be selfish.
I guess his calligraphy wasn't
the only thing that matured.
Mm-hm.
That island
is a wonderful place.
We should go visit
before the cold settles in.
Sure.
Ahem! So...
We just
received word from Akki,
fulfilling his duty
as keeper of the phone,
and it turns out Sensei's coming
home on a plane this evening!
[ALL]
Yay!
Okay!
So let's team up
and make this
place sparkling clean for real!
[ALL]
Yeah!
But seriously,
Sensei's gonna lose his mind
if he sees this mess,
so let's hurry.
[HIRO]
So heavy.
You're
a real piece of work, Sensei.
You leave the island
without a word
and you come back
just as fast.
But man, hope the girls
are cleaning that place up.
[MIWA and TAMA thinking]
Okay, so maybe this wasn't
the best use of time.
--[HIRO] Hey.
--How long have you been here?
No! Please don't ask!
[MIWA]
We somehow got it in our heads
that these things were cool,
but we were wrong.
You don't need to scold us!
We know we're dumb!
[HIRO] Whatever.
Just finish things up, okay?
Hold on, you haven't
even started cleaning yet!
--Whoops?
--Whaddya mean by, "whoops"?
So did you come by
just to help us out?
You wish.
I have my own work to do.
Gotta put slides
on all the windows
before the weather
gets too cold.
Huh.
So what happened
to the old ones,
they break or something?
No, but they fell off
when a typhoon hit.
I've been keeping them
at my place since then.
Wait,
stop changing the subject,
you need to get back
to cleaning up this place!
Aww.
Hurry it up, you guys don't
wanna face Sensei's wrath.
[HIRO]
Separate the trash!
--Kenta, you sweeping the floor?
--Uh-huh!
[HIRO]
You two, wipe the windows!
Lookin' pretty good.
We should take a break.
Break from what?
You two haven't
even done anything yet!
[MIWA] Okay, okay.
I just gotta remember.
We're doing
all this for Sensei.
One for all
and all for Sensei!
--All for Sensei!
All for Sensei!
[BOTH]
[ALL]
All for Sensei!
--[TAMA] Operation Clean Up...
--[MIWA] Complete!
[ALL]
Take that, dirt!
Now I can't wait to make
the place all messy again!
At least hold out
until Sensei comes back.
[MIWA] I can't believe
he's on his way here, already!
Yeah, I know!
--Let's party!
--All right.
Then I'll run home
and bring back some snacks.
Think maybe you can cook
something up for us, Hiro?
You really do
wanna make a mess, huh?
[yawning]
I made it.
Village Leader was
supposed to pick me up,
but I guess he's late.
If I start walking,
I'll catch him.
[DIRECTOR]
Seishu's piece should be
up for review shortly.
[SEIMEI]
Yes. I haven't seen it either,
so I'm looking forward to this.
[DIRECTOR] Kanzaki's work was
quite excellent this time.
I have a feeling
those two youngsters
are going to have
a long-running rivalry.
My only hope is that no matter
the result, Seishu is able
to see what lies beyond it
as an artist.
I believe your son has
a clear vision of the future
and will not lose
his way again on that path.
Now that he's had
his share of setbacks,
I have a feeling he might
rein in that impulsive nature.
[thinking]
"Impulsive."
That's certainly the word.
Though I have a feeling
he still has a while to go.
[groaning]
No cars anywhere.
Did he forget?
A vending machine! Yeah!
[grunts]
Money, money,
money, money, money.
Ugh! No!
Okay, got my money now,
get my tea.
--[machine clunks]
--Oh, no!
Why would they even offer
hot soup in the summer?
[tractor arriving]
Lucky break!
Well, howdy-do, Sensei!
Whatcha doin 'round here?
Did you come to pick me up,
by any chance?
Nuh-uh!
I'm just takin' a drive!
Wow.
They really did forget.
--Sensei?
--Hmm?
Why don't you
hop in the back?
[sighs]
This brings back memories.
This is exactly like when
I first I came to the island.
Matter of fact...
Beautiful weather
and a beautiful view this time.
Ha ha ha!
Ain't no different
than before.
Same sea.
"Same sea." Not everything
needs to change, I guess.
[rings]
Yes?
Kinoshita Shuten's place.
Oh, Mr. Kawafuji, yes,
I haven't seen him,
but I think Sensei made it okay.
The Village Leader
went to-- Wait.
--[KOUSAKU] Pert' got you home.
--[HANDA] Pert what?
Actually,
I think that's him now.
--[HANDA] Huh?
--[AKKI] Sensei!
[MIWA]
Okay, soon as Sensei walks
through the door,
we all pop these!
--I'm gonna tackle him!
--[MIWA] Sweet! Do it!
[KIDS yell]
[ALL gasp]
He's early!
[MIWA]
Oh. Nah, it's just Akki.
--Sorry I'm a letdown.
--[MIWA] Where's Sensei?
[AKKI] He's at the store talking
to Kawafuji on the phone.
I think exhibit results
came in already.
Uh-oh. Scary.
--I didn't think about that.
--Me either.
If he gets second place again,
he's gonna be a wreck.
C'mon.
Sensei's a grown-ass adult.
He's not going to let that ruin
his homecoming party.
[MIWA and TAMA]
Are you kidding?
Sensei's childishness
knows no bounds!
Also, getting second place
really hurts, okay?
Hurry, guys,
Sensei's almost here!
[ALL gasp]
Wait. Where's my
party cracker?
[MIWA]
You had it a second ago!
[TAMA]
Hey! Where's mine?
They're gone!
[ALL screaming]
Here!
I'm home.
[screams]
[HANDA]
Ugh.
[bodies thumping]
--[NARU laughs]
--[MIWA] Ugh. That wasn't funny.
[TAMA]
Oww.
[MIWA]
Sensei, you break anything?
I come back,
and you all try to kill me.
--Missed you!
--Your hands are all sticky!
What've you been
getting into, Naru?
Ah!
He's in a good mood!
Guess he won his thing, then.
Hey, Sensei.
You won the contest, right?
--[BOTH grunt]
--Betcha kicked butt!
Hey! What did we tell you
about traumatizing Sensei?
This is
a very delicate issue!
Oh, yeah.
Ignore what she said,
everything's a-okay!
What gives?
Were you that scared
that I would lose? No big deal.
You're happy with the results?
Well, yeah.
--[ALL cheering]
--[TAMA] What a relief!
[HIRO]
Congrats!
You didn't exactly lose.
The old timers were
just really tough this contest.
Half of those guys'll
be dead soon anyway,
so your time'll come
if you just wait it out.
Then you can sit
on your mountain of awards
and laugh at all the rookies.
[SEIMEI] Oh, I didn't know
you were here.
Oh, hello, sir.
Did you call the island
to let Seishu know the results?
Yes, sir. Even though he left,
I'm sure he was curious.
It wasn't exactly
a triumphant victory.
Do you think
he'll be disappointed?
Who knows?
It's Seishu.
Anyway, at least
he's on the path
to creating
his own style now.
Win or lose, it'll be fun.
[SEIMEI]
Mm.
[ALL]
Cheers!
Tell us! What kinda piece
did you write?
Yeah!
We're dying to know!
It's not really interesting
enough to talk about.
But it was your masterpiece,
wasn't it?
Just tell us already!
Like what was the idea?
What were the words?
Give us the scoop!
[TAMA]
C'mon!
I guess the theme was,
"The most important things
in my life right now."
[TAMA]
Oh, like what?
You, you don't
mean Hiro, do you?
[MIWA] Obviously, it's
our calligraphy homework!
--[HANDA] No.
--[HIRO laughs] Knowing Sensei,
it was probably something like,
"You are what you eat!"
[HANDA] It's nothing
to do with food.
[HINA]
Then maybe a bunny?
[HANDA] Where did you
get that from?
[KENTA] I bet he wrote something
about a beetle!
[YUTAKA]
Or a praying mantis!
[DAISUKE]
Or scorpions!
[AKKI] That's enough, guys,
leave Sensei alone.
[TAMA] You're always
such a suck-up, Akki.
[AKKI]
I am not.
[MIWA] Look at him,
trying to play it off.
Oh, well.
--[NARU] Sensei?
--Hm?
I know
we're all real noisy,
but it's sure nice being
together, huh?
[gasps]
[happily sighs]
[ALL overlapping dialogue]
Just watching all you guys
have fun is an inspiration.
For my work and my life.
Inspiration?
Huh?
[HANDA]
It means you have to soak in
the moment to really be alive.
You get it?
[NARU]
Hmm.
Not really.
♪ You held out
your small hand ♪
♪ Smiling like to you ♪
♪ It was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something
I cannot do ♪
♪ You touched my hand
without thinking ♪
♪ But that was nice
for me ♪
♪ All the time we believed ♪
♪ That the world
was in our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe
I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand ♪
♪ Your warm hand. ♪
[HANDA]
Ready?
[ALL] Thanks for watching,
everybody!
[ALL]
Yay!
[ALL laughing]
[HANDA]
How are you sticky?