[sighs]
[thinking]
Just two more weeks.
But the more stressed I get,
the harder it is to come up
with something good.
It's strange, but ever since
I came to this island,
I started getting these powerful
urges to do calligraphy pieces.
Something rises up inside me.
My hands start to shake.
I need to get that feeling back.
I just don't know how I can.
Maybe I'll feel better
if I take a hot bath.
Huh? Can't get it to click.
Please, no. Oh, no, not now!
[grunting]
Why? Why me? Why this?
Yep. It's busted.
So how long do you think it'll
take for someone to fix it?
Let's see.
Probably be a week, at least.
Figured as much.
Wait a sec. I just realized
we have a backup plan.
Huh?
[YUJIRO] Ta-da! A bath boiler.
If you burn firewood in here,
you can heat your bath
the old-fashioned way.
That's not just gonna burn
my house down?
Of course not. We use a boiler
at my place and I just love it.
Yeah, but you said
this uses firewood.
It's not like I have
that just lying around.
Sure you do.
There's a whole mountain full
of trees right behind you.
[laughter trails off]
Remember, the branches have to
be dry or else they won't burn.
Hey!
[thinking] I wanna tell him
this is a pain in the ass,
but I don't think I have
the heart to break it to him.
There's more over here.
I have to do this crap
for a whole week?
[screams]
--Lovely.
--[screams]
I'm so sorry, sir.
[YUJIRO] This is about how many
branches you'll need.
I bet you wish you had
a pretty young wife
to keep the fire for you,
huh, Sensei?
All I really want is a bath with
a gas-powered hot water heater.
You're at the right age.
You don't have any lucky ladies
in your life you've thought
about marrying?
Not a one, lucky or otherwise.
Aw, come on.
I'm absorbed in my work
all the time,
so it's like, well, I'm the type
who might die alone.
[YUJIRO chuckles]
[HANDA thinks] You're
supposed to tell me I'm wrong.
[YUJIRO]
Well, you should be good to go.
[HANDA] Huh?
--[TAMA] Hey, Miwa.
--Hmm?
Is it just me, or is that smoke
coming from Sensei's house?
Looks like it.
A bonfire?
You think Sensei would do that
kind of thing?
Might be.
A fire!
[HANDA]
Just a bath.
I see.
Sensei,
you big troublemaker, you.
I can help if you like.
I'm really good at this.
Yeah?
Then you've done this before?
Yep. When my grandpa
takes a hot bath,
I'm right there
to watch the fire.
And you're absolutely sure
you're okay doing this?
Leave it to me. I'm a pro.
The prep work's kind of a pain,
but it almost feels like
I'm going to a hot spring.
I'm excited.
Yow!
Sensei, is it too hot?
No. I'm fine.
Don't scare me.
[sighs] It's so relaxing.
[thinks] I can feel
the stress just melting away.
I'm starting to see the appeal,
even with all that wood
gathering.
[NARU] Sensei. Help me!
Are you okay?
[BOTH chuckle]
Hold it.
Naru, what are these two doing
here harassing me?
They came 'cause they thought
there was a fire.
We should punish you for forcing
a kid watch to the boiler.
Seeing you naked will do.
[HANDA]
Where's the logic in that?
You probably want girls to look
at you nude, you sicko.
Sorry, but I'm not a flasher
and my house is not on fire,
so kindly get lost.
He never likes to play along,
does he?
Uh... why the camera?
I need photos to use
for manga reference.
Of him? Even in manga,
you can't show the naughty bits.
What? Sure you can.
You just have to
censor the tip of it.
[thinking]
How am I supposed to relax now?
I'll have to remember not
to take baths in the afternoon.
Maybe if I just wait it out,
they'll get bored
and leave on their own.
You punks trying to melt me?
--[laughing]
--[TAMA] Book it!
So was it hot enough, Sensei?
What do you think?
Look how red I am.
--Book it!
--Wait, not you too.
Ahh. Lot of trouble,
but I do feel better.
Now let's get to work.
[chopping] Hey.
Aah! What're you doing here,
Hiro?
Mom is out,
so she can't cook today.
I thought I'd make you lunch
instead.
Fine, but why here?
First, cut the cucumber.
Add miso and sugar,
about this much.
Toss the cucumber in the bowl
and mix just a bit.
There you go, cucumbers with
miso in just three easy steps.
I see. If it's that simple,
I bet even someone like me
could do it.
First, cut the cucumber.
Add miso and sugar,
then mix. Perfect.
Sensei,
were you watching at all?
What?
It's the same, isn't it?
In what way?
It'll be the same
once you eat it.
I'm a man, okay? My food
looks bad and tastes good.
No, pretty sure that's
gonna be terrible.
[BOTH]
Thanks for the meal.
Whoa! This is really good.
And this is just plain awful.
I'd be better off eating
a cucumber by itself.
Actually, this is yucky.
You're not fooling anyone.
You just said it was good.
Don't get such a big head over
this. It's only miso.
I'm not the one with the big
head, you spoiled baby.
You take that back. Don't speak
to your elders that way.
My "elder" needs to stop
pointing his finger
and act like a damn adult.
--[growling]
--[HINA screams]
Sensei!
What's wrong, Hina?
Hey, tell me what happened.
Would you pull it together?
Crying isn't gonna help.
Don't rush her, Sensei.
Hina, have some tea
and calm down.
She came running here screaming
and crying.
It's got to be an emergency.
Tell me.
[HIROSHI] Let her cry if she
likes. Why are you so impatient?
[HANDA]
What? I just want to know.
So you can help her
or because this is bugging you?
--[wailing]
--I'm sorry. Calm down.
It'll be okay.
It's Naru.
A bunch of bigger kids
from the other village
--are picking on her.
--[BOTH gasp]
Over here.
Naru, are you okay?
[screaming]
Hey, cut it out.
[BOTH think]
Actually, that looks kinda fun.
Naru!
Hina, help me!
You guys went
and got grownups?
Cheater.
Hey, get off their playground.
You kids go on back
to wherever you came from.
Shut your trap, fox face!
You snooze, you lose.
This is our turf now.
[thinks]
"Fox face"?
They must be
from Rokunosaki village.
The high school and middle
school kids from there
are a bunch
of little punks, too.
Come on, Sensei,
make 'em go away.
We were playing here first
and they ruined it.
Okay. Hey look, you
little dweebs, listen up.
We've never even met before, so
why did you call me "fox face?"
What part of me, exactly,
is fox like?
'Cause if it's my eyes,
I have heard that sometimes.
Sensei's really taking
this personally, huh?
You wussy bean sprout. Go away.
Ugh! That hurt,
but my pride hurts much more.
That kid's a genius.
He only saw Sensei for like,
five seconds
and he could already tell
he's a pushover.
Huh?
You gotta take
a stern approach
with brats like these.
Here, I'll show you.
Hey, you turds!
--He's scary.
--He a gangster?
Who cares?
You don't scare me, punk.
You're the big kids here.
You can let the little
ones have fun, right?
Please? Just this once.
If you want it that bad,
then get down and beg.
[laughing]
--[growling]
--Don't flip out!
Screw that.
I'm gonna pound some manners
into this doggone ankle biter
if it's the last think I do.
Book it!
I know they suck,
but you can't go around
punching children.
Sensei, we just wanna play
dodgeball.
Can we do that, please?
Don't worry. There's no way
we're backing down now.
[thinks]
The children are counting on me.
Now's my chance
to get my dignity back.
Listen up, kiddos.
Shut up, you wet noodle.
[thinks]
Somehow, that really hits home.
We're adults,
so we won't resort to violence.
But if you kids loiter
any longer,
I'll have to make a call
and I don't think you'll like
what happens next.
Who you gonna call, huh?
Your mommy?
Hmm. The police.
Whoa, why you gotta pull
the cops into this, huh?
I'm going to make an anonymous
call and tell them
you're bullying
innocent children.
Your parents will be so ashamed.
I bet the other kids at school
will make fun of you, too.
And that is how an adult
wins a fight.
[HIRO thinks]
Wow, that is petty.
Dang it!
To heck with your dirty tricks.
Take this!
Oh! It's over.
You've dealt the finishing blow
to my poor little friend.
Hey, man, chill out.
We just got some poop on it.
Though I couldn't use him after
I dropped him in the ocean,
this loyal partner of mine
at least kept the time.
Are you telling me that thing
don't even work?
You better apologize to us.
How about you apologize
to my phone, you little urchin?
[laughing]
Hiro, were you just laughing?
No, this is all very serious.
What a couple of clowns.
Let's leave 'em
and play some ball.
Hey, Sensei,
those brats are ignoring us.
Don't make me repeat myself.
You kids go back to the
playground in your own village.
We can't. Our playground
got taken over
by these two middle school
girls.
One of 'em's all tough and manly
and the other's got
funny glasses.
[BOTH think]
Them, huh?
That's got nothing
to do with this. Go away!
Naru! Hey, that's going
too far, you hooligan.
Oh, boo hoo.
What, you gonna punch us?
'Cause I don't think my
folks would be too happy
to hear about that, do you?
Then you guys are gonna be
the ones who get in trouble
with the cops. How's that?
You're gonna go to jail
for child abuse.
Unfortunately,
I can't argue with that.
I want to hit 'em,
but they have a point.
Guess we'll just have to
be adults here.
Naru, we can't stop their
baseball game after all.
--Just let 'em play.
--Aww.
You finally get it, now scram.
Those guys can play baseball.
And we can play dodgeball,
right?
Oh, yeah.
--[BOTH] Huh?
--Wait.
I thought you said you
were gonna let us play.
Yeah, stick around and have
all the fun you like.
In the meantime,
we'll be having our own fun.
Me and Sensei are gonna be
outfield,
-so you guys better move it.
-[shouting]
But how do we--
Game on!
[thinks]
That's hardcore, Sensei.
No mercy, even for kids.
You think I don't know how
to play dodgeball?
Who wants some of this, huh?
He hit the ball back at me.
Would you pull yourself
together, man?
If they get the ball,
it's all over.
Come on. You're grownups.
You're not playing fair.
You got it all wrong.
Didn't you know?
[BOTH] Grownups don't have to
play fair.
Time for round two.
We're gonna unleash.
Eat this.
Back up a little bit, Sensei.
They're playing dodgeball
in this heat?
--It's Akki.
--Akki.
Hey, you're not busy today,
are you?
I'm stuck on a boss on that game
you lent me. Can you help?
Hey, you little squirts,
this isn't over yet.
Nah, we're good now.
We're gonna play
with Akki instead.
What? So did we win here?
I'm a little confused.
Sorry about that.
I interrupted your
game, didn't I?
Game? Yeah, that's totally
what it was.
Bye.
We'll be back.
[HANDA] I feel like Akki's
the real adult here.
[HIROSHI] Yeah.
Stop following me.
I'm not doing anything fun.
I'm just going back home.
--Aww. No! Let's play.
--No pulling.
Ah-ha. Let's play Tarzan.
What's that?
Let's go over there
and I'll show you.
You're gonna have a blast.
[yells]
Well, maybe for a minute.
I might as well, right?
[KIDS cheering]
Oh. Wow, this is
like real Tarzan.
Let me explain.
What's to explain? It's just
a vine and a long fall.
I'll go first,
so you watch close now.
Are you kidding?
That's dangerous.
[shouting]
Oh!
[groans] You see? Piece of cake.
[HANDA thinks]
That is gonna send me
straight to the hospital.
Here. Go ahead,
knock yourself out.
Heck, no!
Why not? It's super fun.
And you call yourself a grownup.
I'm not swinging on the vine
because I'm a grownup,
you little imp.
There's no way that thing could
hold the weight of an adult.
I mean, it would have to be able
to support
all of you at once
for that to work.
[KIDS] Hmm.
I take it back!
Please don't do that!
Then you'll try after all?
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Anything, as long as you don't
all kill yourselves on my watch.
Look, guys.
Sensei is gonna be awesome.
I can't tell
if she really means that
or she just wants
to see me hurt myself.
[thinks] This is obviously
an accident waiting to happen.
The kids won't like it,
but I've gotta get rid
of this thing
before someone gets hurt.
Are you ready?
I'll break this off
and that will be that.
--[screams]
--[laughs maniacally]
Stop it, Sensei.
You're pulling it too much!
--No!
--Come on!
[wails] Stop fighting, please.
[gasping]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Agh!
[splashes]
[coughs]
Is everyone all right?
--Yep. Doing great!
--That was so scary!
[thinks] I thought
I was gonna die.
I thought I was gonna die!
--Is that blood?
--Please don't die.
I'm fine. It's just a graze.
We gotta use mugwort to fix it.
Huh? No, it's not that big
a deal. I promise.
Mugwort!
I'll make some medicine
to stop the bleeding.
It's just a scratch.
Also, please don't rub dirt
on my forehead.
[NARU]
Let's take the secret shortcut.
[HANDA thinks]
Another day wasted
without anything to show for it.
I really should find something
more productive
to do than play with kids
every day. This is bad.
I can't afford to sit around and
wait for inspiration to hit me.
The closer I get to my deadline,
the more hopeless it feels.
Yes. It's here.
Finally. I feel it.
All it took was one sunset
for the God of Calligraphy
to shine upon me.
I gotta go write.
Hurry. Hurry! Ugh!
[screams]
Huh?
Is something wrong, Naru?
Sensei's not following us.
He probably went back another
way by himself is all.
You think?
[KENTA] Yep.
Sensei loves doing stuff alone.
[NARU]
I guess.
[KENTA]
I know.
[KIDS laughing]
Huh?
So Sensei never came home today?
Nope, just been the two of us
here as far as I know.
Sensei disappeared when me
and my friends
were coming back
from the mountains.
That doesn't sound good.
Yeah, that's a shame. I bet one
of those mountain titans
--is eating him up as we speak.
--[HANDA whimpering]
[screams]
I don't know about
the whole titan thing,
but I am worried
that he's not home yet.
Even if he's lost
in the mountains,
it's not like the forest
is that big.
There.
A rabbit.
Don't scare me like that.
[thinks] And just when
I finally got some inspiration.
The time I spent with the kids
is already a distant,
fading memory.
I can barely remember
their smiling faces.
[gasps] No, stop.
That's not even remotely true.
You're just freaking out
and exaggerating the situation.
Stay calm and stay on track.
I just need to climb up
a little more.
[grunting]
You can do it, Seishu.
Keep on climbing, Seishu.
Okay.
[gasps]
[screaming]
Oh, crap.
Argh! I hate this!
Damn it. Help should be here
by now. Where are they?
Normally, I just want everyone
to leave me alone,
but the one time I do need them,
there's not a soul to be found.
I'm dead.
I really am gonna die alone.
Somebody help me.
Anyone! Hmm?
What is that?
What's a key doing way out here?
It's the key to my house.
I made five spares, but I
must have lost the last one
when I was up in the mountains.
Oh, so that's it.
[laughs]
This is stupid.
It's no big deal.
I'm practically
in my own back yard.
I'm not gonna get stranded and
die, that's not even possible.
So many stars.
It's beautiful.
You sure can't see this
in the city.
Hey, a shooting star.
Please let my bath be fixed.
Actually, let's try that again.
Please let me get home
so I can write calligraphy.
Okay, he wasn't eaten.
He just fell.
That explains why we couldn't
find him on the path at least.
Sensei, I thought
you were done for.
You guys sure took your time.
Sensei's crying, isn't he?
Yeah, not pretty.
[laughs] Yes! This is it.
Hey, I brought you
a first aid kit, Sensei.
--[HANDA] Finally!
--Oh.
Looks like you're busy.
[HANDA laughing]
Guess there's nothing more
powerful than pure inspiration.
♪ You held out
your small hand ♪
♪ Smiling like to you ♪
♪ It was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something
I cannot do ♪
♪ You touched my hand ♪
♪ Without thinking ♪
♪ That was nice for me ♪
♪ All the time we believed ♪
♪ That the world's ♪
♪ In our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe,
I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand ♪
♪ Your warm hand. ♪
Yeah. I see.
Oh, no, it's fine.
I'll come back.