[MIWA] Huh?
[bird calling]
[MIWA]
Did I miss something?
[NARU]
This, ladies, is a
"pre-mi-um choc-o-late bar."
[MIWA] You can read English
and Japanese now?
[TAMA]
Good job, Naru!
Mmm. It's manly.
Say what now?
[NARU]
I have mastered all words.
When I finished
my summer reading homework,
I became a true man.
[TAMA and MIWA]
Hmm?
I'm flexing the muscles
in my brain.
My mind can see a new world
of adult wonders,
a kingdom of men.
You might even call it...
Mandom!
Where did she learn that?
Now, let me find you something
a little more challenging.
Here.
Can you read this?
"Open with push-ups."
Yeah, that's close enough!
I don't get the manly thing,
but you've sure gotten real good
at reading!
You can take the milk
as a reward.
No push-ups required.
Thank you, ma'am.
Make sure you tell everyone what
a big, manly reader you are!
Kids sure grow up fast
these days.
I mean the studying.
The "mandom" thing is actually
pretty normal for her.
What do you think caused
the big change, anyway?
Probably hanging out
with that calligraphy nerd.
Aha!
Uh, hello there.
Everything okay?
Sensei, can you read
the top of this?
It's "push to... open"?
[NARU] Hmm...
[theme song playing]
Yeah, it's done.
I just mailed it off.
Send it to
the Tokyo Kasho Exhibit.
I see!
You're pretty confident!
That piece is the new face
of my art.
I wouldn't send it
if I wasn't confident.
[KAWAFUJI]
I'll call you when it gets here.
Oh, right.
I almost forget
that I ran out of ink.
[entering number]
Hiro?
Where can I buy ink around here?
Kinoshita Shoten?
[KINOSHITA]
Glad you stopped by!
Ah...
You helped me move in!
Thank you!
Take your time
and have a good look around.
[HANDA, thinking]
Huh.
They've actually got
all sorts of stuff.
Hey, candy!
My parents wouldn't let me eat
any of this stuff growing up.
I should pick something up
for the next time
Naru comes over.
You know, I hear tell
Naru's mighty fond
of those little chocolates
and hard candies.
[HANDA, thinking]
She's psychic!
Huh. Maybe I should buy in bulk.
[KINOSHITA] Save some for
the other young'uns, all right?
Ooh, wonder what this is.
Wouldn't hurt
to take a little peek.
Whoa! What the heck?
I don't get it.
Needles?
Aaah!
No, let me clean it.
It's my fault.
[DOG whimpering]
Here, let me buy this.
I'm really sorry about that.
Don't you worry none.
You cleaned the floor,
and that's more than enough.
These old bones don't like
to bend much,
so that means the world to me.
You're a mighty kind young man.
[HANDA, thinking] Maybe
your back wouldn't hurt so much
if you weren't carrying
that poodle all the time.
Nah, shouldn't say that.
Huh?
[YASU]
Pardon me, howdy do!
[HANDA]
Oh, hello!
It's hotter than
a June bride out there!
[KINOSHITA]
Well, come and rest a spell!
Work must lay a hurtin'
on that womperjawed back.
What's that you're hurting for?
Been hankering to stitch.
It's a stitch, all right.
I'm hankering to stitch.
I, uh, think
she's looking for thread.
Yes! Such a simple thing!
Goodness gracious,
with the way she was acting,
you'd think I was a'speaking
with a mouthful of mush!
I Suwannee, that old biddy
can't hear pea turkey squat.
I didn't understand
a word of that.
[YASU] Got enough wrinkles
to screw her hat on,
but she's flit
and flittering around,
with her back sore
as a risin'.
[DOG barks]
[YASU] That dog has lost
its marbles!
I almost forgot my ink!
[TAMA] Thanks for letting me
have the ink, but is that okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
I can still use an ink-stick.
Well, this really does
help me out,
especially with my deadline.
Oh yeah, you were working on
some manga project, weren't you?
I'm not a super fan or anything,
don't get the wrong idea!
There's nothing embarrassing
about having a hobby.
If you enjoy expressing yourself
with ink, that's great.
Then we have something
in common.
Sensei!
Huh?
Do you think you...
could read my manga?
I was going to submit it
to a shonen magazine,
but I wanted to get some honest
feedback from someone first.
This isn't exactly my field.
Doubt my opinion's worth much.
[TAMA]
That doesn't matter.
There's no one I'd rather
show it to, honest!
Even if you're not
a manga expert,
I respect your opinion
as an artist.
It would mean so much to me!
Can't very well say no to that,
can I?
[HANDA, gasping]
I really tried to grab you
by the first page!
Was this for a horror magazine?
[TAMA]
No, a boy's magazine.
There's not something
wrong with it, is there?
Not "wrong" per se, but you
might want to write something
more suited to your audience.
A story about friendship, maybe?
[TAMA]
Who cares about that crap?
Those tired old stories
about heroes and hard work
are dead, got it?
Blood! Guts!
The death of justice!
A dark hero
traveling a twisted path,
fighting with a rival
who could destroy him
or save his soul.
Also a female character
that gets introduced early,
then immediately
becomes useless!
Yeah, but children
read this stuff!
That's good! The next generation
needs to challenge
the foundations of this world!
That's it!
The loyal butler
that follows the hero
was the last boss all along!
Uh, yeah.
I think this story of yours
is very avant-garde.
[TAMA] Read it to the end.
Give me your honest opinion!
Even if it hurts,
I want to know
every tiny detail
that's wrong with my story.
Okay?
[HANDA]
She says that,
but there's no way
she's gonna listen!
Read these too, so you can
learn more about manga!
[HANDA, thinking]
I want to hide under my bed
where manga can't hurt me.
[sighs]
[TAMA, thinking]
Miwa was the only person
I ever told about
being a manga artist.
I wonder what came over me.
Not only did I show Sensei
my draft,
I went on and on about
all that stuff.
What am I gonna do if he tells
the rest of the town about this?
I mean, if Naru said it...
Tama makes comic books!
[TAMA] ...I could play it off,
but not Sensei!
Everyone's gonna find out
that I'm a closet otaku!
A rival who could destroy him
or save his soul!
A female character
that becomes useless!
I'm not trying
to hook the guys up, I swear!
They're gonna think
I'm a fujoshi!
Aaaah! My love for manga
is pure!
I don't go crazy with shipping
or write dirty fan-fics
or any of that stuff!
I just have a love
for the fine arts!
I will fix this.
Immediately.
[HIROSHI] Did you hear me?
I brought dinner.
[HANDA]
Yeah. Thanks.
You're not looking so hot.
What's wrong?
I was just thinking
that girls these days
have a lot of energy
and manga is scary.
Anyway, thank you,
but I need to go make some ink.
Not a great day.
Yep! I had a feeling you
wouldn't be able to buy any!
And why is that?
Everyone has calligraphy
homework over summer vacation,
so they always sell out.
No biggie.
I brought you an extra one,
just in case.
[dramatic music plays]
Oh, no, no, no!
I can't live in this place
if people think
I'm some kind of dirty fangirl.
Anything but that!
I'll tell them
those were storyboards
and that I'm into writing
and directing!
Yeah, that's it!
I didn't accidentally lend him
my secret book, did I?
It all started my first year
of middle school.
Look at this, Tama!
Your cousin was nice enough
to give you
some of her old manga to read!
[TAMA]
Yay! Neato!
[MOTHER] You really do like
your comics, don't you?
[humming]
Aaaaah! I didn't know this was
a guy-on-guy book, ew!
I thought it was an innocent
workplace drama!
[sobbing]
It's so dirty!
Now I'm traumatized!
Why?
Wow.
I kept that forbidden book
as a reminder,
not because I liked it
or anything.
I didn't put it
with my other books,
so I don't think I would lend it
by accident,
but I can't be too careful!
I want people to think I'm
a literature fan, not a pervert!
Sensei, I--
[screeching]
[HANDA]
Wow, good thing you caught me!
Probably good you brought me
something to eat, too.
Whatever, just stand up
and stop touching me!
[HANDA] When I saw that ink,
I was so happy, I got dizzy!
[HIROSHI]
That's nice and all,
but you're about to bust
your damn head open!
Dude, you tripped over
the noodles!
[TAMA]
Wait, my head's all fuzzy.
What am I even doing here?
I need to go home
and work on my manga.
Manga.
Manga, man...ga.
[shrieking]
Curse my womanly urges!
[HANDA]
Huh? What do you mean?
That work I sent
was my masterpiece!
There's no way it could get
second place!
[chirping]
This is wrong.
Sensei! Let's party!
Uh-oh.
[MIWA]
Yikes, that is one bad vibe.
Oh!
[MIWA]
Oh, gross, is that him?
You got stuff coming out of you.
What's the matter, Sensei?
Huh? What is he mumbling about
over there?
He said he got second place
in a calligraphy contest.
Oh yeah, I heard he was mailing
his work off for some big show,
but what's wrong
with second place?
[HANDA mumbling]
[NARU]
Huh?
He said first place went
to some 18-year-old punk.
[BOTH]
Huh?
All this pouting 'cause you lost
to someone younger than you?
You're that petty?
[HANDA]
It's not petty!
I worked myself sick
producing this!
Calligraphy is my entire life!
I poured my heart and soul
into that piece.
It's unbearable to think
that some rookie
could beat it that easily!
I thought moving here
would give me
a new perspective on my work,
but now I realize
there's no easy answer.
This is what I get for coming
to this damn useless island!
You take that back!
Miwa, no!
Sorry about this, Sensei.
Seems we caught you
at a bad time.
We can talk later.
[door opens, closes]
Why did you apologize to him?
He can't deal with losing,
so he just pins it on us?
[TAMA] He needs a lot
of confidence to do his work
and that's all been shattered.
Right or wrong
isn't the issue here.
Better to leave this to Naru.
Hey, Sensei?
Don't feel bad.
Miwa and Tama didn't leave
because they don't like you.
I know, though
I wouldn't blame them.
I mean, lashing out at
a couple of middle-school girls?
I can't believe I'm so pathetic.
I don't care.
Calligraphy is all I've got.
I'll lie to myself if that's
what it takes to keep going.
If I can't be number one,
then what am I fighting for?
Sensei, are you happy now?
'Cause if you're not,
let's go outside and play!
Everyone's got grocery bags
with them.
What's the event?
We're gonna catch some mochi!
You've never done it?
Boy, you city folk
don't know nothing!
It's that thing
where people toss mochi
after they build a new house,
right?
I've never done it,
but at least I know what it is.
A house?
We're gonna catch mochi
from a boat!
Get with the program!
[AKIKO] Uh-oh, Sensei,
you'd better hurry!
[KENTA'S MOTHER] They're gonna
start the toss any second now!
[HANDA]
What is this for, again?
Kenta's boat!
It's brand new!
Wait, that little kid?
[KENTA, laughing]
Naru! Up here!
[NARU] Wow, Kenta,
your boat is awesome!
[KENTA] Yeah, I know!
It's called the "Kenmaru"!
"Kenmaru"?
I know,
normally you'd name the boat
after the eldest sister
in the family.
Unfortunately, we don't
have any daughters.
I'll toss you a whole bunch
so get ready!
Sensei! Over here!
[KENTA]
Dang it!
Look at me, Naru,
I got mochiiii!
What's wrong with you?
[KENTA] I didn't mean to!
[KENTA'S MOTHER] Never mind!
Just scoop them out!
[KENTA whimpering]
[MIWA]
Well, look who showed up!
Feeling a bit better now,
I take it?
Hiroshi came to play, too!
[HIROSHI] I got dragged here.
I should be studying.
[MIWA] Like you dragged that
baseball glove of yours here.
[HIROSHI] If I'm gonna do it,
I might as well do it right!
[MIWA] Ooh!
Them's fightin' words, partner!
Listen.
About before.
I, uh...
What?
I know you artist-types
are snippy.
Anyway, I'm over it now.
I'd focus on grabbing that
mochi, if I were you.
Now I'll warn you, there are
two mochi-grabbing heavyweights
you'll need to steer clear of.
That's really a thing?
The first one is Yasu.
She's super old, so she's
done this like a billion times
and she always grabs
a whole bunch.
The other one is Panchi.
She'll knock the mochi clean
out of your hand,
so it's best
to leave her alone.
All right, everybody, let's
give it our best out there!
You too!
[HANDA] What, the hand thing?
I don't really--
[KENTA'S FATHER]
Here goes! You ready?
[MIWA]
Let's make some mochi magic!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[HANDA]
Yeah.
Grab some mochi!
[cheering]
[HANDA]
Okay, uh. Don't think.
Just go for it!
Wow, that is harsh.
Damn it, one more try!
All right!
Now let's--
[thud]
Sorry, didn't see you there.
[HANDA, feebly]
That was my mochi.
Why?
Why must the gods test me so?
Tama?
C'mon, Sensei, I know you've got
a lot of drive.
Let's see some of that here.
[HANDA] Drive, huh?
I sure don't feel like it.
Huh. I guess this isn't
so different than calligraphy.
In other words,
no matter how much I try,
I still can't get what I want.
If I'm going to just make
a fool out of myself,
maybe it's better
to just stop trying.
That goes for mochi
and calligraphy.
Uggh!
Huh?
[snarls]
Panchi. It figures!
[YASU]
Hey there, Sensei. Any luck?
Uh, no.
Maybe this just ain't
your cup of tea, then.
Judging by the results,
I'd have to agree.
I'm useless.
If you keep lookin' up
the whole time,
you'll miss half the show!
Just sit still a spell
and you might see
there's all sorts of goodies
lyin' on the ground for you.
Not everybody can fly,
but you'll find your way
if you keep lookin'.
[HANDA]
The ground, huh?
[YASU] Time's a-wastin'!
Give it your best out there!
Wait a sec!
What if I try everything
and it's still not enough?
Like if someone comes along
who's better than me
and I can't beat them
no matter what?
[YASU]
Hmm?
Um, forget I said that.
When that happens,
the answer is simple.
You say "be my guest, friend."
Ain't nobody need every mochi
in the world
and ain't nobody deserve
to take 'em all, neither.
Sometimes you give one
and you find
a bigger one for yourself
somewhere else.
[YASU chuckles]
That seems to work out fine
for me!
[NARU]
Sensei!
Better hurry, or there won't be
any left for you!
Right!
I'm on it!
All right, let's go!
[snarls]
Please, be my guest.
Was this the right thing to do?
[NARU] How many did you get,
Sensei?
Some things you don't ask.
I mean, take a good guess.
[NARU, laughing] I got a whole
28 of 'em, so I'm awesome!
[MIWA] And a full-grown man
got zero.
[HANDA] Nuh-uh! I got one
and gave it to Panchi,
'cause she wanted it more!
[MIWA]
You liar.
[ALL]
Huh?
What the heck is that?
Red bean soup?
It's red bean and mochi soup.
Panchi likes
the thrill of the fight,
but when it's over with,
she always shares
whatever she catches
with everyone.
Some people can't come and some
don't have a knack for it,
but we all win this way.
[MIWA] Yeah, whatever.
I'm winning for real next time.
[TAMA] Ew, gross!
Why's my mochi wet?
[NARU] 'Cause Kenta
dropped it in the water. Duh!
[MIWA]
Aw, I got one too!
[HANDA]
I know I made a big stink.
But in the end,
I had fun today.
Thank you, guys.
[NARU giggles]
See?
♪ You held out a small hand ♪
♪ Smiling, like to you ♪
♪ It was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something ♪
♪ I cannot
do ♪
♪ You touched my hand
without thinking ♪
♪ But it was nice for me ♪
♪ Oh-whoa-oh ♪
♪ All the time
that we believed ♪
♪ That the world's
in our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand ♪
♪ Your warm hand. ♪
[KAZUYUKI] Lookin' to nab
some crayfish too, huh?
[NARU]
Mr. Sakamoto!
[HANDA] It weirds me out
every time that he's a teacher.
You gonna cook up some crayfish
for dinner tonight?
What, are you kidding?
These are bait for bigger stuff.
Aaaah!
What is wrong with you?
The poor crayfish deserve
better than that!
Naru, if we use them as bait,
we can catch beakfish.
Whoa.
They're yummy, huh?
So no more throwing buckets,
okay?
Yeah! Beakfish!
So how do you make the crayfish
into bait, anyway?
Oh. Easy.
You just yank their
little claw off, like this.
Aaaah!
[KAZUYUKI]
Dang it, not again!