Sensei!
I'm here to play!
It's locked?
Sensei!
Huh?
He's gone.
[car horns honking]
[phone ringing]
[door opens]
Hmm?
Hey, you're early.
You got the piece
I sent you, right?
Yeah a while back,
got it right here.
It really catches your eye,
thanks to how big it is.
Yeah.
Wait, are you saying it wouldn't
look good if it was small?
Would you chill?
Kawafuji's an art dealer,
not an artist.
He's just praising its size
because it'll grab people's
attention and sell faster,
not because that's the only
thing praiseworthy about it.
[KAWAFUJI] He's been back five
seconds and this already?
Pull it together,
will you?
The Director will be here
any minute now.
[screams]
Could you possibly
get me
a glass of water, please?
You're not sick, are you?
What's that face?
[HANDA sighs]
What am I even supposed
to say to him, you know?
What do you mean "what"?
Just apologize.
You came back here
'cause he said
he would forgive you, right?
If you're sorry, then tell him
how you feel and that's it.
I did buy these things.
They're souvenir
cell phone straps.
What, do you think he's a high
school girl or something?
Man, and it's ugly, too.
If you keep drinking like this
you are so gonna pee your pants.
What am I gonna do if the
Director doesn't like my piece?
I mean, the exhibit
hasn't even started yet,
and I'll already be done for.
You know any good holes
to die in?
I doubt he'll have
anything bad to say.
Besides, you sent this over
'cause you're confident
in it, right?
Can you tell me what
you think of it? Be honest.
Would you have known
it was something I wrote?
Hmm...
I honestly wasn't thinking
of it that way.
Frankly, I'm not exactly sure
how to answer that.
But the piece is bold
and it draws your attention.
I think it's good.
I guess
I wouldn't have expected this
from your previous style,
though.
--That's the problem!
--Uh-huh?
I don't write this kind of
calligraphy, it's too good!
Don't you see?
What you're saying
is crazy, even for you.
How can I word this?
It just doesn't feel right!
It's almost--
[speed talking]
So what you're saying is,
it was just a fluke.
Uh, it's a little more
complicated than that!
But you're right.
I used Mother Nature
as inspiration,
but I feel like
she deserves all the credit
and anyone
could've done what I did.
Even if that were true,
it's still your work.
Say it was an experiment,
and get back to something
you're more comfortable
with next time around.
Can't question yourself
for trying a new style.
It's just one piece.
If all I do is stay comfortable,
I'll never find my own style.
[sighs]
A farmer can go fishing
and get lucky,
but even if he catches
a hisanio on his first try,
that doesn't make him
a fisherman!
I want to find a special seed
and care for it
until it grows into a flower
that only I can grow
and no one's ever seen before!
Gah! I don't care
about being number one.
I want to be the only one!
Wait, seriously?
'Cause I know you
and you'll throw a fit
if you're second place.
[DIRECTOR laughs]
"One lucky catch doesn't make
a farmer into a fisherman."
That's
a clever perspective, Handa.
I like it.
--[HANDA screams]
--Oh, Director.
--[door closes]
--No matter the profession,
every artist must pay their dues
before they become a master.
I'm sorry I didn't greet you
at the door.
No. I just came
to say hello to Handa.
There's no need
to be formal.
So? Have you been well
in your absence?
Yes, sir!
Very well, sir!
[DIRECTOR] It's fine.
You don't have to be nervous.
You certainly spoke
your mind to me before.
That's only because I wasn't
using my head before, sir!
[HANDA thinking]
Would you calm the hell down?
You're here to ask
for forgiveness.
Don't blow it!
A cane?
I didn't know the Director
had a bad back.
Oh, thank you, Handa.
Of course.
[HANDA thinking] It doesn't
matter how angry I was.
How could I have punched
a man like this?
I'm the scum of the earth.
[HANDA]
I'm truly sorry.
From the bottom of my heart.
I should have apologized sooner.
There's no excuse for my violent
behavior and there's no excuse
for only coming here after
I was told you'd forgive me.
There's nothing
I can say for myself.
I'm deeply sorry.
Director, he--
In all honesty,
I didn't plan on forgiving you.
I just wanted
to drag you back here.
If you were so intent
on running and hiding,
I would have
to put you in your place.
[DIRECTOR] But it seems
that isn't necessary.
Now, with that said.
So long as you can keep
that temper of yours in check,
I forgive you.
--[HANDA groans]
--[DIRECTOR] Hm?
--Hey...
--Just give me a minute.
I don't know what I would've
done if you didn't forgive me.
I can move on.
Thank you so much.
[chuckles]
Good for you, little buddy,
now why don't you give him
the cell phone strap?
That is not even remotely
appropriate at this moment.
One other thing,
while I'm here...
--Yes, sir!
--I'd like to take
a closer look
at your latest piece.
Would you mind lending me
a hand, please?
Uh, of course!
So then this is the new face
of your calligraphy, is it?
-Yes.
-Hmm.
This particular piece is,
not really-- Uhh.
Handa...
Ah!
This work of yours...
[screams]
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
--I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
--[DIRECTOR] How unfortunate.
I see you're
as impulsive as ever.
[KAWAFUJI thinking]
Don't laugh. Don't laugh.
Don't laugh.
This piece is just a trial!
Something I wrote
as an experiment!
My, uh, actual entry
is still back on the island.
I didn't bring it with me.
--I see.
--[KAWAFUJI laughing]
I suppose
it was selfish of me to expect
to see your work so close
to the exhibit's premiere.
No!
It's not your fault.
I'm just sorry you had to look
at this garbage, that's all!
Hey. Handa.
Understood.
Then strictly evaluating it
as an experiment,
allow me to say a few things.
Frankly, I've never seen
anything like this before.
It's very interesting.
Very exciting.
The concept seems childlike
at first,
and yet I can almost see
the night sky
splashed across the canvas.
The stars feel like a light
that can only be seen
from the darkness,
as if they were painted
from a very lonely place.
I'm not this exhibition's
only judge, but personally,
I think this is worthy
of a grand prize.
[gasps]
Thank you very much, sir!
You've certainly got
my hopes up now!
If this is just a trial,
I'll be thrilled
to see what
you've cooked up for Narukain.
--[KAWAFUJI laughing]
--This has turned into
a surprisingly
delightful day.
Well,
I'll see you again soon.
Oh, just a second, sir,
I'll call a taxi for you.
[door opens, closes]
Just kill me already.
[KAWAFUJI]
You're waiting outside?
Yes.
I don't need a taxi.
--My ride is already here.
--Oh.
[KAWAFUJI]
All right, then.
Thank you for stopping by!
[car engine starts]
[KAWAFUJI]
Someone drove him here?
Wait.
I know that car.
I'm quite pleased.
It seems that sending Seishu
to the island was
the right choice after all.
[SEIMEI] He still has
a lot of growing left to do.
--[engine stalls]
--[DIRECTOR] What happened?
[SEIMEI]
I'm sorry, the engine stalled.
I'm bad with a stick shift
and the incline
is giving me trouble.
[DIRECTOR sighs]
Seishu's like me.
We're both quite awkward.
--[engine starts, stalls]
--[DIRECTOR] Stop!
Stop, you're scaring me!
Get this!
Your dad was waiting outside
the whole time!
What the hell?
[HANDA]
Send me back to the island.
[KAWAFUJI]
Uh, hello!
Oh, it's Kawafuji.
I haven't seen you in ages!
Handa, I'm coming in.
[groaning]
You're late.
Nope.
Come back, Kawafujiiii!
[KAWAFUJI]
Let me guess.
You weren't able to bust out
another masterpiece.
--Nope.
--I'm almost afraid to ask,
but did you give yourself
a Naru ponytail for inspiration?
Uh-huh.
It was not as effective
as I'd hoped it would be.
The deadline for
the exhibit is tomorrow.
You might want to use
your time more wisely.
If you want to help, then
tell me something I don't know.
On a positive note,
I did make
another "stars" piece,
like before.
Yeah? You did?
Then stop acting like a weirdo
and show me already!
If the Director's right,
you might be sitting
on a grand prize!
You're sure you didn't
make this back in grade school?
I knew you'd say that!
[crying]
I tried and tried
but I can't write like before!
Even when I look at the stars,
it doesn't work,
'cause the city lights
ruin the mood!
I can't do it!
I can't! I can't!
It's kinda hard to believe
the same person made this.
I'm just sensitive, okay?
I'm influenced
by my environment.
Inspiration
isn't easy to come by.
Well, now you're back home.
You've made plenty
of winning entries
in this exact environment
before, right?
It doesn't have
to be something fancy.
Just do what you always do.
It'll be fine.
Easy for you to say!
If I could just crap out
a masterpiece,
I wouldn't have
called someone like you!
Then who would you call?
I'm the only friend you've got.
I give up,
there's nothing I can do.
Wait!
I know exactly
how you can help me.
[KAWAFUJI]
Huh? Uh... Huh?
[HANDA laughing maniacally]
[KAWAFUJI screams]
Sei, I brought some tea
for you and your friends!
[KANZAKI] I'm failing to see
the logic here.
If you don't shut your mouth,
I'm gonna have to gag you!
I forgot,
who am I supposed to be?
Do I have to be a kid?
Can't I be
someone cool instead?
Just follow my orders, damn it!
You're not
the one who talks, okay?
You only get to cry!
He's into bondage?!
Oh, you must be
Sensei's mother!
--Thanks for having us!
--Ah! Mom!
Sei, sweetie,
what are you doing over there
with your friends?
This is not what it looks like,
it's for my work!
Sensei needed us to role play
as little girls for him!
He said nothing else
would do the trick!
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
He was such a good child, too.
Maybe a little grumpy wumpy
here and there,
but in his heart,
he was a real sweetie pie.
But now he's just
some pervy bad boy!
My cutie patootie is dead!
Dead! And it's all
that awful island's fault!
[crying]
[HANDA]
Mom, wait!
Aw, jeez.
Are you all right?
No, this is terrible,
but all the insanity
is reminding me of the island.
Just 'cause you made
one good piece on the island
doesn't mean everything
it touches turns to gold.
I mean, unless you just
wanna tie me up that badly.
[HANDA] No thank you,
and get out of my bed!
This island calligraphy thing
is unsustainable.
Just move back to Tokyo already
and do what you do best.
[HANDA] Stop searching
under my mattress!
A dirty book!
Ha! I knew it!
--Hey!
--For real?
[HANDA]
My precious!
[sighs] I don't feel like
submitting a piece
if Sensei
isn't gonna do it too.
Not like the prize money's
that great in the first place,
and what do I care if some old
fogeys like my work anyway?
Maybe I should just make
a bunch of new pieces
and do my own show.
You do what you want,
but I'm staking
my entire career
on this exhibit.
Professionally, maybe
it's not that big of a deal.
But as an artist,
if I want to be reborn,
then this is my first step.
I have to take it.
That is so cool.
Damn it,
are you recording me?
My famous quotes,
they're all gone!
Why did you
even bring him here?
'Cause I figured me in a dinky
ponytail wouldn't do the trick.
Well, he's pissing me off!
Hm?
You just
needed some patience.
But who needs us when you can
say hello to the real thing?
--[phone vibrating]
--[KAWAFUJI chuckles]
You never seen
a phone before?
For me?
[NARU on phone]
Hello?
[TAMA on phone]
Did they finally pick up?
--It's Naru!
--[HIRO] Is Sensei there too?
Sensei?
--[ALL] Sensei!
--[KENTA] Sensei, what's up?
C'mon! Give it to me!
But wait, I don't understand.
Ah! He's on!
[screams]
Hey, it's Miwa.
How you holding up over there?
Kawafuji called
and said you were lonely.
So, we all got together
to try and cheer you up.
[MIWA] Hey, you little dork,
I was talking!
[AKKI] We're all crammed in
the store, so it's a bit noisy.
[TAMA]
Sensei, are you okay?
Hiroshi's here with us too!
You should be happy.
He seems
really worried about you!
Okay.
Give me the phone.
Tch!
Hey, punk!
You coulda said something
to us before you left!
You had everyone flipping out!
[NARU]
My turn! Fork it over!
I'm sorry.
I was just--
Sensei!
You holdin' up over there?
[ALL scream]
[MIWA] I already
asked him that! Shut up!
[MIWA]
Sit in the corner!
Go ahead,
tell me how awesome I am.
Good to have a friend.
[MIWA]
Okay, gimme the phone back.
[TAMA] Oww!
You're stomping on my foot!
--[TAMA] Stop jumping!
--Yeah. Thank you.
[ALL] Sensei!
You holdin' up over there?
[KAWAFUJI thinking]
He actually thanked me.
I'm gonna go deaf,
just talk one at a time!
Anyway, you're
coming back here soon, right?
You better hurry!
If you take too long,
we're gonna punish you
and it won't be pretty!
Yeah, okay.
[AKKI]
Hey, it's Akki.
Hey! What's up, buddy?
I hope
you're not doing too bad.
We heard you were pretty
stressed out about work.
Yeah, but thank you for asking
about my emotional well being
instead of getting frustrated
with me like everyone else.
[HANDA sighs]
I think I'll be fine
if I can just remember
my times on the island.
A little inspiration
is all I need.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
[KAWAFUJI thinking] What, did
he just need a child to talk to?
Well, I wouldn't say
I'm in a slump exactly.
It's more like
an emotional barrier.
[HINA]
That sounds real confusing.
Tell me when you change!
I don't know
who I'm talking to!
[KAWAFUJI] He's back
to the old routine.
[KANZAKI]
Seems happy, though.
--[NARU] Sensei?
--Naru?
[NARU]
Uh-huh.
You know, it sure is boring
'round here without you.
I know I lost my ticket,
but there's still a bunch
of stuff I wanna do together.
Everyone wants you back.
We'll have fun
just like before!
[inhales]
[ALL]
So come home real soon!
[ALL laughing]
Think you can
get back to it now?
Uh-huh.
[gasps]
Wait a sec!
What's up? You looking
for something
you brought from the island?
Yeah, it was the last piece
I worked on there.
Don't know if I remembered
to pack it or not, though.
C'mon, c'mon.
Perfect.
Hmm? A name list?
--[HANDA] Ink.
--What?
Now! Bring me
all the ink you've got!
Kanzaki! Go buy me
some paper for practice!
[KANZAKI] Why me?
Ugh, okay, jeez!
[panting]
Finally making his move,
I see.
I hope he isn't
going to do anything strange.
If you recall,
I was against him leaving.
I don't ever want him
to go back to that crazy island!
Don't say that to me,
convince him yourself.
You are horrible!
You know he can't wait
to go back there!
He's going to come back
all wrong in the head
and it'll be your fault,
you awful man!
Perhaps we failed to prepare him
for the world in some ways,
but we certainly did our best
in raising him.
Still, we're not the ones to
determine our son's potential.
However much we fear for him,
our job is done.
If going out into the world
will make him grow,
all we can do is watch.
[HANDA'S MOTHER]
I see.
The path to becoming
a man is cruel.
Eh! The real Seimei Handa!
He is so cool!
--Cut it out.
--Hey.
[HANDA]
Hey, Kawafuji, get up.
I dozed off,
your bed is the devil.
I'm finished.
It's my greatest masterpiece.
[BOTH gasp]
Told you.
This is it.
I've never done anything
like it before.
So what's the title?
[chuckles]
Stone Wall.
♪ You held out
your small hand ♪
♪ Smiling like to you ♪
♪ It was so natural ♪
♪ It may have no meaning ♪
♪ But it is something
I cannot do ♪
♪ You touched my hand
without thinking ♪
♪ But that was nice
for me ♪
♪ All the time we believed ♪
♪ That the world was
in our hands ♪
♪ We were wrong ♪
♪ Maybe it wasn't ♪
♪ 'Cause you're holding
my hand now ♪
♪ Every moment ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I can't believe ♪
♪ When I'm holding
your warm hand. ♪
[FEMALE STUDENT 1]
They posted
the summer assignments
in the hallway.
Think you won
an award this time?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
I doubt it, but let's go see!
It's finally time.
They won't even know
what hit 'em.
Heh. This'll be good.
With our training, we'll get
the gold award for sure.
'Course we will!
And Sensei will be so proud!
We'll bring back
a double gold
and knock
his pretty little socks off!
Sensei's lucky
to have students like us!
We'll be taking
his place someday!
[BOTH]
Yay!
Catch you later, Miwa.
Gotta run
to the bathroom real fast.
[groaning]
[MIWA]
Is Tama better than me?
[TAMA] C'mon, Miwa, cheer up.
It's not a big deal.
[MIWA] I can never show my face
to Sensei again. It's over.
[TAMA]
The silver award is nothing
to be ashamed of!
It's second place!
I poured my heart and soul
into that calligraphy!
It's Sensei!