[GRAY] If you have any
strength left to gather,
then you should use it to
carry the girl to safety.
What for? See all that blood?
No one lives through that!
What's the point in tryin' to
save somebody who's dead?
[GRAY]
Rachel Gardner is still alive.
[gasps]
[GRAY] If you leave at once,
then her life will be saved.
Listen carefully.
Make haste, and you will see.
But you must go immediately!
You'll understand in due time!
Die, Zack... Just die!
[DANNY yells]
[DANNY groans]
[GRAY] Who could have
imagined that things
would turn out this way?
[DANNY gasps]
Reverend Gray. Why?
I admit, I was self‐serving.
And I know I was supposed
to do as you told me.
But still, none of the things
that I did were wrong!
Even if it was for myself,
I helped you!
My efforts to thwart Rachel and
Zack were protecting the rules
of this building from being
broken, so it was your gain!
It's fair to say your endeavors
allowed me to see something
of profound interest
to my study.
At the start, I was
convinced Isaac Foster
was a being that possessed
invisible wings.
But now, after all
that's happened,
those wings are entirely
imperceptible to me.
[DANNY]
Invisible wings?
Did you actually believe Zack
was some kind of angel?
Yes, for a while, I did.
Because he thought
only of killing.
To me, that made
him seem so pure.
But recently. Isaac learned to
wield his blade for the benefit
of someone besides himself.
As a result, his weapon
was destroyed,
and he fell from heaven's
ranks to become human.
No. Perhaps I should say
he was human all along.
What's more, the one who opened
my eyes to that reality
was Rachel Gardner,
the young girl whom I had
denounced as a witch.
Her transformation was as
striking as it was confusing.
How could one so self‐serving
and rife with contradiction
change so much?
But looking back,
it was I who tried to stamp
out Isaac's humanity.
The blame is all mine.
[DANNY] If that's how you feel,
then why did you shoot me?
I suppose, it was
my vain attempt
to atone for what I've done.
Now, my observation and
experiments are complete.
As is my responsibility
to stand in place of God.
After all this, it ends here?
And Danny, you are the one
who brought me Rachel.
But although you were
meant to steal her soul,
your true intention was
helping her gain one.
Admit it, everything you did
for her was part of your attempt
to become her God, was it not?
[DANNY gasps]
[GRAY] But it was no use,
because you are not God.
Doctor, you must have
been aware of that, so‐‐
[DANNY] Without becoming
God in Rachel's eyes,
I'd have had nothing!
When I first gazed into
those perfect works of art,
I knew they belonged to
someone who'd lost all hope
and would never
love another soul.
So I wanted to give them
my love for eternity.
I thought my life was over.
Then, those peepers gave me
a reason to keep living!
I felt like I could
do anything at all!
B‐But. I can't love
them any longer.
If Rachel isn't alone anymore,
There's no one left who'll
accept the ugly thing that I am.
[GRAY] Then, you mean, that by
offering your devotion to her,
you were hoping you could
eventually earn her love
in return, is that correct?
Danny, despite everything,
you and I are nothing
but human beings.
[DANNY gasps]
That's all? No more?
[GRAY] No one who ever
set foot in this building
was anything but human.
Humans are the ones who
create God, and angels,
and the differences between.
In fact, Rachel Gardner
may have been the
greatest example of all.
The only entity who ever
damned anyone wasn't God...
...but mankind.
Reverend Gray.
The people in here.
What was it that you
saw in all of them?
[GRAY] Sadly, what I
observed was no different
than what I'd always
seen in humans.
They were all so ugly.
So selfish. So lost.
Yet so beautiful.
Such simple truths.
Of course, as one
of my "angels",
the same thing is true of you.
But somehow, even though
you were here longer
than any of the rest,
I didn't see it 'til now.
Forgive me.
I think it's obvious that
this is the end for me.
Thank you, but saying
I'm beautiful doesn't do
much good now, y'know?
[gasps]
Mother!
[ZACK grunts]
Hang in there,
Ray. We're almost out.
[ZACK]
Don't you die now!
[ZACK grunts]
[SMALL CROWD mutters]
Hey, look, we made it out.
[ZACK] He said if we escaped,
you'd be saved.
What did that mean?
What do I do now?
Ray! Would you please just
wake up already? Come on!
[ZACK growls]
I'm beggin' ya.
Please open your eyes! Ray!
[sirens]
Wait, when he said that,
he meant the cops were here?
You're kiddin' me!
We have you surrounded, now put
the girl down immediately!
Don't bother trying
to run for it!
Just set her on the ground
slowly and get on your knees
with your hands behind
your head! Hurry up!
[ZACK] Well, this is it, Ray.
But don't forget what I said.
One day. I promise
I'm gonna kill ya.
[inaudible]
[INVESTIGATORS, POLICE murmur]
[FEMALE REPORTER A] As for the
young girl found at the scene,
investigators have identified
her as Rachel Gardner.
Who, after her parents' death,
had recently been
reported missing.
One of the suspects in the
explosion case is Isaac Foster.
In fact, reports say
he's already connected
to several crimes.
[FEMALE REPORTER B] Excuse me,
sir. Has Isaac Foster confessed?
He's not the one responsible
for the explosion.
Actually, he denies kidnapping
Rachel Gardner, and he says
that he has no connection to
the murder of her parents.
[FEMALE REPORTER B] Has he
also denied involvement
in other crimes?
No, he actually owned up to
several without any trouble.
"Nothin' I hate more than
a lie," he kept saying.
[FEMALE REPORTER B] Are you
sure you can believe him?
[MALE INVESTIGATOR A]
Hm... Well, I can say that I
personally think he's
telling the truth.
Perhaps. Eh, I thought
of something,
but it was ridiculous.
Forget about it.
There's no way Isaac
Foster's anything but
a twisted serial killer.
[FEMALE REPORTER B]
One more question.
Have you found out how he's
connected to the girl?
We keep asking
him about her,
but all he tells
us is, "I dunno."
As a matter of fact, when it
came to Rachel Gardner,
he started asking
us some questions.
He wanted to know if she
was still alive or not.
But then, for some reason,
when we told him she was,
all he had to say was "okay."
[FEMALE REPORTER A] Doctor,
what was your first impression
of Rachel Gardner?
She seemed to be a sweet,
beautiful little girl,
but she had such a
hopeless look on her face.
I guess I can't blame
her for that, though.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
I see.
And has she told you anything
pertaining to this case?
Not yet. She keeps saying
she doesn't know any details.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
What sort of counseling
are you giving her, then?
I want to restore
her peace of mind.
That's the main goal here.
However, she doesn't
give many facial cues,
and she seems to have
a difficult time
expressing her feelings.
It's very strange.
All she wants to do is find
out more about that murderer.
You're right, perhaps it
could be that she can't get
the murderer out of her mind?
[DOC] That's my theory, yes.
So, in light of all that,
I've made a serious effort
to shield her from updates
regarding the case.
She's obviously
frightened of him,
so it's been good for her.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
Well, Doctor,
I hope she'll make
a speedy recovery.
I'll keep doing my best to help
her heal from this trauma.
Good morning, Rachel.
Are you awake yet?
[DOC]
Did you sleep alright?
Yes, ma'am.
[DOC] We'll do your counseling
session in the evening today.
[DOC]
It's so nice out.
After your breakfast,
what do you say you and
I go for a little walk?
[RACHEL]
Okay.
[DOC sighs]
Quiet places like this
are always so relaxing,
don't you agree?
Uh‐huh.
[DOC] Actually, could you wait
here for a moment, please?
[MALE REPORTER A] The suspect in
these serial murders and the man
found at the scene was Isaac
Foster, who's since been take‐‐
[DOC] Has anything been
making you feel uneasy lately?
I don't think so.
[DOC] Would you say that
you've been sleeping well?
Yes.
[DOC] Good. Maybe we should
stop here for the day, then.
I hope that's okay. My last
session ran a bit too long.
So, sorry for the late start.
I'll walk you to your room.
I can go by myself.
You're supposed to be
supervised at all times.
I do apologize.
My, look how pretty the sky is.
[DOC]
It's a beautiful night.
[RACHEL]
A beautiful night?
[DOC] Yes, and the
best way to enjoy it
is by going to bed early.
I'm sure you'll have
sweet dreams.
[DOC]
Shall we, then?
Rachel, dear.
You're not afraid, are you?
[DOC] Your condition's improved
a lot since you first got here.
It's like you're a completely
different girl than the one
who always used to ask about
that killer they found you with.
Which is why... I'm going
to tell you something
that you really aren't
supposed to know about.
Perhaps it'll ease your mind.
You see, the murderer...
They sentenced him to death.
[RACHEL]
Oh... really?
[DOC]
Yes. I'm sure it's a shock,
but hopefully now you'll
be able to sleep soundly.
[RACHEL]
Right.
[DOC]
Let's get you to bed.
Go straight to sleep, okay?
You need rest.
[RACHEL] The truth was, I hadn't
slept well the entire time.
[RACHEL]
I couldn't calm down.
And I knew that night
was no different.
[RACHEL] But still, there was
nothing left for me to do
but close my eyes.
[FEMALE A screams]
[ZACK grunts]
‐‐[RACHEL gasps]
‐‐[ZACK] I shoulda known.
After all that,
you're still wearin' that
boring ol' face o' yours.
[RACHEL]
Zack... How?
How? What do you mean how?
Aren't you...
supposed to be in prison?
Yeah, well obviously I
decided to change my plans!
[RACHEL gasps]
But, Zack.
When I last saw you, I said
that I would... carry our vow!
Yeah, that doesn't
quite cut it for me.
Besides. Isn't a promise
made between two people?
Wait... I'm not sure I get it.
Are you still gonna
kill me or not?
[ZACK] What do you think?
You know me.
When I want somethin', I make
damn sure that I get it.
We gotta hurry, though. I don't
have a lotta time here.
And you better not have
forgotten your end o' the deal.
[RACHEL sighs] Of course not,
Zack. I didn't forget.
I could never forget!
We promised, didn't we?
You and me, right?
No matter what gets in our way!
[ZACK]
Hell yeah! So, are you ready?
[RACHEL]
Yes!
It's time now.
So if you would...
Kill me, please.
[ZACK] If that's what you want,
stop cryin' and smile.