[GRAY] Are you denying
that you were the one
who acted selfishly in all this?
Eddie's statement
illustrated it perfectly.
He claims you live
according to your own desires
without any regard for others.
That's a lie.
Not to mention Catherine.
You got her to surrender
to your spell,
like the foul witch you are.
What a shame to see such
a proud woman reduced to that.
-Stop it!
-And now for the verdict.
Rachel Gardner
is found guilty of sorcery.
I sentence her
to be burned alive!
You're wrong!
Witch, I compel thee,
bathe in cleansing flame
and be made pure.
Stop calling me a witch.
Who would believe the words
of a wicked sorceress
accused of such heinous crimes?
It's true.
You continue to stand
by that claim after hearing
all their testimonies?
Come now. Have you no shame?
Why, you have destroyed
the very hearts of angels.
You lied to them,
toyed with them,
and then your soul
consumed them.
What you did was inhuman.
Angels? But I thought...
[GRAY] I can only assume
that you intend
to subject poor Isaac Foster
to the same fate.
No, I don't. I couldn't.
I doubt that.
You'll sacrifice him
to serve your own purposes.
No.
Admit it, Rachel Gardner,
you are a witch
of the most profane kind.
Now you must confess to it
and resign yourself
to your fiery judgment!
May God have mercy on your soul.
I'm not a witch. I can't be.
The God I know never said
what I did makes me a witch.
And there is nothing like that
in the Bible, either.
Well, there's a very clear
explanation for that, child.
For, you see,
this ridiculous God you've been
speaking of doesn't exist.
What? But you've been using
God's name this whole time.
Yes. I'm referring
to the God I worship,
which is quite different
from yours.
In this place, I stand
in the position of God.
The real deity here,
Miss Gardner,
is my own self,
above any other!
[shuddering]
I pull the strings that connect
all the souls in this building.
There is a god in this world,
and he's standing
before your very eyes.
You're really bold enough
to call yourself God?
I am the omnipotent,
all-knowing master of this place
and everyone in it.
Wouldn't you say
that's what God is?
I couldn't say.
I don't think you're a god.
But I guess... I don't know.
I understand your dilemma.
The existence of God
requires a believing heart.
And you, Miss Gardner,
despite your claims,
you never had a believing heart
to begin with.
I believe! I do!
[RACHEL]
God doesn't exist? No.
That isn't true.
I can't accept it. I won't.
And now this priest is trying
to say that he's the real God,
but I know he's wrong.
I don't want to be killed
at the hands of this
terrible man.
But... how can I escape?
Kill me.
♪
[gasps]
Huh?
[pants]
[RACHEL]
What's happening?
[groans]
[gasps]
♪
-[hissing]
-[groans]
[groaning]
[RACHEL]
It's hot.
I'm burning up,
and yet, I'm cold, too.
Something inside me
feels like it's frozen.
What is this?
I don't understand
what's going on.
Wait, I know. It's my fault.
I had something precious,
and I ruined it.
Even though Zack was
always there for me,
every step of the way,
I let him get hurt.
Zack, wait!
Don't go. I'll remember now.
[moans softly]
[gasps]
This is Zack's knife.
[groans]
Ah. I see.
There is a God.
He's right here with me.
[GRAY gasps]
Why have you awakened?
Everything on this floor's
an illusion.
I understand that now.
Because thanks to my God,
I finally opened my eyes.
[sighs]
Then it appears I have failed
to purify the witch.
I'm not a witch, I told you.
I didn't make an unholy pact.
Just a promise.
Besides, my God was the one
who made the agreement with me.
Hmm.
Ah, I see.
That's how you justify it.
Do you mean to tell me
that even if it turns out
you were wrong,
even if you discover
that everything you believe,
everything that makes you
who you are is a lie,
you'll still feel the same?
Look.
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
I don't have time for this.
Just give me the medicine.
[scoffs]
Spoken like the self-serving
witch that you are.
Very well, come along.
[GRAY] You'll find
the medicine in here.
[RACHEL]
Open it.
[GRAY]
Aren't you capable of that?
[RACHEL]
I have no reason to trust you.
[scoffs]
Indeed.
These are the drugs
that belong to Danny.
Medicines to disinfect,
reduce pain,
and even stop bleeding.
Surely something here
will help with Zack's recovery.
Feel free to take
as many as you see fit.
Will you be
returning to him now?
I take it you're
going to let me live.
Why?
You said before that you'd
found your God, did you not?
The existence
of multiple deities
is a guaranteed invitation
for chaos.
Not only that,
but you've made it clear
you have no concept
of human compassion.
It's simple.
You're not getting in my way.
If you interfered,
then I would kill you.
But, no.
I'll leave you be.
You're useless now.
[scoffs]
Very well.
Then, at least allow me
to impart a small warning.
The Lord God is righteous.
He detests liars, as well as
those whose hands are unclean.
But then again,
your God may be different.
Perhaps he'll show mercy,
or perhaps he won't.
♪
[panting]
I'm here.
[groaning]
You're still breathing.
Thank goodness.
♪
[RACHEL gasps]
What are all these burns?
-[ZACK groaning]
-[gasps]
Hey, Zack, are you awake?
[weakly]
Huh? What's this about?
Back off.
I brought some medicine for you.
Oh, yeah.
You're still alive, huh?
-[RACHEL] Yeah.
-[ZACK] Shut up, I can see that.
[sighs]
So, uh, how'd you manage to snag
the medicine without dyin'?
The priest who watches
over this floor gave it to me.
The priest?
-Oh, yeah, him.
-Wait, try not to move.
I'm sewing you up.
Sewing?
Are you outta your damn mind?
You need stitches.
Let me fix you.
I'm really good at that.
Slow down. I can do it myself.
Are you sure?
Can you sew it up nice and neat?
I'm not a freakin' shirt.
No, Zack. It should be me.
I wanna help you.
I swear I'll do a good job.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Fine, then, go ahead.
But don't blame me
if you get all grossed out.
I can handle it.
[ZACK]
Damn, Ray.
What the hell are you, anyway?
[RACHEL]
I'm sorry?
[ZACK]
You're about to sew a guy's guts
back together like it's nothin'.
But, hey, somehow your weak ass
made it back with drugs
and not a scratch on ya.
So, props for that.
Hmm.
You know, you really don't have
to do any of this crap.
Listen, Ray.
Just tell me honestly.
You gotta have some reason
for helpin' me out, don't ya?
It's so sharp.
This will be easy.
You seriously think that you can
just ignore my question?!
Answer, dammit.
Okay.
I wanna save you
‘cause you are my God, Zack.
Whoa! What the hell's
your problem?
That's not somethin'
you say to people.
Hey, wait.
What's with my knife?
It's kind of chipped.
I'm sorry about that.
Ugh!
Jesus, what happened,
a knife fight?
I really didn't mean to.
Eh... No big deal.
[RACHEL] Carrying a weapon
with me saved my life, you know.
[ZACK]
Yeah. They're good for that.
[groans sharply]
Ah, man, easy!
Did it hurt?
Of course it hurt, dumbass.
[RACHEL]
I don't know,
I guess I thought
it wouldn't bother you.
[ZACK] Don't know where
you'd get that idea.
It's not like
I'm some kinda masochist.
If you think I'm God, then be
a little more careful with me.
[gasps]
Hmm. 'Kay, I'll try.
Hey, Zack?
[ZACK]
Now what?
[RACHEL] What about the burns?
Do they hurt too?
[ZACK]
Nah. They're from somethin'
that happened to me
a long time ago.
That's good.
Make it quick.
We gotta move on.
Sure.
♪
-I'm all done.
-Huh? Wow.
You did a pretty good job
with that.
All right, kiddo.
We can take a break.
[sighs]
♪
Um, did I just fall asleep?
Yeah. Ready to go now?
I haven't been able to find
the elevator to the next floor.
So? We can look for it together.
Wait, actually...
[sighs]
[footsteps]
[ZACK] How'd they fit
a whole church in here?
Anyway, what happened to that
priest guy you told me about?
[RACHEL]
I don't know.
I thought you said
you talked to him. Really?
So he just like, handed you
the drugs and walked away?
Well, it wasn't
as simple as that.
It never is with you.
You know, it was strange.
I think he might have had
a soft spot for you, Zack.
[retching]
-It's not that gross.
-Shut up!
Don't say weird shit like that.
What is it now?
Damn, this building's
friggin' crazy.
Yeah, you could
definitely say that.
[ZACK]
Huh?
So, how do we get it to move?
[RACHEL]
Press the button?
[ZACK]
Well, that was easy.
[RACHEL]
Wait up.
Hey, Zack,
can I ask you a question?
[ZACK] What's the point
of askin' permission to ask?
I won't know
till I hear what it is.
[RACHEL]
Yeah, you're right.
[ZACK]
So, what's up?
[RACHEL] How did you get
all of those burns?
[ZACK] Why the hell would you
wanna know somethin' like that?
[RACHEL] No reason.
I'm just curious.
I was thinking it might be nice
to learn more about you.
[ZACK]
Ugh!
Well, it's not that
interesting of a story.
[RACHEL] That's okay. It doesn't
have to be interesting.
[ZACK]
When I was a little kid,
some guy, who I think lived
at my house, set me on fire.
On fire? Why?
I don't really
remember it too well,
but he was at the house, so...
I guess he was the guy
who used to bang my mom?
-[groans]
-[MAN laughing]
[continues laughing]
[laughing menacingly]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[ZACK] The whole thing's
kind of a blur after that,
but I'm pretty sure I bit
a big chunk out of him
or somethin'.
He was probably tryin'
to kill me, but... [chuckles]
he didn't know what
a stubborn little punk I was.
So, then, what came next?
[ZACK sighs]
My whore of a mom
wrapped me up like a damn mummy,
and sold me off
to a shady-ass orphanage.
[RACHEL]
Oh.
[ZACK] That's pretty much it.
You satisfied now?
[RACHEL]
Yeah.
So what'd you think?
Was that story interesting?
No, not particularly.
Ugh.
But now, I know where you got
all your burns from,
and that kinda
makes me happy.
I wanted to know more,
and now I do.
So, yeah, I'm satisfied.
That's your only question?
Mm-hmm.
So you're good?
Glad I could help out.
Oh, and, uh--
I thought you said that was all.
Tell me the truth.
Do you want out of this place?
Huh? Of course I do.
That's a dumb question.
Jeez, Ray, you think I'm goin'
through all this crap for fun?
[RACHEL]
You're right. That's silly.
[ZACK]
Don't you worry.
As soon as we find
a way outta here
and you make
a better face for me--
[RACHEL]
I know.
You're gonna kill me,
like you promised.
[ZACK]
Yeah.
That's good enough.
[sighs]
Do you get weirder
every minute you're in here?
If it helps,
I've never once told you a lie.
I never will, either.
A lie...
right.
[bell rings, fades]
[bell crescendoes]
[gasps]
Hey, Zack,
here's the thing, okay?
-What?
-Hear me out.
You gonna say somethin' or not?
Um, here goes.
You see, I, uh...
Never mind.
Come on!
Don't play games with me.
Sorry. I was gonna
say something, but I forgot.
Jesus, Ray.
Get your shit together,
would ya?
You're the smart one, remember?
[sighs]
Look. We're almost
outta this hellhole.
-[RACHEL] Yeah.
-[elevator bell dings]
[ZACK]
Let's go.
[RACHEL] I can't say it.
There'd be no going back.
Zack says that he hates
liars more than anything,
and I know God doesn't accept
anybody who's unclean.
I've gotten my hands dirty.
If he finds out I've been hiding
that this whole time,
he's going to hate me,
I just know it.
There's no way I can
tell him the truth.
It's too late.
♪
Blood?
[shuddering]
[GRAY]
The Lord God is righteous.
He detests liars, as well as
those whose hands are unclean.
[RACHEL] Oh, no. We're here.
What do I do now?
This is where I was
when it all happened.
Zack, no. Wait.
Please don't look.
Stop. I'm begging you.
You can't go in that room!
♪