Of course, we are dealing
with a monster,
so we can't be sloppy.
But don't worry, dear.
If you shoot him in
the head from here,
there's no hope of survival.
‐‐You're a friggin' nutcase.
‐‐Go ahead.
[ZACK gasps]
[groans]
Why did you do that, Rachel?
Sorry, Doctor. I had to.
I'm the one who is
going to kill Zack.
Ah, right, of course.
I understand.
I'm tired of this.
So let's end it here.
[RACHEL] I know you wanted me
to come live with you forever,
but I can't.
[ZACK]
What's gotten into you?
Hey!
Just... kill me. There's no
way I can be saved.
But first, I have
one thing to do.
I need to own you.
You're mine, and mine alone.
Go for it then, I dare ya.
So you want me to die,
and you wanna die.
Is that supposed to fix this?
What's wrong with you?!
That makes no damn sense!
I know, alright? I know.
Good! Then don't be stupid!
This isn't stupid, Zack!
I'm being serious here!
Are ya now?
[RACHEL gasps]
[grunting]
Come on, Ray. Did you really
think a little wuss like you
had a chance at killin' me?
If you want this to end,
I'll end it for ya!
[RACHEL]
Stop! Please, Zack!
See, you're finally gonna
get what you wanted!
No, you can't!
[RACHEL] Don't kill me.
I'm begging you.
Not the way I am right now.
Because, you're...
...you're not my
God anymore, Zack.
[RACHEL] The God I once knew,
no longer needs me.
And that God I
found for myself?
That god is gone forever!
[ZACK]
Yeah. Seems that way.
And I guess you could say
I'm the one who did it.
You hear that?!
I killed your God!
[gasps]
But obviously I'm alive
and well, aren't I?
You get it, right?
I was the person who promised
to kill you, not God.
Either way. I still think‐‐
No!
[ZACK]
It was me, and only me.
Just forget about your God.
This's got nothin'
to do with that.
I'm more than happy
to keep my word, Ray!
But I'm unclean,
and I'm a sinner!
[ZACK] You think I'm
Mr. Friggin' Perfect?!
I'm a cold‐blooded
serial killer!
I've killed more people than I
can count just 'cause it's fun!
But unlike you and Four‐Eyes,
I don't waste my time thinkin'
about pointless shit like that!
I don't give a rat's
ass about parents or God!
Nobody controls me!
If anyone tried to,
I'd kill 'em!
I decide what I wanna do,
and then I freakin' do it.
End of story! You have your
way of livin' and I have mine.
Why is that so complicated?
I have my own way?
[ZACK] Exactly! So start makin'
decisions for yourself!
I... I...
[ZACK] Hey, Ray, what do you
see in front of you right now?
[RACHEL gasps]
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
Zack.
That's right.
You see a God anywhere?
No. You're just you,
no more, no less.
You know what,
for an insane person,
you are way too damn serious.
I'm the one you can
see with your eyes,
so I'm the one you
should believe in.
Now! Tell me you choose me!
[gasps]
You wanna die?
Swear you'll be killed by me!
And not just to yourself.
I want you to swear
it to me, too!
Okay... I swear!
You're going to kill me!
[ZACK chuckles]
[ZACK] Good. And I swear
the same thing to you, too.
[ZACK] Damn, are you just
gonna sit there cryin' forever?
[RACHEL]
But...
Come on.
Get us outta here, and you
can cry as much as you want.
I mean. Danny said this
was your floor, right?
[RACHEL]
Yeah.
So shouldn't you know
where to find the exit?
[RACHEL] I don't remember
going any farther up.
I never cared to.
Why not? Hey, where you goin'?
[RACHEL]
There is a front door.
Why don't you try
pushing on this?
You should be able
to get it open.
If you say so.
[RACHEL]
There was no reason to break it.
[ZACK] Like I said, there's your
way and then there's mine.
What's back there?
Somethin' bad?
There's nothing.
[ZACK]
If it's nothin', why bother?
Hey look. What's it
say over on that wall?
[RACHEL]
"Miss."
'Kay. Anyway, we should
keep lookin'.
Is there a room around
here you never went into?
[RACHEL] No. I searched
every last inch of this
floor so I could lay out traps.
There's no elevator
or stairs leading up.
You mean nobody's ever
come in here from above?
Guess not.
Oh wait. The doctor used
to go outside somehow.
He must've crawled in through
the ventilation system.
What a creep!
Wait, there's no
way he did that!
There's gotta be somethin' else!
[RACHEL exhales]
Oh, yeah.
[ZACK]
Huh?
The exit must be on one
of the other floors.
What? That doesn't
make sense.
In fact, I think it's
on the next floor down.
Wait a sec!
I don't get it.
Anytime someone came here
from outside, they rode
the elevator up, which means
that they had to have been
brought onto the floor
that's below this one first.
I'm still confused, but I
wanna get outta here, so...
Damn thing's busted.
The power's been switched off.
Now whatta we do?
It's okay. I know where
the power source is.
In that room, where the
music box was.
Right, I know how to get there.
Actually. I think I'd
rather go by myself.
Why?
Well, I'm never coming
back here again.
I want to say goodbye.
Yeah, but why can't
I come with you?
To be honest, Zack,
I'm a little embarrassed for
you to be there for this.
Suit yourself.
I'll stay here and keep watch,
but make it quick, alright?
[RACHEL grunts]
I'll be back soon.
There's no time to sew
you up. I'm sorry.
[gasps]
You again!
[RACHEL]
The gun...
[GRAY]
Do stay calm.
You behave as though I'm going
to bite you, silly girl.
What do you want now?
[GRAY] All I wish is to
ask you a question.
In the end, Zack wasn't your
God after all, was he?
That's right. I finally
figured it out.
[GRAY]
So it would appear.
And now that you've
reached that conclusion,
I hope you have an understanding
of the implications.
We made a promise to each other.
Just us. It had nothing
to do with God.
[GRAY]
By renouncing him as your God,
you've stripped him of his
standing as an ultimate being.
You've transformed
young Isaac Foster
into something that is
neither God nor angel.
And since you made your
vow with a mere mortal,
the same as you are,
there's no guarantee that
you can trust him to
grant your request.
He may end up betraying you.
If you still believe that
your pact is absolute and
will certainly be fulfilled,
then what disqualifies
him from being God,
in your mind?
[RACHEL] I'm not necessarily
sure he'll keep his promise.
I do trust Zack, yes.
But trusting and promising
were choices that he and I
made on our own.
According to what we
felt in our own hearts.
Which means, that even if he
chooses to betray his word,
it was still my
choice to trust him.
I'm responsible for what I do.
I can accept that he's not God.
I'm stronger now.
And in light of
these revelations,
you still desire death?
Yes.
But why? There's been such a
clear shift in your thinking.
Yet, even so, your wish
remains the same?
That's right. It's not like I've
turned into a different person.
I just accept who I am.
I know myself now.
And as a result,
I no longer have any desire
to be forgiven for anything
I may have done
in the past.
Because there's no one left
who would forgive me.
That's why I still
want to be killed.
I can't keep living.
I see. You seem quite
assured in your decision.
[RACHEL]
Yes. Also...
[GRAY]
Hm?
No, the rest is a secret.
Good heavens.
So you really have turned your
back on the Lord completely.
One last question.
Answer me truthfully.
Ms. Gardner, just who are you?
Well, I'm me, sir.
Nothing more than
that and nothing less.
Ah, yes, I understand.
The way you're speaking seems
to suggest that you consider
yourself and Zack to be equals.
Is that how you feel?
Then again, I suppose it might
not be far from the truth.
You're a failure as an angel,
but you have proven not
to be a witch. How curious.
Are you entirely positive that
you are Rachel Gardner?
Are we done here?
We are.
In that case, I need to
turn on the elevator now.
Be my guest.
You won't stop me?
Is that not what I implied?
I've no intention
of interfering.
I'm leaving now.
As you wish, my child.
Oh, and Reverend?
Where's the exit?
Do you expect me to answer?
I've been answering your
questions this whole time.
I think you can at least
respond to one of mine.
Is it on the next floor down?
[GRAY chuckles] I suggest you
take a look at the stained glass
in the cathedral.
I'll do that.
[RACHEL] After this,
there's no coming back.
Bye forever, and I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
I just turned on the elevator.
Sure took you
long enough, didn't it?
You didn't run into
the priest, right?
He's still kickin' around?!
Uh‐huh, but for
some weird reason,
he didn't do anything.
Man, I cannot get
a read on that guy.
[RACHEL]
Oh yeah, the gun.
[ZACK grunts]
[RACHEL]
It's in the living room.
Well then, grab it so we can go!
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
The Doctor.
[ZACK] Jeez, how many times
do we have to kill him?
Just die! I'm thinkin'
he's the monster here!
[RACHEL gasps]
Welp, that thing's no
good anymore. Let's go.
What's wrong?
This is what's
left of my parents.
[RACHEL]
I should say something.
[ZACK] Just say "bye‐bye"
like normal kids do.
Bye‐bye, Mom and Dad.
[ZACK grunts] Where's that
psycho doctor at?!
[RACHEL]
Hiding, maybe?
[ZACK] I say we hunt him
down and finish him off!
[RACHEL]
That's easier said than done.
He seems to know his
way around this building
better than
anybody else does.
We need to play it safe.
Ugh. You're no fun, Ray.
That's weird.
What?
The elevator is coming up.
Ain't it supposed to?
It should've been
stopped on this floor.
Which means somebody must
have ridden it down.
[ZACK]
Oh... That's not good.
‐‐[elevator dings]
‐‐[ZACK] Look out!
[ZACK] Hm? What the hell?
I don't see anybody.
[ZACK] Uh, you wanted to go say
goodbye to that room, right?
So, did you get to?
It was simple, but yeah.
Heh. That place looked
like a total pigsty,
maybe you shoulda cleaned it!
[ZACK grunts, sighs]
There's lotsa stuff in there.
Was that yours, or what?
Those are the things
I was given‐‐
Oh, so it wasn't
really yours, then.
I don't know. I sewed them
up and patched them.
I figured that would
mean they were mine.
But it's not like toys
and dolls can respond,
so I couldn't really
be sure either way.
But still...
I treasured all of them.
So I told them goodbye.
[gasps] I've always had
that music box, though.
I got it as a gift when
I was a little girl.
The music it made was so pretty.
You shoulda grabbed it
and brought it with you.
It's fine. I...
I'll remember the sound and all
the happiness it brought me.
As long as I have that,
I don't really need it anymore,
you know?
[ZACK grunts]
Now where do we go?
When I talked to the priest,
he said to take a look
at the stained glass.
You got a real answer
outta that guy?
He owed me one for
all my answers.
[ZACK gasps]
[ZACK] Alright, Specs,
where are you hiding?
I think this is our way out.
[ZACK] Sure, sure. I'll just
move this over real quick.
[ZACK grunts]
Damn, this is heavy.
Hey, kid!
What's up?
[ZACK] What do you think?
Come help me push!
[ZACK, RACHEL grunting]
[ZACK sighs]
Holy shit, my arms are numb!
Did I make myself useful?
Heh...Yeah, a little bit.
Anyway, call me crazy,
but are you sure there's
an exit behind that?
[RACHEL] Not at all, but I
don't think it's very likely
that the priest
was lying, either.
[gasps]
Huh?
Any ideas?
Just one, and I bet it's
the same one you had.
[ZACK chuckles]
You can leave it to me!
[yells]
[ZACK gasps]
So, are these stairs supposed
to lead us to freedom?
I think so.
Be better if you knew so.
Well, he didn't tell me what to
do after we got to the window.
Oh well. Not much choice.
[ZACK]
Yeah, you got that right.
Jesus, how many stairs
can there be?
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK]
What now?
I remember.
[ZACK]
Huh?
[RACHEL] When I was
first brought here,
I was blindfolded
on the way inside.
How's that help us?
I know that I was taken
down a long staircase.
That's somethin'!
If we keep going,
we should make it out.
[ZACK]
Hell yeah!
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK] I feel like we've been
walkin' up this thing for days!
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK gasps] It's always
somethin' with you.
You okay?
[RACHEL]
Yeah. I'm fine.
Ya know...
...you seem more real now.
Let's go, try not to fall down.
[RACHEL]
What's wrong?
Take my knife.
[RACHEL gasps]
You're letting me borrow it?
No, it's for you.
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK]
It's pretty banged up,
so it probably won't
do you any good now.
But hey, it's better
than nothin', right?
[RACHEL]
Thank you.
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNOUNCER]
Emergency protocol activated.
Initiating building
detonation sequence.
[chuckles]