Somebody's ballsy.
Don't you see
the freakin' scythe in my hand?
Actually...
Can I ask you a favor?
What?
Well, sir...
if you would...
kill me, please.
♪
[retching]
That's gotta be
the most screwed up thing
I've ever heard in my life.
I don't have time
for that doom and gloom shit
from a crazy little
freak like you.
If you've got enough energy
to talk like that,
then at least put up a fight.
I'll help all I can.
If I do, will you kill me?
Give it a rest!
Do somethin' about the door!
[gasps]
Fine, I'll try.
[footsteps retreating]
What is her problem?
This is my floor, so we play
by my rules.
♪
[grunting]
[groans]
[ZACK]
Whoa.
Well, looks like
you figured out the door.
Hmm.
Turns out there was a key
in the doctor's pocket.
I was able to use it
to turn on the elevator.
[chuckles]
Awesome! Who knew?
You're kinda smart, huh? Okay.
You still want me
to slaughter you, don't ya?
That's right.
The thing is, I'm 'bout
as dumb as a rock,
so here's the deal.
You help me escape
this murder hole,
and as soon as we get outside,
you're gonna stop actin'
like a haunted baby doll
and make a more
interesting face for me.
And that's when...
[whoosh]
I'll kill you,
just like you asked.
[gasps] Huh?
You mean that?
Yeah, sure. But, remember,
you have a job too.
I'll do my best.
Don't get all hyper, though.
That'll throw
a wrench in everything.
'Cause when I see
someone actin' happy...
[chuckles]
Well, I just have to
cut 'em down.
But I guess I won't have to
worry about that, will I?
Ugh, you damn zombie.
Anyway, what's your name?
I'm Rachel. Rachel Gardner.
Hmm.
[metal zings]
And I'm Zack. Nice to meet ya.
Now, let's look
for a way outta here.
[RACHEL]
Okay.
♪
That doctor on the last floor,
did you know him?
Ugh. Never mind.
So did you know him?
Who?
The doctor.
You called him by name.
Huh? Are you sure I did?
I guess I forgot.
[elevator bell dings]
Here we go.
[gurgling]
I think there's something
in the water.
Leave it alone.
Probably nothin' useful.
We gotta keep movin'!
Do you really know enough
about this building
to make that assumption?
Huh?
Well, I'm not an expert
or anything.
All I know is, they told me
I could kill whoever
I want to in here,
so I just went with it.
I'm sure it's the same
for the sickos
on the other floors.
I see.
What the hell? That's weird.
They're graves.
I thought it smelled like dirt
down here.
Ugh.
[wood breaks]
Dammit!
It's clingin' to my feet!
Ugh, why is it
so freakin' sticky?
Gross! This is not my day!
[ZACK grunts]
Hey, what are you lookin' at?
Are you fantasizin'
about gettin' one of these?
This whole place is a grave.
Ugh.
Come on.
You got some kinda
creepy-ass grave fetish or what?
Hey, let's go!
Hmm.
[ZACK]
Ugh.
Read it.
"The welcomed
by the Holy Land.
"The chosen by the Lord,
the Good Men.
The Beloved by
the Angels, the Special Ones."
It says to "leave yourselves
in the glory of the Lord."
And then, the bottom part
is addressed to traitors.
"Here will be
their prison forever."
Well, that makes
no damn sense.
And why would there be
graves in a basement?
Hey, don't go
sneakin' off on me.
Now what's your problem?
You're about to crawl in there,
aren't you?
[RACHEL] This one's newer
than the rest.
[ZACK] So? What difference
does that make?
The name inscribed on it...
is "Rachel Gardner."
And that's an unfinished one
over there.
Oh, is that mine? Huh.
I guess they think I could die
at any time.
What a freakin' joke.
I'm not gonna stand for this.
Guess I'll have to
smash the thing.
You can't.
Your scythe'll break.
You shut your mouth!
I know that!
Hmm.
Hey, are you just gonna
stare at it all day or what?
[metal whooshes]
I'm not plannin' on dyin' here
in this dump with you.
As soon as we escape,
you are so--
Huh?
I feel a draft coming
from that hole in the wall.
You sayin' that
there's somethin' in there?
Want me to go in and find out?
How do I know you're not gonna
run away from me?
What would I do that for?
You still haven't killed me yet.
[sighs]
Again with that crap?
You really give me
the creeps, kid.
Have it your way.
Go check out the hole.
Okay, why don't you look
for the exit out here
in the meantime?
Ugh. You tellin' me what to do?
Well, it'll be more efficient
if we're both searching--
There ain't nothin'
but graves here!
There may be a trigger
hidden somewhere.
Don't you think
I'm too stupid to be left alone?
Hmm.
Hey!
Anyway, I'll be right back.
Fine, see ya.
Oh, and, if you get
your freaky ass killed,
let me know
you're dead, all right?!
Dead people can't talk.
[grunts]
[RACHEL] Hey.
You got more orders for me?
If possible, could you
not destroy my gravestone?
Yeah, whatever.
♪
[electricity crackling]
[gasps]
[BOY giggling]
♪
[rattling]
[RACHEL]
It's locked.
[gasps]
"Dear Rachel..."
[BOY]
I've been curious about you
for a long time now.
I want to come meet you,
but that guy's
always in the way.
You know what? I knew right away
that I liked you a lot.
That's why I created
a special surprise.
Just for you.
A place where
you can rest forever.
Rest forever? That's odd.
♪
What's this?
[grunts]
How could there be
a trigger in here?
It's a friggin' graveyard.
The balls.
Somebody actually
dug a grave for me?
They got a pair,
I'll give 'em that.
I wanna trash it.
Huh?
[shuddering]
What the hell?!
So If I consider these
calculations at the bottom,
looking at the total number
of graves--
[rattling]
[ZACK laughing menacingly]
How do you like that?
There's what I think of your
shoddy-ass rush job tombstone!
Actually...
since I'm here,
I'll crush all of 'em!
[laughing menacingly]
♪
[laughter continues]
[rattling]
That's annoying.
[laughs]
[beeps]
-[rattling]
-[gasps]
Did he really get it open?
[laughing menacingly]
[ZACK]
On to the next one, bitches!
[ZACK whooping, laughing]
[electricity crackling]
[BOY giggling]
Is someone in here?
Hmm.
"Watkin Becket. Place of death:
Basement Three.
"The cause:
Blood loss from a bullet wound.
"Cut down on B6. Hanged on B5.
Bludgeoned on B4."
So they all came
to this building.
Hmm.
I'm here, too. I wonder.
Huh?
Suck it, tombstone!
That just leaves the one
she said not to mess with.
[electricity crackling]
-[BOY giggling]
-[gasps]
[giggling continues]
[electricity crackling]
Who's giggling?
[BOY]
I know what you really want.
I can make you fabulous.
It's just a big rock,
why is she so attached to it?
[chuckles]
If possible, could you
not destroy my gravestone?
[sighs]
I still don't get that kid.
-[grunts]
-[metal clangs]
Anyway, she told me
to look for somethin'.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Hmm?
♪
What happened here?
They pissed me off,
so I pulverized 'em.
So, you find anything?
The crack in the wall led me
into some kind of
reference room.
This was in there.
What's that?
It's my profile.
I don't get it.
You know,
it has information about me.
What good is that?
Even if I wanted
to know about you,
it's not like
that'll help me get out.
But, look, it's you, right?
[groans softly]
"Isaac Foster.
Birthdate: unknown.
"Once lived
in an illegal orphanage.
"The poor conditions
were eventually exposed,
"but beyond this entry,
not a single record exists
"of Isaac Foster's whereabouts.
Also found
at the orphanage were--"
How do you feel now
that you have all that info?
♪
'Course that's me.
Congratulations.
My name's Isaac Foster.
So, kid, does that make you feel
any different about me?
Not at all.
It's just a document
with facts about you.
It really doesn't
change my opinion.
You're not scared of me?
Don't lie.
No, I'm not scared.
You know,
you're not the first person
who's tried to tell me that.
[panting]
Are you scared?
'Cause you should be.
No, of course I'm not.
In fact, I, um,
I'm a big fan of yours.
[gasps]
Really. I read about you
in the newspaper.
I've been wanting to meet you.
This is such a huge honor.
My goodness.
You're so strong and handsome.
Maybe, we can--
[gasps]
[groaning]
You bitch, what the hell
are you talkin' about?
Then what?
Well, it made me laugh,
so I gave her five seconds
to run instead of three.
[laughing menacingly]
[gasps]
[groaning]
If you're not scared,
then why did you run?
I lied! You know
I'm afraid of you!
I just said that
so you might let me go!
[WOMAN crying]
[ZACK] Big mistake.
‘Cause I really hate liars.
[gasps]
I'm sorry. But what does that
have to do with me?
Huh?
If I run,
then will you kill me?
Am I supposed to follow
that woman's example?
Ugh, that's right.
You actually
want me to kill you!
Something wrong?
Nah, I'll be all right.
So, was that it?
There's another room that might
be worth checking out,
except, I couldn't
open the door.
If we look around some more,
I'll bet we'll find
another trigger.
Ugh. Why's this
have to be so hard?
Also, there was
somebody giggling.
Weird.
They said they know
what I really want.
Okay, then.
[RACHEL]
What now?
Hmm?
I'm gonna have to demolish
that damn grave.
It's drivin' me
freakin' insane.
-Wait--
-Get over it, short stuff.
Your grave is not here!
[grunts]
[thuds]
[metal zings]
If you wanna die,
you're gonna get me
outta this mess first.
♪
[door rattling]
Of course it doesn't
freakin' work! This sucks!
Hey, squirt, you're gonna help
or just stare at the wall?
I want you to see
what's down there.
Huh? You're askin' me
to get in the water?
Or not. That's fine.
[gurgling]
I don't like this whole
"you callin' the shots" BS.
Hey. You really are planning
on killing me, aren't you?
I told you, I'll do it
after we get out!
If you wanna die that bad,
just kill yourself!
Suicide? I can't do that.
Why the hell not?
I don't know, maybe,
because God said so?
Don't ask me.
Actually, I don't know why.
But, if God says
that it's wrong,
then it's wrong.
So you're one of those, huh?
All right, at least
put some effort
into gettin' me to kill ya.
And how do I do that?
Like I said,
it's all in your expression.
Hmm.
Ugh, come on.
Cry, get mad, somethin'.
♪
[sighs]
What, you don't have
any muscles in your face?
Jeez, just cry!
You sure
you're not already dead?
I'm not, that's why
you have to kill me.
[sighs sharply]
I was being sarcastic, okay?
Try to smile.
I'm not sure if I know how.
[sighs]
Just smile, dammit!
Hmm.
♪
You suck at this.
Doesn't work with those
lifeless eyes of yours.
-[thuds]
-Huh?
Stay there, and I'll go look.
I'm tired of you barkin' orders!
Shut up or I'm gettin' out!
It's way too cold
and nasty in here!
♪
This wasn't here before.
[BOY] No need to be
confused, Rachel.
Your desires and mine
are a perfect match.
You know that, right?
[shivering]
[sneezes]
All right, I've had it!
What is taking
that little brat so long?
Goddammit, she better not
try to run away.
Eh. She probably won't.
Seriously, what's the deal
with her face?
♪
Then again, if you can
ignore those blank eyes.
I guess it wasn't
such a bad expression after all.
-[electricity crackling]
-[sighs]
[BOY giggling]
[BOY]
You grave ruiner.
[grunts]
Hey, there, Zack.