[BOY giggling]
[BOY]
You grave ruiner.
Hey, there, Zack.
Hey there, little shit.
I went to so much trouble
making that grave for you.
Why would you go
and wreck it like that?
[laughs]
If you really
went to so much trouble,
then why does it
look like crap, kid?
I was in a hurry.
But, hey, if it's as ugly
as you say,
that means you'll be
right at home in it, won't you?
Not if I put you
in a grave first, you damn brat!
-[BOY scoffs]
-[ZACK grunts]
My name's not brat
or little shit.
It's Eddie, so use it, okay?
Shut up!
Did you have to mess up
her grave, too?
Now I gotta fix it.
[grunts]
Ah. She's great.
I fell in love at first sight.
You what?
Before now, all I did was
make graves for people
who had already passed on.
It was getting kinda boring.
I like digging graves,
but I don't have any feelings
about the people inside them.
Where's the beauty
in that, right?
So, I decided to create
the perfect grave for Rachel.
I understand her.
She and I are almost
the same age and everything.
Loving a person
who can love you back...
that must be way better
than one-sided feelings
for a messy, decomposing corpse.
[chuckles]
Of course,
if she'd rather it be messy,
that'd be okay with me, too.
Are you trying to get me
to hurl up my guts or somethin'?
I have an eye
for what's beautiful
and what's not.
She'd go so well in here.
That's why I'll be
the one to kill her.
Shut it. You ain't that special!
[grunts]
-[EDDIE laughing]
-[grunts]
[electricity buzzing]
Come out and fight,
you little necrophiliac!
♪
[gasps]
[doorknob rattles]
Huh?
RACHEL: I'm gonna need that.
[torch switch clicks]
♪
It's another letter.
This is exactly like
the previous ones.
"There is nothing
to worry about.
You and I want the same thing."
-[EDDIE giggles]
-[gasps]
-Who's there?
-[EDDIE] Hello, Rachel.
I'm going to grant your wish
for you, isn't that great?
But there's something
I want from you.
You have to entrust yourself
to me completely.
Love's better when it goes
both ways, don't you think?
Ugh.
[EDDIE] I understand you
more than you know.
You want to die.
So...
just tell me "yes."
♪
I'm glad we finally met.
My name's Eddie.
You don't have to run.
I won't try to kill you
out of the blue
like those other guys.
Zack is so sloppy
when he kills people.
He doesn't even care
about making it look nice.
But don't worry.
I'm not like that at all.
I know everything
that happened to you, Rachel.
About your mom and dad.
Your whole story.
Do you really?
Yep. So you're in good hands.
In that case, can you tell me
why I'm in here?
-What, did you forget?
-Mm-hm.
That's okay, it's not important.
[RACHEL]
But I want to--
[EDDIE]
The point is,
I can give you
a totally painless death
and you'll have the nicest grave
you've ever seen.
I can make your wish
come true, Rachel.
[RACHEL]
Hmm.
Hey, why aren't you
saying anything?
Come on, please? It's easy.
You just have to say "yes."
That runt's gonna pay.
Get back in here! Right now!
Damn it.
I guess he can't hear me.
That little
corpse-lovin' weirdo.
Does he think he can one-up me?
No way am I lettin' him
slaughter the bitch
before I get to.
[gasps]
Hang on.
She told me there was
a room inside and to the right.
Ah, man, I gotta do
everything around here.
[EDDIE]
Why haven't you said "yes"?
I know. Say your wish out loud.
Maybe that'll help.
[shudders]
[sighs]
I want to die.
I know you do.
And I'll be the one to kill you.
So just tell me "yes."
♪
This is so annoying.
Is it because of Zack?
Ugh.
Why are you with him, anyway?
Because...
he promised
that he was going to kill me.
Is that all?
Why not let me do it instead?
I'm sorry, you can't.
If I die then he won't have
a way out.
Why should either of us
care about that?
[EDDIE]
It would serve him right.
-[RACHEL] But...
-[gasps]
All right,
little Miss Horror Show!
-You in there somewhere?
-[gasps]
[EDDIE] Ugh. I hate
the sound of his voice.
Anyway, you pick.
Do you want to be killed
by him or by me?
My sweet Rachel.
I'll make sure
you rest in peace, and beauty.
♪
[gasps]
You don't know a damn thing
about what looks good,
you understand me, punk?
If you did,
you wouldn't kill her
with that boring look
on her face.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Would you please keep it down?
I'm trying to have
a conversation with Ra--
-[ZACK] Shut up, coconut-head.
-[EDDIE gasps]
Hey, you! Weird little girl!
You can hear me in there, right?
-Who, me?
-[ZACK] Who else?!
Don't think I'm gonna let you
run around here on your own.
Every sick puppy in this dump
wants to end your stupid life.
But whatever happens,
I'm gonna do the honors,
like it or not.
I swear to God I'll kill you.
[shudders]
[bell rings, fades]
[RACHEL]
You swear to God?
That's right. You heard me.
So...
don't you dare let
anybody else do it first.
[RACHEL]
Okay.
Then you should hit this section
of the wall as hard as possible.
[chuckles]
Hell, yeah!
How's that?
[EDDIE]
This isn't fair, Rachel.
[ZACK groans]
Where is that munchkin at?
[EDDIE] There's no problem
with me killing you.
What are you, touched?
There's a shitload
of problems with it.
[EDDIE] But you'd do
such an ugly job.
What's the difference?
[EDDIE] Listen, you don't want
this jerk to kill you.
He won't be neat or gentle.
It'd be better to let me do it.
I told you to quit your yappin'
and leave her be already
or you're gonna get cut!
[EDDIE] Rachel, I'll be the one
to put you to rest.
When you're ready,
I'll be waiting.
[door creaks]
-[electricity buzzing]
-[scoffs]
Ugh!
You're dead meat anyway,
you know that?
Even if I don't murder you,
something'll kill you
before too long.
-True.
-Hey!
Like I told you before,
if you wanna die,
then you're gonna have to
make yourself useful somehow.
You mean, if I can help you
get out of here,
then you guarantee
you'll kill me?
Yeah, seein' as how
that's exactly
what I just friggin' said.
But it's different now.
How?
"I Swear to God."
That is what you said, right?
To God.
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
You swore to God
that you were gonna kill me.
So now you have to.
You can't go back on that.
Once more.
Please just say it
one more time.
I need to hear it.
[sighs]
There you go again.
Listen, kid. I told you.
I really hate liars, okay?!
I understand.
Now that that's cleared up,
I'll try to find a way
to be useful to you.
[scoffs]
Glad you got it
through your skull.
So, what should we do?
Well, I did hear the sound
of a door opening earlier.
We should head towards that.
That boy, Eddie,
he said he would be waiting.
Great. Sounds fun. Let's go.
♪
I'm starting
to smell dirt again.
Don't tell me there's gonna be
more graves up ahead.
-Probably.
-Great.
Well, do me a favor
and don't go divin'
into the first one you see.
I would never commit suicide.
[ZACK]
Oh, yeah. You did mention that.
So, anyway, I don't think
I caught your name.
You got one, don't ya?
I told you, Rachel Gardner.
[scoffs]
I guess I'm fine
with keepin' you alive
till I can get
some use out of you,
but I gotta say,
dealin' with a sad sack
like you...
is a pain in the ass.
So, we meet again.
♪
Is there any way I can ever be
good enough for you, Rachel?
You have no idea
what a scumbag this guy is.
He's got no sense
of beauty at all.
And he was just as worthless
before he came to this building.
[RACHEL]
I read his profile.
Then why would you
choose him over me?
I can put you to rest
so much better than he can.
What?!
Dead is dead,
you smug little bastard.
I'm sorry, Eddie.
He swore to God
that he'd kill me.
And that's not something
you can take back.
Swearing to God, nothing means
more to me than that.
What kind of God
do you believe in?
I don't get it.
Why would your God want that?
Doesn't sound like
any God I know.
That kind of freedom
doesn't exist
in this place, Rachel.
We don't get to
make choices like that.
The only thing we've been given
is the right to hunt down
anyone who comes onto the floor
we're in charge of.
We make them sleep forever.
And I'm in charge of B-4.
Well, I've made my decision.
♪
And, Eddie...
[gasps]
...it still isn't you.
Suck on that!
Guess you're the loser, shorty.
[EDDIE crying]
[voice breaking]
You can't do that.
It's not your choice!
[chuckles]
What was that?
Can't hear you
over all this victory.
It's not fair,
you don't get to decide!
[heavy breathing]
[crying]
Rachel, I wanted to preserve
your perfect beauty in death.
But...
at least you can rest now.
A grave is really comfortable,
you know?
All dark and cool and quiet.
So...
let me put you inside of one.
[grunts]
[ZACK grunts]
[EDDIE groans]
You don't deserve her.
You're just a violent brute!
You're trying to do
the same damn thing.
Don't compare me to you.
No matter how much bigger
and stronger you are than me,
you're so dumb you can't even
kill people right.
You're stupid,
that's what makes you so angry.
You're the one
who's getting all worked up
because you've you got
such a raging hard on
for dead bodies.
Now you're getting nasty.
[laughs]
That's what your mom said.
Just be quiet!
All I want is you, Rachel.
Nothing else.
I'll seal you up for eternity
under a lovely tombstone
with your name on it.
Once I bash your head in.
-[grunts]
-[EDDIE laughing]
The hell's with these lights?
Doesn't matter
how strong you are
if you can't see
who you're fighting, does it?
I've had plenty of practice
digging graves
in the dead of night,
so I can see you just fine.
[grunts]
Nice try.
Takes more than that to hurt me!
[EDDIE] How long can you keep up
that tough guy act?
[grunts]
[EDDIE]
Whoops, almost had me.
[grunts]
Dammit. Show yourself,
you psycho!
[EDDIE] Watch where you're
swinging that thing.
Shut up! Hey, you.
Can I help?
Do somethin' about the lights.
I'm sure there's
a switch somewhere.
There damn well better be one.
But I can't see in the dark.
Which is why
we need the lights on, genius!
'Kay. Be right back.
Hey, Rachel, wait.
[gasps]
[EDDIE] He can see?
But how's that possible?
[grunts]
Ah. He's just
running on instinct.
[panting]
-[EDDIE giggling]
-[gasps]
[giggling continues]
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps]
I designed it just for you.
[groans]
Rachel.
I'll close you up in that coffin
so you can rest forever.
And I'll remake your headstone
so that it's even prettier
than before that idiot
destroyed it.
But first I need to kill you.
[EDDIE gasps]
Wow, you look like an angel.
Now our love can be complete.
I'll make sure
your timeless beauty
never fades away.
-[gasps]
-[switch clicks]
[EDDIE grunts]
[groaning in pain]
[voice breaking]
Rachel... please.
Please, tell me why.
Even after I built
this amazing grave for you.
I'm the only person
who understands
what you truly desire.
You hurt me so bad, Rachel. Why?
Eddie, I--
-[ZACK] Sorry, little man.
-[gasps]
But the lady shot you down!
[groans]
[chuckles]
[laughs menacingly]
[EDDIE screams]
[EDDIE choking]
[coughing]
[gasping]
[snickers]
[EDDIE]
Oh, Rachel.
[groaning]
I wish I could've put
you in here.
[gasping]
I hope you can see
how much I love you.
Hey, look at that,
it's a pretty good fit.
[weak breathing]
[sighs]
Not bad.
I never would've figured out
that he was usin' a remote
to control the lights.
The timing was too convenient
for it to be a coincidence.
A remote seemed like
the most likely answer.
[gasps]
♪
It's pretty.
Ugh!
So, I hope you found
the "up" elevator
while you were at it.
Well, did ya?
No, but maybe if I push
one of these buttons.
-[rattling]
-[gasps]
It was hidden back here
the whole time.
Nicely done, but don't let it
go to your head.
[scoffs]
Well, Ray, let's go.
Hold on. Did you...
Move your ass! We gotta split.
'Kay.
♪
So, um...
Yeah?
Um, did I help out
enough, mister?
I wish you'd quit
that "mister" and "sir" crap.
You're givin' me
the friggin' creeps.
Should I call you Isaac?
Uh...
Nah, I'd rather
you call me Zack.
Got it.
Anyway, was I
useful to you, Zack?
Yeah, kinda.
But just a little.
Keep it up
on the next floor too, would ya?
Okay. I'll try.
Anything I can do to help you.
-However...
-What now?
You can't forget
what you promised.
Once we get out of this place.
You swore to God
that you'd kill me.
Jesus, Ray.
You're starting to sound
like a broken record.
[chuckles]
Don't worry, I know.
♪
[elevator bell dings]
Hmm.
Why the hell can't we go
all the way to the top?
[grunts]
Well, this is gonna suck.
[whirring]
♪