[gasps]
[RACHEL]
Wait, where's her body?
That doesn't matter right now.
[whirs]
[groaning]
[RACHEL] She could see
the whole floor from here.
-[beeps]
-[whirring]
[groaning]
[RACHEL]
I'll shoot them.
I have to.
They shouldn't have stood
in my way.
♪
[RACHEL]
Come on.
[both groan]
Move it.
All of you are in my way.
[rapid gunfire]
[shuddering]
Move aside.
Now I can get in there.
-[CATHY laughing]
-[gasps]
Goodness, Rachel.
That sure was a terrible thing
you just did.
[gasps]
Laying waste to those poor souls
who were already so miserable,
and all because they were
unlucky enough
to be in your way.
You don't even look sorry.
But as long as
you get your chance
to be killed by Zack.
I guess the end
justifies the means.
You truly are the worst kind
of sinner there is, aren't you?
[laughing]
I thought we killed her.
[footsteps]
[panting]
[metallic creaking]
It seems you were able
to turn on the switch.
Yeah, I was.
And by what means did you manage
to get to where it was,
if I may ask?
Surely you must have encountered
at least a few unsavory pursuers
along the way.
There were some,
but I shot all of them.
And just why did you do that?
Because they got in my way.
[GRAY]
I see.
Well, then.
Shall we continue our trip?
It's all dried up.
You'll find the switch
for this floor
inside the water temperature
control room.
So what's the point of making me
do all these things, anyway?
As I said, my intent
is to determine
what sort of person you are.
But I have to hurry so I can get
that medicine and help Zack.
Believe it or not,
Rachel Gardner,
there has been
some debate about you.
Really, why's that?
You're irregular.
Ever since you came here,
it's been impossible
to discern your nature.
So I'm irregular?
[RACHEL]
I still don't understand
what he's trying
to learn about me.
Then again,
whatever it is, it doesn't
make any difference.
Uh...
He's gone too--
Follow me, child.
Uh...
[GRAY]
Look at that.
What a shameful mess.
Eddie was a kind and gentle boy.
It must have been extremely
upsetting for him
to have his work destroyed.
Perhaps his infinite generosity
was what caused him
to often get the short end
of the stick in life.
But even more pitiable are those
who had been laid to rest
in these graves.
Eddie's compassionate treatment
should have brought them peace
and carried them
on into the afterlife.
But sadly, such a fate
was not to be.
[crackling]
[RACHEL]
Hmm?
[EDDIE laughing]
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
Again?
Why am I seeing people
who should be dead?
[GRAY]
The control room is that way.
Proceed with caution.
[gasps]
A hand that moves on its own?
Is it some kind of toy?
[MAN screaming]
It feels disgusting.
[stones rattling]
[groaning]
[sobbing]
[MAN] Help. Please.
I'm begging you.
[RACHEL]
How annoying.
[VOICES screaming]
I still can't tell
what this girl is.
A lost lamb, or a foul demon?
[screaming continues]
-[EDDIE laughing]
-[gasps]
[EDDIE]
I saw that, Rachel.
You stomped all of those
screaming hands into the ground
like they were nothing.
[RACHEL]
Why does this keep happening?
[EDDIE]
That was really mean of you.
You didn't even feel bad
a little bit
when you heard the way they were
crying and begging for help?
[RACHEL sighs]
[EDDIE] Why wouldn't you just be
nice instead?
How come you never thought about
what would make them happy?
[RACHEL]
Hmm.
[EDDIE] I guess the only person
you worry about is yourself.
The only happiness that matters
to you is yours.
And that's why everyone
you know,
even Zack, is gonna end up
suffering before this is over.
Everyone will suffer, even Zack?
Right.
I need to get back to him soon.
[panting]
Okay, I hit the switch.
That wasn't too hard,
now was it?
So, would you care to tell me
what your methods were
in reaching the switch?
I opened the refrigerator
in the control room.
And there wasn't anything
or anyone in your way?
There were a few hands
moving around.
But I crushed them.
I see, and I assume they must've
cried out in pain?
No, sir.
What makes you say that?
They couldn't.
Because they were fake hands.
Are you certain in your claim
that they appeared to you
as nothing but toys?
Hmm.
Very well, then.
If that is what you say,
then I suppose I--
Can we just hurry up and go
to the next floor now, please?
As you wish.
B5.
Just as you requested.
Hmm.
Danny was both fastidious
and methodical,
much like any good doctor.
He mastered anything
he set his mind to.
I'm sure you'll find
his medicine shelves
pristinely organized.
However,
before Danny died, his neatness
reached an excessive degree--
[RACHEL]
Excuse me.
What is it?
After I find the medicine,
there's something I need
to get from Zack's floor.
Oh, that shouldn't be a problem.
As soon as you've collected
the antihemorrhagic,
make your way back
to the down elevator.
'Kay.
♪
Every time I'm on this floor...
It just feels off.
[ZACK] You help me
escape this murder hole,
and as soon as we get outside,
you're gonna stop actin'
like a haunted baby doll
and make a more
interesting face for me.
And that's when...
I'll kill you,
just like you asked.
Oh, yeah.
We made our promise here.
That's right.
Even if things may look
and feel different to me now.
Our pact is still the same.
♪
[RACHEL panting]
[groans]
Huh?
What was that thing?
I gotta grab the medicine
and get outta here.
♪
The doctor's body
disappeared too.
No time to waste.
There's nothing in here.
Where did all the medicine go?
Not here, either.
[sighs]
[panting]
What's the matter?
You seem to be in quite a rush.
I have to go to Zack, right now.
Did you find something for him?
No.
It's not there?
You said there'd probably be
an antihemorrhagic
on this floor.
But there's nothing.
Am I detecting
an accusatory tone?
Don't give me that
skeptical expression.
I don't understand
any better than you
why Doctor Danny's cabinets
are lacking supplies.
Although, if I had
to guess the reason...
I'd say it's likely
because of you, Rachel Gardner.
You're the common thread
in every awful tragedy
that's occurred here.
Did you not suspect
that it was all your doing?
No, I wouldn't know
anything about that.
I just know that Zack needs me.
Does this mean you no longer
wish to go to his floor?
If nothing else,
you might at least
find a few bandages
down there.
Hmm.
Well?
Yeah, let's go down.
Wise choice.
[RACHEL]
I'll be useful.
Hold on.
♪
Aw, I'm sorry
about that, sweetie.
Are you okay?
[gasps]
[WOMAN]
Uh...
You should put that knife away
and run along home now,
all right?
[gasps]
[shuddering]
I don't have a home
to go back to.
♪
[WOMAN screaming]
[sighs]
[groans]
Is someone in there?
[ZACK gasps]
Quiet, gramps.
A young boy?
Where are your parents?
Surely your mother and father
must be around somewhere.
I'm blind so I'll need you
to speak up and tell me.
-[stomach growling]
-[gasps]
Sounds like
you're a mite hungry.
♪
What were you doing
in that car, son?
Well, that's all right,
you don't have to
explain anything.
If you've got no place to go,
you can stay here
as long as you'd like.
[ZACK]
That makes no sense.
Hmm.
Why would you let me stay
with you for nothin'?
Because I'm lonely.
But, you're welcome
to leave at any time.
I won't try to stop you.
I never said
that I wanted to leave.
Hmm.
♪
[ZACK] Why do I feel
this weird chill all the time?
Maybe I can stop it.
For some reason,
I don't think
killing the old man is gonna
make me feel any better.
[drunkenly] Who's up for
another round of whiskey?
Whoops. Watch where
you're goin', buddy.
[MAN laughing]
[groaning]
[ZACK]
It didn't help.
I still feel
that annoying chill.
What's wrong with me?
Don't need this anymore.
[GRAMPS]
Where have you been all night?
[sniffs]
Blood?
Yeah, I killed a guy.
I felt like killin',
so that's what I did.
I see.
And what is it you want
to do now, young man?
You must be tired.
Get some sleep.
♪
-[door creaks]
-[groans softly]
Where did he run off to?
[gasps]
I can't read, you idiot.
What's takin'
that geezer so long?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, man.
Can you believe
this was all
that pathetic old fart
was carryin'?
No way, it's nothin'
but chump change.
Yeah, guess we didn't have to go
to the trouble
of killin' him, huh?
[gasps]
[MAN] What the hell
are you lookin' at?
Get lost.
It sure looks like
you're havin' a good time.
People with happy faces
like those
are always the ones
that end up bein' monsters.
[WOMAN]
Monsters?
Cut it out,
you creepy little bastard.
[both gasp]
-[ZACK grunts]
-[MAN groans]
[WOMAN screams]
-[ZACK grunting]
-[WOMAN shuddering]
[WOMAN screaming]
[stabs]
[grunting]
And what is it you want
to do now, young man?
[ZACK] I wanna cut down everyone
who smiles and laughs,
and make them wish
they'd never been born.
Yeah!
I'm a monster!
[ZACK laughing menacingly]
Why'd you have to
get yourself killed?
[footsteps approaching]
[DANNY]
Ah. You're still alive.
And so weak.
Shall I put you out
of your misery?
Well, Zack?
♪