[RACHEL]
I'm not giving you orders
or wanting favors.
I'm just asking for your sake.
What about you?
[bell rings, fades]
♪
[sighs]
No matter what kinda
vacant expression you may have
on your face right now,
it's still way too hard
to hold myself back.
I mean, if I knew how to stop
myself from murderin' people,
I wouldn't have been
brought to this building
to begin with, now would I?
♪
[grunts]
[inaudible]
[sighs]
[shudders]
[groans]
♪
[WOMAN screaming]
[ZACK]
Oh.
I get it.
[music stops]
Yeah, I know
how to fix my problem.
♪
[groans]
[shudders]
[ZACK grunting]
[panting]
[stabbing]
[exhales]
[laughing menacingly]
Thing is, like I said before,
I can't stand a liar.
And you know what I mean
when I say that, don't ya?
Mm-hmm.
There's a good girl, Ray.
So, for now, do me one favor.
I'm beggin' ya.
Please don't let me
kill you just yet.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[continues groaning]
[RACHEL]
It's not like before.
I'm not running to save myself.
This is to save Zack.
[laughing]
[RACHEL]
For his sake,
I can't let him kill me yet.
[panting]
[ZACK laughing menacingly]
[RACHEL] Those drugs made him
lose his mind.
I have to keep running.
[ZACK laughing]
[gasps]
-It's a dead end.
-[door opens]
[gasps]
[ZACK grunting]
Zack, stop.
[ZACK laughing]
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[ZACK gags]
[CATHY laughing]
Hi.
I can't believe
you two made it this far.
Sorry I had to cut
the party short.
And just when it was
getting good, too.
You've entered
my firing squad room,
hence the bullet in your arm.
Look around you.
You're surrounded with
more machine guns
than you can shake a scythe at.
And the best part is,
I'm able to control
every one of them
with the push of a button.
It's just the handiest thing.
Anyway, it sounds like
you've had a spat.
It's fun watching
the drama unfold.
Especially with you, Zack.
You truly are exceeding
my expectations as a criminal.
The way you surrender
to your evil impulses,
despite your every
desperate effort to resist them.
It takes my breath away.
[ZACK groaning]
Shut your damn mouth.
[grunting]
What's the matter?
Feeling a little dopey?
Those drugs threw you
for a loop, didn't they?
You're attacking
the wrong person.
Doesn't make
no difference to me.
-[gunfire]
-[groans]
[CATHY]
You adorable oaf.
I already told you, dear,
you've got the wrong girl.
Oh, no.
Don't come near me!
-[shuddering]
-[sighs]
That's interesting.
I was thinking
a gunshot wound or two
would make you
more rational, but, nope.
Same old Zack.
So sad.
[chuckles]
You can't help it.
Moving on.
Rachel Gardner.
[snaps fingers]
[drumroll]
[CATHY]
How about we even the odds?
It looks like poor Zack
brought a scythe to a gun fight.
Go on.
Slaughter each other.
And then,
whoever's left standing
will receive an even more
glorious judgment from me.
-[laughing]
-[ZACK grunting]
But if we do that,
then what'll be
the meaning of it?
Unh.
Ugh.
You really are
a boring little sinner,
do you know that?
What's the point
in looking for meaning?
Do you think that would change
what's happening?
After all, nothing good
can ever come
from the actions of a criminal,
so why try to understand?
You could find much better ways
to waste your time.
Are you ready
for the main event?
I am, so put on a good show
for me, will you, darling?
[applause over speakers]
[shudders]
[ZACK]
Come on!
If you're gonna shoot me,
then just do it already.
[CATHY]
What's this?
Do my eyes deceive me,
or is somebody getting
a little gun-shy?
I should've expected as much
from an unremarkable girl
like you.
Be quiet.
Even if you don't fire the gun,
I can't stop myself
from cuttin' you open.
I won't kill you.
Oh, yeah? Well I wanna kill you
so bad it's tearin' me up!
I'm sorry, Zack.
I guess you'll have to do it
while I still have
this dull expression.
Damn right, I will!
And I'll feel like shit
once I finish the job, too.
I'm gonna give you
one more chance to stop me.
If you shoot me at point blank,
there's no way you can miss.
Mm-mmm.
Ask all you want,
but my answer won't change.
I'm not going to kill you, Zack.
That's the decision I've made.
I'll be happy
for you to kill me.
But I won't let this end
the way she wants.
Because, that woman,
she's wrong.
We're not tools.
To murder, or give in to death,
they're our choices to make.
And ours alone.
[laughing]
Jesus, you sure picked
a bad time
to start givin' a damn.
I can't hold back anymore.
Hey.
Try smilin' one more time.
Come on.
[grunting]
What a lame smile.
Man, can't you have some life
in your eyes for five seconds?
Oh, well.
If it did turn into
a real smile one day,
I'd love that!
When I think about how fun
it would be to kill you then,
it starts to make me smile too.
See, Ray,
look how glad I am now.
So glad, it makes me
wanna kill myself!
[gasps]
♪
[thuds]
Zack, no.
[screaming]
[gasps]
[CATHY]
It makes me so angry.
Neither one of you
is my ideal criminal.
Rachel Gardner couldn't
deign herself to commit murder,
and Isaac Foster turned out
to be such an imbecile
that he did himself in
just to satisfy
his own bloodlust.
You're failures.
How dare you deny me
the pleasure of punishing you?
You're such a supremely
dreary little brat, Rachel.
Sorry, but I already knew that
without you
having to point it out.
[grunts]
Talk back to me again
and see what happens,
young lady.
Do you think it's fun
judging someone so passive?
It hurts me much more
than it hurts you, Rachel.
Honestly.
I wish it would've been
Zack who lived.
He would have looked
so much better
with his body all riddled
with bullet holes
than you're about to.
But, no, you couldn't even
pull the trigger.
You're a disappointment
as a criminal.
Ugh, how did you even
make it this far?
How? Let's see.
[sighs]
I don't really care.
[whirring]
-[ZACK gags]
-[gasps]
[panting]
Oh, my goodness.
Still kicking, are we?
-Fabulous.
-[ZACK groaning]
[laughing]
You're going to kill him?
Of course.
Such a fantastic criminal
deserves quality punishment.
And I'm the only woman
suited for the job.
[gun clicks]
[RACHEL]
You can't.
Well, now.
Look who's finally
showing some teeth.
Go ahead,
you've got a clear shot.
You just need the guts
to follow through.
You're no fun at all.
And I almost thought
you might do it.
Not that it matters.
Even if you had been
brave enough to shoot,
there were never any bullets
in that gun anyway.
[gasps]
Too bad.
You were close
to redeeming yourself
as a criminal in my eyes,
but you've gone and found
another way to let me down,
haven't you, dear?
That said,
I did appreciate
how spunky you were
when you pointed that gun at me.
-Bang.
-[gunshot]
[gasps]
[groans]
-[groans]
-I'm glad you're not dead.
The more life a sinner has left,
the more enjoyable
they are to punish.
[laughing]
♪
[bell rings, fades]
[RACHEL]
No.
You can't kill him now.
Because Zack is the only one...
who can kill me.
Bang, bang.
[CATHY gagging]
You!
Worthless tramp.
You finally showed
your true colors.
Now you're a real criminal.
Oh, I love it.
Get ready to be punished.
This is your day of reckoning,
you wretched sinner!
Make whatever disinterested face
you want, it doesn't matter.
I'll make sure you pay dearly!
Shut up, already.
Nobody should ever look
that excited about bein' shot.
Seein' you like that made me
wanna cut you open so bad,
it brought me
right outta my funk.
[weakly]
This can't be real.
You bet your ass it's real!
You believe it now, don't ya?
How'd you...
[CATHY gagging]
No.
You have to be judged.
And If I don't do it...
[groans]
[laughing]
[gagging]
Finally, some peace and quiet.
-I thought you were hurt.
-I am.
My gut's friggin' killin' me,
what do you think?
I couldn't help but notice.
You looked really happy
when you sliced yourself open.
[grunts]
Don't put me
in the same category
as Miss Crime and Punishment,
all right?
I just did what I thought
would be the best option.
I couldn't kill you
with that dumb face
and then turn around
and get killed by her.
And speakin' of faces,
you did see hers, right?
Yeah.
I got such a kick
outta that. Oh, man.
You didn't do half bad, either.
I'm feelin' a lot better now.
Are you really?
Sure.
I'm so relieved, the pain
isn't even botherin' me.
Well, let's keep movin'.
Um, you sure you can?
Quit naggin'.
You just worry
about your own damn self,
would ya?
Uh, sure.
[door rattles]
Argh.
Of course it's locked.
It might open if we do something
with these devices.
Okay, then give it a try.
[applause over speakers]
Clapping? What the...
This must be
how she was controlling
all of those lights
and sound effects.
Guess that's what happens
when you're a sadistic freak
with too much time
on your hands.
Mm-hmm.
This one.
Nice work. Let's go.
♪
[RACHEL] "To open the door,
give your name to God.
"If there are no lies
in your life,
"give Him your true name.
But God does not need
the sinner."
[ZACK] Does that wall say
somethin' interesting or what?
Uh...
Oh, sorry. It's nothing.
Well, you're sure as hell
not staring at it
like it's nothing.
I just zoned out.
Come on, we need to get going.
Why does this look so familiar?
Because it was the first area
we passed through.
So she had the nerve
to clown around like that
right next to us?
I'm gonna kill her.
Ah. That's right,
we already did that, huh?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, she's dead.
So, how do we
get up to the next floor?
Hmm.
[door opens]
-Hey.
-Uh...
Let's try there.
The wall's open now.
[ZACK] Whatever. It looks like
some weird door to me.
But how are we supposed
to get through it?
[RACHEL]
Uh...
I thought you'd be able
to make it move
with those stupid machines.
No, I don't think
I saw a switch for the elevator.
There must be some other way.
Yeah.
This usually works better
if I leave
the brainstormin' to you, so...
[gasps]
[RACHEL]
That looks important.
The writing we saw on the wall
back there said,
"Give your name to God."
The things from when she made us
take those pictures.
Now what?
They'd fit that frame perfectly.
"But God does not need
the sinner."
It should work now.
[ZACK]
Sweet.
Wait.
What are we supposed to do
with the other one, then?
I'll throw it out.
-Are you sure?
-Uh-huh.
We don't need it.
♪
[elevator whirring]
[groaning]
Hey, Ray, listen.
You really were
a total badass earlier
you know that?
What do you mean?
I'm talkin' about when you
looked that psycho bitch
right in the eyes
and shot her dead.
You made me feel cool
just by lookin' at ya.
Huh.
Tell me, how did you end up
trapped in this building anyway?
Uh...
Well, I witnessed
a terrible murder.
That's why I had to come here
for counseling.
Then I was in a room
with a blue moon
outside the window.
Blue moon?
That doesn't make
a lot of sense.
And not just that.
The gun you shot
that chick with,
it didn't belong to her.
So where'd you get it?
It's, um, it's mine.
Where the hell
were you hidin' a handgun?
It was in my bag,
wrapped up in a handkerchief.
You were packin' heat
this whole time
and you didn't
pull it out before?
I can't kill myself.
God wouldn't forgive me
for a sin like that.
No.
I wasn't talkin' about--
And besides, you're the one
who's supposed to kill me, Zack.
Jesus.
You're either really smart
or really stupid,
I just can't figure out
which one.
Well, whatever.
Either way,
you did the right thing
puttin' a bullet in her gut
as soon as you got the chance.
I crack up
whenever I think about it.
The timing
was so friggin' perfect.
You're smiling.
Are you happy?
Yeah, kinda.
Aren't you in a good mood, too?
[laughs]
[RACHEL]
Yeah.
[elevator bell dings]
Looks like we're here.
Are you ready?
Come on, Zack.
Oh, no.
Zack.
♪