[RACHEL breathes heavily]
[ZACK] I feel like we've been
walkin' up this thing for days!
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK] Huh? It's always
somethin' with you. You okay?
[RACHEL]
Yeah. I'm fine.
Ya know... you seem
more real now.
Let's go. Try not to fall down.
What's wrong?
Take my knife.
[RACHEL gasps]
You're letting me borrow it?
No, it's for you.
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK]
It's pretty banged up,
so it probably won't
do you any good now.
But hey, it's better
than nothin', right?
[RACHEL]
Thank you.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Emergency protocol activated.
Initiating building
detonation sequence.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
‐‐What the hell kinda‐‐
‐‐Run! Hurry!
Wait up!
[GRAY] "Who really are you?
You should ask yourself.
You must seek to discover
your true nature.
Are you the real 'yourself',
or the one you believe to be?
An angel or a sacrifice?
Know yourself, and new
doors will open."
[gasps]
No...
[RACHEL gasps]
[ZACK grunts]
[ZACK]
I got this!
[RACHEL]
You can't break that!
Shut your damn mouth
and watch me!
[metallic clanging]
[ZACK grunts]
Stupid bars! Now what do we do?
[gasps]
[GUY A laughs]
[breathes heavily]
Just breathe. It's okay‐‐
I can't be burned
to death. I just can't.
Don't worry. I'm here.
I'll figure something
out for us.
Zack. Trust me.
You're gonna be alright.
[heavy breathing continues]
[RACHEL gasps]
[RACHEL grunts]
[ZACK]
Shit. Here we go.
What are you tryin'
to do, you idiot?
I'm going to get the
two of us out of here.
[ZACK gasps]
[ZACK]
Just move. Let me handle it.
But you‐‐
Shut up! I said let me!
[ZACK grunts, yells]
[giggles]
[gasps]
Yeah, that's right!
[yells]
[ZACK giggles] Sorry 'bout that.
I'm back to normal now.
You ready?
[RACHEL]
Hm. Let's go!
[ZACK]
Yeah!
[ZACK yells, chuckles]
The stairs are broken,
what do we do‐‐
[giggles]
Wow, Zack, you're having
fun with all this.
[ZACK] Quit talkin',
you'll bite your tongue!
[RACHEL]
I can see the exit!
Let's leave this dump forever!
[BOTH gasp]
[giggles] Hey, you wanna see
me do somethin' awesome?
[RACHEL]
Huh?
I can break through that stuff.
All you gotta do is
say the magic words.
Now, Zack! Break it!
[ZACK laughs, yells]
[RACHEL gasps]
It's ruined...
Welp, this thing is useless now.
Are you comin' or not?
[RACHEL]
Yeah.
Bye‐bye.
[ZACK sighs] Damn, this place
had us doin' jacked‐up shit
all the way to the end.
[ZACK] You handled it
like a pro, though.
If it hadn't been for you and
your brains, my dumb ass
wouldn't have
lasted five minutes.
[RACHEL]
You were helpful, too.
[ZACK] Nice, We finally get to
kiss this murder mansion goodbye
once and for all!
What's with you?
[RACHEL grunts]
One more time.
After we get out, you are going
to kill me, aren't you, Zack?
You wanna bring this up now?
[RACHEL] I'm sorry. I just need
to know this is what you want.
[RACHEL] I still wish to die
more than anything, of course.
But if... you're gonna kill me,
then it's better if you want to.
The thought of dying
makes me happy,
but when I imagine being
all alone when it happens,
it kind of makes me sad.
So I think if you kill me
because it'll bring you joy,
maybe I'll feel
better about it.
I know it's selfish to say
after you gave me this‐‐
You wanna know why
I gave you that?
'Cause I want you to
keep yourself alive...
...till it's time
for me to kill ya.
[RACHEL gasps]
I'm not a thoughtful guy.
Come to think of it,
this is the first time I've
ever given anything to anybody.
You know me. I don't do anything
I don't wanna do. Not ever.
Do you mean that?
What'd I just say? I've told
you a thousand times.
I really hate‐‐
You hate lies, right?
[ZACK sighs] We've spent
way too much time together.
[ZACK] Anyway, make a
good face for me.
You're pretty decent
at some things,
but smilin' ain't one of 'em.
[RACHEL]
Zack...
[DANNY laughs]
[DANNY] Oopsie,
How terribly unfortunate.
What a horrible little
mess you've made!
I'm the one who activated the
building's emergency system.
You're welcome.
Soon enough, you'll be
engulfed in a sea of flames,
and I know how much
you love that!
[DANNY laughs]
Why don't you just die alre‐‐
[ZACK grunts]
My, you're so brave for
charging straight toward
a loaded gun, Zack!
So brave, and so stupid!
I hate to tell you this, but it
looks like it's too late for you
to make good on
your little deal.
[laughs]
Sorry, Zack.
[gasps]
Please forgive me. I swore it'd
be you, but I think it's over.
Don't you dare say that!
I told you, if there's
one thing I hate it's‐‐
[ZACK grunts]
[DANNY] You can't run,
and you can't save her.
You're not getting any
options this time!
And you definitely
can't kill Rachel.
Tell me how it feels, Zack.
Having your one dream
ripped away from you!
Shut up, five‐eyes!
Oh, what a great comeback.
Well done, as always!
[ZACK]
Come on, Ray, keep it together.
If you die now,
you'll make a liar outta me.
Please. Don't make me turn
into the thing I hate the most.
Ah, a monster without his fangs.
What could be more entertaining?
[RACHEL] You're wrong.
He's not a monster.
[DANNY scoffs]
[RACHEL]
He's not God, either.
Zack is..
...a human being.
No more and no less.
So, there's no reason he has
to give me everything I want.
It's fine.
[ZACK]
Ray...
[DANNY] You're satisfied with
him giving you nothing?
Rachel! I've always
given you everything!
All the food, and toys and
clothes you could want!
And I gave you your floor!
Did that mean nothing to you?!
As far as I know, he only
ever gave you a knife.
That thing belongs
in the damn trash!
[DANNY]
Oh, wait.
I suppose he did give you
that silly death promise.
Of course! What a
nice gift that was!
After everything that I've done.
I've worked so hard to keep
you alive up until now
and this is the thanks I get!
[RACHEL] But, Doctor...?
I never asked to live that way.
I just hoped someone would want
me alive, even for a moment.
And that I'd also be...
...wanted in death.
After I made that vow with Zack,
and we started
trying to get out.
I understood that...
that would be enough for me.
[DANNY]
If that's true,
then shouldn't you feel
even more despair?
After all,
I've just taken the possibility
of having that away from you.
[ZACK]
That's enough.
[DANNY]
Shut up and let me speak!
Yeah? Make me!
[RACHEL]
You didn't take it away.
[ZACK gasps]
[RACHEL grunts]
No matter what, I know that
a vow cannot be stolen.
Even if it turns out that it
can't be fulfilled, it's okay.
It's still ours. It's something
we share, and it always will be.
[RACHEL]
Zack.
I've decided I'm going to carry
our promise with me forever.
And that means you
won't be a liar.
So it's okay if you don't
get a chance to kill me.
[DANNY whimpers]
[ZACK gasps]
Ray no. You can't.
Ah, poor Rachel.
Never looked to anyone else.
Never trusted a soul.
If your eyes had
remained doubtful,
if you had spent the
rest of your life lonely,
I can honestly say I
wouldn't have minded dying.
But now this.
What have you done, Rachel?
Why have you strayed so
far from your loneliness?
You have destroyed everything.
[DANNY]
Either way, it's all over now.
I'll kill your wish
along with Zack's.
And finally, my own.
All with this single shot.
I never knew what a truly
selfish man you could be, Danny.
Reverend... It's you. Why?
[DANNY groans]
Not yet!
Goodbye, Zack. You've eluded
me for the last time!
[GRAY] Now, son. Are you
still able to move? Well?
Listen, preacher. I ain't got
time for your games. Save it.
[GRAY] If you have any
strength left to gather,
then you should use it to
carry the girl to safety.
What for? See all that blood?
No one lives through that!
What's the point in tryin'
to save somebody who's dead?
[GRAY]
Rachel Gardner is still alive.
[gasps]
[GRAY] If you leave at once,
then her life will be saved.
[ZACK]
What are you sayin'?
Make haste, and you will see,
but you must go immediately!
You'll understand in due time!
[chuckles]
The moon is so
pretty and blue.
But, it almost looks like
it's not real or something.
[ZACK] Big mistake.
'Cause I really hate liars.