[weakly] Hey.
Take this.
I don't know
if you'll be able to use it,
but maybe it'll come in handy.
[groans]
Thank you.
And I promise,
I'll be useful.
I have to find the doctor
and get that medicine.
♪
[pulsating]
A rabbit?
[gasps]
I should hurry.
[panting]
[shrieks]
[gasps]
Where am I?
Rachel.
I'm so glad you came back.
You again.
Huh?
Don't get in my way.
[grunts]
[EDDIE] You still want to die,
don't you?
Yes, but I can't yet.
No. You have to.
I'll kill you right here
and now.
Eddie.
Come on.
Let me out of this thing.
Come back.
Zack doesn't have much time.
That's it.
[gasps]
♪
What's going on here?
[CATHY chuckles]
[CATHY laughing menacingly]
-[electricity crackling]
-[screams]
[laughing continues]
[panting]
Huh?
A mirror.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
In the way.
Zack!
[gasps]
♪
[GRAY]
Even if, as you said,
Zack did swear to God
to kill you,
do you claim to have
divine knowledge
that God would accept
such a promise?
And if God's choice
goes against your desires,
Rachel Gardner,
would you defy his will?
[bell rings, fades]
Here's the thing, Ray.
There is no God in this world.
[ringing crescendoes]
♪
That can't be.
I don't believe it.
Make it stop!
Zack is supposed to kill me.
I can't just let him die.
But if it turns out
that's not the will of God...
or if there isn't a God
in the first place,
what should I do?
I must say,
I wasn't expecting this.
Why are you here
all by yourself?
What has become of poor Zack?
Have you forsaken him?
Tell me where the doctor is.
I really need to talk to him.
I crossed paths with Danny
a while ago,
but I'm not quite sure
where he is now.
I know you're lying to me!
No, I never lie.
Although, since his behavior
has been less than admirable,
I did relieve him
of a few medications.
What?
You mean, you have them?
At this point,
it's a necessary precaution.
Please, sir.
Could I have some of it?
Do you honestly believe
you can obtain it that easily,
simply by asking me politely?
Give it to me.
You took that weapon,
leaving Zack defenseless,
and now you have the audacity
to point it at me?
How do you know this knife
belongs to Zack?
Very simple, my dear.
You see, it was I who found him
and brought him to live in this
building in the first place.
Now his body is badly wounded,
and you are the one
who's to blame.
After all, you deceived him.
No.
Danny was quite an intelligent
and prudent individual.
That's why he was more familiar
with this place
than anyone else,
and why he refrained
from any self-indulgent conduct.
[ticking]
What about young Isaac Foster?
Despite his sins,
his heart is simple and pure.
And yet, look at how much
he's had to suffer,
all because of your desire
to be slain by his hand.
Everything that troubles him now
has only come about
since your arrival.
I didn't do it.
It isn't my fault.
Just who are you,
Rachel Gardner?
It's still a mystery to me.
You have no answer?
[shudders]
Then perhaps you were only
pretending to believe in God.
That's not true!
[panting]
[GRAY] So, why won't you answer
my question?
My theory is this.
Because you don't know
the answer.
In your desperation
to be desirable to God,
you allowed your heart to become
steeped in falsehood.
And we angels were
deceived by you.
You detestable witch!
No, please.
You're wrong.
Am I?
In that case, we must
conduct a thorough trial.
♪
And now, the witch trial
shall start.
The Lord Almighty desires
an untainted soul.
Yet here you stand today,
under suspicion of being a witch
and deceiving this
holy host of angels.
Worst of all, you formed
an ungodly contract
with Isaac Foster.
How do you plead?
Not guilty, sir.
It's true that we made
a promise.
But it's a promise to God too.
There was nothing wrong with it.
Using our most righteous Lord
as an excuse.
Unfortunately for you, we don't
choose what's right and wrong.
Only God can pass judgment
upon our souls.
Now then, who wishes
to give testimony
regarding Rachel's actions?
[switch clicks]
♪
[CATHY]
Hi! Have I got a show for you.
You wouldn't believe
what a naughty little criminal
Miss Rachel Gardner's been.
I'll tell you the whole story.
[EDDIE]
Don't forget me.
I could talk all day long
about how wonderful Rachel is.
But she does have
a stubborn streak.
So even I want to do
something mean to her.
It seems only I can attest
to her true nature.
And as luck would have it,
I'm here.
Rachel! You're safe!
I've come to defend you.
-Doctor Danny.
-Very well.
Let us commence
with the testimonies at once.
[CATHY]
Sounds great.
I'll start,
if you all don't mind.
Un-huh.
That's not fair.
How come you get to go first?
That's a good question, kiddo.
It's because,
out of everyone here...
[groans]
...I've suffered the most pain.
Um, okay.
Right.
Miss Catherine Ward,
present your statement.
Sure.
I'd be glad to, Your Honor.
May I have
the court's attention, please?
The person you see
before you may look
like a sweet,
innocent young lady.
But she's rotten to the core.
There's not a doubt in my mind
that she is a bona fide witch.
I'm not a witch.
And yet she denies it.
You seem to be pretty talented
at lying through your teeth,
don't you, dear?
Exhibit A!
Take a look at this, everyone.
Zack, do as I tell you.
There you have it, folks.
She's used poor Zack
as a tool this whole time.
What a nasty thing to do.
You took that completely
out of context.
He's right, that's not
admissible evidence.
Well, I have the floor.
So you two shut it!
[groaning]
Order in this courtroom.
Are you finished now?
Or do you have more to say?
Oh, much more, Your Honor.
Actually, thanks to
the little witch here,
I was torn away from
the responsibility
of punishing sinners.
[EDDIE groaning]
[CATHY] Issac Foster was once
an illustrious criminal,
but Rachel found
a way to declaw him.
It was heartbreaking to watch.
I had to do something,
so I took matters
into my own hands.
And then, can you believe it?
This brat had the gall
to shoot me.
I'm a world-class prison guard.
Being outmaneuvered
and shot down
by a criminal
is just shameful.
You're a devastatingly cunning
and calculating evildoer,
wearing the guise
of an innocent girl.
I'm certain of it.
There's no way
you're not a witch.
I wasn't trying
to outsmart you--
Quiet, you whore!
[heavy breathing]
Would you mind showing the rest
of your video, Cathy?
Hmph.
Why, what are you getting at?
I just want us to hear
the whole story.
Oh, my.
Why are you making that face?
Looks pretty happy,
if you ask me.
That's right, Eddie.
Cathy was happy in that moment.
This is the stuff I'm good at.
Don't even try to fool me.
Now, let the record show,
that Miss Catherine Ward's
true nature is actually--
That's not it!
The truth is, I was more
infuriated than anything!
Because as disgusted
as I am with that girl,
her criminal mind thrills me!
[laughing]
That's your problem, not mine.
Leave it to the ultimate sinner
to heartlessly rip me away
from my life's calling
and say that it's my problem.
Then what manner of punishment
do you suggest?
I believe she deserves
something special.
And since this is a witch trial,
I say, we try, drowning,
♪
Not to brag,
but it's a splendid idea.
We could kill her quickly,
but this will be more fun.
Go on and scream for me, Rachel.
I wanna see your face
overwhelmed with terror.
Give me an even bigger rush than
when you aimed that gun at me.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid?
Come on, I want you to cry
for help as loud as you can.
What the hell?
How can you still have
that blank expression?
I want you to show me
how much you're suffering!
That's quite enough!
[shudders]
Father, wait.
I'm not done punishing her.
I didn't ask you to
administer her punishment.
Now stand aside.
But she needs to--
The next to give testimony
will be young Edward Mason.
Please give us
your personal account
regarding
the defendant's crimes.
Mm-hmm.
That won't be a problem
at all, Father.
I'll tell you what I love
and what I hate about her.
Then you may begin as soon
as you are ready.
Okay.
So, Rachel's a really cute girl.
She has the prettiest voice
in the world.
And best of all,
she's a lot like me.
You buried that bird that died
on Zack's floor, right?
[RACHEL]
Yes.
See?
We are a lot alike.
I knew we were made
for each other.
And she said she wanted to die,
so we both want the same thing.
I tried all kinds of stuff
to get her to like me.
I made her a nice grave
and wrote her letters.
I even filled up her coffin
with flowers.
But sadly...
none of it worked.
No matter what, she didn't
respond the way I wanted.
This is a courtroom, you twerp.
We didn't come to listen to your
little puppy-love sob-story.
Shut up. It's my turn!
Fine.
All I wanted was Rachel.
Every single thing
I did was for her.
But she didn't feel that way.
All she cared about was
what would make her happy.
You're so mean.
And cruel! Cruel!
You said you wanted
to be killed,
but you wouldn't give me
the joy of killing you.
Why is it all about you?
You're selfish
and you're stubborn,
and I just don't understand
why you won't let anybody
but Zack do it.
And on top of all that, you guys
left me in a grave to die!
Rejection's a part of life.
[EDDIE]
I do love graves,
but that wasn't
how I wanted it to turn out.
That was when I finally
understood
what the biggest difference
is between Rachel and me.
She doesn't know
what happiness is, so,
she won't let anybody be happy!
Don't you think that might
make you a witch?
-I'm not.
-You are, Rachel.
You deserve to die.
But not a nice death.
A painful one.
What's the matter?
Are you mad at me?
Come on.
Say something.
Why are you so quiet?
Please, I'll do anything.
Just don't ignore me.
Fine, then.
Go ahead and fall!
That's enough!
I'm sorry, sir.
But if she won't answer me,
I don't know what else to--
It's clear that the witch
has tainted your heart, Edward,
so the court has no
further use for your testimony.
No, wait. I'm not done.
I can see your fear
of the defendant,
is struggling to coexist
with your unwavering
affection for her.
Rachel.
Let me hear your voice.
Please, I'm begging you.
The next witness to testify
will be Dr. Daniel Dickens.
It's the moment
I've been waiting for.
Doctor.
Is there any more medicine?
You seem so relaxed, Rachel.
Aren't you happy
to see that I'm alive?
[GRAY]
Danny.
Are you planning to testify,
or just waste our time?
Of course I'm going
to testify, sir.
After all, I'm the only one
in the room
who knows the defendant
for who she truly is inside.
If I don't speak,
how will everyone know
what a charming young lady
she can be?
Though, if you ask me,
I think it's silly that I have
to explain something
that anyone with eyes can see.
All of you have been blind
to what makes her so special.
It all began
in the counseling room
where she and I met
for the first time.
A day I won't forget.
All my life I've been searching
for the perfect pair of peepers.
The kind that are dead,
but forever alive.
And that was when
I first saw her.
Thinking back on it now fills
my heart with happiness.
No other eyes in the world
have ever been so enchanting.
Like peaceful oases
in a dark void.
Their brilliant
yet muted blueness
absolutely stole my heart.
I knew as soon as I saw them.
Those peepers of hers,
living and lifeless at once,
were exactly
the priceless treasures
I'd searched for all along!
Anybody with a pair of eyes
like those has to be abnormal.
I'll agree with you on that.
Her soul is damned
beyond salvation!
We've heard
quite enough, Doctor.
Her soul is damned
beyond salvation!
Settle down!
Her soul is damned
beyond salvation!
[GRAY]
Danny!
And I'll tell you why,
it's because the soul
of Rachel Gardner--
[RACHEL]
Stop it.
Her soul can never be redeemed.
After all,
Rachel consumes
everything she sees.
She's merciless,
endlessly taking
from the people around her
in hopes of satisfying
her own emptiness.
All her soul can do is take.
Ah, those blue eyes.
Let me look into them.
Strikingly lovely.
Now, this is the real you.
Spend your days with me, Rachel.
I'll keep you safe.
I swear.
You're out of order, Danny.
[DANNY]
Sorry.
Have you completed
your testimony?
Well, if you're still curious
about her charms,
I would be happy to explain them
to you in deeper detail.
Hold your tongue.
I've heard everything
that I need to hear.
This witness is
hereby dismissed.
[DANNY]
Hmm.
Don't worry, Rachel.
Just remember what I said.
The true nature of your soul
is to steal from others,
not to be stolen away.
[shudders]
[GRAY] This concludes
the witness statements.
Now then, Rachel Gardner,
I have determined your fate.
The testimonies we've heard
have been most informative.
Dr. Danny's
was especially revealing.
And I suppose he has known you
longer than the other two.
He spoke nothing but the truth
and didn't refute
a single thing you said.
The man is desperately
infatuated with you.
Maybe, but that's not my fault.
He was the one who decided to--
Are you denying
that you were the one
who acted selfishly in all this?
Eddie's statement
illustrated it perfectly.
He claims you live according
to your own desires,
without any regard for others.
That's a lie.
Not to mention Catherine.
You got her to surrender
to your spell,
like the foul witch you are.
What a shame to see such
a proud woman reduced to that.
Stop it.
And now for the verdict.
Rachel Gardner is
found guilty of sorcery.
I sentence her
to be burned alive.
You're wrong!
♪