[ZACK gasps]
[MALE REPORTER A] Once there,
police found a disturbing scene.
The two had knife
and bullet wounds,
suggesting it
was a murder.
It appears the two
died a week ago,
but perhaps the
most striking detail
was that they'd been
crudely sewn together.
Hang on. They were
sewn together?
Standing near them was
their child, Rachel Gardner.
The girl was seemingly unharmed.
She was escorted
to safety,
but her behavior suggests
a state of confusion
that would indicate the child
may have been present
for this gruesome event.
[ZACK gasps]
♪
[ZACK]
That asshole!
I think during today's session,
I'd like to go into more detail.
There's nothing for you
to be scared of, okay?
Oh, you're making eye contact!
You really do have some
beautiful peepers!
One of my eyes
is artificial, you see.
I was born with an empty socket.
My mother was deeply
troubled by it. In fact,
it disturbed her so much,
that her own eyes went dark.
In the end, I couldn't
even see myself in them.
But despite that, I still
loved my mother very much.
Her eyes were so precious to me.
Tell me, did you hate
your parents, Rachel?
No, sir.
[DANNY]
But if that's true,
how could you possibly
have done that to them?
What do you mean?
[DANNY] You cut them up
and sewed them together.
Oh, right. Because...
I wanted to have a family.
[DANNY] Was there something
that pushed you to do it?
[RACHEL] I found a puppy in
the alley near our house.
[RACHEL]
It was so tiny and helpless.
I wanted to take it home
with me and keep it forever.
But I decided I should probably
try to get permission from
my mom and dad.
But when I came in...
[RACHEL'S DAD] I'm the one
who pays the damn bills!
[RACHEL'S MOM]
You may be a cop,
but you're still
a useless drunk.
I have no respect for you.
[RACHEL'S DAD]
That's enough!
[RACHEL'S MOM]
What are you doing?
They sound mad. I wonder
if they'll listen.
‐‐[RACHEL'S MOM shouts]
‐‐[crashing]
[gasps]
Where've you been? It's late!
Quiet as always, huh?
Somethin' wrong
with your head, kid?
Hey, um...
What, are you
gonna nag me too?
Ugh.
[RACHEL'S MOM]
Hey.
What?
[RACHEL'S MOM]
Do you get some kind of joy
out of making me suffer?
Ha!
Really? You're laughing
at me now?
You know what? I'm just
gonna go buy my happiness.
[RACHEL'S MOM]
Oh, it's that easy?
Then why don't you pick up
some happiness for me too,
while you're at it?
I'm in a living hell,
so I could sure use a little!
[RACHEL'S DAD]
Shut your mouth!
[RACHEL'S MOM grunts]
[RACHEL'S DAD]
Heh.
Hey, Dad, listen. I have a‐‐
Can it! I don't
have time for you!
But, I‐‐
[RACHEL'S MOM]
You're disgusting.
[RACHEL'S DAD grunts]
[RACHEL'S MOM] You're tearing
this family to pieces
with those filthy
hands of yours.
You've ruined my life,
are you satisfied now?
Hey, um...
[RACHEL'S MOM] All that alcohol
has destroyed your body
and your mind!
Pfft!
[RACHEL'S MOM] You've gone
and driven yourself crazy!
[laughs]
Stop laughin'!
I said stop, dammit!
‐‐[laughing continues]
‐‐[smacking]
Excuse me?
Me? Crazy? That's rich.
[RACHEL]
Dad?
[RACHEL'S MOM
continues laughing]
[RACHEL]
Um. Can I talk to you?
Mom. One second, please?
[RACHEL'S MOM
continues laughing]
I'll show him. Just wait.
Then he'll be sorry.
Mom, listen.
Now what!
[RACHEL] There's something I've
been trying to ask you about.
Get out. I don't have the
time to deal with you.
But you get mad when I don't
ask permission first, so,
I just want to see if‐‐
I said get out!
[laughs] Even my own
daughter won't listen to me!
You know, it's because of you
I can't just walk away
from this nightmare!
Damn, I hate you, Rachel!
Go to your room!
If I do what you tell me,
does that mean you'll
let me talk to you?
Just get up there!
[RACHEL] I couldn't
convince either one of them
to hear me out. After that...
I went back to see the puppy.
But this time, its little
body was trembling.
And then it bit me, real hard.
Everything after that
is kind of a blur.
The next thing I knew, I was
in my room fixing the puppy.
[DANNY]
Fixing it?
[DANNY] Do you remember
anything after that part?
Well, let's see.
That whole day was
really complicated.
[RACHEL]
There you go. Good dog!
Now you can stay
with me forever.
It's your fault that our
daughter turned out to be
messed up in the head,
you crazy bitch!
You're wrong! Don't blame me!
There's nothing to be scared of.
Let me go check on them.
[RACHEL'S MOM] The only
reason we're messed up
is because of you!
[RACHEL'S DAD]
What'd you say?
[RACHEL'S MOM]
You ruin everything you touch,
‐‐you can't do anything right!
‐‐[RACHEL'S DAD] Shut up!
[RACHEL'S MOM]
Wait, what are you doing?
Why do you have that thing?
No, stay away from me!
Stop! Stop!
Oh, I see. And what
about after that?
[RACHEL'S DAD grunts]
You saw, didn't you?
[gasps]
I had to. I never asked
for such a pathetic life.
I just couldn't
take it any longer.
Everything in this
house pisses me off!
[RACHEL'S DAD grunts] So all
I need to do now, is kill you!
[gasps]
[RACHEL'S DAD]
Where you goin'? Come back!
[RACHEL'S DAD laughs]
[door handle rattles]
Everything is fine.
No need to be afraid.
[crashing]
You think I've gone crazy too,
don't you, Rachel?
[RACHEL whimpers]
[RACHEL'S DAD] But you're a
hell of a lot crazier than me,
talkin' to that
nasty old thing.
You were the one who
killed it, weren't you?
You slashed it open, stitched
its belly back together,
and sewed its mouth shut.
Did that make you feel good?
[RACHEL]
It's mine now,
and that means I need
to take good care of it.
[RACHEL'S DAD laughs]
[RACHEL'S DAD]
Stupid. No one needs you.
[RACHEL'S DAD] You're not
good for anything, Rachel.
[clicking]
Where'd you get that thing?
I'm your father,
you better tell the truth!
It belonged to Mom.
Huh? Oh really? That bitch
was hiding a gun from me?
[RACHEL]
Hey, Dad?
Yeah, what?
I want us... to become
a perfect family.
It's okay... I know how I
can make everything right.
[RACHEL] And that was when I
decided to sew my Mom and Dad's
bodies together.
Since Dad's arm was no good,
I just replaced it
with a stuffed one.
And my Mom looked sad,
so I stitched up her mouth
to make it seem like
she was smiling.
I made myself the
perfect set of parents.
[DANNY]
Ah, I see.
It was nice.
The three of us played with
our new puppy together.
But then, when the policemen
came to take them away from me,
It upset me.
You were sad. I understand that.
More than you know.
Could I ask you...
one more question?
While you were staying
at that orphanage,
another small animal died.
Can you tell me
what happened to it?
Were you the one who killed it?
I heard you were in charge
of taking care of it.
Um... Yes. It really
meant a lot to me.
But it was still no use.
What was no use?
[RACHEL]
Well, I wanted to keep it.
I wanted to be able
to call it mine.
But for some reason,
nothing worked.
I couldn't have it.
[DANNY]
That's very interesting.
Let's think about that, Rachel.
Do you wish you had more things
that you could call your own?
My mother, she took her life,
all because of me.
My eye killed her. It's the
whole reason she's gone.
And your eyes,
they look just like hers
did the last time I saw her.
Endlessly dark and silent,
and so beautiful, too!
Oh, how I adore those peepers.
Lifeless and brilliant
at the same time!
They'll forever be‐‐
So by watchin' this tape,
does that mean I know everything
about Ray? What's the point
of showin' me all that crap?
Man, I can't wait to
get my hands on that
eyeball‐crazy sicko!
[ZACK]
Open up, already!
[DANNY]
There's no need to be so rough.
Come in, it's unlocked.
[ZACK grunts]
Hey, Zack.
Okay, look. First off,
tell me something.
Do you kill everyone
who comes to this floor
like all the other clowns here?
Jeez, Ray. Answer already!
Do ya or don't ya?
[gunshot]
Please be respectful
of my patient,
she's been through a lot.
You little‐‐
Well, well. You know
the whole story now.
[ZACK] That was some pretty
sick shit you made me watch.
I do apologize. Counseling can
be upsetting work.
[ZACK] I didn't come to
hear you complain.
[DANNY]
Huh?
I still want Ray to
answer my question.
I'll ask you again.
Do you kill everyone who
comes to this floor, or not?
And if so, does that mean
you're gonna kill me, too?
‐‐No, Zack. I just‐‐
‐‐[DANNY] Ah‐ah‐ahh!
It isn't nice to lie.
I think it's much better if
you tell him the truth now!
Okay?
Or maybe I should tell him.
Yes, Zack. Everything
is exactly as you‐‐
Please, stop it!
Too bad. Might as well move on.
He saw it all.
You can't change that.
When she got here,
Reverend Gray made
Rachel the resident angel
of this floor at my request.
However, she underwent a
serious mental breakdown,
and all because of
that Bible over there.
You were always so
calm and reserved.
Why did that cause
you to lose your mind?
I wanted to reach perfection,
like it says to.
That's the way it had to be.
But the Bible says
something else, too.
That the kind of person I am,
is the kind that can
never be forgiven.
Precisely. That's why
you were trying so hard
to get Zack to
kill you, right?
Rachel. I think you may
already know this, but,
no matter how much
you study the Bible
or recognize your shortcomings,
That feeling in the pit of your
stomach won't go away.
[DANNY] Oh, this is so
wonderfully awful!
What do you think, Zach?
Do you understand now?
It's time for you to choose.
You can do nothing
and die right here,
or you can give up
on being her God
and leave this
building alone.
So, what's your call?
Is this guy tellin' the truth
about your past or not?
I told you, she's been
deceiving you this entire time!
I asked her. Have you been
keepin' all this from me?
Don't go, Zack.
I need you to keep on
being my God, alright?
Makin' my own decisions
is hard enough,
don't ask me to make yours too.
Sorry, kid. I'm not your God,
and I'm never gonna be.
[RACHEL gasps]
You're absolutely right, you're
just a worthless human scumbag!
Which means you can go
back to being your old self,
isn't that nice? And I'll
happily grant any wish you have.
I've done terrible things,
so I'm unclean,
and that hasn't changed.
But knowing that I've sinned,
doesn't make it go away.
I'm not sure what
else I should do,
now that it's already happened.
So, Zack, you... you're really
going to stop being my God?
That's right.
But... I want one.
[RACHEL]
A God that's mine!
Come on, that gun
isn't loaded, Ray.
Oh, I loaded it earlier!
[ZACK gasps]
[ZACK]
What?!
[DANNY] My, look at that!
Just when I thought those
peepers of yours couldn't
be more lovely!
Ah! Rachel, dear. It's too much!
And Zack, one thing. I'm sorry,
but I can't let you go free.
You see, my number‐one
priority now is fulfilling
her every desire!
Are you sure you
want to kill me?!
[grunts]
Hold up!
I‐It's over.
I'm becoming a slave to
those immaculate blue eyes!
I'll make sure she gets what
she wants, no matter what.
[gasps]
[yells]
[ZACK growls]
You bitch!
Quit runnin' from me!
[gasps]
Don't mess with that,
you'll burn the place down!
[RACHEL]
I see you still hate fire.
Cut the crap!
That's enough, Ray!
[ZACK]
Damn it!
Stop messin' with me!
This isn't funny!
You can run around all you want,
but it won't fix anything.
[ZACK]
Go on, shoot.
[RACHEL]
You're about to die, Zack.
[ZACK]
If you plan to kill me...
...then I'll just have to beat
you to the punch, won't I?
That isn't enough, not now.
I still believe it's
right for me to die.
That someone needs
to take my life.
But since I'm unclean, God
doesn't even want me anymore.
He has no use for me.
[RACHEL]
No one needs me.
Even so, you're the one who
said you were going to kill me.
You swore to.
And then, when I found
out there was no God,
you gave me purpose by
becoming my replacement.
Ray, look, I told you.
I'm no God.
Yeah. I know that.
When my lie was exposed...
[RACHEL] ...the new God that
I had set up, also died.
[ZACK grunts]
[ZACK]
You're never gonna listen to me.
You just hear whatever you
want and block the rest out.
All you ever do is
run away, isn't it?
You owe me an answer!
[DANNY] It would appear that she
has nothing more to say to you.
[ZACK gasps]
Your guard is down,
that is quite out of
character for you, Zack.
Watch it.
I'm the one holding
the gun. And Rachel?
Usually you keep things a
bit more simple than this.
Why don't we wrap it up?
Of course, we are dealing with a
monster, so we can't be sloppy.
But don't worry, dear.
If you shoot him in
the head from here,
there's no hope of survival.
‐‐Go ahead.
‐‐You're a friggin' nutcase.