You’re smiling.
Are you happy?
Yeah, kinda.
Aren’t you in a good mood too?
[chuckles]
-[RACHEL] Yeah.
-[elevator dings]
Looks like we’re here.
Are you ready?
Come on, Zack.
[metal clanging]
[RACHEL]
Oh no. Zack. Zack!
[doors rattle]
♪
Zack, please be okay. Wake up!
[ZACK groaning]
All right. I’m awake.
Oh, thank goodness.
Are we on the next floor?
Well then,
let’s get this over with.
-[ZACK groans]
-[blood pools]
No, wait! Don’t move!
[ZACK]
Eh, it’s no big deal.
It’s only a little scratch.
[chokes, groans]
Don’t try to stand up,
you’re bleeding too much!
Didn’t I tell you earlier
to just worry about yourself?
You’re hurt!
Yeah, so?
Wait a sec.
What’s with the face?
Somehow, you look even
weirder than usual.
[ZACK gasping]
Oh no!
[RACHEL]
He’s still breathing.
He just passed out.
But I’m not strong enough
to carry him any farther.
[sighs]
♪
Wait here, okay?
I’ll find you some medicine
or something.
[RACHEL]
I can be useful to you. I swear!
♪
[door creaks open]
-[organ music plays]
-[RACHEL gasps]
[gasps]
[RACHEL] There's something
really strange about this room.
What’s that?
Some sort of purple smoke.
It smells kind of sweet.
I have to hurry. Zack.
-[music stops]
-[RACHEL gasps]
That’s weird.
It’s gone.
[gasps]
♪
“The ones God desires,
"must be clean
and devoid of falsehood.
"So, who are you?
Ask yourself that question.”
“Are you a desirable sacrifice?
Or are you an angel?”
“Or, even
if you are neither,
"if you truly hope
to find God’s salvation...
reveal and confess
all your sins.”
I’m Rachel Gardner.
[crumbling]
[organ music plays]
[whooshing]
[gasps]
A mirror?
I don’t understand.
I can see my reflection.
It’s me. Just me.
[cracking]
[shattering]
[glass tinkles]
So I need to collect
my own pieces
and know my true self.
[whooshing]
[RACHEL]
“Spit out your sins.
"If you don’t know...
tear up and drag them out”?
So weird.
I wonder where all this
writing is coming from.
[GRAY] "Can you recognize
your sins, Rachel Gardner?"
[gasps]
[GRAY]
"If they are blacked out,
"then, the only explanation
is that you have
done so yourself.”
“Did you erase them?
Or did you not realize
that they were sins?”
If you’ve lost your own sins,
then make them
complete again.
You must accept every sin
that flows forth!
This is your Confessional.
Who’s there?
[GRAY]
Spit out your sins.
Accept your sins.
But I--
[GRAY]
Now, tear up and drag them out.
Tear up and drag them out!
[voices joining]
So I have to tear up my sins.
And then drag them out.
Is that the answer?
Tear up...
and drag them out!
[EDDIE screaming]
It’s three sheep. A family?
[RACHEL'S MOM]
Ray. Ray. Ray!
Why don’t you come closer?
What’s wrong with you?
Aren’t you glad to see us?
[RACHEL]
It doesn’t matter.
The only thing I need
to do right now is save Zack.
[blade slices]
[BOTH screaming]
I’ll tear up my sins.
And this will be my proof.
This place is weird, too.
But I don’t have time
to look around.
[gasps]
Why are my footprints red?
Is it blood, or what?
I shouldn’t get distracted.
[organ music plays]
[RACHEL]
What’s back there?
[door rumbles heavily]
Where is that music coming from?
♪
“What is it that you need
to confess?
“And are you certain
that your heart truly desires
"to be redeemed from sin?
“Can you bear to lift up
your iniquities
"to the Lord,
as they are now?
“More importantly,
"you lack the ability
to recognize a sinful heart.
“If you wish to be saved,
reveal your impurities here,
in this room.”
But what does that mean?
[gasps]
If my sins are in this vial...
♪
[hissing]
[loud discordant music]
It’s so loud!
My head.
It hurts.
[music stops]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
♪
[gulps]
Tell the truth.
Who are you?
Speak wisely, young sinner.
Answer me.
I’m sorry, but, who are you?
I am the priest who watches
over this righteous church.
My name is Gray.
You’re really a priest?
It’s your turn
to answer my question.
Okay, then.
I’m Rachel Gardner.
I’m guessing
you must be the person
who’s in charge of this floor?
Essentially.
I suppose that’s a fair
statement from your perspective.
[RACHEL gasps]
[GRAY]
You needn’t be frightened of me.
I’ve yet to determine
what sort of person
you truly are, Miss Gardner.
I will not decide your fate
until that has been done.
Any judgement I could pass
upon you at this juncture
would be a blind one.
Now, what brings you here?
Uh, I need something
that stops bleeding.
Ah, yes.
An antihemorrhagic.
And I assume you’re seeking this
medicine to help young Zack?
[RACHEL gasps]
-[RACHEL] Wait, you know Zack?
-[GRAY] Naturally.
I know more about
the residents in this building
than they know about themselves.
Unfortunately, I don’t believe
there’s anything here
you can use to treat him.
However,
if there was something,
I imagine you’d find it
on Danny’s floor.
[RACHEL]
But...
how do I get down there?
[GRAY]
You wish to go back down?
Yes.
[GRAY] Then your task
will be quite simple.
You may visit
the lower floors
provided I’m with you.
You mean,
that’s the only option?
[GRAY]
Yes, precisely.
I’ll be happy
to show you the way.
How do I know I can trust you
and this isn’t a trap?
I can assure you, I never lie.
If you accept my conditions,
I’ll need you to undergo
a bit of a trial
before we’re on our way.
A trial?
[GRAY]
In here, one must be tested.
My intention is to discover
what kind of person you are.
Make your decision
from the heart.
I do not require
an immediate answer.
I’ll be waiting right here
in the sanctuary.
Speak with me again once
you’re certain of what you want.
[RACHEL]
Hmm.
Well, in that case,
I’d like some more time.
[RACHEL] This priest is
the only lead I have,
but I should go
check on Zack first.
♪
-[door rumbling]
-[gasps]
That’s funny.
I think some rooms
are missing.
[gasps]
Zack!
[ZACK groans]
I said stay put.
[ZACK]
Ray, where’d ya wander off to?
I was looking for something
to stop the bleeding.
Huh?
Why the hell would
you go by yourself?
You’re lucky that you
didn’t get slaughtered.
-[groaning]
-I know,
but I couldn’t
carry you any farther,
so I had no choice.
And besides,
you had fallen asleep.
[ZACK] So why didn’t you
wake me up, dumbass?
I couldn’t do that, okay?
[ZACK groans]
Fine, whatever.
-You find anything good?
-Not yet.
Except, someone told me
there might be something useful
on Danny’s floor.
Danny?
You know that’s
the opposite way, dontcha?
Yeah, but...
-[groaning]
-Don’t move!
You’re still bleeding,
you need to sit down!
[ZACK]
Shut up. I’m not a little kid!
[ZACK panting]
[ZACK growls]
My scythe is so heavy.
What the hell?
I could lift it fine before.
Stop it or you’ll die!
It’s heavy because your body’s
trying to tell you
you’re at your limit.
Would ya quit talkin’ about
how I’m gonna die already?
Come on.
You and I both know I wouldn’t
kick the bucket that easy!
[RACHEL]
Let me help.
Please, Zack.
I’m begging you.
I want to be useful to you.
Oh, you’re beggin’ me now?
Damn, you must not
know me at all
if you think that’s gonna
make a lick o’ difference.
I’m serious.
[ZACK scoffs]
[ZACK groans]
So? You really think
you can get down there?
[RACHEL]
Well, I have to try, at least.
Goin’ down is one thing.
I just have a feelin’
you won’t make it back up.
I’m sure I’ll manage somehow.
Go for it, then.
I guess I’d be nothin’
but dead weight
if I tried to come with you now.
[RACHEL]
Zack.
Come on, Ray,
I know it’s the truth.
Listen.
If you can honestly promise me
you’ll make it back here
without dyin’,
I suppose I’ll let ya leave.
I’m gonna... sleep.
Sure.
♪
[gasps]
Since you’re goin’ anyway,
could ya stop on my floor
while you’re at it?
Y’know, B6.
The one where we first met
and I almost killed ya.
There’s somethin’ I want you
to bring back here for me.
When you get there,
go into my room
and find my knife, okay?
-Okay.
-[ZACK snoring softly]
♪
[footsteps approaching]
[GRAY]
Welcome back.
Have you decided?
[RACHEL]
I can’t let Zack die.
If there’s even the slightest
chance to save him,
I have to take it.
I want to go to Danny’s floor.
Zack really needs
some medicine.
So, yes.
I’ll take your test.
Aha! As I thought.
But, you have to swear
you won’t do
anything to hurt Zack.
[GRAY]
Of course.
-[gasps]
-[organ music]
[RACHEL]
That scent again.
[GRAY] Shall we be
on our way now, Rachel Gardner?
[RACHEL gasps]
Goodness, I didn’t realize
you were so determined
to keep me away from Zack.
You needn’t glare so.
I swore I wouldn’t harm him.
I do wonder what would
make you place
such importance on saving him.
Losing Zack would be a problem.
A problem?
I’m afraid I don’t follow.
Zack swore to God
that he was going to kill me.
If he dies, he won’t be able to.
I see.
So that’s the reason, is it?
How quaint.
A bizarre agreement, though,
to say the least.
[RACHEL]
The smell.
It’s coming from him.
[RACHEL gasps]
Well, Miss Gardner,
it appears we’ve arrived.
That didn’t take very long.
Now, I believe it’s time
for you to be tested.
But, you were supposed
to take me to Danny’s floor!
[GRAY] I would like you to
complete a trial on each level.
-[chair clatters]
-[RACHEL sighs]
Fear not, it shouldn’t
be too strenuous.
All you must do is turn
on the electricity
that powers the prison elevator.
And how can I be sure
the mechanism’s
really in there somewhere?
Cathy wanted several
machines on this floor.
I’d say it’s more
than likely you’ll find it.
She was quite gifted
at using them
to manipulate
the minds of her victims.
In my opinion, hers was
an effective method
of leading people
to repent their sin
and strive for salvation.
She had a tendency
to be a bit of a spendthrift,
but one might say
that was just part of her charm.
Now that Cathy’s
no longer with us,
it stands to reason
that a few “lost souls”
may be wandering this floor.
[pages rustling]
Well then, let’s commence
with our test.
Do your best,
and may the light
of salvation guide your path.
[RACHEL]
There’s no time to lose.
♪
[panting]
[gasps]
There it is!
[growling]
[PRISONERS moaning, growling]
[gasps]
[PRISONERS moaning]
[RACHEL]
Ugh, they’re holding me back.
-[gunshot]
-[body thuds]
[door slams]
[PRISONERS growling]
[PRISONERS snarling]
[RACHEL]
The gun room!
[gasps]
Wait, where’s her body?
That doesn’t matter right now.
-[door locks]
-[beeping]
[moaning, snarling]
[RACHEL] She could see
the whole floor from here.
[whirring]
I’ll shoot them.
I have to.
They shouldn’t have
stood in my way.
[rapid gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
♪