[NARRATOR] Revolutionary
Calendar, year 228.
It's been seven years
since Japan was invaded
by the Holy Empire of
Britannian and renamed Area 11.
To stem the spread of Britannian
power in western Eurasia,
the United Republic of Europia
carried out commando raids
with Alexanders
piloted by Elevens.
Leila Malcal and
General Smilas were attacked
while traveling
from HQ in Paris.
Their assailants were
a young gang of Elevens
who lived in the
Paris underground.
They nearly
kidnapped the general.
However, their plan was
foiled by Akito, singlehandedly.
Leila promised
to spare the lives
of Ryo and his two friends
under one condition--
that they join her
wZERO assault unit.
[VELAINES] In the name
of the heavens, the Earth,
and the Holy Spirit. I, Duke
Velaines, decree the following:
Shin Hyuga Shaing
shall be named commander
of the Holy Order of Michael,
one of the Four Great
Orders that is bound
to serve and protect the Empire
we now know as Euro-Britannia.
Lord Shang, if you would
approach the throne.
[CROWD]
All hail Britannia!
[cheering]
[ASHLEY]
This'll be exciting.
Why's that, Master?
If I fight alongside
Lord Shaing,
I can take the world.
I'm ready to see
some action, y'know?
The late Manfredi was
a dear friend of mine.
There's no way that he
would ever take his own life.
I can assure you, for I knew
him better than anyone else.
Rest assured, sir, I shall
deal with the Ghost of Hannibal,
and I will make certain
that my Order of Michael
works to restore the honor
of your Order of Raphael.
[YOUNG SHIN]
Die.
Akito. Die now.
[YOUNG AKITO]
No!
[YOUNG SHIN]
Die.
[YOUNG AKITO]
No!
[YOUNG SHIN]
Die!
[whispering voices]
[LEILA]
This place has a silence to it
that makes the bustle of
the city seem like a dream.
Revolutionary Calendar,
year 228, Prairial the seventh.
It's been a month since our
operation center was relocated
from Paris to the
remote Weiswolf Castle.
I have yet to hear from General
HQ regarding mission plans.
While I enjoy
the peace and quiet,
I fear that it will
not last very long.
[LEILA]
This peace will soon be replaced
with the bloody cries of war.
Akito.
[SOPHIE] So tell me, how are
things progressing, Joe?
[JOE] Without a hitch the data
transfer from the neuro device
should finish right
on schedule, Dr. Randle.
[SOPHIE]
Anna will be glad to hear it.
[JOE]
You want a lolli?
Not right now, thanks.
[JOE]
You sure? They're delicious.
What about the other three?
How do their E.E.G.s look?
Pretty promising, if you ask me.
I realize that
they're kinda scary,
but they've all got AAA
compatibility ratings.
It's amazing.
They seem to be a
good match for Akito, too.
What's the BRS
success probability?
I would say it's around
eighty-seven-percent.
Oh really?
Yeah, and they're not
even parents or siblings.
Strange, huh?
Yeah it is. Very strange.
[AYANO]
Hey, Ryo.
How long do you plan
to stick around here?
[RYO] As long as we continue
to get free room and board.
And y'know, I dig how
it looks like an old castle
but it's all modern
and high-tech inside.
Plus there's not
a rat to be seen.
Right, Yukiya?
Yep, that's true.
What'd Ayano call them? "Icky"?
You realize they're gonna
slap uniforms on us
and send us to war, right?
[RYO]
Don't get so worked up.
We both know the real
reason Ayano's freaking out
is 'cause they
confiscated her dagger
Truth.
Yeah, so what?
It belongs to me!
They've no right!
How could a
Japanese citizen work for--
Hey, Yukiya, have
you finished setting up
our next game yet?
Yeah, just about.
What does that mean? Tell me!
Look, don't worry, you'll
find out soon enough.
C'mon, just tell me guys!
[YUKIYA]
Ayano.
All you need to know
is that we belong here.
Trust me.
[HAMMEL] Are you
sure it's a good idea
to keep those Eleven...
Er... Excuse me,
I mean those Japanese
kids running loose, sir?
[CLAUS] Why? Has there been
a problem, Major Hammel?
[HAMMEL] You do realize
that they're criminals?
They attempted to
abduct General Smilas.
[CLAUS]
I know, I know.
Under normal circumstances,
they would be executed.
That's right!
Don't you think they should
be brought to justice, sir?
Commander Malcal
brought them here,
and said she wanted
to use them somehow.
So why not?
I mean, General Smilas did
give his approval, after all.
If they were to take
any hostile action,
it'd be difficult to subdue
them with nothing more
than my special forces team.
You worry too much.
There's no way
they could outsmart
the elaborate
security system here.
Besides, Major, it's good for us
to have people like them around.
People who won't be
missed if they disappear
or perhaps even die.
[AYANO]
I'm so sick of those simulators.
[YUKIYA]
At least they're comfy.
They're better than the
machine that spins you around.
Yeah, didn't you
puke on that one?
It's not my fault I'm
that I get motion sickness.
A cat?
[YUKIYA]
That's why there's no rats.
[EARL ORLEANS]
May I offer my congratulations
on your son's success?
The Shaing family's
position is now secure.
Why, thank you, Earl Orleans.
That's nice of you to say.
To be honest, we owe it
all to the late Sir Manfredi.
Pardon me ma'am, but where
is the party's guest of honor?
I've been looking everywhere.
Well, I'm not sure.
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him for a while.
[SHIN]
Come in, Alice.
You don't want Mother
to worry, do you?
[ALICE]
I hate these silly parties.
I don't know a
single person in there.
Here's an idea.
Why don't you and I take a
drive to the coast tomorrow?
Wouldn't that be fun?
Please, promise me
we'll go, Brother.
I have to be at the Order of
Michael's review ceremony.
Awww... That's tomorrow?
[SHIN] Yes, and I won't
be back for some time.
I'm sorry.
But I promise as soon
as I have leave,
I'll spend some
time with you, Alice.
[ALICE]
You mean it?
[beeping]
Hello?
[CLAUS] Sorry for calling
at this hour, Commander.
I didn't wake you up, did I?
Oh no, I'm working late.
[CLAUS]
Good on you.
Anyway, I thought you
should know operation orders
were just received from HQ.
[CLAUS] I'll bring them
over to you right away.
You can unseal them there.
[CLAUS]
Another suicide mission...
[coughs] I mean,
we've been tasked with another
difficult mission, Commander.
Well, according to this,
they're moving up the
Warsaw garrison force.
But aren't they
for internal matters?
I can only assume that
the latest public opinion poll
rattled the government bigwigs.
They know that if they can't
keep the populace distracted
by what's going on elsewhere,
it'll buy them time
to cover their own butts.
[LEILA]
And so they've decided to have
the Wyvern Squad drop
inside of enemy lines?!
[CLAUS]
Well, to put it bluntly,
they're going to
be used as decoys.
They're sacrificial pawns.
They don't stand a
chance against the enemy.
They don't have the
manpower needed
to carry out a
mission like this!
You can't just disobey
their orders, can you?
You're going to have to think
outside of the box, Commander.
Sound reasoning won't help you.
I suppose that
you have no choice.
Here's the thing,
if you want those Elevens
to come back in one piece,
you'll have to think of a
way to make that happen.
It's your duty as the Commander.
[LEILA] Lieutenant Hyuga,
it's good to see you again.
Thank you for meeting with me.
Well, you ordered me to be here.
No need for pleasantries.
You're right, I did.
Have a seat and
we'll get started.
May I offer you some tea?
It's a fantastic blend
with a lovely aroma.
Is this about those three kids?
Yes. I was hoping that
I might get your opinion
on the matter, Lieutenant Hyuga.
I'm sorry, here.
I'm a bit dubious.
Do you really think
they'll follow orders
and march into battle for you?
I think they've
accepted their fate.
That's simply what you
want to see, Commander.
That isn't the reality.
If they leave,
they'd be putting their
lives in grave danger.
[AKITO]
And why is that?
Because they're criminals?
Or because they are Elevens?
[LEILA]
I only meant that--
[AKITO]
No, it's all right.
I'd rather you speak
the unvarnished truth.
I don't want to waste any time.
I can only assume they
know what you have in mind.
In that case...
Be careful.
You can be sure
they're looking for an exit.
[ANNA]
You're planning on using drones.
I'll admit
I think using unmanned machines
in combat is a great idea.
But with our current AI system.
I doubt it'll live up
to your expectations.
They'd have to to react to
their targets instantly, right?
But that level of artificial
intelligence doesn't exist yet.
[CHLOE] Being in the
military's a lot harder
than I thought it'd be,
eh, Sergeant Hilda?
[HILDA] I thought I was getting
a cushy civil service job.
Guess not.
Yeah.
I thought that, too.
If we stick with it,
maybe we'll become
Technical Officers someday.
We cut the time down
by point-zero-five seconds!
It's a new record!
Seems that the 25D
unit worked like a charm.
[ANNA] Hello, ladies.
Is the upload complete yet?
[CHLOE]
All done, Boss.
We're running the final checks.
[HILDA] It's working
really well now, ma'am.
And it's all thanks
to Akito's data.
Good to hear.
It looks like this will help us
roll out the Type 02.
[YUKIYA]
Hey, Ayano, what time is it?
[AYANO]
Hmm? It's 3:02.
Wow, it's already three?
I'm kinda hungry.
What about you, Ryo?
Yeah, I guess I could eat.
Do you wanna head down to
the cafeteria for a quick bite?
Nah, have you ever
tried their snacks?
So gross.
[RYO] Then why don't
you hold out until dinner?
[YUKIYA] Yeah, you're right,
I'm not that hungry.
I'm sure I can
tough it out till then.
It's probably for the best.
We've got more simulator
training later today.
Eat too much now
and you'll be puking.
And there we go.
Okay, we're in the clear now.
Attaboy, Yukiya!
All right, you guys.
Let's get started!
It's not like I know
anything about it.
[MALE TECH 2A]
Major Hammel.
Anything to report?
Be sure to keep an eye
on those new wZERO recruits.
[MALE TECH 2B]
We've been watching, sir.
But there's nothing new
to report at the moment.
[ANNA] You've always been
such a workaholic, Leila.
You need to relax
and unwind sometimes.
We can't let this beautiful
garden go to waste, now can we?
[ANNA sighs]
I think we've got a problem.
[LEILA]
What is it, Anna?
[ANNA]
Up there. Look, on the ledge.
Isn't that your kitty cat?
Eliza!
[YUKIYA] I managed to
hack into the main server.
I've got the security cameras
playing looped footage
of us hanging out in this room.
Even better...
I also tweaked these.
I loaded them with fake data
that'll allow us to pass
through their security.
[LEILA]
I don't understand
how she could've
gotten out of my room.
What?
A secret passage?
[YUKIYA]
Welcome back.
Akito Hyuga.
[AKITO] That a handmade
bomb you've got there?
[YUKIYA]
Don't come any closer.
Akito.
You'll never let
my friends leave.
That's why I've decided
to die and take you with me.
You've gotta be kidding me!
There aren't any
Knightmares in here?
These're cockpits.
They must be down there.
[YUKIYA]
You know, you and I.
We've got a lot more in
common than you might think.
Let's have a chat before we die.
[AKITO]
Get it over with,
before the special forces
squad shows up.
I'm not worried about that.
They're busy watching a virtual
reality show I constructed.
But enough about them.
Take a look at this.
What do you think?
Ugly, isn't it?
I've got plenty more scars
where that came from.
Know how I got them?
[AKITO]
I couldn't care less.
[YUKIYA]
Aw c'mon, don't be like that
why don't you try
having a little fun?
I mean, you are about to die.
[sighs]
You're a tough audience.
Look, I'll throw it
in free of charge.
My parting gift to you.
Three years ago.
I lived in Amsterdam's
Japanese ghetto.
The adults' sense of inferiority
and discontent trickled down
and infected the youth.
The kids took their
frustrations out on those
who were weaker than them.
The Japanese persecuting
the Japanese.
But I fought back.
They deserved to die so
I took them out with a bang.
I don't give a rat's ass about
the Japanese, the "Elevens."
The world's better
off without them.
I escaped the ghetto.
But in order to
avoid the police,
I had to stay
underground in the sewers.
[YUKIYA] That's where
I met Ryo and his gang.
For the first time in my life,
I had friends I could trust.
They're the closest
thing I have to family.
Which is why I won't let
any more of them die.
I'll do anything
to protect them.
What makes you think
that going into battle
means certain death?
I'm still alive, aren't I?
[YUKIYA]
That's true, rumor has it
you survived by using your
squad mates as human shields.
[AKITO]
Only one way to know for sure.
And that's to
come fight with me.
There's one of me
and three of you.
You have the advantage.
[YUKIYA]
I hadn't thought of that.
But you're right. Hahahaha!
Akito, you're
an interesting guy.
There aren't gonna be
any communications cables
out here in the forest.
Freaking Yukiya!
Are you heading
back to the castle?
I'll show you the
way if you tell me
what your friends are up to.
Talk to me!
I promise I'm on your side!
Like hell you are!
You're planning to use us
as disposable pawns!
[LEILA]
No, that's not true!
Just hear me out.
I want to ensure your safety
and I've found a way to do--
[AYANO]
Shut up!
You've never even been on the
battlefield before, have you?
[AYANO]
How many of us have to die?
Tell me,
how many Elevens have been
killed in your stupid campaign?
[LEILA]
No one else will die.
I'll see to that myself.
I'll be there.
I'll fight beside you.
Damn it!
[LEILA]
Go ahead.
[CLAUS]
It's Lieutenant Colonel Warwick.
Do you read me, Commander?
[LEILA]
Yes, something wrong?
[CLAUS]
Well, I couldn't help but notice
that you're on your way
to the launch site.
So... has something
happened with the Elevens?
[LEILA]
Why do you ask?
[CLAUS] Well, the video
surveillance feed
of their room cut out
suddenly and...
...we're not quite sure
what to make of it.
[LEILA]
I think I know what caused it.
[CLAUS]
Oh, you do? Care to fill us in?
I'm sorry but I'll have
to explain it to you later--
I can't talk right now.
[CLAUS]
Ma'am, wait!
What in the hell is that?
No way.
[LEILA] An ultra-long range,
extra-atmospheric transport.
Using this new
weapon we can drop
behind enemy lines for
surprise commando assaults.
I see now.
This thing's got
Knightmares inside it.
So you'll shoot us into space,
then watch us die.
[LEILA]
As always in times of war.
There's a chance some soldiers
won't make it back alive.
That said, I would like
for us all to return safely.
[RYO]
What was that?
You said "us" like you're
gonna come along.
[LEILA]
I am.
Hahaha!
Wait a minute, you don't
really mean that, do you?
'Cause if so you're either
naïve, or you're a fool.
[LEILA]
Well either way.
As the person who
planned this operation,
I consider it my duty to ensure
that everyone returns safely.
If you think that makes me
foolish, then so be it.
[RYO]
It's your funeral lady.
Sir Kururugi,
we should be arriving
in St. Petersburg in
about twelve hours.
[SUZAKU]
I see.
[MALE GUARD 2A] May I ask how
the Military Advisor is feeling?
[SUZAKU]
He's fine. You may go now.
[MALE GUARD 2A]
Yes, my lord!
[LELOUCH] Suzaku, please,
would you get me some water?
I'm begging you... I need water.
Help me.
Water.
[grunts]
[MALE COUNT VOICE 2A]
82. 81. 480.
[SARA] We're at
eight minutes to liftoff.
The launch countdown has begun.
Please stand by.
[ANNA]
All systems are normal.
[CLAUS]
Here we go.
Let's see how far
this little lady takes this.
Well, as long as she makes
it back in one piece,
then she's good.
Joe Wise, do we have a timeline
on the BRS program
calibration just yet?
Just a little longer.
I'll have it done
before the launch.
Hey, Hilda?
How much longer for the
Type 02 upload to be completed?
Forty-five seconds.
That's cutting it close!
[SARA] All systems now switched
from external to internal power.
[MALE GENERAL 2A] An order
has been issued instructing
all forces to
prepare for battle.
[MALE GENERAL 2B] We'll begin
our advance precisely one hour
after Apollo's Chariot launches.
That's good. Remember,
we're merely carrying out
the orders of Joint Staff HQ.
Be sure not to go above or
beyond what's asked of you.
[MALE GENERAL 2B] Here's hoping
this operation is successful.
And if it fails, we won't
have to take the fall for it.
[CLAUS] All right everyone,
the purpose of this mission
is to assist the main EU force
that's stationed in Warsaw.
They will march on
Area 24A of the Eastern front.
Our Wyvern Squad will drop
in behind the Britannian forces
that are already
deployed in the area.
Once they've landed
and regrouped,
they'll conduct a commando raid.
This'll throw the enemy lines
into chaos, weakening them
just as the 103rd Corps
begins their frontal attack.
So you're dropping us
right into the enemy's lap.
Sounds like you're trying
to burn off a few Elevens.
C'mon, guys,
don't be so pessimistic.
Look, all you have
to do is meet up
with the advancing 103rd Corps.
They'll make sure that
you get back here safely.
Yeah, should be easy when
we're surrounded by enemies.
Assuming we live
through re-entry.
What's with you
former Japanese kids?
You're a bunch
of negative Nellies.
Let's change the
subject, shall we?
I have an announcement that
should lighten the mood in here.
The commander herself
is going to be taking part
in this operation.
[gasps]
[ANNA] Huh?!
Leila, are you serious?
Yes, I don't have a choice.
A commando raid
will be ineffective
without sufficient troops.
It is my duty.
I know that it's dangerous.
However, we only have
a handful of personnel
who're capable of fighting.
To bolster those numbers,
I've decided to employ the
use of unmanned drones.
But in order for them
to be successful,
someone must act as an
operator to control the drones.
That's why.
I'm going along with
the Wyvern Squad.
He smiled.
Ayano.
You should try to
get some shut eye.
I mean, it's not like
we're gonna be
doing anything for a while.
[YUKIYA]
He's got a good point.
And if you doze off you'll get
to die peacefully in your sleep.
[OLIVIA]
T-minus one minute to liftoff.
Activating drive batteries.
[MALE COUNT VOICE 2A]
56. 55. 54. 53.
10. 9. 8. 7. 6. 5. 4.
[OLIVIA]
All systems ready for launch!
Igniting the main engine now!
This is it! Go, baby, go!
[MALE COUNT VOICE 2A]
36. 37.
78. 79. 180.
[OLIVIA]
T-plus three minutes!
Primary engine burn normal.
[SARA]
Altitude, 108 kilometers.
Velocity is stable.
Apollo's Chariot
is flying smoothly.
Primary engine
burn is now complete!
Separate first stage rocket!
First stage rocket
separation complete.
Secondary engine, begin burn!
Altitude, 255 kilometers.
Velocity. 5.6 klicks per second.
[SARA] Apollo's Chariot,
secondary engine burn complete.
Inertial guidance
is operational.
That went smoothly
now onto the hard part.
If this is the last thing
we're gonna see,
we could do worse.
Everything looks so
tiny from up here.
Feel like I could smash it.
It's beautiful.
[ASHLEY]
God, I'm bored. Bored. Bored.
I'm going to die of boredom.
How long are we gonna
have to stay cooped up
in this musty dump, huh?
Joannes!
Yes, sir? What is it, Master?
We have some time on our hands.
So how would you
like to play a game?
Tell me something.
What's the one
thing that you need
in order to survive
on the battlefield?
Um, the skill to... win?
[sighs] C'mon, surely you
can do better than that?
[gasps]
[ASHLEY]
Listen closely.
Wanna know the one thing
that's crucial to survival
on the battlefield?
It's luck.
It doesn't matter
how skilled you are
or how hard you fight,
the fact is you lose you die.
And why is that?
It's because luck
wasn't on your side.
But not me, I'm very lucky.
Would you like a
demonstration? Allow me.
Don't do it, Master Ashley!
Please! No!
See? Luck's definitely
on my side.
[JEAN]
You're pathetic.
You honestly believe that
luck will keep you alive?
I never pegged you for
a romantic, Ashley Ashra.
Jean Rowe!
[ASHLEY]
Of course I believe it.
My good fortune is
whats gotten me this far.
Let's see how lucky you are.
How about it?
Are you feeling confident?
This has to stop!
It's against regulation!
You can't do this,
Master Ashley!
[ASHLEY]
Just watch me!
Stay where you are
or you'll be next, got it?
How lucky are you, Jean?
Well...
It looks like you've got
a pretty healthy dose
of luck yourself, Jean.
Don't you have better things
to do than play stupid games?
[ASHLEY]
I can't help it, I'm bored--
I'm sick of being
stuck in this palace.
[JEAN]
I see. Well, in that case,
you won't be bored for long.
I'm here on behalf
of Lord Shaing.
He'd like a word with you.
It took him long enough.
Time to test our luck,
Ashra Force!
[OLIVIA] Thirty seconds
to fairing separation.
This is going to work. I hope.
Leila.
System shows all clear!
Now commencing!
Capsule separation confirmed.
System is activated.
All units show green.
Here goes nothing.
Time to free fall from
300 kilometers above Earth.
Don't remind me!
[OLIVIA]
20 seconds to reentry!
[SARA] We've got 10 seconds
to capsule reentry!
Wing deployment successful.
Got it! Aw man,
that was a piece of cake!
They opened!
Not too shabby!
[LEILA]
I'm flying off course!
Everything went smoothly
in the simulation.
[LEILA]
All drones confirmed.
Please report. Warrant officers.
Do you copy?
I need to know your location.
In the fog of war,
you've gotta keep your
eye out for friendly fire!
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga!
Look, whatever you do.
Just make sure that they're
captured unharmed!
I can't make any promises.
Safe landing of all
Wyvern is confirmed!
Beginning deploy-- Wait!
Hold on.
Why would they be
exchanging fire already?
Have they been spotted?
[CHLOE] It sure looks like
friendly fire to me.
[HILDA] Yeah, seems that
way from this telemetry.
[RYO]
Now, Yukiya!
Target Hyuga from behind!
[YUKIYA]
You want me to kill him here?
Feels like kind of a waste.
Lieutenant Hyuga!
Yukiya. What are
you doing? Hurry!
Okay. Fine.
What's all this?
Somebody please
tell me what's going on.
Possible enemy bombardment!
Multiple heat sources!
[ANNA] Shells impacting
at the Wyverns' drop point!
[CLAUS]
You've got to be kidding me.
Do we know where
the fire is coming from?
[SARA] I'm not detecting
any large-caliber canons.
Signal from the high-altitude
observation balloon is down.
I've lost their coordinates!
[CLAUS] Can't you do a
trajectory calculation?
Calculation complete!
500 klicks northeast.
[CLAUS]
Did you say 500?
Hey, Sara.
Are you sure you ran
those numbers correctly?
[SARA]
Yes, I'm positive, sir!
Jeez.
We didn't expect them to
use ultra-long range cannons.
Seems our Britannian buddies
had a clever idea of their own.
If we bear north-northwest,
we may be able to
clear the impact zone.
It's a Britannian
Knightmare squad.
[RYO]
We'll settle things later.
After we've made it
out of this mess!
[YUKIYA]
Seriously?
I wish you'd make up your mind.
Ayano! Try to keep up.
[JEAN]
We've pinpointed
the Ghosts of Hannibals'
coordinates, Lord Hyuga.
As you predicted,
they're currently heading
towards Slonim.
[SHIN]
What about Ashley and his team?
[JEAN] They're
standing by in position,
as per your orders, sir.
Jean, prepare
Vercingetorix at once.
Does this mean you're going into
battle yourself, Lord Hyuga?
That's correct.
I want to see these
so called ghosts.
No one's here.
[RYO]
This feels off.
Am I the only one getting
the creeps right now?
[YUKIYA] I bet there's something
fun just around the corner.
No offense Yukiya,
but your opinion of what's
"fun" is kind of messed up.
Drone units in formation.
Let's go.
An ambush?
[AKITO]
I've got this.
Stay behind me, Commander.
Lieutenant Hyuga!
I won't let you
get yourself killed.
Those drones won't
work if you're dead.
Yes, understood.
I'll do my best to make it
back with the rest of you.
These weaklings are
the Ghosts of Hannibal?
[RYO]
Whoa! It's go time.
[KUZAN]
Wait, is that--?
There are drones mixed in
with the Ghosts of Hannibal!
[AYANO]
I don't see any sign of them.
[YUKIYA]
They're close, I can feel it.
Ayano! Head's up!
[JAN]
Rene! Franz!
Got my eyes on the Ghost of
Hannibal.
[JOANNES]
Master Ashley!
It appears that most of the
enemy Knightmares are drones!
That's disappointing.
This "Ghost of Hannibal" guy
doesn't live up to the hype.
[JOANNES] Enemy units heading
your way, Master Ashley!
Nice. I'm sick of waiting!
[AKITO]
We need backup, Commander.
Can you summon
the drones over here?
There are three...
No, make that two of them
engaging the enemy.
Well then, we'll just
force our way through.
Stick close to me
and you'll be fine.
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga!
[AKITO]
Stay back!
Commander. Get to safety.
It's a red Knightmare!
Ah! So there you are Hannibal!
[ASHLEY]
You think you can outsmart me?
Lieutenant Hyuga.
[AKITO]
Die. Die. Die!
[JOANNES]
Master Ashley!
Die!
What the--?
What was that?
Akito?
What's causing
this sudden spike?
Die! Die! Die!
You won't defeat
the Ashra Force!
[AKITO]
Die!
Are these things really ghosts?
[SOPHIE] Kate, check
the values of the pilots'
neuro devices immediately!
[KATE] From what I can tell,
there's been a signal backflow
in Sayama, Kosaka, and
Naruse's neuro devices, ma'am.
Their brainwaves are
almost completely in sync now.
Somehow they've networked.
Die!
I see you!
What in the hell
are these things?
Ferilli. Report!
Can you confirm on your end?
[FERILLI]
Yes, ma'am! Confirmed!
What about you, Kate?
[KATE] I'm seeing the
same thing you are.
It looks like the
other pilots' brains
are receiving
something from Akito's.
Report, Joe!
I'm gonna need a minute!
This might not be
the best time to ask.
But what's going on?
Can't you see that I'm busy?
[SOPHIE]
Hurry up, Joe Wise, I need data!
[JOE]
Yes, ma'am!
I'll admit you're a lot stronger
than I thought you'd be!
[JEAN] The Ashra Force
is breaking formation.
They can't handle a few
Europian Knightmares?
Embarrassing.
[SHIN]
Jean, you talk too much.
My apologies, sir.
I'll keep quiet.
[SHIN] Those Knightmares are
simply fascinating aren't they?
Do you see what I see?
[JEAN] I'm not quite
sure what you mean, sir.
I sense it.
You're alive, after all.
This isn't looking good!
He keeps comin' at me!
No escape!
This guy won't let me breathe!
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga!
Anyone! Please respond!
Wyvern Squad!
Do you read me? Report at once!
Somebody please answer me!
Mental cloud
intensifying, ma'am!
Their ego boundaries are
at their breaking point!
Akito's nervous system
is somehow co-opting
the others' via
their neuro devices.
It appears that the
other Warrant Officers
are no longer in control.
It's a... brain raid!
I can't keep this up!
[FRANZ]
Simon, eject! Hurry!
Right, Franz!
We won't lose to
inferior soldiers damn it!
Die!
[FRANZ]
You damn monster!
This can't--
I wasn't through with you!
They call you a ghost,
but that's not right!
[ASHLEY] You're some kind
of demon or angel of death!
[AKITO]
Die!
[JOANNES]
Ashley!
No... Joannes?
[JOANNES] Good luck
to you Master... Ashley...
[YOUNG SHIN]
Akito!
Die, now.
Who's that?
[YOUNG SHIN] You're not
supposed to still be alive.
Big brother?
[YOUNG SHIN]
Die!
What in the hell's going on?
That kid, it's...
I feel sick!
A Malamud flash!
Ego boundaries, restoring!
Mental backlash. Incoming!
[SHIN]
Ashley. Withdraw.
Lord Shaing.
Let me do this!
[SHIN]
Silence!
I ordered you to fall back.
Do it, Ashley.
Fine. As you wish, sir.
Who's in that Knightmare?
[SHIN]
Akito.
[SHIN] I can't believe
you're still alive
and a Europian soldier, to boot.
It can't be.
[SHIN]
Exposed like this,
even someone
like you could kill me.
Akito.
Brother.
"Brother"?
[LEILA]
But how?
He's a Britannian knight.
Hyuga?
Akito?
[SHIN]
Now I get it.
The gods must have allowed
you to live simply for my sake.
They must support my ambitions.
Akito.
I would be honored if
you took the blood oath
with my Order of Michael
and then, offer up your life
for the creation of a new world.
After all, Fate
brought you to me.
Brother, you... want me?
[SHIN]
That's correct.
I want you... to die.
Die for me, Akito.
But he's... your brother!
I don't understand
why you're doing this!
[RYO]
Hyuga!
Fall back!
I got you covered!
Interrupting the joyous
reunion of two brothers?
Your squad mates should learn
some manners. Akito.
Akito!
[AKITO]
Watch out! Stay back!
[JEAN]
Lord Hyuga.
It appears the 2nd Field Army
has neglected to follow orders.
They've redirected their forces.
I can't believe those fools.
Well, Akito, you'll live today,
but I will come for you.
I promise, Brother.
[JEAN]
I'll cover you, Lord Hyuga.
[SHIN] Jean, that's
enough of your jokes.
Akito! You alright?
Yeah.
That was wild.
You know that guy?
I think he... he looked like...
...my brother.
[SARA] The 242nd Regiment
has crossed the front lines.
They're advancing!
[CLAUS] And you're absolutely
sure about this, Sara?
Yes, sir. The enemy
forces are retreating.
It's behind schedule,
but Operation number 237-A17
will be completed as planned.
[CLAUS chuckles]
Well, I'll be damned.
I can't believe we
actually pulled that off.
[SARA] Successful
reclamation of Slonim
into allied territory confirmed!
[OLIVIA]
Message from Command!
All Wyvern Squad members are
now present and accounted for!
Oh, thank goodness. Leila.
[SOPHIE]
It was exactly as you said.
I was finally able to
confirm a BRS event.
I wish you'd seen it.
We're one step closer
to having proof.
We did it all thanks to you.
Good night, my love.
Pleasant dreams.
Hanging around with
directionless youngsters all day
can sure drive a man to drink.
If only I were a
few years younger.
I enjoy my job, but...
it's gonna work me
into an early grave.
You must be tired
from your long journey.
I'll take you to the Guest
of State house momentarily.
It's a pleasure to
meet you, Sir Kururugi.
On behalf of His Highness,
Grand Duke Velaines.
I welcome you to St. Petersburg.
I... am Michael Augustus.
Nice to meet you, sir.
A Knight of the Round
as his escort.
And traveling on the
Imperial Family's private train?
I must say,
that's quite a welcome.
This man. He must be special.
His Majesty wouldn't
do that for just anyone.
[LELOUCH]
What is this?
This all the welcome I get?
I'll forgive it.
This time at least.
But next time
I come to your city,
I want to see the
streets lined with people.
Everyone chanting my name
and cheering my victory!
[LELOUCH] By order
of His Imperial Majesty.
All Eastern front operational
planning will hereby
be conducted... by me--
Military Advisor,
Sir Julius Kingsley!
[MALE SOLDIER 2A] I heard
that they didn't last even
30 minutes!
[MALE SOLDIER 2B] Really?
Man, the front lines are scary!
[MALE SOLDIER 2C] If it were me,
I'd be cryin' like a baby!
[MALE SOLDIER 2C] Now the rear
lines, that's where it's at!
[MALE SOLDIER 2B] Maybe I
should just ask for a desk job.
[MALE SOLDIER 2D]
I put in a request for leave.
[MALE SOLDIER 2E]
You're lucky, man!
[MALE SOLDIER 2F]
I'm jealous.
[AYANO] I swear,
these people are idiots!
[YUKIYA] I'm not exactly sure
what you're so worked up over.
I mean it all worked
out in the end.
We pushed the enemy back and
the EU allies retook Slonim.
Is that supposed to
make me feel any better
about risking my life?
[YUKIYA chuckles]
[AYANO]
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing.
It's just you remind me
of Akito sometimes.
His brother. Hmph.
How'd it go, Commander?
They're letting
us use a transport.
We'll be heading back home
the day after tomorrow.
[AKITO]
Really? That fast, huh?
[LEILA]
Yeah.
Apparently, General Smilas
had it authorized for us.
[AKITO]
Shall I escort you to your tent?
[LEILA]
Thank you.
Um, may I ask you something,
Lieutenant Akito?
So... that Britannian knight.
He kept saying he's
your brother, is that true?
[AKITO] That man's
practically a stranger to me.
This is the first time
I've seen him
since we were separated
over ten years ago.
I see.
But you are brothers,
aren't you?
Yeah, we're brothers I suppose.
The same blood runs
through our veins.
We share a past.
That's why he wants to kill me,
I guess.
What?
Kill you? He's your brother.
I'm sure that you
can change his mind.
Maybe you--
I've already
died once, Commander.
And that's why, this time
I want to return the favor
and kill him.