[cicadas chirping]
[NARRATOR]
August 10th, 2010 a.t.b.
In a blitzkrieg attack by
the Holy Empire of Britannia,
the nation of
Japan was conquered
in the span of a single month.
[NARRATOR] Its culture,
and even its very name,
were erased from the world.
[NARRATOR]
And so,
these islands in the far
east were renamed Area 11
and became an imperial province.
[LEILA] "Revolutionary
Calendar, year 228.
Floreal 18th.
The EU Army's
132nd Regiment
attempted to
retake St. Petersburg,
but their route was blocked
by the Britannian Army,
which had caught
wind of the plan.
They were surrounded in Narva,
a city southwest
of St. Petersburg.
[LEILA] My team,
Assault Unit wZERO,
launched a strike operation
against the enemy blockade
in order to rescue
the isolated regiment.
The soldiers comprising
the unit were youths
from what was once Japan.
The survival rate of this
operation was close to zero."
Meow!
[LEILA] "Politicians, hoping
to avoid the public backlash
that would certainly result
from the loss of EU
soldiers' lives in the war,
are now bolstering the army's
ranks with former Japanese,
who aren't considered
official citizens.
[LEILA] I, myself,
am complicit in this."
Auugh!
Looks like we've lost
signal on frame four!
Eleven remaining Alexanders!
More enemy
Knightmares are inbound!
I can't prevent
them from panicking.
Joe Wise, try using
steroids on them.
I'm injecting them, but... it
doesn't seem to have any effect.
The pilots are
starting to burn out.
Except for him.
Look at this soldier's readings.
He's still fine!
[FERILLI]
That's Akito.
Hahaha.
[MALE TECH 1A] Enemy
force has breached F line!
[MALE TECH 1A]
Enemy Frame down!
[MALE TECH 1B] Wait! Three
friendlies disappeared with it?
It looks like the damn
cowards are self-destructing!
Don't let them close in!
Keep them all at range!
C'mon men!
Another self-destruct!
Four more friendlies lost!
[MALE TECH 1B]
More incoming!
[KATE]
Frame 8 self-destructed!
Two enemy Knightmares destroyed!
Not enough! Don't back down!
Make them advance!
Move in and grab the enemy!
[LEILA]
Commander Anou,
the 132nd Regiment
must withdraw
within the next forty
minutes at the latest.
I know that,
Staff Officer Malcal!
What is this? Why in the hell
are there more enemy frames
than you anticipated?
As I'm sure you're aware,
all enemy engagements that
go on longer than an hour
will inevitably let our theater
of operations be pinpointed.
Excuses?
Don't you dare attempt to
justify your miscalculations!
I would never claim credit
for your alterations to my plan,
Commander Anou.
Hmm?!
So you wouldn't have
added self-destruct devices
to the Alexanders?
[LEILA] A foolish plan
that wastefully depletes
one's own forces,
tactically speaking,
is cowardice.
[chuckles] It's only
the Elevens that are dying.
They don't have any use
for your naïve humanism.
[ANOU]
As I'm sure you're aware,
these Elevens are descendants
of a race that found honor
in suicidal acts such as
seppuku and kamikaze!
What do you care if
some foreigners die
in a suicide mission?
This is war!
You think it's just
their lives at stake?
[ANOU]
Hmm?
What are you saying?
If our squad is
completely wiped out
and the Britannian
intercept line holds strong,
because of us,
the Narva retreat will end
with the entire
regiment slaughtered.
[LEILA]
If Operation Alpha fails,
yhe blame will fall
on the wZERO unit,
since we were supposed to
secure an escape route for them.
[LEILA] Do you believe
that General HQ in Paris,
and the Politicians there,
will accept the public backlash
that is sure to come
with such losses?
These are statesmen.
You know that they'll shift
the blame onto someone else.
[ANOU grunts]
Uhh...
[ANOU]
I... I will not be the one
who takes the blame for this.
With all that's happened.
I still...
[ANOU]
I...
All of this is your fault!
[ANOU] It was your plan,
and I will not be blamed for it!
I refuse to be a
scapegoat for your failings!
Leila!
[gasps]
[JOE] Oh, god.
This isn't happening.
You're going to...?
You don't have it in you.
What?
[ANOU]
No! Let go of me!
Please! Let go of me!
[HAMMEL]
What is going on?
Who discharged their weapon?
Well, if it isn't Major Hammel
of the Special Forces.
That was fast.
[LEILA] Allow me to correct
you on one other detail.
They're not "Elevens."
They're Japanese.
[HAMMEL]
Major Malcal.
Is that akido?
It's most impressive.
[ANOU]
Damn it, Hammel!
Please! Get this bitch off me!
She's out of control--
[HAMMEL]
Would you mind explaining
just what happened
here, Major Malcal?
Requesting order
three oh five.
Lieutenant Colonel!
Loud and clear.
Deputy Commander
Claus happily affirms
the requested change in command.
All yours. The change
has been recorded, Commander.
Disengage all Alexander
self-destruct devices!
Now Captain Clement!
Uh... Right!
[ANNA] Chloe! Hilda!
Message all frames!
She's really hitting
the ground running.
Well, she deserves it.
Seems I'm surrounded.
[AKITO]
Self-destruct disengaged?!
[MALE TECH 1C] Lord Wilhelm!
We've lost signal
from the Third Platoon!
The Ghost of
Hannibal, huh? Huh?!
Here he comes!
The hell is that?
[AKITO]
Die!
God damn you to hell!
[MALE TECH 1A]
Signal lost!
Wilhelm Squad seems
to have been wiped out.
[MALE KNIGHT 3A]
Please, Sir Farnese.
We must request
reinforcements immediately.
[MALE KNIGHT 3A]
I'm sorry.
I don't think our forces can
hold the line any longer.
[FARNESE] Without knowing
the full measure of the enemy...
...reinforcements would
be unwisely put at risk.
[AKITO]
Now die!
Die!
What?
[AKITO]
Die!
Bastard.
Sorry pal, I don't
believe in ghosts!
[HILDA] Zero enemy
Knightmares detected!
Combat zone clear!
[CHLOE] 132nd Regiment
has begun evacuation.
What's Wyvern unit's
Remaining troop strength?
Already verifying.
One frame!
It's... receiving
pilot biometrics now.
[OLIVIA]
Second Lieutenant Hyuga.
It's Akito Hyuga!
All remaining forces
are to rendezvous with G1.
Withdraw! Activate main engine!
[MALE TECH 1A]
Number two, speed!
To think, the Holy
Order of Raphael
facing EU militia soldiers
still failed to hold our own.
Sir Farnese.
[FARNESE]
All that remains.
Is to give proper burials to
our brothers who fell in battle.
[MALE SOLDIER 1A] Looks
like we're finally going home!
[MALE SOLDIER 1B]
Sure took those reinforcements
long enough to get here!
[MALE SOLDIER 1A]
I didn't mind, honestly.
It was almost like camping!
[MALE SOLDIER 1B] Ha!
That's one way to look at it.
[MALE SOLDIER 1A] This war
is turning into a vacation!
What are you doing way out here?
You all by yourself?
I am. Can you give us a lift?
Huh?
That a Knightmare?
Never seen that model.
Just to be safe,
show me your ID.
You're a long way from
home, that's for sure.
Tch! You're a damn Eleven?
[MALE SOLDIER 1A]
I'll give you a lift,
but only if you ride in the
back with the Knightmare.
[LEILA]
One survivor.
My plan succeeded.
But only because so many
young Japanese men
sacrificed their lives.
[LEILA] My father told me
that it was the duty
of a citizen to
protect his homeland.
But... to these
disenfranchised few.
[LEILA] To these people
who have lost their homeland.
Do I come across as a
detached chess master
hiding safely in her castle?
[SMILAS] "Major Leila Malcal
is now a Lieutenant Colonel.
Officially installed
as the commander
of Assault Unit wZERO."
The 40 Chair Defense Committee
approved it yesterday.
All Thanks to your
Narva evacuation, I assume.
Congratulations, Leila.
[LEILA]
Thank you, General. I accept.
[SMILAS] I expect
great things from you.
The wZERO unit was
based on your proposal.
So it's only fitting that
you should be it's commander.
What is wrong?
You don't seem
too happy about it.
[gasps]
General Smilas,
my Attack Plan 145A is to launch
sneak attacks on enemy positions
utilizing multiple squads
of Knightmare forces.
So, it will require
the commitment
of a much larger
number of troops.
If it continues with small
forces like this time,
then our losses will
become unsustainable.
Please, let me expand the
unit with Europian Troops.
I understand your point,
but sending regular forces
isn't quite so simple, Leila.
Public opinion grows rancid
when Republic soldiers
die in this war,
and the Joint Chiefs
of Staff determined that
the survival rate of soldiers
in Attack Plan 145A will be low.
Are you telling me
you're fine with people dying
as long as they're Elevens, sir?
[SMILAS]
Leila.
You know that
it's a fool's errand
to try to find any kind of
logic in wartime politics.
[LEILA]
But, sir!
[SMILAS] It takes more
than sound arguments
to win people over.
In the Narva operation
the other day,
the number of Japanese soldiers
who managed to come home alive
was exactly one.
But you saved the lives of
nearly 15,000 Europian soldiers.
[LEILA]
I didn't--
[SMILAS] Meanwhile,
you haven't shown any regret
over the incident
with Lt. Col. Anou.
[LEILA] I regret not removing
him before the operation began.
I understand.
Anou was just
recently reassigned
to the Warsaw supply force.
Seems we're not the only ones
who are aware of his aptitudes.
The Committee will
meet again tomorrow.
There's another meeting?
Those cowardly politicians
and bureaucrats
find comfort in meetings.
It might do you some
good to sit in on one.
[LEILA]
Yes, sir.
[SMILAS]
Which reminds me,
you remember
tonight's engagement?
I'm attending the party
celebrating the
successful Narva retreat.
Sorry I kept you,
Lieutenant Hyuga.
[AKITO]
It's all right.
I'm on escort duty.
That's what I'm here for.
[LEILA]
Oh, fine. So it is.
Is this your first
time in Paris?
[AKITO] No, but
it's been a while.
[PARTY MAN 1A] That painting
fetched a rather tidy sum.
[PARTY MAN 1B] Art's a safer
bet than gold these days.
[PARTY MAN 1A] Nonsense. Nothing
beats national bonds in wartime.
[PARTY MAN 1B]
True.
But Britannia doesn't seem
to want to expand the war.
[PARTY MAN 1A] It's best
when both sides simply glare
at each other like they are now.
[PARTY MAN 1B]
A war without fighting
is more profitable
than peace, I suppose.
[PARTY MAN 1B] Perhaps
I should have invested more.
[PARTY MAN 1A]
You bankers are terrible.
[PARTY MAN 1B]
That's true!
[laughter]
[PARTY WOMAN 1A]
Look at her.
A military uniform? Here?
[PARTY WOMAN 1B]
Ah, that Malcal girl.
[PARTY MAN 1D] The young lady
we've heard so much about?
[AKITO]
You know,
there's something about a woman
at a party reading
Guibert's tactical writings,
that says, "keep your distance."
Why, Lieutenant Hyuga,
you do have a sense of humor.
This is my first time inside
the Palais des Tuileries.
Pretty much what I'd expect
from a Bien Nation
Conglomerate party.
So this is to celebrate
the success in Narva?
I don't know what
they're celebrating.
[LEILA] Look around. We're
the only two soldiers here.
[DANIEL]
Leila!
[DANIEL] Is that the one
and only Miss Leila Malcal?
Ah, excuse me.
Begging your pardon, everyone.
Now why didn't you call ahead
to say that you would be coming.
Leila, It's been a whole
year since we last saw you.
[LEILA]
I know.
It's been too long, Daniel.
And you too, Stefan.
Leila, why on earth
did you decide
to wear that to a
perfectly good party?
I would have hoped you'd
put aside such boorish attire.
My uniform is
considered formal attire.
I see that your tone is the
same as it always was, Leila.
[IOAN]
As I live and breathe!
Well, if it
isn't our little sister.
Brother... Ioan, hello.
Ah. Now I get it. So this
is the lieutenant Eleven?
Lieutenant Hyuga--
my bodyguard.
Nice to meet you.
I'm one of
Leila's big brothers.
Ioan Malcal, third oldest
of the Malcal family.
The pleasure is
mine, Lieutenant.
Oh, right and before
it causes confusion,
my lovely sister just
happens to be my fiancée.
[gasps]
The Malcal family, get this, was
gracious enough to adopt her.
Leila is the apple of our
father's eye,
which I'm sure is the reason
he decided that we
should be married.
Ioan!
The thing is...
...I have no interest in
marrying the likes of you.
[DANIEL]
Please, you're drunk, Ioan.
[STEFAN]
Behave yourself!
[IOAN]
Wait!
What do you say I make
you my mistress, eh?
My girl on the side!
That would suit
you perfectly, Leila!
Oh. So sorry.
You little... son of a...
You know how Elevens are all
masters of bladed weapons?
If you'd like,
I'd be more than
happy to demonstrate
on that face of yours.
Let me go! Get off of me!
[AKITO]
Here.
Sorry about that little spill.
[AKITO]
Shall we go, Commander?
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga?
Hey! Wait a minute!
[LEILA] I didn't know you
were an expert swordsman.
[AKITO]
What do you mean?
[LEILA] You said you were
a master of bladed weapons.
[AKITO]
Ah, that.
[AKITO] You Europians are
all the same, aren't you?
You all think we're
masters of karate or swordplay.
You either fear our culture.
Or mock it.
I am not like that!
Hmm?
Speaking of,
I heard somewhere that you're
ranked in aikido, Commander.
And where exactly
did you hear that?
Captain Clement
mentioned it to me.
[sighs]
That Anna can't keep her
mouth shut, can she?
So is it true that you and
the Captain met as classmates?
When we were young,
after the Malcals adopted me.
[LEILA]
See, apparently,
my birth parents were
Britannian aristocrats.
[AKITO] Britannian?
They defected to Europia?
[LEILA] Yes.
In fact, I was born here.
But my parents
died 12 years ago,
leaving me to fend for myself.
The Malcals,
a huge conglomerate,
took me in as an orphan
because they wanted
a claim to noble lineage.
Their intent was
to eventually marry me
off to their youngest son Iaon.
That's why he's your
brother and fiancé. Hmph!
Your world is funny.
Always Jockeying for the
best bloodline and fortune.
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga!
[AKITO] You know, if you
don't like it, Commander...
[AKITO] ...I'd be happy
to get rid of it for you.
This world, I mean. Heh.
[ORANGE JACKET MAN]
Eighty-five of my crew are dead.
And there are another 37 who
are laid up in the hospital ICU.
[ORANGE JACKET MAN]
Not to mention,
20 of your own friends have
entered the great beyond.
It was 18.
Get your facts straight.
[ORANGE JACKET MAN]
This is the first time
a war of this size and scale has
been fought in the Underground.
But you know that.
So listen up kid,
you and I have both paid
a steep price, right?
Let's end this.
With that in mind,
I've prepared a little gift
for you and your friends.
Ryo!
The pilot ID's been rewritten.
You're all set.
Thanks, Yukiya.
[ORANGE JACKET MAN]
Seems there was a deposit
in my bank account?
Oh yeah?
Well, I guess since
we've paid for it.
We'll stop calling it a gift,
like you did us some big favor.
Oh, get over yourself Ryo!
We both know you're paying
with money you skimmed
from the net banks.
You're just a bunch
of two-bit thieves.
Yeah? Why don't
you do it too, then?
Assuming you can, that is.
Watch your mouth,
you filthy Eleven rat!
Boys, boys. Let's
just take it easy, all right?
Come on, old friend.
Thought you knew
better than that.
Show a little respect
for your elders alright?
You and this crew
of yours need to chill.
Hmph! Bold words
coming from a thug.
Right, Yukiya?
Give him a break, Ryo.
These old farts don't have too
many lectures left in 'em.
Ryo, we need this deal
to pan out for the plan.
Relax, Ayano.
Fifteen. Fourteen. Thirteen.
How 'bout this, Ryo?
Why don't you join
our organization?
We could really use someone
with your particular talents.
That'd make things easy.
But there's one small problem,
you make me sick.
What was that?
Four. Three. Now, Ryo!
Wow. Body parts everywhere.
Man, what a mess.
Gonna be a bitch to clean up.
[RYO]
Good work.
But it won't
always be this easy.
[YUKIYA]
Yeah, I know.
People are so
fragile in the end.
[ORANGE JACKET MAN] Somebody,
please, I need a doctor.
It's over. Just help me.
[RYO] Well, I'll be.
You're still alive, huh?
You've gotta help me.
[RYO] Sure,
I'd be happy to help you...
...for a small fee.
[gasps]
I mean, your life
isn't worth much.
Give me a ballpark estimate.
Hahahaha!
[ORANGE JACKET MAN] Wait, are
you kids with those terrorists?
[RYO]
Huh?
[ORANGE JACKET MAN] Those
Elevens I've heard about...
The Black Knights?
[RYO]
Nope.
We're a little different.
But you don't need
to worry about it.
[RYO] Yukiya, Ayano.
Next time's for real.
[YUKIYA]
About time.
[YUKIYA chuckles]
Things are about to get fun!
[SMILAS] Ever since the
revolution 300 years ago,
Europia has maintained
its republic system...
[SMILAS]
...but,
what the revolution might
have actually given rise to
is this devastating
money-worship.
The end result of a
lifetime of self-interest.
That's true
even for those
who claim to be
this country's leaders.
If this keeps up,
we'll be conquered by
Brittania before you know it.
[SMILAS] They may
be distant descendants
of the royals and nobles who
were driven from this continent
and into the new world,
but they still feel
entitled to all of this.
And that's why
I can't help but think:
If only General
Napoleon Bonaparte,
hero of the revolution,
had become emperor of Europe,
rather than dying at
the guillotine like he did.
He tried to make
himself a dictator.
The dictatorship of one talented
man is far more beneficial
than the democracy of
the ignorant masses.
That is what your late
father wished for, as well.
It's why he was murdered.
[gasps]
I was really young when
my father was assassinated.
So I don't really--
Oh. No. Sorry, you don't have
to speak to his politics.
I admired your father, but I
admire your compassion as well.
[gasps]
[SMILAS] Keeping the Elevens who
live in Europia locked away
in internment camps out of
fear of Britannia is cowardice.
Yet another shame
of republicanism.
[SMILAS] But I can't pity the
ones who didn't resist.
[MALE GUARD 1A]
You like any of those
scroungy Eleven ladies
out there, eh?
I wonder if the one
in the back knows them?
[laughter]
[YUKIYA] Target
has entered the area.
Right on time.
[YUKIYA] That's about the
level of security I expected.
All right. Let's get
this game started!
[YUKIYA]
5 minutes.
[YUKIYA] Is the
drive beacon coming in?
[RYO]
No doubt about it.
This is the route the
nav system's showing.
[engine powering down]
Damn, the hatch is stuck.
Okay, now let's party!
[MALE GUARD 1C] Deploy! Hurry!
[MALE GUARD 1D] Knightmare 46,
prepare to intercept!
This is too easy!
[LEILA]
A Knightmare!
Think they're terrorists?
I'm sure.
Let's stay put for now.
General, get out!
Move!
[LEILA] Driver! Hurry!
[DRIVER]
No, Lieutenant Colonel!
It's too dangerous out there!
Come back!
Shall we...
test how sharp this is?
Ayano has
secured the target.
[RYO]
Good. We're out of here!
[YUKIYA]
Okay!
[RYO]
Ayano!
Take the geezer and
go meet up with Yukiya!
[RYO]
Another one? Just my luck.
Let's wrap this up!
[RYO]
Who is this guy?
He's taking on a Knightmare.
He's even crazier than we are.
If you're that eager to die...
[RYO]
...I'm happy to help!
Dammit!
This is bad!
[RYO grunts]
Ah, Crap!
[beeping]
Ryo?
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga!
I want you to
take them alive.
[AYANO]
Ryo!
To the Pilot of the Glasgow,
your friend is my prisoner!
Resistance is useless.
Come out of there at once!
[RYO] All right!
Just don't hurt her!
I'm coming out!
[RYO]
Woopsie-daisy.
Huh? Hold on,
what the hell is this?
You're just a kid.
[LEILA] You two don't seem to
be that different in age to me.
Commander Malcal,
letting them live
would only put us at risk.
Heh. You're smarter
than you look.
[AYANO snickers]
He's right, y'know.
[YUKIYA]
Let them go!
Now! Don't try
to stall for time!
Or I'll blow us all sky-high.
What do you say?
Either way,
your friends are dead.
Do I look like I would back
down over a threat like that?
Pretty much.
Just do it, Yukiya!
We're all going to be
killed if they capture us,
so what's the difference?!
Just tell me why you did it.
All of this was to
kidnap General Smilas
so I assume you wanted
to trade him for something?
At the very least I
figured he was worth
a few top-of-the-line
Knightmares.
You want Knightmares?
How long do you
think you can hide
after taking
something like that?
We'll keep running
for as long as it takes,
blending in with
the other Elevens.
Idiot, the army will stop
at nothing to kill you,
even if that
means an air strike.
[LEILA] There
had to be more to it.
What did you and
your friends really want?
This wasn't just
about Knightmares.
[RYO]
A place to belong.
To belong?
Man, I wish I was as
dumb as you people are.
You made a mess
of the whole world,
and now you're all perfectly
content to just lie in it.
But us, we don't belong here.
There's no place in this
world for Elevens anymore.
If that's what you want,
then what's your plan?
Found your own country?
Look, I don't have any interest
in becoming the
representative for all Elevens.
All that we want...
...is a place for ourselves.
Somewhere to call home.
If you want a place to belong,
I can give you one.
Huh?
I'll allow you to join my team.
It's as close to
a home as you'll find.
Yeah, I think I get it.
If we say no...
Heh.
...then we go boom.
That's it, right?
We don't have a choice, do we?
[MICHELE] Duke Velaine
has issued an command
that the Order of Michael is
to relocate to St. Petersburg.
[SHIN] St. Petersburg, sir?
[MICHELE] The Order of
Raphael was destroyed
in a battle at Narva not
far from west of there.
Our reports say that the enemy
was a Knightmare squad that
appeared behind our lines.
It just doesn't
make any sense to me.
The EU forces that
occupied Narva were,
by all rights,
completely surrounded.
It's unlikely
that reinforcements
could have gotten
to them undetected.
[MICHELE]
The enemy appeared
without warning
amidst the siege line.
[SHIN]
Without warning?
[MICHELE] That's what
the survivors are saying.
They supposedly just
appeared out of thin air.
That brings General
Hannibal to mind,
attacking the ancient
Roman empire.
Hannibal?
I see your point.
The "Ghost of Hannibal," indeed.
If there are
any ghosts here,
it's Europia United itself.
The ghost of a revolution
three centuries past.
They're a bunch of cowards
who are loyal to nothing
but their own interests.
It's up to noble-minded Euro
Britannia to oust statesmen
such as these and lead
the region in their stead.
Our cause is a just one!
[MICHELE]
Shin,
the blood of Oriental
warriors flows in your veins,
and you will soon be
a part of the aristocracy
and its storied
thousand-year history.
[SHIN] Your words
honor me, Sir Manfredi.
[SHIN]
And now...
...I will take over
the Order of Michael.
[laughs]
You know,
you're always so serious
it's difficult to tell
when you're joking.
In another five years.
I will step down
and you will lead the Order
of Michael as my successor.
I'm actually looking
forward to that day, Shin.
Y'know, after all this time,
you've come to mean more
to me than my own brother.
Brother?
[MICHELE]
That's right.
Let's enter the
new world together.
You're horrible.
[MICHELE]
Shin.
[SHIN]
It's rather unfortunate.
You don't have what it takes
to command the Order of Michael.
What are you saying?
You are unfit. Apologies.
[SHIN] Sir Manfredi.
Please begin your journey.
[MICHELE]
Of course. It is time.
At your command,
Shin Hyuga Shaing, my lord.
Safe travels, Manfredi.
[LEILA]
Akito?
Why, good morning,
Commander Malcal.
Good morning to you,
Lieutenant Hyuga.
[LEILA] What are
you doing out here?
[AKITO]
I'm keeping a promise.
[LEILA]
To who?
It's a grave for those
killed in the Narva operation.
So it's a monument?
That's nice of you.
[AKITO] We all made a pact
before the mission.
Those who survived
would build something
here for the ones that didn't.
I was the only survivor.
I could have done more.
Acted sooner.
All of them should
have made it home alive.
[AKITO] They set out on the
mission excited to serve the EU.
Yep. That's correct.
Because we died in battle,
our families are
now full EU citizens.
That's enough.
[BROWN HAIR FIGHTER 1A]
And yet I wonder,
why do you fight, Akito?
You don't have a family
or a country to protect.
You're alone.
What do you live for?
So I can die.
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Hyuga?
[LEILA] Did I say something
I shouldn't have?
You got quiet all of a sudden.
[AKITO]
No. It's not that.
I was just talking
with them, that's all.
With who?
[AKITO] They're supposed to be
dead, but I can still hear them.
I can hear their voices.
[AKITO] Because...
I died myself once.