[beeping]
[explosion]
[RYO]
Yukiya!
[AYANO]
Ryo!
You can't help him now!
These Alexanders aren't
equipped for water.
I don't care! We can't just...
Akito.
And Leila.
[LEILA]
Ryo! Ayano! Come in!
What? Yukiya's inside?
[AKITO] I've picked up the
beacon from his machine.
Akito! Please save Yukiya!
I'm going to do
everything that I can.
[ANNA] Come in.
Leila. What's going on?
What just crashed into the lake?
Was it a float system's
reactor core?
[LEILA]
No time! Yukiya's in there!
[gasps] That's terrible!
[LEILA]
Help me think, Anna!
There has to be a
way to save him!
[ANNA]
Hmm. Leila. It's an Alexander.
Those models have
shock-absorbing balloons.
So if you can access Yukiya's
system and activate them,
the cockpit block will
fill with balloons,
making it buoyant
enough to float!
[LEILA] But how do we access
Yukiya's machine remotely?
[ANNA]
If Akito uses his BRS,
it will connect his
Alexander to Yukiya's.
Akito. You heard that, right?
Activating now.
Requesting system control.
[AKITO gasping]
It came up!
It's Yukiya! We found him!
Bring us in closer!
You got it.
So that chick is
your CO, is she?
Yeah, she's a damn good one.
And her name's not "chick,"
it's Leila Malcal.
[ASHLEY]
Hmph. Leila it is then.
Oh, hey. Akito.
Don't talk. I'm gonna
get you out of here.
Heh. What's gotten into you?
You're not one to
talk like the hero.
No. I'm not.
[LEILA]
Anna, we just retrieved Yukiya,
but he's very seriously injured.
Please inform Dr. Randle
immediately!
Oh, no, Yukiya.
Captain. What's wrong?
Uh! I've got you!
[SARA] The wZERO Unit and
the commander's group
are coming back.
Tell the doctor!
I'm on it.
I'm sending her their location.
[BRONDELLO] Transport the
wounded to the garrison!
Do a head count of all
squads Knightmares!
Abandon any damaged units
where they're standing.
[DORE]
Sir Brondello!
My squad is down to
fewer than ten machines.
[SCHOLZ] Well, we're lucky
you made it out alive, Dore.
You fared well, Sir Scholz.
More than half your
squad is undamaged.
Yeah.
That's only because we were
at the back of the formation.
[JEAN]
What are you doing?
Grand Master Shaing never
gave the order for a retreat!
Two thirds of our
forces are destroyed.
We require time to regroup!
[JEAN] Did that attack turn
you all into cowards?
Of course not!
But Knights don't force their
troops into honorless battles!
Not that a rookie
upstart like you
would know anything about honor!
[JEAN growls]
[SHIN]
Jean.
Lord Hyuga?
[SHIN]
I heard everything.
I'd like the Three Swordmasters
to retreat for now.
Are you certain, sir?
[SHIN]
Yes. But don't worry,
I plan to test their mettle
as knights very soon.
[SHIN] I'll crush them. Along
with the rest of this world.
Suzaku.
Would you...
...bring me some water, please?
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[JULIUS groans]
[JULIUS]
S-Suzaku.
[gasps]
[JULIUS] I want you to
kill me... Suzaku.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[JULIUS coughing]
Suzaku. Please...
...kill me.
[SUZAKU]
I want to go get her.
You and me.
Let's go get Nunnally.
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
General Smilas.
We've received reports
that Lord Shaing
has taken control
of Euro Britannia.
Lord Shaing is an
Eleven, I believe.
That seems to be true, sir!
Then we'd better not
underestimate him.
[AYANO] I told you to
hurry up and jump ship.
You just had to take
your time. Freak'n Yukiya.
[DAVID] His pancreatic
artery's bleeding a lot,
but I think I can fix it.
I just hope this
connection holds out.
Would you believe this is my
first time doing telesurgery
on a patient in a
secret location.
You know, I wouldn't just
do this for anyone, Sophie.
[SOPHIE]
I appreciate your help, David.
[DAVID]
Then promise me something.
[SOPHIE]
What's that?
[DAVID]
When Takeru wakes up,
I want to be the
first person you call.
[SOPHIE gasps]
[DAVID] I don't know where
you are right now, but,
I assume he's with you.
Just let me know.
Thanks, David.
I'll do just that.
I promise.
I'll hold you to it.
As it stands,
Takeru's got way more
chess wins against me
than I've got on him.
I need to catch up.
Tell him to wake
his ass up, Sophie.
Even if it takes a miracle.
[LEILA]
Yukiya's surgery was successful.
[CLAUS]
Thanks to him,
we wiped out two thirds
of the enemy forces.
They've still got the advantage
when it comes to
numbers, though.
Then I'll have Major Hammel's
security team pilot
Alexanders as well.
[CLAUS] Well, Hammel's team is
just supposed to be support.
[beeping]
Anyway, looks like I just got
the most recent data
from Captain Clement.
How many drones will we have?
We're gonna have
ten at the most.
The bulk of our parts
went into the Alexanders
for Hammel's team.
[LEILA] And do we still have
the Alexander I used before?
[CLAUS]
Major Hammel got that one.
[LEILA]
Oh, I see.
You've got a Knightmare
for me though, right?
You're going to need my
help to win this thing.
We're up against the
Holy Order of Michael.
You used to be on their side.
Well, that was before
Shaing tried to do me in.
And besides. I owe Akito one.
[ASHLEY]
Heh.
Hey, Pops! Give me some!
Well, help yourself...
All right.
I'll let you pilot one
of the Alexanders.
That's a great plan,
Commander. Smart move.
Yeah, you sure know what
you're doing, Leila.
[CHLOE] It's a good thing we
got that Knightmare data
from that boy with the red hair.
Right, Sergeant Hilda?
[HILDA]
Yeah. I think I caught his name.
It's Ashley.
That's why we're using
the Schrötter Steel.
This'll be much better.
Altering those designs has been
rough on the boss though.
[CHLOE]
Yeah, she had to completely
rework the new
Alexander model,
and the upgraded
model for Akito.
She's really talented, huh?
She sure is.
Military-use robotics
are just the beginning
of what she can do.
[MECHANIC 5A] Do we have
any spare elbow motors?
This one's fried!
[MECHANIC 5B]
We're all out.
Grab one from the spare units.
[MECHANIC 5C]
Yeesh.
It's hard to work
without supplies.
[MECHANIC 5D]
No choice.
We'll just have to make
do with what we've got.
[sighs] Lord Hyuga.
[clang]
[JEAN gasps]
[gasps]
[ASHLEY]
Hey.
[JEAN]
A-Ashley?
And in their uniform no less.
[ASHLEY] Just hear me out
before you up and kill me.
[JEAN]
Why should I?
[ASHLEY] You and I are
a lot alike, you know.
We were orphans.
All alone in the world and
knocking on death's door.
Until Shaing took us in.
So we owe him our li--
He's different than
he used to be.
I don't know why.
All he wants is bloodshed.
It's like he's possessed.
[gasps]
[ASHLEY]
Despite all that,
I got a buddy who wants to save
the bastard from himself.
Since they're brothers...
Akito... Hyuga.
[ASHLEY]
Jean. Er...
Wait, you went by Jeanne
before he found you, right?
Well, Jeanne, I think we
oughtta help them out.
'Cause if anybody can
bring Shin Hyuga back,
it's Akito.
[wolves howling]
Now. Shall we begin?
All forces, advance!
The time has come to bring
order to the Order of Michael!
Sir!
Dore! I'll go in first!
Godspeed, friend.
We're behind you.
[KNIGHT 5A]
No good! We can't puncture it!
Then we need to push forward
with the Canterbury!
[KNIGHT 5A]
Yes, sir!
We still don't have a visual?
[CHLOE]
Working on it!
Ah! Got it!
Eight o'clock! Range, 250!
[SARA]
Begin counterattack!
[KNIGHT 5A]
We're taking fire from the wall!
[KNIGHT 5B] Close the distance!
Don't back down!
[KNIGHT 5C] We have to
protect the Canterbury!
[KNIGHT 5D] Alpha Platoon,
move forward! Now!
[BRONDELLO]
Hang in there!
We can fall back and regroup!
[BRONDELLO]
Lord Shaing.
[SHIN]
If you cowards retreat now,
I'll have to shoot you.
[BRONDELLO growls]
Bastard!
[SHIN]
Is this your idea of honor?
I must say I'm disappointed,
Sir Brondello.
Oh, no, there's a
crack in sector A23!
[KNIGHT 5D]
We're latched on!
[KNIGHT 5E]
Let's go!
Enemy Knightmares
found in sector A17!
[gasps] Stop them.
[KNIGHT 5B]
Damn! We can't get any closer!
[KNIGHT 5C] We can't reach
the Alpha Platoon! Ah!
By the time we can
attack the castle,
we might not have
any troops left.
[SCHOLZ]
Dore!
[DORE gasps]
[SCHOLZ] I'll have my team
create an opening.
The rest'll have to be
up to you, brother.
Roger.
I'll be joining you and
Lord Manfredi before long.
I look forward to
seeing each other again
on the other side.
Move out!
[yelling]
[gasps]
[SARA]
We've got an explosion in A23!
[OLIVIA]
Our defenses are crumbling!
[SHIN] Fools are only
useful as pawns anyway.
Prepare to advance
on the enemy castle!
[KNIGHT 5D]
There it is! Going in!
[SARA] The Knightmare squad
just got into the castle
through the old gate!
[KNIGHT 5B] Let's head for
the command center!
[gasps]
[KNIGHT 5D]
The path's blocked off!
[KNIGHT 5F]
Get the wounded out of here!
So, they want to make
things difficult.
[LEILA] wZERO squad.
Prepare to strike.
Captain Hyuga,
get ready to launch!
Captain Hyuga! Do you copy?
[ASHLEY]
Heh.
I think this baby's gonna
be a perfect fit for me.
[RYO] Why the hell did
you get the new one?
[ASHLEY]
Oh, quit crying.
[RYO]
What'd you say?
There! Open fire!
[KNIGHT 5B]
They've got eyes on us!
[KNIGHT 5D]
They're on top of us!
Fall back! Get out of range!
[KNIGHT 5D]
It's an ambush!
I'm Ashley Ashra!
If any of you clowns are
dumb enough to try me,
step right up!
[KNIGHT 5D]
The Ghost of Hannibal!
Ashley from Ashra Force?
Then we'll keep pushing forward!
[RYO]
Here they come!
[ASHLEY]
This oughtta be fun!
[DORN growls]
He's here.
Final enemy Knightmare inbound.
Incoming at high velocity!
You got a visual?
[SARA]
Just a second, sir.
Got it!
[SARA]
It's the four-legged unit!
[gasps]
All forces, move
into the castle.
Destroy the command
center first.
[AKITO gasping]
Dammit, Shaing!
I can't believe I used to
look up to such a coward!
[SHIN]
Is that you, Ashley?
How hard did they make you
beg for that Knightmare?
[ASHLEY]
Shut your mouth!
[RYO] Heads up, Akito!
He got past us!
[AKITO gasping]
[ASHLEY]
You're mine!
[SHIN]
You'll be the next to die.
But don't worry,
your new friends will
be joining you soon.
That's just how generous I am!
Damn you!
[RYO] Ashley! C'mon,
you're way too close!
Brother!
I don't know why you
insist on fighting!
[SHIN]
Because ending this cruel world,
is all that I care
about! That's it!
[SHIN]
Time's up, Akito.
Forsake this mortal coil. Die!
They're still fighting
in sector A23!
Akito, Ryo, and Ashley
are running at full power.
I just hope they don't overload.
[AKITO]
Commander.
I need a favor.
Could you hold onto this?
[LEILA]
Akito.
[AKITO]
If I get killed,
and there's nothing left
of my body, bury it.
[LEILA]
You'd better...
...make sure you come back.
[AKITO gasps]
Because I...
I have some things I
want to say to you,
but now's not the time.
So...
I want you to promise me Akito.
Promise me that you'll come
back safe with the others.
[SARA]
Order of Michael Knightmare!
They are breaching the gate!
Defensive maneuvers. Hurry!
Akito! They're coming!
You little...
[AKITO]
Ashley.
[ASHLEY]
Uh.
Fall back to sector 18.
If you say so.
[KNIGHT 5C]
We've reached the middle gate!
[KNIGHT 5E]
The Platoon's goin' in.
They let us push
them back so easily.
[gasps] No, wait!
[SARA]
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
[YUKIYA]
A-Ayano. Hey.
[AYANO]
Yukiya!
Wait, what? Where am I--
[AYANO] Yukiya!
Oh my god, you're okay!
[YUKIYA groaning]
[AYANO]
Oh, sorry!
[YUKIYA]
It's fine. How long...
Have I been under for?
Six days. Seven, counting today.
That's crazy. It's
been a whole week?
What about...
[gasps] Oh, no.
[AYANO]
Yukiya, wait!
You're not supposed to get up!
I have to. I have to talk
to Leila right now!
[AYANO]
Uh?
Mariko and Shinji
told me something.
It's all up to us. Only
we can save the world!
[AYANO gasps]
[SARA]
Explosion in sector 23!
Enemy Knightmare
squad eliminated!
[OLIVIA] There's another squad
on the sector 4 castle wall!
[KNIGHT 5C] Changed ammo
to cluster warheads.
Loading is complete!
We've got the target in sight!
[gasps] Take cover! Hurry!
[OLIVIA] Sector 25's been hit!
They're firing at us!
[AYANO]
Leila, do you copy?
[LEILA]
Ayano?
Yukiya and I need our
machines prepped now.
Wait did you say Yukiya's
with you? Is he--?
[YUKIYA]
I'm fine.
[gasps]
[YUKIYA]
Leila. After all this time,
I finally get it.
Me hating this world
is never gonna change
anything for the better.
[YUKIYA]
So if it'll help my friends,
I might as well...
love the world.
[HAMMEL]
They're here!
Stay calm! We're not letting
go of this position!
The enemy forces have
just entered sector 13!
They're coming over
the northwest wall!
All we want is their commander!
Fire MPA cannon!
Take out that artillary!
[gasps]
[BRONDELLO groans]
[OLIVIA] They're gathering
at the control tower.
Olivia.
I'm ready.
We're the only ones who know
how to use these things.
[OLIVIA]
Hope we don't have to.
[JEAN]
Lord Hyuga,
I've just finished rewriting
the transport's flight program
at the launch site.
[SHIN] Good. Launch it
as soon as it's ready.
[SHIN]
Jean.
It won't be long now.
Everything... will be wiped out.
Yes, Lord Hyuga.
[AYANO] Freeze! One wrong move
and it'll be your last!
There's nowhere to run.
Nobody has to get hurt.
We can talk.
No way.
I've heard of you.
You're the lady knight
Ashley told us about.
[AYANO]
He told us the whole story.
[JEAN] Stop talking and
get down on the ground.
You're getting ready
to blow up Pendragon.
The whole world's
gonna be torn apart.
Is that really okay with you?
[grunts] I told you to
get on the ground!
[AYANO]
I know what it feels like.
To want to do everything
the person you love says.
But listen. That's not
what love's about.
Stay away!
Being in love with someone means
doing what's best for them.
[JEAN]
Silence!
Not just doing what they wan--
[groans]
That's not how you show
someone that you care.
How I feel is irrelevant to me.
The only thing that matters now
is Lord Hyuga's objective!
I'm going to make it come true!
Even if you obey his every word,
it won't be enough to
make him love you back.
[gasps]
If that's true...
...then what should I do now?
Got you.
[ALL gasping]
[SARA] We've lost signal from
the observation balloon!
Don't panic!
We can still track their
position from the sensors!
Yes ma'am!
[AKITO]
Stop this now!
[SHIN] The only cure for
foolishness... is death!
[AKITO grunts]
Just stop!
We're too close! Back off!
[YUKIYA]
I don't think so.
Lieutenant Naruse?
The best way to handle a bully
is to get right up in his face.
[KNIGHT 5F]
He's closing in!
[KNIGHT 5G]
Shoot him, quick!
[KNIGHT 5C]
He's in our blind spot!
Fire antipersonnel cannon!
Now die, Akito!
You first!
Evasive maneuvers!
Bye, bye.
[KNIGHTS scream]
Yukiya!
Dammit! That's as far
as you're gonna get!
They're swarming us guys!
We'll have to swat
the lot of them!
Akito!
[AKITO gasping]
There's a spike in
Akito's brainwaves!
The BRS is rapidly
becoming entangled.
[FERILLI]
A wave resonance?
[KATE] Ashley and Sayama
have completely synced
with Captain Hyuga!
What's the BRS operation rate?
[KATE]
Uh! Over 300%, doctor!
[LEILA gasps]
Akito!
He's disappeared?
This place...
[OLD MAN 5A] I must congratulate
you, Young Master.
You now have a younger brother.
Shin. Come and
meet your brother.
Why don't you
introduce yourself?
So he's... my brother?
[CROWD chatting]
[SHIN]
I realized it in an instant.
Who Akito's real father was.
Sara! Can you track Akito
and the enemy Knightmare?
I lost sight of them.
Somehow... their signals
just vanished!
Oh, come on! Not right now!
Must be the brainwave resonance.
I think it's interfering
with spacetime.
Could this be a singularity?
You should take
my life as well.
Just kill me.
Let me finally be free
from your cruelty.
[SHIN'S FATHER]
Foolish woman.
You may have betrayed me,
but that has no bearing
on how the world works
or your place within it.
Instead, I will spare you,
and as punishment for your sins,
you will remain at my side
for the rest of your
miserable life.
You're a monster.
[SHIN]
Disgusting.
That I was born of
this harlot's womb.
The thought makes me sick.
[AKITO]
But...
She's still our mother, Shin.
[SOPHIE] It must've fused
with Akito's waveform.
Actually, no. No,
they're resonating.
Joe Wise! Is there
a telemetry error?
Nope. I'm not seeing any
obvious program errors!
There's an anomaly
in the BRS values.
Oh, no! I can't track
any of the Alexanders.
The coordinates are too jumbled!
It might be a Penrose effect.
What's the correlation
of the brainwaves
and spacetime movement?
[JOE] You're asking for a
comparison of mental
and physical phenomena?
[SOPHIE]
Yes.
The coordinates are
obviously scrambling
because of this anomaly
with the brainwaves.
If I understand correctly,
you're saying that
a human mind is affecting
the physical world?
[SOPHIE]
Perhaps. Easy to forget,
but the world around
us is only concrete
because we're here
to observe it.
The intersecting brainwaves
of multiple people
allows us to create an
observer much more powerful
than any one human being.
After all, our universe
is constructed
from the billions of
brains observing it.
Which are products
of the universe.
As Nietzsche once said,
"if you look into an abyss,
the abyss looks into you."
Never-ending cycles
such as this one
may make it possible for
us to alter the past,
or even create a new universe.
Uh. New universe. Say what?
[BOMBER 5A panting]
[BRONDELLO]
Let's go!
The enemy's breaching our
final defensive perimeter!
Oh, no!
[panting]
[GEASS SKULL chuckles]
Tell me, young one.
[SHIN gasps]
[GEASS SKULL]
Do you desire... power?
[SHIN]
Yes. If I had the power,
I could punish this
sickening world.
[GEASS SKULL]
All those who bear true hatred
for this miserable world
shall inherit my power.
You'll find none more
worthy of it than me.
I promise you that.
[GEASS SKULL] But if you accept
it, your life will be solitude.
[GEASS SKULL laughs]
[SHIN]
I'm not afraid to be alone.
In fact, I hunger for it.
[OLIVIA]
They're inside the corridor!
Take shelter in
the command post!
[ALL gasping]
Chloe?
I'm so scared, Hilda!
[LEILA gasps]
[ANNA]
Chloe! Hilda!
Don't shoot us!
You don't have to--
[CLAUS]
Commander!
Hold your fire! Stop shooting!
[BRONDELLO]
So much blood.
Lieutenant Colonel.
[BRONDELLO gasps]
[LEILA]
Anna? Dr. Randle?
You can't all be... No.
[CROWD chattering, laughing]
[LEILA]
Where am I?
[BREISGAU]
Hello, Mademoiselle.
You seem perhaps a little lost.
Can we help you find something?
Oh, Bradow. This woman
is clearly a soldier.
You should address her formally.
[BREISGAU]
Ha, ha. I'm sorry.
--[LEILA] Father? Mother?
--I've never seen that uniform.
Whoa!
Akito!
No!
[AYANO]
Look out!
[MANFREDI]
You have great potential.
In Britannia, you
can become a knight
even if you are an Eleven.
If you're a good fighter.
[ALICE]
Look, Mother!
What a delightful little boat!
[ALICE laughs]
[SHIN]
Alice. Your hands are freezing.
I think that's enough
for now, don't you?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[LEILA gasps]
They're alive!
[CARETAKER]
It's difficult for humans
to balance instinct
with intellect.
I'm sure you understand
that, Leila.
I'm sorry, but who are you?
[CARETAKER]
I am no one.
Outside the perspective
of those who observe me,
I don't exist.
[LEILA]
Like the witch in the forest.
[CARETAKER]
Oh no, she's a human. Like you.
Just think of me...
Rather... Perhaps you
should think of us
as a sort of collective
consciousness,
if that makes sense to you.
An entity that effects the
evolution of the universe.
I'm confused.
Are you saying you're the one
who decides the fates of humans?
[CARETAKER]
Not at all.
You sought power for
yourself and claimed it.
But that power isn't
quite the same as mine.
Listen. I just want everyone
to live and be happy.
[CARETAKER] The most basic
desire of every living thing
is to continue to exist.
But the fact remains,
all things must one
day disappear.
That may be true,
but our lives are
still worth living.
[CARETAKER]
Yes, there is a certain beauty
to the fragility of humans.
But you're different. You wield
a fragment of a greater power.
A fragment?
Of the Geass,
which I've come to think
is beyond your kind.
Perhaps we should remove
it from your world.
[LEILA]
Geass?
You know, in the
beginning I thought
humans weren't all that
special as a species.
I thought you couldn't and
didn't deserve to use the Geass.
That you ought to go extinct.
[LEILA]
Please, wait!
[CARETAKER] But given
the way things turned out,
perhaps you can prove me wrong.
Assuming you can stop that
man and his corrupt Geass,
of course.
[gasps]
We have explosions
at the control tower!
[LEILA grunts]
What about the Liberte?
[CHLOE]
Still can't get a signal!
[LEILA gasps]
Joe Wise! Record this, please!
Right. It's already recording!
[CHLOE]
Hilda, what's this?
[FERILLI]
Ashley's gone out of control!
[KATE]
Doctor!
I'm sending you the
brainwave measurement!
[LEILA gasps]
The enemy's breaching our
final defensive perimeter!
[gasps] Apply the
anti-explosion gel!
Roger!
[KNIGHT 5D grunts]
[KNIGHT 5D] I'm sorry, sir,
we can't destroy the door!
[BRONDELLO]
A blast-proof hatch?
[OLIVIA]
They're inside the corridor!
Commander! Should we use
the gas to wipe them out?
Not yet!
Open up a channel
to the outside.
I'll talk to their leader.
Come on. Snap out of it!
[SHIN yells]
[LEILA] We would like
to request a cease-fire.
We have no desire to
fight you any longer.
A woman?
[LEILA]
This is Leila Breisgau.
The Commander of this base.
[AKITO]
Commander.
[LEILA]
Uh?
[AKITO]
I know this beautiful painting,
of a woman with an angel.
The woman in the picture
looks a lot like you.
This is the one.
It must have been hanging
in the house I grew up in.
Did you like this painting
when you were a child?
I don't know.
But I do like the expression
on the lady's face.
She looks so kind.
[LEILA]
Akito.
[LEILA grunts]
What's wrong?
Lieutenant Colonel. Shut
down the command center.
What?!
[SHIN groans]
You're different now.
[SHIN groaning]
Brother!
I'm gonna make sure you suffer!
[AKITO grunts]
[AKITO grunting]
[RYO screams]
[gasps]
No!
I'm not losing another teammate!
Hey! You're pretty tough.
I was hoping for a challenge!
Silence! It's over for you!
[ASHLEY groaning]
[AKITO]
Stop this now!
[AKITO yelling]
[SHIN yelling]
[LEILA]
Akito!
[RYO grunting]
Dammit, it's stuck!
How'm I supposed to get out?
Akito!
[SHIN cries]
Mother.
Oh, Mother.
I'm going to miss you.
Listen. I'm so sorry.
But at least now, you'll
never get hurt again.
[AKITO]
Big brother?
[SHIN]
Mm?
What's happening?
Akito. You're not
supposed to be alive.
This world is cruel.
You're so innocent.
[SHIN] I imagine what this
place will do to you and--
[AKITO laughs]
[SHIN]
I can't bear it.
Akito... Die.
[AKITO]
Brother. Don't do this.
Killing everyone isn't
gonna solve anything!
Of course not.
I'm well aware of that.
But still, I know.
It's what they truly want.
Even you crave violence
like the rest of them.
You're wrong!
[SHIN] Let me give you
this gift brother!
Your suffering in this
miserable world...
...ends now!
[AKITO whimpers]
Akito!
[SHIN yelling]
[AKITO groans]
I will kill you, Akito! I swear!
Death is a blessing!
I'm just doing
what's best for you!
Don't do it!
Leave him alone!
Please, don't!
Begone, spirits!
[MANFREDI] You truly love
your younger brother.
[SHIN grunts]
You wish to free
the people you love
from the pain
of human existence.
We understand.
[MARIA] We realize that your
intentions are noble, my son.
That said,
I don't think that killing is
the answer to your fears.
I know what I'm doing!
[ALICE]
Brother,
we don't doubt that you did
this out of your love for us.
But still. It seems your
methods are misguided.
This world is full
of possibilities.
There must be a better way.
That woman there.
She clearly believes it.
There is no other way.
Not in this world!
Shin, please don't kill Akito.
So he means that much
to you, does he?
If you loved me, you would
have killed him at birth!
Please believe me.
I loved both of you
with all my heart!
Liar!
[AKITO]
Listen! Just stop!
[SHIN]
It has to be this way!
[AKITO groans]
[SHIN grunting]
Akito!
You're supposed to
die at my hands.
Why can't you see that?
I'm not letting you kill Akito!
[SHIN growls]
Stay away from our friend!
Akito. You're safe.
We're with you!
[SHIN]
Hm? Uh.
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[HAMMEL]
Don't harm him.
[SOLDIER 5C]
I won't let you kill Akito!
[SOPHIE]
Listen to us.
[JOE]
You can't kill Akito!
Enough of this!
[SHIN yelling]
[LEILA]
Ah!
I don't want you...
to suffer any longer.
[SHIN] How could you
possibly understand, Jean?
I-I love you, Lord Hyuga.
I always have.
[SHIN]
Stupid woman.
Just like my mother.
Look what you've done.
[AKITO grunting]
[SHIN grunts]
[AKITO]
Brother!
[SHIN]
Just go away!
[AKITO]
No! I won't!
I won't.
[SHIN grunting]
[AKITO]
Big brother?
Big brother!
[SHIN sniffles]
Go away!
Come back, Shin.
Let's go home.
Get lost!
[AKITO cries]
[SHIN]
Stop crying.
[crying continues]
I said stop!
[SHIN]
Come on. Climb on my back.
[AKITO]
Thank you.
[SHIN]
No more crying Akito, okay?
[AKITO]
I love you, Shin.
Akito.
[AKITO]
Shin.
Brother.
Are you...?
[SHIN]
You can let go. You won't be...
...alone when I'm gone.
[SHIN] This world may be
cruel, but... [groaning]
I want you to live.
[AKITO]
Where are you--?
[SHIN]
Jean. Jeanne...
[JEAN]
Shin.
[SHIN]
I'm here.
[JEAN]
Shin! I've missed you so!
[SHIN]
I'm so sorry, Jeanne.
We're together now. For good.
[JEAN]
I'm glad, Shin.
[LEILA]
Akito.
[FEMALE JUGEND 3A] Enemy units
have emerged from the pillbox.
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
It seems they'd rather die
than surrender.
Yes, so it seems.
[SMILAS]
Uh!
[ASHLEY]
Uhh! That was quite a ride.
That sounds like... Could it be?
I would know that red
Knightmare anywhere!
Master Ashley!
Is that you?
We've waited so long!
Master Ashley!
[ASHLEY]
Of course you guys survived!
That's my Ashra Force!
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
General!
An enemy Knightmare
force is inbound!
Take them down!
[CARETAKER] He's willing to face
anything for his comrades.
You should be more
like him, Gene Smilas.
[SMILAS gasping]
But sadly, you won't
get the chance.
[ALL screaming]
[ANCHOR 5A]
The death of General Smilas
marks the end of Europia's
experiment in dictatorship.
Now, once again,
Europia will be a republic
of and by the people.
[FARNESE] The rebellion by
the Holy Order of Michael
gave the homeland the excuse
they needed to intervene.
I'm very sorry, Your Highness.
[VELAINES] It is quite a shame.
Tell me, Lord Farnese.
[gasps]
The Europian commander
who sent in the
Ghost of Hannibal.
Do you have any information
regarding this person?
[FARNESE] I only know that her
name was Leila Breisgau, sir.
[VELAINES]
Just as I thought.
It's come to my attention that
the castle Shaing attacked
happened to belong
to the Breisgau family
before the revolution 300
years ago. Quite interesting.
We'll be mindful of the
Briesgau name going forward.
[VELAINES] Indeed. We can
only hope that someday
a descendant of
the Breisgau line
returns to claim
that land again.
[ANOU groans]
[CON ARTIST 3E]
Ugh. Good grief.
For a former soldier,
you sure are useless.
[ANOU sighs]
I know. I'm sorry.
[AYANO]
Stop goofing around, Anou.
What are we gonna do with you?
You sure know how to
handle a knife, Yukiya!
[GRANNY 3C]
He can handle me any day!
Look at him.
He's even more
handsome now that...
[YUKIYA] Hey. Cut it out!
You're embarrassing me!
[RYO]
Whoa! What is this?
You better not be
groping Yukiya!
We've got plenty of love
for you too, hot stuff.
Ah. I mean, I guess
I won't stop you.
[GRANNY 3B]
Ooh, you're so strong and manly!
Oh, you think so?
Yeah, I guess I am!
[ASHLEY] Well, aren't you
popular with the ladies?
[RYO]
Uh.
[ALL]
Ashley!
[BOTH gasp]
Uh, hello.
[AKITO]
Are you sure about this?
[gasps]
Of course I am.
I've really come to enjoy
the life we have here.
Just take a look around us.
It's so beautiful.
Um... What do you think?
I think so, too.
I've got such a big family now.
[LEILA laughs]
Let's head back now,
Commander. Okay?
I mean... Leila.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[ROLO]
Don't be alarmed.
I'm here to retrieve you.
[JULIUS gasping]
[ROLO] It would appear
His Imperial Majesty
wishes to meet with Lord
Julius Kingsley once more.
[ROLO] Won't you return
to Britannia with us,
Sir Kururugi?