[LEILA] Revolutionary
Calendar, year 228.
After the battle of Slonim,
Leila, Akito and the others
were stranded in Warsaw,
where their bonds
of trust deepened.
Meanwhile, due to propaganda
from Britannia's
military advisor,
Julius Kingsley,
riots engulfed Europia
under the shadow
of a warship called the Ark.
Akito and the others set
their sights on the Ark
in hopes of preventing
a Britannian invasion.
[G1 OP 4A]
The course is clear.
You'll be able to reach
ten kilometers in one go.
Ah. A Float System?
The homeland has
outdone themselves.
[G1 OP 4A]
Commencing countdown.
[JEAN] Confirming destination.
Entry complete.
Auto-nav system... activated.
Hilda, Chloe.
Status update on
Alexander Variants.
Everything looks okay.
[CHLOE]
No problems.
[SARA] T-minus eight
minutes to liftoff!
Countdown has commenced!
[OLIVIA]
All systems are go!
[LEILA grunts]
All right.
Just to be on the safe side,
let's confirm BRS, Joe.
So far it looks, uh,
fine, Doctor Randle.
Make sure that you
come home safely.
Fingers crossed, eh?
And now we wait.
[SARA]
All systems ready!
Start the main engine now!
So, that's Apollo's Chariot.
It's beautiful.
[SARA] T-minus 30 seconds
to fairing separation.
27... 26... 25...
Capsule reentering
in ten more seconds!
8... 7...
[ASHLEY laughs]
I can't wait to see you again.
Akito Hyuga. [laughs]
[SARA]
Separation successful!
And confirmed!
[CHLOE]
All Alexanders show green!
[RYO grunts]
[YUKIYA]
Hmph.
[AYANO grunts]
[AKITO gasps]
Wyvern Squad has a
visual on the Ark!
[LEILA exhales]
[OLIVIA]
Commencing countdown!
25... 24...
...23... 22... 21...
[OLIVIA] Observation balloon
has a lock on Wyvern Squad!
This is it. They've
arrived at the Ark!
This feels weird, right?
[OLIVIA gasping]
[SARA] Still closing in! Ark
interior scan data received!
[gasps] Captain Clement!
I've finished
analyzing the data.
But it's strange.
[LEILA]
How so?
In relation to volume,
its mass isn't big enough.
It's almost as if...
It's... nearly empty.
Wyvern Squad!
Requesting weapons!
The Alexanders have
gone to combat output!
Somebody's home!
There's more than I thought.
[SARA]
They're engaging the enemy!
[LEILA]
But who?
And how many?
[SARA]
Still analyzing!
[CLAUS growls]
[JOANNES] Good luck to you,
Master... Ashley.
Oh, Joannes.
You must be getting
lonely over there.
[SIMON]
Master Ashley!
Please, Master!
We're begging you!
Why won't you allow
us to come too?
Let us accompany you!
Master Ashley!
I will not repeat myself!
I'm going alone, you hear me?!
Just you wait. I promise
I'll avenge you.
Even if it kills me!
[gasps] This is...
Emergency message from Joint HQ!
Joint HQ? And who is it from?
It's a direct line,
from General Smilas!
[gasps]
Put it on the main screen!
Thank goodness
you're safe, General.
[SMILAS]
I'm fine, yes.
But the government and the
military they are scattering.
Paris is in shambles.
It's bad. But, I won't be
going anywhere. Trust me.
Sir, the... The cause of
the riots you speak of.
The Ark Fleet is...
...a bluff by the
Euro-Britannian Army.
[SMILAS]
Do you have proof of this?
[LEILA]
A mission is currently underway
to get the Wyvern Squad
onto the Ark, sir.
So far it seems the
only thing aboard
are a few Britannian
Knightmares.
We must relay this to the
people of Europia at once!
That may not be too
helpful at this point.
Leila.
This frustration with the
government has built over years.
We may have to let it
burn out on its own.
But, sir. There must be
something we can still do.
Anything at all!
Then our best bet is
if it comes from you.
[gasps]
Only you can reach them now.
Only you can find the words.
They'll listen to you.
For you're the daughter
of Bradow Von Breisgau.
These damn Knightmares
are a dead giveaway.
Britannia's behind this!
[RYO]
Ayano!
They're quick to run,
aren't they?
This thing is...
These things are just drones.
[RYO] Heh. They don't know
who they're messing with!
They're everywhere!
Are you reading me, Ryo?
[ASHLEY laughs]
About time.
I was getting sick of waiting!
[ASHLEY]
Heh. Ha!
[laughs] I'll take you apart!
Now... die!
Akito!
[RYO growls]
Ryo!
[ASHLEY laughs]
Die! Die!
Wait. Is that...?
It's that red Knightmare.
Ah, man.
And Schrötter Steel armor?
To the citizens of Europia.
Please listen to my words
with an open mind.
It is the height of
foolishness to riot
in response to Britannian
media manipulation.
I lead a unit that battles
Euro-Britannia covertly.
[SARA]
Connected!
Link to all of
Europia confirmed!
[LEILA]
What's more,
these soldiers fighting
on the front lines
are those we call Elevens.
And keep in internment camps.
They are the Japanese.
Out of fear--
fear of the Britannian empire--
we are robbing them
of their freedom.
[AKITO grunts]
You'll never escape!
You're dead!
He's all over Akito!
Yukiya! Ryo!
I'm going in!
Ayano?
Akito! It's all yours!
[LEILA] Britannia's flying
weapon doesn't exist.
After terrifying the
people of Europia,
and breaking us with discord,
they will invade and
occupy us militarily.
[AKITO exhales]
Normal rounds won't work.
But these might.
[RYO grunting]
[ASHLEY]
Heh. Die!
You've got to be joking!
Knock it off!
[ASHLEY]
Oh, no you don't!
Why do we hurt one another?
[LEILA] Why must we find solace
in the diminishing of others?
Die.
[AKITO]
Die!
We cannot let ourselves
be ruled by hate!
Go to hell, bastard!
Akito!
We need freedom.
In every aspect
of our existence.
C'mon.
[LEILA] However. With freedom
comes responsibility...
Die!
[LEILA]
...so we may live peacefully!
So that we may improve
on our own world!
[AKITO]
Die!
[ASHLEY growls]
You know,
my father, Bradow Von
Breisgau, always believed
that this was the
future of Europia.
Die. Die!
This is...
Again?
[AKITO]
Die!
[gasps] No! Akito!
[JOE groaning]
[KATE] There's a spike
in Akito's brainwaves!
Neuro-devices are
out of control!
BRS event is in progress.
Record it! Now, Joe Wise!
[JOE]
I'm doing my best, Doctor!
I need more time!
Die!
[AKITO]
[ASHLEY grunts]
Damn you, angel of death!
Die.
Die!
[ASHLEY]
You'll never take me!
[AKITO]
Die.
[AYANO]
Akito, that's enough!
[AKITO gasps]
[ASHLEY groaning]
[ASHLEY]
Joannes.
Bastard! You killed him!
What? Just kill me, you monster!
Kill me like you killed Joannes!
Hurry up!
Die.
[ASHLEY groans]
I'm waiting.
[AKITO gasping]
Akito...
[AKITO]
Die.
[ASHLEY groaning]
[AKITO]
Die!
[ASHLEY groaning]
[RYO]
No!
Stop, Akito!
Please, there's been
enough killing already.
Let it go!
Take control.
Don't let your pain
eat you alive!
[AYANO]
Akito! Akito!
This isn't you!
Don't let this thing
make you a monster!
[gasps]
Now's the time
that true freedom
can be ours if we
reach out and take it!
[ASHLEY gasping]
[ASHLEY coughing]
So I will not give up!
[AKITO panting]
I'll face the darkness.
My name is Leila Breisgau.
And I hope you will
stand with me.
That's really
Breisgau's daughter?
Leila Breisgau!
[ALL]
Leila Breisgau! Leila Breisgau!
[ASHLEY gasping]
[AKITO]
Go ahead.
Avenge your friend, soldier.
Kill me.
[ASHLEY gasps]
[inaudible]
[gasps]
[ASHLEY sighs]
Well. All out of bullets.
Just my luck.
Right, Joannes?
You're kidding me.
[YUKIYA]
Mm? He misses his buddy.
Oh, just grow up, Yukiya!
[YUKIYA]
Yeah, yeah.
All of the Wyvern Squad
beacons just vanished!
What in the world just happened?
[LEILA]
What's the Ark's status?
It disappeared, too. I'm
re-scanning as we speak.
Did it... Did the Ark explode?
[LEILA gasping]
Akito.
What's wrong? Why have
we lost their vitals?
Everyone's biometrics...
Signals aren't
back online yet!
A bug. It must be.
[JOE cries]
[SARA]
Olivia. Any luck?
No. And no guide, either.
[CLAUS] We cannot give up
on them! Just keep trying!
[beeping]
[ALL gasp]
What is it?!
[SARA] Units with unknown codes
have breached the perimeter!
And they're heading our way?
Yes.
[SARA]
Most likely Britannian.
Knightmares, huh?
Please. I wish for us
to go together Alice.
Can't we?
Yes.
We will, Mother.
[AKITO gasps]
Someone's certainly in a hurry.
[LEILA gasps]
Get up!
The enemy's here. You're needed!
[LEILA]
I just...
I'm sorry. I can't.
Just suck it up!
[ANNA gasps]
[HAMMEL]
Uh?!
[ALL gasp]
[CLAUS]
On your feet!
Come on. You still have
your duties to perform.
[LEILA]
Uh.
You have a responsibility here.
There are lives that
need protecting.
[LEILA gasps]
[CLAUS] You're the
Commander, aren't you?
Act like it.
[footsteps]
Report enemy positions!
[ALL gasp]
[SARA]
Right!
Leila...
Distance, 25.
From the northeast!
Speed is a 140
kilometers per hour!
A hundred forty?
Through a forest?
Any thoughts, Captain Clement?
Moving in such dense foliage
at that rate is unheard of.
But possible on four legs.
A four-legged Knightmare?
[gasps]
[AKITO]
Brother.
[CLAUS]
Uh...
[LEILA]
The minefield.
Activate southea--
No, wait! Make that
all defense systems!
Uh!
Use everything we
have to stop them!
They saw us already?
They seem smarter than
Europia's frontline forces.
This ought to be fun.
[SARA]
Enemy speed is maintaining.
[OLIVIA]
Approaching minefield!
Detonation confirmed!
[SARA]
Enemy speed isn't slowing!
[CLAUS]
That means it's running faster
than the mines can detonate.
Enemy is changing course!
Shifting 12 degrees eastward!
[gasps]
Lord Hyuga! You've gone
out too far ahead!
Lord Hyuga!
[SHIN]
Jean, support fire. Here.
Support... commencing.
Front gate taking fire!
Sigma System 3 down!
Defensive wall activation...
90 seconds!
[SHIN grunts]
[SHIN growls]
[JEAN]
My Lord!
Lord Hyuga.
Are you all right?
Lord Hyuga!
A wall sprouted
around the castle.
Scout it out.
[exhales]
Yes, Lord Hyuga.
That was pretty clever.
This commander is going to
offer quite a challenge.
[OLIVIA] The defensive
wall has been deployed!
[SARA] We've got a visual
on the Knightmare!
Heh. Nice effort.
But you'll have to
try harder than that.
[LEILA] Maintain highest
state of alert for 24 hours.
And... Also.
Keep hailing Wyvern Squad.
[SARA]
Roger.
Hey.
Perhaps now is a good time to
get a little rest, Commander?
[LEILA]
I'm not tired.
I'll handle things
around here.
Might be the only
chance you get.
[LEILA]
Lieutenant Colonel.
Sara? You and I are
staying here, okay?
[SARA]
Sir!
[CLAUS] The rest of you
can go on a quick break!
[ALL]
Huh?
There. See?
Keep an eye on things here.
I'll be back soon.
[CLAUS]
Heh, heh.
[HAMMEL]
Lieutenant Colonel.
[CLAUS]
Hm?
Do you think Akito
and the others
will make it back alive?
C'mon. Those guys would
never die that easily.
[HAMMEL]
Mm.
[SHIN]
As soon as the Order arrives,
we launch a full-scale assault.
Jean, I'll leave command to you.
[JEAN]
Yes, Lord!
[SHIN]
Akito...
Still alive out there?
Eliza.
Akito.
[CLAUS]
Sorry about this, Sara.
But you and Olivia are the
only military personnel.
Oh, I understand.
I have been trained to handle
long-duration
missions like this.
That so?
Still, if it's up to me,
I'd rather this castle not
turn into a battlefield.
[JULIUS]
Suzaku.
Hey, Suzaku.
It's hot again today.
Look, Suzaku.
[JULIUS]
The sunflower.
Isn't it pretty?
I think so.
Don't you? Isn't it pretty?
[MESSENGER 4A]
The Order of Michael's Black,
Blue, and White Regiments
have all arrived, sir.
Have all troops take
their positions.
Remain on 24-hour
combat alert.
Tell them not to forget
where they are.
[MESSENGER 4A]
Yes, Lord!
[CROWD] Leila Breisgau!
Leila Breisgau!
Leila Breisgau! Leila
Breisgau! Leila Breisgau!
C'mon, let us see Breisgau!
Yeah, show us our Leila!
[FEMALE 4A]
Please, take these flowers!
If you would,
give them to Leila.
Leila Breisgau!
[ANNOUNCER 4A] Stand by for
an emergency broadcast.
The provisional government
has a very important message
for you, the citizens.
[PATRONS gasping]
[CROWD gasping]
Citizens of Europia.
I'm afraid that I have terrible
news to report to you.
I've received word
the woman who inspired
so many of us
with her courage and hope,
Leila Breisgau
has been killed.
[CROWD gasping]
[SMILAS]
Leila Breisgau has...
...been killed.
She will live on forever
in our memories.
[SMILAS]
We now have confirmed reports
that Weiswolf Castle Base,
where Leila Breisgau
was stationed,
was destroyed by
Euro-Britannians.
Though it's located roughly
1,000 kilometers away
from the border between
us and Euro-Britannia,
our enemy crossed over
and attacked it.
I shall continue what
Leila Breisgau began.
The Euro-Britannians may
have killed our Leila,
but I will make them pay.
[SMILAS]
For centuries,
our ancestors were exploited
by royals and nobility.
And then, they freed themselves
by means of the Revolution.
Much blood was spilled,
but those who spilled it were
unsatisfied and called for more.
They finally avenged a
millennium of injustices
by killing royals.
Nobles.
All who abused power.
And now,
descendants of the
kings and nobles
who escaped to the New World
have returned to take
their revenge on us!
[CLAUS] It's starting to look
like General Smilas' regime
has assumed full
control of Europia.
[SMILAS] Soon, the descendants
of those fiends
will enter the lands they were
driven from by the Revolution
and try to reclaim them!
He's cut a deal.
Some sort of agreement
with Britannia.
Do you have any proof
to support that?
I'm in touch with
the Brittainians.
I sold them intel.
[gasps]
[CLAUS] If the General really
did care for you, tell me.
Why'd he make me your
second in command. Hmm?
You needed money for your
daughter's medical bills.
[growls]
So you knew I was a liability
and still let me do this?
I have faith in you.
Well you shouldn't!
I am a spineless liar!
[CLAUS sighs] Just hand over the
castle and the secret weapon.
That's what
Euro-Britannia wants.
That's the only way you guys are
going to get out of this alive.
If Euro-Britannia
gets their hands
on the ultra-long
range Transport,
war will cross the
globe like wildfire.
You can risk your neck
fighting if you want to.
It won't change anything.
The world's not
that nice a place.
I only want--
Listen to me!
You just need to worry
about saving your life,
and the lives of everyone here!
That's more than enough!
Nobody could fault you
for that, could they?
[SMILAS] Don't hesitate
to lay down your lives
in the name of freedom!
Though you may die,
the light of your resolve
shall shine on!
Do not cling to a
life of slavery!
I for one, plan to fight!
Fight for freedom!
Rabble-rousers like him
aren't the ones who suffer.
They just make a
mountain of corpses,
and use them as stepping
stones to reach
whatever the hell they're after.
[SMILAS] Fellow citizens!
Stand with me!
The tomorrow Breisgau
fought for,
and tried to protect,
will be ours!
[CROWD cheering]
The General's trying to make
himself emperor of Europia.
You were just a
means to that end.
[CLAUS] I'll set up negotiations
with Euro-Britannia.
Please, draw up a
letter of surrender.
[BRONDELLO] We would like
to see Lord Shaing.
[JEAN] If there is an issue,
I shall see to it.
Our Grand Master is very busy
with Euro-Britannian
government affairs.
[DORE] You don't have to
tell us that, you know.
We're perfectly aware.
[SCHOLZ]
Right, and that's the problem!
We demand that he explains
why we must cross the border
to take some crumbly castle
in the middle of nowhere!
[JEAN]
If you don't know the reason,
then will you be
afraid to fight?
You dare to insult the Three
Swordmasters of Michael?
[JEAN] It seems in quite
poor form for a knight
to draw his sword so
lightly, is it not?
Is this what Lord
Manfredi taught you?
What did you say?!
Scholz, that's enough!
[DORE]
We allow no one
to mock our honorable
master, Lord Manfredi!
[JEAN] Your Lord Manfredi
is dead and gone.
[SWORDMASTERS gasp]
[JEAN]
What's more, as per his will,
Lord Shaing is now Grand Master
of the Holy Order of Michael.
[BRONDELLO gasps]
[JEAN]
In which case...
...your duty as knights
is to obey his orders.
Prove on the battlefield
the spotless reputation of
the Three Swordmasters
is not a lie.
When is this battle
to occur, then?!
I cannot tell you
that just yet,
but I am certain that when
the battle finally arrives,
the Three Swordmasters of
the Holy Order of Michael
will be ready.
[SHIN'S MOTHER]
Shin.
My sweet little boy.
[SHIN'S MOTHER]
Shin.
My darling.
[SHIN'S MOTHER] It was not
my desire for you to turn out
the same way your father did.
I beg your forgiveness!
Forgiveness?
You were no mother to me.
You threw that away when
you debased yourself.
[SHIN'S MOTHER]
Then at least forgive Akito!
The avatar of your betrayal?
Your father was a great
man in many ways, Shin.
He loved you.
But his cruelty knew no end.
He killed Akito's father.
And then you killed me.
Your own mother.
The woman who gave birth to you!
Leave me alone!
[SHIN'S MOTHER screams]
[MANFREDI]
Shin. My little brother.
Shin Hyuga.
Lord Manfredi.
[MANFREDI]
Hurry to my side.
Shin, we must stand
together once again.
[SHIN]
I won't be long.
Patience. I will join you...
Manfredi.
[MARIA]
I am also waiting.
I may only be your
foster mother,
but I love you all the same.
And I you, Maria.
I hope to... see you again.
[ALICE]
Brother.
I... really miss you, too.
I'm so very cold. Please hurry.
Hurry up and join us, Brother.
Please. Say that you will.
If I am able.
I love you all.
[JEAN] Lord Hyuga!
What are you doing?
Stop it, please!
It's like their ghosts
are haunting me.
No. Surely there is no
such thing as ghosts.
There is nothing decent in this
world that would be worth
hanging around for.
[SHIN laughs]
If it meant I could be with you,
I would follow you
to Hell itself.
[HAMMEL]
Please stand clear!
[ANNA]
Be careful, Leila.
Don't be worried, Anna.
Go prep the Alexanders
so that they're ready
to be disarmed immediately.
You'll be notified when the
negotiations have concluded.
Huh?
If you're thinking of joining
the Commander, sir,
who will be in charge
of Weiswolf Castle
if something goes wrong?
Well, I suppose,
you can do it, Major Hammel.
[HAMMEL]
But I'm not qualified!
[CLAUS] Then it's a good thing
it probably won't come to that.
Just keep an eye on things.
[CLAUS] It's gotten colder.
I hope it doesn't stick.
So you're the
Schwarzwald Mole?
That's right.
This is the draft of
the surrender document.
Our one condition
is that you allow
all base personnel
to leave here unharmed.
[JEAN] Where's the base's
decryption cypher?
[CLAUS laughs] Oh, it's in
there if you really want it.
[JEAN] And the data
on Apollo's Chariot?
[CLAUS]
Inside.
[JEAN] In appreciation
of your hard work,
I could arrange for asylum
in Euro-Brittania.
[CLAUS]
Heh.
That's kind of you.
I might take you up on that.
[SHIN]
Ancient Roman ruins.
You have excellent taste,
Lieutenant Colonel.
[LEILA] And do you find
my terms acceptable?
[SHIN] Theres no need
to rush. We have time.
To think that a girl like you
actually planned the Ghost
of Hannibal operations.
They were quite the surprise.
We Euro-Britannians suffered
heavy losses thanks to you.
[LEILA grunts]
[SHIN]
Now, don't misunderstand me.
I have no desire for
revenge against you.
No. I wish only to thank you.
Wait, thank me?
[SHIN]
The Euro-Britannian nobles
used to rely on chivalry
nonsense from the Middle Ages.
Till you struck fear into them.
[laughing]
Most entertaining.
Anyway, they fell
right into my lap.
Even sooner than
I had anticipated.
Lord Shaing. This is not
the first time we've met.
[SHIN]
Hmm?
Hmph.
I see.
You were the one
in that Knightmare.
Is that right?
Lieutenant Hyuga...
He said you're...
...his brothe--
Akito is dead now.
[LEILA gasps]
A brother who would
disobey my command
is of no use to me.
But Akito is still alive!
[SHIN]
Hmm?
And what do you know about it?
[LEILA]
I just know what he promised me.
Heh.
Akito told me about what
you did to your family.
About what you did to him.
What of it?
Akito said he'd stop you.
And I believe him!
How revolting.
[SHIN]
You whiney sentimental types,
you make me sick.
You 'believe'?
You still don't get it, do you?
That you've been betrayed?
[LEILA]
You mean General Smilas?
[SHIN]
Allow me to edify you.
Faith and loyalty are
nothing more than illusions
devised by the clever
to exploit the stupid.
Do you really think that mankind
is worth believing in?
If I didn't, Lord Shaing,
how can I ask anyone
to follow me?
[laughing]
That's why you've been
betrayed and exploited!
[gasps]
[SHIN] Humanity isn't noble and
good natured like a fairy tale.
We're animals.
It's always been every
man for himself.
Take yours and to
hell with others.
And it's only gotten worse.
[SHIN] These days, the more
miserable others are,
the easier it is for the
fortunate to convince themselves
that they are happy.
Such contemptible creatures.
That's just so sad.
What is?
You're broken!
[SHIN grunts]
Watch it!
[CLAUS growls]
Believe what you will.
You're pathetic.
You'll be gone from this
world before he's back.
Heh.
Die!
[SHIN groaning]
[SHIN]
Ah! What was that?
[JEAN]
Lord Hyuga!
[SHIN panting]
[JEAN]
Are you all right, Lord Hyuga?
[SHIN]
Yes.
What did you just do?
Lord Shaing, you want
Apollo's Chariot.
What are you going
to attack with it?
[SHIN grunts]
Pendragon.
[gasps] Brittania's capitol?
Pendragon?
[gasps]
[SHIN]
Correct.
So you're planning
to kill the emperor?
If he were to die now,
Britannia would--
No, not just Britannia.
The chaos would be widespread.
War would engulf the planet.
My plan exactly.
I want to see the whole
world buried in corpses.
You're... insane, aren't you?
[SHIN]
I do not accept your surrender.
We will conquer that castle,
and kill everyone.
Anything that I require,
I will take.
Jean. Kill both of them.
[JEAN]
Huh...
I'm sorry. I really am.
It's not use, you have
to surrender Claus!
Heh. Look, I know I'm a coward,
but even I would never do
something that spineless.
Stand back.
[JEAN gasps]
Things look rough down there.
Kill all of them.
[gasps] But Lord Hyuga...
They may still be of
use to us if we--!
--[SHIN grunts]
--[JEAN yelps]
[SHIN]
Shoot to kill!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[LEILA, CLAUS gasp]
You don't know when to give up.
Look, sir!
[SHIN]
Huh?!
[gasps]
[CLAUS]
Take cover!
Was that... an
explosion shockwave?
[OLIVIA]
Oui . It must have been.
[gasps] I'm receiving
a transmission!
The Alexander beacons
are back online?
Whose Alexander?
[SARA]
Synchronized!
[YUKIYA]
Hey guys! Do you read me?
[ALL gasp]
[YUKIYA] It's Wyvern Squad here!
If you read me, respond!
[gasps] Yukiya!
[YUKIYA]
Hey, Sara! Been a while.
You're sounding well.
[LEILA, CLAUS grunting]
Was that...?
[SHIN]
From above, huh?
[JEAN]
Lord Hyuga.
[SHIN]
It's Akito.
He is alive.
[ANNA] Did you see a
flash of light just now?
[HAMMEL]
I certainly did.
What do you think it was?
[ANNA gasps]
[ANNA]
An Alexander! Uh! Akito!
[HAMMEL] Uh. Wait.
You can tell it's Akito?
[SARA]
But how?
And why didn't you
radio us before?
[YUKIYA]
"To deceive one's enemies,
begin with one's allies."
That's mean!
We were so worried!
So they're... alive, after all!
I'm so happy!
There, there. It's
gonna be okay, Joe.
Nothing to cry about.
That's fantastic.
Just wonderful.
Akito! I see it!
Brother.
Akito!
[AYANO]
So tell me,
why are we trusting that guy?
The Ashley guy, I mean.
[YUKIYA] Jealous?
That's not a good look on you.
[gasps] Who are you calling
jealous? Jealous of who?
Please, you never could
hide your emotions.
Your face is an open book
Ayano. Always so dramatic.
What?
Wow, you've gotta be kidding me.
And from you of all people.
It's time, Ayano. Let's bail.
You and me are gonna have a long
talk when this is all over.
Yeah, yeah.
[RYO] We'll be waiting
for you on the ground!
Roger that.
I'm behind you, just gotta
make sure we're good here.
[AYANO]
Yukiya.
[YUKIYA]
Uh?
Don't keep us waiting.
[SHIN]
Well, Jean?
Isn't it just as I said?
Oh, crap! It's a
damn Knightmare!
Stay back!
It's the Vercingetorix! Akito!
Wait.
Akito.
[ASHLEY]
Lord Shaing!
Bastard.
You've got some nerve blowing
up the Ark with me on it!
[ASHLEY grunting] Hey, what
the hell are you doing?!
Shut up, you traitor!
I'll kill you myself!
[ASHLEY]
Get real!
It's you who's the
traitor, dammit!
Who the hell's that?
We have to get to the boat!
Hey! Just hold on a minute!
Surprise! Akito sent me!
Now let's get out of here!
And who are you exactly?
[SHIN] You haven't changed
one bit since then.
You're still just a child.
You've no clue how
the world works.
[AKITO]
That's not true Shin.
Violence won't change anything.
People insist on following the
same petty and feckless rulers.
I can't allow that to continue.
Akito,
if you are indeed
my little brother,
you of all people
should understand
what I'm trying to do.
Brother.
Stop it!
Commander?
Don't do this!
You're not like him!
[SHIN growls]
Akito! Kill that woman, now!
[AKITO whimpers]
[SHIN] You take your
orders from me alone!
[gasping]
[SHIN]
Kill her!
Kill her.
I can't.
Akito!
Let's go.
You're gonna want to hang on.
[SHIN]
Hmm?!
[gasps]
Lieutenant Colonel!
Akito! Jump on!
Ready? Hold on tight now.
I'm gonna jump.
Come on! Let's punch it!
[CLAUS] Huh? Sure, but it's
a little cold for a cruise.
[HAMMEL]
Uh!
[HAMMEL] The Commander
and Akito's Alexander?
All right!
Leila! Leila!
[YUKIYA]
I hate to do this.
But... It's war, after all.
[YUKIYA]
Sorry.
But I'm afraid that my
friends' lives come first.
[SOLDIERS chattering]
Regroup! [gasps]
Goddammit.
[SHIN]
The enemy's above the clouds.
I'm sending coordinates.
Shoot it down with a Canterbury.
[gasps]
God!
Yukiya.
Yukiya!
[SHIN]
Akito.
The time has come for me to kill
everyone you have ever loved.
And I'll do it...
...right before your eyes.