[LEILA]
Revolutionary year 228.
Seven years ago,
Japan was conquered
by the Holy Britannian Empire
and renamed Area 11.
In Europe, the United
Republic of Europia
remained resistant
against Britannia.
Leila entered battle
with Akito and the others.
During the fight, they
encountered a golden Knightmare
operated by Shin Hyuga Shaing.
Shaing is Akito's older brother,
whom he had not seen
since childhood.
[footsteps]
Why don't you kneel?!
Show some respect,
Lord Kingsley.
You should be kneeling!
I've been granted his
Majesty's full authority.
But don't take my word.
The imperial scepter!
You get it. From now on,
you will obey me as
you do the Emperor.
My word is law.
[CLAUS]
Sheesh, it's cold!
Lucky for me,
I've got a little booze
to warm up my bones.
[ANNA]
Eliza!
Here, kitty!
It's time for lunch;
I hope you're hungry!
Eliza! Come get
your yummies girl.
Kitty?
C'mon. You've just gotta
get used to me.
Don't be shy.
[ANNA sighs]
[ANNA] I'm trying, but
she won't warm up to me.
[ANNA]
Leila...
[AYANO] Ugh, we've been
stuck here for a month!
[LEILA] I've been contacting
HQ every day, but...
...they can't seem to
arrange for transport.
[AYANO] But this place is
a dump, I'm sick of it!
And the people are so--
[SOLDIER 3A]
Check it out.
You're Eleven soldiers, right?
Ha, ha, ha!
[SOLDIER 3B]
I'm so happy you guys are here.
To take the bullets for us!
[SOLDIER 3C]
Yeah, that's about all
Elevens are good for, anyway.
[SOLDIERS laugh]
[SOLDIER 3D]
Right, the supply trailer.
[SOLDIER 3E]
We've copied the supply sheet.
[SOLDIER 3AA] We still need
the C.O.'s signature.
[ANOU] This request form
isn't formatted right!
So I'm denying your
request! Moron!
That Lieutenant
Colonel. So mean.
Don't let him hear you!
[ANOU]
What are you, deaf? Fix it now!
And save your smart-aleck
remarks for your own time!
Hm? My name?
Ohh, you wanna know my name?
Is that supposed to scare me?
I am Lieutenant Colonel Pierre
Anou of the Supply Corps!
What a punk. Those supplies are
gonna get "lost in transit."
All right, look alive, boys!
I want everybody busy!
I'm surrounded by idiots...
[ANOU]
Huh?!
Wait a minute!
You don't have it in you.
[ANOU]
What?!
Well, what do you know?
Looks like it's time
for a little payback,
Ms. Leila Malcal!
[SOLDIER 3G]
Aye, who knew bein' a soldier
would be such a pain in the ass!
[SOLDIER 3H]
Yeah, I'm sick of this crap.
[SOLDIER 3I]
Eh, quit whining.
[AYANO] What's the point
of coming to the bazaar
if we're broke?
[LEILA] My ID has a
credit function on it.
[RYO]
Oh, yeah, how much you got?
[LEILA]
About a million Euros?
[AYANO, RYO, YUKIYA]
What?! A million?
[AYANO]
Sweet! Let's eat a proper meal!
[RYO]
Hell, yeah!
[YUKIYA] Gee. Must be nice
to have that kinda moolah.
[AYANO]
Oh, wow! These are incredible!
They're all so gorgeous!
Ooh, I want one!
Please, Leila? Come on. Please?
[LEILA] U-Uh. Um, I suppose
we could buy a few.
The army still hasn't reissued
us uniforms, after all--
[AYANO]
Over here!
[LEILA]
Uh!
Ah! Now this one's quite lovely.
Hey, this would look
pretty on you, Yukiya.
Probably better than
it would on you.
[AYANO growls]
[RYO]
Hm...
I dunno. This one's
got a weird face.
Cut me a deal?
[GRANNY 3A]
You poor thing.
[gasps]
I pity you, young man.
[AYANO]
Are you serious?
No. Your machine must be broken!
I checked it twice, guys.
I can try one more
time if you want.
Sorry. But your
credit's no good.
How can that be?
[LEILA]
Uh!
You'll have to come
back with cash.
[AYANO]
Hey, don't be rude!
Something fishy's going on here.
[LEILA]
Uh!
[GUARD 3A]
Oops. Code error.
Looks like the registration
on that thing is blank.
No entry without proper ID.
But you checked it when
we left here earlier.
Don't you remember us?!
Jeez, how stupid can one guy be?
[GUARD 3A] Sorry, miss,
I don't make the rules.
Civilians have to get clearance
through the Public
Relations Department.
[RYO] You know damn
well we're not civilians!
[RYO] Asshole. That guy's
lucky he was behind glass.
[LEILA] Violence isn't the
answer, Officer Sayama.
[RYO] You sayin' that
guy didn't piss you off?
[LEILA]
It doesn't matter.
The military's regulations have
to be upheld regardless.
[AYANO] I think that guy
was just screwing with us.
That's possible.
[GRANNY 3A]
Poor thing.
[AKITO gasping]
[LEILA]
Oh, dear.
Poor cursed little child.
[AKITO]
Let go.
[GRANNY 3A] Oh, the curse
you have upon you
is terrible indeed.
But if you like,
I can lift it for you.
[GRANNY 3A laughs]
--[AKITO] No!
--[GRANNY 3A groans]
[RYO]
Whoa dude, calm down.
[GRANNY 3A] My knee!
He broke my knee!
[GRANNY 3C] Her leg is banged
up. She can't walk!
[LEILA]
Are you all right?!
[GRANNY 3B]
She's in such poor health!
Even a scratch could kill her!
We don't have enough money
to take our poor, sick
friend to a doctor.
If only we could afford medicine
for our dying friend here.
You tryin' to shake
us down? Huh?
[LEILA gasps]
[GRANNY 3B]
How dare you accuse us?
Kids these days
have no respect.
[GRANNY 3B] You're the
ones who assaulted us!
I see a light. Goodbye.
She's at death's door!
It's all over!
We're sorry for the
misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding is right.
Sorry ladies, but we can't even
afford a place to sleep.
We are just as broke as you are.
[GRANNY 3A]
You're what?!
What is the meaning of this?
Turns out they're broke.
All that for nothing?
Well, there is another way
you can pay us back.
[GRANNIES laughing]
[GRANNY 3B] Nothing like a glass
of wine after a hard day's work!
[GRANNY 3E] Sure is nice to
have these cute young servants!
[GRANNIES laughing]
[GRANNY 3C] But those outfits
of theirs are so indecent!
[GRANNY 3G]
My goodness!
[GRANNY 3C] I think I
might have a heart attack.
[GRANNY 3D]
You know you like it!
[GRANNIES laughing]
I thought old ladies were sweet.
In my experience, not so much.
So much for being at
death's door, huh?
I'm sorry to rush off,
but we really should be--
[GRANNY 3C]
Trying to run?
[LEILA]
Uh!
Uh, no, that's not what I--
Good. Then hurry up and get
your working clothes on.
[AYANO]
Hey, what are you doing?
[GRANNY 3E]
Hold still!
[GRANNIES laughing]
Stop looking!
[GRANNY 3G] You've have
beautiful skin, dear.
[LEILA]
Oh. Thank you very much.
[GRANNY 3G] Takes me back to
when we were young and sexy.
[GRANNIES chattering]
I'm not sure this fits right.
It looks gorgeous on you!
Almost as good as me
when I was your age.
[LEILA]
Oh...
[AYANO] Ugh! Hate this
stupid outfit! So musty.
[GRANNY 3G]
Well, that's 'cause I haven't
taken them out in 50 years!
[RYO]
Dammit. Crazy old bats.
[RYO yelling]
[GRANNY 3E]
You could bounce a coin off it.
[RYO]
Hands off, grandma!
[YUKIYA]
So, are you sure this isn't
one of the ladies' outfits?
You look so pretty.
[GRANNY 3D]
Oh, come on.
You better put some pep in your
step if you want to eat tonight.
Not fair! This is a
job for two people!
[GRANNY 3D]
Then get yourself a helper.
[AYANO]
Leila! Leila!
Where'd she run off to?
[GRANNY 3F]
Young man.
Akito, was it?
[AKITO]
Yes ma'am?
[GRANNY 3F]
Take those buckets
and fetch some water
from the river for me.
[LEILA] Wait, Lieutenant!
Let me do that instead.
I can handle it.
I just...
You should find a job you're
more suited for, Commander.
I think I did that right.
[AYANO]
You done, Leila? Uh!
[LEILA]
Oh? It's no good?
You sure know
what you're doing.
Well, when I was a kid, it was
learn to cook or go hungry.
[laughs] What a
good boy you are.
[AYANO]
Okay, pasta's ready.
--[LEILA yelps]
--[glass shatters]
[AYANO, YUKIYA]
Uh?!
[AYANO]
Great.
[LEILA groans]
Oh, no.
Ayano?
[AYANO] Uh! That's okay, I don't
need help with the food!
[GRANNY 3E] Akito, be a dear
and fetch the wine for me.
[AKITO]
Is it in the cart?
[GRANNY 3E] Yes, thank you.
Ryo's already unload--
[LEILA]
Leave it to me!
[RYO] How can you broads
drink this much?
[LEILA]
I'll help you!
[RYO gasps]
[RYO] Wait a minute, Leila!
Those are kinda heavy.
Stop.
[LEILA]
It's fine, I can manage it.
[RYO]
No, stop!
If you drop it, they'll break.
Just let me do it!
Well, if you insist.
[ANNA] It's not like her
to disappear! What if...?
Stay positive, boss!
She'll be all right.
Yeah Anna, she sent a report
from the Warsaw garrison.
I'm sure there's nothing
to worry about.
[CLAUS]
I know that, Major Hammel.
But still. She's a grown
woman, you know.
[HAMMEL] There's been no word
from Commander Malcal
for three days,
Deputy Commander!
At this point, we have
cause for concern!
[CLAUS]
Yeah, maybe.
But we can't do anything
about it from here.
[HAMMEL] We can at least file
a search request. Please, sir.
[CLAUS]
I dunno...
[gasps]
What do you think of this?
[ALICE]
Such nice fabric!
[DRESSMAKER 3A]
In my opinion,
this material best complements
your exquisite beauty,
Miss Alice.
[ALICE]
This pattern is so pretty.
But I love the color
of this one.
What do you think, Brother?
Which do you like?
[SHIN]
I'm not sure.
Oh, come on, just choose one!
I think you should ask Mother.
Oh, Shin. Are you embarrassed?
[WOMEN laugh]
Please, Mother. I wish
you wouldn't tease me.
[laughs] Look at brother!
He's turning red!
[WOMEN laugh]
Now, now, dear.
[gasps]
[ALICE] Okay. How 'bout this
pattern in this color?
[JULIUS]
Water.
Water...
Now... Hurry!
Please, Suzaku! [gasping]
[crash]
[JULIUS]
I need...
...some water.
[RYO groaning]
[GRANNIES snoring]
[gasps]
I'm right here, Sister.
[LEILA]
Huh...
[LEILA exhales]
[AKITO]
Can't sleep?
[gasps]
[LEILA] It's embarrassing how
bad I am at basic chores.
[AKITO] The others had to take
care of themselves as kids.
It's not your fault.
[LEILA] Am I supposed to
find that comforting?
[AKITO] No, not really. I'm
just being honest with you.
It's not a big deal.
It's not like you're gonna die
cause you can't chop carrots.
Really? Those skills
seem pretty important.
Things that every adult
should know how to do.
Don't stress out about it.
It's better to have
not needed them.
I suppose you're right.
But still. It upsets me
to feel so helpless.
Just like with Father.
What was your father like?
[LEILA] Like any famous
politician, I suppose.
The European who
left Britannia...
Your dad... was
Assemblyman Breisgau?
So you've heard
of him, Lieutenant?
That's right.
I'm the daughter...
...of Bradow von Breisgau.
[CROWD]
Breisgau! Breisgau!
[BREISGAU]
We can have freedom,
but it won't be handed to us!
And of course, the answer
doesn't lie with policymakers.
Those who have obtained
freedom for themselves
have a responsibility to pass
it down to future generations.
Liberty cannot be won
without sacrifice.
[AKITO] Assemblyman Breisgau
was killed, right?
[LEILA] Oui . I was only
six years old then.
And your mom died the same day.
[LEILA]
Right.
We got caught up in the
aftermath, and then...
[CROWD screaming]
Take Leila and run, Claudia!
[LEILA]
Mama?
Leila...
I was the only person
who survived.
I'm forever grateful that
the Malcals took me in
despite me being a
stranger to them but...
Still...
I'd rather have the strength
to survive on my own terms.
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
General Smilas.
What do you intend to do
about the wZERO unit?
[SMILAS]
I assume you're familiar with
the Maid of Orleans?
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
Joan of Arc, sir?
[SMILAS]
She was a French woman who lived
during the Hundred Years'
War against England.
Said God called
her to save France.
We could use someone like her.
Our very own Joan of Arc.
[GRANNY 3B]
Put your back into it!
[LEILA]
Yes, ma'am!
[GRANNY 3B]
Come on!
[LEILA]
Yes, ma'am!
[GRANNY 3B]
You gotta hit harder than that!
[LEILA]
Yes, ma'am!
[GRANNY 3B]
Even harder!
[LEILA]
Right!
Thank you for teaching
me how, ma'am!
That's kinda sad.
[YUKIYA]
I kind of respect the effort.
[RYO] Let's lend her a
hand when we're done.
[AYANO]
Uh?
Leila!
You have to hold on tight.
[LEILA]
I will, I promise!
Okay, ready...
Set...
Go!
[LEILA gasping]
[RYO]
You know, that looks kinda fun.
Want me to take over?
[AYANO]
No way. You have your own job.
Go get the water.
All right, let's wring it out.
[LEILA]
Okay!
[RYO]
Fine then...
[GRANNY 3E]
Can't keep my hands off it!
[RYO]
What did I tell you?
[GRANNY 3E] Can't an old
girl get a little love?
[RYO]
Not from me-- [yelps]
[YUKIYA]
Ryo!
[AYANO]
He doesn't know how to swim!
[LEILA]
Hurry, help him!
[RYO coughs]
[AYANO]
Are you okay?
[RYO]
Damn hag.
[YUKIYA] That water's
deeper than it looks.
[LEILA] I had no idea
you couldn't swim.
[GRANNY 3G] Why aren't you
down there with your pals?
[AKITO]
Mm? It's not my business.
[GRANNY 3G]
Uh?
[RYO]
Hands off, ladies.
I love a man who
knows how to eat!
[RYO]
Gimme some space!
[GRANNY 3E]
How's everything, dear?
[LEILA]
Lovely. Thank you, ma'am!
Whoa! Hey, Akito. You
gotta try this meunière!
[AKITO]
I'll pass.
[AYANO]
Uh? Oh.
Don't like fish? Sorry,
I didn't know that.
I don't understand how
anyone can eat that stuff.
[RYO] So you hate fish? What
kinda Eleven won't eat fish?
[AKITO]
Drop it.
[LEILA] Then you don't like
sashimi or sushi either?
[AKITO] Of course not.
I can't stand the smell.
Oh, come on! I think
you'll like this.
Say "ah"!
No way.
[RYO]
Ayano?
[AYANO]
Heh.
[AYANO, RYO chuckle]
[RYO] I'll hold him while you
shove it in! Come on!
[AKITO]
Let go!
[AYANO]
Just try it!
[RYO]
Don't be a chicken!
[ALL chattering, laughing]
[GRANNY 3A] Well, that's enough
fun for one night-- [groans]
[LEILA]
Oh no, be careful!
Why don't I walk you back over?
[LEILA]
Look out for rocks.
[GRANNY 3A]
Yes, thank you.
You know, you're such
a sweet child.
Would you like a reading?
[LEILA]
Uh?
I can read your fortune.
Currenta preteria futurum.
It looks like you met a witch
in the forest long ago.
[LEILA]
A witch?
And not only that,
but she put a curse on you.
A curse.
[CLAUDIA]
Leila...
Leila.
[LEILA]
Mama?
Run away, sweetie. Hurry!
[LEILA cries]
[LEILA screams]
[C.C.]
Will you live?
[C.C.] You could if you
possessed the power.
[LEILA gasps]
[C.C.]
I'll make a deal with you.
If you accept my contract,
then your life will be that
unlike of any other human's,
as long as you live in
the same world as them.
In another place.
And another time.
The power of the king
will set you apart.
If you feel ready for it,
I will grant that power.
[C.C.]
Still, you are but a child.
For that reason, I'll give
you until the time you reach
adulthood to make a decision.
If you accept, there will
be no turning back.
If you refuse,
it will cease to exist.
[LEILA gasping]
But I thought that was a dream.
[GRANNY 3A]
It wasn't a dream at all, dear.
The stones also say that
your power can save him.
[LEILA]
Save him? Who is it?
[GRANNY 3A]
Who can say?
But it's someone dear to you.
[GRANNY 3E] Do you know where
Yukiya and Ryo ran off to?
[AYANO] Beats me. Probably
somewhere goofing off.
Man, that PC's
kind of a dinosaur.
Yeah I'm speeding it
up with holo-discs.
If you take too long to crack a
password, we'll be in trouble.
Don't worry.
With this setup, I can be
in and out in no time.
[AYANO]
Hey!
What are you doing
with my Kodachi ?
[AKITO]
Were your ancestors samurai?
[AYANO]
Yup! Sure were.
At least that's what
I've been told.
So, were you born in Europe?
I was. How 'bout you?
Yeah, I was actually.
[AYANO]
Ryo and Yukiya too.
[AYANO] I'd love to
go to Japan one day.
All of us.
Commander Malcal gave me this.
[AYANO]
Uh?
She said that after
the mission was over,
to give this back to you.
That's weird. Why you?
She thinks I'm the
soldier in our squadron
with the best chance of
surviving this operation.
Oh...
It was a wise choice
on her part,
but it's not like I'd let my
commanding officer
get killed anyway.
You should hold onto it.
[AKITO]
Huh?
That things supposedly
kind of magical.
It's supposed to ward
off evil and stuff.
Then maybe you should--
No, I want you to keep it.
It's not like I'm gonna go
and get myself killed.
I'm more the type to run away
when things get rough.
[GRANNY 3C]
What a clever boy you are!
[GRANNY 3B]
That's our Yukiya!
[YUKIYA]
Our IDs got erased.
Looks to me like someone decided
to break into the army server.
[LEILA]
Like a hacker?
Nah, hackers have to be smart.
This joker's not even
covering their tracks.
The work of an idiot.
So... Did you get our ID data
back or is it lost for good?
[YUKIYA]
I got it.
That kind of illegal tampering
isn't too difficult to undo.
[ANOU] Dammit. Who builds
a military base so far--
[YUKIYA] Someone oughta
teach him a lesson.
So I decided to leave
him a little gift.
[AYANO, LEILA, RYO]
Hm?
[GUARD 3A] Your registration
data's not on file.
[ANOU growls]
But you waved to me
when I left earlier!
[GUARD 3A] Civilians need to
contact Public Relations.
[ANOU]
Kiss my ass!
[GRANNY 3A] You're really
planning to leave us so soon?
[GRANNY 3B]
We'll miss you kids so much!
We'll miss you, too.
Thank you so much for
opening your home to us.
And putting us to work.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll look
back on our free labor fondly.
Please, grannies!
Don't you dare go senile
and forget me, okay?
[GRANNY 3F]
Don't worry, dear.
[GRANNY 3D]
That body's unforgettable.
[GRANNY 3C] As if we could
forget that tight posterior!
[RYO]
Get one last handful, ladies!
[laughs] Your turn!
[LEILA laughs]
[YUKIYA]
Hey, don't stop dancing!
The party is just starting!
[RYO]
Yeah, let's go!
[GRANNY 3E]
What do you say, Akito?
Wanna go for a spin with me?
[AKITO]
Count me out.
This is stupid.
[LEILA]
Akito?
Akito!
[AYANO]
Leila!
Ryo!
Let her handle it.
What's your deal?
Ugh. Come on, move!
[LEILA]
Akito. Can we talk?
You all right?
I'm afraid.
Uh.
[AKITO] Moments like this
always make me feel
like something bad's
just around the corner.
[LEILA gasps]
[AKITO]
This reminds me of that night...
The moon looked so pretty.
My parents and the rest
of the clan were laughing
and having a great time.
Except for my brother.
Your brother?
[gasps]
Just like that, they were dead.
[AKITO]
So was I, at first.
But for some reason I came back.
And when my brother
saw me, he just said...
[SHIN]
Akito. Die now.
[AKITO] I was supposed to die
with the others.
But I...
I...
I didn't.
[AKITO]
There's no hope for my brother.
And I have no choice...
I must kill him.
[LEILA gasps]
[LEILA]
Akito.
I'm happy that he didn't
kill you that day.
That you survived.
[LEILA] If you had died,
I never would've met you.
[SOPHIE]
Is wine all right?
[CLAUS]
Sorry. I know it's really late.
So, how's the husband?
[SOPHIE]
Hm. Come see him.
Claus is here to
see you, my darling.
Dr. Randle. Good to see you.
The experiment caused
this, did it not?
That's right.
Five years back.
Our dream was always to put
BRS into practical use.
It's our hypothesis that
feelings can be shared
by manipulating resonating
brainwaves.
[CLAUS]
That is amazing.
I still believe... in miracles.
[GRANNY 3D]
Take care, children!
[GRANNY 3B]
Be sure to eat healthy!
[RYO] Those crazy old
broads. Good riddance.
Y'know, I'm going to
miss them, won't you?
[RYO]
...No! It's my allergies.
[YUKIYA] Who knows, maybe
we'll see them again.
[AKITO]
Commander.
[gasps]
[AKITO]
Someday...
[gasps]
...I hope we can go to Japan.
[JULIUS] The conquest of
Europia will be child's play.
My plan is already in motion.
But... Recent battle reports
revealed some troubling news.
Namely, the presence of
a Europian battle squad.
Some sort of
"Ghost of Hannibal"?
Sound familiar?
I was told you might know
something about them.
[SHIN]
Two months ago,
I encountered that
squad in battle.
Regrettably, I failed
to stop them.
You failed to stop them. Ah...
Even so, I'd like your help.
Heh. Lord Shaing.
[ANNA] It's nice to hear
you had some free time
to bond with your team.
But you know, I'd be lying
if I said I wasn't worried.
I was beginning to wonder
if you'd ever come back.
[LEILA] Oh, Anna. I might've
stayed there forever.
It was lovely.
[ANNA]
Mm. Still...
I'm happy you came home.
[RYO]
Hey, never seen that one before.
[AYANO]
The colors are different.
[HILDA]
The components are the same.
We've just upgraded
the programming.
We were able to increase
the speed by 30%.
Oh, interesting, did you use
our combat data for that?
Yup, you guessed it!
We've also received schematics
from the Barcelona labs
to build some new weapons.
[AYANO]
Good ones?
Weapons aren't really
within our expertise.
So we are just constructing
them from the plans.
[CHLOE]
In fact,
the parts are coming through
the elemental printer now.
[RYO]
New weapons.
[AYANO]
This'll be fun.
[ASHLEY] Stupid old man!
How far do I have to walk?
[OLD MAN 3A]
If you stop here, you'll freeze.
So unless you want to die,
you'll have to keep walking.
[ASHLEY]
What?!
How dare you take that
tone with a member
of the Order of Michael?!
[ASHLEY]
Hey, s-slow down!
Don't leave me
out here! Wait up!
[NOBLE WORKERS chattering]
[GREAT NOBLE 3A]
He's the emperor's lapdog!
To think he actually
summoned the Grand Duke!
Indeed! He'll slip
up before long.
[FARNESE]
What is he plotting?
[gavel bangs]
[GUARD 3B]
Announcing His Highness,
the Grand Duke Velaines!
Well then, Lord Kingsley.
Are we now ready to begin?
[JULIUS]
We can skip the formalities.
I can resolve this swiftly.
Unlike the rest of you lot.
[FARNESE grunts]
[JULIUS]
Thus far,
Europia have managed to avoid
an all-out confrontation.
But I intend to finally force
them out onto the battlefield!
[VELAINES]
Hm...
[GAUDEFROY]
Of all the nerve!
[RAYMOND]
Restrain yourself, Gaudefroy.
[SHIN]
Hmph.
Now then. Shall we pull
back the curtains?
Sit back, and let's
enjoy the show!
[CLAUS]
Brrr, it's cold.
Oh, and thanks for the tea.
Of course.
Is it good?
[CLAUS]
Hm? Oh, yeah, it's delicious.
Well, it's not like I'm
some sort of tea expert,
so I wouldn't know the
difference anyway right?
Let's get this straight.
Your report said you encountered
a Britannian officer
while in Slonim, yes?
[LEILA] Mm. With a special-model
golden Knightmare.
[CLAUS]
That's no good. Well...
In that case, we should
assume our enemy
has inside information
regarding wZERO squad.
What makes you say that?
[CLAUS]
Think about it.
We've carried out
some operations
that have had an outsized
impact on Britannia.
[LEILA]
So they know.
The long range transport?
Exactly. With that, we can
strike anywhere on the globe.
[MAN 3A]
I'm sick of all these blackouts.
[MAN 3B] Did you hear about
the North Sea power plant?
[MAN 3C]
Oui , I heard it was terrorists!
[MAN 3D]
Terrorists?
[MAN 3C]
Whoever it was,
they posted a video
claiming responsibility.
Is it this one here?
[JULIUS] Attention, all
citizens of Europia.
This message is from the
World Liberation Front.
Just call us the Ark Fleet.
[ENGINEER 3B]
What the hell?
[JULIUS] Our goal is
to liberate a society...
[ENGINEER 3D]
The terrorists have hacked us!
[ENGINEER 3B]
How did they get in?
[ENGINEER 3D]
I don't know; it's crazy!
[JULIUS] We've destroyed
your offshore power plant
in the North Sea.
And here's the proof...
[JULIUS] Those who waste time
on meaningless pursuits
and wallow in
unnecessary luxuries
must face the wrath of the gods.
Very soon, Paris will
be met with destruction.
Change your sinful ways. Repent!
Do exactly as I instruct,
and you may be spared our wrath!
[CROWD screaming]
[CROWD MAN 3A] There was a
bio-terror attack in London!
[CROWD MAN 3B]
It's all over now!
Just let it burn!
[CROWD MAN 3C]
An explosion on the metro?
[CROWD MAN 3D]
This is genocide!
[CROWD MAN 3E] The fat cats are
all fleeing to the New World!
[CROWD MAN 3F] They think
they're better than us?
Let's hang 'em!
[MOB] Hang them! Hang them!
Hang them! Hang them...
[SARA]
I just can't believe it.
[FERILLI] This is happening
in Geneva and Berlin, too.
[KATE]
So it's all over Europia now?
[SARA] The cities are overrun
with people rioting.
[OLIVIA]
Scary stuff.
[CHLOE] They're saying
the North Sea bombing
is what started
the whole thing.
[YUKIYA] Seeing it on social
media doesn't make it true.
[AYANO] Yeah, but, a whole lot
of people have posted that!
Listen people just get excited
about scandals and tragedy.
Doesn't matter if
it's the truth.
That's just human nature.
Nothing spreads faster
than a nasty rumor.
You're telling me
somebody's spreading
false reports on purpose?
Who would do that?
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
We've received reports
that the Eastern Front Forces
units that were fighting
against Euro Britannia have
begun to retreat.
They're using terrorism as an
excuse to leave the front lines!
They're nothing but
a bunch of cowards!
The 40 Man Committee
has already called for
an emergency meeting.
But our intel says some
assemblymen are leaving Paris!
How could those
cowards betray us?
This is troublesome, General,
but it might also
be an opportunity!
The people have realized
that the government is weak.
[MALE JUGEND 3A]
This could be the perfect time
to make your ideals a reality!
The new aristocracy's
full of greedy capitalists!
General Smilas!
Europia cannot survive if
it's continually exploited.
It's time we had a revolution!
We're ready. Just say the word!
Lovely.
Let it burn. [chuckles]
Burn it to ashes.
[door slams, footsteps]
[STEFAN]
Daniel! I have terrible news!
Rioters are attacking our banks!
We must keep them
away from the money!
[phone rings]
[STEFAN]
This is Stefan.
[IOAN chuckles]
[STEFAN]
What?!
They're rioting at the
Marseilles factory as well?
That's awful!
I don't believe this.
Here, sir.
[IOAN]
Huh?
For you.
Now what's the fuss about?
The power plant?
[JULIUS] There's one sure-fire
way to control people.
And that's fear.
Especially the fear of
something that can't be seen.
That's the most effective kind.
[FARNESE]
Curse him.
Here's your job, Duke Velaines.
Order all your
troops to advance.
[VELAINES] But if we march
on Europia now...
Surely you're aware that
countless innocent people
will be caught in the crossfire!
And that bothers you?
Heh. If one hopes
to make an omelet,
one cannot be daunted by
the breaking of a few eggs.
[VELAINES]
Lord Kingsley!
The Emperor's glory should
be our only concern.
[VELAINES grunts]
Obviously, his
Majesty's ambitions
are not of utmost
priority for you.
No. You intend to rebel.
[VELAINES]
Uh!
Which is why I must
place you under arrest...
for treason.
[gasps]
He's been planning this!
[GAUDEFROY]
Why you!
[SUZAKU grunts]
[GAUDEFROY]
You dare arrest Duke Velaines?
I'll kill you!
[GAUDEFROY groans]
I feel it's only
fair to warn you,
defying Lord Kingsley is
second only to treason.
[GAUDEFROY growls]
[SHIN] I urge you to follow Lord
Kingsley's commands for now.
I suspect that's in
your best interest.
Please, give the order.
[VELAINES] Uh... This...
cannot... be happening
[AKITO]
Another riot.
Clement Industries this time.
The more fake stories
and rumors come out,
the more anxious people get.
[AKITO gasps]
[IOAN]
Leila.
It's been too long.
I hope you've had enough
of playing soldier.
It's time to give it up.
[gasps]
[IOAN] Britannia's
spreading false stories
to get people to riot.
The North Sea power
plant is still standing!
The explosion was a hoax!
This is all just a cover-up
so they can invade
during the chaos!
We need you to come home! Hurry!
I appreciate you worrying
about me during all this.
But, I'm looking for the freedom
I can't find back home.
Leila!
[IOAN sighs]
[IOAN]
Stupid woman.
[LEILA]
Thank you so much, Ioan.
[JULIUS] It was time
for Duke Velaines to go.
Clearly he'd lost his mind,
defying the Emperor
the way he did.
[JULIUS laughs]
[JULIUS] He'll be in custody
until the Emperor
can witness his
beheading firsthand.
[SHIN]
And what about the Great Nobles?
[JULIUS chuckles] I highly
doubt any of them would have
the backbone to attack
the Britannian homeland.
I plan to oversee
Euro Britannia myself.
I think that's checkmate.
Right, well played.
[JULIUS laughs]
Your tactics were
revealing, in fact,
the chessboard reflects
your moral compass.
At one point, you
would've beat me
if only you'd thought to
sacrifice your queen.
[SHIN]
What are you saying?
[JULIUS]
I'm saying,
some things are just too
precious to surrender.
Aren't they?
Just think about it.
Everyone possesses
this weakness.
Be it for a family member, a
friend, or perhaps a lover.
But not me. I'm different.
Are you?
The person I care for,
and the only person
I would die for,
is our exalted Emperor!
[JULIUS gasps]
[SHIN grunts]
[JULIUS groaning]
But His Majesty...
I must protect His Majesty!
[JULIUS yells]
[JULIUS] Wh-Who's there?
Identify yourself!
Well, now.
[JULIUS groaning]
That isn't who I am!
I don't understand. Where am I?
The Tokyo Settlement?
Is this Kamine Island?
Release your hold on
me now, Julius Kingsley!
This is interesting.
[SUZAKU] Lord Kingsley
isn't feeling well.
I'm afraid you must leave.
But please, come
back another time.
You know, the first
time I heard about
the Ark Fleet plan, the idea
reminded me of someone.
A certain terrorist in Area 11.
The strategy put forth
by Lord Kingsley
is strikingly similar
to his efforts.
In fact... it's the same.
Your point?
He is actually the rebel Zero.
No, Zero's dead!
The Emperor put him to death!
But it's obvious.
Why else would Suzaku Kururugi,
a Knight of the Round,
be guarding him?
Enough of these false claims,
or I'll have no choice
but to silence you!
[SHIN] I must admit you've
impressed me, Kururugi.
Look at you! The son of
Japan's last prime minister.
And now you've become a
knight of its conqueror.
[growls] What about it?!
I just think it's brilliant.
Knights of Michael?
[SUZAKU grunts]
[SUZAKU]
Honestly.
Do you think this is proper?
Barging into His
Majesty's emissary
with a squad of Knightmares?
[JEAN] He may be a
Knight of the Round,
but do not be afraid!
Let us slay Lancelot
for honor and glory!
[FIGHTER 3A groans]
[yells]
[JULIUS groaning]
[SUZAKU growls]
[MALE FIGHTER 3B groans]
[MALE FIGHTER 3C yelps]
He's outnumbered!
Hold your ground!
These idiots!
[JEAN gasps]
[JEAN growls]
After him! Quickly!
[JULIUS whimpering]
[gasps]
[SHIN]
Kururugi, look.
Take a look around you.
[SHIN] This world is rife
with blood and death.
Exactly what you asked for.
No! I don't want to fight!
[SHIN]
You've given up on this world.
All of it. Trash.
The entirety of the human race.
No!
[SHIN]
Don't deny it.
All you want is to
destroy the world.
Shut up.
You're just like me.
[JULIUS]
Who are you?
Who...?
[JULIUS]
Your Majesty!
Tell me...
What is this place?
Nunnally...
[SHIN]
So you're the Emperor's.
I see!
You're the Eleventh Prince
I've heard so much about.
Damn you. I'm finished.
I can see it as plain
as day, Suzaku.
The darkness that dwells
deep inside your heart.
[SHIN chuckles]
[SMILAS]
Under no circumstances
shall the details of
our plan be revealed.
We'll work with them on a
need-to-know basis, Genera--
[SMILAS]
Hm?
[SMILAS grunts]
[CARETAKER]
Since the dawn of time,
the young have rushed
to their own deaths.
It can't be.
[CARETAKER]
Every hero
is just another
dead man walking.
[SMILAS] It's not like I enjoy
sending soldiers to die.
[CARETAKER]
Of course not.
You'd never express
it in those words.
But still...
You are leading them
to the slaughter--
for your own gain.
[SMILAS]
What's your point?
It's very simple.
Your ambitions to become
king of this world
are of no interest to us.
But the fact remains...
...there was a time when
you conspired against us.
And the time has come to atone
for your transgressions.
Atonement?
But how?
What are you asking me to do?
This is an order in
the name of The Geass.
[SMILAS gasping]
You are to assassinate
Lord Shin Hyuuga Shaing.
[SMILAS]
What? Lord Shaing?
But how do you even
know about him?
[gasps] No, wait... Is he...?
If you kill Shaing,
we will be satisfied.
But if you don't,
we'll have to...
[SMILAS]
Uh! I'll do it.
I-I give you my word.
You are now bound by a
contract. Remember that.
As long as the balance of
spacetime remains undisturbed,
we shall be content.
We care not who becomes
king of this world.
[SMILAS exhales]
[LORDS chattering]
[GREAT LORD 3C] Lord Shaing
was adopted by royalty.
He's not even blood!
Indeed, how insolent of him
to summon all of us here!
[GREAT LORD 3A]
There he is.
[GREAT LORD 3B]
That bastard.
[SHIN]
I have received some information
that I must relay to
the House of Lords.
The man who calls
himself Julius Kingsley,
the military advisor of the
Holy Britannian Empire,
is concealing his true identity
as the rebel called Zero.
[GREAT LORD 3A]
Zero?!
The terrorist who wreaked
all that havoc in Area 11?
[GREAT LORD 3B] That can't
be true. He was executed!
That was merely a fabrication
created by Kingsley.
But don't worry, I've
already taken care of him.
[LORDS chattering]
[GREAT LORD 3E]
You killed Kingsley?!
Without consulting the empire?!
Any of you would have
done the same.
You all harbor discontent
with His Majesty, do you not?
[GREAT LORD 3F]
If we defy the emperor
it will be an all-out war
against the homeland!
Then I suggest you
be prepared.
To the west is Europia!
And Britannia lies to the east.
If Euro Brittania
hopes to survive,
fighting is our only option.
[GREAT LORD 3A]
But what about Duke Velaines?!
What does he say about this?!
It doesn't matter.
The battle's already underway.
If you wish to survive,
hand over the reins to
those willing to fight.
[GREAT LORD 3C] Have the Four
Great Orders agreed on this?
Unfortunately, the other
commanders were afraid to fight.
They threatened to flee.
So I was forced to take
matters into my own hands.
[LORDS gasping]
That's Lord Villon!
And Lord Saint-Gilles. Dear god!
The time has come for
decisive maneuvers.
We can't stay idle!
I request a transfer of
the Grand Duke's control.
As well as absolute authority
over the House of Lords!
[KNIGHT 1A]
The rebels are likely
from the Order of Michael.
Lord Shaing, of course.
First he killed Manfredi,
and now he plans to kill me.
[OPERATOR 3C] We can't reach
the Orders of Gabriel, or Uriel,
not even HQ!
They must have been attacked
by the Order of Michael.
They're trying to
dismantle our leadership.
You'll pay for this, Hyuga!
[LEILA]
So regarding the Paris blackout,
the incident wasn't caused
by a terrorist attack.
The North Sea power
plant is still there,
completely unharmed.
So...
What about that video that
was all over the internet?
[LEILA]
That file was carefully edited.
But... There've been
attacks all over Europia!
Those reports were
falsified as well.
They're spreading fake news
hoping to cause mass hysteria
and start riots in Europia.
Weakening our resolve.
Okay...
Well if that's true, than
the Ark must be fake too.
Actually, the Ark is very real.
Uh...
[LEILA] A giant flying
weapon is the perfect way
to instill widespread panic.
That said, the Ark...
...is just a bluff.
A bluff? So it's for show?
Yes.
We do not believe
the Ark is equipped
with any kind of
high-yield bombs.
So it poses no actual danger.
This is nothing more
than a strategy
to prey on the citizens' fear.
If we want to put a
stop to the riots,
then the best course of
action is to expose the Ark
for what it truly is.
And you want to use
the Wyvern Squad?
Correct.
But I'm sure that whoever
designed such a brilliant plan
is expecting us to launch a
direct attack against the Ark.
Which is why--
[RYO]
Count me in.
[LEILA gasps]
We kinda have to go. Don't we?
Sounds like it
I'm down.
I can handle this alone.
[ALL]
Huh?
[RYO]
What'd you say?
I don't need you tagging along
and getting in my way.
--[RYO grunts]
--[AKITO yelps]
You think you're a tough guy?!
I don't need you!
We all know what
you're thinking,
so don't even try it!
No! Stop fighting guys!
[AYANO]
Just let them.
[LEILA]
Uh...
He talks tough, but Ryo
would never hurt Akito.
[AKITO, RYO grunting]
Anna. Won't you have some tea?
It's quite delicious.
[ANNA]
But Dr. Randle!
Should we stop them?
Ah, to be young again.
How much steam do they
need to blow off?
This is the only thing
they know how to do.
[AKITO, RYO panting]
[RYO] Look, I know that
you're afraid Akito.
But we're all gonna make
it back together, okay?
Just trust me!
[gasps]
I hope you're right.
What's happening?
I'm leaving, Alice.
[ALICE]
Brother...
[SHIN]
I love you.