♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
No!
‐Mocchi?
‐Mocchi!
Hey, what took you so long?
(grunting)
You should lie back, Mocchi.
Mocchi fine, 'chi.
Mocchi no talk, just
lie back and rest.
Mocchi lose match.
Even so, it was a
good battle, Mocchi.
Yeah, you said it,
even I was impressed!
There's no reason
to feel bad about it.
But Magic Stone.
Now we never save
Holly's father from disk.
But you tried your best
and that's what's important.
‐'chi?
‐You did everything you could,
and that means a lot to me.
Sure, it would've been
nice if we could've won,
but hey, there's always gonna
be another Legend Cup next year,
‐right?
‐Right.
So, what's stoppin'
ya from winning then?
All right, we'll be
your sparring partners!
'chi, next year Mocchi
battle Most in Legend Cup!
(cheering)
♪
At last, the time has come.
(in unison)
Yes, sir.
The time for me to merge with
Moo's infinitely evil soul,
and begin my reign of terror
over the entire wretched world.
Master, you mustn't allow
yourself to become so excited.
You must hurry and steal
the Magic Stone from Most
while his strength
is still drained
from the Legend Cup match.
(in unison)
Yes, sir.
Leave it to me, General.
I'll deliver that Magic Stone
to you in no time at all.
Why'd I have to go
and open my big mouth?
I don't care how tired Most
is from the Legend Cup match,
we still don't stand
a chance against him.
You fool, he may be a superhero,
but that doesn't
mean he never sleeps.
We just have to sneak
in and grab the plate.
Gobi, see if you can open it up.
Okay.
♪
Keep it down or you'll wake him
up, you useless hunk of tin!
‐Wake who?
‐Most, of course!
Who do you think I mean?
(screaming)
How come you're here?
Just out for some fresh air.
So, more importantly,
what're you doing here?
‐Who, us?
‐We were just‐‐
Uh, you know, we
were just, kind of‐‐
Then perhaps you wouldn't
mind what he's up to.
‐Gobi!
Know what I think?
That you're not just
ordinary thieves.
Urgh, we'll have to
force it from him now!
Now, Gobi!
Double pounder!
(shouting)
You're a hopeless case, Gobi.
This isn't a circus, you know!
‐Yes, ma'am.
‐Oh, don't bother.
You wouldn't stand
a chance against me.
(yelling)
Cherry blossom blizzard!
♪
Mocchi cannon!
This is all your fault again!
What's that, you
wingy fruit bat?
Can it, you old has‐been!
No fight, no fight!
All right, it's time
for some answers.
What exactly do you
three want from me?
♪
‐Hand over the stone.
‐Huh?
‐The stone?
‐What'd you tell him for?
What difference
does it make now?
Your B and E plan
got busted, didn't it?
Most, hand over the Magic Stone
that's on your Winner's Plate.
Hm, wait, that reminds me.
Mocchi wanna be strong.
Mocchi wanna be
strong like Most,
and win Legend Cup, 'chi.
All so that you can get
that Magic Stone in
the Winner's Plate?
Mhm, we bring him back
with Magic Stone, 'chi.
‐Bring back who?
‐Holly's father
trapped inside mystery disk.
♪
He said they needed
the Magic Stone
to bring someone back to life.
You seem to know a lot
more than you're letting on.
You're right, we need
the Magic Stone in order
to bring Moo's evil
soul back to life again.
Bring back Moo's soul?
We're not going anywhere
till you hand it over!
‐Yeah!
‐So they need the Magic Stone
to bring back Moo's soul?
Lightning!
Uh‐oh, now I'm in trouble.
See ya!
‐After her, Gobi!
‐Right!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Vain Mum Mew, Durahan's pest ♪
♪ She's buying gizmos
to look her best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Assistant Gobi,
he pays the price ♪
♪ Count on them and
you're rolling the dice ♪
♪ Poison acts like
Durahan's doll ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it,
unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
That's quite an
appetite you got there.
Mocchi must build
up strength, 'chi.
We've got plenty more,
so don't hold back.
'chi!
(groaning)
Water!
Here.
That's what you
get for eating fast.
(engine whirring)
Most in sight, 'chi!
Are you positive?
The evil monsters are
after this Magic Stone.
They said they need it to
bring back Moo's evil soul.
But who's orders could
they be acting on?
It must be a monster who used
to be a high‐ranked leader.
‐He's their new boss.
‐But Big Four baddies
were revived and
became good monsters.
And it couldn't be Moo,
'cause he's locked in the disk.
(in unison)
Hmmm.
♪
You break trophy, 'chi.
What'd you do that for?
Take the Magic Stone.
If it's in your hands I know
it'll be put to good use.
But are you sure, Most?
‐You've worked so hard.
‐Hmm.
We can't let those monsters
revive Moo's soul again.
Here.
♪
Thanks, this means a lot.
But now what do we do
with the Magic Stone?
I don't know any shrines
where it would work.
‐I do.
‐Huh?
Once when I was passing
through the north
on my iron bird, suddenly,
my other Magic Stone
started to react to
something down below.
There you go, so
there is a shrine!
‐Come on, gang, let's go!
‐Hold on!
What if we can't find the place?
Yeah, but what are our choices?
Let's just go and
see what happens.
This south, how we
get all way to north?
‐Hmmm.
I think I might have an idea.
♪
This last box outside,
no more onboard.
That'll lighten
up the iron bird.
The seven of us will
just barely make it on
under the weight restrictions.
‐Ahhh.
‐Sure about this?
You don't have to lend us
your personal iron bird.
I wouldn't have
offered if I needed it.
Well, it's very
kind of you, Most.
We can't thank you enough.
‐Don't go, Most!
‐Hm?
Mocchi try for Legend Cup, 'chi!
Mocchi trying to
become much stronger,
then challenge Most again, 'chi!
Good luck, Mocchi.
See you in the ring.
'chi.
♪
(mixed remarks)
Good luck, my friends.
Mocchi, I look forward
to our next battle.
♪
Let's see if we can find
that place Most told us about.
Here, 'chi!
At this rate, we might even
make it there by this afternoon!
That might be the case
if we had a real pilot
‐onboard the bird with us.
‐A real pilot?
I'll have you know
that back in the days,
I was considered a real‐‐
(screaming)
(groaning)
That's just what
I was talking about.
I'm not the problem,
the problem is that
there are seven of
us on a small craft,
and we've gone over
the weight limit!
Just keep your eyes
on the controls.
You're the only
qualified pilot we have.
'chi!
This sure has been
a long journey.
‐Huh?
‐I left my village,
met all of you guys,
I fought off the monsters.
We've been through
a lot together.
Suezo?
Once we rescue
your father, Holly,
let's head for my village.
‐Sound like a good plan?
‐Mhm.
Golem will open new
restaurant in town.
You, a restaurant,
in my village?
Golem cooking get
better every day!
I hear ya, big fella, I
was just pullin' your leg!
Golem, you're making
us lose balance!
Stay still back there!
♪
Oh, Father.
Golem, you're supposed
to stay still!
It's not him, what was it?
(groaning)
‐Can't you fly this right?
‐Tiger.
I, I didn't do it,
I don't know what it was.
What's this?
♪
(evil laughter)
It's been a long time,
my brave warriors.
Doesn't that sound like‐‐
(in unison)
Durahan!
♪
Moo may have been sealed
in the disk, but not I.
I will merge with his soul
and become the world's
undeniable and
undefeatable tyrant.
♪
You hand over the mystery disk
and Magic Stone, or else.
Never, 'chi!
You monsters are pure
hatred and evil!
We won't do it!
(yelling)
Watch where you're aimin',
you're supposed to be firing
warning shots, not
shooting 'em outta the sky.
‐I know that, Weed!
‐Capture them,
and bring me those treasures.
‐I'm on it, General.
‐We're so close now.
Can't wait to pay
them back for once.
Yeah.
Now force them to land,
and they'll be ours.
Genki?
Can't you fly this
thing any faster?
No chance, we're way too heavy.
We have to lighten
our load somehow.
But we already left
all the cargo behind.
The only thing left
is the passengers.
I've got it!
♪
‐Let's go.
‐Yeah!
(grunting)
This doesn't look important!
'chi!
Do you see that?
What's going on up there?
♪
We're gaining altitude!
It's working, guys,
so keep at it!
♪
‐Increase our altitude.
‐Yes, sir.
♪
‐More altitude!
‐Yes, sir!
♪
More altitude!
(panting)
♪
We're not getting anywhere!
‐Fire at them!
‐Gladly.
♪
‐Hare!
‐On it!
♪
We got the fire out, but now
we've lost one of our engines.
‐What?
‐Ha‐ha!
Admirable job, Poison.
Oh no, there's nothing
left to chuck!
Now we can't gain
any more altitude!
Poison, take out
that other engine.
Aye‐aye, sir.
The Magic Stone and mystery
disk are within my grasp,
and with them, my
glorious victory!
Well, can't knock
us for trying hard.
‐Gol'.
‐Hey!
What're you think
you're doing, Golem?
‐We jump!
‐Ahhh!
‐Suezo, Golem!
‐Golem!
Target locked.
‐Wait a sec.
‐Here goes nothin'!
Something's coming.
(screaming)
What's going on?
Suezo, quick, use teleport.
Teleport!
♪
You fools!
‐You did it!
‐You two okay, 'chi?
If I had knuckles,
they'd be white.
Good thinking, that
was a great plan, Golem!
‐Maybe for the spectators!
‐Once more.
Oh no!
♪
Suezo.
Tele‐‐teleport.
♪
This time, let us go with ya.
‐Ready when you are, Golem.
‐Gol'!
I told ya I don't
wanna be on the bottom!
(shouting)
Durahan!
Why, you!
‐Gobi, finish them off!
‐Right!
Lightning attack!
♪
Nooo!
How will we be able
to control our ship?
‐Come on, let's get outta here.
‐'chi!
(grunting and yelling)
♪
Suezo, use your teleport!
Teleport!
♪
Holly.
‐We got 'em.
‐Genki!
Hm?
Oh no!
And we can't get any altitude!
That's right, I don't
know what to do.
We've gone from the
frying pan into the fire.
'chi.
Tiger.
What is it, Tiger?
Shhh, let me concentrate.
♪
‐It's coming.
‐What?
Hare, hard to starbird.
The wind is coming, we're
gonna ride the current.
♪
What did Tiger mean,
"it's coming"?
♪
(cheering)
‐Oh yeah.
‐Yay.
♪
‐It's glowing!
‐'chi!
It's just like Most said.
We must be close.
♪
Hey, look at that.
It must be the shrine.
♪
The suspense is
killing me, Holly.
‐Hurry and open it!
‐Right.
♪
We finally made it, now you
can be reunited with your dad.
You think we're doing
the right thing?
‐Huh?
‐I mean,
what would happen if I
tried to revive my father
and accidently revived Moo's
evil spirit at the same time?
♪
That'll never happen, besides,
we're right here with ya.
Genki?
♪
My dear friends.
You're right, what
am I worried about?
‐Yeah!
‐Mm!
♪
All set, Holly?
Mhm.
'Kay.
Unlock!
♪
I hear something, a voice.
The Magic Stone is
saying something to us.
It's saying that it's putting
everything in our hands,
that our feelings
about the mystery disk
have been relayed
through the Magic Stone.
So the Magic Stone
is no more to us
than just a means
of communication.
And reviving the
mystery disk depends
entirely on our feelings inside.
Gol', good soul
and evil soul.
What're you talkin' about?
There's no way we're gonna
be reviving the evil soul!
He's right, we
have to have faith
and believe we can
revive Holly's dad.
'chi!
♪
Father!
The black shape is disappearing!
♪
Father!
Oh, Daddy!
♪
I missed you so much.
Father, I missed
you for so long.
(sniffling)
♪
Who are you, young one?
Huh?
I don't know.
Where am I?
I, I can't remember anything!
No, Father!
(crying)
Father!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪