♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
(rumbling)
The Legend Cup
will be held tomorrow.
Your opponents
will be Poritoka and Most.
You must decide the order
of your matches on the day
of the championship.
Gotcha!
‐'chi!
‐What's that?
You mean he's gotta go up
against two opponents?
Yes, and he's gotta
win both matches
to win the championship.
Don't you know anything
about the Legend Cup?
Everyone know the rules.
Not quite everyone,
it would seem.
Fooled ya!
I was just pulling your
legs to loosen things up.
We've made it all the way
to the final championship,
so let's practice
till the last minute.
'chi!
♪
Mocchi, have you decided
who you're gonna fight first?
Yes, 'chi, Mocchi wanna
fight Most last, 'chi!
Which means you'll go up
against Poritoka first.
The legendary
great white eyeball.
(clears throat)
All right, Poritoka and I
are both the same species.
You can practice on me.
Come on, I'm ready.
You'll counter his tail attacks
with your Mocchi Cannonballs.
Mocchi no lose to Poritoka!
Hello, is anybody
listening out there?
All right, you can
practice with him, Suezo.
Fine, just say the word.
Come on, little guy,
I'm ready for you.
(grunting)
♪
Mocchi, do it!
(grunting)
Tail Attack!
Mocchi Cannonball!
♪
Suezo, you all right?
This mansion's enormous.
Can you imagine actually
living in a place like this?
Look like summer house.
Ha, what a waste of money.
(grunting)
Lucky you hit me when
I had something in my eye.
Hey, whose house is this?
Who are you
and why are you here?
Poritoka.
You know who I am?
Sure we do.
Mocchi here is gonna
be your opponent
in the Legend Cup tomorrow.
He's been practicing hard,
so let's keep it clean
and may the best monster win.
'chi!
That's why you were fighting
with the likes of him?
Hmm?
So, you were watching?
I heard some noises in my yard.
You mean this is your yard?
Then, this huge mansion
must be yours, too.
This is just one
of my many summer homes,
and commoners such as you
have no right to trespass.
You'll have to leave at once.
Man, the nerve.
But, before you leave,
I'd like to give my opponent
one last word of advice.
Your friend there might be
the same species as me,
but you're kidding yourself
if you think he has even
a fraction of my skills.
Believe me, you don't
stand a chance against
my invincible Tail Attack.
You're nothing but
a weather balloon
full of hot air!
Come on, let's just walk away.
♪
Why are you waiting?
Your boss ordered you
to leave already.
(growling)
Let's go, Suezo.
♪
What's wrong with you people?
Didn't he make
your blood boil?
(growling)
Of course he made us mad, Suezo!
'chi!
He's lucky he got
away with that!
Now I really want you
to beat him tomorrow, Mocchi!
Mocchi must beat Poritoka.
Yeah, 'chi!
But I wonder if Poritoka's
Tail Attack is really
as terrifying
as he made it sound?
Hmm, I do know Poritoka
wasn't entered in
the last Legend Cup
championship.
So, we don't know, 'chi.
We're gonna have
to practice tonight.
Practice, 'chi!
Count me in!
I'll come along, too.
Go!
They're totally
underestimating Poritoka.
I gotta do something
before the championship.
Suezo, where do you
think you're going?
I left something back
here, I won't be long!
Huh?
♪
He should find himself
a designer with some real taste.
Teleport!
♪
Hey, I'm getting better,
I made it on the very
first try this time.
♪
How am I gonna find Poritoka
with this many rooms?
(groaning)
♪
You okay?
We better hurry
and get him to a doctor.
Careful, grab the other side.
♪
Poritoka must be
in that room practicing.
♪
I'm not moving till I see
Poritoka's Tail Attack
with my own eye.
(shivering)
How are you gonna fight Poritoka
if you're shaking like that?
It's just...I've seen
what he can do with
his Tail Attack.
You're not gonna get hurt
with that headgear on.
Besides, Poritoka's wearing
a glove on his tail, isn't he?
Now, get in there!
Right.
Hold on.
Hmm?
You'll get a better view inside.
I know you want to watch me.
No, no, it's just
that your place
is so enormous, I couldn't
find my way outta here!
What are you doing trespassing?
He's a friend of my opponent
in the Cup tomorrow.
So, you came here
to spy on us?
No, I just got lost
and was trying
to find my way out.
No one breaks
into Poritoka's house
and comes out in one piece.
(laughs nervously)
Look!
Teleport, teleport, teleport!
Nice try!
Don't be too hard on our friend.
(growling)
♪
Come back here
and fight like an eye!
♪
(yelps)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Baku's a pet
who does a brave deed ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ That kinda monster
is one that we need ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Beware the Knight Mocchis,
look sweet but they're not ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ If you see them coming,
don't you get caught ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Metal Jell is
a jell with a 'tude,
don't wanna meet him
when he's in a mood ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Lightning Attack!
'chi!
Dragon Kick!
Tornado Attack!
'chi!
Looking good, Mocchi!
If you move like that tomorrow,
the championship's
yours for sure!
Go, Go, Go!
I wonder what's taking Suezo.
♪
(gasping)
That's Poritoka!
(chuckles)
What'd you do
to our friend, Poritoka?
I found him sneaking
around my mansion,
so I gave him a private tour.
You'll pay for this!
Yeah, 'chi!
Go!
Stay back, you guys.
But, Genki!
Wait until tomorrow.
We'll settle this
in the ring, Poritoka.
I don't know how
I'm going to get any sleep.
Oh, man, that guy
gives me the creeps!
Golem never
give him famous soup.
Suezo, wake up,
can you hear me?
I snuck into Poritoka's house,
now I have his
Tail Attack memorized.
Suezo.
♪
(sniffing)
Hmm?
Wahoo, food!
Gimme, gimme, gimme,
food, I gotta eat‐‐
Are you feeling any better?
Hey, what are you
doing here, what's up?
Where'd all these
bandages come from?
Knock it off, Suezo,
that's not funny.
Now I remember,
I went to Poritoka's house,
then I roughed up him
and his men a little.
He's the one who
brought you back here.
Hang on, we don't
have time to lose!
We gotta get practicing
our defense against
Poritoka's Tail Attack!
Right.
Mocchi ready!
But first, I'm gonna need
some of that nice stew.
Bring on the stew, Holly!
Uh, yeah, sure.
I'll try to go easy
on you at first, Mocchi,
but you're still in
for a rough ride.
'chi!
Enough talking, let's start!
All right, here goes,
but don't say I didn't
give you fair warning!
Yeah!
(growling)
(yelping)
♪
Genki, Mocchi!
Those are just flesh wounds.
A little splash of water
and they'll be up and at 'em.
I'm not gonna let you
do this to them!
They need this practice if
they're gonna make it tomorrow.
He's right, we have
to practice until
they have these
defense moves down pat.
But you guys‐‐
They're right, Holly.
Besides, we're not hurt.
Then at least wait a while
before you continue.
We don't have time.
Let's get started.
Let's start, 'chi!
Come off it.
Stay outta this, would ya?
'chi!
Come on, let's do it!
(growls)
♪
Get up, let's try it again!
(fireworks bursting)
(cheering)
♪
I wonder if this Poritoka
and Most are as strong
as everyone seems to think?
At the very least,
they'd have you two
begging for mercy.
You haven't even seen
my angry side.
Calm down!
Speaking of bad taste,
what are you doing
wearing a tuxedo?
Who, me?
(stammering)
I told you to disguise yourself!
I didn't say anything
about dressing up for
a costume party!
At least explain yourself!
Oh, my aching head!
Enough of this!
General Durahan!
You really should try to keep
your blood pressure
down, General.
I know that, you fool!
Now, what's going on
at the stadium?
The championship's
about to begin.
Excellent!
Remember, get the Magic Stone
and mystery disk
after the tournament.
It'll be a cinch
after they're exhausted.
Excellent!
At last, I'll be able
to fuse with Moo's soul
and take over the world!
(sinister laughter)
Ladies, gentlemen, and monsters!
Welcome to Togle Stadium:
Home of the ultimate
in monster battles,
the one and only Legend Cup,
which promises to be
even more dramatic
than last year!
And now, the challenging team
is about to enter the stadium!
The challengers have scrimped
their way to the top by winning
every single IMA game this year!
Let me present you
with Genki's Team!
♪
(cheering)
(gasping)
What do we have here?
Genki's team looks like
they've been through the wringer
and the battle
hasn't even begun!
How are they going
to fight in that condition?
Yeah.
And now, the reigning champs!
(cheering)
♪
First up, the legendary
great white eyeball,
Poritoka!
And finally, the master
of the Aurora Attack, Most!
(cheering)
♪
Most!
In order to win the Legend Cup,
the challenger must defeat
both Poritoka and Most.
Now, the question is
which will Mocchi decide
to battle first?
Him, 'chi!
♪
The answer is in: Poritoka!
Mocchi will battle
against Poritoka first!
(cheering)
♪
Contenders to center ring!
Go for the gusto!
Mocchi try, 'chi!
♪
Be careful.
Are you ready?
It's smackdown time!
The championship to determine
who will walk away
with 10,000 golds
and their name
in the hall of fame
and it's about to begin.
Will the victor be Poritoka
or the challenger, Mocchi?
Ready?
Fight!
(ding)
(growling)
Double Pounder, Double
Pounder, Double Pounder!
Tongue Slap!
Mocchi, use the Cannonball!
(growls)
Mocchi Cannonball!
(grunts)
I suppose it was too much
to hope for
an interesting match.
Here it comes.
(growls)
Ladies and gentlemen,
unless I'm mistaken,
Poritoka's about to use
his legendry Tail Attack!
♪
(grunting)
Now Mocchi!
♪
I don't believe my eyes!
Mocchi's managed to dodge
Poritoka's formerly
unbeatable Tail Attack!
♪
That extra training
we did last night
really paid off.
Sure did.
Suezo have good plan this time.
They grow up so fast.
♪
I'll try to go easy
on you, Mocchi,
but you're still in
for a rough ride.
All right, here goes!
Tornado Attack!
♪
Tail Attack!
The only way to defend yourself
against Poritoka's Tail Attack
is to practice and practice
getting hit with
its spinning force.
♪
(cheering)
You're pretty clever
sending one of your friends
to spy on my practice.
(growls)
What on Earth is going on?
Poritoka's Tail Attack
has failed him, and yet,
he's still smiling?
Prepare yourself.
He's using
the Tail Attack again!
Ready, 'chi!
(growls)
(yelps)
A Teleport!
Go!
♪
Mocchi, on your left!
Behind you!
(yelps)
Mocchi, are you all right?
♪
No one beats my
Tail Attack/Teleport combo.
(growls)
And now, for my victory!
(grunts)
Go for it!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
(chuckles)
As if I didn't see
that one coming.
Oh, no.
Poritoka know he
use Mocchi Cannon.
And he keeps using
the Teleport.
If only there was something
Mocchi could do to turn
the tables on him!
Mocchi, we're rooting for ya!
So, where's
this courage of yours?
♪
You don't stand
a chance, little monster!
Just do him in
and get it over with.
If Mocchi loses,
then the three of us
will have to make
a fast change of plans.
You're not suggesting we'll
have to steal the Magic Stone
from Poritoka and Most?
♪
All that courage
of yours has amounted
to absolutely nothing.
You'll never be anything
but a pitiful monster.
♪
That's not true, Mocchi.
You know we made it
past every obstacle
with our courage
and our hard work.
That's right!
You bet!
Mocchi, listen to
your heart, not that bully!
You've got what it takes!
He no have courage like Mocchi.
(grunting)
All right, if that's
what you want.
♪
Mocchi, use my energy
like it's your own.
(grunting)
♪
Feel out your enemy.
Think with your heart!
(grunting)
♪
Mocchi got energy back!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
(yelps)
Yeah!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
It's all over now.
No, this can't be happening!
♪
Knockout, the match
goes to Mocchi!
(cheering)
♪
Well, at least we're
one step closer to getting
the Magic Stone in our hands.
They're our enemies,
but let's acknowledge
their hard work
in the ring today.
(laughs)
Mocchi beat Poritoka, Genki.
Yeah, it was
a classic knockout, Mocchi.
Thanks for energy, 'chi.
Huh?
Most.
I'm proud of what you
did out there, Mocchi.
Now, let's make ours
a good, fair match.
♪
Yeah, 'chi.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're down to one last match
between Mocchi and Most!
Don't miss it
because it's bound to be
the battle of the century!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪