Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into the world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the
game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it
to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release the
Phoenix in time ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
What's that?
Are you serious?
Yes, ma'am.
A mystery disk with the
baddies' crest on it, you say.
Gobi, what do you think?
I said, "What do you think?"
Answer me, Gobi,
what's your problem?
Spit it out!
Answer me!
My head.
Forget it.
♪
Huh?
(laughing)
Well, somebody's feeling
pretty good today
so he says he wants
to speak to you.
Promise to keep
it short, though.
He'd overexert himself
with a long talk.
I appreciate your
assistance, Weed.
You're too kind, sir.
Nonsense!
You became a partial
cyborg to save my life.
But your sacrifice
will not be in vain,
for I will become the
most powerful monster
that ever lived.
Oh, master.
Mum Mew, Gobi.
‐Yes?
My soul screams for action.
I am certain that an
evil soul lies dormant
in that mystery disk.
I lost everything that
was precious to me,
but now I have
managed to rebuild
my collection of
fierce warriors.
And this shall be the
first one I dispatch.
My deceptively
tantalizing warrior,
hear my voice and awaken.
Fierce and merciless
one, Pink Jam!
(zapping)
♪
You summoned?
Mm, looks like jam.
Makes my legs turn to jelly.
Pink Jam!
Go forth, my brave soldier,
and retrieve the
mystery disk at any cost.
(laughing)
(sighing)
Chi!
Hear anything?
Not at all.
I wonder if I was
just imagining
that I heard my
father's voice.
Try it again.
Pretend it's
your magic stone.
Mmhmm.
(humming)
♪
Father?
Holly!
♪
You're alive!
It's too good to be true.
Father!
Stay back, it's dangerous!
You must be careful.
There's evil in
this mystery disk.
(grunting)
♪
Father!
Oh?
Are you all right, Holly?
‐Father.
‐I told ya.
You heard him again, right?
Yes, but an evil soul
was in there with him.
No prob, the important thing
is that you talked to him.
Evil soul is dangerous, chi.
I know, but Holly's
father is still alive.
All right, Holly's
father's still alive!
(singing)
Genki.
Okay, what we
have to think of
is a way to get him out
of the mystery disk.
Maybe something Monol
told Holly can help, chi.
You talked to Monol?
What did he have to say?
Well, it was
after the battle.
♪
Where are my friends?
Don't tell me
those lights are‐‐
Yes, but fear not.
Monol, it's you.
Your friends are
alive and well.
They are?
Yes, Holly.
So long as wish you hard
enough to see them again,
one day your dream
will come true.
(laughs)
I'll see them.
Wait a sec, where
does that leave Moo?
I'm afraid that
he, too, lives on
in some shape or form.
Holly, you told me before
that your father was
possessed by Moo.
‐Yes.
‐In that case,
if they're both back
inside a mystery disk,
you could try to seal
the evil soul inside,
that way you'd be able
to bring your father back.
And how do I seal
in the evil soul?
(snoring)
Ah!
Man, that Monol
has lousy timing.
He's always falling
asleep during a crisis.
‐Yeah, chi!
‐That's okay.
Monol gave me some
valuable advice,
and that's why I started
looking for everyone.
Chi, and that's how
Holly found Mocchi!
All right, now all we
gotta do is find out
how to seal the evil soul,
then unlock the mystery disk
and Holly can be
with her dad again.
Yeah!
Well, we better hurry.
And leave?
No, and eat!
Oh.
Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Wondar brothers,
one young, one old ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Sparring leaves
the strong one cold ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Once but farmer
with world‐class power ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ His brother's dreams
are going sour ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Face was won,
the other's grudge ♪
♪ Friend or foe,
you be the judge ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Whoa, sure is crowded.
With people and
monsters, chi.
Torble is the biggest city
on the continent after all.
Look, a restaurant!
Okay, you guys, but don't
order anything expensive.
Yeah, I'll race ya!
‐Chi!
‐Uh...
(sighing)
Step right up,
boys and girls.
Now I'll admit
this city's hopping
with a lot of
freaky monsters,
but we're a whole
other ball of wax.
Go.
Now before we start
passing the hat,
let me introduce the
co‐star of our two‐man show,
the monster who helped me
defeat the evil Moo, Golem!
Go!
Okay, enough of him,
now if you will just
cast your eyes back over
this way, I'm Suezo,
and for one gold,
I will autograph anything
that ain't moving.
Form a line now,
who will be first?
He's just another fake
trying to make some money.
(indistinct chattering)
You know, this
place really stinks!
Now how are we gonna
make some money,
not to mention
meet up with Holly?
Golem say we lucky.
‐Huh?
‐We together.
Yeah, come to think of it,
we were lucky to find each
other right after the battle.
We go to Suezo's village now
and look for
others along way.
Mm, Holly might be waiting
there for me even as we speak.
Ooh, and pink Suezo might
have been unlocked as well.
Okay, let's give these guys
a show they won't forget.
Yes, show go on.
Step right up,
ladies and monsters!
We have right here your
typical green handkerchief,
nothing unusual about
it, as you can see.
But this is magical
handkerchief,
very mysterious.
'Cause when you spread it out
and count to three like this:
One, two, three.
Teleport.
Now show up over here.
Yeah, yeah, so he
teleported himself.
They caught on to us.
Okay, I know what to do.
‐Great show.
‐Come back, people!
That was only Act One!
Bleh!
(mouth warbling)
This is one lady you don't
want to mess around with.
He's right, I wouldn't
mess around with her
if you paid me!
Now I've
transformed into horn.
And, finally, the
best of both worlds!
Thank you, thank
you very much.
You very kind.
Boy, I feel like my
stomach is gonna burst.
Chi.
Yeah, but now
we're out of money.
Don't be so cheap.
Yeah, chi, Mocchi fight
battle and win some gold.
Let me help you practice.
Sure, chi.
I hear a couple of
weirdoes are doing
some magic tricks
around here.
You want to go check it out?
‐Magic?
‐Chi?
Hey, let's go and see.
Chi, Mocchi go.
‐Come on!
‐Chi!
♪
Move.
(crying)
Hey, are you all right?
Daddy!
Hmm!
(stomping)
Come back here!
Chi!
I said come back,
bunch of cowards.
Huh?
So you do have
ears after all.
Sounds like you're
looking for a fight.
Okay, you're on.
Better quit while you can.
You have no idea what
you're up against here.
He's the famous Battle Rocks,
winner of six
grand championships
and a competitor in
the Legend Cup today.
These are his
championship cards.
Bow before the champ.
You're the ones
that should bow.
Yes, sir.
Hey, wait!
You tricked us, you brat.
What did you push
that little kid for?
Say sorry, chi.
You two keep out of this.
But, master!
Challenging me in public.
I can't back down now.
♪
I accept, but you're
going to regret this.
‐Yeah, right.
‐Better do something fast,
or I'll make the first move.
Double forehead jab!
Mocchi, Genki!
‐Move out.
‐Yes, master.
Oh, poor Mocchi.
That was a lucky shot.
Chi.
(groaning)
Genki, Mocchi,
oh, you poor guys.
Genki, can you hear me?
Here you go.
♪
Feeling a bit better?
Yeah, where's Mocchi?
(crying)
Mocchi want to
become strong, chi.
It's just about time
for the competition!
Let's hurry!
Wonder what they're
talking about.
Maybe it's that Legend Cup
the Baddies mentioned.
Mocchi go watch.
If that Baddie's
gonna be in it,
then I want to go
and see how he fights.
Chi!
(fireworks exploding)
Ladies, gentlemen,
and monsters,
what a grand day it is
here at the Torble Stadium.
Today, our first challengers
will be competing
for the Legend Cup,
the ultimate trophy in
monster battle competitions.
Wow, the crowd
here is going wild.
Yeah, chi!
As you're all aware,
competitors in the Legend Cup
must have won at
least six winner cards
in order to qualify.
Those are the same
cards that Baddie had!
And now the challenger.
Introducing a monster that
has crushed one opponent
after the other
with a single blow,
the fierce and
mighty Battle Rocks!
(cheering)
Next, the defending champions.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you the legendary
white knight Poritoka!
He looks like Suezo.
And the one you've all
been waiting for, Most!
♪
Chi.
He looks just
like you, Mocchi.
You could almost be twins.
In order to win
the Legend Cup,
the challenger must defeat
both Poritoka and Most.
Who will Battle Rocks
fight first?
Battle Rocks, choose
your first opponent.
♪
And Most it is.
Battle Rocks has chosen
Most as his first opponent.
I doubt if Most will be a
challenge for Battle Rocks.
Battle Rocks is strong, chi.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
I was just thinking,
Suezo and Golem might
be here watching.
Like they'd ever be
interested in a monster battle.
(grunting)
Want to see Legend Cup, Suezo?
Counting my taste buds
might be more fun.
But Genki and Holly and
others might be there.
Yeah, right.
I'm napping.
(snoring)
10,000 golds and the
championship are on the line.
Let's get it on!
Ready, go!
♪
Say your prayers, cream puff.
(chuckling)
(gasping)
♪
Battle Rocks is going in
with one of his specialties,
the twin slam!
♪
(grunting)
Ooh!
(chuckling)
(grunting)
♪
Most is in his
usual good form.
Just look at that
fancy footwork.
♪
This will stop you!
Twister attack!
♪
Huh?
Hmm!
Flower shower!
♪
(groaning)
(gasping)
Done in by a bunch of flowers.
Most wins with
one blow knockout!
He beat Battle Rocks.
And with only one blow.
One blow, chi.
To the victor Most,
we present this prize
of 10,000 golds!
And the trophy will remain
in the reigning
champion's possession!
Holly, is that what I think?
What, I don't believe it.
The golden trophy symbolizes
the champion's victory
and is adorned
with a magic stone
possessing supernatural powers
from which the holder can
obtain immeasurable strength.
(humming)
♪
Folks, it seems that Most has
impressed the magic stone!
It's starting to
glow as we speak!
Holly?
I tried to contact it.
I'm sure it's
the magic stone.
Chi!
But it disappeared.
Then it must have
either recrystallized
or else maybe
someone found it.
Yeah, and considering how old
it is, I guess it's possible
that there'd be more
than one magic stone.
And there they go,
our reigning champions.
Come on, folks, let's give 'em
one last round of applause!
(applauding)
♪
Bye‐bye, magic stone.
Hey, hold on.
‐If we had that stone...
‐Mmhmm.
If we had that magic stone,
we might be able
to get your dad
out of that
mystery disk, Holly.
Chi!
Yeah, right!
Oh, but it's too dangerous.
Don't worry, Holly.
You know, the magic
stone will probably help
keep the evil soul
in the mystery disk.
Hmm.
Come on, let's go
talk to the champions
and see if they'll
lend us the stone.
‐Okay.
‐Chi!
Ah, what do you mean
you don't know?
I'm sorry, young man,
but no one knows
where Most and Poritoka live
or where they keep
the magic stone.
They show up when and where
the Legend Cup is held.
Oh, well, then do you know
how I can get myself
a magic stone?
You'll just have to
win the Legend Cup.
Huh?
Mocchi try!
Mocchi try to win Legend Cup!
If you're going to
enter the Legend Cup,
then you'll have
to win all six
of these
pre‐tournaments to qualify.
Mocchi try!
Ah, that a boy, Mocchi!
And I'm gonna enter
the tournament with ya.
This championship is
for monsters alone.
(sighing)
Only monsters, huh?
Can't you even make one
little exception for me?
I'm afraid rules are
rules, young man.
But your friend here can
still register if he'd like.
Mocchi, don't feel like you've
got to do it just for me.
I'm sure there must be some
other way to release my‐‐
‐No, Holly!
‐Huh?
Mocchi want to be stronger,
that way Mocchi
can win contest.
That's why Mocchi
want to win!
Mocchi!
Hmm.
Okay, I'm gonna register as
my monster friend's trainer.
On the double, ma'am.
Oh, right away.
♪
(sighing)
First, the physicals,
then the written tests.
Ah, man, I'm beat.
Chi.
Well, what now?
It's late in the day
and we're out of money,
so I guess we should
find a place to camp.
Okay, let's find the
best campsite we can.
Chi!
I wonder if Suezo and
the others are somewhere
looking at this
very same sunset.
‐Yeah.
‐Chi.
I hope we catch
up with them soon.
So do I.
Where is everyone, chi?
(grumbling)
Looks like they weren't
in this village either.
Golem very unhappy.
Might as well look for a place
to camp out for the night.
Oh.
(stomping)
Huh?
Suezo, Golem!
Genki, Mocchi!
Holly!
(grunting)
Ah!
♪
‐Golem!
‐Golem sorry.
(laughing)
We find you.
Golem and Suezo search
for you everywhere.
We look for you, chi.
I missed you crazy kids!
‐We did too.
‐You bet.
Holly, I never want to
leave your side again!
Same with me.
Then we'll just have
to stay together.
Yeah!
(laughing)
All right.
♪
So, what are we here for?
Because this is where we
lost that pesky group.
And you figured you
should bring me back here?
Precisely, Pink Jam.
Do you think
they're crazy enough
to be lazing around
this place still?
Hear that?
He almost made a rhyme there.
Crazy and lazy.
See, did I tell ya
he was smart?
(grunting)
Quiet, you dimwits!
♪
(laughing)
Oh, just you wait and see.
Once my body and that
evil soul has united,
then I'll show you all.
I will conquer the world.
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪