♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(birds squawking)
‐The ocean.
‐Chi!
♪
We've gotta make the
crossing to get to Calia.
Then let's go see if we
can find ourselves a ship.
Uh!
Hmm?
Ocean.
Golem scared.
Don't worry, Golem.
We'll find a big boat
to take us across.
It'll be so big
it won't even rock.
No be scared, chi!
Then Golem will go, but
only if you find big boat.
Yeah, come on, gang,
we've got places to go.
Yeah!
Gol'.
♪
There they are.
Better report
this to Mum Mew.
♪
So I can get from this to this
if I put this on
for three days?
Yes.
Are you sure about this?
Don't forget, Gobi, these
get‐slim‐quick gimmicks
have conned me out of my
hard‐earned money before.
You've done your research
on this, I assume.
Yes, of course.
(snapping)
You're wasting your time.
Nothing can help you, kitty.
General Durahan, we
succeeded in locating Genki
and all his friends.
Finally.
So where are they?
Right now, they're
searching for a boat
to take them across
the sea to Calia.
Then we haven't
got time to waste.
Leave things to me.
I've sent some men.
Ha, so you actually
did something?
Usually you're glued
to your own reflection.
♪
This time, we'll get the
mystery disk for sure.
Ha, we'll see about that.
I'll be expecting
some good news.
(laughing)
♪
It quiet, chi.
It doesn't look like
anybody is around.
Give me another iced tea!
Not on your life!
You haven't paid me
for the first one yet.
Ah, come on, matey.
Just one more mug.
Have a little compassion
for a fellow sea dog
who's down on his luck,
will ya, me hearty?
And stay out!
(coughing)
I ought to keehaul ya.
‐Horn?
‐Huh?
I knew it, it is you.
I don't know who
you think I am,
but maybe you should
listen to your mom
and not talk to
strangers, mate.
Don't you remember us?
Take another look.
Huh?
Hey, it's the land lubbers!
Have we met before?
Are you serious?
You really don't remember us?
This pirate would never
forget a lassie like you.
How about a reunion smooch?
Ah‐ha, if you remember her,
you must remember who I am.
‐Huh?
‐Hey!
Sure, yellow matey,
how could I forget you?
Eyezo.
It's Suezo, ya
sea‐swarming pirate!
Oh, you brig rat!
Calm down now.
This is good timing, Horn.
We were just thinking we
should start looking for ya.
Hare's telling the truth.
We need to find a ship.
Horn, you'll help
us out, won't you?
Don't worry,
we're gonna pay ya.
Well, about that
ship of mine...
Huh, someone stole
your ship from ya?
Who did it?
How would I know?
I wasn't on board.
Ya see, me mates and me
were having ourselves
a little R‐and‐R.
I was treatin' me loyal
men to some time off,
and we was restin' our weary
bones on a quiet desert isle.
To the best darn soda
float swillin' mates
a pirate can have!
Ah, it was a
night to remember.
But the next morning when
we got ourselves out of bed,
our ship was
nowhere in sight.
I guess that's
the whole point
of leaving someone on board
to stand guard, isn't it?
So, what happened next?
Did you find your
ship or what?
Of course not!
Why would I be
wasting my time here
with a bunch of land lubbers
if I had my ship back already?
Well, then, be seeing ya.
Ahoy, how can you turn
your back on your old matey
knowing the fix I'm in here?
Cinch, we need
to find a pirate
running a ship, not a dock.
Love to help ya, but we're
really short on time.
We must go to Calia.
Come on, gang, let's go find
a ship to take us across.
Land lubbers,
some mates you are!
Too bad they didn't ask if
I had a replacement ship
or I'd have
offered 'em a ride.
Huh?
So let's see the ship.
I knew you'd come through.
Follow me.
Ta‐ta‐ta‐da!
What do ya think?
It's a raft.
This is no raft.
It's the unprecedented,
unparalleled,
unsinkable warship Horn II.
It isn't exactly the kind
of ship we had in mind.
I think we're
gonna have to pass.
Move along, me hearties.
No need to be shy.
Whoa!
(splashing)
What should we do, gang?
Well, at least
this thing floats.
It might be faster to
just take the raft across
rather than start
searching for a proper ship.
Are you serious?
Then let's set sail,
you swabbies.
(grunting)
♪
Blow me down, that salt
air really does something
to cheer up a pirate's heart.
It is nice, and we're
making good time.
Just keep on paddling.
The sun is going down.
Get real, Tiger, put some
muscle into it, would ya?
Yeah, right.
♪
I'm bushed.
Ditto, chi.
I give up.
My taste buds have blisters.
Eyezo, I'm the captain here,
so paddle until I
tell you to stop.
You look tired, my dear,
how about a little
stargazing with an old pirate?
Uh, I'm really not tired.
I could paddle for hours!
Come on, Horn, how much
longer do we have to go?
We're almost ready
to collapse here.
Despair not,
me fine hearties.
At this rate, we'll be
there in three days.
Ah!
I've never heard
so much grumblin'.
These waters are dangerous,
so consider yourself lucky
to be with a pirate like me.
Dangerous?
Golem not like this
idea from start.
Right, it's time you learned
about the legends 'round here.
On dark nights, a mysterious
glowing fog has been known
to surround ships
in the area.
And through the fog
comes a piercing laugh.
(laughing)
And just when you figure
nothing could be worse
than that shrilling,
haunting laughter,
an enormous ship suddenly
appears from out of nowhere.
Legend goes, one encounter
and you'll never be
heard from again.
'Course I've never been
afraid of legends meself‐‐ah!
Who's that ramming
me precious ship?
♪
Ah!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Shaped like an urn,
Bajar hoards men ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Including a town, can't
tell where it's been ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ General Kato is
good and wise ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ He knows how it works,
but some are surprised ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monol is flat,
but Monol is deep ♪
♪ His biggest problem,
he falls asleep ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Hang on, me hearties!
Wait a sec, look at that.
Huh?
Do you see that figurehead?
Shiver me timbers, my ship!
Whoa, where'd that come from?
Do you think
someone is on board?
Seems like they want us
to come up on deck.
I don't see anyone.
Don't think it's
a ghost, do ya?
We'll soon see.
Wait!
What are the chances I'd
be rammed by my own ship?
I'm going on board
to find the bilge rats
that stole it from me, ha!
Haven't you heard?
Ghost ships are bad luck.
Come back, Horn!
Tiger.
It's too dangerous to finish
the crossing in this raft.
We're better off
taking this ship
the rest of the way to Calia.
♪
They've ruined my ship.
This is creepy.
I think we should take
our chances on the raft.
I'm going on in, come on!
What do you mean, "Come on"?
Golem will guard
ship from here.
Got ya, stay right
here, we'll be back.
No, don't leave us!
Uh, wait up for me, you guys!
Show yourselves,
you yellow bellies!
The place is deserted.
Let's go look around
the other rooms.
Ah!
Ah, they've broken me
favorite penny jar!
(panting)
♪
No one here, chi.
Something's not right.
Huh?
I felt something, but
every time we open the door
the feeling disappeared.
Are you suggesting it's‐‐
Ghosties?
Holly, hold on to me, I'm so
scared, I don't know what‐‐
Hey, ya big faker!
Eyezo, quit shouting at me!
I don't remember this hat
being on the table
a minute ago.
(shouting)
It's a ghost!
Ah!
(laughing and gasping)
He's got my mystery disk!
Holly!
Lightning attack!
Look at 'em all.
Hey, they got
the Baddies' crest.
They're monster ghosts!
Dragon kick!
Lightning attack!
(laughing)
They keep disappearing on us.
‐Hmm.
‐Wait, Mocchi.
Cherry blossom blizzard!
(shouting)
♪
The mystery disk!
Got it!
It fell through.
That's a storage hold below
so it's not going anywhere.
Good call, let's go get it.
Follow me, me hearties!
♪
There they are.
(laughing)
Hey, you're not
getting away this time.
Give us back that bag
before we get angry.
Look!
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
This is going a bit too
far, wouldn't you say?
Ah, I've never been
so embarrassed.
(laughing)
Great fashion
statement, Tiger.
That fox fur thing
was getting tired.
You're asking for it!
Just try and get me, furball!
We've got to find
a way out of here.
Suezo, Horn, do something.
Aye‐aye, I'll get us out.
Ah!
Just you watch, Holly.
I'll use me horn
and get us all out.
I'm stuck.
How about the teleport?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Teleport!
Ta‐da!
And, now...
How about a thank‐you kiss?
Come on, Holly.
Shouldn't you be
concentrating more
on getting your ship back
from those ghost Baddies?
Oh, yeah, those guys.
Prepare yourselves
for a frontal attack!
Yeah!
Wait a minute, if we charge
in there without a plan,
then the same thing
is gonna happen.
That's right, if we only knew
what their
vulnerable point was.
‐I know.
‐Huh?
I got a plan, and
it just might work.
There's one thing I heard that
conquers ghosts every time,
and I can do it.
In fact, all
Suezos can do it.
So tell us what it is!
Hurry up and tell us, chi!
You mean your tongue slap?
‐Strike one.
‐Then your tail attack?
‐Strike two.
‐How about your teleport?
‐Strike three.
‐Enough suspense.
Just tell us.
Well, you won't believe this,
but I can't remember.
Then what was all
that suspense about?
I've been trying to jog
my memory, all right?
All righty then.
This'd be a good time
to move on, so let's spy
on those ghost Baddies
then come up with a plan.
Put Eyezo and me in
charge of the stakeout.
All right, no fighting.
Use teleport, chi.
Suezo, forget about that
plan of yours for now.
Got ya, now how did it go?
Hey, what are you doing?
You're not the greatest
at this teleport thing,
so why don't we
go as a double?
Teleport coming through!
(grunting)
So...
Where do you think we landed?
This a pantry or something?
Yeah, it's the
pantry, all right,
but there sure wasn't this
much stuff on board before.
Ah‐ha, now I've got it.
Those ghost Baddies
go around pretending
this is a pirate ship,
then they steal treasure
and valuables
from other ships.
They do what?
See, there never was
a real ghost ship.
The rumor just started
because the ship looked
so creepy, that's all.
They're gonna pay!
Teleport!
♪
Oh.
Oh, no, they've got
Golem surrounded.
Whoa, check out the
parade behind us!
Ah, they're
stealing my treasure!
Shh, keep your voice down.
(indistinct chattering)
Blimey, the nerve of those
sea dogs stealing treasure
from a hardworking pirate.
Yeah.
Look!
He's got our mystery disk.
The one with the yellow
glasses must be the boss.
♪
What are they tying
down the wheel for?
That'll make the ship
keep going straight.
Wait a minute.
Unless I'm mistaken.
Aye!
I knew it, land ho!
Those ghost Baddies are
going to run my ship ashore!
They're gonna what?
Those ghouls!
They're gonna run this
ship aground and sink it,
and then get away
with our mystery disk
and all the treasure.
‐Oh, no, they won't!
‐Get back here!
Let me go, I gotta get
my ship back on course
before we crash.
Yeah, sure, but
with just two of us,
they got us outnumbered.
Let's teleport back.
We'll get the
others to help us.
Mm, right, let's get going.
Lightning attack!
♪
Hmm!
Hey, ghostie,
lightning attack!
♪
Free Golem!
Golem!
Holly!
‐Got it!
‐Chi!
You're free, Golem,
now let's move.
Golem afraid of water.
Ah!
(shouting)
♪
Double pounder, double
pounder, double pounder!
You know, fighting ghosts is
a lot harder than it looks.
(grunting)
♪
Ta‐da!
Lightning attack!
♪
(grunting)
Ah!
Ah, whoa!
Genki!
Go!
Whoa!
Oh!
Golem, Genki!
Don't worry about us,
just get the disk.
Ha‐ha‐ha!
Eyezo, we gotta
untie the wheel
or else we'll all be
heading for the drink.
I hear ya.
Get ready, ghosts!
Tail attack!
And a Horn tail attack!
Ah!
Oops, bad landing approach.
(gasping)
(humming)
♪
I just remembered how
to conquer ghosts!
Teleport!
Hey, not bad, I must
be getting better.
♪
(screaming)
Testing, one, two, three.
Your attention, please.
I finally remembered.
I know what
ghosts can't stand,
so now without further ado
just sit back and
enjoy the music.
♪ My name is Suezo
and I'm here to say ♪
♪ My tongue slap will
whip ya any old day ♪
I'm bringing tears
to my own eye.
Come on, fella, get
a grip on yourself.
♪ If'n you need a hero,
then I'm your man ♪
What's that terrible sound?
Ah, my head's gonna break!
♪ I'm your eyeball ♪
♪ I can fight like
no other eyeball can ♪
♪ My name is Suezo ♪
I gotta stop this.
Teleport.
Hey, what do you think
you're doing to my ship here?
Calm down, I was just
getting to the good part.
Ya got everybody on deck
looking like they're
going through the bends.
Here, let me show
you how it's done.
♪ I was raised on the ocean ♪
♪ By a one‐legged friend ♪
Enough already,
we'll do anything
to stop that
horrible singing.
How's a singer supposed
to do his warm‐up drills
when Old Yeller's doing
everything to trip him up?
Then couldn't we at
least make it a duet?
Great idea, me swabbie.
That's enough!
The ghosts already took
off a long time ago.
Too bad, I was just
getting to the chorus.
How 'bout another
song to celebrate?
Forget it!
Everyone's a critic.
Didn't need to
get rude about it.
Well, at least we got rid of
those no‐good
pirate ghost Baddies.
Wait a sec, something tells me
we forgot about something!
The rope, the rope!
♪
(rustling)
Ah, another glorious
day on the sea,
and I got my ship and
all me men back on board.
Land ho, Captain,
Calia's in sight!
(cheering)
The island people
would be terrified
if they saw a fierce
pirate ship like mine,
so we better get going
before they spot us.
Thoughtful of you.
Don't go losing
your ship again.
Chi!
Eyezo, practice up for
our singing match.
I'll be singing sweet
till next we meet!
Oh, no, more singing.
You said it.
No more singing for me.
Goodbye, Horn.
I hope we can meet again.
♪
Bye!
Have a safe trip!
Farewell, me hearties!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪