♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(birds cawing)
(grunting)
You see, Gobi,
I told you that old mirror
made me look fat.
Don't I look wonderful now?
Um.
Poison's got attitude,
but she hasn't got any curves
that I don't have.
Something's not right.
(grunting)
Oh, head hurting!
What's your problem?
♪
General Durahan,
you'll be pleased
to know we've located
Genki and his group
along the coast near Mandi.
What?
Man, why didn't
you tell us sooner!
You incompetent fur ball!
Enough squabbling!
On to my collection!
Hear my voice and awaken,
Strong and Composed One.
Jelly Gaboo!
(zapping)
♪
I'm certain that
you warriors can do the job.
Count on it, General.
♪
Well, Holly, any luck?
No, I still can't hear him.
But you could hear
your dad's voice
up until a few days ago, right?
Keep on trying, 'chi.
There's no point,
I've been trying all night.
Holly‐‐
Don't worry, you guys.
I can feel him.
I know that he's safe,
but, for now, I can't hear,
that's all.
Holly.
Then, as long as you make sure
to hang on to that mystery disk.
One day, you'll see
Father for sure.
But it'll never happen
if you lose hope.
Right, 'chi!
I'll lend you an ear
anytime at all.
You guys.
Come on, it's time
to move out, everybody.
(cheering)
♪
What's this?
Hey guys, there's
something here
I think you should see!
(laughter)
♪
This is great!
It doesn't look
like anyone's around.
I wonder what they're
dredging up from underwater?
♪
Look out!
(zapping)
♪
(yelping)
Not more Jelly Babies!
Look, they're baddies!
Hey, Mocchi, blow 'em away
with your Mocchi Cannon!
'chi!
Great idea.
♪
Sorry, Mocchi not ready yet.
(all groan)
Let's get 'em, boys!
(all grunting)
♪
Lightning Attack!
Tongue Slap!
♪
(cannon fire)
Huh?
♪
Oh, the mystery disk!
After it!
♪
'chi!
Oh, no!
♪
Genki, Mocchi!
How dare you obstruct
my important work!
Huh?
Oh, don't play innocent!
You're after my treasure!
Your treasure?
You know what I mean!
The pirate ship
that sank in these waters.
Pirate ship, around here?
We don't know anything about it,
so lay off, old man!
I demand some respect!
I am the great adventurer,
Professor Gordish.
I caught you two red‐handed!
You and the Jelly Gaboos
were searching for my treasure!
You'll regret that!
Oh, you looking for a fight?
Huh, look out, you guys!
(yelping)
I'll get you.
(rumbling)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Jura Walls in
the creepy swamp ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Wood Golem loves
its forest stomp ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Tombstones
with a cutting flair,
keep 'em distant
from your hair ♪
♪ Don't be shy now,
stand up tall ♪
♪ 400 monsters, unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it,
unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
We've gotta get that disk back!
You run along the beach and see
if you can distract the old guy,
I'll jump in the water
when he's not looking!
Right.
Wait, diving for the disk
is way too risky.
The water's just too deep.
Too deep?
Then, how are we supposed
to get the Mystery Disk back?
(groaning)
You're the brain,
Hare, can't you come up
with something?
Yeah, but it's not
as easy as it sounds.
The disk's on the seabed,
too deep to dive.
Huh?
Wait a second!
Well, it looks like
I frightened off
those scallywags!
♪
All right, we're
following the troops.
Now what do they want?
You want what?
(hysterical laughter)
Are you outta your
minds or something?
Why would I let you
on board my sub?
Come on, Professor,
we need your help here.
We've gotta hurry and find it
before those giant gummi bears.
Ha, we won't make it
at this time of day.
The currents are too strong
for Jelly Gaboo or my sub!
Good, then
the mystery disk is safe!
We'll go after it again
first thing in the morning.
♪
What do you say, Professor,
will you help us in the morning?
Pretty please, 'chi?
Why would I even bother
when there's obviously
nothing in it for me?
Go on, get lost!
Hold your horses, skip.
In return for the favor,
we'll do any chores on board.
Cooking, cleaning,
we'll even swab the decks!
Please, Professor.
Please help us find it!
That disk is important to us.
I mean, the mystery disk
means everything to me,
so can't you find it
in your heart to help us out?
♪
I know we said we'd do anything,
but this is ridiculous!
We're doing it for
the mystery disk.
♪
Man, I've never had to do
anything so demeaning.
(laughing)
Maybe you should get
a job as a maid.
Wanna get eaten?
What did you say?
(humming)
♪
Here you go, I hope
you like my soup, Professor.
(sniffs)
It certainly smells good.
Professor, thanks
for everything.
What do you mean?
The mystery disk,
you'll help us find it?
Of course I will; I don't lie.
Ah.
You know, you sure are
a close bunch of friends.
Everyone pitches in
to help retrieve a mere disk.
'chi, we're good friends, 'chi.
Friends, huh?
Huh?
Is this a photo of you
and your friends, Professor?
(slurps)
I don't have any friends.
But isn't that your sub
in the background?
Those are my old diving buddies.
We used to be friends,
but the fools abandoned me
when they realized
finding treasure
wasn't as easy
as they first thought.
(slurps)
♪
I'd like to go along,
I'm the only one who can sense
where the mystery disk is.
Fine, but it's too cramped
to take the whole lot of you.
Take you two, but that's it.
The four of us will go.
(chuckles)
As for the rest of you‐‐
Huh?
What is it?
Yeah, what?
We'll do anything!
Return to cleaning duty.
You're kidding me!
I'll stand guard instead,
seeing as the baddies
might be back!
Oh, no, I'll stand guard
and you do the laundry!
What?
Golem on guard.
Oh, no, I want in on this.
(commotion)
Ha, good friends, you say?
(chuckling)
We'll keep an eye
on things while you're gone.
Don't come back empty‐handed!
Bye, we won't.
Now, let's get that disk.
'chi!
♪
(grumbling)
(gasps)
Is everything
all right, Professor?
It sure seems
like a bumpy ride.
Nothing to worry about,
I know these currents
better than anyone!
The seas will be
calming down soon.
♪
Oh, you're right.
Feels a lot calmer already.
Holly?
Right.
♪
Father, where are you?
Please answer me.
Father... Father?
♪
There he is, I feel him.
Further down, on the left.
We're counting on you, big guy.
Sure, but before we descend,
I'm gonna need you two to work.
Anything you say.
'chi!
Start pedaling,
we need to save fuel!
(groaning)
No griping, now get
those feet pumping!
Yes, sir.
We need to head deeper.
(grunting)
♪
Even deeper.
Keep going straight,
that's the way, straight on.
♪
Huh?
I didn't know there
was a cave down here.
I can really sense it,
we're getting very close!
We're heading into
another strong current!
♪
(yelping)
Now where are we?
'chi!
♪
Look, it's our mystery disk!
We found it.
(gasping)
Professor, what is it?
Is something the matter?
(gasping)
It's the lost pirate ship
you've been searching for!
'chi!
At last, I found my ship!
♪
(grunting)
Wow, check it out,
Holly, a real cannon.
(laughing)
♪
Finally, the treasure
I've been searching for!
(gasping)
This must be worth millions!
It's incredible!
Congratulations, Professor!
Let's start packing it up!
'chi!
(rumbling)
(yelping)
The Jelly Gaboos!
Run for it, guys!
♪
(laughing)
How'd they beat us up here?
Thanks for leading us
straight to the disk.
Now, you can hand it over,
along with all these treasures!
(grunting)
♪
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
Huh?
♪
Mocchi, save the Professor!
'chi!
I don't need your help.
I've always been able
to hold my own.
(grunting)
♪
(yelps)
'chi!
(grunting)
♪
This definitely means war.
(chuckling)
(grunting)
♪
(explosion)
(cannon fire)
Professor!
Come on, Holly, let's go.
Right.
(grunts)
♪
You saved the day, Professor.
It's not over, hold on!
♪
After them!
Mocchi, jump down here!
♪
No use, won't open.
That last explosion
must've broken it!
♪
Mocchi!
Do something!
Here goes.
(grunting)
♪
My sub's starting
to break apart!
♪
Now finish them!
(gasping)
♪
'chi!
(grunting)
Professor!
(snickering)
♪
Go get that disk!
(grunting)
♪
Mocchi Cannon!
(screams hysterically)
♪
Mocchi got 'em all!
(gasping)
Where's that coming from?
♪
Huh?
Now, that's what I call
a good entrance.
(mixed celebration)
Mocchi, you did it!
(laughing)
(yelps, splash)
♪
Keep searching, everyone!
We're bound to find
some of that treasure!
I don't know, skip, that was
a pretty big explosion.
We'll never find
the old man's treasure.
What do you say we give up?
Didn't we have an agreement
that you were gonna
do anything for me?
A little longer
won't hurt, Suezo.
(laughs heartily)
♪
Now that's enough my friends!
You certainly are
true to your word.
I know you got things to do,
so I'll let you be on your way.
Whoa, and thanks again!
You sure we can go?
I'm surprised you
didn't sneak off earlier!
We'd never sneak off
from a friend in need.
Besides, you kept
your promise to us.
Professor help us find disk.
Thank you, 'chi!
Thank you, Professor Gordish.
Well, I'm not one
for sentimental goodbyes.
Where you off to, Professor?
Where else?
To find me some treasure!
Huh?
This isn't the only place around
that has a sunken treasure ship!
(all groan)
(laughs)
Farewell, my friends!
♪
Bon voyage, Professor!
'chi!
Thanks again!
♪
Bye‐bye!
See you later!
Happy sailing!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪