♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
I'm so glad we found Tiger.
Now we just need to find Hare.
'chi!
Huh, we'll get by
just fine without him.
Huh, listen to him, he's the
one who misses Hare the most.
Want to rethink that?
Come on, I was just kidding.
Hmmph.
What's the next
championship, Genki?
The Mandy Cup, it's
a two on two match.
Well, then I'm
going to go in it.
‐You'll win for sure!
‐Tiger is strong.
Hm.
Hey, hang on a sec.
When Mocchi was unlocked from
the mystery disc he'd forgotten
all of his fighting techniques.
You think that
happened to Tiger, too?
Ha, Mocchi and I are
in two different leagues.
I think not.
That's mean, 'chi,
then try something, 'chi.
(chuckles)
Watch.
♪
Lightning Attack!
(grunting)
♪
Blizzard Attack!
Technique no work like Mocchi.
Not a whole lot of
oomph in that blizzard!
Suezo funny, 'chi!
(cackling)
Quiet!
I was afraid this might happen.
Poor Tiger.
I'll be right here to
practice with you, 'chi.
Oh, yeah, good idea!
I still don't believe this!
Blizzard!
♪
Lightning Attack!
Blizzard...Lightning Attack...
Blizzard...
(groaning)
(snoring)
Lightning Attack...
B‐Blizzard Att‐‐
(yawning)
Time to move on yet?
(panting)
♪
General Durahan never
learns his lesson, does he?
Meaning?
He was betrayed before
by a woman named Lilim.
Now he's got that
Poison woman around,
and I think I know
where that's headed.
Oh?
Honestly, men can such fools,
it really scares me!
You're a man, tell me, Gobi,
what's going on in
that head of yours?
Well, I‐‐I‐‐I‐‐
Oh, my head hurts!
(loud clank)
♪
Poison.
(laughing)
So glad to see you're looking
after your master, Poison.
Good news, Master,
we've located the Jells.
Excellent!
My magnificent collection.
(gears clicking)
My witty, striped warrior,
hear my voice and awaken!
Fierce and agile one,
Zebra Saurian!
(steam blowing)
♪
Oh, animal print, that would
look great as a halter top.
Zebra Saurian!
Get me that mystery disc!
Cheer up, Tiger!
Yeah, you can still use
your Torpedo Attack!
Ugh, I need more than
a single fighting technique.
If I don't change
them once in awhile
my whole rhythm's thrown off.
Mocchi only use Mocchi Cannon
and Double Pounder.
I thought I told you
not to compare us!
(grunt)
Is something the matter?
Is it a Baddie?
I don't know, but
someone's watching us.
Huh?
♪
It's Datonare and Daton.
(in unison)
Master, Tiger!
Who are they?
Oh, I know, they're
Tiger's old friends
who he used to hang out with.
Tiger's followers!
Yeah.
I thought you became mystery
discs when the Baddies
were chasing us?
We did become Mystery discs,
but some human unlocked us,
so we thanked him and took off
to live in the wild again.
The rest of our group
must still be out there,
but we haven't found them yet.
‐That's good news.
‐It's a really good thing
that mystery discs can
be unlocked, huh, Holly?
Yeah.
It's time to celebrate, follow
us, Master, we'll have a feast!
Right!
Hey, Tiger, wait for us!
‐'chi!
‐What's the rush?
Go!
♪
See, all the mangos
you could ever eat.
Only problem is
we can't get them down.
Hey, you guys, are you sure
these aren't on someone's farm?
Of course they are.
We're thieves and our job
is to steal from people.
You shouldn't steal from people!
We won't take much.
Oh, Tiger!
(groan)
♪
Whoa!
(loud crash)
(groaning)
♪
Ugh, looks like the one guy
who could stoop this low.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk! ♪
♪ Furred Suezo,
a timid type ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ When there's scrappin',
he just won't bite ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Fly Eye Bully
you don't wanna cross ♪
♪ Furred Suezo takes
on their boss ♪
♪ Make a stand,
no need to brawl ♪
♪ So many monsters
unlock them all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(laughing)
Looks like another victim has
fallen for that trap of mine!
Look, it's Hare!
Genki, you found me!
Ah!
(laughing)
I missed you!
I'm so glad we found you, Hare!
'chi!
Golem happy, Hare.
How've you been, rabbit?
Pretty good, considering.
This is great, now all
of us are together again.
Hare, get me out of here!
Well, well, if it isn't
my old friend, Mr. Tiger.
You're in for it!
Is that so?
You know, I kind of missed
you too, you old furball!
(chuckling)
Hare, could you help me
out with these mangos?
♪
(chewing sounds)
So, that's where
the Magic Stone is.
That's right.
And in order to get it‐‐
Mocchi going to fight in
Legend Cup and win, 'chi!
Then we seal evil soul
in mystery disc.
Then we'll be able to bring
Holly's father back.
I getcha.
So what have you been
doing since we saw you last?
Where should I begin?
I found him and
brought him here.
(giggles)
Wait a sec.
Hey, I thought you
were a little boy!
Can't you tell the difference
between a boy and a girl?
I should have introduced you,
this is Tama and she's
the owner of this orchard.
The one and only.
This brat is the owner?
I'm 11 and I'm taller
than your friend here.
‐Are not!
‐I am too!
(grunting)
Calm down now,
let's all be friends.
♪
So how did you come across Hare?
We still haven't heard.
Oh, right.
My parents left this orchard
to me and I've been running it
on my own but there are so many
outlaw strays in the area
that come harvest
time they steal
practically all my ripe fruit.
(in unison)
Hmm.
Gah!
(laughing)
I'm not talking about you.
Yeah, I know, sure we're strays
but we're new around here.
And we never could
reach your fruit.
Anyway, the orchard was so big
it was too much work for me.
I'd almost reached
the point of giving up.
(loud explosion)
♪
(moaning)
And that's when I met Hare.
You mean you were like us
and didn't get turned
into a mystery disc?
What, did some of you get
turned into mystery discs?
That's right, Mocchi
and Tiger, 'chi!
And because of that
they've both lost most
of their fighting
techniques, Hare.
‐Are you serious?
Hey, lay off!
(giggling)
Getting back to our story, I
stayed on the orchard to pay
Tama back for saving me.
I thought about you guys all the
time and wanted to go find you,
but I just couldn't leave
Tama here on her own.
Before I knew it
a year had flown by.
Hm.
♪
Sorry there isn't
more room in the house
but hopefully you'll be comfy.
I'll bring you guys some
warm blankets later.
Hope you have a good sleep.
Thanks, Tama.
♪
How are we ever gonna
ask Hare to come with us?
It'd be pretty selfish asking
Hare to leave Tama on her own
and help the six of us.
Selfish, 'chi.
Maybe we should spare him
the dilemma and not ask him.
But what if we get into
trouble and need him?
What do you mean?
I mean trouble when the
evil soul is unlocked.
We need five to become Phoenix.
You mean Tiger and
you fought together
on the Legendary Phoenix?
I knew Master Tiger
was something special.
Huh, even if we can't
become the Phoenix,
I'll take care of any trouble.
One Blizzard, hold the ice.
‐(growling)
‐(whimpering)
Fighting no good, stop!
Tiger's right about
not asking Hare.
Because if Hare stays,
then for one thing,
he'll never have to fight
with the Baddies again.
I'm sure he'll have a
much happier life here
on the orchard.
(collective sigh)
♪
Thanks again for
letting us visit.
Yeah, sure, no problem.
Oh, don't look so worried,
we'll be just fine.
You said it, we
even talked these two
into coming along with us.
We'll try to protect them.
And try not to
get into any trouble.
That sounds terrific.
Personally, I'll be
glad to get rid of you.
Hm?
♪
That reminds me, you've
forgotten your technique,
so here's something
you can use.
(whispering)
Hm, now who do you think
you're talking to, here?
Sorry, just trying to
help out an old friend.
You take care of yourself, Hare.
Think of us while you're
feasting on mangos!
You can count on it.
We'll see you again, right?
You betcha, Holly!
See ya!
We'll miss you, 'chi!
Bye, you guys, and
thanks for coming!
Stop right there!
(in unison)
Huh?
You came here to take
Hare away, didn't you?
No, we just came
for a short visit.
Yeah, right, Hare, feel free
to take off with your friends.
No, I wanna stay.
You know, I don't like it
when people lie to me, now go!
I can run this orchard
without you now, Hare.
So don't you worry about me.
But, Tama...
But before you go away,
there's something
I've wanted to say to you,
Hare, thanks for all your help.
♪
‐Bye, Hare!
‐Wait, Tama!
Sorry guys, but I
just can't leave her.
Tama!
♪
Come on, we should
be on our way now.
(crying softly)
Listen, Tama.
What's the matter,
you forget something?
Actually I was wondering
if you wouldn't mind
if I stayed a little longer?
♪
Are you sure?
(sobbing)
Hare!
(crying)
♪
We did the right
thing, didn't we?
Yeah.
(whimper)
Golem miss Hare.
Hey, stop getting all mushy!
Do your thing, Genki,
we need pumping up!
Sure thing, come on everybody,
it's time to move out!
(weak cheering)
(deep sighing)
♪
Hare, what do we need
from the store tomorrow?
Hm?
♪
Earth to space bunny.
I'm digging, I'm digging, see!
Look, I'm digging!
What's that supposed to be,
a well or something?
Huh?
Come on, you wanted to go
with your friends, right?
Not a chance, that's ridiculous!
Oh, that's right, I should be
out patrolling for strays, ha!
♪
Hey, what you doing, Hare?
I'm keeping my eyes out
for strays of course.
Come on down 'cause
dinner's ready!
♪
On my way!
Uh‐oh, I've never seen those
monsters around here before.
♪
Oh, they're Baddies!
And they're headed
the same way Genki went!
I don't know what's going on but
Baddies can only spell trouble!
(humming)
Should I go?
If I left right now I don't
think I'd ever have the heart
to show my face
around here again.
But I've got to warn
Genki and the others!
No, wait, the gang has some
strong allies with them,
so they should be pretty safe!
Oh, for crying out loud
how did I ever get myself
into this mess?
♪
Fireball!
(screaming)
(grunting)
(whimpering)
♪
Are you Baddies?
The worst kind, now be good
and turn that mystery disc
over to us!
(gasps)
We'll never give that disc
to the likes of you!
Ha, after them!
(shouting)
Come on, Mocchi!
'chi!
Double Mocchi Cannon!
Tongue Slap!
Tail Slap!
Ay!
‐Attack!
‐Yes!
(grunting)
♪
Now, go after Golem,
men, all at once,
he's the only one
who can fight!
♪
(explosions)
‐Golem!
‐Holly!
(whimpering)
Send out a second barrage!
I don't think so!
Blizzard!
(screaming in unison)
♪
Ha, Hare's advice
wasn't bad after all.
Just fake a Blizzard!
(groaning)
Trust Hare to come up with
something lame like that.
Come on, gang, let's charge 'em!
Holly, they'll come after
you if you're hanging
onto that mystery disc,
hand it over, and you run away.
Thanks, Suezo.
Pump up the volume, boys!
(shouting)
♪
Muah, muah, muah!
Tornado Attack!
♪
(whimpering)
Holly!
Dinner's ready!
♪
Yoo‐hoo!
(material flapping)
♪
If you value the life
of your friend here
then you'll hand over
the mystery disc!
No, don't give it to him!
Holly!
Don't even think about
trying that teleport gag!
Now, hand it over!
Holly.
Genki, don't do it!
(chuckling)
You Baddies are
always playing dirty!
♪
Dragon Punch!
(fire roaring)
(loud crashing)
Captain Brave Hare
here to save the day!
You came!
(ding)
Way to go, Hare!
Huh, what a ham, waiting
to make his big entrance!
I'll stay here and protect
Holly, you guys take care
of those badly dressed Baddies.
(grunting)
♪
Golem mad now.
That makes two of us!
You'll wish you never met me!
Come and fight us!
♪
I should warn you that
I have a special technique
that's utterly invincible.
Is it called running away?
Run for your lives!
(whimpering)
♪
You're right, he is pretty
good at running away.
‐Yo, Hare!
‐Hm?
♪
Tama!
Ha, you forgot something.
Boy, Hare, that was
mean leaving this behind
instead of saying goodbye.
♪
Tama, I'm sorry.
Here, you guys
are probably hungry.
Whoa, isn't that
your entire crop?
Not quite, consider
it Hare's payment.
I'm not sure I follow you.
I'm paying him now because
I decided that Hare's fired.
Hey, what'd you do that for?
Don't argue with me!
I want you to go
with your friends
and get rid of all
the Baddies in the world.
I promise.
(crash)
That's my little bunny boy!
(laughing)
Are you sure you can handle
the orchard on your own?
I'm not worried because
I've gotten a lot stronger
over this last year.
I'll protect my fruit
like never before!
I'm still worried about her.
You could always let us
protect her and the orchard.
Huh?
Right, we'll guard Tama's
orchard with our lives!
You all have a very important
mission to accomplish,
we wouldn't want
to get in the way.
Thank you, men.
We'd be honored to serve
someone as brave as you are.
We're a perfect match!
That makes me so
happy, you guys!
Let's do it!
Yes, ma'am!
♪
Take care, everybody!
You too, Tama, take
care of yourself!
‐Farewell.
‐Be safe!
‐Bye for now!
‐See you later, 'chi!
We promise to come back
and see you soon!
Alright, come on, gang,
it's time to move out!
Yeah!
(cheering)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪