♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Well, gang, we finally
made it to Papas.
Wind feel good.
Yeah, it's a nice breeze.
That's the great thing
about being in the hills.
The fresh air!
Doesn't it make you
feel glad to be alive?
Come on, let's register
for the M‐1 Grand Prix.
Chi!
So, you're saying
we need three fighters?
And on top of that,
the other two contenders
have to be from
the five species
designated by the Association?
That's correct.
♪
Suezo and Golem
are the right species.
‐Huh?
In this championship,
there's only one other team.
So if you win against them,
you'll advance one step closer
to the Legend Cup.
Golem will fight.
Well, you can count me out!
Well, in that case,
I'll take his place.
Afraid not, you're out.
Who's gonna stop me?
That's enough, Tiger.
Golem is proud
to fight for Holly.
Good, there you have it.
Golem and Mocchi
will fight three matches
between 'em and you
won't even need me.
Good luck there, boys.
Okay, the order we'll
be going in is Golem,
then Mocchi, then Suezo.
And I'll be coaching
them all, of course.
Fine.
Come on!
There's still time
to fit in some training.
Chi!
I wanna fight
in the championship!
Sign me in!
I insist or I won't budge.
I'll trade places any day.
Now, before we begin
our workout today,
I'd like to call on
your instructor, Tiger,
for a few words.
(growls)
This is Golem and
Suezo's first match.
Prepare yourselves
'cause I'm a tough trainer.
Go!
Let's start off with a little
jog to limber us up, everyone.
‐Yeah!
Sounds goods‐‐huh?
What happened to Suezo?
Huh?
He took off on us.
Who needs a bunch
of training when
you got six‐pack abs like I do.
Or would if I had a stomach.
Besides, I got better
things to do than wear
myself out before a big match.
No, don't!
Stop it!
Hand it over.
Here.
Hah, these cards
aren't that great.
You must be hiding something.
No, really,
that's all I have.
(licking)
♪
(laughing)
Yoink.
No, not that one!
Maybe that'll teach
you for lying.
Quit picking on
that little fella!
Come on, guys,
let's go.
♪
(Suezo groans)
Hey, you all right, kid?
Yeah, I guess.
You gotta stick up
for yourself,
otherwise they'll
keep coming after you.
If I fight back,
they'll be even more mean.
That's no excuse,
little fella!
Sometimes a guy's
gotta stick up
for what he believes in,
even if he doesn't win, kid.
Fighting hurts too much.
Hmm?
"Hurts too much"?!
Small price
for some dignity!
I got other reasons
not to fight.
I don't want to get dirty
or mess my nice fur.
Yeah, good point.
Well, I guess I'd
better get on my way.
You're just gonna leave me?
Hmm?
You monster!
How could you
just abandon me?!
Abandon you?
(cries)
You're being mean to me.
Meanie!
(cries)
♪
That's enough, kid.
Let's go someplace
we can talk, okay?
You really mean that?
This fella's such
a chicken and a phony.
He's just like me
when I was a little tike.
No luck, I couldn't find him.
Must be goofing
off somewhere.
I bet he took off
so he could get out
of practicing.
There's not much time
till the championship.
What if Suezo late?
I'm sure he'll make it back
in time before his match starts.
Trust him.
Suezo come back.
Hmm.
I see.
So, those Fly Eyed
bullies stole
your autographed picture of
the White Eyeball Poritoka?
Uh‐huh.
That picture meant
more to me than anything.
You know, I saw
Poritoka fight once
in the Legend Cup.
You did?!
You're so lucky!
Yeah, he's pretty cool,
but he hasn't got
my winning charm.
Poritoka's my number one hero!
His opponents can't
get past his defense,
and his offense
is so perfect!
Yay, yay, Poritoka!
Chomp 'em to pieces!
No one can beat you!
Whoa, you really
like this guy.
Just looking at
his picture makes
me feel like I can
stand up to any bully.
Hmm?
Then I'll go
get it back.
You will?
You're great, old man.
I'm not that old,
little guy.
How about you start
calling me Suezo?
I'm Furred Suezo.
Scaredy Cat Suezo's
more like it.
Who you calling scared?
(fireworks popping)
Look, fireworks!
Oh, yeah,
the championship!
Hurry and take me
to the tournament coliseum.
Sure, come on.
Welcome to the M‐1 Grand Prix.
The third championship
as our contenders
advance their way
to the Legend Cup finals.
It's starting and Suezo
still hasn't come back.
Probably busy taking
a nap somewhere.
Suezo...
First, let me present
the team of challengers.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Captain Black Dino,
one of Moo's best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Leads the Black Dinos
on every conquest ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Little Spot Dino,
harmless enough ♪
♪ To unlock a Kuro
you gotta be tough ♪
♪ Captain Kuro
will stomp and brawl ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock them all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Look how many
we're up against.
I heard that
the Fly Eye boss
is so tough he eats
Suezos for breakfast.
Oh, really?
Well, you could've
fooled me.
Why don't we
just forget it?
I can always get another
picture somewhere.
No chance!
That picture means
a lot to you!
You...
Yes?
You want something?
Oh, well, I...
heard you looked
like a movie star,
so I came to see.
See?
Didn't I tell you
it was true.
You got something
you wanna say to us?
(nervous laughter)
Bye, nice chatting to you.
(hums)
Huh, those cowards
make a perfect match.
(malicious laughing)
(Suezo growls)
What?
Got a problem?
No, no problem here.
You all have a nice day.
(malicious laughing)
♪
Hey, old guy,
try to cheer up.
I don't feel bad
about what happened.
Stop the "old guy" stuff.
I guess it's like
the saying goes:
Know your limits and
don't try to exceed them.
That's the adult way.
Huh?
I can't give up now
otherwise this kid
will always get
pushed around.
Wrong!
We ran away from
them just now
to trick 'em into
thinking they'd won.
Now, stay there while
I go get your picture back.
Don't go!
Stay there and don't follow me.
♪
Autographed, huh?
Yeah, so I'm sure we'll be able
to get a good price for it.
♪
Now, for a little
teleport show.
(whirring)
What a lousy time for a bout
of performance anxiety!
In that case...
♪
He's the guy who was
with the crybaby.
After him!
(grunting)
(timber crashes)
♪
The first match will
be Golem versus Cawken.
(caws)
♪
Go for it, Golem.
Go!
Ready, fight!
(bell tings)
♪
Oh, no!
Cawken is using his
windmill flap attack.
Go!
Tornado attack.
Golem counters
with his famous
tornado attack.
(audience cheers)
♪
Go!
‐Behind you!
‐Huh?
Oh!
Golem is out of the ring.
The match goes to Cawken.
Whoa!
Oh...
We really need Suezo
if we're gonna win
this championship.
I'm going out to see
if I can find him.
♪
Old man, you're back.
You got it!
Thanks!
I was sure you ran away
and weren't coming back.
Hah, you underestimate me.
I'm the brave and witty Suezo.
Brave you say?
♪
We'll have to fight
our way out of this.
Don't worry if we lose, kid.
Just fight hard
for your pride.
But I told you before,
I hate fighting.
So do I, but I also
hate getting beat up!
♪
Please, just let me go free.
Get him.
♪
Oh, no you don't.
Next contenders to the ring!
Mocchi!
Show 'em who's boss, Mocch.
Representing the
defending team is Gaboo!
Mocchi!
We're counting on you to win!
Good luck, Mocchi!
Fight.
(bell tings)
Chi, Chi!
Ga‐Gaboo!
Ow.
Got it...
after a fight.
♪
Come on, boys.
Let's go watch
the M‐1 Grand Prix.
(muttering)
♪
(Suezo chuckles)
See, doesn't it feel
good to stand up
for yourself?
Hardly.
You don't feel good
about standing your ground
and defending your rights?
Not a chance!
I'm sore and dirty,
and more than anything,
I feel humiliated!
I see.
♪
I promise I'll go back
and get that picture for you.
But now I gotta go.
Where to?
I've got a date at the M‐1
Grand Prix Championship.
♪
But you're too weak
for a match!
I told you, sometimes
a guy's gotta take a stand,
even though he knows
he doesn't have
a chance of winning.
(grunts)
See you around!
♪
Huh?
Found him!
Mocchi's hit!
Mocchi!
Now's the time to use
all your stored up energy.
Chi!
♪
Cherry blossom blizzard.
Knockout!
Mocchi wins the match.
All right, Mocchi, yeah!
Mocchi wins with
the cherry blossom blizzard.
Mocchi!
The next match
should be really good.
The score is now tied
at one a piece,
so the next match will
determine the new champions!
This just in,
some disturbing news.
Suezo hasn't arrived yet.
(crowd muttering)
Well, I'm afraid you'll just
have to forfeit the game.
Can't you wait
a little longer?
He'll show up.
Chi, please wait, Chi.
Go!
It's not that simple.
The rules are the rules.
You'll have to forfeit
the championship.
But please!
You looking for me?
Suezo!
♪
(Suezo grunts)
Have you been in a fight?
(chuckles)
Let's just say I was doing
my own brand of training.
No need to worry.
Think he can fight
in the shape he's in?
I'm pretty sure he'll
come through for us.
I agree.
Let's put our faith in him.
(struggling)
I recognize that guy.
(laughs)
A coward like that
doesn't stand a chance here.
(heavy breathing)
Old man.
Old man!
Hmm?
Watch closely, kid.
I'll show you what
being brave's all about.
(rumbling)
Zilla!
(chuckles)
(whimpers)
That's my opponent?
Fight!
Suezo!
Keep your distance
and wait for an opening.
Keep my distance?
Great idea.
Zilla!
(Suezo whimpers)
♪
Coming through,
coming through.
(laughing)
The chicken's not
even putting up a fight.
(Zilla growls)
♪
That's the way.
Keep dodging like that and
you'll wear him down real fast.
Tail attack!
♪
Tail attack,
tail attack, tail attack!
♪
Look out!
(Suezo grunts)
Oh, Suezo!
Zilla hit Suezo
with his tail slap.
(growls)
Suezo, teleport now.
Yeah, sure, if only
things were that easy.
(Zilla grunts)
Old man!
Throw in the towel
before you get yourself hurt!
Not a chance.
(Zilla growls)
♪
He should give up.
He doesn't need
to prove how brave he is.
♪
Ain't got me yet.
Suezo!
Please, old man.
♪
If you give up now,
no one here will
think you're a coward.
(Zilla grunts)
No, Zilla's gonna
finish him off
with a head butt.
(Suezo groans)
I think I've had it this time.
No!
Old man.
You can do it!
♪
Furred Suezo.
You remind me so much
of me when I was a kid.
♪
I'm back with a vengeance!
(Suezo yells)
♪
Yow!
You're through now.
(Zilla grunts)
Uh‐oh, it's Zilla's body press.
Don't give up,
don't give up.
No, I won't.
Teleport.
I'm going for the glory!
Tail attack!
(Zilla groans)
♪
(thunderous rumble)
Match to Suezo!
He did it!
Huh?
Yay, Suezo!
Suezo, he did it.
Yeah.
I knew that we
could count on him.
And now, Genki's team
will be presented
with the prize money
and the winner's card.
♪
Old man!
Hmm?
Furred Suezo.
I watched you in
the ring, old man.
You really are strong, huh?
You bet!
(laughs)
Hey, I told you not
to call me "old man."
You know how old I am?
♪
Really?
You look so much older!
Hmm.
Hang on there, Fly Eyes.
What?
Ah!
Don't you have something
you want to give back
to Furred Suezo?
Yeah, good of you
to remind me.
Move!
Uh, sure boss.
♪
I don't want
that anymore.
Huh?
I don't want
that picture,
'cause I got a new hero.
Furred Suezo.
♪
It's sure nice
and quiet today.
Yes.
It almost makes me
wonder why it's so quiet.
Huh?
(rumbling)
(metal creaking)
♪
Mum Mew, Gobi.
Yes, General.
Give me a progress
report on the plan.
What plan is that, sir?
The plan to steal
the mystery disk, you fur ball!
I forgot all about it!
Uh‐oh.
(laughing)
You fools!
Get on it at once!
Yes, General, right away.
That's far enough, kiddo.
Okay.
You know what?
What?
When I was your age,
I was getting bullied
all the time.
People used
to bully you?
Yep, but then
I made some friends
and life was
never the same.
I don't get it.
Friends like these change
everything for the better.
And I hope you'll
find some friends
as nice as mine are.
I'll try to, Suezo.
I know you will,
'cause you're no quitter.
You're gonna be
just fine, kid.
Thanks, Suezo.
Take care, you.
Goodbye!
(laughing)
See ya.
We'll meet again, right?
Yeah.
Count on it, little guy.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪