♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(humming)
I hear what you're saying,
so Moo's inside the‐‐
So, Holly's dad's
inside this disk?
Yeah, and we got to help him.
Which means trapping
the evil soul inside
and freeing Holly's dad.
That's why we need magic stone.
Hi‐ya, Mocchi fight
to get stone, 'Chi, ha!
Now it's all making sense.
Stew's on!
(laughing in unison)
Me‐me‐me!
Me first!
(gobbling)
♪
Your stew's as good
as I remember.
♪
I know somebody who could
use a good cooking lesson
or two from you, Holly.
You mean Golem
did all the cooking
when you two were on your own?
You bet, and that reminds me.
The last time we saw you guys,
we were flying through the air
at the end of the battle,
and when when we came to,
none of you were around.
It was just Golem and me.
Lucky you weren't turned
into mystery disks.
No kidding‐‐anyway, we decided
to head back to my hometown
and search for all
of you along the way.
Which brings me back
to Golem's cooking.
But Golem think
Golem very good cook.
Might have a better chance
if you left out the landfill.
Golem might not look
like much of cook,
but I think he'd be good.
Holly think so also?
Golem have dream.
One day, Golem want
to own restaurant.
I'd rethink that
one if I were you.
Nice dream, 'Chi!
Hey, yeah, let's start our own
restaurant when we get back.
Restaurant together?
Right, and we could
live in my hometown.
'Chi!
And live together, 'Chi!
Good idea.
What, we're all living together?
(growling)
I mean, super,
sounds like a riot.
♪
(collective snoring)
I wonder what Hare
and Tiger are doing.
I hope we meet up with them.
Yeah, I do, too, Holly.
♪
Now, on to Colart, gang.
(cheering)
Mocchi, we'll be training
for the Rookie Cup.
Training, on the way?
‐Yeah, let's get going, Moch!
‐'Chi!
You know, running's
a great workout.
Do the double pounder
when I signal, okay?
‐Mocchi.
‐Huh?
Hm, Mocchi want to use cherry
blossom blizzard soon, 'Chi!
Don't rush things, okay,
Moch, if you keep training,
you'll be using your Cherry
Blossom Blizzard in no time.
Right?
Pounder!
Come off it, the double
pounder is really important,
so put some snap into it.
‐See!
‐'Chi!
Double pounder!
Don't forget about
your distance!
‐Come on!
‐Pounder!
‐Double pounder!
‐That's the ticket.
‐Follow me!
‐'Chi!
Glad I'm not training.
Mocchi having good time.
Yeah, come on, gang,
better hurry if we're going
to make it to the tournament.
So this is Colart, Holly?
Yes.
Finally here.
It only took a week to
get here, I need a massage.
Thank goodness we made it
here in time for the tournament.
Mocchi still can't use
Cherry Blossom Blizzard.
Cheer up, Mocchi, come on let's
go register for the tournament.
♪
(sinister muttering)
We finally found them.
♪
Let's see, Mocchi's a
contender and Genki's a breeder.
‐Yes, sir!
‐'Chi,'Chi!
Will you be coaching
him during the fight?
Yeah, we stick together
during fights, don't we?
'Chi, 'Chi!
Will be coaching
during the fight.
Excuse me, what shall I do
with the mystery disk prize?
(together)
Huh?
Could you take it over
to the coliseum for me
along with the other
contest prizes?
‐Sure.
‐Okay.
You mean the prize this time is
a mystery disk instead of money?
Yes, in group battles such as
the Mandy Cup here, it could be.
‐Group battles?
‐That's right,
it could be two against two
or even five against five
as long as the they're even.
'Chi!
If one person is registered,
the whole group can enter!
Golem want to enter.
You can count me out.
Suezo help fight, 'Chi!
I'll be on my way.
♪
(grunt)
Holly.
Hey, I know that voice.
It's Tiger!
Tiger, is that you?
Thanks for catching that.
Here.
♪
You heard Tiger's voice?
Yeah, coming from
that mystery disk.
'Chi, Tiger must be
inside that disk, 'Chi.
We must get disk.
'Cept it belongs to the IMA now.
They wouldn't just
give it to us.
Then I guess our only choice
is for you to win
the Rookie Cup, Moch!
Mocchi try, 'Chi!
Yeah, that's what
I want to hear!
Should we go after them now?
No.
This Tiger is so strong he's
even defeated Gray Wolf before,
he'd be a perfect ally,
don't you think?
That's brilliant.
But first I need to do
a little multitasking.
I'll enter the tournament, beat
Mocchi and get the mystery disk.
You're a miracle worker.
Find out who else
is in the tournament!
What?
Here comes someone now.
♪
(humming)
Huh?
(grunting)
(laughing)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Fairy Hare a heart of gold ♪
♪ Wild Hare bandit,
he's brave and bold ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Reunion of hares,
partners all three ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Trader among them,
which one will it be ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Michelle is six,
sweet and demure ♪
♪ Golem believes her,
can you be so sure ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Welcome to what promises
to be another exciting day
here at Colart Coliseum.
Today IMA's newly registered
members will battle each other
in hopes of winning
the Rookie Cup,
the first of six championships.
The contenders must win
all six championships
to qualify for the Legend Cup!
That's sure rough.
And now for the first battle,
introducing Purple Seuzo!
(cheering)
Ah, he'll be a pushover.
You know him?
Never seen him.
Our next contender
is adorable in pink!
But don't let his cute
appearance fool you,
ladies and gentlemen, Mocchi!
Mocchi!
Give it everything you've got!
(cheering)
This is so exciting,
just like Monster Goshujin.
Wait a sec, this is just
like the computer game,
and I've got a
championship under my belt.
(grunting)
Come on, Purple Suezo,
you can do it!
(whimpering)
Keep loose, Mocchi, limber up
your arms and legs for me.
Aye, he's stiffer than
a frozen flounder!
Ready, go!
(bell chimes)
(cheering)
Mocchi, move those feet!
(cracking sound)
No use, Mocchi
can't even hear me.
Get 'em with your tongue slap!
Whoa, Purple Suezo used
his first tongue slap!
Come on, Mocchi,
concentrate on my voice.
Genki?
Go for the tail attack!
‐Look out!
‐'Chi!
Way to go, Mocchi!
Now move in and get him
with your double pounder!
Right, 'Chi, double pounder!
Great, now try and
get those feet moving
with your double pounder!
(grunting)
♪
Double pounder, double pounder.
Hit him with your wet shot!
(grunting)
‐Mocchi!
‐Oh, no!
That's one nasty tongue,
he's mastered the wet shot.
Poor Mocchi.
(grunting)
♪
Keep it clean!
All right, my friend,
double whammy time!
Mocchi, get out of the way!
(slurping)
(groaning)
Can't look!
‐Oh, Mocchi!
‐Don't give up yet!
Purple Suezo, finish him
off with your tail attack!
Mocchi!
(grunting)
♪
Mocchi, get him, you got
to try and concentrate.
♪
That's it, now use
your Mocchi cannon.
(grunting)
(loud thud)
♪
That's the fight, Mocchi wins
the match by a knockout!
(cheering)
Yessiree, Bob, Mocchi's
cannon has cost Purple Suezo
the match, ladies and gentleman!
(cheering)
Now our next match
is Mocchi versus Weed!
(chuckling)
(cheering)
♪
Ready, go!
All right, Mocchi,
go get him.
Come on, Weed, use
your seed machine gun!
(rapid gunfire)
Mocchi, tumble your
way out of there.
♪
Now, Weed, the honey attack!
Gotcha ya!
The Weed can only attack
you from a distance.
Move in and give him
your double pounder.
Double pounder!
Come on, your thorns!
Thorns, anyone?
Get 'em!
(loud thud)
That's the fight, another
KO win match for Mocchi!
(cheering)
(all together)
Hooray!
♪
That's good, 'Chi!
You're getting stronger
every time you fight!
Way to go!
(chuckling)
I've got some nice
peaches to celebrate!
Thanks, Holly, 'Chi!
(chewing noises)
Golem make you
boulder rice cakes.
Thank you, Golem, but now
Mocchi full, 'Chi, honestly!
Hmm.
So Mocchi not think
Golem's cooking any good.
'Chi!
No, you're a good cook.
Then have some.
Actually, I'm pretty
stuffed myself.
Then it's true, Golem bad cook.
Golem.
We've got trouble!
Whatcha talking about?
I just went to check out
Mocchi's next opponent
and you're not going to believe
how strong that monster is.
(grunting)
He blew away Purple Suezo
and Weed like they were
harmless dust bunnies
or something.
He's in a league
all by himself.
Hm.
Mocchi not lose, 'Chi!
That's it, if you try your
best, you're bound to win!
Right on, 'Chi!
♪
On to the last match of the
day between the two contenders
who've won all their matches!
The champion of
the Mocchi cannon
and double pounder, Mocchi!
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi!
And the rookie who's mastered
some advanced techniques
if his short career
as a fighter, Muddy Jell.
(cheering)
And the winner of this match
will win the Rookie Cup!
Ready, go!
(bell chimes)
Come and get me!
Huh?
♪
'Chi, double pounder!
What's the problem, thought
I said, "Come and get me!"
Don't let him psyche
you out, Mocchi!
Keep an eye on his movements.
Mocchi!
Double pounder, double pounder!
‐(grunt)
‐Mocchi!
Muddy Jell's jelly whip
has overwhelmed Mocchi!
And now I'm going
to take what's mine!
Mocchi, he's coming in!
Huh?
Jell press!
Mocchi cannon!
(grunt)
(thud)
'Chi?
Well, it looks like Muddy Jell's
awesome skills have left Mocchi
at a complete loss!
(whipping sounds)
(grunting)
'Chi?
♪
Mocch, don't give up!
I know you can do better!
♪
It's Tiger!
Mocchi, if your skills
won't work against him,
then your only choice
is to win with courage!
Courage!
That's right!
The one and only thing that we
have more than everyone else!
Yeah!
♪
Mocchi energized!
Double pounder, double pounder!
♪
'Chi?
Yikes, look!
That look like Baddie crest!
How did a Baddie get
into the competition?
Stop the fight, that Muddy
Jell up there is a fake!
A fake‐‐referee, call the match!
Oh, right away!
(loud grunt)
No, I've been discovered.
(cracking sound)
Look, his skin is falling off!
♪
Now I've really got
nothing to lose!
If I'm going down,
you're coming with me!
♪
Mocchi, do it!
Mocchi cannon!
(whistling sound)
(loud crash)
(groaning)
♪
These guys are baddies too!
Then we should pay them
back for all the trouble
they've caused us in the past!
(laughing weakly)
Oh, what's that coming this way?
♪
Tricked ya!
‐Yeah, Mocchi, you won the cup!
‐'Chi!
(laughing)
Actually, we need
to talk about that.
I'm afraid we can't recognize
Mocchi's victory, seeing as
the actual contender wasn't
a registered a member.
‐Wait a second.
‐Huh?
It wasn't what you'd
call a formal match,
but I really did lose to Pink
Jam, so if Mocchi won his match
to Pink Jam, then Mocchi
deserves to be the champion.
Thank you.
Thank you, 'Chi!
Right, I have to agree!
The official winner of
the Rookie Cup is Mocchi!
(cheering)
♪
Mocchi, all my
instruction worked.
The championship goes to Mocchi!
Right now the IMA
official will present him
with the winner's card!
(laughing)
(cheering)
In addition, let me present
you with this mystery disk.
The identity of
the monster locked inside
remains to be seen.
(chuckling)
♪
(buttons beeping)
(digital beeping)
♪
Unlock!
(howling)
(cheering)
♪
I told you before,
don't pull the tail!
You know how much I hate that
mushy kissing and hugging stuff!
(laughing)
(loud roar)
You pests, how many times
do I have to tell you
not to touch the fur?
Hm?
Holly?
Tiger!
♪
Tiger.
(giggling)
So he doesn't mind if
it's Holly touching him.
‐Holly, 'Chi!
‐What's the deal?
(growling)
(laughing)
♪
Gumbie, what's the
word on Pink Jam?
Who‐‐who me, oh, I, um, I‐‐
Come on, out with it!
My head hurts!
Oh, never mind!
Actually, Master Durahan,
they left this note behind
then hightailed
it out of here.
Oh well, we couldn't
possibly have any use
for cowards like those.
(laughing)
‐Read it!
‐But, Master, this letter‐‐
He said read it, Mew!
(growling)
"It's plainly obvious
that General Durahan
will be angry at us when
we return, so goodbye.
P. S., please don't
come searching for us.
Your eternally faithful
servant, Pink Jam."
I'm going to miss them all.
‐Put a cork in it!
‐Silence!
You must find them, we're going
to need that mystery disk!
(in unison)
Yes, sir!
I still don't get it.
Don't you think it
would have been easier
to steal Tiger's mystery disk
instead of enter the tournament?
Then why didn't you
suggest that before?
Now, now, what's done is done.
I'm more concerned about these
crests, are you sure they're
okay just painted over?
No one will even notice!
They'll think it's a
fancy badge or something.
(groans)
I knew I shouldn't
have quit my day job.
Come on, boys, let's
continue our quest!
(all together)
Yes, sir.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪