♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(crow cawing)
♪
R‐report?
W‐well, a‐actually, I...
I'm waiting for you here.
Oh, oh, I...
Ugh, positively irritating!
Oh, my aching head!
I'll report on his behalf.
Captain Zebra Saurian ran away
with his tail between his legs.
What?!
Oh, Master Durahan.
Please, don't let
yourself get over‐excited.
Hey, don't you have any
real soldiers in there?
This will impress you.
♪
Hear my voice and awaken,
fierce and cruel one.
Drill Tusk!
(electricity zapping)
♪
Ooh, wow.
These fellas look dangerous.
♪
Drill!
Tusks!
Go forth, my minions,
and return with
that Mystery Disk.
(laughing)
♪
(laughing wildly)
Yo there, Genki,
you're just in time.
Check out what the boys caught.
Nobody's laughing.
Hmph.
Go.
It's hard to believe those fish
didn't fall through the nets!
(laughing)
So, how did you guys make out?
(chuckling nervously)
(laughing)
You didn't do any better, huh?
Why don't you show
us what you got?
Ta‐da!
How's that?
This'll last us for a while.
You can always count on me
to bring home the bacon.
Go ahead, help your‐‐
(smack)
‐You got two, not two hundred!
Go!
(chuckling)
Hang on a minute, shouldn't
Mocchi be back by now?
Yeah, you're right.
♪
Can't find anything, Chi.
(exclaiming)
Jumbo potatoes, Chi!
(panting)
It won't budge.
Here it goes.
(grunting)
Got it!
Huh?
(gurgling scream)
(groaning)
♪
(laughing)
Uh, did you want
these potatoes?
Sure, thank you, Chi!
You want me to pick more?
Yes, please, Chi.
Come to Papa.
You're so strong, Chi.
Mocchi try, too.
Come to Mocchi!
(grunting)
Ah, what's going on?
Is this a big one?
(screaming)
Are you all right, you guys?
My glasses.
I can't see.
(groaning)
♪
(clearing throat)
(grumbling)
♪
(sighing)
Genki, Mocchi here!
(groaning)
Mocchi bring us back
jumbo potatoes, Chi!
(exclaiming wildly)
♪
(munching)
(slurping)
Potatoes are delicious, Chi.
Glad to hear you like 'em,
'cause I grew 'em myself.
Oh yeah!
I can down another dish of that.
Just out of curiosity,
where are you
young folks heading?
(chuckling)
The Mandy Championship.
You're going there, too, huh?
You mean that's
where you're headed?
Hmm, my brother's gonna
win the championship
and become the world's
strongest monster.
Not if we can do
anything about it.
(laughing)
You really have a lot to learn.
No one will ever defeat
the Wondar Brothers.
My Herculean brother here
can pull out a whopping
200 potatoes in
one fell swoop.
Mocchi believes it's true, Chi.
(grumbling)
Huh, something wrong, Chi?
Uh, nothin', little fella.
Chi?
You two might be strong,
but you can't beat our courage.
Not to mention this
steel trap brain of mine.
Strength alone is not
gonna win you any battles.
Got you beat there,
too, I'm afraid.
(clearing throat)
You see, I was the
official village advisor,
and I was the genius who dreamt
up the rotating watering can.
Rotating watering can?
What's that, you
never heard of it?!
You don't get into
town much, do ya?
It's an ingenious
farming invention.
♪
(laughing)
If an archaic invention
like that has you bragging,
then I can't wait to see
what kind of battle plan
you come up with.
You're askin' for it.
Maybe we should have
a pre‐championship match.
Never hurts to practice.
Chi, Chi!
Have a match now?
I'm not so sure.
Quit worryin' and
show 'em your strength!
Now keep your distance and
wait for an opening, Mocchi.
Chi.
Look how fired up that runt is.
Don't go easy on him
just 'cause he's small.
But, brother, I don't
feel good about this.
Quit blabbin' and start jabbin'!
(shouting)
Ah, jump out of the way, Mocchi.
(screaming)
♪
(rumbling)
Whoa, he makes King Kong
look like a baby chimp!
Get back here!
Huh?
(grumbling)
♪
Chi!
He split that boulder.
Always keep your eye
on the opponent.
Hmm?
♪
(grunting)
That's the ticket.
Keep it up, Mocchi.
♪
Double Pounder!
Double Pounder, Double Pounder,
Double Pounder, Double Pounder!
Don't just stand
there, go after him!
♪
Huh?
Where'd he get to?
Up here!
Huh?
(groaning)
(screaming)
♪
(gasping)
Mocchi!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Tama the farmer,
Hare's her friend ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ They saved her
orchard in the end ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Daton and Datonare
from Tiger Team ♪
♪ Guarding mangoes is a dream ♪
♪ Tama's one gal
who's on the ball ♪
♪ She loves these monsters,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(groaning)
Chi!
(kissing)
You saved Mocchi!
Oh, he's all right.
What'd he go and save
his opponent for?
It was the perfect chance
to show that group
just how strong he really is.
♪
‐Double Pounder!
Try harder, Chi.
Er, okay, Mocchi.
Double Pounder, Double Pounder,
Double Pounder, Double Pounder.
That's better, Chi!
Those two have
sure become close.
They're good for each other.
You need rivals
to become stronger.
A little moral support
wouldn't hurt him either.
Mocchi is becoming
much stronger.
I just may have
underestimated these guys.
Got something you want to share
with us there, Mr. Wondar?
What, were you listening to me?
Remember, strategy
is inspiration,
not something you can
plan in advance, pal.
I don't need no
advice from a rabbit!
The Mandy Cup will be ours,
just you wait and see!
My brother was goin'
easy on ya back there.
Huh, why he angry, Chi?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Not true, Chi.
Uh...
Mocchi, I don't want to
go in the championship.
Well, then you no go, Chi.
I'm much happier on the farm
growing my vegetables.
Must do what make
you happy, Chi.
I know, but I don't know
how to tell my brother.
Tell him the truth, Chi.
I can't, I‐I mustn't
oppose my brother.
♪
(screaming)
Oh, no!
(groaning)
I got her.
Oh, thank goodness
you saved her.
(gasping)
The Mystery Disk!
After it!
♪
(screeching)
Got it, Chi!
What on Earth are
you people thinking?
You all risked your lives just
for a worthless Mystery Disk.
That worthless disk
means everything to us.
Huh, are you serious?
(laughing)
Huh.
That gives me an idea.
(laughing menacingly)
Are you sure you have to leave?
Yes, I‐I have to
take care of something
before we get
to the tournament.
That's too bad,
but we understand.
See you later, Chi.
You've got my promise.
Come on then, let's get going.
See you at the
Mandy Championship!
We'll see you there, Chi.
Don't talk to
strangers along the way!
Now, how about we
have a little grub?
Ah.
‐Looks delicious!
It was nice of the
elder Wondar Brother
to make us stew
before he left.
He's not such a bad guy.
(slurping)
And a pretty good cook,
if I say so myself.
You know, I'm starting to think
I had him pegged all wrong.
(gulping)
A gastronomic delight.
(slurping)
Potato stew yummy, Chi.
(munching)
♪
Ahh!
That is good.
(yawning)
I'm so stuffed I can
hardly keep my eyes open.
(groaning)
Go.
I'm feeling sleepy
myself all of a sudden.
Yeah, so am I.
Ah, Mocchi sleep.
It's not healthy
for you to fall asleep
right after you've eaten dinner.
Yeah, whatever.
Come on, Suezo.
Now I'm starting
to get sleepy, too.
♪
This magic sleeping herb
should do the trick.
Don't hold this against me.
(laughing)
♪
Oh, back already?
Where did you get to?
Isn't that their Mystery Disk?
Never mind, come on,
let's just go.
But that's not right.
(digging)
That's deep enough.
Now let's bury it.
♪
I really don't feel good
about this, big brother.
Are you questioning
my judgment here?
If we hide this disk,
they'll be so busy
looking for it,
they won't make
the championship.
And if they're
out of the way,
nothing will stop
us from winning.
Yes, but, brother...
There's nothing to worry about.
They'll never think we were
the ones who stole it from them.
I know, but...
Stop talkin' back to me!
You got a great future
ahead of you, boy.
Yes, brother.
♪
(all snoring)
(rumbling)
Huh?
Huh, what was that?
Something's coming!
(screaming)
They're Baddies!
♪
We're the Subterranean
Earthquake Brigade.
Drill Tusks!
And now you'll quietly
hand over that Mystery Disk
if you value your lives.
If you want it,
then come and get it.
Go!
‐Yeah!
‐Hmph!
It's gone!
The Mystery Disk is gone!
(screaming)
‐Gone?
‐Huh?
Where is it?
(all speaking)
(laughing)
Think we're going to
fall for that old trick?
Hand it over!
Oh, we better find it.
We must find it,
it's here somewhere.
Captain, I think they
really have lost it.
Find that Mystery Disk!
Find it now!
(shouting)
♪
Where could it have gone?
What's this?
Hmm.
I think I've got it.
‐Huh?
The Wondar Brothers
stole our Mystery Disk.
What?
But hold on, they
left us last night.
I've got the
evidence right here.
That stew they made was laced
with magic sleeping herbs.
The Wondar Brothers
no do that to friends!
Wait a minute, we did get
awfully sleepy all of a sudden.
That older brother always
did give me the creeps.
But why do they
want us sleeping?
I think I know why.
They knew we'd search for
the disk if it went missing,
then we wouldn't make it
to the championship.
(laughing)
Then we have no more
use for you people.
We'll beat you to
the Wondar Brothers
and steal the Mystery Disk.
‐Drill!
‐Tusks!
♪
(rumbling)
You fool!
Now those giant mealworms
are gonna get our Mystery Disk!
Let's go after 'em.
Right!
♪
(rumbling)
What on Earth's going on?
The mountain gods must be
punishing us for what we did.
Don't be ridiculous.
We already apologized
for our wrongdoings.
I know, but...
(screaming)
The Wondar Brothers, I presume.
Who are you and
what's it to ya?
Look, brother.
Huh, that symbol.
Grandpa warned me about them.
They're Baddies,
and they're the ones
who's always
stealing our potatoes.
(whimpering)
Look in the basket, now!
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
(growling)
Come on, now's our chance.
Oh, right.
Nothing but vegetables
here, Captain.
There's no disk?
Go!
Yes, sir!
(screaming)
♪
Where's that Mystery Disk?
Mystery Disk?
You're askin' the wrong guys.
We don't know what
you're talkin' about.
You shouldn't take us for fools.
Now!
Double Pounder!
(grunting)
Are you okay, Chi?
Mocchi!
Drill!
Double Pounder!
Stay on 'em.
Get that disk or
you'll face dehornment!
(groaning)
Tongue Slap!
(rumbling)
Let's get out of
here while we can.
But these are our friends,
and they're fighting for us.
Let 'em fight if that's
what they want to do.
But if you get hurt
in this scrap,
you'll never become the
world's strongest monster.
No, brother, wait.
Underground!
♪
What do you think
those guys are doin' now?
Huh?
♪
(gasping)
Mocchi!
Don't do it!
Here comes my Potato Pie!
Chi!
Are you okay, Mocchi?
You saved Mocchi again, Chi!
Oh, isn't that
what friends are for?
Are you ready, boys?
'Cause we got work to do.
(cheering)
(grunting)
Mocchi Cannon!
Potato Pie!
I told you not to
fight with them!
Come on, let's go!
(trembling)
♪
Take that!
Yah!
Tornado Attack!
Retreat!
♪
(cheering)
(chuckling)
That'll teach you for messing
with the Wondar Brothers.
Get lost and don't come back.
♪
I'm sorry, my friends.
Don't feel bad about it.
Ha, we're still
gonna be the ones
to win that Mandy Championship.
Did you see the
Potato Pie punch of his?
That just leaves
your fighting strategy
to work out, doesn't it?
Details, details.
We've got it in the bag.
Time to move out, brother.
♪
Come on, no time to dawdle.
(groaning)
What's the hold‐up now?
Uh, actually...
Don't make me lose my temper.
(grumbling)
Huh?
Chi, Chi.
Hmm.
(clearing throat)
Brother!
Uh, what's gotten into you?
I won't be going to Mandy.
I'm going back to our village
to grow my vegetables.
He did it, he did it!
Don't be so ridiculous, brother.
We're winning the Mandy Cup
and becoming the world's
strongest monsters.
Now quit wasting
my time, come along.
Stop there and hear me out!
I like growing
my vegetables
more than anything
else in the world.
There's nothing I like better
than watching people enjoy
the fruits of my labor.
Farming means so much more
to me than fighting ever will.
Can't you try to understand?
♪
My dream is to grow the
most delicious vegetables
in the world.
♪
Look, brother!
The shoots are up!
(wind howling)
♪
(sparkling)
Look, they're ready to eat!
♪
Well, why on Earth
didn't you tell me sooner?
I tried, but...
I didn't want to disappoint you.
(sobbing)
I'm sorry I've been
pushing you so hard.
Can you forgive me?
I'm to blame as well.
I should've told you sooner.
Oh, my dear brother.
♪
Chi.
Bye‐bye, new friends!
‐Goodbye!
He looks so happy now.
He should, now that he'll
be able to do what he wants
and farm his land.
Don't forget to send us some
of those delicious potatoes!
I guess we'd better
think about going, too.
Yeah!
Come on, gang.
The Mandy Championship
is waiting for us.
(cheering)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪