♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Mum Mew!
Gobi, Mum Mew!
Gobi!
Now, where have those
bungling fools gotten to?
(gasping)
Oh, figures she'd come up
with something like this.
♪
"My dear General Durahan,
It is with great remorse
and, indeed, shame
that I must apologize to you
for our disappointing failure
in securing the mystery disk."
Hmm, sounds like
a form letter.
Enough, now read.
"In an attempt to spare
your precious collection,
Gobi and I have gone
after Genki and the others
to get the mystery
disk ourselves.
Yours very,
very, very truly."
Ah, what diligent subjects,
taking on the task themselves.
Good luck, my servants.
I'll await your return.
(laughing)
♪
Fighters and their
breeders don't have to pay
to get into the
training park,
as long as they're
registered with the IMA.
Free, huh, I don't know.
Places that are free
usually aren't even
worth setting foot in.
That's true, but this is a
full‐scale training area
designed for fighters like us,
so it'll definitely be worth
taking a look around,
don't you think?
Full‐scale training area?
Ooh, can I take your order?
Guess it won't hurt
to stop in for a while.
Mocchi want to try
many food here, chi.
This'll be a perfect
chance for us to rest up.
We're all really tired.
Well, I guess some of us
could use the rest
more than others.
Yeah, kids are always the
first to run out of steam.
Right, little guy?
‐What's that?
‐You heard me!
Fighting no good.
Let's get going, gang.
Chi!
Perfect.
They'll never expect
an ambush here.
‐No mistakes now.
‐Right.
Courage and timing,
that's what it takes
to make a good thief.
‐Right.
‐Let's move.
Right.
Attention, Colart
Agricultural Club,
if you'll all just
follow me this way!
(shouting)
Gobi scared!
♪
Oh, I see, so each
type of monster
goes to a separate building.
Yeah.
Looks like I'm over there.
And this is where
I'm supposed to go.
Mocchi there.
Well, then, we all
go different areas.
Fine with me, we could
use some time apart
every once in a while.
Yeah, it'll be kind of nice
to have a little bit
of time to ourselves.
Ok, gang, we'll meet
back here in 24 hours.
Until then, we're on our own.
Okay, Genki.
(grunting)
♪
Dragon Punch!
Ah, sand shower feel good.
(zapping)
(shouting)
Lightning attack!
♪
(laughing)
This food sure
look good, chi!
The Great White Most,
I'm his top student,
don't you know?
You are Most's top student?
Seriously?
Wow, does that mean
he's taught you
all of the special
fighting moves?
Yes, but believe me, when
Most says strenuous training,
you know he's serious.
Oh, yeah, I bet.
(humming)
Wait, chi!
Hmm?
(heavy breathing)
Need favor, chi!
Please introduce
me to Most, chi!
Most is a celebrity and
I'm pretty busy myself,
but if you're desperate,
I may be persuaded
to introduce you for a
small fee of 10,000 golds.
10,000 golds?
Chi, Mocchi no
have that much.
Then stop wasting my time.
Oh.
♪
Hmm.
Hmm?
What's the matter?
You seem down.
Who, me?
Nah, just thinking
about the others.
I wonder if Mocchi is lonely.
Don't worry, everyone's
probably having a great time.
Yeah.
Anyway, it's not like
we'll be apart for long.
Yeah, you're right,
it's not for long.
Now you better start
eating that before it melts.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Here come come
the Arrowheads
fighting with claws ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Not like Eared Mew
who only has paws ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Tainted Cat Brothers
are quick and they're bad ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ They're whirlwind‐fast,
so don't get 'em mad ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ So many monsters,
so little time ♪
♪ Check 'em all out,
they're still in their prime ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(sighing)
(snoring)
Chi.
♪
Mm.
Mocchi miss Genki and friends.
(engine whirring)
♪
(gasping)
Oh, Mocchi tired.
(thudding)
♪
That was a piece of cake.
These Mocchi monsters
fetch a good price.
We made quite a haul, fellas.
Let's get out of here.
♪
(whirring)
(whooshing)
♪
We're hitting turbulence.
It's gonna be a rough
ride so hang on!
That hurt, chi.
Wake up, chi.
Wake up!
Huh?
You, what do you
think you're doing?
(gasping)
♪
(grunting)
(screaming)
♪
Everybody all right, chi?
You're gonna pay for
this, troublemaker.
(shouting)
(grunting)
Who are you?
After him, fellas!
We'll deal with
the others later.
(shouting)
♪
Aurora Attack!
(shouting)
♪
(whimpering)
Come back, chi!
Let's get out of here!
This time you're lucky.
♪
(gasping)
Most, chi.
(panting)
Wait up, chi.
Don't come, it's
too dangerous.
Please lend Mocchi
magic stone, chi.
What's that?
Mocchi seen it.
Stone in championship.
You mean the magic stone
on the winner's plate.
Chi.
I'm afraid I don't have it.
Chi?
Poritoka has the winner's
plate you're looking for.
Then where's Poritoka?
I don't know.
I only see him during the
monster battle championships.
Wait!
(sighing)
Genki, wake up.
What's the emergency?
It's Mocchi, I think
he's gone missing.
Ah!
Kidnappers?
Mmhmm, it looks like they only
went after Mocchi monsters.
Hey, look, it's Genki.
The Mocchi monsters
made it back.
Over there, at entrance.
♪
Mocchi!
Where are you?
Can you hear us?
I don't think Mocchi's here.
Excuse me, your friend
chased after them, I think.
Chased after who?
Uh, the kidnappers.
Huh, he did what?
♪
Chi.
(grunting)
Ah!
♪
(panting)
Thanks for saving me.
I warned you it
was too dangerous.
This easy compared
to fighting Moo.
♪
You fought Moo.
That surprises me.
Chi, Mocchi beat
Moo with friends,
Genki, Suezo, Golem,
Tiger, Hare, and Holly too.
I did not know.
What wrong?
Why are you following me?
I told you Poritoka has the
plate you're looking for.
Mocchi want to be strong.
Mocchi want to be
strong like Most
and win Legend Cup, chi!
And all that so you
can get the magic stone
from the winner's plate.
Mm, we bring him back
with magic stone, chi.
Bring who back?
Holly's father trapped
inside mystery disk.
Now I understand you.
I've heard that magic stones
have mysterious powers
imbued in them that allow
them to control all life.
♪
I am gonna find
those kidnappers
and release the rest
of the hostages.
You can come with me
if you want, Mocchi.
Ah.
♪
‐Mocchi!
‐Where are you?
Are you out there?
Mocchi, where are you?
Unless it's was mistaken,
it was right around here
that the other monsters
got separated from Mocchi.
‐Over here.
‐Hmm?
‐Come on.
‐Right behind ya.
(whooshing)
♪
(grunting)
(screaming)
(panting)
♪
Chi, can't hold on, chi.
Don't give up now.
Remember your mission, your
dreams, and determination.
Hmm!
(grunting)
♪
(heavy breathing)
Good work, Mocchi.
Thank you, Most.
You helped me, chi.
You helped yourself, Mocchi.
No need to thank me.
Huh?
♪
I didn't fight Moo.
I had no interest
in him whatsoever.
My sole purpose
was to strengthen
and enlighten myself.
♪
One day, I heard about
a group of monsters
who were risking their
lives to fight Moo.
I never heard of
anything like it.
It was a turning
point in my life.
So that's when I
came to a decision
to work for others.
I enter battles to
demonstrate how to use
one's own power and to
save those in trouble.
♪
In order to become strong
then, first, you must
become one with nature.
Hmm?
You must become one
with the earth, the sky,
the wind, the sun.
Discard your outer shell.
But Mocchi no
understand, chi.
Of course not, but the day
will come when you will.
♪
Ah!
We made it, chi.
Let's move.
What?
You lost them?
Boss, I'm so sorry.
It wasn't our fault.
That one monster
was so strong!
Enough excuses.
Just who is this monster
and why is he so strong?
Care for a closer look?
Hey, that's him over there!
Huh?
(grunting)
Now, how about letting
out those hostages?
Open door right now, chi.
I don't think so.
(whimpering and laughing)
♪
Wouldn't want her
to get hurt now.
No, don't.
Get 'em!
(shouting)
♪
You're fast, just as I
expected, but speed alone
won't save your friends
this time, I'm afraid.
Hmm!
Never confront the enemy
with anger and hate.
Always stay calm.
Remember what you're
standing up for.
Never forget
those two things.
Huh?
(whimpering)
Discard your outer shell
and become one with nature.
Become?
Become one.
(grunting)
♪
Ah!
Aurora Attack!
♪
(shouting)
Run for it, men!
(whooshing)
They gone!
(cheering)
♪
Most, where's Most, chi?
‐Mocchi!
‐Huh?
Mocchi!
Genki, you find me, chi!
♪
Most?
You don't mean the
legendary Great White Most?
Chi, Mocchi met him, chi.
Well, isn't that nice?
Mocchi, it's not
nice to tell tales.
This no tale!
Most teach Aurora Attack!
(gasping)
Aurora Attack?
Golem would pay
to see that, ha!
Mm.
Watch, chi.
♪
Ooh.
Aurora Attack!
♪
(groaning)
Come on, what was that?
That no fierce technique.
Chi, why no work?
Mocchi, you
shouldn't tell fibs.
Next thing you know, the
police will be after ya.
Mocchi never tell fib!
No way!
Okay, we hear ya, little
fella, but meeting Most,
well, that's just a
little hard to swallow.
Well, I believe him.
I know you were
with him, Mocchi.
Mocchi and Most teamed up,
and then together they
defeated those kidnappers.
That's how all the monsters
were freed, right, Mocchi?
We're proud, Mocchi.
‐Go.
‐Hmm.
Chi.
♪
Hmm.
Poison, where is
my mystery disk?
Oh, what's take Mum Mew
and Gobi so long?
Well, you know what those
two are like, incompetent.
(yawning)
♪
Nothing like a little
sun to perk a monster up.
Yeah.
Still, I kind of
get the feeling
we're forgetting
something important.
Hmm?
♪
Well, next stop, the
Greatest Four Championship.
So let's move out
and do our best, gang.
Yeah!
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪