♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Mum Mew, what's taking
you with that mystery disk?
You don't have
to yell in my ear.
Obviously I do, otherwise
we'd have the disk by now!
‐Ladies, ladies!
‐Put a lid on it!
You're the most incompetent
monster I've ever seen!
Well, guess who I am?
(whimpering)
Look, the big guy's lost
his tongue yet again.
(crying)
♪ Gobi's crying ♪
♪ He's crying ♪
♪ Poison made him cry ♪
Stop this nonsense!
♪
General Durahan!
General!
So, which warrior
in your collection
will you be dispatching?
‐I won't need one this time.
‐Hmm?
My faithful servant
Weed has already left
to enlist the aid
of a strong ally.
He'll get my
mystery disk for me,
I'm sure of it.
(laughing)
We finally made it!
We're back in Colart!
This makes it our
second time here.
Before was Rookie Cup, 'chi!
Let's go register.
Yeah, come on.
♪
‐You're in luck, Tiger!
‐Yeah.
You're one of the
five types of monsters
that can enter the championship
today with Mocchi!
At last I'll have a
chance to prove myself.
Hang on, I'm one of the five
types of monsters myself!
And let's face it,
I'm sure the crowd would
get a lot more enjoyment
seeing my fine form
out in the ring!
‐I could eat you!
‐Like to see you try!
That's enough, you two!
I say we let Tiger
have his chance here.
That best idea.
You heard 'em.
(laughing)
You didn't think I really
wanted to go, did ya?
I was just pulling
your leg a little bit!
Want me to practice
my Cold Bullet
and Blizzard attacks on ya?
Huh, you mean you can
do those moves again?
Stand back and find out!
No, I didn't think so.
Save fighting for ring!
Uh, excuse me, but there are
others waiting in line as well.
Oh, sorry about that.
Our contenders are
Mocchi and Tiger.
I'll be coaching both
of them during the match.
Fine.
♪
I've gotta get some training
in before the match tomorrow!
Come on, you guys, hurry up!
Wait up, Tiger!
'chi!
(panting)
♪
Gray Wolf.
(grunting)
♪
Tiger.
Tiger, is that you?
‐It really is you!
‐Brother!
♪
‐You were unlocked!
‐Yes, but Tiger,
I'd heard you'd
completely vanished
after turning into
the Phoenix!
I was turned into
a mystery disk.
I was just
unlocked not long ago.
Thank goodness you're well.
And you, too.
Hey there, Gray Wolf!
Is she the one who
unlocked your mystery disk?
Mhm, her name is Nina,
and that's Hopper
she's piggybacking.
Don't tell me this
is the big brother
you're always going on about.
One and the same.
The timing couldn't be
better, hey, Gray Wolf?
(panting)
Hey, isn't that
Gray Wolf over there?
Oh, yeah, you're right!
He must've been unlocked!
'chi!
Hey!
Over here!
♪
I see, so Moo and
the Baddies still exist.
That explains why
Weed came to see me.
‐He did?
‐That's right.
He wanted me to
become a Baddie again.
Don't tell me you did.
(roaring)
Get me outta here!
Good for you, Little Brother.
‐That's sure a load off!
‐Yeah, 'chi!
So how did you end up with Nina?
Why don't you let me
fill them in, Gray Wolf?
Hopper and I were deep in
the mountains in training.
Hopper, Lightning Attack!
Hey‐ah!
♪
(yelling)
Hmm‐‐what is it?
(wind howling)
♪
It's a mystery disk!
Unlock!
♪
(howling)
Look, it's Gray Wolf, Hopper!
Gray Wolf!
This is great!
In the past, every human
that unlocked my disk
ended up abandoning
me soon after.
That's why I was incapable
of loving any human.
My name's Nina,
and this is Hopper!
Well, hiya!
We'll always stick together,
no matter what happens!
Have we got a deal?
♪
Lighten up, Gray Wolf!
How about a smile?
(laughing)
Oh, what a funny face!
(barking)
♪
We'll stay together for a while.
You're breaking my
heart, Gray Wolf!
"For a while," he says.
No way!
We're a team for keeps!
‐You got that?
‐Yeah, so you got that?
That's when I decided to
give humans another chance
and started to put
my trust in Nina.
Hey, lighten up!
What's with all
the serious talk?
I told you not to touch the fur!
(giggling)
Nina, I'd like to thank you
for taking care of
my little brother.
I'm the one who
should be thanking him!
After all, it was
Gray Wolf's idea for us
to enter the Legend
Cup Championship!
♪
The Legend Cup?
‐All three of you, 'chi?
‐That's right.
‐Why'd you ask?
‐Don't tell me
you're going in it, too!
I'm afraid that it's true.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ High in the mountain,
look for a thrill ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ A monster that ice‐fights,
that would be Jill ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Gangster's tricky
like most monsters are ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Especially the Weeds,
too tricky by far ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Some are too kind,
and some are not nice ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all,
it's good advice ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(snoring)
♪
(wind blowing)
(roaring)
Is this the monster that stole
your meat from you, Gray Wolf?
(growling)
♪
No, Tiger!
Tiger?
♪
Can't get yourself to sleep?
Same as you, Tiger.
Mmm.
It's been a long time since
we were together like this
looking at the moon.
It has.
What's wrong?
I don't know what I should do.
I wanna win the
championship for Nina,
but I don't wanna fight
against my own brother.
Being with Nina and Hopper,
it's like I've felt true
kindness and friendship
for the first time!
That doesn't include the time
I spent with you, of course.
No, I'm the same.
It was only after
I met my friends
that I started feeling
kindness towards others.
I didn't feel it with you.
No surprise.
We call each other brothers,
but in actual fact,
we're not even related
to each other, Gray Wolf.
What are you saying?
We were just thrown
away in the same box.
That's our only connection.
You are my brother.
Stop calling me that!
♪
We've already started to
follow our separate destinies,
and when our two paths do cross,
I won't think of
you as my brother.
You're my enemy.
♪
Ladies, gentlemen, and monsters!
Welcome to the Colart Stadium!
We've all seen or
heard the results
of the M‐1 Grand Prix,
the Winner's Cup,
and the World Monster's Cup!
And today we're here to witness
the Greatest Four Championship‐‐
the final step
towards the Legend Cup!
Each team will
fight two matches!
In case of a final tie, a
sudden death match will be held
to determine the champions!
And now, let's
await the contenders!
♪
(cheering)
Our teams are now both in place!
Let's meet the contenders!
On Genki's team,
Mocchi and Tiger!
And Nina's team with
Hopper and Gray Wolf!
♪
The first match is
Mocchi versus Hopper!
(cheering)
Fight!
(yelling)
(grunting)
♪
Come on, Mocchi!
Give him your
Cat Scratch, Hopper!
Cat Scratch!
Use your Mocchi Cannon!
Mocchi Cannon!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
Use your Hopper Roll !
♪
This is unprecedented!
We have both contenders
outside the ring!
Contenders outside!
We have a draw!
Mocchi!
Don't worry about Mocchi, 'chi!
Are you sure you're
all right, Hopper?
Hopper good.
The championship rests on
the outcome of this next match‐‐
Tiger versus Gray Wolf!
We're countin' on ya.
This is going to
be tough for Tiger.
Especially fighting his brother.
He's got no choice
but to win this
if we're gonna make
it to the Legend Cup.
Gol.
Ready?
(thunder rumbling)
♪
Oh, no, it's starting to pour!
And fight!
♪
Tiger, help me!
Where are you, Tiger?
♪
What's wrong?
(sobbing)
Don't cry!
Strays stole my food!
You've grown up,
in body and mind.
♪
This meat belongs to me now!
What?
But the humans had
it, and I stole it!
Well, it's mine now!
Wanna fight for it?
Yeah, right, like I'd ever
be able to win over you!
Don't be so spoiled!
Everyone's gotta
take care of himself!
(crying)
You were always
tough on me, Tiger,
but it made me stronger.
You're my enemy.
♪
(growling)
‐Blizzard!
(shattering)
♪
‐Blizzard!
No, Big Brother!
(grunting)
Lightning Attack!
(groaning)
Tiger!
'chi!
Oh, no!
Tiger holding back his
true strength from brother.
Golem's right‐‐come on, Tiger!
♪
Come on, Tiger, stand up!
'chi!
(grunting)
♪
Did you mean what you said
about not wanting
to be my brother?
Yes.
You're no more than an enemy!
(growling)
Do it, Gray Wolf!
One more attack and
the match is ours!
What's wrong?
Use your Lightning Attack?
I can't concentrate
enough to make it work!
No lightning, 'chi?
But that's our only hope
if we're gonna win
the championship.
Shall we postpone this?
No, don't.
Here I come.
I'm waiting.
♪
Finally I found that Gray Wolf.
I'll pay him back
for what he did to me,
and then I'll get
the mystery disk!
Come and get me
if you're so tough.
(growling)
Seed Machine Gun!
(gasping)
Lightning Attack!
♪
Oh, who is that?
It's a Weed Baddie!
A Baddie?
(indistinct chatter)
Lucky shot!
Take this!
Mocchi Cannon!
Ahh!
I'll remember this!
♪
Between this downpour
and the interruption,
I'm postponing the match!
Just let us continue.
Why'd you do it, Tiger?
You used your Lightning Attack
on Weed, but not on me.
If you'd used it on me
when you had me cornered,
then you would've
won the match already.
♪
So, why did you spare me?
Did you do it out of pity?
I did it because I let emotions
that have no place in the
ring get the better of me.
You mean you lied yesterday
so we'd both leave our
feelings out of the match!
Matches like these are
supposed to be contests
of skill and courage.
I knew you'd let your
emotions get in the way.
Tiger.
♪
(cheering)
I'm putting everything
into this next fight
with no holds barred.
I expect you to do
the same as well.
You can count on it.
Give him everything
you've got, Tiger.
That goes for you,
too, Gray Wolf!
(growling)
♪
(gasping)
‐No, Tiger!
‐Oh, Gray Wolf!
♪
Come on, stand up!
'chi, 'chi!
(grunting)
♪
(panting)
It's a knock out!
The match goes to Tiger!
'chi!
We did it!
Tiger wins with a knock out!
Genki's team are the new
Greatest Four Champions!
♪
Are you okay, Gray Wolf?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks, Tiger.
Nina, sorry I lost.
What are you saying?
The only thing that counts
is that you tried your best.
You tried so hard!
‐That's all that matters.
‐Yeah!
And now, it gives me great
pleasure to present Genki's team
with the Winner's Card
and their cash prize
as the new Greatest
Four Champions!
♪
So, do you have any plans now?
We're going back into training
for the next championship!
Good luck with that.
I hope everything goes well.
You take care, Big Brother.
You do the same.
Hey!
What's the hurry?
Goodbye then!
Till next time!
‐See ya!
‐Bye, good luck!
Bye‐bye, 'chi!
Goodbye, everyone!
Bye, everyone!
♪
Why were you in such a
big hurry to leave, Tiger?
‐I can see him anytime.
‐'chi?
It doesn't matter
how far apart we are,
Gray Wolf's always right
here with me in my heart.
After all, we're brothers.
Mocchi want brother, too, 'chi.
I could be your brother
if you want, Mocchi!
No, thanks!
Why you little‐‐!
(laughing)
Ha, come on, you guys.
We've got a mission ahead of us.
Yeah!
I'm going on ahead.
Huh?
Wait, Tiger!
(laughing)
Aw, you're the best.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪