♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Mum Mew?
Gobi?
Mum Mew!
Gobi!
Where are those
blunderheaded fools?
What is that?
♪
Oh, brother.
Another letter from Mum Mew.
"My dearest General Durahan,
as your ever faithful servants,
Gobi and I feel
personally responsible
for the inability to
retrieve the Mystery Disk."
Maybe we'd have it by now
if she wasn't in front of
the mirror all the time.
Just keep reading.
(sighing)
"Since the powerful
Metainer failed us..."
"... Gobi and I feel
that the responsibility
to get the disk lies
in our capable hands.
We promise to return
with your long‐awaited
Mystery Disk, General.
P. S.:"
"Sorry for not asking first,
but we've taken Weed with us."
At last they've started
taking their mission seriously.
I have great hopes for
you, Mum Mew and Gobi.
The day when I'll have
my disk draws ever nearer.
(laughing)
♪
Whoa, this dinner's
fit for an emperor!
♪
I figured we should celebrate.
We made it so far today,
we should get to
Torble by tomorrow.
All right, the Legend Cup
is just around the corner.
(moaning)
What's the matter, Mocchi?
Nothing wrong, Chi.
The little guy only gets down
like that when he's nervous.
No nervous, Chi!
Mocchi, there's no
reason to hide it.
Tiger's right.
Everyone gets nervous before
going in a big championship.
Poritoka and Most very strong.
Yeah, but we're gonna be
right there backin' you up.
I'm sure you'll win.
Have a little faith.
'Kay, Mocchi try hard, Chi!
Hmm, that's the way, Mocchi.
Come on, let's eat up, gang.
Chi!
Boy, am I hungry, let's eat!
(munching)
Oh, this is good.
The Legend Cup?
What are they so determined to
get into that championship for?
‐Hmm.
Hmm.
Hm.
Thanks, you two,
you've been a huge help.
(snoring loudly)
♪
(footsteps approaching)
Can't you sleep, Mocchi?
Holly, Mocchi scared.
If Mocchi lose Legend Cup,
Holly's father no
be rescued, Chi.
Listen, I'm the only one who
should be worrying about my dad.
I'll be grateful if
you just try your best.
But Holly, Chi.
You're a good friend, Mocchi,
and knowing you're
doing this for me,
well, nothing else even matters.
Really, Chi?
'Kay, Mocchi try hard, Chi!
Win Legend Cup
and get winner's plate
with Magic Stone inside!
So that's what
this is all about.
If we can get our hands
on that Magic Stone
from the winner's plate, we'd
be able to resurrect Moo's soul.
Yeah.
But first we must get that disk.
We'll wait till
those two go to sleep,
then we'll move in and steal it.
♪
(snoring)
(yelping)
♪
(screaming)
They're gone!
We must have fallen
asleep before they did.
Which one of you was
doing all that humming
that put me to sleep?
I told you to sing
something jazzy, didn't I?
Who's to blame?
It's her own fault
for fallin' asleep.
She shouldn't be blamin'
us, the nutty old coot.
♪
Hmm.
Hey, Mum Mew, you gonna
eat all that or you‐‐
You concentrate on the plan!
♪
(panting)
What's this?
100,000 gold reward
for information
leading to the arrest
of the Gatlin Brothers?
Hmm, that's it!
Mum Mew, I have a plan!
It's so brilliant,
you'll love it.
(whispering)
That does sound good.
And here I was, starting to have
my doubts about bringing you.
Aw, gee, I'm flattered.
(chuckling)
The queen bee always
needs more sustenance.
♪
Attention, my fellow citizens,
we have an emergency
on our hands.
A band of seven ruthless thieves
are on a wild rampage
and are headed this way.
Anyone who provides information
leading to their capture
will be rewarded
with 100,000 golds!
Attention, one and all!
♪
Hmm.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mocchi is pink,
but Mocchi is tough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Zuum troops and their
captain play kinda rough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Suezo looks far,
soars through the skies ♪
♪ Looking for Rockies,
they aren't bad guys ♪
♪ Horn the pirate
says that he's pure ♪
♪ But he's a monster,
can you be sure? ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
On our way to Torble.
(all chanting "Torble")
Legend Cup!
♪
(groaning)
I don't believe it.
A hotel!
‐A hotel?
Yeah, unless we're all
seein' the same mirage.
Holly, think we can stop
and rest up for a while?
We've been walkin' in
this heat since morning.
Golem so thirsty.
Come on, you guys,
you know we don't have
enough money to afford a hotel.
(groaning)
Wait, check it out.
Someone's over there,
and they're eyeballin' us.
He's wavin'!
♪
So, you're on your way
to Torble, are you?
Then you'll want to rest up
a while before you continue on.
You've still got a lot
of ground to cover.
And you're sure you're not
gonna charge us anything?
Today is customer
appreciation day,
celebrating 100
years in business.
Just this once, we're offering
all our rooms free of charge.
Come, friends, right this way.
Oh, man, I'm beat.
Look, look, juice I bring.
Nectar to soothe the soul!
Many have, very thirsty you are.
Thanks so much.
(slurping)
♪
Many juices they drink down.
Then let's waste no time
and make our call.
♪
(snoring)
Glad you came so soon.
And you're sure
it's the same gang?
Yes, that's them, all right.
They'll be in a deep
sleep for a few hours
judging by how much of my
special juice they just drank.
‐Good, let's go.
‐Right.
‐Just a minute.
‐What do you want?
Let's clear up the little matter
of my 100,000 gold reward.
100,000 gold reward?
(laughing)
♪
Do you realize who
you're dealing with?
And you think I've never seen
a Baddie out here before?
(snapping fingers)
♪
(groaning)
Who are they?
About that reward.
I'd like to collect it in
advance if you don't mind.
You know, we're called
Baddies for a reason.
Show them we're serious.
Right!
♪
Twin Slap!
(groaning)
(laughing)
Now let me at 'em.
Hmm?
Ha, don't know when to stop.
♪
(grunting)
Enough of this
spastic jig, Gobi!
Now just finish
the little twerp off.
Yeah, sure.
Spinning Attack!
(chuckling)
♪
Look out below!
Huh?
And now my money.
I'd prefer to get
that out of the way.
Our only chance now is
to make a run for the hotel
and hope we're faster than him!
(beeping)
(screaming)
(groaning)
♪
I'll collect that reward
in advance if you don't mind.
Ha, as if I've got
that kind of money on me.
I'm sorry to hear that.
(beeping)
(gasping)
♪
What in the world?
A person's got
to be prepared
with all these
criminals in the area.
I'd advise you
to be on your guard
if you know what's good for you.
(screaming)
(groaning)
(coughing)
Mum Mew!
Watch it, mister.
A person could get
hurt by those things.
I'll collect that reward
in advance if you don't mind.
I keep telling you,
we don't have
that kind of money.
In that case...
(screaming)
(explosions)
(snoring)
♪
It seems to have stopped.
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah, yeah,
is that all you ever say?
You couldn't even handle
that little Fairy Hopper.
Oh, me?
You're supposed to be
the brawn part of the team,
but you're nothing
but dead weight,
always cowering
behind us brains.
You're a disgrace
to the Baddies.
(sobbing)
Just ignore the old tabby, Gobi.
She doesn't know what
she's talkin' about.
Huh?
(whimpering)
(scowling)
Uh, forgive me.
No, Mum Mew, I didn't mean it!
Oh, please, have mercy!
(grumbling)
All systems go, master.
Launch weapons.
♪
Huh?
(screaming)
♪
This‐‐this isn't happening!
They're headed straight for us!
Ahh!
Let me out,
let me out, let me out!
♪
(snoring continues)
(screaming)
♪
Oh, this is gonna leave a mark.
(screaming)
♪
All right, I'll pay
you your money!
♪
(sighing)
Now that was a sticky situation.
♪
I knew you'd come
to see things my way.
♪
(people chattering)
I still don't get why we have
to resort to robbing a bank.
So we can get the Mystery Disk.
I figured that much out.
Stick 'em up, this is a robbery!
Huh?
(screaming and gunfire)
♪
Everyone up against the wall
and no one will get hurt!
Move it!
Hang on a minute.
This is supposed to
be our bank robbery.
Hey, this is our robbery,
and we were here first!
Won't anybody listen?
It looks like another one
of your brilliant plans
has gone down the
tubes again, Einstein.
Should've gone with
a stagecoach robbery.
So what do we do now?
Since we're already here,
let's just steal the
money from the thieves.
This better work or I'll
find a replacement for you.
I got it all figured out.
Then convince me.
♪
Yeah, that's the way.
Let's move, men!
Stop right there!
What?
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to
liberate that money from you.
Hand over the dough.
No!
(laughing)
They're Baddies!
I didn't know
there were any left.
(people chattering)
(Mum Mew laughing)
Drop the gold and
run for your lives
if you know what's good for ya.
♪
Ha, a few Baddies
never scared me none.
Come and get it,
iffen you ain't too yeller.
If that's the way you want it...
‐Gobi.
‐Right.
(grunting)
(whimpering)
♪
Gobi!
(crashing)
♪
(Weed whimpering)
Still want a piece of me?
(growling)
Can't y'all take a little
joke from a Southern girl?
I was only funnin' ya.
Aren't you new around here?
I could sure use 100,000 golds,
and you seem the generous type.
Vamoose, you dusty old feedbag.
You know you can't make
a silk purse from a sow's ear.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're an old has‐been,
a wannabe, a never‐was.
♪
I'm an old has‐been?
Hold it, mister?
What now,
you doofus old tabby cat?
♪
I'm an old has‐been, wannabe?
A never‐was?
Well, excuse me!
Leavin'!
(shrieking)
Get her, men!
♪
Scratch Buzzer!
Electric Stance!
♪
(cheering)
Hmm?
I dare ya to call me
an old has‐been again.
Come on, tough guy,
let's hear you say it.
(whimpering)
Forgive me, pretty little miss.
I shouldn't have
never said that to ya.
Pretty little miss?
That rolls nicely off
the tongue, now doesn't it?
(cheering)
Wonderful!
And thank you very
much, young lady.
Thank you for all
your help, young lady.
I don't get it.
Are you calling me "young lady"?
I'm just glad you got your
money back safe and sound!
(laughing wildly)
♪
(crickets chirring)
(snoring)
♪
(groaning)
‐Huh?
‐Ahh!
(scoffing)
(whimpering)
Wakey, wakey, wakey,
wakey, wakey, wakey!
Wake, wake, wake, wake, wake!
Welcome back.
Here's the 100,000
gold I promised.
(coins clinking)
I'd better count it
up to double‐check.
Many golds you get.
It was a reward for helping to
capture this wanted bank robber.
Got a thank‐you note, too.
Huh.
Old tabby find criminal?
Who are you calling
an old tabby,
you scrawny little furbag?
You can't even talk right,
you furry little freak!
100,000 golds, on the nose.
You'll find the seven
criminals you're looking for
asleep upstairs in
the deluxe room, ma'am.
If you'd let me go anytime
soon, we could get 'em.
Right.
(panting)
♪
Well, let's put away our money
and start closing things up
for the night, shall we?
Huh?
♪
Where are they,
where are they, huh?
♪
"Though we wanted to
express our gratitude to you,
we left without disturbing
you since you were asleep.
Thank you very much
for your hospitality.
On behalf of all my friends,
Holly."
(chuckling nervously)
We sure lucked out going there
on customer appreciation day.
Free juice good, too, Chi.
Go.
I still can't get over how
long we all fell asleep for.
No kidding.
We went down for a short nap
and slept right
through the night.
‐We were all so exhausted.
‐Chi!
We'll walk all night
to make up for lost time.
Yeah!
(laughing)
(wind howling)
♪
A letter of thanks?
What's this all about?
Look, we caught
this bank robber.
We're not running
a Good Samaritan club here!
That's enough, Poison.
General?
(General laughing)
Who would've thought
there'd be a Magic Stone
in the Legend Cup
winner's plate?
♪
Prepare yourselves.
We have
a championship to attend.
General Durahan?
You're coming, too, General?
Correct.
We'll wait until they
have the Magic Stone,
then steal it and the
Mystery Disk from them.
‐Yes, sir!
(laughing deviously)
♪
This Torble City.
Home to the famous Legend Cup.
Oh, yeah.
Mocchi try hard, Chi.
All right!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪