♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(panting)
We made it to Parepare!
This is a famous
resort, you know!
We don't care about
that kinda stuff.
We came here to enter
the championship.
Yeah, we're gonna
get the Winner's Cup.
‐Right, Mocchi?
‐'chi.
‐Huh?
Come on, Mocchi,
the tribe has spoken,
so don't go giving us any lip.
Mocchi no have lips.
Mocchi, is something the matter?
Nothing the matter, 'chi.
♪
Are you serious?
As a registered fighter,
Mocchi's partner has to be
one of these five
designated species?
The only one who's the right
kind of monster is Golem.
Golem make up for
last bad fight.
‐This time Golem win.
‐That's the spirit, big guy!
In this fight,
two challengers
will fight the
defending champions
with a sudden‐death match
in the event of a tie.
Golem try his best!
We'll try hard too,
won't we, Mocchi?
‐'chi.
‐Uh, Mocchi?
♪
'chi.
(in unison)
Mocchi!
(panting)
He's got a high fever.
Tell us how you feel, Mocchi.
Like Mocchi in big stew pot.
Mocchi need doctor right away.
Yeah, Golem, you carry him.
♪
Well, doctor, what do you think?
Oh, it's just a bad cold.
♪
Do you think our friend
will be all right?
His fever should
drop by tomorrow.
The best thing for him is
to get a good night's rest.
I suggest he stay the
night here in the hospital.
Ha, hear that, Mocchi,
all you need is some rest.
Aren't you glad
it's nothing serious?
'chi.
♪
He won't be able to go in the
championship in his condition.
The most important
thing is to work on
getting Mocchi healthy again.
Maybe we should back
out of the championship.
(grumbling)
We no back out.
Golem win first match.
Think you'll win?
Then it wouldn't
matter if Mocchi lost.
If you lost one match
and won the other,
you could still win the
sudden death playoffs.
Golem try hard, now go practice.
(yelling)
♪
(bird chirping)
Hello, how are you?
Hello, girl in pajama.
Would you like to look
at the flowers with me?
Huh, huh?
Gol'?
(chuckling)
♪
Aren't they beautiful?
Golem like flower.
Also like bird.
(giggling)
I didn't mean to laugh,
I just can't believe
how sensitive you
are, considering.
‐Gol'.
‐I'm happy we met,
'cause I love flowers
and birds like you do.
We have so much in common.
Hi, my name is Michelle.
Me Golem.
Oh, I see.
So you're on a mission
to win the Legend Cup.
Tomorrow, Golem will
fight in Winner's Cup.
You will, terrific!
(laughing)
You mentioned that you like
birds and flowers, Golem.
‐What else do you like?
‐Gol'?
‐Like cooking.
‐Oh?
‐I like looking at the ocean.
‐Ocean?
What's the matter, don't
you like the ocean?
Um, uh, oh, love ocean!
Golem love water and ocean
just like Michelle do!
That's great!
♪
I've been stuck here
ever since I got sick,
so I haven't seen
the ocean in ages.
I'd give anything to
spend some time there.
‐Ah!
‐Golem take you to ocean.
‐Are you sure, Golem?
‐Gol'.
♪
‐Something the matter?
‐Oh, it's nothing.
I'm just so happy to be here.
But I can't help
wondering what lies
out there beyond the horizon.
♪
‐Michelle go there and find out.
‐Pardon?
Michelle get better,
then go on journey
to see beyond horizon.
Hm.
Golem, I'd sure love to
see your fight tomorrow.
‐Gol'?
‐Something tells me
that watching you
in the championship
will cheer me up, and who knows?
‐Maybe it'll help me get better.
‐Gol'!
(coughing)
‐Michelle!
‐Gol'?
♪
You know you're not supposed
to leave the hospital, Michelle.
I know, sorry to
worry you, Grandpa.
This not be Michelle fault.
Golem bring her without asking.
Who's your friend, Michelle?
We met at the hospital, Grandpa.
His name's Golem.
♪
Michelle, she very sick?
Yes, I'm afraid she is,
but it's nothing that an
operation couldn't cure.
Gol', Golem glad, Gol'.
Well, it's a little
more complicated.
Gol'?
The operation she
needs is very expensive.
Hmmm.
It's not an easy thing to admit,
but I just don't have the
kind of money to afford it.
‐How much money you need?
‐Hm?
‐Operation, how much it cost?
‐I don't understand though.
‐Why do you ask?
‐Golem just want to know.
‐It costs 5,000 golds.
‐5,000.
Same amount as Winner's
Cup prize money.
(grunting)
♪
Golem must win tournament
money tomorrow.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Think of a square
standing on end ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ You got Color Pandora,
watch it defend ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Lilim is cute,
but this one's no fun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ She wants all the marbles
for her honey‐bun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ General Durahan
demands it all ♪
♪ He's seen the world
at his beck and call ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
What do you mean you wanna keep
all the prize money
for yourself?
You know, Golem, 5,000 golds
is a pretty big chunk of money.
‐Gol'.
‐Hang on a sec, gang.
Golem's not the type
of guy to ask for much,
so I'm sure he's
got a good reason.
I agree with you,
Golem's a good monster,
and we should
respect his choices.
Golem promise no waste money.
Use prize money to save
friend in big trouble.
Hmmmm.
Settled, Golem
can use the money
‐any way he wants to.
‐What?
But I've been counting
down the minutes to when
we'll be able to eat
in a restaurant again.
If you need some money, I could
win some in a prize fight
‐and lend it to you, Suezo.
‐Win some?
Isn't that your way of
saying you'd liberate some?
‐You're asking for it!
‐I don't think so!
Gol', Golem have
many kind friends.
Win championship.
(grunting)
Hey, watch it with those things.
♪
Huh?
Mocchi!
(laughing)
Genki!
Are ya all better?
'chi, 'chi!
Mocchi's fever has dropped,
but he's still
feeling a little weak.
‐Mocchi just fine, 'chi!
‐We needed some good news!
Better rest up
for your big match!
‐Mhm.
‐Don't worry.
Golem win first
match, Mocchi rest.
'chi.
(crowd cheering)
Welcome to another fine
day at Parepare Stadium
where the contenders will battle
it out for the Winner's Cup
in this, the fourth step
toward the Legend Cup!
Before we begin
our first match,
here's Golem from the
challenger's team!
(crowd screaming)
♪
And from the defending
team, Shellkedo!
(screaming)
Ready,
fight!
♪
Golem, you gotta keep
your distance from him.
♪
Shellkedo puts up a relentless
attack with his enormous claws!
How long can Golem keep dodging?
(shouting)
Now's your chance!
♪
Golem's turned things around.
Now it's Shellkedo who's
having to defend himself!
♪
Golem's gonna have to fight hard
if he wants to win this match.
I can't remember ever seeing
him fight this well before.
♪
‐Are you all right?
‐Look out, 'chi, 'chi!
♪
Golem, defend yourself!
Shellkedo's shooting off
his fire cracker attacks
like there's no tomorrow!
♪
Watch out, Golem,
you're on the edge!
♪
Golem, no!
Tornado attack!
♪
Knockout, match to Golem.
(crowd cheering)
‐We won!
‐We did it, we won!
♪
‐Michelle feel better today?
‐Mhm.
She insisted on coming
to see your match.
Mhm.
Golem fight hard to make
Michelle get better.
♪
Presenting the next contender
from the challenger's
team, Mocchi!
‐Try your best, but be careful.
‐Yeah, 'chi!
And from the defending
champions, here's Noble Jell!
Ready,
fight!
♪
What's this?
Mocchi fouls out.
The match goes to Noble Jell!
(crowd screaming)
Mocchi's breeder has
jumped into the ring
and grabbed him during the bout!
And that move has
cost Mocchi the match!
‐Genki?
‐Sorry,
‐but you're still too sick.
‐No worry, Mocchi.
Golem win sudden‐death match.
‐'chi.
‐Genki made the right move.
Mhm, he had no choice but to
pull Mocchi out of the ring.
The teams are tied
at one match a piece,
which will take us
into sudden death!
Which contender will fight?
‐Challengers?
‐Gol'.
♪
Defending team?
(growling)
There you have it,
folks, the deciding match
will be Golem versus Noble Jell!
Ready, fight!
(yelling)
♪
Go after him, Golem.
Oh no, Noble Jell's
spike top hits the mark!
♪
He's gonna use
his parabola beam.
Use your rolling stone!
Rolling stone!
♪
Incredible, Golem's
rolling stone attack
hasn't even slowed
down Noble Jell!
Jells aren't like
other opponents because
they just bounce
back from an attack.
He'll have to think of
something to win this.
Sure, but what?
We're rootin' for ya, Golem!
Come on, Golem.
Gatling attack!
(gasping)
♪
Golem's heading fast to
the edge of the ring.
Watch the edge!
Golem, no!
♪
(shouting)
Now, for the finishing touch!
♪
‐He's in trouble.
‐Oh no!
He's gotta find some
way to get outta there!
(grunting)
♪
Golem, come on, don't give up!
I know you can make
it out of there!
Would you like to look
at the flowers with me?
Something tells me that
watching you in the championship
will cheer me up, and who knows?
Maybe it'll help me get better.
We have so much in common.
♪
(yelling)
That's the way,
Golem, you did it!
‐Yay!
‐Michelle!
♪
Fickle finger of fate!
It's a knockout!
The match goes to Golem!
(bell ringing)
Golem clinches the match
with his magnificent
fickle finger of fate!
(crowd cheering)
Golem, you did it!
Way to go, Golem!
Now, we gotta go.
Goodbye, Golem.
♪
Well done, team.
Congratulations on
winning 5,000 golds
and the Winner's card!
♪
Michelle health
worse than before?
Her health has taken
a turn for the worse,
and she needs to have
that operation right away.
That terrible.
‐You use prize money.
‐Are you sure?
‐Yes, now hurry and go.
‐Thank you.
♪
Oh Golem, all along you
wanted that prize money
so your friend Michelle
could get her operation.
Golem worry about Michelle.
Genki, why don't we
all go to the hospital?
♪
It looks like this room's empty.
Hm?
♪
‐What happened to Michelle?
‐I don't know what you mean.
We have no patient
here named Michelle.
Michelle, she stay
in this room here.
That's part of the old wing,
none of our patients would stay
in there because the
whole wing is closed.
My suspicions were
right after all.
What do you mean
your suspicions?
He means that Golem's
so‐called friend deceived him.
Faking a sickness to get
sympathy is an old trick.
Faking?
Not Michelle.
♪
That Michelle's bird.
Gol'?
I'm giving you back
half of the prize money,
'cause I feel a
bit guilty about it.
It's under the bed.
I wanna say one last thing.
I could've scammed anyone,
so don't take it personally.
You're a really nice guy.
Ohh.
See it under there?
Yeah, I found it,
it's our money.
There's still time
to catch them.
I'll go get the rest
of our money back.
Mm‐mm.
They lie about
Michelle's sickness.
Golem happy.
Michelle not really have
sickness, make Golem glad.
Man, Golem, trust you
to come out smiling.
Michelle, take care.
♪
What were you thinking?
We only came away with
half of the prize money.
So, it doesn't hurt to
be nice once in a while.
Ohhh, next she'll tell
me she has a conscience!
♪
On to the next town.
Let's try to get
there before dark.
♪
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
I‐‐I think so.
♪
Huh?
I suppose this means they've
forgotten about their mission
to get back the mystery
disk for you, General.
Time to find replacements
for those incompetents.
♪
Let's move out, gang, the
next championship is waiting.
(cheering)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪