♪ Mon‐mon‐mon‐monsters‐‐
Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ To the world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it
to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem
that fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
♪ Monster Rancher,
Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
monsters rule ♪
‐Mum Mew: It didn't work.
It still hasn't descended.
Huh?
‐Poison: You'd better fix that
or you'll be in trouble.
Durahan's starting to get edgy.
‐I know that.
‐Gobi: Fixed it.
‐Then let's try it
one more time.
Hear me and awaken,
fierce and powerful soldier
of darkness,
whose strength is unrivaled.
‐(gasps)
Mum Mew, what have you done?
‐(shrieking)
‐Gobi: What?
‐Poison: I told you
never to release that monster.
You've got to stop it.
‐I know that. Gobi!
‐Gobi: I'm trying, I'm trying.
Oh, my aching head.
‐(coughing)
‐Gobi!
‐Phew.
‐Durahan: What's going on?
‐Gobi and Mum Mew:
General Durahan.
‐Hmm.
‐(chuckling)
Oops.
‐Durahan: Hmm.
‐General Durahan, don't worry.
This isn't the crystal ball
with the skull mark on it.
Oh!
‐Durahan: Skull mark?
I expressly told you
to never release that warrior.
‐I'm not part of this charade.
I tried to stop her,
but she's stubborn.
‐Durahan:
It's too late for excuses.
Poison, leave us.
I don't want you here
when he is released.
‐Yes, of course, General.
‐Durahan: Move.
‐Shogun: Ah. Durahan,
you thought you had imprisoned
me for all of eternity,
but nothing can stop
Shogun the mighty.
I am prepared
to take you on, Durahan.
‐Durahan: It's been
a long time, Shogun.
‐Shogun: Your body.
Who hath wreaked havoc
on you thus?
‐Durahan: The most powerful
warrior of all.
‐Shogun: Most powerful?
‐Durahan: Yes. Seven veteran
warriors who united and became
a single unstoppable force.
‐Shogun: Seven became one.
Interesting.
‐Durahan: They are the reason
I've resurrected you.
I want you to find the seven
and get my revenge.
‐Shogun: (laughing)
Nothing would give me
more satisfaction.
Those seven warriors will regret
the day they encountered
Shogun the mighty.
(laughing)
‐Poison: Is Shogun
really so terrifying?
‐Durahan: Yes. Especially
with monsters like you,
although Mum Mew
will have nothing
to worry about.
‐Mum Mew: Oh, Shogun.
‐Shogun: Shogun the mighty,
if you please.
‐I still don't get
how you ended up frozen.
If you're so strong,
then why didn't you
show them who was boss
before he had the chance
to freeze ya, hey, Shogun?
‐Shogun: Well, it began the day
I overwhelmed Durahan.
‐Lilim: General Durahan.
‐Shogun: (laughing)
Taste the power of
Shogun the mighty.
I am invincible.
‐Durahan: Run, Lilim.
‐Huh?
‐Shogun: A fair maiden!
‐(shrieks)
‐Shogun: Oh, my dark rose,
your beauty hath bewitched me.
Such beguiling beauty.
(yelling)
‐Mum Mew:
You mean you just slipped
into the ice water?
‐Shogun: Oh, you misunderstand.
Beauty as profound as hers
can serve as the source of
a brave warrior's strength.
‐Oh! So that's why
Durahan sent me.
(chuckling)
Shogun, I'd be honored
to let you use my looks
as a source of inspiration.
‐Shogun: Actually, I said
beauty was what motivated me.
‐Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
Don't you think I'm beautiful?
I've been known
to turn a few heads.
‐Shogun: (stammering)
I was just saying‐‐
‐(yelling)
‐Both: Shogun!
‐Genki: Whoa!
This weather is something else.
‐Tiger: I love that breeze.
‐Holly: It feels good,
doesn't it?
‐Hare: It makes me
wanna yell to the world...
‐(both yodeling)
‐Chi.
‐Nobody's gonna
answer you here.
That's for in the mountains,
where there's an echo.
‐Shogun: Help me!
‐Mocchi: Someone in river‐chi.
‐Genki.
‐Right.
‐Shogun: Help me.
‐Grab on.
‐Shogun: Much obliged,
gentle maiden.
‐But I didn't do anything.
‐Hey! You can't touch
whoever you want!
‐♪ Mon‐mon‐mon‐monsters‐‐
Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a Disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your Disk! ♪
♪ Gali, one of Moo's
Big Bad Four ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all! ♪
♪ Big Blue, a monster
with power and more ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all! ♪
♪ Pixie's a mystery,
whose side is she on? ♪
♪ Unlock your Disk! ♪
♪ She's one of Moo's Four,
but for how long? ♪
♪ Unlock your Disk ♪
♪ Flips and tornadoes,
without 'em, within ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
someone will win ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐Shogun the mighty, you say?
‐Shogun: The one and only,
young man.
‐Hare: Never heard of ya.
‐Suezo: You didn't
look too mighty
floundering your way
down the river.
‐He can take down
100 men in a single motion.
‐All: Huh?
‐It's the truth.
Shogun the mighty
is feared by all
and is also known
as Black Lightning.
He's a fierce warrior.
‐I've heard about
Black Lightning as well,
but I thought it was
just a legend.
His stroke's so fast,
his opponents only see
a flash of light.
‐100 men?
All in a single motion?
‐That fast‐chi.
‐Golem: Goh!
‐Shogun: That's a legend.
I can do much better. (laughing)
Boy, you missed a spot.
‐Oh, sorry‐chi.
‐Here you are.
This bowl of stew
should warm you up.
‐Shogun: Your gentle smile
warms this cold heart.
‐I still can't believe
our good luck,
meeting Shogun the mighty
way out here
in the middle of nowhere.
‐Hmm. Shogun, will you train us
how to fight like you do?
‐We try to win
Legend Cup championship‐chi.
‐Shogun: The Legend Cup?
(laughing)
Those contests
are nothing but games,
unlike the heroic duels
fought on the battlefield.
Real battles are the only
true show of strength.
‐That championship
means a lot to us.
Don't knock it.
‐Shogun: I'm simply
telling it like it is.
‐Sure. But throwing
a little respect into the mix
wouldn't hurt.
‐Chi.
‐We wouldn't have
asked you to help train us
if we weren't serious.
‐Golem work very hard.
‐I'm serious about this, too.
‐I am Shogun the mighty.
I have no time
for such futile dawdling.
‐Shogun...
‐Shogun: Then again,
basking in your warm smile
might do a soldier good.
(chuckles)
‐(Mum Mew imitates
Shogun laughing)
Lovestruck fool. Why doesn't
he hurry up and attack them?
‐Wait a minute, Mum Mew.
This might be part of his plan.
‐Mum Mew and Gobi: His plan?
‐Yes, there's seven of them.
So rather than taking them
all at once,
he's befriended them
and he's waiting
for the right moment.
‐Mum Mew: I see.
‐Gobi: Good plan.
‐Shogun: The most important
battle technique
is the hardest to achieve,
mastering one's mind.
‐(all grunting)
‐So, what's the big deal?
‐Shogun: To master your mind,
you must block out
all distractions.
Boo!
‐(all shrieking)
‐Shogun: A scarlet rose,
heaven‐sent.
‐Uh, thanks for catching me.
‐You just staged that
so‐called training maneuver
so Holly would fall
into your arms.
‐Oh, Shogun the mighty
would do no such thing.
‐All: Hmm.
‐(Shogun laughing)
(clears throat)
Now, onto the next maneuver.
‐Mum Mew: I don't think
he has any plan.
He's just trying
to get to know that girl.
‐(all grunting)
‐Tiger: Huh?
‐All: Huh?
‐That Zuum stole my bag.
‐Catch him!
‐No, Holly, stay here with me.
‐Gobi: Halt.
‐Huh? How dare you!
Oh.
What? They are the ones
I'm after?
You mean‐‐
‐Gobi: Uh‐huh. Uh‐huh.
‐Shogun: Hmm.
Very sly indeed.
But there's no fooling
Shogun the mighty.
I knew what they were up to
the minute I saw them.
‐You did not know!
‐(yells) How dare they
take advantage of my goodwill?
They will regret it.
Shogun the mighty will
teach them a lesson!
‐Tiger: That Zuum
will think twice next time
he tries to steal something.
‐Holly: Maybe we were
too hard on him.
‐He's gotta learn that
crime just doesn't pay.
‐Stealing no good.
‐(groaning) Please help me,
Mum Mew.
‐Huh? Where's Shogun?
‐Mocchi: Not here‐chi.
‐Hare: He took off on us!
‐Talk about nerve. You'd think
he could've said goodbye first.
‐I was hoping
he could stick around
and train us some more.
‐Yeah. Me, too.
‐Wait. I can sense him nearby.
‐Shogun: So, you are
the seven veteran warriors
united as a single force.
‐What do you mean,
"seven veteran warriors
united as one"?
‐Never heard of 'em.
‐And on that note,
why don't we drop the subject
and get back to our training?
‐(laughing) I have discovered
your true identity
and I challenge you
to a duel.
‐Challenge us‐chi?
‐What do you want to
fight us for, Shogun?
We are your friends.
‐We just wanna train with you.
We're not looking
for any battles.
‐Shogun: You tried to steal
my invincible battle techniques.
Cowards! Now, transform
into your monster shape
and fight me fair and square.
‐All: "Monster shape"?
‐How long will you
keep up this act?
Fine, then I'll make
the first move.
‐Shogun‐‐
‐Don't bother.
‐Suezo: I think he's serious.
‐Prepare for a taste
of my lightning sword.
‐Wait. Don't do it.
‐Shogun: (chuckles awkwardly)
I‐‐
Oh, seven‐in‐one warrior,
only the greatest soldiers
have ever stopped
my lightning sword.
‐What's this "seven‐in‐one
warrior" stuff anyway?
‐Stop feigning innocence!
Ring of steel!
Oh, it must have been weakened
from the years in ice.
Well, a broken sword
isn't enough to stop
Shogun the mighty.
(panting)
Strange, how easily
you avoided my sword.
‐It wasn't that hard,
seeing as it's only
a foot long.
‐Shogun,
what's gotten into you?
‐Shogun: Enough idle chatter!
‐Stumble Samurai.
‐Huh? Tiger!
‐Words won't get through to him.
‐(Shogun laughing)
‐All: Huh?
‐Seven‐in‐one warrior,
at last you have
revealed yourself.
The duel has just begun.
Prepare for my
whirlwind attack!
‐Are you okay?
‐(groaning) My reputation,
it falls into disrepair.
How utterly frustrating.
‐He's pathetic.
‐All: Shogun?
‐Shogun: Unhand me.
A great soldier knows
when to admit defeat.
But you can never destroy
my pride.
‐Get a grip, Shogun.
‐Quit acting weird!
Now, get up!
‐Shogun the mighty, my foot.
Zuums, just forget Shogun
and go after them yourselves.
‐Mocchi: Baddies‐chi.
‐Golem, you stay here
and protect Holly and Shogun.
‐Golem: Goh.
‐Tiger: Lightning attack!
‐Double pounder!
Double pounder!
‐Tongue slap!
‐They've outnumbered us.
‐They just keep on coming.
‐Let's bolt till we have a plan.
‐All: Yeah!
‐Shogun: Unhand me, you brute.
‐After them!
What? You still
haven't found them?
‐Is the coast clear?
‐Bad news‐chi.
‐They've got us
completely surrounded.
‐Then we'll have to sit tight
and try waiting them out.
Tiger should be back
fairly soon.
‐Genki: Hmm.
Any progress?
‐Mmm‐mmm.
‐Stubborn man here won't budge.
‐End the duel
and have your victory.
‐Come on, Shogun,
it was a one‐way fight
in the first place.
‐Shogun: A duel is a battle
for one's integrity and pride.
No, take your victory
and let me proceed down the road
of failure and ridicule.
‐Even if you did lose,
that's no reason to give up.
You can always train
and have another duel.
‐Shogun: Black Lightning
being retrained like
a mere apprentice?
(scoffs) Such an undignified act
I could not commit.
‐So what if it's undignified?
‐Shogun: Hmm?
‐You might not agree,
but to me, what matters
is having the courage
to never give up.
That's more important
than winning.
‐(Shogun chuckles)
What do you know about it?
You don't understand
what it means to be known
as the mightiest warrior
in the land.
‐I'm sorry.
‐Huh? What did you find out?
‐There's a rocky stretch
not far up ahead.
I think we can lose them
once we get past it.
‐Well, then let's make
a run for it.
‐Holly: Yeah.
‐Chi!
‐Well, shall we go?
Huh?
‐Shogun: Go on without me.
‐But Shogun‐‐
‐You heard what the man said.
Let's leave him.
‐We can't.
‐It's us the Baddies are after,
not Shogun,
so there's no sense
worrying about him.
‐Let's get going.
‐Uh, yeah. Sure.
What matters is having
the courage to never give up.
That's more important
than winning.
‐Shogun: 9,995.
9,996.
9,997.
9,998.
9,999.
(groaning)
10,001.
10,002.
10,003.
Now I have the true spirit
of a warrior.
‐Zuum: That way.
‐Genki: It's a dead end.
‐(Mum Mew laughing)
This time, you won't
get away, I'm afraid.
It is only seven of you,
after all.
We should have done things
this way from the start
rather than counting on Shogun.
‐Gobi: Yeah.
‐Huh?
What are you talking about?
‐I heard the legends
of Shogun the mighty,
so I gave him orders
to defeat you
and your friends,
but unfortunately,
he turned out to be weaker
than I thought.
‐So you sent him after us.
‐(laughs)
I have to say, it was nice
working with a monster
who was so gullible.
‐You're despicable.
‐You mean‐chi.
‐Sticks and stones, my friends.
Now, how about handing over
that Mystery Disk?
A long wait, but at last
the evil soul will be back
in our hands.
And with it, the greatest power
and the key to allow the Baddies
to reign supreme!
(laughing)
‐Shogun: So that was
your true motive.
You still rely
on Moo's evil power,
but the only invincible power
comes from within
after much training.
Witness it firsthand!
‐All: Shogun!
‐(laughing)
Lookout, everyone,
he's got a big stick.
After him!
‐Shogun!
‐The legendary
lightning flash technique.
‐Whoa! I don't believe it!
‐(Mum Mew whimpering)
‐All: Shogun!
‐(Shogun laughing)
‐Genki: Thanks for
all your help, Shogun.
‐Shogun: It is I who owes
a debt of gratitude.
You made me remember
something very important.
‐What's so important‐chi?
‐To have passion and conviction,
and to never give up
on your dreams.
‐Shogun.
‐Shogun: Today,
I will train myself anew.
And good luck to you
in the Legend Cup.
‐Mocchi: Chi.
‐Shogun: I hope to challenge you
to another duel someday.
Then, you must transform
yourselves and show me your
seven‐in‐one warrior techniques.
‐All: Transform ourselves?
‐Shogun: Farewell,
seven fierce warriors
who fight as one.
‐Wait, Shogun.
‐I think he's got us
mixed up with someone else.
‐Yeah. But, hey, don't you think
it kind of suits us?
‐We're veterans of many battles.
Seven soldiers
who fight together as one.
‐Genki: Hmm.
‐Yeah.
‐Shogun, here's to making
dreams come true.
‐♪ Mon‐mon‐mon‐monsters‐‐
Monsters rule ♪
‐(theme music playing)
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪