♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
That's all of them!
The big one's next.
Legend Cup.
We've sure had our
share of adventures!
Yeah, but we've finally made it.
One last championship, and
we'll have our magic stone!
Yay, 'chi!
Yeah, nothing's
gonna stop us now.
(together)
Yeah!
Look at the time!
Why didn't you
wake me up sooner?
Oh, how am I
gonna explain myself
to General Durahan this time?
(grunting)
It's inexcusable to sleep in,
but won't you allow me to pretty
myself up for you General?
You're too lovely
to need cosmetics,
and with a charming
smile like yours,
how could I be angry?
Oh, General Durahan!
He'll be wrapped
around my finger.
You don't really
think he's gonna fall
for that amateur act, do you?
What did you say to me?
I'll show you the proper
way to approach him.
Oh, General Durahan,
please forgive me!
Hmm, that's pathetic.
This is much better.
General Durahan.
General Durahan!
‐General Durahan.
‐General Durahan!
General Durahan!
(together)
Gobi, which of us sounds cuter?
Ugh!
‐It's me, isn't it?
‐No, I'm way cuter!
(whimpering)
(crying)
♪
General Durahan!
You slept in, Mum Mew.
(chuckling)
I suppose you're wondering
about Genki and the others.
Stop that!
I already have them surrounded.
Forgive me, oh, Great One.
I've dispatched one of
my most cunning henchmen,
and I know he will return
with my mystery disk.
My, I can hardly wait!
(growling)
(evil laughter)
♪
Man, I could sure use some chow.
We ran out of food last night,
so we'll have to
wait for breakfast
till we get to the next town.
Unless of course we find a
buffet laid out in the forest!
Yeah, sure, Suezo, like
that's ever gonna happen.
♪
‐There it is.
‐My buffet!
Stay back, Suezo!
♪
(gasping)
Pit trap very obvious.
I can't believe someone
actually fell for that.
Oh, that's hilarious.
(laughing)
My intelligence is no secret,
but this time I
really outdid myself
with this ingenious trap!
I know these guys, and we don't
stand a chance against them.
Why'd we have to bring
this stuff with us, anyway?
Yo, boys, Mew is frozen,
so maybe his brain
isn't working yet.
Why you just standing there?
Let's get that mystery disk!
(yelling)
Lightning Attack!
(groaning)
Let's get 'em, Mocchi!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
♪
Tornado Attack!
(groaning)
See ya!
♪
(panting)
Are you okay, Granny?
First of all, I'm not a granny!
Second, mind your own business.
Ohh.
This all Golem's fault, Granny.
Very sorry.
I might be able to help.
Can I check your back?
This is hardly the first
time I've put my back out.
Leave me alone.
♪
Oh, what do you
think you're doing?
Golem take Granny
home and fix back.
I told you I don't
need your help!
Quit fighting it, Granny.
Why don't you just
let us take you home?
Stop calling me Granny!
I have a name and that
happens to be Rosetta!
Rosetta, nice name, Granny!
Hmm?
What rosy cheeks
you have, Granny!
Better to see you with.
(groaning)
♪
She sure had a lot
of veggies on her.
She must have at least
a ten‐day supply here!
It's only enough for tonight.
It is?
Granny, you should
watch your calories.
Who said I was going to eat it?
That's for my
restaurant customers.
Restaurant?
♪
Oh, hmm, ah!
Enough of this idling.
Hold on, Rosetta, you shouldn't
be working in your condition.
Who asked you, sonny boy?
Golem help Rosetta do cooking!
Oh, no, you won't!
Golem's dream is to
become a cook someday.
That's why he's offering.
Gol.
Hmm, I saw what you
did back in the forest,
and I don't need any tornado
attacks here in my kitchen.
You'd still be there
if it weren't for us.
A little pepper of gratitude
wouldn't hurt, Granny.
If you remember, I asked
you people not to help.
This is getting personal!
Let's stop wasting our time.
Move out, gang.
Wait, Tiger!
Hold on.
Here.
(cheering)
Leftovers from lunchtime.
Oh, Granny, you shouldn't have.
Now I don't suppose you
have one without peppers.
Don't eat the thing if it
isn't good enough for ya!
I'm so hungry right now,
even a gumboot topping
would go down good.
I'm digging in!
♪
Hey, are you gonna
make it, Suezo?
Ahh!
‐Now that's pizza!
‐Let's see.
♪
Whoa, that's scrumptious!
Come off it, you people.
Don't you have any pride at all?
You try, 'chi!
(growling)
(grunting)
Told you it was good, Tiger.
(panting)
♪
Delicious!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Gray Wolf and Tiger,
brothers but foes ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Golem doesn't think
fighting solves woes ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Join up with Hare
who likes a good box ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ He's the team planner,
smart like a fox ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Some of them friendly,
some of them not ♪
♪ 400 monsters, which
ones have you got? ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Rosetta, teach
Golem to make pizza!
Calm down, boulder boy,
you're starting to scare me!
Golem be very good
student, promise!
This is ludicrous.
I've gotta get going
on my meal prep‐‐ow!
Back out again?
Yeah, but I got a
lot of work to do
before the dinner
crowd gets here.
You're in no shape to
do dinner on your own.
Why don't you let Golem
help you do the cooking?
This is my restaurant,
and you keep your grubby
hands away from my pizza!
Rosetta!
Golem help!
♪
Why won't anyone listen to me?!
(humming)
Consider yourself lucky
that I'm letting you help,
'cause it's a first and last.
Quit manhandling
the dough already
and do it the way
I told you before!
I need five pizzas
and two spaghettis.
'Kay.
Oh, where do these
customers keep coming from?
♪
Now concentrate on
your fingertip and twirl.
♪
‐Not like that!
‐Uh‐oh.
Golem's causing more
trouble than he's worth.
Come on, Granny, where's
that pizza I ordered?
What's taking so long?
That's enough of your grumbling!
No pizza for you!
You call this a restaurant?
‐Hey, where are you going?
‐'chi.
She probably put
her back out again!
You think she'll make it
to the cook‐off tomorrow?
What cook‐off is that?
You should think
about retiring, Granny!
Be on your way, young man!
♪
Customers gone, 'chi!
Over half of my customers come
here for my specialty pizza!
They leave if I don't have any.
Golem's fault there no pizza.
Mhm.
So what's this cook‐off
that guy was talking about?
Once a year, all the
restaurant owners in the area
get together for a competition
to test their cooking skills!
Now that's something
I wouldn't wanna miss!
Your pizza is so delicious,
I'm sure it would win that
annual cook‐off hands down!
Sure it would‐‐
I've won every time
for the last few years!
I've got a secret
ingredient in my sauce,
and that's why my
pizza can't be beat!
Now if only my back would
get better by morning,
then I could make the dough
and go into the contest.
Golem help Rosetta.
I don't think so.
I've already seen what
you do to my dough.
Golem stay up all
night and learn!
You haven't convinced me so far.
Golem do it, try very hard!
Mhm.
♪
(snoring)
Do it right if you're
serious about this!
Stand up straight,
put your back into it!
I don't care how tired you are,
keep twirling till I
tell you when to stop!
(grunting)
♪
Pass me that jar
down from the shelf?
♪
Now you see this?
This is my secret
flavoring that no other chef
has ever been able to duplicate.
♪
Here, have a taste.
Mmm!
Gol, that good!
This golden mushroom only
grows in the springtime
in the nearby mountains.
It's the secret ingredient that
makes my pizza so delectable.
But don't ever tell a soul!
Gol.
(chuckling)
We gotta use our domes and
come up with some kind of plan!
What kind of plan?
Just leave the
planning to me, Clays!
Shh!
I just thought of
something brilliant!
But we'll have to wait
until those two fall asleep.
♪
Look good!
Let's see how it tastes.
♪
Wow, it's not too
bad for a first try.
(laughing)
The contest isn't over yet!
We'll have to do a whole
lot better than this to win!
Gol.
Now let's get some sleep
and rest up for tomorrow.
Golem no rest.
Golem stay here,
practice more making pizza!
Well, I'm going to bed.
Just make sure you
get up in time tomorrow.
♪
(yawning)
Ooh, I'm so sleepy!
♪
(snoring)
Wake up!
Wake up, Golem, please!
Oh, good morning, Rosetta!
Listen, Golem,
where's my secret jar?
Up on the shelf where Golem‐‐
Oh?
‐What's going on?
‐'chi?
Secret jar not on shelf.
‐Jar?
‐Secret ingredients jar!
'chi?
Golem, what's that
sign on your back?
Huh?
Come to the forest clearing
with the mystery disk
if you want to get
back your precious pot?
Only hours before
the last cook‐off
and my luck has run out.
I'm getting old now and my
back's giving me a lot of grief,
so I figured I'd
make one last go
at the cooking competition.
You mean you're not going?
No, Rosetta no give up!
Golem try hard and
win cooking contest!
But how?
You don't have the secret sauce.
We're gonna get your jar back!
Come on, let's go!
Hold on, we've
gotta find some way
to get Rosetta's jar back
without having to hand over
the mystery disk to the Baddies.
Hare have some plan, 'chi?
I have a plan that
I think might work.
♪
Hey, welcome to the
Great Annual Cook‐Off,
the day chefs in town battle
it out skillet to skillet
for a chance at
this elusive title!
The chefs will only have
until that sundial's shadow
hits that red mark to
make their creations!
Don't freeze up on me
now when I need ya most!
The contest is gonna start!
I wonder if they'll
make it back on time.
My idea's brilliant, and
it's working perfectly!
I knew it would.
But I'm the one who
came up with this plan!
Ahh!
Here they come!
♪
Stop, we'll exchange
the goods in the center.
I'm going in.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let the cook‐off begin!
(cheering)
♪
‐No, not yet!
‐Huh?
Knead it some more
before you roll it out!
Hand over the jar!
Sure, right after we
get the mystery disk.
♪
Here, now the jar!
I got it, I got it!
I got the mystery disk!
And it wasn't
even brain science!
What are you doing?
Grab the disk and get
away from the enemy!
Oops!
Oh, no, you don't!
Hold on, you better check that
jar before we go any further.
Check it?
♪
It's just a drawing!
‐What?
‐Figures.
Then where's‐‐
(tires squealing)
Hey, come back here!
That's it, that's the way!
Shape the dough, nice and even.
(groaning)
Oh, back bad again?
Oh!
(gasping)
Look what you did!
A good chef must always
keep his eye on the dough!
Golem worry about you!
You're getting a bit too mushy.
This is important, so
stop worrying about me
and concentrate on
what you're doing.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
(groaning)
(panting)
Stop right there!
Take a look at that!
(laughing)
♪
Mocchi!
No, don't pull it!
(yelling)
(laughing)
‐Clays.
‐We don't have time for this!
♪
The other teams already
have their dishes in the oven.
What's taking Golem and Rosetta
so long with the pizza dough?
Let's move on to the
sauce and finish it up.
♪
Gol?
A different kind of mushroom,
but I hope they'll
taste the same.
But Rosetta!
We don't have time to argue!
We're using them, end of story!
No!
What do you think you're doing?
Move it!
This not Rosetta's famous sauce!
Wait for Genki!
They come back soon!
Sure of that?
Thanks for the
mystery disk, suckers!
Is this the real
jar or isn't it?
Check it for yourself.
You'll be able to tell.
‐We didn't need it anymore.
‐Since we got the mystery disk!
Maybe you should check that
mystery disk before you go.
Hmm?
This mystery disk
smells vaguely familiar.
Mmm.
How'd you like
Holly's mystery cookie?
You tricked us!
♪
Come on, guys,
let's get out of here!
(together)
Yeah!
♪
(yelling)
This'll teach ya!
Ahh!
He's getting ready to use
that lightning
attack thing again!
Run for it!
(yelling)
The finished dishes are
starting to roll in now,
and judges are busy
tasting them all!
What do we have here?
Rosetta, the reigning champion,
has stopped cooking her pizza!
Genki and the others
better show up pretty soon!
I think it'd still be too late.
Make way, coming through.
♪
Got it, 'chi!
Golem, let's make that sauce!
Gol!
♪
Golem, take it out!
And the time is up!
Oh, we made it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I will now announce
this year's new champion!
Let's give a big
round of applause
to the pizza queen
of the region,
our very own Rosetta!
(cheering)
(laughing)
You win, Rosetta!
Yeah, thanks to you.
No, Golem do nothing.
Rosetta win because
her pizza best!
Thanks for your help, Golem.
♪
Rosetta, Golem never
forget your cooking.
I'm not real big on
these mushy farewells.
If you have to go,
be on your way.
Come on, let's get going, gang.
‐See ya sometime, Rosetta.
‐'chi!
‐See you around, Granny!
‐Bye, Rosetta.
♪
Hang on, Golem!
Huh?
Take this.
♪
It's for when you open
your own restaurant.
♪
Chef hat.
Thanks, Rosetta!
Let's have a look
What is it, Golem,
what'd she give you?
It's secret, no tell you!
Golem show you when
open own restaurant.
No fair, let's see it!
No, Golem's secret.
Wait, come back here!
‐Please?
‐No.
‐For me?
‐No!
‐Come on!
‐No.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪