♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Mum Mew, Gobi,
show me the highlights
of the Legend Cup so far.
♪
(cheering)
(grunting)
♪
Feel out your enemy.
Think with your heart!
(grunting)
♪
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
Yeah!
Mocchi Cannon!
(yelping)
This can't be happening!
♪
Knockout, the match
goes to Mocchi!
♪
So, now only one battle remains
between Most and Mocchi.
Yes, it's scheduled
for tomorrow.
Yeah.
Either way the match ends,
they'll both be
exhausted afterward.
That'll make it easier
to steal the magic stone
and the Mystery Disk.
This plan of yours
is rather underhanded.
It suits me just fine.
Oh, General Durahan,
no need for thanks.
‐It's my job.
‐Yeah, yeah.
Ha, we'd already have the disk
if it weren't for you.
And you'd be out of a job
if it weren't for
that act of yours.
(grunting)
Stop this, both of you!
Apologies.
Our real battle will commence
once theirs has ended.
We must conserve
our energy until then.
Morning is about to break;
the time is drawing nearer.
(crazed laughter)
♪
(chuckling)
Seeing this much food
all at once sure does
make a guy feel good inside.
You said it, the stomach part
of my insides is feeling
especially happy.
You've both got the wrong idea.
This food all belong to Mocchi.
You can't be serious.
Mocchi needs to eat lots
and build up his strength
before the match.
Don't even think about
trying to take something.
(groans)
Hmm, what?
That's Most.
Huh?
Double‐Pounder,
Double‐Pounder‐‐
Mocchi.
What do you think
you're doing, Mocch?
You promised to stop working out
and rest up before
the big match, remember?
Mocchi battle Most, 'chi!
No time to rest now, 'chi!
Mocchi?
Mocchi know how strong
Most is, 'chi!
Discard your outer shell
and become one with nature.
(grunting)
Aurora Attack!
♪
(grunting)
Double‐Pounder,
Double‐Pounder‐‐
Yo, gang, you know
that poster?
It's about
a public sparring match
that Most is sponsoring.
Public sparring match?
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the charity
sparring match.
The donations we receive
from today's event
will be used to build
a gymnasium for young boys
and girls, as well
as monsters who want
to fight in future
monster battles.
Our first challenger is
a monster of incredible speed:
Rock Saurian!
Each match
is three minutes long.
Let the match commence!
(growling)
Ready, fight!
(ding)
(growls)
♪
We have a winner!
(cheering)
He's fast.
What a move.
'chi.
Next, we have
the heavyweight champ, Titan!
A Golem Titan!
He looks strong.
Yo, Most, you're
gonna regret this!
♪
Ready, fight!
Oh, no.
♪
That's the match!
(cheering)
He lifted Titan
as if he were paper.
I've never seen
that kind of power.
(grumbles)
For this match,
Most has requested
that he be pitted against
two opponents at once!
What, he's gonna fight two?
So, battling one monster
at a time isn't even a challenge
in Most's mind.
And now, Rocky Fur
with his dreaded Dragon Kick
and Gaboo Soldier with his
frightful Dragon Knuckle!
♪
Most, you think you
can take us both on?
This might be a charity event,
but I gave at the door!
Ready?
Fight!
(growling)
♪
Dragon Kick!
Dragon Knuckle!
♪
Double‐Pounder!
That's the match!
(cheering)
Incredible.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Don't pet Jagd Hound
'cause he will attack ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Unless he decides
to do a backtrack ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Half horse and half man,
Chariot will fight ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Any old creature
he finds in his sight ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ If you were End Bringer,
would you call it a day ♪
♪ I wouldn't bet on it;
forget it, no way ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
I knew Most was supposed
to be strong, but still.
♪
Yeah, that was intimidating.
Most is fast and powerful.
He stays so calm
during the match.
His mental control's impressive
and his offense and defense.
He has all aspects mastered.
What would you do
if you were fighting him?
If I were fighting him?
I dunno, I have no idea.
How could he have beaten
two strong opponents with just
a Double‐Pounder?
He didn't even use
his Cherry Blossom Blizzard
or his Mocchi Cannon,
or Aurora Attack.
What are we gonna do?
No worry, 'chi!
Huh?
First time Mocchi
see Most in person,
that when Mocchi first decide
to become strong, 'chi.
Mocchi.
Most is Mocchi's hero.
Now Mocchi has chance
to face in ring!
Mocchi's so happy, 'chi.
I guess you should be.
Sorry, Mocch, I shouldn't have
got so down about the match.
Our only chance is to face Most
together with all we've got.
(all muttering agreement)
♪
(rainfall)
They've put the match
on rain delay for now.
But if it keeps
raining like this,
the whole thing
will be postponed.
I see.
Might be better to postpone it.
That would give Mocchi
some more time to rest up
before the big match, at least.
Go!
But Mocchi
wanna fight today, 'chi!
If no match, then Mocchi
lose tension, chi!
Atta boy, if you
go in there today,
you'll stay all worked up
for the big match tomorrow.
Hmm?
(all gasping)
Most!
Mind if I come in?
No, of course not.
♪
Mocchi, you've obviously
become much stronger
since the last time we met.
'chi?
You've managed to win
six monster battle tournaments
and you've made it
to the Legend Cup.
You couldn't do that
without some kind
of supernatural strength.
What exactly
are you getting at?
Hmm?
♪
The truth is, I'm concerned.
Concerned?
As I mentioned,
I wanted to have a good,
fair match with Mocchi,
but, well, that was until
I started to worry.
What's that supposed to mean?
A long time ago
in the Legend Cup,
I was pitted against an opponent
who reminds me a lot of Mocchi.
(grunting)
♪
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
(grunting)
♪
He was a strong opponent
and I used all
my strength on him.
I regret turning him
into a Lost Disk.
(gasping)
♪
Mocchi, what would you say
to forfeiting the match?
Huh?
We're both
monster battle contenders,
so I know how important
this match is to you,
but if anything bad
were to happen to you,
I couldn't forgive myself.
On the other hand,
if you backed out of the match,
you could continue
improving your skills,
but consider the alternative.
♪
'chi.
Most, thank you
for worrying about Mocchi.
And will you forfeit the match?
Uh‐uh.
Mocchi defeat many monsters
to battle in championships
and get to Legend Cup!
Mocchi disgrace those monsters
if Mocchi back out now
without trying, 'chi.
Mmm, I see.
Then, I'll see you
in the ring, Mocchi.
Have good match, 'chi.
♪
Mocchi.
(all awwing)
♪
(fireworks bursting)
(groaning)
♪
The rain has stopped.
Agh, Gobi, Poison, get up!
♪
I'm so gorgeous.
Quit blabbering and hurry up
or we'll miss the Legend Cup!
Legend Cup.
I'm a legend.
Gobi have another helping?
Get up, you fool!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the skies have cleared
over Torble Stadium
and we're all very excited
to be here at the climax
of the monster battles,
the Legend Cup!
(cheering)
The challenger
has scraped his way
through all six prelims
and has already defeated
one of the defending
champs, Poritoka!
I give you Mocchi!
And now, the final
reigning champ
standing between Mocchi
and the title,
presenting Most!
(cheering)
Mocchi try hard, 'chi!
Golem root for you!
We're with you
in spirit, Mocchi!
Don't take any chances, Mocch.
Play it safe out there!
Don't push yourself too hard!
Come on, Mocchi!
Both contenders to the center!
Good luck.
Mocchi fight!
♪
This match will have
no time limits;
it's a no‐holds‐barred
one‐game match
with a 10‐count
determining a knockout.
Ready?
We made it on time.
Look, they're down
there in the ring.
May the worst man win.
Please, be so tired
after the match
you won't even notice us!
Ready, fight!
(ding)
♪
(grunts)
Double‐Pounder!
You can do it, Mocchi!
♪
Mocchi, use your Mocchi Roll
now and shake things up!
♪
Do it!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
Behind you!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
(gasping)
In the last Legend Cup,
Most's Cherry Blossom Blizzard
knocked out
the infamous BattleRocks
in a single blow!
Mocchi's courage usually
gets him out of a tight spot,
but is it enough
to save him this time?
Mocchi!
(grunting)
Use my energy as your own.
♪
Eight!
Nine!
Can you continue?
Yeah, 'chi!
Fight!
(grunting)
So, you use your friend's energy
to increase your courage,
that's why you're so strong.
Double‐Pounder!
(nervous tittering)
♪
Double‐Pounder!
'chi!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
(grunting)
He got him!
♪
You've got courage.
Now he's turning things around!
Most is finally starting
to feel threatened.
No, he's starting to realize
just how strong Mocchi is.
(grunting)
Double‐Pounder!
Did you see that,
ladies and gentlemen?
Mocchi has managed
to surprise Most
with an outstanding
Double‐Pounder!
That's the way, Mocchi,
now make sure you keep on him.
Double‐Pounder,
Double‐Pounder!
(grunts)
Oh, no!
Mocchi, don't give up!
♪
Keep at him, Mocchi!
I never used to think much
of his Double‐Pounder.
All that training
has really paid off!
Four, five, can you continue?
Of course I can!
Most getting nervous.
That's good.
Go for it!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
Aurora Attack!
Wow, Most has finally
unleashed his ultimate weapon,
the Aurora Attack!
Genki, you've gotta pull Mocchi
out of the ring before he really
gets hurt out there!
I know that.
No, Genki!
Huh?
Mocchi.
(grunting)
Mocchi fight.
That a boy!
Mocchi!
You can do it!
Don't give up!
Tiger, Suezo,
Golem, and Hare.
♪
I know you can do it, Mocchi.
Holly.
Now, summon your courage!
(grunts)
♪
Can you continue?
'chi!
I can see how much
this match means to you.
Then I'll give it
everything I've got.
Show me how much
courage you have.
(grunting)
♪
Aurora Attack!
(cheering)
I don't believe my eyes!
Mocchi has also mastered
the Aurora Attack!
One, two, three‐‐
That was perfect.
But Mocchi's used up
all his energy.
Six!
Seven!
Can you continue?
Thank you, Most!
Now Mocchi can use
Aurora Attack as well, 'chi!
Fight!
♪
Mocchi, your courage is
all that'll help you now.
Use your courage.
Double‐Pounder,
Double‐Pounder!
(grunting)
Double‐Pounder,
Double‐Pounder!
(nervous tittering)
♪
(panting)
Let's go.
'chi.
♪
(cheering)
One, two,
three‐‐
Mocchi!
Mocch!
(gasping)
Nine...
ten!
Knockout, the match
goes to Most!
(bell dinging)
(laughs)
No!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪