(magical music)
(thunder cracking)
(suspenseful music)
(groaning)
- What could make Meicoomon more furious
than having to watch her human partner suffer?
That's it Meicoomon, let the fury burn inside you.
Give yourself up to the transformation.
(groaning)
Let the anger bloom.
Let it grow.
(groaning)
(gasps)
Digivolve or you partner dies.
Digivolve into your true form and then destroy this world.
This world into which
you should never have been born in the first place.
(eerie music)
CHAPTER 5 COEXISTENCE
(birds fluttering)
- [Meicoomon] Meiko where are you?
1999 FALL TOTTORI PREFECTURE
(peaceful music)
- Meicoomon, answer me please.
(bush rustling)
Huh?
Oh.
Meicoomon, is that you?
Hello, is somebody there?
- Meiko.
- Thank goodness, I'm so happy to see you, Meicoomon.
I was so worried.
Now it's all better.
- I was really scared.
- [Meiko] Well don't worry, you're safe now.
- [Meicoomon] Can we go home?
- [Meiko] You got it.
You know, sometimes I get scared out here too.
(water drips)
- [Meiko's Mom] Your dad will be home any minute Meiko.
You should try to finish washing up soon.
- She was really dirty from all
that running around out there.
We like playing in the woods, huh?
- Yeah.
- Let's keep your little adventure a secret okay?
- You heard her Meicoomon, quiet, shh.
- Shh.
(giggles)
- (gasps) Meiko.
- Yeah, Mom?
- [Meiko's Mom] What happened?
Did you get hurt?
- Huh?
What are you talking about?
- These, look.
They look like blood stains.
- Huh, but who from?
(laughing)
I don't see anything wrong with her.
- [Meiko's Mom] Then what did this?
- [Meiko] More testing?
Meicoomon's fine,
why do you have to take her back to the lab?
- It's all routine now.
Don't worry, I just wanna make sure she's healthy.
Some of the people from the Tokyo Research Group
will also be there to observe.
We won't be gone more than a couple of days.
(slurping)
- [Scientist] It's turned into a monster!
Quick!
Seal the lab!
- [Meiko] What did they do to you?
What's going on?
Father?
- Call the cops! - No.
No outsiders.
(growling)
- Get out of here, Meiko.
(grunting)
(gasping)
- Where am I?
- Poor thing.
- Meiko!
I missed you so much.
- I'm right here.
Everything's fine now.
Father, you're hurt.
Did she--
- [Meiko's Father] It's nothing.
But clearly there are still things
we don't know about her.
(yelling)
(lightening striking) (grunting)
- You should never have existed,
but I was waiting for you to be born.
And now that you're here, you shall do exactly
what you were born to do.
You will be the one who destroys the world.
(dramatic music)
- [Digimon] What are those things things again?
- Daigo and Durtles.
- Durtles sounds kind of dorky.
- Petals sounds pretty.
- As he would know exactly what to call them.
- The portals.
- [Digimons] That's what they're called.
- [Boy] Is that our world?
- [Digimon] Look at all the Digimon.
(groaning)
- Meicoomon, is that you?
Come back!
Don't go.
You belong here with me.
Don't believe anything Gennai says to you.
Please.
(screaming)
(gasping)
(grunting)
- What are you doing?
She was gonna kill you!
(growling)
- What's going on with Meicoomon?
- I don't know.
- She's gonna be the one who destroys the world.
- What are you talking about?
- That's what Gennai said.
He's figured out a way to manipulate her.
- [Tai] What?
- Meicoomon should never even have been born.
He told her that.
- Don't repeat anything that creep says.
He's a big liar!
There are no Digimon who should never have been born.
- You're right, but I don't think there's
any mystery in what he's doing.
If Meicoomon shows up with that much destructive power--
- [Matt] Look over there.
There are hundreds of Digimon on the move.
- [Boy] Are they all going to Earth?
- [Girl] That can't be good.
- [Woman] Oh, hey, wait a minute.
- [Man] What's the problem with
the number six satellite feed?
Our communication link just went down.
Is there an error in the system?
- [Man] It's not just the satellite, sir,
we've lost the GPS signal, too.
We have power but it's not letting me
re-establish contact.
- Comm is completely frozen, sir.
Global satellites don't seem to be communicating.
All systems are down.
One by one the satellites are going offline.
- [Man] All right, then, manual override.
Shut it down.
Reboot the system.
- There's just too much data pouring in.
- Is this really happening?
Is it really possible that the digital world
and the human world are both changing?
I'm so glad.
You are reborn.
Tapirmon.
You were lost, but finally, thanks to Homeostasis,
you are back again.
And I know you don't remember me now, but you will.
Because in the end you and I are partners.
Partners forever.
This time I will be chosen.
This time you and I are going to save the world.
We'll be together again just as we used to be.
(chuckling)
I'll find you again.
And this time, I'll never lose you.
Never.
ABNORMALITIES IN ELECTRONIC DEVICES AROUND THE GLOBE
- Now this.
Scientists at the national laboratory
are confirming that weather satellites around
the world have been malfunctioning.
And Fall seismology readings have been
reported near mysterious digital surges.
New Digimon sightings have also been reported,
and for the sake of public safety,
certain regions have been ordered to evacuate.
ABNORMALITIES IN ELECTRONIC DEVICES AROUND THE GLOBE
So far no one has been hurt by the activity.
And Digimon sightings have become a source
of public curiosity and speculation.
- I figure they'll probably all fly to Paris next.
- That's where I'd wanna go if I were a Digimon.
- Hi, we have a poll at school to see who
can predict where Digimon will show up next.
- I got a text but there's no number.
Whoa, is this some kind of joke?
And now it won't even let me delete it.
This phone is all jacked up.
(groans)
- [Boy] What's with this game, man?
It's going all wonky all of a sudden.
- [Boy] Whoa, I've never seen that screen before.
- [Boy] How'd you do that?
- [Homeostasis Voiceover] Humans are unnecessary.
They are a virus.
They must be destroyed.
- I know Himekawa isn't here, I don't know where she went.
Look, why aren't we getting any updates
at all on what's going on?
Listen up, the kids are still in the digital world.
Are you there?
(grunting)
What a mess.
(yelling)
(hissing)
DIGIMON APPEARING ALL OVER THE GLOBE
- Thanks.
I'm coming to you live from our action news helicopter
with reports that Digimon sightings
are now confirmed across the world.
Authorities are closely monitoring the situation.
- [Man] More satellites are failing, sir.
We're losing communication control.
- Run the diagnostic again.
- I'm trying, sir.
- Sir, the grid.
It's down.
- It's getting worse.
What is going on?
(beeping)
DIGIMON APPEARING ALL OVER THE GLOBE
- [Reporter] Why have the Digimon suddenly
appeared in such numbers?
Many nations are calling for emergency meetings
to discuss this latest crisis.
- Oh, kids, are you okay?
I feel so helpless.
But I know you're both fine and you'll come
home safe and sound to me.
And I promise I'll make you the best home-coming meal ever.
- [Reporter] Our next story explores the surprising spike--
(sirens wailing)
- [Reporter] The government has not declared
a state of emergency as no casualties have been reported.
GOVERNMENT RESPONDS TO DAMAGE CAUSED BY DIGIMON ACROSS REGIONS
Top level officials are currently meeting with experts
from across the globe to initiate a plan of action.
- What are they gonna talk about without you there, doctor?
No one knows more about what's going on.
One good thing; at least they don't consider
this to be a critical situation yet.
- [Doctor] Of course it is.
- Oh?
- I already know what's going on
because it's happened before.
- [Daigo] Tell me.
- Meicoomon's the key.
EMERGENCY TALKS OVER APPROACHING CRISIS!
- Exactly.
How many times are these creatures gonna run amok
through our cities like some gang of juvenile delinquents?
- The question is, why do they do it?
- Because those monstrous beasts lack any heart or soul.
- The real problem clearly lies with
our increasing reliance on digital technology.
We've allowed computers to take over our lives.
- And all of us have kids at home who
would rather play on their cell phones than eat.
- I'm sure you're familiar with the concept
of symbiosis where two individuals adopt each other's moods.
I've observed recently that Meicoomon and Meiko are aligned.
Not only that, it looks like this connection
is growing even stronger and becoming dangerous.
Meicoomon's become a violent creature
when they've been separated in the past
and then calmed down again when Meiko is present.
- Doctor, if what you say is true,
then Meicoomon isn't even a Digimon.
- [Doctor] No, she is a Digimon.
But there is no doubt she is unusual.
- And much too powerful. (gasping)
- Hackmon.
- Who is this?
- He's a messenger for Homeostasis.
Is that why you've come?
Are you here to protect Meicoomon?
- I think you may have the wrong idea
about the purpose of Homeostasis.
- You want harmony.
Don't you need Meicoomon for that?
- [Hackmon] The Libra has been unstable since it was born.
- Who is Libra?
- Meicoomon is Libra.
- A part of Apoclymon's data is contained in the Libra.
That shard is from a dark corner of the digital world.
The Libra's powers have made her an outcast.
The only thing limits the Libra's destructive power
has been the presence of a partner.
That connection contains the Libra's power
from exploding into its fearsome potential.
The partner maintains balance.
- Meiko stabilizes her, then.
- That's right.
- Now it makes sense.
Whenever my daughter and her Digimon are together,
Meicoomon is happy and the perfect companion.
But when they're apart, like when Meiko is at school,
Meicoomon tends to get upset, even dangerous.
- That's why it was important to keep
the Libra and her human partner connected.
Because its unsuppressed power is vast.
If it becomes uncontained it will strike
with relentless force.
Then the Libra's destructive power will
be so great that she will no longer recognize a partner
and she will stop responding to Meiko.
(groaning)
Perhaps she already has.
Events would suggest it.
And as the Libra's power grows, it threatens stability.
- What a mess.
Man.
- [Doctor] Oh, Meiko.
My poor daughter.
- [Hackmon] She carries a heavy burden on her shoulders.
Even for one who is a DigiDestined.
(screaming)
(thudding)
(groaning)
- Enough!
Wow, that really hurt.
How in any world could that even happen?
We all ran right off a cliff like a bunch of lemmings.
- It's like someone yanked the ground
out from one of us while we were running.
- I think that's exactly what happened
and Meicoomon's part of it.
But this goes beyond just the reboot.
- At this point we don't even know where she is.
(rumbling) (gasping)
(cracking)
(roaring) (screaming)
- Uh oh. - You've gotta be kidding.
- [Digimon] Allow us!
- You guys, get to someplace safe.
- We got this!
(panting)
(screaming)
- Let me go. - Hey, watch it, get off!
(panting)
- Biyomon, thank you.
- Help, they got us! - We're up here!
- [Meiko] And getting higher!
- Oh no, hang on!
Pepper Breath!
(groaning)
- [Tentomon] Sorry about the landing.
Yet, you held onto your computer.
- Good thing.
- Are you all right?
- Thanks to you, I am.
- Those vines, they were like ropes.
- Yeah.
- That was bizarre.
- Let's get outta here. - Huh?
Oh, sure.
Right away.
(grunting)
Thanks, Tai.
- This way.
(panting) (grass rustling)
Okay!
Wrong way! (screaming)
(groaning)
- I'm definitely gonna need a spa day after this.
- [Digimon] Mimi?
- Who's that?
- Your legs are--
- Fine, I landed on something soft.
- Glad I broke your fall.
(screaming)
- I'm sorry.
- Ouch. - Look around, guys.
Is anything else about to attack us?
- It doesn't look like it.
Remember the first time we came to this area?
Didn't Kuwagamon attack us in this very same place?
- But we sure weren't attacked by a bunch
of strange plants before.
- It hates us.
(gasping)
We don't belong here.
The digital world, it hates us.
(dramatic music) - But what do you mean?
- [Kari] It thinks we're in the way.
We're nothing but a nuisance.
- [T.K] How did we become a nuisance to
the entire digital world?
- So, are you going to tell us how to control Meicoomon?
There's gotta be something her partner can do.
What do we do to stop this thing?
- [Hackmon] You can't.
Time is up.
The judgment has been made.
(light music)
- It became night so quickly.
The sun was out just a minute ago.
- You're right.
But is this really nighttime?
I'm not sure what to believe anymore.
- So sad.
If we didn't know what they were,
those Digimon would look like shooting stars.
- If they were shooting stars, I'd wish for a ride home.
- But we've gotta find a way outta here.
And find Meicoomon.
- Hey, Izzy.
Have you made any progress on getting us home to our world?
- [Izzy] I've been running searches since we got here
trying to find a portal or some other way out
but no dice.
- I'm sorry.
(gasping)
It's true, this is my fault.
- Oh, not this again!
- [Meiko] You're just too nice to say so.
But we all know what happened.
- [Joe] We may know what happened,
but we still don't know why.
So how can it be your fault?
- [Meiko] I'm Meicoomon's partner and I couldn't stop her.
I couldn't' do anything, and now look where we are.
I don't know what's happening.
Are we not partners anymore?
- Just because you're partners doesn't mean
you're not gonna have hard times.
It takes work.
Both of you have to try or your bond could be broken.
Permanently.
- [Sora] It's a two way street.
- Yeah.
That's the truth.
You have to listen to each other.
- It can be tough.
Even I'm not perfect all of the time.
But our faults balance each other out.
- That's right.
That's why we have partners.
- [Meiko] I've watched all of you with your partners.
Even though your connections may be different,
they all seem to work so well.
Your ties are strong.
I don't know, maybe Meicoomon and I
just don't have a good connection.
- Oh, Meiko.
You never give yourself a break.
Look where you are.
You would not of come all this way
if you weren't partners.
That is a strong connection.
- Yeah, but, what if that's the problem?
If that's why she transformed?
- What are you saying?
- I think I'm what's wrong here.
- What? - Oh.
- Why me?
What was I chosen to do?
I can't do anything to help her
and now Meicoomon's become this.
This--
- Oh, Mei Mei.
(screaming)
- [Meiko] I'm scared.
If I'm not the right person, why was I chosen?
Someone else, someone better
should have been Meicoomon's partner.
But I was chosen, and now I've caused everything
to go so wrong.
It's all my fault.
(gasping)
- You're forgetting something.
Because you were chosen, we're friends,
and we'll be friends forever.
That's why we're all here together.
(light music)
- Don't close yourself off, Meiko.
It never works out.
Loneliness is tough.
It grows like a thorn in your heart.
Fight it off and let us in.
We're here for you.
- Meiko, listen.
Meicoomon will come back to you
because your feelings for her are that strong.
There's no getting around it.
You two are partners through thick and thin.
- I hope so.
I hope she believes it.
I miss her so much.
- [Meicoomon] Meiko, dun dun.
(fire crackling)
- [Kari] You'll just have to have faith in Meicoomon
and in yourself, don't let those doubts creep in.
They'll only make you weak and none
of us can afford that right now.
If you still feel connected to her,
then you can still help her.
I know this has been a hard time for you.
We all understand, even though you don't think we do.
But we have to stay strong and stay together.
And when you're feeling weak, you can lean on us.
- [Meiko] I don't even know why
I was chosen to be her partner.
- You keep forgetting that we weren't just chosen,
we were DigiDestined.
(gasping)
- Your problems are ours, too, so let's share them together.
- What are we sharing, guys?
Something delicious, I hope.
- [Gatomon] Go back to sleep.
- What?
(chuckles) - Oh man.
- Figures.
Same as ever.
- Well, if there's no food, then why'd you wake me up?
- He has a point, that was mean.
Next time you talk about sharing something
make sure you've got bacon.
(laughing)
- You know, even though they're not to blame for this,
our Digimon are gonna take the heat for what's happening.
- Yeah, unfortunately.
You're probably right about that, Izzy.
(snoring)
It's a shame, they all put out a 100% for us.
Now it's our turn.
We have to give it 100% just like they did
and fight to protect all of them.
That includes Meicoomon.
(gasping)
As long as we keep on fighting together,
as a team, we'll win.
(humming)
- You gotta believe you and Meicoomon are partners
no matter what might happen.
If she's in your heart, there's still a chance.
- I hope so.
Let's try.
- That's the spirit, let's go rescue her.
- You might as well know.
Homeostasis is now planning to remove the Libra.
- Remove her?
- That's just code.
You mean to eliminate her.
Monstrous.
- [Hackmon] The Libra's out of control,
you've seen it yourself.
The reboot failed to stop her violent attacks.
There is no other choice.
- So you say.
- We now believe the reboot caused
the Libra to undergo some sort of genetic mutation.
- [Daigo] Mutation?
You mean it Digivolved.
- Digi evolution is never completely destructive
the way this has been.
- [Daigo] That's true.
- Therefore, we have to end this now
before Meicoomon's next mutation makes her too strong.
- Aw, come on!
We can't just quit.
We've been trying for months to save Meicoomon.
Now that she's become too powerful,
you wanna throw all that aw-- (phone ringing)
Yes?
Are you serious?
But why wasn't I informed before y--?
Very well.
I understand.
(phone clicking)
- Now what?
- [Daigo] The self defense forces.
They're preparing to send out troops.
- Correct.
Your armed forces are cooperating with us.
(groaning)
Your government agrees that this is
the best way to handle it.
- And you didn't even have the courtesy to tell me?
- Why?
What good would that have done?
Are you just going to watch again as a world meets its end?
Everything you know could go up in flames.
Your entire world is in danger.
What do you suggest?
That we stand by and let it happen?
We will not.
Our goal is harmony and balance,
but sometimes that means making hard choices.
Infections spread and get worse.
All impurities will be dealt with.
- [Daigo] What's Homeostasis trying to do here, doctor?
Why destroy Meicoomon?
Why won't they just let us do our job?
And what was the point of involving the DigiDestined?
Why were all those kids chosen in the first place?
- Listen-- - If you're just going
to cut them off.
And now they're stranded.
(suspenseful music)
(zapping)
(beeping)
(rumbling)
(dramatic music) (alarms ringing)
(screaming)
- [Reporter] In breaking news, reports are flooding in
of a huge explosion into
Green Valley Geothermal Power Plant.
We now go live to our correspondent on the scene.
- There's no confirmation yet,
but witnesses reported a flying Digimon
right before the blast.
You can see the fire behind me is growing
and first responders and fire crews
are already on the scene.
They need to control that fire,
because if it gets any hotter,
additional explosions could result.
(booming)
And if the whole plant blows up,
then in addition to the loss of power,
I'm told that the seismic shock could set off
a chain reaction of volcanic eruptions in the mountains.
So the recent malfunctions of computers and phones
is now spreading to major industries and networks.
What are these Digimon trying to do?
- [Doctor] What was it Hackmon called her?
An impurity?
(rain dripping)
- It was a nice sunny day just a few minutes ago.
- [Tentomon] What is it they say?
Some Digimon feel the rain, but others just get wet.
- Just who have you been talking to?
- [Palmon] Does the rain make me look wilted?
- [Digimon] I wouldn't touch that with a 10 foot horn.
- Hey.
Kari, let me ask you something.
- Huh?
- Earlier you said it's like the digital world is mad at us.
- No, I said the digital world hates us
and wants to get us out of here.
(gasping)
I know it's not actually saying that,
but that's what it feels like to me.
Think about it.
The ground, those vines, now the clouds.
It's like it's all rejecting us.
- [Gatomon] That's not entirely true.
- [Kari] What do you mean, Gatomon?
- We're all part of the digital world
and we're not rejecting you.
- Yeah, I wanna be with you forever!
- Me, too!
You wanna stay with me, don't you?
- [Mimi] Oh, Palmon, of course I do.
- I'm sorry.
I wasn't talking about you guys,
you haven't abandoned us or rejected us.
We're in this together.
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
It's like the digital world is fighting us
the way a body fights back when it gets sick.
- As if we were germs or an infection or something.
- Infection?
- [Izzy] Think about it.
The digital world is sending the elements against us
like it would to a virus it was trying to get rid of.
- I'm no germ!
No way!
- Then this digital world must be different
from the other one we went to.
- Maybe 'cause of the reboot.
- It's possible.
But we don't know if these events are happening naturally
or being done on purpose to get rid of us.
- It doesn't matter.
We're the problem.
Any minute we're going to be cast out of the digital world.
It hates us.
It wants us gone.
- Why, Kari?
Why does the digital world hate us all of a sudden?
- Could it be 'cause it knows that we're the DigiDestined?
No.
(wind howling)
- [Sora] Look, everybody, the rain stopped!
- [Agumon] Well, this is nice.
Dry and steady and safe.
(gasping)
- This is all different, but familiar.
This is the spot where we met Agumon
when we first came to the digital world.
How did we get here?
(zapping)
(screaming)
- [Gennai Voiceover] You don't know it yet,
but soon you will see with your own eyes.
And you'll know you were about to meet your demise.
Together.
(light music)
(gasping)
(groaning)
- [Boy] What was that?
- Where are we?
(light music)
- Are we back home again?
- We are!
We're home!
(gasping)
- Look. - Uh oh.
Can that be?
No, it can't. - Hey, Tai.
Where are we now?
This is weird.
- Uh, don't worry.
- I can't believe it.
- So, this is the human world, huh?
- Are those Digimon?
Hi! (kid crying)
- Are we scary looking?
Or are they crying because we're so cute?
- Maybe that's how they say welcome.
Maybe humans cry all the time.
- Ya think so?
- Well, we can cry if it makes them feel better.
- Wah, nice to meet ya.
- Nice try, but humans say hello same as you.
- Oh, that's a relief.
- Let's go, then.
I wanna make friends with everybody in this world.
- Yeah, me too!
- Hey, you.
What's going on here?
Is there a problem?
- No problem.
Everything is fine here, officer.
- Maybe now's a good time to start crying.
- Don't play me for a fool.
Those are Digimon!
- Come on, let's go.
(gasping)
Run, you guys.
We gotta get outta here!
- [Officer] Code nine, officer needs assistance.
Unidentified kids carrying Digimon near downtown.
- Where are we going?
I can't keep running forever.
- Don't worry.
At this rate we'll never outrun the police.
- Nice, Tai.
Running just makes it look like we're guilty.
- Yet here we are following him.
- If we weren't in trouble before, we are now for sure.
- You may be right, but it's too late to stop now!
- Uh, Tai, could you let go?
I can actually run on my own.
- Oh yeah, my bad.
(panting)
Let's go through this gate.
- [Officer] There they are!
Stop, you kids. - It's locked.
Dead end.
- Uh oh.
Fly away, Biyomon.
- No, I'm staying here.
- Now what?
- We have to hide them.
Hide them all quick, Izzy.
- Yeah, but how?
- This is our world.
Your laptop should work.
- Right.
(dramatic music)
- [Officer] We have you surrounded.
There is no use running.
Remain where you are.
(growling)
- No, Gatomon, don't do anything.
- Why?
I just wanna help.
- [Officer] Easy now, no funny business.
- Looks like we're out of options, Tai.
- Almost got it.
It's open!
Jump, guys!
- Uh, jump where?
- Jump into the screen.
- Hurry up.
- But what about you?
- We'll see you again soon.
Now go.
(grunting)
- This is not gonna look good on my permanent record.
- You oughta be more worried about life in prison.
- Don't even joke around about stuff like that.
- Don't worry, Joe.
They say wearing stripes makes you look thinner.
- [Joe] Don't laugh.
If I'm going, you're all going with me.
- [Officer] I wanna know exactly
what happened to those Digimon.
My officers report that each of you
was seen to have a Digimon accompanying you.
- We were just hanging out with your friends, sir.
- Friends are humans.
- I'll be friends with whoever I want.
- It's not that simple, son.
Digimon are incredibly violent.
- Now, that's just nonsense.
- That's right!
There are lots of good Digimon.
- How can you not know that whole cities
are being destroyed by Digimon all over the entire world?
(gasping)
- The entire world?
- Be more specific.
We've kinda been out of touch.
(knocking on door)
- Daigo Nishijima, management officer, eh?
And what exactly does the government want
with a bunch of kids?
- They're not ordinary kids, detective.
- Well, I'm sorry, but I can't release them
until our investigation is completed.
They were seen with a number of Digimon
but somehow hid them before we got there.
- They felt threatened.
They were just protecting their friends from your men.
- Their friends, huh?
That's the same word they used for those Digimon.
Not a surprise from them, but hearing it from you?
Ridiculous.
- Listen to me.
I represent the Incorporative Administrative Agency's
National Data Processing Bureau's information
and communications strategies sections
information management office.
- [Detective] Is that supposed to impress me or confuse me?
- Okay, then, try this one on for size.
Release them or you'll be working on a fishing trawler
by the end of the week.
- Are you insane?
We know for a fact they're harboring Digimon.
This could be a huge disaster.
- Not for you to worry about.
I'll handle it.
I know you guys are probably really tired
and all you wanna do is go home.
- Recording live. - Great, can you see anything?
- [Daigo] But, unfortunately, none of you can go home
because the press has all of your houses surrounded.
- [Mimi] The press?
How did they find out?
- There must be a leak somewhere.
- I see, so you say. - Pretty common
in government work. - He's a loner.
- So, when will we get to go back home?
- Don't worry, it won't be too long.
We're going to a safe place.
Your parents have been notified and they're cool with this.
I have custody of you for now.
- What exactly has been happening in this world?
- It's Meicoomon.
- Meicoomon?
- [Daigo] I believe that's her in the photo
although she does look a little different.
- [Tai] Yeah, it's her.
- She stayed in that form.
Please tell me she hasn't hurt anyone.
- I'll fill you all in later.
- Are we going to your bureau of whatever?
- Better.
You'll know this place.
It's all closed up for the Summer.
We won't attract attention.
- [Sora] You're kidding.
We're going to school?
BIG PLANT FIRE CAUSED BY DIGIMON!?
BIG PLANT FIRE CONTINUING TO SPREAD
- The fire at the power plant is still burning
out of control with brave fire crews
continuing to pour water
on the flaming wreckage - Horrible.
As they have done
for the past five hours - Mei did that?
Without respite. - Yeah.
It's like what happened with Kuwagamon.
- Actually, this one is even worse.
Meicoomon did this with a single hit.
What if she kept going?
Or even worse, what if every Digimon
went out of control the same way all at the same time?
- Game over.
Game over for the entire world.
- And then there's us.
We'll be blamed for any destruction the Digimon cause.
- No we won't!
We'll just chase them away.
- We wait.
- You serious?
- Do you remember Odaiba?
We can't rush in.
- So what are you saying?
That we should just stand here and watch
while the world's destroyed?
- Of course not.
I wanna take action the same as you do.
The same as we all do.
But you said it yourself, Matt.
Each one of our battles from now on
will be for the entire world.
That means we're fighting for more than just ourselves.
It's for all of our Digimon, right?
- Yeah, right.
I get it.
- Man, Meicoomon's really screwed things up now.
- Watch it.
(yelling)
- Poor Meicoomon I meant.
- I know what you meant, but I do feel bad for her.
She's out there all alone.
- [Daigo] She may have already been removed.
- Removed?
- What do you know?
Tell us.
- As reports continue-- - So you're saying
that Homeostasis ordered Meicoomon to be removed?
Do you have any more information?
What is removal even mean? - Valley Power Plant.
But that fire continues to burn
out of control. - Someone who should never
even have been born. - Only 5% containment.
- That's Gennai described Meicoonmon to me.
Someone who no one ever wanted.
Maybe that makes me unwanted, too.
It makes me a pretty terrible partner.
- Stop that, Meiko.
- Stop being so hard on yourself, and Meicoomon, too.
- Look at that.
All that destruction.
Isn't that something a good person would prevent?
And who is powerless to stop it.
What kind of a partner is that?
- Meiko, you're not powerless.
Meicoomon is still out there and she needs
you now more than ever.
You're still connected.
- Huh?
- I think when you're partners,
you become each other's best hope.
- Kari's right, Mei Mei.
You are the.
Now we're the only ones who can save Meicoomon.
- Don't ever give up.
There's still hope.
- That's it.
That's good.
Hope.
- One thing I still don't get.
When all this started, why did Meicoomon
get targeted in the first place?
There are a lot of Digimon sightings around the world,
but those other Digimon came later.
Meicoomon got here first.
- Maybe it's part of a bigger plan.
Maybe there's something that--
(gasps)
Maybe there's a switch that activates Digimon.
Could it be that Meicoomon's that switch?
- You think someone's using her to destroy the human world?
- That would make sense.
But who?
- Who do we know that would want our world wiped out?
- Nobody!
- King Drasil.
He's been interested in Meicoomon for a long time.
- He probably brought us back from the digital world, too.
We're just the next step in his scheme.
- So why isn't Homeostasis helping us out?
Or are they?
- Doing what?
Removing Meicoomon?
- [Daigo] Homeostasis says they have no other choice now
that Meicoomon is out of control.
- [Agumon] Tai, can you hear me?
We've gotta talk.
- What is it?
- I feel so weak trapped inside this screen
with no food anywhere.
(laughing)
- Well, some things never change.
- I need something good to eat, and fast!
- [All] Yeah!
- Okay, what do you want?
- I'll get 'em a little bit of everything.
- [Gatomon] How can you two chow down like this
when we have such big problems to worry about?
- [Gomamon] Problems seem smaller when you're full.
- Can't save the world on an empty stomach.
- Nope, no way.
- Oh, you're full of something.
- [Both] Thank you!
- [Agumon] Bring on dessert.
I can still fit a little more in.
- [Sora] I guess the saying is right.
The way to a Digimon's heart really
is through their stomach.
- [Agumon] Oh, I like that one.
I'll have to remember it.
(light music)
- What a peaceful night.
It's so quiet.
- Yeah.
Hard to believe our world is in any danger
at all when it's like this.
- That's the problem.
- [Both] Huh?
- What is?
- [Kari] Well, maybe not a problem, exactly.
You see, we think we know about all
of the trouble in other parts of the world.
We see it on the news and hear about it at school
but we don't really understand it.
We don't get it until it happens to us
or to someone we know.
- [Joe] That's a scary thought.
(screaming)
- [T.K.] No need for panic yet.
We're about to spend the whole night
in this huge empty school building.
You know what that means?
- I know, I know.
You want us to sit on your heads.
- Story time!
- [T.K.] Ghost stories.
- That is so lame.
No way.
- Oh come on.
That's what you say every time, Matt.
You're not scared, are you, bro?
- I.
That's not it at all.
I just don't think this a time for goofing around.
(whispering) - He's always like this.
- Cut that out, you three!
I know what you're whispering about
and you're totally wrong, okay?
I'm not afraid of ghosts!
(muffled whispering)
And the same goes for all you guys, too!
(eerie music)
- [Joe] So there I was all alone in the classroom.
It sent shivers down my spine.
I swear, you guys, it was the scariest thing
I've ever seen in my life.
Pinned to the wall.
I got a B minus on the final exam!
(groaning) - Really?
- Come on!
That's not scary.
- You wanna try it again?
- What do you guys want?
You said tell us something scary
and a B minus is the scariest thing ever.
Plus, it's a true story.
- Most of us would not be that scared by a bad test grade.
- [Joe] Because you don't live in
a constant fear of failing.
- So you call that scary, huh?
- [Tentomon] We would classify that as a bad joke.
- Does that mean I failed the ghost story challenge?
- Let me try to come up with one.
One night this guy was wandering in his castle.
- Ha, this already sounds so fake.
I can tell you're just making it up.
- That was so bad.
Worse than Joe.
- Hey! - Go, Meiko.
- Huh?
- You tell a story.
Please?
- Yeah, and make it scary this time.
- Uh.
Hmm.
- Something from down south where you come from.
- Well, my father looked down
on people who believed in ghosts.
- Wow, tell us about him.
He sounds scary.
- I don't think I ever heard a ghost story,
but my mom used to read me folk tales.
- We'd be happy to hear one of your folk tales.
- Uh huh. - Yeah.
- Well, okay.
There was this one time when something disturbing happened
that I've never forgotten.
- [T.K.] Yes!
Now this is the proper way to start a scary story.
- [Meiko] I was walking home one night on the street
a few blocks from where we lived.
Every single street light was out
and the only light came from the sliver of moon in the sky.
(gasping)
I knew the way home so I wasn't
that worried and I kept going.
But then, out of nowhere I heard a little bell
somewhere behind me, like the bell on a bicycle.
(bell dings)
I turned around thinking someone must be behind me,
but no one was there.
I started walking faster.
I was so close to home, but then I heard the bell again.
It got closer and closer.
- Wow, you don't have to keep on
going if you don't feel like it.
- Wait, I was just getting to the weird part.
(nervously moaning)
- So, I turned around but there was nothing there,
same as before.
Then, suddenly, I could hear breathing.
It got closer, I could hear the bell again.
The street lights came on.
I could barely breathe.
And then I saw him.
(booming)
(screaming)
- [Daigo] What's going on in here?
Why do you have the lights off?
- [Tai] Uh, we were trying to save electricity?
- Okay.
I think I'm gonna check you guys into a hotel.
- Hotel?
- I thought you were going to take us all home.
- There are photographers camped out on your lawns.
You gotta lay low for a little while longer.
- Then why move?
- We're in a school?
- Whoa!
Where are we supposed to take a shower?
- [Tai] There are tons of showers here in the locker rooms.
And never ending hot water.
- Okay, I'm sold.
Anyway, I wanna hear the end of the story.
- No, no ghost stories!
No ghost stories, okay?
- You know, Matt, you could go stay at the hotel alone.
- I'm not scared!
And you three, I can hear you whispering.
- Well then, what next?
- Well, I--
- Hold up!
No one's asking what I wanna do.
- Okay, Joe.
What's your plan?
- I'm still workin' on it.
- We'll stay.
Everybody better call home.
- This'll be tricky.
What do I tell Mom?
- Don't worry about it, just tell her you're fine.
- [Tentomon] Finish your story.
- Okay.
Where was I?
(light music)
- [Kari] I can't wait to come home and see you, mom.
Sure, well, let me put Tai on.
- Hey, Mom.
- [Yuuko] Is Agumon okay?
- Are you more worried about Agumon or me?
- [Yuuko] I know you're gonna be all right.
(giggles)
- [Tai] Oh, I see how it is.
- [Yuuko] You take care of your little sister
and Agumon, and Gatomon, too, okay?
- Yeah.
- [Yuuko] And be careful.
- And Tai?
It's just like old times.
- [Tai] That's one way to put it.
- All your friends and their Digimon are together again.
- [Tai] Yeah.
Yeah, it's like a Digi reunion.
- Goodnight, Tai.
- If she only knew.
- You hung up?
- You can call her back.
I'm going outside for a minute.
- [Meiko] Y'all don't have to keep
on asking me if I'm okay so many times.
I told you, I'm fine.
I'm not alone.
You know that.
Sorry about Meicoomon.
What do I think?
Well, it's confusing.
Goodnight, then.
(light music)
FATHER
That was a lie.
I told him I was okay but I'm not.
Not even a little.
Meicoomon, what am I supposed to do?
Are you to blame?
I heard what Gennai said.
That you were never even meant to be born.
Is that the truth?
Is that why you're so angry now?
Oh, Mei, I still love you so much.
I really thought we would keep playing
like children forever.
I don't know what I'll do without you.
Everyone keeps telling me that you and I are partners,
that I'm your salvation and you're mine.
But what if they're wrong?
Why is my stomach always in knots?
'Cause I'm sad?
Maybe.
(gasping)
Tai.
- I wasn't trying to spy on you or anything,
but I heard you talking.
Was that a southern accent you were using?
I've never heard you talk like that before.
It's kinda cool.
Sorry.
- Well, aren't you a peach, hun?
It's a southern way of saying you're a nice guy.
- Oh.
Well, thanks.
I guess.
- [Palmon] She told him he's like a nice piece of fruit?
- Kari should know about this.
- I think I oughta tell Sora about it.
- Maybe I should give Matt a report.
- [Tentomon] A report about what?
That didn't even make any sense.
- What do you think, Agumon?
- [Agumon] I love this floor!
- [Meiko] So what do they see?
- Wavelength distortions.
Izzy made 'em.
I used to think that they were some things
you could see when you were a kid
that you didn't see anymore after you grew up.
And I believed the flip side was true, too.
Things that you never noticed when you were little
suddenly seemed really obvious when you got older.
I even thought time would turn
me into somebody totally different.
Lately, though, I just keep wondering about it.
When is all that supposed to happen?
Then when I saw Agumon again I wondered
if we were still connected.
Except it was like we'd never been apart.
Really.
And just like that I knew everything was gonna be okay.
That we'd always be connected.
- You truly are partners.
Mine should never have been born.
- Gennai said that, but he's wrong.
- What if he wasn't even talking about Meicoomon, though?
What if he meant me?
Think about it, Tai.
If I was never born then I wouldn't have a partner
and Meicoomon would never have gotten infected--
- Mochizuki, shut up!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to be a jerk.
But you do know that's not true, right?
Have some faith.
- [Meiko] I've really made him angry.
Great.
- [Agumon] Hey there, how's it going?
- [Meiko] Oh.
Hi, Agumon.
- [Digimon] Why did we send Agumon out there?
- Because he should be the one to clean up Tai's mess.
- I think Tai should clean up Tai's mess.
- I hate it when things are messy.
- So, listen.
Let's go get something to eat.
- Huh? (groaning)
- He's hopeless.
- [Meiko] You're funny, Agumon.
- [Agumon] You're not hungry?
- No, but.
I do feel kind of empty in here.
- Your heart is hungry?
- Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
- Doesn't he ever think about anything else?
(giggling)
- That's not what I meant, but it's close.
I feel like I'm missing out.
On what you and Tai have.
And Gabumon and Matt.
And well, all of you.
- I get it.
- And I'm really sorry for all
the trouble I caused you guys.
- Well, you never cause any trouble at all.
I think you're talking about someone else.
(light music)
But that's not your fault, either.
- Huh?
- You know, I miss Meicoomon.
I like her a lot.
I think everything's gonna be okay.
(crying)
- [Meiko] Oh, thank you, Agumon.
That means a lot to me.
- And I'm sure that Meicoomon loves you
a whole lot too, Meiko.
- Hey, look, I think it worked.
- Or she's really upset.
- [Tentomon] Why are humans so confusing?
- I should ask Sora what this means.
- She's still hugging him.
- I gotta report this to Joe.
- I should tell Kari so she can tell Tai.
- [Tentomon] But we don't even know what really happened.
- [Agumon] Hey, Tai.
- Huh?
Oh, hi, Agumon.
I'm feeling kinda bad.
- [Agumon] How come?
- 'Cause of Meiko.
I yelled at her.
- [Agumon] Oh yeah, that was bad.
- You were spying on us?
- [Agumon] Uh, no?
- Don't worry about it.
- [Agumon] Why did you yell at her in the first place, Tai?
- I'm not really sure.
- [Agumon] I'll bet it's 'cause you were hangry.
- No.
(sighs)
Do you think Kari's right about how we
don't get things until they happen to us?
Or to someone we know?
And what about understanding other people's feelings?
How's that even possible?
I worry that there's no way I can really understand
what Meiko's feeling right now.
I don't know what it's like inside her head.
And I'm worried that I don't know how to help her.
I feel so useless.
And then I start worrying about the fact that I'm worrying.
- Maybe your brain is too full
and it's time to stop thinking so much.
(Tai sighs)
Don't be sad, Tai.
When the time comes, you'll know just what to do.
- [Tai] I hope you're right.
(zapping)
(dramatic music)
(growling)
(screaming)
(gasping)
- Meicoomon's here.
(roaring)
- Listen!
Meicoomon!
- I'm here.
Meicoomon, it's all right.
Meicoomon, you have to stop this.
Let me help you.
This is not who you are!
(yelling)
I know you got this way because of me.
- Huh?
- I'm the reason all of this is happening!
I let you down.
You got like this because you were trying to protect me.
- Don't say that.
- I'm to blame.
Meicoomon, aren't we still partners?
(roaring)
(glass shattering)
Can't I save you?
Can't we save each other?
- That blue mist.
That film surrounded her at the power plant
right before the explosion.
- Agumon? - Say the word!
- No, don't.
If they go in they could all wind up getting infected.
We don't dare risk having that happen again.
- That's right!
- We gotta do it.
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- [Agumon] Let's go, Tai.
(dramatic music)
(rock music)
(light music)
- [All] Digivolve to...
(singing in foreign language)
- Greymon!
- Birdramon!
- Alphamon! - Angemon.
- Koromon.
- [Ikkakumon] Ikkakumon!
- [All] Digivolve to...
- MetalGreymon! - WereGarurumon.
- MagnaAngemon!
- Birdramon!
- MegaKabuterimon.
(grunting)
- Move in.
Surround her!
(screaming)
(gasping)
(cawing)
(eerie music)
- Meiko?
(soft whimpering)
(screaming)
(gasping)
(zapping)
- She's scared.
She's crying.
- [Tai] Then why does it look
like she's getting even stronger?
(yelling)
(zapping)
- [Joe] Oh no!
Zudomon!
- Yeah, that's what's happening.
Look.
The distortion around Meicoomon is growing.
- Unbelievable.
Could she be gaining power as she gets more and more upset?
(grunting)
(screaming)
(zapping)
(booming)
(gasping)
- She's destroying everything.
But why?
Doesn't she understand we're just trying to help her?
- No! - Meicoomon!
(zapping)
(booming)
(panting)
- [Joe] She knocked 'em all out with one hit!
- It's arrived.
(grunting)
(booming) (dramatic music)
- What's that?
- [Daiga] That is a Digimon sent by Homeostasis.
- Homeostasis?
- Jesmon.
(roaring)
(evil laughing)
- [Man] There it goes!
You should've known better.
Thank you, Homeostasis.
This is fascinating.
(gasping)
- Oh no!
What is that?
- It's erasing everything.
Her mere existence is destructive.
(grunting)
(screaming)
(booming)
- Meicoomon!
- This doesn't make any sense.
Didn't Homeostasis tell us to take care of Meicoomon?
What's going on?
- Maybe it's all part of their plan.
Maybe they just don't need us anymore
so now they're cutting us off.
- Up until now I thought it was King Drasil
who wanted to get rid of us and remove
us from the digital world.
But maybe it was really Homeostasis.
- Now what?
Just who are we supposed to be fighting?
(dramatic music)
(booming)
What do we do?
I don't know who our real enemy is anymore.
(booming)
(zapping) (grunting)
(thudding)
(booming)
(screaming)
(panting)
(grunting)
- Meiko!
(thudding)
- Whoa, did you all see what I just saw?
- [Mimi] Yeah, I did.
- I did, too.
Meicoomon just saved Meiko from getting crushed.
- But wait.
What does that mean?
- [Mimi] It means they're still partners!
(grunting)
(thudding)
- Well, then shouldn't we be trying to protect Meicoomon?
- We have to.
- [Matt] Tai, time to level up!
- You're right.
MetalGreymon, Digivolve and then see
if you can lure Meicoomon out over the ocean.
- [MetalGreymon] MetalGreymon, Digivolve to...
(light music)
WarGreymon!
- Let's get in on this.
- MagnaAngemon! - Lillymon!
- WereGarurumon. - MegaKabuterimon.
- [All] Digivolve to...
(singing in foreign language)
- Phoenixmon. - Rosemon.
- Seraphimon. - HerculesKabuterimon.
- MetalGarurumon.
(grunting)
- To the ocean!
(heavy breathing)
- Stop this.
Your quest is hopeless.
- What did you say?
- You are merely being foolish.
- Homeostasis.
- Why do you think we're being foolish?
- [Homeostasis] Harmony and stability must be maintained.
Anything that obstructs harmony
and stability will be removed.
- [Tai] That's why you wanna get rid of Meicoomon?
- As if we'd let that happen!
- We are merely finishing the task
you were unable to complete.
Anyone who endangers our objectives
will also be removed.
- [Matt] You wouldn't dare!
- Just wait a minute.
That's outrageous.
The DigiDestined are not your pawns.
- There is nothing anyone can do to help.
Your interference will be stopped.
- No way.
I'll never abandon my friends.
- Our friends.
(dramatic music)
(booming)
(screaming)
- That Digimon is beyond your control.
- What good is harmony if you destroy
someone's life in the process?
- [Homeostasis] Some sacrifices are required.
- [Matt] Just like that, huh?
- Stop using me to say things!
Get out of me!
- Yes.
Good.
- Get out of my head right now, whoever you are.
You're wrong about everything you said.
They're our friends, and one of our friends
is suffering because of you!
A sacrifice?
How selfish are you?
We won't allow it.
(laughing)
- At this point, it is too late
for you to do anything about it.
Your concept of teamwork has failed you this time.
It's over.
(singing in foreign language)
(grunting)
(gasping)
- Meiko, no!
(panting)
(grunting)
- [Izzy] The distortion is closing!
- We need Omnimon.
- Come on, Matt.
- [Matt] Let's save our friends.
(yelling)
- [Omnimon] Omnimon!
- [Meiko] There it is!
- [Tai] We're right behind you.
(grunting)
- [Sora] Here we go.
(yelling)
- Celestial arrow!
(thudding)
- We got a message for you, Homeostasis!
What you tell us is right or wrong doesn't matter.
What matters is this.
Looking out for each other.
We will always protect our friends.
(dramatic music)
(shattering)
- Alphamon.
- Why, King Drasil?
(thudding)
(grunting)
(gasping) - Seraphimon!
(dramatic music)
(clanking) (grunting)
(groaning)
Look out!
Alphamon's about to blast you both!
(zapping)
He blasted everybody.
(screaming)
(panting)
(clanking)
(zapping) (screaming)
(water trickling)
- Tapirmon, why are you doing this?
Why won't you come back to me?
You can't just leave me after all this time.
You can't leave me with them.
(suspenseful music)
(gun clicking)
Stay away, creeps.
Stay away or I'll dust you all!
Tapirmon, please!
Please come back!
Let's save the world.
I'm still your partner, aren't I?
I'm.
I'm begging you.
Come back-- (wave crashing)
It's too late!
(gasping)
(grunting)
- [Daigo Voiceover] I couldn't save you, Hime.
When it came down to it I couldn't do anything.
(blasting)
(light music)
If we're all really this powerless.
Then why were we chosen in the first place?
(water rippling)
(crashing)
(grunting)
(blasting)
- I don't even know who to root for anymore.
(clanking)
- Meicoomon, you have to stop this or they'll destroy you.
If not for yourself, do it for your partner.
Can't you see what this is doing to Meiko?
Don't you care?
Don't you have any feelings left for her?
- No.
Just please kill her.
Just do it.
It'll be better for everyone
if Meicoomon is destroyed forever.
(grunting)
- You don't mean it.
- Mei Mei, don't even think like that!
(booming)
- Why?
What else can I think about?
I can't take it anymore, I can't.
(roaring)
(clanking)
- Listen, Meiko.
You've gotta let your partner know there's still hope.
You're just.
You're just giving off despair.
- [Meiko] Because I know what has to happen to now.
- Meiko.
You can't really believe that.
You think killing Meicoomon is really our only hope?
- [Meiko] Please don't.
(clanking)
- This is awful.
I just can't believe this is real.
It's just too sad.
- Oh, Mei.
I still love you so much.
Homeostasis said Meicoomon had to be destroyed
to restore harmony.
Meicoomon is the problem.
- She's right.
- No, Tai.
- No way, Tai.
- I'm going to stop Omnimon from fighting Meicoomon.
It's taking too long and he may never
be able to defeat her.
Stop!
- Tai.
- If Omnimon can't destroy Meicoomon, then Jesmon will.
This is the only way.
- Just hang on, guys.
Even if Meicoomon is the reason everything's gone wrong--
- Calm down, Joe.
- It's not fair!
This is wrong.
Meicoomon and Meiko are partners.
They'll be partners forever.
- He's right.
So what if Meicoomon does deserve all the blame
and she should be destroyed?
Can you really make that call, Tai?
- Yeah, I can.
And I will.
We're going to end this ourselves.
We don't have to let Homeostasis have the final say.
Maybe we can figure out how to restore balance.
Meicoomon is one of us.
That's that.
We protect our own!
I will not run from a friend in pain,
and all of us are so much more than that.
We are the DigiDestined.
(pounding)
- Oh, things are definitely out of control.
- [Tai] No, you idiot!
Stop fighting!
(dramatic music)
- Meicoomon.
It's going to be okay.
I'm sorry.
(thudding)
(cracking)
(groaning)
(zapping)
- [Sora] Don't watch.
- It didn't help.
- Let me tell you something, Tai.
My plans do not include sacrificing any of our friends.
Not ever!
If you-- - Whoa!
Break it up, you guys.
We're in this together.
All of us.
(booming)
(grunting)
- [Tai] Sorry, Matt.
(screaming)
- Thank you.
- [Sora] Meiko, where are you going?
- Mei Mei! - Wait, you fool,
you can't go out there!
- [Tai] Come back here, both of you!
- [Meiko] This is my decision.
- Stop, you guys.
- [Mimi] But we have to help them.
- I'll handle it.
- Take me! - Stop!
(zapping)
(grunting)
No. - Let me go.
Let me go!
(screaming)
- Un Pour Tous.
(dramatic music)
(blasting)
(gasping)
- Jesmon.
(blasting)
(rumbling)
- [Tai] Matt!
(grunting)
(groaning)
- Are you all right?
Come on.
Run.
- [Tai] Omnimon!
Hey!
- Come back!
(grunting)
- Look out!
(rumbling)
- [Daigo] Hold on, Tai!
(crashing)
- Oh no.
(grunting)
(gasping)
- [T.K] Tai.
Where'd he go?
- Brother.
- [Gatomon] Kari, what happened?
Where are we going?
Are we gonna find Tai?
- Find Tai.
- Wait for me!
- Where's my brother?
Oh, Tai.
How could you go and just leave me behind?
- Wait!
Wherever you're going, I wanna go, too.
(dramatic music)
- Kari.
- What's happening to her?
- [Izzy] Let me look.
I think it's.
- Oh, brother.
You fool.
- [T.K] Kari!
- What's happening?
I feel funny.
What should I do?
(blasting)
(gasping)
- [Sora] What is that, Izzy?
- [Izzy] That is prodigious.
(grunting)
(screaming)
- Even that didn't stop Meicoomon.
- How sensitive and so fragile.
The more innocent they are, the easier it is to break them.
(laughing)
- Kari! - Snap out of it!
Get ahold of yourself!
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
- Do it.
Take over.
- [Meiko] Why is this happening?
- [Mimi] What?
What is it, Izzy?
- [Izzy] I don't know.
It looks like chaos.
(gasping)
(light music)
(groaning)
- Destroy it all.
- Disappear.
Everything, disappear.
- [Meiko] What's going on?
- I think the harmony has started to collapse.
(roaring)
(splashing)
Maybe this was always King Drasil's plan.
This was his goal.
Our world is going to be swallowed by the digital world.
- Why does Homeostasis have such
a big problem with us trying to save our friends?
What's wrong with that?
- Thanks a lot, Tai.
Everyone, on your feet.
- And do what?
- And fight, obviously.
What's sitting around gonna do?
What's feeling sorry for ourselves gonna do?
None of that's gonna help anybody.
You can save your tears for later.
It's time to stand up and get moving!
(light music)
We still have each other, and we still have hope.
We have not been defeated.
- [Koromon] Where is Tai?
Come back!
Where'd you go?
- [Matt] Stop that, Koromon!
- But I'm supposed to protect him.
And now I can't.
My heart.
It feels empty.
No Tai?
- I'm sorry. - Don't apologize.
It's done.
Tai did what he wanted to do.
- Now what?
- We go.
(light dramatic music)
[ ♪♪♪ ] ]