[COLLEGE GIRL A]
Hey, check him out!
Oh my gosh, he's totally hot!
Yeah, but the way he's dressed,
it looks like he's
going clubbing.
Kinda strange.
[COLLEGE GIRL A]
He could be lost.
If we give him directions,
maybe he'll take us with him!
[bike bell ringing]
[TOHRU]
Well, winter break is over,
and our third school
term has begun.
Living with the Somas is
still a non‐stop adventure.
[CASHIER A]
See you again soon!
Thanks for waiting!
[KYO]
I'm sick of your smug face.
Let's take this outside!
We're already
outside, you idiot.
Um, you guys.
[YUKI] Thank you for doing
the shopping, Miss Honda.
Here.
There's a lot, sorry.
I guess I went a little
overboard with the groceries.
It's no trouble.
Why don't you try
making yourself useful
for once, dumb Cat?
Watch who you're callin' dumb!
Give me those, I'll
carry both of 'em!
[YUKI]
Sure you...
[TOHRU] A lot of things
have changed lately,
but these two are still
at each other's throats.
I made a wish at New Year's
for them to start
getting along better.
I don't think it worked.
...waste my time running an
errand with you of all people.
You could've stayed home.
[KYO]
You should've stayed home.
Will you do us all a favor
and just shut up already?
Heh. If you want me
to stop talkin'...
Wait! Please, can we
just talk this out?
Poor thing! Are you
going to be okay?
That should keep him quiet
for a while, at least.
[coughs]
[SHIGURE]
All done!
Who wants the next turn?
Yuki, bath time!
I'll skip it today.
Uh! No bath? How disgusting!
You dirty boy!
[YUKI] One of these days I'm
going to throw him off the roof.
I think I have
a cold, that's why.
Uh! A cold? Are you
running a fever?
You do feel a little warm.
The quicker you
can treat a cold,
the sooner you'll feel better.
Let's see if I can find
you some medicine.
You should probably stay
home from school tomorrow
just to be on the safe side.
No, it's all right.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
[TOHRU]
But we're running the marathon.
You'll just make yourself worse!
Oh.
Running in this chilly weather?
That sounds like torture.
These old bones
couldn't handle it.
Hold on a second.
Did you say... marathon?
Y‐Yes.
‐‐[KYO] As in a race?
‐‐Didn't you know about it?
[YUKI]
I know that look.
[KYO]
A race run in groups.
Which means...
it's a competition!
‐‐[YUKI] Yep, there it is.
‐‐All right!
I'm freezing just
looking at you, Kyo.
‐‐Put on a sweater or something.
‐‐...faster I am than you!
No, but Soma has a cold.
He can't run tomorrow.
[KYO]
A cold?
You're gonna bail on the race
'cause you've got the sniffles?
[TOHRU] He sure is...
enthusiastic about this.
[KYO] It's on! You
better not back down!
[SHIGURE]
Seriously, don't overdo it.
If your body gets too
weak from this cold,
you're going to transform.
And I really doubt
you want that.
[YUKI]
I know.
[TOHRU] I have a bad
feeling about this.
Soma has no business racing
tomorrow. He needs to rest.
But something tells me Kyo's
not gonna let that happen.
Hmm...
Please let everyone get
through tomorrow in one piece.
[GYM TEACHER A] Be sure to warm
up those muscles, people!
[GIRLS gasping, chattering]
I just can't stop looking.
Yeah.
Is there any sight more
beautiful than that?
[GIRLS] Yuki's bare legs
shining in the sun!
[TOHRU]
Soma.
You, um, you didn't eat very
much breakfast this morning.
Maybe you shouldn't run.
No, it's fine.
I'll make it through
somehow. Besides...
If I don't compete, I'll
never hear the end of it.
Oh, hey. I don't think
I've seen Uotani today.
I'm think Uo‐chan's skipping.
Hana‐chan should
be here somewhere‐‐
Hey. Honda!
You and Yuki are looking awfully
buddy‐buddy over here.
The girl's race is about to
start. Better get moving!
Let's go! We wouldn't wanna
miss out, now would we?
[IWATA laughing]
I'll see you later, then.
[GYM TEACHER A] All right!
We'll start with the girls.
Hey, what happened?
You don't look so good.
[TOHRU]
It's nothing. I'm fine, really.
Okay. If you say so.
Does the air feel weird
to you all of a sudden?!
[TOHRU]
Hana‐chan!
Let's go and run our best,
in honor of Uo‐chan!
Sounds good.
I'm not a terribly strong
runner, but I'll try my hardest.
[GYM TEACHER A]
On your marks, get set...
[gunshot]
Alas.
Oh, no! What happened?
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry, Tohru.
I can't go on. Leave me.
Run well and don't worry
about me. I'll walk. Slowly.
You're sure? Really?
[GYM TEACHER A]
You can crawl the whole way
for all I care, Hanajima.
Just get moving.
The boys are next.
Everybody ready?
[KYO growling]
[GYM TEACHER A]
On your marks, get set...
[gunshot]
Hope you're hungry 'cause
you're gonna eat my dust!
Shut up and run.
[KYO] And don't even think
about holding back!
It's not a sprint.
Jeez. Slow down.
I know, right? I can't
even see them anymore.
[KYO]
I'm gonna beat you!
[TOHRU]
I'm worried.
Is Soma really going to be okay?
[TOHRU gasps]
White hair!
An elderly person?
Excuse me, sir!
Do you need help?
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
I am sorry!
I saw your hair, so I thought
you might be an old person
who tripped and fell, and I
wanted to make sure you were‐‐
[TOHRU groaning]
[HATSUHARU] Hey, have you ever
heard of the Soma family?
Uh, sorry, why do
you wanna know?
Uh! Oh, are you a Soma,
too, by any chance?
I am. You do know them?
[TOHRU] Yes! It's nice to
meet you. I'm Tohru Hon‐‐
[HATSUHARU]
I think I hear them now.
[TOHRU]
Uh?
[KYO yells]
Well, Rat, are you
giving it your all?
I told you to be quiet.
[coughs]
[KYO yelling]
[TOHRU]
Huh.
Um, string?
[HATSUHARU]
Got one.
Oh, no! Are you okay?
That was a really bad fall.
Hey. What happened?
What in the hell was that for?!
[HATSUHARU] Figured it was
the only way I'd be able
to get you to stop.
[KYO]
Uh? Haru?
That was a very
dangerous prank.
Not everyone's skull is
as thick as Kyo's here.
Never, ever try this at home.
It still hurt, jerk!
So, it's your turn now.
Everyone's coming to visit.
Don't you have school, though?
[HATSUHARU]
Uh.
I set out from home on Sunday
and wound up in a neighborhood
I didn't recognize.
Somehow, three days passed.
It's a mystery.
[YUKI]
No, it's called getting lost.
[TOHRU]
Uh.
Uh... maybe we should find
somewhere else to talk?
[YUKI]
Agreed.
Miss Honda, this is
Hatsuharu Soma.
He's a third‐year
junior high student,
so one year younger than us.
Haru, this is Miss Tohru Honda.
Oh, that's who you are.
Nice to meet you.
Ah! No! It's my pleasure!
[TOHRU] Hatsuharu's so
polite and soft‐spoken.
He seems really
mature for his age.
So, you gonna tell us
what you're here for?
To fight you.
Huh?
[HATSUHARU] I was gonna
challenge you at New Year's,
but you skipped out,
so I came to you.
Now let's go.
[KYO]
Whoa, hold on.
I'm kinda in the middle of
an important race here.
[HATSUHARU] I traveled
three whole days for this.
[KYO]
No, you just got lost!
[HATSUHARU]
Come on, let's fight.
It's not gonna happen,
so just go home.
No thanks.
This won't end well.
Why?
Hey, Kyo. It might be a good
idea to go along with Haru.
[KYO]
I said no, and I meant it!
We're done, man. Leave.
Too late.
I'm not interested
in your petty excuses.
Now get up!
It's time for you to prove that
you're a real man, kitty‐cat.
Fight me and die!
‐‐[HATSUHARU cackling]
‐‐Could we skip the dying part?
‐‐Damn brat!
[TOHRU screams]
That's wonderful.
He summoned Dark Haru.
Who's Dark Haru?
The guy's usually
a space‐cadet,
but sometimes
he'll totally snap.
We call that version...
Dark Haru.
[TOHRU]
Huh. I see.
So it's kind of like when
Kagura gets a little violent?
[YUKI]
No.
Unfortunately,
he's much creepier.
Don't just stand over on the
sidelines and watch, Yuki.
Today is the day that
I make you mine.
And do what with me?
‐‐Now, stand up, Kyo!
‐‐I'm already standing up!
Miss Honda, you should go on
ahead; this could take a while.
I should stay.
Too bad.
I thought you had a spine,
but I guess you must've
lost it at some point.
You are seriously messed up when
you turn dark, you know that?
Ouch, that hurt.
You better hurry up
and fight me.
I might decide to make
that girl mine, too.
What the hell's that
supposed to mean?!
[HATSUHARU] We'll spend some
time gettin' to know each other,
doing a little of this
and a little of that.
[KYO] What are you
even saying right now?
[KYO] This blockhead always got
lost on the way to the bathroom
when we were kids,
so I had to walk him there.
And this is how he repays me?
And anyway, what's "a little
of this and a little of that"?
Whatever it is, girls have
nothin' to do with this.
Still, for some reason,
I'm extra pissed off now.
[KYO]
That's it, you damn brat!
Stop! Please!
There! That's what you
shoulda done from the start,
you pathetic coward!
Come here, bastard. I'm gonna
punch your damn teeth in!
No, seriously. I'd get going.
This'll definitely
take some time.
I can't, 'cause Kyo...
Hey, don't just sit there.
Yeah, at least run a few meters.
[KYO, HATSUHARU yelling]
Let's go!
It's your funeral, kitty!
Try throwing a punch, loser!
[KYO] You can talk as much
trash as you want to‐‐
‐‐it isn't gonna save you.
‐‐Oh, yeah?
[TOHRU]
It's like we've been transported
into a martial arts movie.
Um, guys?
It's okay. Really. They'll wear
themselves out eventually.
Besides, I don't know about you,
but I would greatly prefer not
to get caught in the crossfire.
[TOHRU]
Yeah, right.
[bang]
That punch! Kyo seems
really strong today.
Yeah. I would say he's probably
the stronger of the two.
They've both studied martial
arts since they were kids,
and they appear to enjoy it.
[coughs]
Well, of course.
Didn't you study it because
you enjoyed it, too?
Maybe.
[YUKI]
It's hard to say.
[gasps]
Huh? Is there something wrong?
What happened, Soma?
Please say something!
Soma, please! Answer me!
Yuki! An attack?
Man, you're really burning up.
I'll call the main house and‐‐
No, you don't wanna do that?
Huh.
Kyo, is it okay if I take
a rain check on our fight?
Uh. Yeah, sure.
I think our best bet is
Sensei's house, then.
We could take a taxi there.
No, that's out.
In this condition,
Yuki might transform.
[TOHRU]
Is there some way I can help?
Please, I'll do anything!
Yeah, all right. I think
I'll take you up on that.
It's a good thing you're cute.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
I'm saying if I'm
gonna hug someone,
I'd prefer it be a
cute girl like you.
[gasps]
Uh, 'scuse me,
what are you doing?
Ask permission first, you jerk.
[HATSUHARU] It'll be easier on
Yuki if I carry him this way.
You'll have to keep holding
onto me so I don't turn back.
[TOHRU yelps]
[moos]
[HANAJIMA]
It's here.
At last. The moment
I've been waiting for.
I have a diamond royal
flush. You lose.
[HIROSHI]
Seriously?
Why do you always get
the good cards? No fair.
[GYM TEACHER A] That's it!
All three of you, go home!
[SHIGURE snorts, laughs]
Well, you boys certainly know
how to make a grand entrance.
Keep laughing and
I'll punch you next.
[SHIGURE] I bet you attracted
quite a crowd on the way here.
[SHIGURE laughs]
‐‐[KYO] A pack of little brats!
‐‐[BOY A] A cow!
‐‐[BOY B] How cool!
‐‐[KYO hisses]
‐‐[GIRL A] Moo!
He's fast asleep. This
attack wasn't a bad one.
He has a fever,
but he'll be fine.
Oh, thank goodness!
Sorry you got
dragged into this.
We've got it now.
You can go back to school.
No, I'll stay here
and watch him.
Going to school is important,
but not at the cost of
abandoning someone sick.
And, well, colds
can be dangerous.
They shouldn't be taken lightly.
If my mom were here,
I know that she'd agree.
All right, then. You three stay.
I'll go to the school
and retrieve your effects.
[TOHRU] Hm? You don't
have to do that, really!
Don't worry about it,
it's nothing.
Kyo, you let the good doctor
know what's going on.
What? Why should
I have to call 'im?
I'll do it.
[TOHRU screams]
[HATSUHARU]
Where's the phone, again?
Don't just wander around
naked, you creep!
[SHIGURE]
Okay, kids. I'm off!
Take good care of Yuki.
Don't worry, we will!
Thanks for doing this!
[TOHRU]
Shigure's always so willing
to sacrifice himself for others!
[SHIGURE] ♪ High school
girls. High school girls. ♪
I got it. Thank you.
Well, what did Hatori say?
[HATSUHARU] He chewed me
out for some reason.
It's a mystery.
Maybe 'cause you
disappeared for three days?
So, what now?
Rat‐boy seems to
be doing better.
You wanna go finish the fight?
[HATSUHARU]
Eh. Why bother?
There would be no point.
I forgot how strong
you were, Kyo.
You're kidding me here!
You can't put me
through all that
and then just randomly
decide you're done!
When the heck did you stop
being Dark Haru, anyway?
‐‐[HATSUHARU] Owie.
‐‐[TOHRU] Huh?
You mean you changed back
into being Light Haru?
Uh... Yes.
[TOHRU]
Soma was right.
He's a totally
different person now.
How's Yuki?
[TOHRU]
He's still sleeping.
I was going to go get
an ice pack for him.
No attacking in his sleep.
Yeah, obviously.
I'm gonna win against him,
and I'll prove that I can
do it fair and square!
[scoffs]
This is lame. I'm
goin' back to school.
Bye.
Those two, they get into
fistfights every day?
Not really. They do argue and
yell all the time, though.
Oh, yeah?
Sounds like they're getting
along a lot better lately.
That's "better"?
Sure it is.
Their vibes have
changed a little,
and they're not as
uptight anymore.
Not sure what's different now.
Although... maybe it has
something to do with you.
Me? It's not me!
I don't know what
I could've done
to change things between them!
It's not like I've
been watching you,
so I could be wrong.
But as long as things are
changing for the better,
that's good.
Especially for Yuki.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
He was my first love.
[TOHRU grunts]
I like Kyo, but Yuki's
special. To me, anyway.
He's special?
Yeah, although I did hate him
back when we were little.
And why was that?
[HATSUHARU]
Because he's the Rat.
In the folk tale, remember?
The Rat rode up to the banquet
on the back of the Ox.
I resented him so much for that.
The adults all laughed and
said the Rat used the Ox
so he could get to
the banquet first.
That he was only able to
because the Ox was an idiot.
Of course, it felt like
they were laughing at me
and calling me an idiot.
So, I got really down on myself,
and I blamed it on the Rat.
I was always on edge,
losing my temper at
the drop of a hat.
That's when it came out.
The "dark" personality.
Put my parents through hell.
I took up martial arts
hoping it would help somehow.
But the... the baggage I
carried was still there.
I enjoyed my training,
but it didn't stop people
from making fun of me.
Then one day,
I came across Yuki.
We'd never actually spoken
to each other before.
[HATSUHARU]
I completely snapped.
Unleashed all my
pent‐up rage on him.
I hate you so much,
you sneaky Rat!
It's your fault people
make fun of me!
It's your fault for being
a dirty cheater!
It's your fault I'm stupid!
That I'm an idiot!
[YUKI]
Really? Are you?
Are you an idiot?
Are you stupid?
Is that what you think?
[HATSUHARU]
No. I'm not.
I'm not stupid. I'm not...
...not an idiot.
[HATSUHARU]
I'm really not.
[YUKI]
No.
No, You're not.
[HATSUHARU] After that, I didn't
lose my temper as much.
I'd been bottling
that up for so long,
but Yuki helped me to say it.
And by doing that,
he set my heart free.
I was stunned.
He was totally different
from the Yuki I'd imagined.
I was like the others.
I'd decided he was
the "dirty Rat"
without bothering
to get to know him.
I'm glad I ran
into him that day.
Otherwise, I would
probably still hate him.
And that... would be stupid.
That was a wonderful story.
You know, I noticed
something earlier.
You were standing
there next to Yuki
and he was smiling softly.
He never used to
smile like that
when he was living
with the main family.
But with you, he did.
It's why I thought you
might have something to do
with the difference in him.
[gasps] No! Like I said before,
I really don't think
I've done anything
that would change anybody!
Okay, then. A test.
[TOHRU]
Uh?
[HATSUHARU]
Try calling him by...
[TOHRU] Really? Are you
sure that's a good idea?
You're here, Miss Honda?
Yes! I'm so glad you're awake!
I transformed!
Careful! You shouldn't
push yourself.
Hold on. How did I get home?
Simple. Hatsuharu transformed
so he could carry you.
Oh. Thanks, Haru.
I told her how
much I love you.
I just thought you should know.
[YUKI] Why would you tell her
something ridiculous like that?
What if she actually
takes you seriously?
[HATSUHARU]
I am serious.
And besides, I think
it's a really sweet story.
Don't you... Yuki?
Come, now. You don't‐‐
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Hatsuharu.
I think it's safe to say
that I failed the test.
[HATSUHARU] Try calling
him by his given name.
It'll make him happy.
[TOHRU] And so the day
of the marathon ended
without anything
going too wrong.
Ha! Three of a kind!
I've got a full house.
[HANAJIMA] Meanwhile,
I have five of a kind.
Ah! How'd I lose again?!
‐‐[YUSUKE] She's too good.
‐‐I want one more round!
[TOHRU]
That night,
Yuki wasn't the only one
in bed with a cold.
Well, what do you expect
when you play poker
outside all day?
[HATORI] Obviously, the family
is trying to work me to death.
[KAGURA]
"It's Valentine's, after all!"