[HANAJIMA]
When I was a child,
I hated going out.
[PEDESTRIAN D]
Ugh. She's so annoying!
[PEDESTRIAN A]
What am I doing with this idiot?
[FATHER A] I just wanna
go home and take a nap.
[MOTHER A]
Why did I marry him again?
[OLD MAN A]
I hate this stupid park.
[OLD WOMAN A]
Who's that old letch looking at?
[MAN A]
You idiot!
[MAN B]
So bored.
[MAN C]
You just don't get it.
[MAN D]
Shut up already.
[WOMAN C]
I hate her.
Saki.
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER]
Uh?
Saki!
[HANAJIMA'S MOTHER]
Saki‐chan!
I'm sorry. I thought for
sure you'd be okay here.
Come on. We'll leave.
[laughter]
[HANAJIMA]
Be quiet.
[WOMAN D]
I'm so sick of this.
[HANAJIMA]
Be quiet.
[MAN E]
My back hurts.
[WOMAN E]
I wanna go home.
[HANAJIMA]
The voices... won't stop.
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER] I know she's
had this power since birth,
but it's still hard
to see her like this.
I'm her dad and I can't help.
We'll figure something out.
If we took her to a hospital,
we might do more harm than good.
That's true, but I'm
worried about her.
The power she has,
people will fear it,
and perhaps her, as well.
They fear what they
can't understand.
[HANAJIMA]
A kind family. Kind voices.
I didn't want them getting
hurt because of my power.
So I did what I could to keep
it secret from others.
[CLASSMATE A]
There she is!
Yeah, the witch is here!
You gonna say somethin', witch?
[CLASSMATES laughing]
You guys are being
jerks. Stop it.
[CLASSMATE B] Why should we?
Look how creepy she is.
[CLASSMATE A]
She never even talks.
[CLASSMATE D]
How does that make her a witch?
[CLASSMATE A]
Eat this!
Aw, come on, aren't ya hungry?
My sister said
witches eat live newts,
so I thought you'd like it.
You're wrong. I can't eat tha‐‐
[CLASSMATE A]
Shut it! Help me hold her head!
‐‐Try and open up!
‐‐What are you doing?!
Ew! She actually ate it!
She really is a witch!
[CLASSMATE A, CLASSMATE B
laughing]
[CLASSMATE A]
Witch! What a freak!
[HANAJIMA]
Shut up.
[CLASSMATE B]
Gross! Ha‐ha!
[HANAJIMA] If I'm a witch,
what does that make you?
You think this is a joke?
You think it's funny?
Tormenting someone like this?
I hate you. I hate you so much.
You should just die.
Just die. Just die. Just die.
Die!
[gasps]
[HANAJIMA'S MOTHER] He finally
regained consciousness
this morning, but shortly after,
his mother collapsed, too.
I suppose the strain
was too much for her.
Do they know why the boy
lost consciousness?
No, that's still unknown.
[HANAJIMA] It's because
I wanted him to die.
I willed that boy to die over
and over again in my mind,
and that's why‐‐
[HANAJIMA'S MOTHER]
Saki‐chan, don't!
When are you going to have
the police come and take me?
They'll arrest me
for what I did.
They have to. I tried
to murder someone.
They won't.
There's no proof your power was
responsible for it. You only‐‐
[HANAJIMA]
There's no proof my power
wasn't responsible
for it, either.
Saki.
[HANAJIMA]
It's true.
I wanted him to go away.
Forever.
Next time, it might work...
I might actually kill someone.
I'm scared.
[STUDENTS whispering]
[HANAJIMA]
From then on, I only wore black.
We don't want a witch
like you in our school.
Stay away from us, freak!
[HANAJIMA]
The other students disliked me
even more than before,
and kept their distance.
[HANAJIMA] After what I'd done,
I felt like I deserved it.
[STUDENT A, STUDENT B chuckling]
[STUDENT B]
Hey! Watch it!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENT A yelps]
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[STUDENT A gasps]
Ow, man.
You witch! You just
cursed him, didn't you?
No way! Why would you
make him fall down?
[STUDENT A]
It hurts!
He'll be fine, but he's staying
the night in the hospital.
[HANAJIMA'S GRANDMOTHER]
I don't understand.
Why are they blaming our Saki?
Because... the kids say she
made it happen with a curse.
[HANAJIMA'S GRANDMOTHER]
You're kidding! That's absurd!
Megumi. What's that?
Why are you reading
those books again?
They're for research.
Granny said they might
help us figure out
what your power is
and how it works.
Saki, you don't tell.
No matter what they do
to you, you don't tell.
Why don't you speak up?
Say something about how
the other kids bully you?
Do you think you deserve
it? Is that why?
[HANAJIMA] There's no proof,
so the police can't arrest me.
But still, I should be punished.
It wasn't just some
childish taunt or insult.
In that moment,
I honestly wanted him to
die more than anything.
Of course I deserve
to be punished.
[MEGUMI]
You really mean it.
And is that all other people
will ever be to you?
A way to punish yourself for
thoughts you had as a child?
Is this how you're gonna
live your entire life?
All right, then I'm
going to pray for you.
You're lonely, and
whatever may've happened,
you shouldn't have to
live like that forever.
This world is full of people,
and I know that somewhere in it,
there is someone who will see
you for who you truly are.
They'll see.
And they'll cherish you for it.
So, please, whoever you are...
...wherever you are...
...come to her.
If you're in a country
far away, get on a plane.
Come to Saki as fast as you can,
because she deserves
to meet you.
Please.
[HANAJIMA] I thought it
was a ridiculous prayer.
One that would
never be answered.
[STUDENT C]
They say you can use evil waves
against people when you get mad.
Come on, you gotta
show us, just once.
[STUDENT D] I don't think
this is such a good idea.
[STUDENT C] Don't chicken out.
Keep holding her down.
[STUDENT E]
But I heard she can actually
kill you with her power.
Are you really
such scaredy‐cats?
I, for one, am not
afraid of this girl.
[gasps]
[STUDENT C] Now... She just
needs a little inspiration.
[HANAJIMA]
Don't!
[STUDENT C laughs]
[STUDENT F]
Aw. Did you get an ouchie?
[STUDENT E]
Poor baby.
[HANAJIMA] Don't think of
anything. Clear your mind.
Focus on nothing but the pain.
Don't let your anger take over.
Don't let anyone
get hurt or die.
Don't go out of control.
Don't kill anyone!
What's going on in here?
[STUDENT E]
Crap!
[STUDENT C]
Oh, uh, Sensei.
Hanajima was playing
around with matches.
[STUDENT D] Yeah, we were
just trying to stop her.
[HANAJIMA]
This is good. Nobody got hurt.
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER]
We should move.
Look, I know you
don't want to admit
that those girls are to blame,
but your mother
and I are worried.
This can't keep happening.
We'll find a new school.
One you can actually enjoy.
You three should move
away and leave me here.
If I went along, I'd just cause
even more trouble for you.
No, never!
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER]
Saki.
Don't assume that you're
causing trouble for anyone.
This is how parenting works.
We'll always be concerned.
That's because we love our
kids with all our hearts.
It's true. We love you, Saki.
So, please...
Don't give up just yet.
Things are gonna get better.
[TEACHER A]
Come here, Hanajima.
Care to explain why
your nails are black?
And on the first day of
school, too. Take it off.
[HANAJIMA] It's because I
can't wear a black uniform.
Uh. And what does your uniform
color have to do with anything?
The wearing of black is
a symbol of my prior sin.
Don't you want the
other students warned?
[CLASSMATE G]
Sensei!
Hanajima's wearing
black nail polish.
[TEACHER A] Apparently,
it's her badge of sin.
Let's go together...
[HANAJIMA] Even though I
was in a new environment,
I was careful not to
get close to anybody.
Doing so wouldn't
have felt right.
Like I'd be ignoring the
horrible thing I'd done.
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER]
Don't give up just yet.
[HANAJIMA]
On what?
What am I supposed to
be holding out for?
Huh?
It smells good.
Yeah I know, right?
Thanks so much.
[TOHRU]
Hope you enjoy it!
We're giving out bigger servings
today. Glad you're here!
By the way, I'm Tohru Honda.
Nice to meet you, Hanajima.
The food at this school
is so delicious,
I just know you're
gonna love it!
‐‐Let me know what you think.
‐‐[CLASSMATE J] Shut it, Honda.
We're all starving here
and you're holding up
the whole line.
Please accept my
humble apologies!
[HANAJIMA]
Awfully flighty.
And why does she
speak so politely?
I'm surprised she talked
to me without hesitation.
Most people are too afraid.
[UOTANI]
Yo. Newbie transfer student.
I bet you're planning
to eat lunch alone, huh?
That kinda bothers me,
so take a seat right here.
[HANAJIMA] Another person
who's not intimidated.
You've got a whole doom
and gloom vibe about you,
that's why people are
keeping their distance.
Hey. Tohru, over here!
Thank you for waiting for me!
This is perfect! Are you gonna
have lunch at our table, too?
Uh‐huh. I just
scored us a third.
Oh! What a wonderful surprise!
[HANAJIMA]
Maybe she's polite to everybody.
[TOHRU] Right this way.
I promise neither of us bite.
Please sit and make yourself
at home as we eat together.
"Hanajima," huh?
If Kyoko was here, she'd say,
"You're now Hana‐chan!"
Oh, yes! Naturally!
Can we call you
that from now on?
[HANAJIMA]
They are so odd.
I apologize. But I'm afraid
I won't be eating with you two.
The fact is, it's
better if you don't
involve yourselves with me.
It would only bring
pain, nothing more.
[UOTANI]
Huh?
Oh, no, am I the same way?
Do I bring nothing
but pain to people?
I bet people get double the pain
whenever they get
involved with me.
[UOTANI cackling]
I don't know what got lost,
but it wasn't my intention
to depress her or
make you laugh.
Understand?
[gasps] Yes. I do understand.
I'll work harder to bring
happiness into people's lives.
[HANAJIMA] Nor was I asking you
to create new life goals.
[UOTANI]
Eh. Whatever.
No need to sweat over
anything like that.
Think about the good parts
of your transfer today.
It's beautiful outside,
we've got good food,
and you get to eat with
us big ol' weirdoes.
Lunch is better together.
You are both so strange.
[BOTH]
We get that a lot!
[TOHRU, UOTANI laugh]
[TOHRU] I hope we get the
chance to see you soon.
[UOTANI] Of course we will.
She does go to school here now.
Then let's have a
second lunch date.
See ya tomorrow.
[HANAJIMA] No one's ever looked
forward to lunch with me,
or said, "See you tomorrow."
Will they greet me
with "good morning"
like we're friends as well?
[TOHRU]
Hi! Good morning, Hana‐chan!
P.E. is gonna be great today.
I can't wait for the pool and‐‐
Oops, you seem lost
in thought, so...
[UOTANI]
What's goin' on?
You're blushin' like you
just confessed your love.
[TOHRU]
Maybe... Maybe I...
[HANAJIMA] It happened
because I was happy.
I kept thinking it was a mistake
for them to get me
involved in their lives.
But before I knew it,
we were a trio.
Suddenly, I belonged.
[UOTANI]
Whoa!
Another gorgeous red sunset.
[TOHRU]
So pretty!
It's such a gentle color.
[UOTANI]
Agreed.
You're right!
[HANAJIMA] We'll have good
weather tomorrow, too.
[UOTANI]
Hope so.
[TOHRU]
Oh, me, too!
[HANAJIMA] Swept up by
these new friendships,
I almost forgot
my place in life.
But after two seasons,
I remembered.
[CLASSMATE F]
Um. Hey, Hanajima.
They say you killed a boy,
back in elementary school.
That can't be true, right?
[CLASSMATE K] I heard you used‐‐
What did they call them?
Evil waves or something?
Huh? Waves?
[CLASSMATE F] I mean,
it's probably just a rumor.
But people are also
spreading the word
that you were a delinquent
who smoked all the time
and burned the arm of a girl
who tried to get you to stop.
[CLASSMATE F]
You killed...
[CLASSMATE K]
And that you transferred here
because you caused
problems for everyone.
[CLASSMATE F]
You killed a boy.
Ouch!
Hey!
[HANAJIMA gasps]
Ow.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
[CLASSMATE F] There was
suddenly this sharp pain
shooting through my head.
Did you... do this?
[CLASSMATE F]
But why?
Hana‐ chan ! Don't go!
Please, come back!
[HANAJIMA]
I'm so... scared.
Did I just use my power again
and not even realize it?
[TOHRU]
Hana‐chan!
[HANAJIMA]
Stay back!
You shouldn't come near me.
I'm not right.
I should've been honest
with you. I'm so sorry.
But please... This is the end.
You two shouldn't hang
out with me anymore.
Those girls? They were right
about my wave powers.
I almost killed someone.
So, please. Leave me.
[HANAJIMA] I have a sin
that will never fade.
A stain that won't wash away.
I don't want to hurt
anyone else.
If the punishment
for what I've done
is to be shunned
the rest of my life,
then so be it.
But we're growing into
such close friends.
Don't you feel that?
I do, and I don't
want it to go away.
I want us to grow even closer.
[TOHRU] There may be things
I still don't know about you,
but please, give me the
chance to learn them.
Okay?
Don't let this be
the end, Hana‐chan.
I love you.
So much.
Do you hear me? We both do!
[HANAJIMA]
But I might hurt you.
Like I did to that boy before.
Maybe I don't deserve this.
[UOTANI]
It's your decision.
[gasps]
Don't go assuming that
you're causin' us trouble.
Do you really wanna
break things off?
That's what matters.
It's all I need to know.
[HANAJIMA'S FATHER]
Don't assume that you're
causing trouble for anyone.
[HANAJIMA] Before them,
when I'd walk home,
the sky would make me
feel so terribly lonely
that I'd begin to tremble.
But at some point, the sky
took on a certain gentleness.
And there was more than
one shadow on the ground.
It seemed like such a
small thing at the time,
but we were together.
[HANAJIMA]
I'm sorry.
Together.
Please.
I want to be friends
with you so much.
[MEGUMI]
I'll pray for you.
There is someone who will see
you for who you truly are.
They'll see.
And they'll cherish you for it.
[MEGUMI]
I'll pray.
So, please...
Don't give up yet.
[HANAJIMA gasps]
[HANAJIMA'S MOTHER]
Hm? What is it?
I couldn't hear anything.
I think... I was able to
block the voices just now.
You mean it? Saki!
That's wonderful!
Whaddaya know...
How did you do it?
[HANAJIMA] There was a flash,
and then a whoosh.
Hey, kid, that make
any sense to you?
Basically, she learned
to trick the waves.
[HANAJIMA] It would still
be a while before I learned
to fully control my power.
I couldn't help but
wonder, though,
if this was all because I
didn't feel so alone anymore.
Regardless, I never
used my power
for the mere pleasure of it.
[KINOSHITA] Ah! Does the air
feel weird to you all of...
[HANAJIMA]
Just to chastise people a bit.
I think it's more
than just a bit!
[MEGUMI] How much longer are you
going to dress only in black?
[HANAJIMA]
I'm not sure.
It's been so long since
I've worn anything else.
I'm not certain I'd be able
to relax in other colors.
You don't have to
keep wearing black
just to make me feel better.
I promise I don't mind
being the only one.
No, this color helps
me to relax, too.
And besides, think
what would happen
if we suddenly started
wearing pastels.
I bet the entire neighborhood
would freak out.
That's true. That could be
quite interesting, though.
In some ways.
[HANAJIMA]
I'm grateful, you know.
To Dad and Mom.
And you.
[TOHRU]
Hana‐chan! Megumi!
We should probably get going!
Less talking, more walking.
[HANAJIMA]
Sometimes, my heart hurts.
Mostly when I think
about how selfish it is
that I felt I needed more,
even though I had a family
who loved me so much.
[KYOKO]
We need other people.
You just can't live a
fulfilling life without them.
In fact,
I bet that no matter how much
others might oppress you,
how hopeless you feel,
or how loved you
are by your family,
you'll always want to be
accepted by other people.
That's my theory. Ha.
And also, for parents...
Well, as long as our
kids seem happy,
then... that's really the
only thing that matters.
That's why, even if
someday you three
go your own separate ways,
doesn't mean anyone gave up.
And you don't need to feel
lonely if that happens.
Trust me on this.
[KYOKO] Because the
memory of your friendship
will always stay with you.
There are some things
that last forever.
[KAZUMA]
"You look well."