[ART grunts]
[MOGETA]
Moge!
Aw, man. How can I beat
somebody this strong?
[DEMON LORD A laughs]
[DEMON LORD A]
Look at you, Art!
Trembling in the
face of my power!
As you should be.
This is a welcome
change from home,
where my wife rules with
an iron fist and no mercy!
[ART]
Ah!
Seriously? What is
wrong with you?
Don't take your marriage
issues out on me!
Mogeta!
[ART]
Let's go, Mogeta!
Triple Turbo‐Charge Swat...
I guess even bad guys have their
own struggles to overcome, huh?
But his wife probably
has reasons for acting
the way she does, too.
Aw. This is a complicated issue.
[TUKI]
I have issues with this show,
but its complexity
isn't one of them.
[door opens]
[SHIGURE]
Good morning.
Good morning to you, too!
Try again. It's evening now.
Why can't you sleep
like a normal person?
But that's precisely
why I became a writer.
So I wouldn't have to. Uh.
Who's this? She looks
an awful lot like Kisa.
How would you like some
yummy candy, Sat‐chan?
Are you still asleep?
Or was that just another of your
creepy attempts at being funny?
[SHIGURE]
You wound me!
What have I done to deserve such
coldness from my dear cousin?
Let the poor thing go.
You'll contaminate her.
[SHIGURE] Well, anyway,
tell me the latest.
How's school?
Good. I've been
trying very hard.
It's easier now. Trying, I mean.
Because my mom's there for me,
and all of you are, too.
I'm not alone, so...
I love you so much!
It's an explosion of cute.
[HIRO]
Auntie, where's Kisa?
Oh, right.
She's actually having a little
sleepover at Shigure's house.
I swear, that girl is positively
smitten with Tohru.
[HIRO]
Hm.
Oh, wow. I got here a little
earlier than I usually do.
Guess I can kill some time
in the changing room.
[TOHRU]
A shoe?
I wonder where it
could've fallen from.
[HIRO]
Hey.
Pick that up.
[TOHRU] Aww. Oh my gosh,
he's adorable!
[HIRO]
Well, hurry.
Right. Of course. Here ya go.
[chuckles]
I can't believe you
picked it up. Cretin.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[HIRO] Do you have no sense
of identity or agency?
Would you dance if
I said to dance?
Or fall to the ground
if I told you to?
[TOHRU]
No?
[HIRO] I can't stand people
who let themselves
be pushed around so easily.
Well, are you going
to give that back?
Or steal it? You a thief?
Uh. No, of course I'm not.
[TOHRU]
I'm so confused.
Come on. Couldn't you at least
make an effort to be polite?
I came all the way
here to meet you.
Huh? But why would you‐‐?
Ask yourself, who'd
wanna waste their time
coming to see you?
Or does that kind of analysis
hurt your tiny brain?
[gasps] You're a zodiac!
It's about time, you idiot.
[TOHRU]
Oh. Sorry.
[HIRO]
Pathetic.
You don't live up to
your reputation at all.
This was dumb. I should've
just stayed at home.
You'll have to take
me out to eat now.
Uh. Huh?!
What? Problem?
I figure you owe me a meal
for the inconvenience.
[TOHRU] Oh, but I really can't
be late for my shift at work,
and I don't have much
money on me, so I don't‐‐
Wait, so you're expecting me
to pick up the whole tab?
Real jerk move,
mooching off a kid.
Honestly, extorting an innocent
child to fill your own stomach?
How low can you get?
[TOHRU]
But.
So selfish. You ought
to be ashamed of yourself.
Well, I don't‐‐
Are you lying about
having no money?
Uh.
Show me your wallet
and prove it!
Oh, don't. I‐‐
Well, your bag's sure
seen better days.
[chuckles]
This pocketbook isn't
too bad, though.
The color's nice enough, anyway.
Think I'll keep it.
What? No, please!
You can't take that.
[HIRO]
I'm Hiro Soma.
Might as well introduce myself,
although I doubt
we'll meet again.
Bye. Thanks for the amazingly
boring experience.
Wait. Please come back here.
Hey, you don't understand.
There's a picture of
my mother... in there.
My mom was just kidnapped
by a member of the zodiac.
She's gone. I need
to get her back.
I can't worry about getting
to work on time right now.
[MOMIJI]
Tohru?
Why are you sitting in the
middle of the sidewalk?
Momiji, it's gone.
[MOMIJI] Whatever it is must be
important. You look so lost.
[HIRO]
So she's a mama's girl, huh?
What a loser.
[KYO]
Hiro?
What the heck are you
hangin' around here for?
[HIRO] I don't see why
it's any of your business.
Wait, hold on. Are you saying
that I can't sit here?
I need your permission
all of a sudden?
You must think pretty
highly of yourself,
giving orders like that.
Ha! Everyone bow
before King Kyo.
[KYO]
Okay, brat, cut the crap.
I don't have to listen to this
from some stupid little kid.
Real mature, losing your
temper with some "kid."
Agh! I'm gonna punch
you into next week!
[TOHRU]
Hiro!
My pocketbook. I need‐‐
What's wrong?
[TOHRU]
I need my pocketbook.
Mom's in there.
Hiro! What did you do to her?
It sounds like you're
accusing me without proof.
In which case, I hope
you're prepared
to make restitution
if I'm innocent.
All I did was take
her pocketbook.
[KYO] Then obviously
you're not innocent!
Give it back right now!
Why should I, though?
That idiotic girl practically
begged me to take it.
All right, that's enough!
Shut your mouth
before I do it for you.
‐‐[TOHRU] Kyo, wait!
‐‐If you wanna get arrested
for beating up a child,
be my guest.
Ah!
[KISA]
Hiro‐chan!
Hiro‐chan, did you
steal from Tohru?
Please say no.
Ah, Kisa, what a fun surprise!
But I don't get it.
What're you doin' here?
[chuckles]
[HIRO]
Someone fetched her.
It seems the Rabbit's
been sticking his nose
where it doesn't belong.
So it's true?
But stealing is wrong.
You have to give back
what you took from Tohru,
or she'll be sad.
[KISA]
Will you? Please?
[HIRO]
This is dumb.
I don't even want
this thing. Take it!
Das ist keine Art!
Hiro!
[TOHRU] No, it's okay.
Everything's fine now.
It's not fine!
[KISA] Hiro‐chan, tell me:
Why did you do that?
I don't like it when you do
things that make people sad.
It's mean.
What's so great
about her, anyway?
It's like that idiot
is the only thing
you can talk about these days.
You even took the Mogeta DVD
straight to her place to watch.
I lent it to you.
I was gonna watch it with you.
I don't understand.
It didn't seem like you
wanted to watch it before.
I figured you wouldn't care.
[HIRO] I'm not interested in
this, but you like it, right?
You can borrow it.
It's nothing I'd watch.
Seriously? Do I have to spell
out everything? Just think!
She's not a mind reader.
[HIRO]
Shut up, bunny boy!
I mean, I know I couldn't
do anything to help
when you were going
through all that stuff.
But still... I was worried.
Really worried.
And I just felt so helpless.
[gasps]
Any idea what's going on?
You're so dense, Kyo.
‐‐Huh?
‐‐Isn't it obvious?
Hiro was jealous of Tohru.
He's trying, but...
You remember what sixth
grade was like, right?
Feelings are scary.
[KISA]
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
We'll watch it together.
Next time, okay?
So he lashed out because
he thought he had
a rival for Kisa's affection.
I wouldn't want to
be in your shoes.
Huh?
There's one more thing.
I want you to tell Tohru
that you're sorry.
She's right, Hiro. Do it.
Tohru is late to work
because of you.
Actually, an apology's
not enough.
I think Hiro needs to
be punished for this.
You do, do you?
And what's this
"punishment" gonna be?
[TOHRU] I sentence you
to the hug penalty!
Come on. What kinda
punishment is that?
[MOMIJI chuckles]
I guess she couldn't wait
to find out what year he is!
[giggles]
You're forgiven. I'm so glad
I got to meet you, Hiro!
[TOHRU] I met a new member
of the zodiac today, Mom.
I can tell he's super smart,
but he's still so young.
And it turns out he's in love‐‐
in the most adorably
awkward way.
[DEMON LORD A laughs]
[DEMON LORD A]
Look at you, Art.
Trembling in the
face of my power!
As you should be.
This is a welcome
change from home,
where my wife rules with
an iron fist and no mercy!
What, so he'd quit being a jerk
if his wife was a little
bit nicer to him?
Does it not occur to this guy
that maybe he just sucks?
The character development
in this show is lacking.
Perhaps we could all just keep
our insights to ourselves.
[HIRO]
Well?
How long are you gonna make me
wait for another cup? Fill it.
Unless you were intentionally
depriving me?
No! I didn't notice
it was empty.
Like you even care. I can't
stand inconsiderate people.
Be nice.
It's fine. I don't mind, really.
[HIRO] It's not fine.
You should be more observant.
Right! I'll do my best.
[KYO] Hey, stop treating
her like she's a servant.
You're a guest in this house,
so try actin' like it.
And why are you spending all
your days off here, anyway?
Isn't there anyone else
you can go and annoy?
[HIRO]
Did I miss something?
'Cause last time I checked,
the Cat wasn't the
master of this house.
What are you contributing
that gives you the right
to complain about it?
People who whine about their
situation while accepting
no responsibility
are so irritating.
[KYO]
I wanna punch this kid so hard.
[HIRO] Any snot‐nosed brat
can point out an issue
without solving it.
[KYO] I'm lookin' at a
snot‐nose brat right now!
[SHIGURE] Okay, stop.
Go easy on the boy.
It's only a phase. Some
pre‐teen rebelliousness.
Oh, yeah?
Well, he can go rebel at
the main estate, then!
And preferably do all of
his flirting there, too!
Don't be cruel.
That sort of thing is already
difficult enough for any kid.
Being a member of the
zodiac just makes it harder.
Flirting's not easy in
or out of the compound.
It takes determination
and skill. Y'know?
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
Anyway, you shouldn't let him
put your back up like that.
Losing your temper only proves
that you're still in
your rebellious phase.
[KYO]
Tch.
Strive to emulate a
mature adult, like me.
[MITSURU]
"Adult"?
In what world does a man
who can't meet his deadlines
count as an adult?
Hello.
She was at the door, seconds
away from hanging herself.
Tell me why!
Why won't you finish on time
no matter how much I beg you?
[SHIGURE]
It's a real mystery, isn't it?
We may never know.
[cries] You're a jerk, Sensei!
[SHIGURE]
Okay, okay. I'll do it.
What? You're gonna
write, really?
[MITSURU giggles]
Oh! I just remembered
a pressing errand.
Don't worry. I'll be right back.
[MITSURU screams]
No, wait! Whatever it is,
do it later! Sensei...
It's so noisy.
What's it take to get some
peace and quiet around here?
More tea. I'm still thirsty.
I told you to stop that!
I'll go get another pot started.
And you stop obeying
his every word!
Forget you guys.
I'm outta here.
[YUKI]
Peace and quiet?
That's definitely in short
supply these days.
Hiro‐chan, you act
kinda mean around Tohru.
Do you hate her?
Dunno. Yeah, maybe.
Um, okay, but then why do you
always wanna come over here?
[HIRO]
For you.
I may not like her, but you do.
You're right.
I get this warm feeling inside,
just from being around her.
Sorry it took so long.
Hm?
[HIRO]
Bathroom.
I'm sorry. He, um,
really is a nice person.
[TOHRU chuckles]
You two seem so close. You
must be friends from way back.
[KISA]
Actually, for a long time,
I thought Hiro‐chan hated me.
About a year ago, we would
play together all the time.
But then...
...he suddenly started
ignoring me, completely.
And I didn't know why.
[KISA] So when he said that
stuff earlier, I was surprised.
[HIRO]
I was worried. Really worried.
And happy.
It must've been nice to hear.
[HIRO]
Hey.
Oh! I didn't realize
you were back.
The tea is ready
if you'd like some.
You're off today.
I'm bored here.
You should take us out.
Somewhere fun.
Um, okay, where would
you like to go?
Really? You can't even decide
that much for yourself?
Don't you have opinions
about anything?
Or are you happy
to blithely walk along
whatever path others
set out for you?
Wow! That must be an easy life,
letting everyone else
take the initiative.
I'm sorry.
[HATORI] Whether out of
ignorance or innocence,
Hiro must not have realized
how Akito would react
to what he was going to say.
And likely thought it was safer
than staying silent
on the matter.
[HIRO]
I love her. I love Kisa.
[HATORI]
You can guess the result.
It took Kisa two weeks to heal
after Akito was done with her.
I can only imagine what
kind of shape she was in.
[HATORI]
From the sound of it,
Hiro avoided her as much
as possible after that.
Which means he wasn't
around to help
when Kisa's classmates
started bullying her.
A person Hiro loved
got badly hurt
because of something he did.
Anyone would be scared.
And now, he's probably furious
with himself for what happened,
but he doesn't know
what to do with that rage.
It's not as if he
can blame Akito.
So he's taking it out on
poor, innocent Tohru instead.
Another victim of
youthful folly. Tragic.
[HATORI]
I'm surprised, though.
By what?
I assumed you would've known
about this long before now.
I thought Akito told you about
anything concerning the family.
[SHIGURE laughs]
Apparently even I am
only trusted so far.
Let Akito scheme.
[HATORI]
Hm?
When the dust settles,
one of us will be sorry.
But it won't be me.
You're a child.
[SHIGURE] Yes. I'm disgustingly,
unrepentantly immature.
I worry what will happen
if Akito eventually does
take it out on Honda.
Like Hiro did.
I have to say, we really
are terrible at this.
The whole "love" thing.
When it comes to cherishing
another person,
we Somas are lost.
[HIRO]
This is just a park.
[TOHRU]
Yep! Cool, huh?
Uh, no.
You could've taken us to a
movie or an amusement park,
but your pea‐sized brain chose
this dump of a place instead.
Are you kidding?
[TOHRU]
Well, honestly,
I don't have a lot
of money right now,
so this is the best I could do.
It's great! I like
coming to the park.
Fine, I forgive you.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
Look! There's a
crepe truck here.
Would you guys like to get some?
Kisa, want one?
Sure.
Okay, what kind do you want?
I'll have a chocolate one.
Right! And do you have
a favorite flavor, Kisa?
Maybe strawberry.
But, no, wait...
[TOHRU]
Is there another kind you like?
[KISA]
Banana.
Both, then, and
we'll go halfsies.
[KISA]
Mh‐hm!
[TOHRU] Give me a sec.
I'll be right back.
[TOHRU]
Okay, I'll take
one chocolate, one strawberry,
and one chocolate banana please.
[VENDOR A] Got it!
It'll be a minute or two.
Thank you!
Let's see...
[TOHRU grunts]
Uh, I'm sorry, did you
need something?
I'm paying for my crepe,
and Kisa's, too.
[TOHRU]
Right. Okay.
[HIRO]
I don't understand.
You're nothing but a
spineless space cadet.
If you could do it,
why couldn't I?
[TOHRU]
Hm?
Hey, are you as great
as everybody says?
[TOHRU]
Uh.
Can you magically make
people's worries disappear
and give them hope
where they had none?
Can you erase sorrow?
Eliminate pain?
Can you save people?
Uh, no. I can't do
anything like that.
Modesty only makes it seem like
you're fishing for compliments.
It's stupid.
Right.
[HIRO]
I loved her.
I wanted to be true
to my feelings.
And I thought I could
make Akito understand.
[HIRO]
But... I'm a coward.
Kisa got hurt because of me,
and I didn't say anything.
Not to her or Akito.
[HIRO]
Why?
I'm such a child.
Pathetic and naive.
I mean, I can't do anything.
I'm just a bratty kid.
[HIRO] But I got jealous
when she showed up
and actually helped.
What's wrong with me?
[HIRO] I'm sick of how
childish I am. How useless.
I don't wanna be like this.
I wanna be an adult.
Someone she can count on.
But I don't know how.
You're amazing, Hiro.
It's really hard to believe
you're only in sixth grade.
Shut up.
I wasn't asking you to make
me feel better or anything.
Hold on, are you
buttering me up?
No, I promise I'm not.
My mom told me that it's
really scary to admit
you're still a child and have
a lot to learn about the world.
A lot of people avoid facing the
truth and ignore it, instead.
It's hard.
So if someone can admit they've
still got growing up to do,
well, they must be
really brave, right?
You say you can't do anything,
but that's not true.
Someday, you'll be
able to protect Kisa,
like a prince out
of a fairytale.
So, do me a favor.
Don't sell yourself short, Hiro.
You have courage in your heart.
[HIRO]
I see.
Basically, you're trying
to tell me that there's
nothing princely whatsoever
about me right now, is that it?
Uh! No! That's not
what I meant at all.
Well, guess you're
not wrong about that.
[VENDOR A]
Here you go, dear.
Thanks!
Hang on.
I figure that little speech was
worth the price of a crepe.
So I'll treat you, this once.
Uh.
[HIRO]
She's so embarrassing.
"Prince"? Please.
You can't say stuff like that.
Not without anything
to back it up.
What if she's wrong about me?
Is she gonna take
responsibility?
If I just.... can't?
[TOHRU]
You have courage in your heart.
What happened?
You're kinda smiling.
Did something make you happy?
[HIRO]
I'll do it. Just you watch.
I swear.
[TOHRU]
Hiro! You forgot your change!
[HANAJIMA] "I never back
down from a wave fight."