Hey! I can't find her.
She's gone!
Don't get your
whiskers in a knot.
She said she was going
out to visit a friend.
Are you incapable of
listening when people talk?
Uh.
She never goes out, so what
am I supposed to think?!
Well, I'd say Kyo's
hissy fit has shown us
just how much a part of the
household Tohru's become.
He's positively lost
without our fair maiden.
[TOHRU]
Wow. This place is huge.
I came without telling
Soma and the others
just like Hatori said I should,
but now I wonder if that
was such a good idea.
[MOMIJI]
Tohru! Hallo!
[TOHRU yelping]
[MOMIJI]
You're here right on time!
I'm sorry! You startled me!
‐‐[door opens]
‐‐Huh?
Come on in. Welcome
to the Soma estate.
Thanks. It's really something.
Harry's house is down this way.
[TOHRU]
I can't believe how quiet it is.
Almost like nobody
actually lives here.
I guess it's sort of peaceful.
But it's also
making me nervous!
Welcome to my home.
[TOHRU panting]
[HATORI] I didn't realize the
walk here was so arduous.
Oh, it's not.
Come on in and have a seat.
Momiji, bring us
something to drink.
Ja!
A drink sounds great, thanks.
[TOHRU]
Huh.
It's kinda surprising to see a
woman's photograph on his desk.
He comes off as a
really stern person,
and something about his voice
makes it sound like
he's always angry.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Is that why I'm here?
Is‐Is he going to scold me for
being hopelessly incompetent?
[MOMIJI]
Tohru?
[TOHRU yelps]
What's the matter?
Do you feel sick?
Harry is a doctor.
[TOHRU] Oh, no! I'm
absolutely fine, I swear!
'Kay. Then why don't we
go ahead and sit down?
[TOHRU] So, um. Are you
a doctor at a hospital?
Did you have to take time
off to meet with me here?
No. I don't treat anyone
outside the Soma clan.
I'm the family doctor.
Though half my job is
babysitting its head.
Constantly getting sick
is Akito's specialty.
[MOMIJI] Plus, all of the
Somas are super busy today,
so nobody will stop
by for an exam.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
They're getting ready
for New Year's!
It's a big event here for us,
so outside people will pitch in
to help with the
preparations, too,
and not just inside ones.
[TOHRU]
Outside? Inside?
Yep!
See, the members of the main
family are on the "inside."
Remember the tree‐lined road?
The one that leads
to the front gate?
We call the residents of that
area "outside" people.
I think there are
about ein hundert?
A hundred of them.
There are another 50
living on the inside.
And all 150 of us are Somas!
Wow. That's a really big family!
[MOMIJI] The only people
who can live "inside"
are zodiac members like us,
or people who know our secret.
Shii‐chan and Yuki
are gone now,
but they used to live here, too.
Kyo was outside, though.
I don't know how skilled
you are at math,
but that means even
within the Soma family,
a full two‐thirds aren't
aware of the zodiac secret.
So perhaps you can see
how outrageous it is
for a complete stranger
like you to know it.
Ordinarily, I would've
wiped your memory
as soon as you learned about it.
But Akito hasn't given me the
order to, for whatever reason.
Tell me, do you enjoy
living at Shigure's house?
Uh, yes. I do.
I recommend moving
out immediately.
Stay away from the
Somas from now on.
You seem to think our possessed
family is fascinating,
maybe even delightful.
But it's not.
We're monstrous.
Loathsome. Cursed.
So listen when I tell you:
Leave before you regret ever
associating with the Somas.
Make no mistake, Akito
is trying to use you.
[doorbell rings]
[HATORI]
Wait here for a moment.
[TOHRU] "Cursed"?
What did he mean by that?
[MOMIJI]
You should know.
Harry is almost entirely
blind in his left eye.
He used to have a girlfriend.
Her name was Kana.
She was really nice.
They were even
going to get married.
But... Akito got angry.
[MOMIJI]
So, so angry.
Said they weren't
allowed to get married,
then lashed out, and
injured Harry's eye.
But you know what?
Harry never blamed Akito.
As for Kana, she blamed herself.
She said it was her
fault he got hurt.
She felt so guilty,
she became depressed.
Like she'd never be happy again.
Finally, Harry decided to
erase Kana's memories.
He couldn't stand to watch
her fall apart anymore.
So, he took away all
the memories she had
of them being in love.
[MOMIJI]
Kana left the estate.
Harry cried when she went.
But even then,
he didn't blame Akito.
[TOHRU]
Why not?
[MOMIJI]
Because... that's the curse.
Harry doesn't want to see any
more people end up like Kana.
He doesn't want you to get hurt
by the curse like she did.
[TOHRU crying]
[MOMIJI]
Wait, are you crying?
Oh, no! Did I make you cry?
Tohru. I'm so sorry!
[TOHRU]
It's not that.
It's just... Hatori's so kind
to be worried about me.
Whatever happens,
I'm glad I met all of you.
Even if Hatori's right, and I'm
being used for some reason,
I can only feel grateful for it.
And I know I'll never regret
meeting Soma and
Kyo and Shigure.
If it weren't for them,
I wouldn't be who I am now.
And me, too?
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[MOMIJI]
Are you glad that you met me?
Of course I am.
[SHIGURE]
Don't look so glum, you two.
I promise we're not using Tohru.
‐‐[TOHRU] Shigure!
‐‐[MOMIJI] Shii‐chan!
Doc Hatori here can be
a bit melodramatic.
It's a character flaw.
[TOHRU]
What brought you here?
My gut! It told me
to come, Tohru!
It's a novelist thing.
I have a keen sixth sense.
Clearly a lie.
You only came to check on
the New Year's preparations.
[SHIGURE] Ugh. The common folk
are so quick to envy geniuses.
Tragic, really.
[HATORI]
Genius?
You'd never guess it,
but those two are best friends.
Honestly, with all
the worrying you do,
it's a wonder
you're not bald yet.
I keep telling you Akito
doesn't mean any harm to Tohru,
but you refuse to believe me.
And now you've gone
and scared the poor girl.
What if she actually moves out?
[TOHRU]
Please. It's okay, really.
Just knowing you were concerned
about me means a lot, thank you.
But I'm going to stay
where I am for now.
Very well. Be sure to
take this with you.
[TOHRU]
Hm?
[HATORI] It's the camera
from the culture festival.
Why give it to me?
Our deal. Have you
forgotten it already?
I told you that
if you came here,
I would surrender
the camera to you.
If you don't show up,
I trust you know what'll happen.
[TOHRU]
That's not what he said at all!
I guess Hatori and
Shigure are both
"my way or the highway"
types of people.
I forgot. I haven't
introduced you to Akito.
Um. It's okay, really.
I don't mind.
I was wondering, though,
you're a member of
the zodiac, too, right?
Which of the spirits are you?
[SHIGURE laughs]
Now that's an
excellent question!
And the answer's hilarious.
I'll call your publisher
and tell them
every embarrassing thing you've
done since you were four.
Right. Lips sealed.
[HATORI]
I apologize for today.
Huh?
All I did was make
you cry. I'm sorry.
[SHIGURE]
I'll stay for a bit.
I still need to sneak a peek
at the celebration set‐up.
And I've got a dance
rehearsal to get to.
[TOHRU]
Dance?
Yes, it's sort of like a ritual
we perform every New Year's.
Now, Hatori, you behave
yourself around young Tohru.
Let's go.
[TOHRU]
'Kay.
Bis bald!
I'll see you later!
So, is it true that you're best
friends? You and Shigure?
Us? Best friends?
Well, that's what Momiji said,
b‐but maybe he was wrong?
[HATORI] I'm stuck
with him, that's all.
[gasps]
[TOHRU] Maybe he doesn't
wanna talk about Shigure.
[HATORI]
Hey, watch your step.
Huh? Ah!
[gasps] Are you okay,
Hatori? I‐‐ Uh!
[TOHRU]
Ah!
What do I do?
Water!
Wait, hold on! Which kind
of water does he need?
Fresh water or salt water? Ah!
[HATORI]
This brings back memories.
Tohru Honda isn't the first
person to react this way.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kana Soma, and
I'll work very hard
to be a good assistant for you.
Right.
[KANA]
I've always found it strange
that we've never
spoken to each other
even though we're a
part of the same clan.
Hm. You may have
heard this before,
but you're quite the popular
guy on the outside.
Let's get to work, shall we?
[KANA]
It's snowing!
I thought we'd get snow.
Hey, I've got a
question for you.
What comes of snow
when it melts?
The answer to that
is obviously water.
[KANA mimics buzzer]
[KANA giggles]
The answer is spring comes.
Spring is my favorite season.
[HATORI] She was my spring.
My new season.
Somewhere along the line,
trapped in my dark cage,
I'd frozen.
I was snow.
But then Kana came into my life.
A fresh, bright spring.
[KANA giggling]
[HATORI]
I fell in love
like it was the only
logical thing to do.
[giggling]
[HATORI]
And then... she found out.
[KANA]
What do I do?
Water!
Wait, hold on! Which
kind does he need?
Fresh water or
salt water? Hatori!
For future reference,
putting a real seahorse
or seadragon
in the bath like
that would kill it.
[KANA chuckles]
Got it, sorry.
But this does answer
one question for me.
You've never held me
in your arms before,
and now I know why.
It makes sense. This
must be pretty scary, huh?
Of course you wouldn't
want people to know.
Of course you'd keep
them at a distance.
Especially someone you love.
But please, don't get scared.
Don't reject me for knowing.
[KANA] I'm glad I met you.
That hasn't changed.
Loving you has made me so happy.
I want to be with you.
[HATORI]
I wept.
For the first time in my life,
I felt somehow forgiven.
Somehow saved.
Like a river of snow melted by
the first breath of spring.
The tears wouldn't stop flowing.
For almost two months,
life was like the best dream.
She smiled and said it was
as if I was condensing
a lifetime of happiness
into a handful of weeks.
But then we begged Akito
to allow us to marry,
and the dream came
to an abrupt end.
[gasps, yells]
You think I'll give him
to someone like you?
Akito! Wait, just calm down!
[HATORI]
Akito!
[AKITO]
You can't even lift the curse!
‐‐[HATORI] Akito, please!
‐‐[AKITO] You're not wanted!
[AKITO]
We don't need you!
‐‐Hatori!
‐‐You're the one to blame!
[AKITO] It's your fault
if Hatori goes blind,
do you hear me?
This is all your fault!
It's all your fault!
[HATORI]
She fell ill.
No matter what I
said or what I did,
the crying never stopped.
The curse. She grew
more and more sick.
Her heart was suffering.
Her mind, too.
[AKITO] Isn't this exactly
the type of situation
where your little memory trick
would come in handy?
You ought to wipe the
slate clean for her.
What's stopping you now?
You've never been shy before.
The poor girl's only suffering
because she remembers
her time with you.
Her love for you.
Don't you owe her
this much at least?
To save her from that agony?
What she really
wants, deep down,
is to be set free
from your love.
Give her that freedom.
Let her forget.
[KANA]
This wouldn't have happened
if only we'd never met.
[HATORI] Am I just
getting what I deserve?
Is this my punishment for
blindly following orders?
For stripping away
people's memories,
regardless of how
much pain it caused?
Even so, I never imagined I'd
have to erase with my own hands
the memories most
precious to me
from the mind most
precious to me.
[KANA]
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault.
I couldn't protect you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Hatori.
[HATORI] I'm the one who
owes you an apology.
I'm the one who failed
to protect you.
[HATORI]
Thank you for everything, Kana.
It's all right now.
It's over. You don't
have to suffer anymore.
[KANA]
I'm glad I met you.
That hasn't changed.
[HATORI] God, please let her
meet someone better than me.
Someone who can give her
the happiness she deserves.
I'll do anything.
I'll be snow in a world
without spring.
Frozen until the day I die.
Just please... Please.
[TOHRU]
Hatori. Hatori!
Can you hear me?
Are you okay? How do you feel?
I'm freezing.
Um, that's because under your
coat, y‐you're... kinda naked.
[HATORI]
So you saw?
Oh, no, I didn't look I promise!
[HATORI]
You saw my zodiac form?
[TOHRU]
Well, yeah.
Huh?
I don't think it's weird
or anything. It's great!
And of course, there's
the surprise factor!
I mean, who doesn't love
a good surprise?
Oh, your shoes! They're
probably back by the stairs.
I'll just go and get them.
[MAYUKO] So, you're finally
getting married, huh?
Congratulations, Kana.
Thanks, Mayuko.
[SOMA WOMAN A]
Well, what's the lucky man like?
[KANA] Huh. My heart always
feels calm when I'm with him.
His face isn't quite as
handsome as Hatori's, though.
[SOMA WOMAN A]
You're terrible! Don't say that.
Gimme a break, he was
the man of my dreams.
Even if he never felt the same.
I wish I'd gotten to tell him
"hi" while I was visiting.
[SOMA WOMAN A]
Easy! You've already got a man.
[KANA] And I'm madly in
love with him, so don't...
[HATORI]
Two years after I last saw her,
and she's smiling like
she did back then.
So, she found happiness.
I'm glad. So glad.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry,
congratulations for what?
[HATORI]
Nothing. Never mind.
[TOHRU gasps]
Do you see that? It's snowing!
No wonder you were
feeling so cold earlier.
[HATORI]
Yes.
Please, let her be happy.
I'll be the snow.
Frozen until the day I die.
Just please...
[KANA] What comes of
snow when it melts?
[TOHRU]
Hatori?
You look sad. Is
something the matter?
I'm fine.
Tell me, what do you suppose
comes of snow when it melts?
Huh, let me think for a second.
[TOHRU gasps]
When snow melts, spring comes!
No matter how cold it is now,
spring will come again.
It never fails.
Pretty mysterious, huh?
Yes.
It is.
[TOHRU] Thanks for walking me
to the gate. I appreciate it.
[HATORI]
Sorry about the incident.
[SHIGURE]
You're still here? Slowpokes.
[TOHRU]
Shigure!
[SHIGURE]
Now, doctor,
you haven't been behaving
improperly, have you?
No! He hasn't done anything!
See you later.
Thank you for
inviting me to visit!
Poor Tohru.
It was quite rude of him to
summon you here like that.
But he's not as much
of a jerk as he seems.
[TOHRU] Not at all!
He was very kind to me.
Well, let's get home.
All this New Year's prep
has me positively famished.
[SHIGURE] Speaking of,
what are we having for dinner?
[TOHRU]
Shigure.
[SHIGURE]
Hm?
Will you tell me...
about the curse?
Sorry, it's just...
It just seems like I should
be doing something to help.
And you are, just by
being yourself.
But for now, I don't think I
should tell you anything more.
I'm sorry.
[TOHRU]
After today,
I feel like I understand
more about the Somas,
and also like I don't
understand anything.
It's strange feeling
both things at once.
I still haven't
officially met Akito.
I wonder if I will someday.
[SHIGURE]
I guess it's true what they say.
A kotatsu can put even the
fiercest demons to sleep.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[SHIGURE]
All right...
[TOHRU] Anyway, whatever
I know or don't know,
nothing changes how much
I wanna cherish this.
And I will. Today, tomorrow...
I'll cherish each and every
moment I spend in this house.
[TOHRU]
"See you when you get back."