[KAGURA]
Um.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not expected,
but is it true?
Is Kyo here?
That's right. You don't know me.
I'm Kagura Soma.
Oh, Kyo's just inside.
Facing a strong
opponent: Chives.
[KAGURA]
It is true.
He came back to me.
‐‐Kyo, I'm here!
‐‐[TOHRU] Hey, wait!
[TOHRU] She's so cute and‐‐
Wait, what did she say?
If she's a Soma, then that
means she must be...
[SHIGURE]
Yuki.
Stop that. You'll
end up choking him.
[KAGURA]
Where are you?
Oh, hello there.
[KYO]
Wha‐‐? Kagura?
It's you.
You disappeared for
four whole months.
You didn't even
say bye. Nothing.
I was scared. Worried.
Do you know how
much I missed you?!
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[KAGURA]
I thought about you constantly!
You jerk!
Do you have any idea
what you put me through,
running off like that?
Huh? Do ya?
[YUKI] Seems it's time
to replace the doors.
Why does everyone
go out of their way
to trash my poor house?
[TOHRU]
Are they okay?
Yeah, don't worry about them.
This is Kagura's way of
showing she cares for him.
You know, like how little kids
are always mean to
the people they like.
It's the same thing.
Sure, if you say so.
But, uh, doesn't it seem
like her personality
did a complete 180 to you?
She just gets that way
when she's emotional.
Especially whenever
Kyo's involved.
She may not act it, but she's
two years older than us.
That's right. And
part of the zodiac.
I knew it!
What year is she?
You've gotta tell me!
Uh. Watch her a while and
I bet you figure it out.
[TOHRU] I'm kinda worried
she's gonna end up killing him.
I doubt it.
[gasps]
[KAGURA]
Uh! Kyo! What happened?
You poor thing.
You're all beaten up!
Who did this to you, my love?
Cue the waterworks.
[sneezes]
It's cold.
Yup. Breezy.
I'm sorry.
I think I was just so
excited to see Kyo again
that I couldn't
hold myself back.
[TOHRU] She's like a
totally different person.
But, Kyo, it is
partially your fault.
You disappeared for four months
and didn't even bother
to call me once.
Why should I have to worry
about telling you where I am?
Don't be silly.
Of course you should keep
your future wife in the know.
Future what now?!
I didn't know you had a
fiancée! That's so sweet.
[YUKI] You must be relieved
someone would consider
such a cruel fate.
[SHIGURE]
Congrats.
[KYO]
You guys aren't helping.
[KAGURA] You see,
when we were little,
Kyo told me we'd get
married one day.
[KYO] Only 'cause you threatened
me with kitchen knives!
What's wrong?
You should want to marry
another animal spirit.
It's your best chance
at happiness.
We could suffer our
curses together.
And of course,
we don't transform
when we hug each other.
Oh, whoa! It's true!
Watch, I can hug
Yun‐chan, too!
That's really interesting.
Why don't you change?
Wish I knew.
There are two others, though.
Female zodiac members, I mean.
And we've found that
they don't trigger
our transformations, either.
Really? Two more?
Where are they now?
Aw! I wanna meet them, too!
Would you like to
know their animals?
[TOHRU]
No, thank you.
On second thought, it'll
be a lot more exciting
if I get to see them and
figure it out for myself.
[YUKI chuckles]
That's very like you.
Anyway!
You know things don't usually
go so well for our kind
when we marry normal people
of the opposite sex.
Right, Shii‐chan?
Well, you have a point.
There are plenty of
problems tied to that.
It can be hard for us
to have regular jobs.
And of course,
you'd still transform every time
your spouse embraced you.
Sex wou‐‐
Too much.
[TOHRU]
Hm?
[KAGURA]
Kyo!
You can't play coy
with me anymore.
Tell me, do you like me or not?
Huh?
'Cause I like you so much.
More than anyone else
in the whole world.
No, make that the universe!
If I were your wife, I'd cook
you amazing food every day
and forgive any affairs as
momentary lapses of judgement.
No matter what
your feelings are,
it's obvious you're never
going to find another woman
who loves you as much as I do.
Understand?
Speak up!
Why aren't you agreeing with me?
[SHIGURE] He loses all boldness
when it comes to girls.
Oh, right.
Tohru, you're quite
a fan of the Cat.
What do you think of this?
What's that? A rival?
You can't have him.
I don't care what you feel,
nothing will stand in
the way of our future!
What is it you like about
him, anyway, Tohru?
Because I like all of him.
Every single bit.
I cherish the good things about
him along with his flaws.
Even if he were to change
into his true form,
I wouldn't think
of him any diff‐‐
Not another word.
[TOHRU]
His "true form"?
If you keep babbling on like
that, you're gonna regret it.
[KAGURA]
How dare you threaten me!
[TOHRU] I wonder what all that
"true form" stuff was about.
Well, whatever the case,
Kagura seems to be overflowing
with love for Kyo.
Unabashedly.
[TOHRU] It's amazing
she feels so strongly.
I haven't had my first love yet.
Oh, Kyo! I'm here to
scrub down your back!
[KYO growls]
Dear. No need to act
shy around me!
[TOHRU] Honestly, I think
I'm kind of jealous.
[KYO]
Dammit.
Why is this my job?
No complaining. You are
partially at fault here.
[KYO] Shut up! Are you
kidding me right now?!
Hey, you should be
pitching in, too, Rat‐boy!
No, thanks.
Cats should be able to
clean up their own messes,
even stupid cats.
What did you just say?
Stand up. We're
fighting this out.
‐‐[KAGURA] Hey, Kyo!
‐‐Uh. What?
Look at this!
Aw, a cute little kitty.
Quit playing around.
You're the one to blame for‐‐
[stomach growls]
I know it's a little early, but
I think I'll start on dinner.
Stay out of that kitchen!
Okay?
I'll cook tonight!
What? Why would you
want that hassle?
So I can treat my beloved Kyo.
Then why don't you
let me help you out?
Don't worry, I can handle
a simple meal on my own.
Kyo, dear. Hope you're
looking forward to it.
[SHIGURE] Kyo, dear. You should
have time to fix that door.
[TOHRU]
Wow! This is incredible!
I can't believe you just
whipped up such a nice meal!
Oh, stop.
Looks great, but how many
people are you feeding?
[SHIGURE]
So much for all our groceries.
I was so excited about
feeding my true love
that I may have gotten
a little carried away.
Uh, speaking of Kyo,
where is he?
Probably upstairs.
[KAGURA]
I'll go get him!
Dinner for my darling.
Darling! Your dinner is ready!
Not hungry.
[KAGURA] Don't lie. Your
tummy was growling earlier.
[KYO]
No, it wasn't.
I even cooked extra to make sure
you'd leave the table
nice and full.
Don't want any.
But why not? Some of your
favorite foods are on the table.
Lay off! I already
told you I'm good!
[KAGURA]
But this was for you.
I did my best to make you smile.
I wanted to feed my beloved!
[screams]
[TOHRU coughing]
Wha‐‐?! Oh my gosh!
Uh. Should we get some help?
Well, great.
The feast is ruined.
Oh, no!
Why does everyone
destroy my house?
I'm sorry, I'll make
more food right away.
Using what? The fridge is empty.
Go home already.
Kagura. Wait!
[SHIGURE]
Stay here. I've got this one.
Where are you off to?
The store.
At this hour? The roads
are dangerous at night.
[KAGURA]
Hey, Shii‐chan.
Do you think I could
live here with you?
I don't like him living
with another girl.
I'm worried.
You know you can't, so why ask?
[KAGURA] Apparently,
you don't understand love.
Or how anxious it
can make someone.
That's not true.
Even I get jealous sometimes.
Should I order delivery?
[KYO]
I'll take Katsudon.
No. Please, wait a bit longer.
[CLERK A]
That'll be 3,700 yen.
Got it.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Here. I'll take care of it, sir.
Here. How 'bout I carry
some of that for you?
I've got it.
[KAGURA]
Hey, Tohru.
Yes?
[KAGURA]
Do you like Kyo?
Well, that's a tough one.
You know, if it's a
yes or no question,
then of course
I like him, but...
I sort of always have.
Even when I was little, I loved
the Cat in the zodiac story.
Because of that,
you could call me a Year
of the Cat fan, I guess.
So you're a fan?
That's right!
When I heard the zodiac story,
all I wanted was to be
a Year of the Cat.
I think I get it.
But that's nothing.
I mean, the two of
you have been close
pretty much your whole
lives, haven't you?
[KAGURA]
That's true.
I first met him
when we were kids.
He was drawing a fried
egg in the dirt.
A fried egg?
[KAGURA]
Yeah.
Hiya.
If you want someone to
play with you, I will.
You mean it?
Yeah! Of course!
And from now on,
I'll stay by your side.
You and I will be
together forever!
[TOHRU]
That look...
I can tell you've
always liked him.
Hey, Tohru. I wanna thank you.
[KAGURA]
For coming to find me.
Come on, we should get home.
I bet everyone's gotta
be starving by now.
Yeah.
[TOHRU]
So, what're you gonna make?
[KAGURA] I was thinking
hamburger steaks.
[TOHRU]
I'd love to help, if you want.
[KAGURA]
Yes, please do!
[TOHRU]
My mouth is already watering.
[stomach growling]
It's possible I might starve.
Same.
‐‐[TOHRU] Hi, everyone.
‐‐[KAGURA] We're home.
And we're saved.
Welcome back, girls.
We'll get dinner together
as fast as we can.
I'll follow your lead.
Let's not waste any time, 'kay?
Right!
[TOHRU, YUKI giggle]
'Kay, these are almost ready.
Could you go ahead and
set the table maybe?
I'm already on it.
Dinner's about to be served.
Smells heavenly.
Where'd Kyo go?
[YUKI] He went upstairs a while
ago and hasn't come down yet.
Hey, Kyo! It's almost
time to eat dinner.
Ah, there you are.
I should've known
I'd find you up here.
The food'll be done in a minute.
I'm gonna pass.
Kagura worked really hard
to put it together, though.
She said she just wants
to make you happy.
[KYO] Yeah, well, she's always
saying crazy things.
Like all that marriage stuff.
There must be something
wrong with her brain.
It's so annoying.
[TOHRU]
But...
Isn't it a blessing to have
someone care about you?
Someone who worries
about your happiness
and wants to always
be by your side?
You know, I'd like to think
someone cares for me that way.
Even if that person and I are
separated by a huge distance.
I find it very reassuring.
And it's amazing to me
the way someone can
love another person
with their entire heart.
'Cause after all,
doesn't everybody dream
there's someone out there
destined to be with them?
Uh... I don't know about that.
I know what you dream of.
You wanna defeat
Soma, don't you?
That's why you went into
the mountains to train.
Ugh. Shigure's been blabbing.
[TOHRU] That training must
have been hard on you.
Especially since you were
by yourself out there.
[KYO] I wasn't alone. I had
my master there with me.
[TOHRU]
Oh, I didn't know.
Is he a very strong person?
Obviously, he has to be!
He's an amazing fighter.
Even Yuki couldn't beat the guy.
He's been teaching me since
I was just a little kid.
Which is why I've
gotten so strong.
Plus, even though he's a
member of the Soma clan,
he actually understands me.
You wouldn't believe
how tough he is.
I could hardly wait for
our lessons each morning.
Don't get me wrong,
the training was harsh,
but it was also
incredibly fulfilling.
I felt myself getting stronger.
Just thinking about it
gets me so pumped up.
[TOHRU]
I've never seen him so excited.
He's got so much passion.
[KYO] Man, I could really go for
a few sparring rounds right now.
[TOHRU] It's not that he
just wants to beat Soma.
He truly loves martial arts.
[KYO gasps]
Oh. This is probably boring
to a girl like you, I bet?
What? No way!
Okay, sure, I don't know
much about martial arts,
but I'm not bored at all!
I promise! This is
really interesting!
Yeah? 'Cause I'd be
bored in your shoes.
It's not like you care
about this stuff.
True, I do have trouble
not falling asleep
when people are talking
about, like, physics,
but I'm not completely
uninterested in martial arts.
I even know a few moves!
Like, let me think!
There's the, uh, um, what's
it called? Right‐handed jab!
Horrible.
[TOHRU] I feel like I've
caught another glimpse
of the true Kyo.
Underneath that grumpy look,
he always has on his face,
he's hiding an awkward smile.
Thank you for waiting.
[SHIGURE] You took so long, I
thought I was going to pass out.
Sorry 'bout that.
[KAGURA]
Here.
This one's yours.
[SHIGURE]
What's this?
Now why did Kyo get a
fried egg on top of his?
Looks good. Let's eat
it before it gets cold.
[SHIGURE]
Thanks for the food!
‐‐[YUKI] Thank you for the food.
‐‐[TOHRU] Thank you, Kagura.
This is delicious.
It really is.
My tastebuds are so happy.
What are you waiting for?
Have a seat and join us!
Sure.
[SHIGURE]
It's getting late, Kagura.
It would probably be best
if you stayed the night.
[KAGURA] Really? Yay!
Let's share a bed, Kyo.
[KYO]
Not on your life!
[KAGURA]
Aw, no need to be shy.
Today we must part.
Please be well, my love.
I'll come back to see you soon.
I'll be fine as long as you stay
as far away from me as possible!
Well, they're in high
spirits this morning.
So, what's your guess?
Did you figure out
Kagura's year?
No, I didn't.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Fine! Just for that, you're not
even getting a kiss goodbye!
I'm not going to take any
more of your punches‐‐
[SHIGURE]
My TV!
I can't believe him.
How can he be so mean?
But... I love him!
‐‐[SHIGURE, KYO] Who's that?
‐‐Someone's there!
Oh, good morning.
How can I help you, sir?
Oh, I, uh... forgot
to deliver your paper.
Thank you!
[SHIGURE]
Perfect save.
[TOHRU] Soma's even more
dazzling than usual
this morning.
That was a close one.
Be more careful, Kagura.
[KAGURA]
Sorry.
[gasps]
[KAGURA]
I didn't know there'd be a man
on the other side of the door.
Okay, I figured out her year.
It turns out her zodiac
is the Year of the Boar.
[SHIGURE] I don't think this
counts as "figuring it out."
And yet, you seem so
pleased with yourself.
This makes perfect sense.
When you have a goal,
it's all you can think about.
This must be the Boar's
influence on you.
[SHIGURE] That's less of a
deduction and more of a fact.
I've gotta hug you.
You're the cutest little piggy
I could ever imagine.
She's ignoring me.
Hey, Kagura. I think
I kinda see now.
At first, I didn't understand
what could make you
love Kyo so much.
But after last night,
I can tell there are a bunch
of great things about him.
I hope I can see more of them...
How dare you cheat on me!
I knew it!
I can't take my eyes off of
you for a single second!
[KYO]
What are you talking about?
I thought you said you'd
forgive his affairs.
I never said he wouldn't
be punished first!
[TOHRU]
Excuse me.
I think there's a
misunderstanding.
I meant that I wanna become
someone more like you,
who's able to see
the good in people
even when it isn't obvious.
Does that make sense?
[gasps]
You mean it? Like, for real?
Yeah! I think it's a fantastic
trait to have, don't you?
[gasps]
Yeah, I do.
Put some clothes on!
You need more training, dummy.
[KAGURA]
See ya later, darling!
Let's get together real soon!
[KYO]
Hurricane Kagura has passed.
Darn it.
With all this chaos at home,
I didn't get to plant anything.
[TOHRU gasps]
So, are you going to
grow something new
at your secret base?
Yeah, strawberries.
Really? I love strawberries.
I'd hoped you might like them.
We're gonna be late.
[TOHRU] For some reason, I have
way more motivation lately.
[TOHRU]
I'll take these.
[LIBRARIAN A]
All right. One moment.
[TOHRU] I wanna learn
more about the things
that Kyo and Soma
are interested in.
And what they dislike, too!
If I do that, then maybe...
...maybe I'll get to
see more of the sides
that they keep hidden
from the world.
At least, I hope that happens.
[MAYUKO]
Oh, there you are.
Honda. There's a call for
you in the staff room.
[TOHRU] Hello? I hope you
weren't waiting long.
Grandpa?
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
I'd gotten too comfortable.
I knew my living
situation was temporary
and that one day
I'd have to leave...
Yet, somehow, I managed to
fool myself into believing
that the Somas and I
could be a family.
[TOHRU]
"I've been fooling myself."