[TOHRU] The Culture Festival
is coming up next month,
and things are suddenly getting
really busy at school.
[YUKI]
It's decided.
For the festival, our class
is going to operate
a rice ball stand.
With that settled, I'd like
to hear everyone's thoughts
on the kinds of fillings
we should use.
[TOHRU]
Oh!
What if we did
tricolor rice balls?
So that in every rice ball,
people get three
different fillings to try.
A bargain!
That's cute. I like it.
[KINOSHITA]
Seriously?
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
We totally need to
ditch that idea, Yuki!
Yeah, what if she suggests a
tuna, kelp, pickled plum combo?
Oh my gosh, that would
be so disgusting!
[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH scream]
Nowhere near as disgusting
as your personalities, morons.
What kind of psycho brings
a steel pipe to school?!
I say we should do
rice ball battles.
Battles?
Yeah, brutal
head‐to‐head matches.
First to pin their
opponent wins.
Weapons are allowed,
and customers have to duke
it out for their rice balls,
and the only rule is no killing.
[STUDENTS]
Hard pass.
[KYO]
I'm trying to contribute here!
You jerks could at
least think about it!
That's one idea.
What if some of the rice
balls are actually duds?
We could make a deal
where you buy three
and then choose a
fourth one for free.
Only some of the choices
are simply... empty.
[STUDENTS]
Sounds great!
You shoot me down,
but accept his dumb idea?
Sorry, Kyon‐Kyon,
yours was way too weird.
Don't pout about it, Kyon‐Kyon.
[KYO]
Don't call me Kyon‐Kyon!
[YUSUKE]
Don't be mad, Kyon‐Kyon!
[IWATA]
Look, cats!
[CLASSMATE H]
What the heck?
[CLASSMATE F]
When'd they get in here?
How cute!
[KYO]
That's it! I'm outta here!
Wait, Kyon‐Kyon!
You've gotta tell us
what's up with the cats!
Very strange.
[TOHRU squeaks]
Yeah, don't worry.
You're still the strangest
person at this school.
That guy's got a seriously
hot temper. Doesn't take much.
He's the total opposite
of our prince.
[cats meowing]
I thought I'd find you up here!
You really like being up
on high places, don't you?
Oh, hello there, kitty.
They're adorable!
I guess it's not surprising
cats like you so much.
It's not like I encourage them.
They show up on their own.
It happens to all of
us with our animals.
We can't stop 'em.
Aw, that way you'll
never be lonely.
It's not a good thing!
So, why are you here?
I was worried, so I
came to check on you.
Don't you wanna help out with
the Culture Festival project?
[KYO]
You don't need me.
Everything'll go fine
as long as Yuki's there.
He's always been so
smart, and capable,
and good with people.
Everybody automatically
respects his talents.
They trust him.
I'm the one who started
martial arts first, you know.
And now he's better
at it than I am.
[SOMA WOMAN A]
I knew it.
Rat children are always
special, aren't they?
[SOMA WOMAN B]
Indeed.
A pity the same can't
be said of the Cat.
[KYO]
It pisses me off.
I can't magically make
myself more like him.
But I would if I could.
Let's play Rich Man‐Poor Man!
No. Go and bother Yuki.
I don't wanna play.
I would, but Soma's
not around right now.
Bummer, I was looking
forward to playing you.
You're so stupid
and incompetent,
I figured you'd make
for easy pickings.
Way to ruin my fun.
Thanks a lot.
Running away from a fight
like you're some scared
little boy, it's pathetic.
[KYO grunts]
Okay, you're on!
But I'm not gonna dry
your eyes when you lose,
got it, Gangster Girl?
Whoever comes in last has to do
everyone else's cleaning duty.
[HANAJIMA] Cozy. It's such an
inviting maelstrom of waves.
[TOHRU] That's strange. I wonder
why Soma's not back yet.
[YUKI]
I'm sorry.
But I'm just not interested
in dating anybody right now.
It's not you, really.
I'm just trying‐‐
[STUDENT A] No! Stop it!
I don't wanna hear this!
Yuki!
I, um, didn't mean...
You're really nice, Yuki, but
you don't let anyone in, do you?
[gasps]
Everybody says it!
Yuki's different from
regular people.
An ordinary girl would never be
enough for someone like him.
[STUDENT A crying]
[KYO]
Revolution!
What kinda under‐handed
trick was that, you sneak?
The kind that's
allowed in the rules!
Revolution turns the
strong cards weak,
so I don't know
which to play next.
I do.
Revolution Reversal.
[KYO]
Not cool!
[UOTANI]
She really got ya, Carrot Top.
Nice work, Hanajima.
Not lookin' good for Kyon‐Kyon.
Shut it! We're just
getting started here.
[STUDENT A]
You're really nice, Yuki,
but you don't let
anyone in, do you?
[YUKI]
Rich Man‐Poor Man?
I know the rules. I've
never played it, though.
Uo‐chan just taught me,
so I don't know too
much about it, either.
You should play
with us next time!
So, it looks like he ended up
the poor man this time around.
Um. I really don't mind helping.
No, I've got it.
A loss is a loss.
I'm gonna win the
next game, though!
And that includes beating you!
Don't you ever get tired
of your empty threats?
No, because winning against you
is my ultimate goal in life!
Hearing that over and over's
my ultimate annoyance in life.
Your condescending,
high‐and‐mighty attitude
really pisses me off!
Your inability to comprehend
complex thoughts pisses me off.
[TOHRU]
And they're fighting again.
Sure, they're the
Cat and the Rat,
but I don't think that's
enough to explain
why they're always at
each other's throats.
Now that I think about it...
[KYO]
I'm gonna win.
I'll beat you and become
a full‐fledged member
of the Soma clan.
[TOHRU]
I didn't realize it at the time,
but was Kyo saying that
if he could beat Soma,
he'd finally be included
in the zodiac?
If he was... the Cat would
join the other animals
and they'd become 13!
That would be wonderful!
Still, the fighting's no good.
‐‐Um, Kyo.
‐‐I'm comin' for ya!
[KYO yells]
[KYO]
Get ready, rodent!
[YUKI] Just looking at
you... makes me sick.
[TOHRU gasps]
Soma, wait.
[KYO]
Dammit.
Why can't I ever win?
[TOHRU] Are you all right?
You didn't bite your tongue‐‐
[KYO]
It's not my first fight!
Get out of here already.
Uh. I mean...
It's just that...
I keep losing to him,
and I hate it.
Huh?
Never mind, okay?
You should head home.
You've got work today, right?
[grunts]
[KYO] He was a lot rougher
on me than usual.
Guess he's in a bad mood.
[TOHRU]
Bye! Have a good night!
Soma's so polite.
And he's always considerate
of other people.
But maybe he can
only be that way
if he bottles up all
of his own feelings.
Until...
[yelps, screams]
[TOHRU]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Guess I shouldn't think so hard
when I'm going down stairs.
[STRANGER laughing]
Oh, hello there.
[TOHRU]
It's so late in the day.
I'm surprised someone's here.
[STRANGER]
Oh?
"Tohru"?
[TOHRU]
Huh?
You're Tohru Honda?
Yes, that's me, but
how do you know‐‐?
Sieh da! Welch ein gluck!
[TOHRU]
Huh? What language is that?
Schon dich‐kennenzulernen.
[TOHRU] I'm sorry,
but I don't understand.
[TOHRU gasps]
[STRANGER]
Sehr hubsch!
Uh. Okay! I mean, that was...
Sorry, but I've gotta go now!
[STRANGER]
Hm?
What's this?
[YUKI]
Miss Honda, you seem flustered.
Huh?! Oh, there was just
a stranger, and I, um...
[YUKI]
Stranger?
[TOHRU]
Soma?
Scare you? I'm sorry.
I wasn't expecting to see you.
Are you here to walk me home?
[YUKI]
Mh‐hm.
You shouldn't be out
this late on your own.
Thank you for
thinking about me.
You and Kyo are always so kind.
Well, then, shall we?
Please! Wait just second!
I wanted...
Well, I wanted to tell you
that if there's anything
that's been bothering you,
I'm happy to listen.
It's like how telling
somebody your bad dreams
makes them not so scary.
I thought, if you
felt comfortable
sharing your burdens with me,
then maybe they wouldn't...
All right, kiddos,
it's gettin' late.
Quit flirtin' and
go home already.
I meant it about
wanting to help.
Only now it looks like I've gone
and made everything worse,
like I always do.
[YUKI]
Back when I lived at home,
it felt like I was in a cage,
with the main family and
Akito always watching.
I longed to have a normal life.
To be surrounded
by normal people.
That's why I applied to a co‐ed
high school and left home.
But I was deluding myself.
I haven't really managed
to leave the cage.
I'm still living
in a Soma house,
and I still have no idea how to
interact with normal people.
I think I'm subconsciously
keeping my distance
so nobody will get too close.
But... Kyo is different.
People are drawn to him.
And he may be anxious at first,
but once he's used
to them, he relaxes.
He's always been like that.
Even if he can't be
one of the 12,
he knows how to get along
with regular people.
That's better, if you ask me.
I wish I could be like that,
more than anything.
It's why he gets on my nerves.
When I see him trying
so desperately
to join the same Somas
I wanna escape,
I can't help but think,
"What's wrong with me?"
[TOHRU]
Nothing's wrong with you.
Plenty of people out there
are drawn to you, too.
Girls at school really like you.
They think you're a kind person.
[YUKI] I'm only being kind
because I want them to like me.
Same as a child
handing out candy
because he wants the other
kids to play with him.
I'm nice for my own benefit.
[YUKI]
Maybe I'm a phony.
[TOHRU] I think I'm
starting to understand
what the problem is.
Kyo is jealous of Soma,
and Soma is jealous of Kyo.
That's why they resent
each other so much.
[TOHRU]
I guess it makes sense.
But as far as I'm concerned,
they're both really
great in their own way.
So why...?
I wish you and Kyo could‐‐
[TOHRU yelps]
Just wonderful.
[NEWSCASTER A]
An unexpected typhoon will bring
high winds and heavy rain
through tomorrow morning...
We're home. Is that the weather?
It's getting ugly out there.
They're saying it's an
unexpected typhoon.
It is really coming down.
[SHIGURE]
Uh! You're dripping everywhere!
[TOHRU]
Huh?
Soma!
[gasps]
[YUKI] Miss Honda!
It's dangerous out here!
This is nothing!
When the last typhoon
came through,
I spent the night outside
my tent holding‐‐
[yelps]
You okay?
I'm fine, sorry.
But, Soma, what're
you doing out here?
This way.
I don't understand.
Where are we going?
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Wow, it's a farm!
[YUKI] I'd say more of a
vegetable garden, actually.
How cool! Did you plant
it all yourself?
[YUKI]
Mhm.
The secret base I mentioned.
That's so heroic!
Risking life and limb to protect
your base from the typhoon.
Please allow me to join
you in your noble fight!
[YUKI]
You're a truly kind person.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[gasps] Oh, gosh.
You're kidding, right?
I mean, nobody's ever said
anything like that to me before.
[yelps]
Well, maybe it's sort of like
what you were talking
about earlier:
A phony kindness to make it
seem like I'm a good person.
[YUKI] No, in your case,
I think it comes naturally.
[TOHRU]
You know, my mom once told me
that it was always better
to believe instead of doubt.
She said human beings
aren't born with kindness.
That's something that
only comes to us later.
All we have at
first are desires.
For things like
food and shelter.
Basically, just
survival instincts.
She said kindness is our
hearts growing inside us.
Growing like people‐‐
at different rates,
in different ways.
And... that's why one
person's kindness
might look different
from another's.
So...
[KYOKO] It's simple to
understand desire,
because it's something
everyone has from birth.
But each person's kindness is
pretty much handmade by them,
so it's easy for others
to misunderstand it,
or assume that it's phony.
But, Tohru...
[TOHRU] It was exciting to think
there were different shapes
of kindness in the world,
like round ones or pointy ones.
None quite the same.
This may sound strange,
but your kindness
reminds me of a candle.
It lights up.
When it does, I can't
help but smile
at the warmth it gives off.
There's nothing phony about it.
That was probably a pretty
strange analogy, I bet.
[YUKI]
No, not at all.
Actually, I'm kind of ashamed.
I shouldn't have unloaded
all of that on you.
[TOHRU]
I'm glad you did.
[gasps]
The more you tell me about
your life and feelings,
the better friends
we can become.
It makes me so happy you
felt you could let me in.
Oh. I guess that
was pretty rude.
No, I wasn't thinking
that, I promise.
[TOHRU yelps]
I'll be quiet now and continue
my mission to protect the base!
[KYOKO]
But, Tohru...
...I want you to
believe in people.
Doubting is easy.
Anybody can do that.
You be the kind of girl who
can have faith in others.
One day, I know...
that will help someone.
We defended it to the end!
At the low cost of
getting half‐drowned.
Are there any vegetables
ready to harvest?
[YUKI]
Well, the chives might be.
[TOHRU]
Chives?
Chives, chives.
[YUKI]
Miss Honda.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[YUKI] I'll play Rich
Man‐Poor Man next time.
That's wonderful!
Although, if you're not
interested, you don't have to.
[YUKI] Mhm. It's just,
everyone else was so outgoing.
I didn't feel comfortable.
[YUKI]
But I'll work on that.
It may take me a while,
but I want to learn how
to interact with people.
It'll be so fun!
Hana‐chan is great.
Uo‐chan, too.
I'm super proud to
call them my friends.
Plus, I'll bet you'll
be good at it.
And I know they'll
love the chance
to defeat a strong opponent.
[gasps]
I'll win. Just wait.
[TOHRU]
Oh, wow.
I think that's the first time
I've seen his true smile.
We'll have to take hot
baths when we get home
or we'll catch cold.
[TOHRU] Someday, maybe he'll
even smile like that at school.
I can't imagine how
popular he'd be then.
[giggles]
The hell's goin' on here?
Plannin' to start
a rice ball business?
[TOHRU]
Oh, good morning, Kyo.
I'm experimenting to get ready
for the culture festival.
You're out of bed early,
as usual, huh?
It's not early. It's normal.
So were you out at the garden
with Yuki all night long?
Oh! Ow, ow.
That's really hot.
Yeah. We needed to defend the
vegetables from the typhoon.
I'm particularly
proud of that one.
You'll have to tell
me what you think.
What are these?!
Rice balls made with chives.
So you don't like them, then?
No way! I freakin' hate chives!
What's wrong with sticking
to something normal,
like salmon or octopus filling?
I'll just make my own.
Wow! That's so amazing!
Huh?
[TOHRU] The way you
shaped that rice ball!
You're great! Really!
It's not a big deal.
I had to make my own food
while I was training.
But just 'cause I can make it
doesn't mean it'll taste good.
It's still impressive.
If someone was working hard
training to make rice balls,
I think they would
be very jealous
of how good you are at it.
Rice ball training isn't
something people do.
Where do you even
get these ideas?
[TOHRU] But that doesn't change
the fact that it's great.
[TV HOSTS]
Good morning!
[TOHRU]
Why doesn't he realize?
[gasps]
I think I know.
Maybe you can't see it
'cause it's on your back.
[KYO grunts]
Huh?
Just think, if a person
is a rice ball,
and what's great about that
person is a pickled plum,
the problem is, the
plum's on their back,
where they can't see!
Maybe everyone in the
world is walking around
with plums on their backs.
All different kinds.
No two of them
are exactly alike.
But since they can't
see their backs,
they can't see the plums
that make them unique.
They think they don't
have anything special‐‐
that they're just
plain white rice.
Even though that's
not true at all.
Even though they really do
have a plum of their own.
Maybe that's the
reason we get jealous.
'Cause when it comes to plums,
other people's are
a lot easier to see.
So trust me when I say,
I can see it.
Plain as day.
You have a plum right
there on your back.
Sure, Soma is great,
but the thing is, so are you.
Uh!
Okay, seriously! Where do
you get these ideas?
And why did you have to
pick plums of all things
for your stupid analogy?
I'm sorry, you're right!
Maybe I should've used
salmon instead!
[whistling]
[TOHRU]
Whoops. The kettle.
[KYO]
Hey.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[KYO] You've got one,
too, on your back.
You know, a plum.
[KYO]
I can see it.
[gasps]
I do? Really? Are you sure?
Yeah. It's only a
little one, though.
A really, really,
really little one.
[TOHRU]
Little ones are delicious.
You're up already?
Oh! Actually,
I never went to bed.
Are you kidding? You didn't
get any sleep at all?
Nope!
With all the exciting
things to think about,
my brain wouldn't turn off.
What's this?
Rice balls with chives.
Kyo says he doesn't
like chives, though.
[KYO]
Yeah, because they're inedible.
Ah!
Eat it.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU]
Is it a lost cause?
Will they hate
each other forever?
I can't help but think,
if they could each understand
the other's good points,
maybe they could get along.
You know, I've really
misunderstood you.
I'm sorry.
Right back at ya. Sorry, man.
We should cherish
our friendship!
Let's never fight again, 'kay?
Yeah!
[TOHRU]
Somehow, that's not any better.
[doorbell rings]
[TOHRU]
Coming!
[KAGURA]
Excuse me.
Hello?
[KAGURA]
Um.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but is it true?
That Kyo is here?
[TOHRU]
"What year is she?"