[GIRL A]
Stay down!
[GIRL A] I thought you were
supposed to be tough.
[GIRL B] She's nothing
but a weak little
middle‐schooler wannabe!
[GIRL A]
Hey, call the others over here.
[GIRL B]
Yeah, this'll be funny.
[GIRL C] Make her bow down
and show respect.
‐‐[clatter]
‐‐[BOTH] Huh?
You little‐‐
[GIRL B] You'll pay for this.
Get back over here.
Yeah, real hardcore picking
a fight with someone
who's younger than you.
Idiots should act their age.
[GIRLS yelp]
What's your problem?
Keep moving.
[UOTANI gasps]
[TOHRU]
Oh my gosh.
I am so sorry I crashed
into you again.
Please. Can you forgive me?
[GIRL A]
Uotani!
[GIRL B]
Where are you?
[GIRL A]
Over there!
Ah, crap.
[GIRL B] Uh! Don't you dare
make us chase you.
[GIRL A]
You're dead, dammit!
[UOTANI] I'm only running
'cause... she just grabbed me.
Why'd you help me?
[panting]
One sec. Hi.
[UOTANI]
You all right there?
[TOHRU] Oh, yeah. Please
make yourself at home.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[TOHRU] We should to tend to
your cuts right away, Uo‐ chan.
[UOTANI]
Stop calling me that, dammit.
Gimme this.
[TOHRU]
Of course. Sorry.
I‐I'm sure you'll handle it.
[UOTANI] I can't believe
I ended up back here again.
[UOTANI]
That must be her dad.
Didn't know he was dead.
[UOTANI]
They're so disgusting.
[UOTANI] That tofu she dropped
was probably for dinner.
Ah, well. They'll be fine.
[NEWSCASTER A] It's such
a shame that the clouds
never went away last week.
[NEWSCASTER B]
Tell me about it.
The humidity was so bad
that my clothes wouldn't even
dry completely on the line...
[BOY A]
Bye. See ya tomorrow!
[BOY B]
Later.
[NEWSCASTER A]
...sunny skies and no rain.
That's right!
It's finally going to feel like
spring is in full bloom.
Time to break out those
warm‐weather clothes.
[NEWSCASTER A]
I can't wait.
I'm not usually one
for hot weather,
but I just bought the
most adorable sandals
I've been dying to wear out.
Uo‐chan! I mean, Uotani.
I'd be honored if you'd join
us for dinner tonight.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Is everything okay?
Of course I'm uncomfortable.
The home you guys have is...
It's so foreign to me.
I never had this.
It feels wrong.
I know I don't belong,
so I'm basically an outcast,
which only makes me
more uncomfortable.
Thing is, even if I did
have something like this,
I'd still yell at my dad
and tell him to go to hell
like I didn't give a damn.
If my old man had dinner
waiting for me after school,
I just wouldn't go home.
Or I would, but I'd
refuse to eat it,
and tell him it
smelled like crap.
I know that's the truth,
even if it's never
happened to me before.
No matter what my
home life is like,
I'll always be the
same delinquent.
Either way, I'll still be this.
[UOTANI] So what are these
feelings? Why am I jealous?
Why do I still wish
this was my life?
I'm an idiot.
No, Uo‐chan! Oops.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to say it. Um‐‐
[UOTANI]
Whatever.
What is it?
Uo‐chan.
[UOTANI]
The skyline at twilight...
The smell of dinner cooking...
Houses full of light...
The home you go back to
after a day with friends...
Where others are
waiting for you.
Kind people who welcome
you home... with a smile.
[UOTANI] Have I been
lonely this entire time?
[KYOKO]
I just relaxed a bit.
And it feels nice.
[UOTANI]
Maybe I have been all my life.
Maybe this whole time,
I've been looking for something.
[UOTANI] Trivial moments...
but precious ones nonetheless.
Are those what
I've been missing?
[UOTANI]
Man, listen to me.
Blabbering on about what a
sad‐sack I was back in the day.
The point is... I love her.
Yes. Same.
That's great.
But what happened between
you and her mom?
Oh, yeah, right.
I guess I kind of left her
out for a while, didn't I?
[UOTANI]
Hmm...
[UOTANI] Maybe I shouldn't tell
them about the next part.
[ISHIHARA]
Hey, Uotani!
Huh?
We've got business
with you, so step outside.
Alone, obviously.
Yo, weren't those
noodles good?
Yes, more than satisfactory.
‐‐[ITO, TAKEMURA yelp]
‐‐Did she just blow us off?
[TAKEMURA]
You see that?
I told ya we shoulda
called her out earlier.
[ITO]
It's 'cause you took forever
taking pics a'
those pretty boys.
That's not my fault!
I couldn't get a good angle
from where I was standing.
[CLERK A]
Please come back again!
Hey, where do you
think you're going?!
Oh, wait, not you
guys. Just her.
[UOTANI] Nope. I should
probably keep my mouth shut.
[UOTANI]
Because what I did next...
...was seriously embarrassing.
[ISHIHARA]
Stop walking away!
I know you can hear
me, Arisa Uotani.
[TAKEMURA]
Quit ignoring us, dammit!
So, you sure you don't
know who these girls are?
They're calling you out by name.
I've never seen 'em in my life.
That outdated delinquent
act is so lame.
[GIRLS]
Hey, look who's talkin'!
You'd better take us seriously.
Sure, we may be low‐level
punks at the moment...
...but we're gonna make names
for ourselves 'round here
by thrashing all the
show‐offs like you!
Our delinquent army'll scare
the shit outta people.
And before long,
this whole neighborhood
will be our territory.
Good luck.
[GIRLS]
She's mocking us!
Delinquent army? What
would that even look like?
Perhaps it would be best
if I took care of them.
Horrible idea.
[UOTANI] The sad thing is, I
used to be just like those kids.
[UOTANI] I wanted people
to pay attention to me,
even though I wanted
to be left alone.
No matter how old people get,
they never stop being
a little bit selfish.
Everybody.
That includes me.
Y'think so?
Then why do adults act like
they're so much better than us?
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO]
My sincerest apologies!
[chuckles]
[UOTANI]
From then on,
I went to Tohru's house
on the regular.
[UOTANI] Kyoko always welcomed
me with a warm smile.
I was grateful.
She listened to me,
and carefully considered
my problems.
Even though they were childish.
[KYOKO] All right!
These peas are ready to go!
[TOHRU]
I appreciate your hard work.
Hey. Why do you always
talk so politely?
[KYOKO sighs]
[KYOKO]
It's Katsuya's fault.
Ah, Katsuya is
Tohru's dad's name.
He always spoke like that, and
she just kind of picked it up.
Thank you so much for your help.
But I don't mind it.
It's adorable.
You really are a doting
parent. I guess it's cute.
[UOTANI] Before I knew it,
I was comfortable in their home.
I had no one to blame for
that but Tohru and Kyoko.
Anyway, that's how
I started spending
so much time with them.
I became friends with Tohru.
And even started going
to school all the time.
Because if I went to school,
I got to hang out with her.
[TOHRU]
The Battle of Sekigahara.
Okay. What about
the third shogun?
[TOHRU]
Iemitsu Tokugawa.
Right. The year 1853.
[TOHRU]
Hmm...
[UOTANI]
First hint: A foreigner.
[TOHRU]
Um...
[UOTANI]
Second hint: A boat.
Ah‐ha! The arrival of Mr. Perry!
Bingo! But you can
drop the "Mr."
[TOHRU]
Oops. Force of habit.
[UOTANI]
Studying was kind of fun
once I understood how it worked.
And Tohru was easy
to get along with.
Probably because she was
always standing beside me,
from the beginning.
Looking back on it,
she was there for me,
even when I didn't
know I needed her.
[UOTANI]
Like I could pass that up.
Miss Uotani.
[UOTANI]
Huh?
[TEACHER A] What do you think
you're doing bothering her?
Hey. Hold on.
We were only talking.
[TEACHER A]
Miss Honda, are you okay?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
Uh.
[UOTANI] Thing is,
to the people around us,
we apparently didn't look like
we should've been friends.
Which I can understand.
[DELINQUENT A]
Haven't seen Uotani in a while.
Heard anything, Akimoto?
[AKIMOTO]
No.
[DELINQUENT B]
Word is she become some kinda
straight‐laced star
student lately.
[DELINQUENT A] Oh, hell no, that
is not happening. Go get her.
Yeah, we should teach
her a real lesson.
[CLASSMATE A]
Hey, so I had a question.
Yes?
You and Uotani are close,
right? Like, best friends?
[TORHU gasps]
Well, I... It would be an honor
to be her best friend,
so I hope maybe
one day I will be.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU] But what if Uo‐chan
doesn't feel that way?
Sorry.
Huh?
[CLASSMATE B]
No way. They can't be friends.
They're just too different.
It doesn't make any sense.
[CLASSMATE C]
Pretty sure our teachers
have been keeping an eye
on both of 'em, too.
Who knows?
Maybe Honda's different
outside of school
and does horrible
stuff in secret.
[CLASSMATE B] I mean, if she's
hanging out with Uotani,
I bet you're right.
[UOTANI]
How can I go in there?
I don't care if anyone
talks about me,
but I don't want them spreading
any rumors about Tohru.
Maybe it'd be better for her
if I wasn't around at all.
If I distanced myself...
she might be happier.
[CLASSMATE A] Hey. You made
too many of those, Honda.
[TOHRU]
Nope! This is for Uo‐chan.
[DELINQUENT A]
Huh?!
You wanna leave the gang?
Musta lost your damn mind.
Do you think you can
just say you're done
and we'll forget about ya?
If you wanna quit, you gotta
take the punishment.
[UOTANI]
I know.
[DELINQUENT B] Then I don't
wanna hear any complaining!
[DELINQUENT A]
Circle up on her.
[DELINQUENTS shouting]
[UOTANI]
This is terrifying.
I wanna run... so badly.
But I can't. Because...
[DELINQUENT A]
First one's on me.
Uh‐uh. The night
is just beginning.
[DELINQUENTS shouting]
[UOTANI]
I wanted to change my life.
It was the first time
I'd ever felt that way.
I didn't wanna live
like that anymore.
I would be different.
[UOTANI]
I had to because of her.
How's that feel?!
[DELINQUENTS shouting]
[DELINQUENT A]
Come on, get up.
How long you gonna lay there?
[KYOKO]
I think she's had enough.
[DELINQUENTS]
Huh?
[DELINQUENT B]
Who's that?!
Kyoko? I...
You awake?
[UOTANI]
Kyo‐‐
Easy now, or we'll both fall.
Plus, your leg's hurt.
Some older girl from your gang
dropped by the house tonight.
The one with a mole on her chin.
She knew what was
going to happen
and that she couldn't
stop it herself,
so she asked for my help.
[UOTANI]
Akimoto.
It's just that... I like her.
You know how it is.
If she wants to go straight,
then she should.
She said leaving the gang
would be the best
thing for you, so...
[UOTANI]
Senpai.
But anyway, I'm sure
that quitting
took a whole lotta guts.
You did good.
Don't say that.
It just caused trouble.
Even for you.
Oh, no. It was nothing.
All I did was shoo a few kids
on back to their houses.
I wouldn't call that hard.
[KYOKO]
You know, this wasn't so bad.
You had someone kind in the
gang looking out for you.
Many people have gone through
a lot worse trying to get out.
You really are a lucky one.
[UOTANI crying]
I'm stupid.
[UOTANI] I don't learn
anything till I get hurt.
I'm such an idiot.
One thing I've discovered
is that sometimes
you can't understand
your feelings
until you make trouble...
and get hurt.
Sometimes we don't
know how we feel...
...until we're at our worst.
Then it all becomes clear.
[KYOKO] You can rebel
against what's pure,
but then, when you
find yourself filthy,
you start to long for the very
thing you turned away from.
You have to know
gentleness to feel pain.
Just as you only notice the
darkness if you have the sun.
You can't underestimate either.
'Cause everything
has its purpose.
So, even if you
screw up sometimes,
it's never for nothing.
As long as you make sure
you recognize that,
those mistakes will nourish you,
and help you grow even stronger.
'Least, that's my theory.
Listen, Kyoko. I just‐‐
Your daughter... I wanna
be Tohru's best friend!
I want her to be proud
to stand beside me.
That's the reason
I quit. I had to.
[UOTANI] I was determined
to make myself better for her.
Even if it meant leaving
my old life behind.
[KYOKO]
Hmm.
[UOTANI] It's a little
embarrassing to think about
how much I bawled as she
carried me back to her house,
as if she was giving me
a piggy‐back ride.
[UOTANI]
But it wasn't for nothing.
[UOTANI] For a while after that,
people picked fights with me,
but I came out of things okay.
It's really amazing
to not be alone.
[UOTANI] Unfortunately,
I never saw Akimoto again.
I heard around town
that she moved far away.
[UOTANI]
School gradually grew on me.
I started eighth grade,
then later, met Hanajima.
[UOTANI] Kyoko always laughed
when we were around.
She really liked us.
But then, one day all
of that changed...
[UOTANI] I couldn't believe
the apartment window
had gone dark.
[UOTANI]
I missed her.
She saved a random delinquent.
Someone she didn't have
any obligation to.
Kyoko was honest and warm.
At heart, a big softy.
I loved her.
[TOHRU]
Hey!
Hey, Uo‐chan?
Huh? Yeah? What's up?
Well, things are...
...getting a little out
of hand back here.
It's kinda scary.
Ugh.
Hanajima, take it easy on 'em,
they're just dumb kids.
I'm well aware.
I'm being as gentle as
possible. They're fine.
Don't mess with us, loser!
You're gonna regret
underestimating us
this whole time!
[UOTANI]
Aren't you done talking?
You shut up!
I'll send you flying!
[ISHIHARA]
My arms don't reach!
Come on! Stretch!
Let her have it!
If the kid was smart,
she'd of aimed low.
She's got a lot to learn.
I just hope this
is over with soon.
[UOTANI] It's kind of a blessing
to be underestimated sometimes.
If you wanna show off
how tough you are,
there are plenty of
other ways to do that.
Stop acting out like this
while you still can,
before something
serious happens.
If you want someone
to scold you,
I'm happy to do that any time.
[UOTANI]
All right. Let's head back.
[KYO]
Finally.
[TOHRU] I'm glad everything
turned out okay.
Hey, so are you good?
[TAKEMURA] What are you doing?
We gotta go after 'em.
I'm not worthy.
[ITO, TAKEMURA]
What'd you say?
[TOHRU]
We should be getting home.
The sun's going down.
[UOTANI]
Sounds good.
And thank you for such
a wonderful time.
It was a blast. Really.
See you at school
in the morning.
[UOTANI]
Kyoko isn't around anymore.
However, she left important
things for me here.
[UOTANI]
Her words, her feelings...
...and best of all, Tohru.
These things nourish me.
And because of them,
I've been able to grow.
[UOTANI humming]
‐‐[can pops]
‐‐‐[UOTANI] Hm?
Drop it, right now!
Your doc said to start
drinking less, old man.
Whoops. You caught me.
Yeah, yeah, real cute.
Put the can down.
And back off the salt!
Dummy.
You're hopeless, Pops.
[ITO]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[TAKEMURA]
Yo. Wait.
Really? What are you wearing?
Ha. Like it?
Made it myself.
[TAKEMURA] Ugh. You care way
too much about how you look.
Stop trying to copy Uotani.
We're totally different.
Well. Yeah. I guess
that's probably true.
[TAKEMURA]
Huh?
[ITO] If you want to show
off how tough you are,
there are plenty of
other ways to do that.
So stop acting out like
this while you still can,
before something super
serious happens.
If you want someone
to scold you,
I'm happy to do that any time.
[gasps]
‐‐Shut up!
‐‐Ow, that hurt!
[TAKEMURA] Who do you think you
are stealing Uotani's lines?
[ITO growls]
[ISHIHARA]
Hey! You guys!
[laughing]
[ITO, TAKEMURA]
Huh?! Are you kidding me?!
[laughing]
[YUKI]
"What's important is."