[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU]
It's so beautiful! And big!
Do you really find it
that remarkable?
Yes! I've never actually
seen a lake in person!
[chuckles]
This is just the sort of cabin
Jason might show up at.
Jason?
A particularly vicious bear
that lives around here.
I thought everybody knew that.
Yeah! Of course
I know about it!
[HATORI]
Shigure.
I wonder why someone
would name a bear Jason.
[HATORI, YUKI sigh]
[TOHRU]
Wow, Mom.
It's amazing how quickly
things happen lately.
We've suddenly found ourselves
at the Soma vacation house.
I was surprised when
Hatori came, too,
but that just makes the
trip even more perfect.
Except...
[YUKI]
Hey, Miss Honda?
Yes?
Well, um...
[YUKI]
Never mind.
It's nothing. Sorry.
[TOHRU]
I don't know what...
[TOHRU] ...but something
strange is going on.
Yuki and Kyo don't
seem like themselves.
[TOHRU]
It started last night.
We were eating dinner after
visiting the gravesite.
So, um...
Hello, kids.
I‐I hope your errand went well.
It did.
Now tell me, who would like
to go on a trip tomorrow?
[TOHRU, KYO, YUKI]
Huh?
A trip! It'll be the first
day of Golden Week.
What better time to
get away from it all?
'Kay, what's with the
last‐minute vacation planning?
You drunk or somethin'?
I may drink,
but I never get drunk.
[YUKI] I'm not really sure
we'd know the difference.
Let's go.
The Soma family
maintains a lake house
for just such an occasion.
Well? You in?
Uh. Oh, no, I couldn't possibly.
I mean, I already went on the
previous Soma vacation, so‐‐
Ah, but you see,
that trip doesn't count
because I didn't
get to go with you.
Such a shame,
missing out like that.
I was heartbroken.
Then let's go!
[YUKI, KYO]
You manipulator!
Well, it's settled.
I assume you boys
will be coming along?
Unless, of course,
you want Tohru and me
to be all alone in the
wilderness together.
[BOTH grunt]
Then off we go!
Hop in the car and we'll
be there in no time.
[SHIGURE sighs]
Thank you for
volunteering, Doc.
You're such an excellent driver.
[TOHRU]
And there you have it, Mom.
That's how we ended up
at this cabin by the lake.
But these two still seem upset.
I'm really starting to worry.
Hey, why'd you really pack us up
and bring us out
here so suddenly?
Huh?
You have always had
an ulterior motive.
Your lack of trust saddens me.
Can't a man just take a trip
with the people he
cares most about?
Perhaps instead
of tormenting me,
you should make the most
of our lovely surroundings
and take Tohru for a
walk down by the lake.
Hey, what's wrong with
you two? So moody!
No, it's okay. I don't
mind going by myself.
[SHIGURE]
Hmm...
This won't do. We need
someone to brighten the mood.
I know! I'll call Aya!
[growls]
[KYO, YUKI]
Call him and you die.
[SHIGURE chuckles]
[HATORI groans]
[SHIGURE] Serves them
right for not going
the first time I asked.
They've both been a bit
down since yesterday.
It's odd.
You know, I think I've figured
out the real reason
for this impromptu getaway.
It's all a ploy to
torment your editor.
[screams]
[COWORKER A]
Mii‐chan, just come back
to the office for now, okay?
It'll be fine, I promise.
He's only teasing you again.
So please, don't do
anything drastic!
It's all in good fun.
I'm just teasing her a little.
[HATORI]
I pity that poor woman.
[grunts]
[TOHRU]
I'm not sure how much longer
I can handle the awkwardness.
It's so bad, they
aren't even arguing.
Everything seemed pretty
normal yesterday
when we went to visit the grave.
So what happened?
Oh, no!
The only explanation
I can think of
is that they're angry with me!
Maybe I did something rude
while we were having our picnic.
I have to fix this!
[TOHRU]
Um, guys.
I'm really sorry!
[KYO, YUKI]
Huh?
[TOHRU] I know that
sometimes I'm super spacey.
I can be rude without
realizing it.
So... So if I did
something to offend you,
please tell me what it was
and I won't ever do it again.
I won't. I swear.
But please...
[TOHRU]
...go back to normal.
Wait, Miss Honda.
I don't understand.
Yeah, me neither. What the
heck are you talking ab‐‐? Ah!
Oh, no! Are you okay?
Damn it. What is that, anyway?
A... footprint?
It's Jason!
Jason's here?!
Thanks, Shigure.
What should we do?
Shigure said he was vicious!
We have to go right now! Ah!
Miss Honda!
[KYO gasps]
[MITSURU] You have to
stop torturing me...
[SHIGURE]
Calm down, it's fine.
The manuscript is already
finished. It was a joke.
‐‐[MITSURU] Then turn it in!
‐‐Yeah, yeah.
‐‐Please, Sensei.
‐‐Okay.
‐‐Just turn it in!
‐‐Bye, now.
[MITSURU screaming]
Happy? I told my editor
the truth, as instructed.
Was that so hard?
But who's going to keep
me entertained now?
Hey, I'm bored, too.
Oh, dear! No, we can't
have Doc Hatori bored.
Never fear, I have just the
thing. A little light reading.
It won't kill you to sit back
and relax with a book.
You've always enjoyed reading,
almost as much as me.
[HATORI]
I see.
It's because of Kana's wedding.
Maybe this is his way
of looking out for me.
[HATORI]
Shigure.
Yes?
Thanks.
Reading a book does sound nice.
It's been awhile.
[SHIGURE] I wonder how Tohru
and the boys are getting along.
[HATORI]
With her there, they'll be fine.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[YUKI]
Miss Honda, are you okay?
Yuki! I'm so sorry!
Come on. Look where
you're goin', will ya?
[TOHRU]
Sorry.
[YUKI]
Like you have room to talk.
You're the one who tripped
first. Over a footprint.
Yeah? What the hell do you know?
A shut‐in like you doesn't
belong in the woods!
[YUKI] Seems I'm doing
better than you,
despite all your so‐called
training in the mountains.
Screw you, Rat! Go back
and mope in your room.
You wouldn't even last
two days out here.
You've got no survival skills.
[YUKI] At least I'm not an idiot
with no knowledge of the world.
So you know, Jason isn't a bear.
He's a character
from a horror movie.
[KYO] So there's a bear
in a horror movie.
What do I care?
[YUKI]
Like I said: Idiot.
You're dead! I mean it.
I'm gonna freakin' kill
you for real this time!
[YUKI] You keep saying
that, and yet, I live.
Ditch your little
rodent buddies.
Fight fair and square
like a real man!
[YUKI]
Given our respective sizes,
you'd have an unfair advantage.
[TOHRU giggles]
You're back to fighting!
[giggling]
[YUKI]
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I shouldn't
be laughing.
You were in the middle
of a serious argument.
That was rude of me.
I couldn't help it.
I was just so relieved.
I never thought I would be
this happy to watch you fight.
But it means you guys
are finally back to normal.
I'm so weird.
[TOHRU laughing]
[YUKI]
Miss Honda, you know...
What you said right
before you fell,
about whether we
were mad at you.
I just want you to know,
it wasn't that at all.
If it seemed like I was
angry, it's because...
...because...
...I guess I just
wasn't feeling well.
But I'm doing better now.
And I'm sorry for
making you worry.
[KYO]
Same here.
I wasn't mad or anything.
Just... wasn't feelin' so great.
You know, like Rat Boy said.
[YUKI]
Copying me?
No!
[TOHRU gasps, screams]
[TOHRU]
Anyway, thanks for telling me.
I'm glad it was just because
you weren't feeling well.
Wait! I mean, I'm not
glad you were sick.
But I am happy that
nothing's changed.
Why would it?
I promise you,
everything is the same.
[BOTH] I still hate
this guy every bit
as much as I always have.
Huh? What was that?
Did you say something?
[KYO] Yeah! That I'm gonna
hate your stupid guts
for the rest of my life!
[YUKI] I assure you, the
feeling is entirely mutual.
[TOHRU laughing]
[TOHRU]
That's much better.
It's good to see them
so full of life again.
I'm happier when they're
screaming at each other
than when they're quiet.
That's probably pretty strange.
But somehow, for them,
it feels right.
[YUKI] Why don't we head
back to the cabin?
[KYO] We'll go down
to the lake tomorrow.
[TOHRU]
Okay!
You like it?
It's revolting.
[YUKI]
Are you ready to go?
[TOHRU]
Yep! I'm all set.
You're going to the lake?
Try not to fall in, Kyo.
Like I would!
[YUKI]
No guarantees Miss Honda won't.
Well, we're going.
We'll see ya later.
Uh.
[SHIGURE] Is the good
doctor taking a nap?
[TOHRU]
Yes.
Huh. Hatori actually sleeps?
Naturally. People tend to
die without sleep, you know.
I'm aware of that, idiot.
But he doesn't seem
like the type
who'd fall asleep in
front of other people.
Ah. Hm.
It's unusual, but he's tired.
He's been through a lot lately.
Here. A blanket.
He might catch cold
if he's not covered up.
You're so kind, Tohru.
You'll make a wonderful
wife someday!
[TOHRU]
Uh! It's just a blanket.
[BOTH]
You idiot.
[AYAME] He's right. That
was wondrously attentive.
Allow me to praise you.
What's wrong?
You're all so quiet.
Because a snake
suddenly showed up!
Why do you keep doin' that?!
Where'd you slither in from?
I came through the door
like a civilized person.
Not the sharpest tool in the
shed are you, Kyonkichi?
[KYO]
Shut up. I'm plenty sharp!
‐‐Um, hello, Ayame. It's nice‐‐
‐‐[YUKI] Stay back.
I do not trust this viper.
[AYAME]
Greetings!
No doubt the mere sight of me
has taken your breath away,
but please calm yourselves.
I came out here on
important business,
thanks to a certain
interested party.
[YUKI, KYO]
But who would‐‐? You!
Ah! Wait! Hold on! it wasn't me!
There's nothing
to fear, darling!
Should the world turn on you,
I will remain ever at your
side, steadfast and true.
Je t'aime, mon amour.
Bon voyage!
Aya! You are the only
one I can depend upon!
Annyeong hasimnikka!
Will you quit screwin'
around and tell us
what the heck
you're doin' here?!
Now, now. No reason
to get testy.
In the words of
William Shakespeare,
"Love all, trust a few,
do wrong to none."
Okay. Your point?
It's such a great line.
[YUKI, KYO]
You just wanted to say it?
I'm tired. Just seeing
you is exhausting.
Go home. There's no reason
for you to be here!
How rude!
Behold, my reason.
Yuki. Today, we will deepen
our brotherly bonds.
I'll drown you in the lake
myself before that happens.
[AYAME] How poetic! We shall
be together even in death.
[YUKI] I wasn't planning
to drown with you!
Um.
What have I told
you about making
a nuisance of
yourself, Ayame?
Why, hello, there, Tori.
I'm sorry. Did we
wake you up, Hatori?
I don't know anybody
who could sleep through
all of that yelling.
[SHIGURE] Sorry for ruining
your beauty rest.
Had I known you were sleeping,
I would've been as quiet
as a mouse, sweet Tori!
[HATORI]
Somehow I doubt that.
Well? What brings you
to the lake house?
Oh. Simple, really.
I went to the main estate,
where I spoke to a maid,
who was 53 years old,
and she told me you'd
gone to the cabin.
I immediately decided
to join you here.
I got in a car and
the rest is history.
[YUKI]
You've got to be kidding.
[KYO] Sure, he answers Hatori's
questions right away.
Yuki. Kyo. You should be going.
Didn't you have plans to take
Honda down to the lake today?
[YUKI, KYO grunt]
Uh! Is that true, boys?
Then you had best make haste.
You gentlemen are
escorting a young lady.
And she should not
be kept waiting.
I don't know why you're
not gone already.
[YUKI, KYO]
It's your damn fault.
Right! We've got our things,
so we'll be going now.
Wouldn't wanna waste
this beautiful day! Bye!
[SHIGURE] I figured you'd at
least try to go with them.
And spoil their fun? What sort
of lout do you take me for?
Besides, it's been so long
since the three of us had
quality time together.
The night is ours.
You won't sleep a wink, lover.
I can't wait.
It will be a pleasure to share
your dreams tonight, sweetling.
[BOTH]
Nice!
Doesn't that ever get old?
[TOHRU sighs]
Looking at this view,
you can almost feel your
worries melting away.
[YUKI] That jerk. Is he
gonna stay the night?
He's your idiot brother.
Do somethin' about him.
Don't you think
I would if I could?
I hate people
who're so dependent.
You're the one piggybacking
off of Shigure.
Sounds like dependency's
a family trait.
Shut up. That's none
of your business!
Don't talk to me about my life!
I don't wanna
talk to you at all.
The only reason I'm
even lookin' at you
is 'cause you're in my space.
[YUKI]
In that case,
‐‐[YUKI] maybe you should leave.
‐‐Hey, you guys.
‐‐[KYO] I wish I could.
‐‐Let's calm down.
‐‐Trust me.
You really think I'd be
at the damn lake with you
if I had a choice?
I promise, being here
is an exercise
in torture for me, too.
Ha! Well, this dumb place‐‐
[YUKI, KYO]
Uh.
It's not that, Miss Honda.
I just don't like
it that he's here.
That's the problem.
Right.
Huh?
[YUKI, KYO]
Uh...
[YUKI]
I mean. Uh, never mind.
[KYO]
As long as you understand.
[TOHRU]
Isn't it beautiful?
Maybe we should do
a lap around the lake
so we can see the whole thing.
[YUKI]
Okay.
[KYO]
Sure.
[AYAME]
This is for you.
What's that?
A photo. It was taken
at Kana's wedding.
Whether or not you look
at it is up to you.
Hold on. You went?
No, no. It was a
gift from Mayu.
Really? You ran
into Mayu, huh?
Indeed. The Mayu who
dumped you after a month.
The same Mayu who said
you were nothing more
than a "ripple on the water."
Ah. The Mayuko who was good
friends with Kana in college
and lost interest in you
almost immediately.
Uh. Yes, well, I was
young back then.
So anyway, I take it you didn't
go to the wedding, either.
Can't blame you for not
wanting to see her.
[HATORI] I was afraid she
might get flashbacks.
I didn't overwrite her
memories with others.
It would've been problematic
if she'd happened to
remember something.
Would it, though?
If she had remembered you,
maybe you two could've
fallen in love again.
Stealing the bride
on the wedding day,
how very dramatic.
Like something out of a movie.
No, it's over. Kana and me.
We could never go back.
If we tried, it would only
end in sorrow. Again.
[HATORI] We can't be
the people we once were.
The naive couple who thought
they would spend
their lives together.
The guilt would always be there.
It would fester and
fester until, inevitably,
she would fall ill again.
I would like to believe that
we still love each other,
but being with her is no
longer something I want.
Nor do I have any
desire to see her.
[HATORI]
All I can do is pray...
...that she'll be happy.
I cannot accept that.
Yes, I'm biased in your favor,
but that doesn't change
how wrong all of this is.
It's not fair to you.
Kana has it easy.
She's forgotten everything
and found her chance
at happiness.
And you're stuck
shouldering the burden
of those memories all alone.
I can't help but feel that she's
left you behind with nothing!
Has she?
I wouldn't say that.
This is the problem with you!
Kindness is your
greatest strength
and your biggest weakness.
It's why you get hurt. Why you
endure needless suffering.
He's right. Nice guys
get taken advantage of.
[HATORI] That's rich,
coming from the two of you.
Fine, I won't tell you to
get back together with her.
However, I want to make
one thing perfectly clear.
Whatever it may take,
somehow, someway, Tori,
I want you to be approximately
2,000 times happier than Kana.
Okay. Why 2,000?
One thousand is too little!
[HATORI]
Hm.
You should try showing this
aggressive side of yourself
to Yuki sometime.
Uh. Should I?
Hmm...
All right. No Kana.
But maybe... you'll find
someone else to love.
Someone who doesn't bring
you pain and sadness.
A woman who brings you
joy and hope instead.
Well said, Gure!
You're such a poet.
As a novelist, I take
offense at that.
[HATORI]
Someone else to love?
That would be a foolish
thing to hope for.
Better to be grateful
for what I had.
Cursed as we are,
perhaps having a short time
with someone like Kana
is the most we can
expect from life.
I don't believe I could
ask for anything more.
[SHIGURE]
Ah. They're back.
[HATORI]
All I can do is watch over them.
So they don't make
the same mistakes.
So their smiles don't
wither and die.
Yuki! You've returned!
Did you have fun
with your friends?
I am not his friend!
‐‐By the way,
‐‐[KYO] Hey!
Tori gave me some sound advice
regarding our relationship.
I shall be more aggressive
in my attempts
to deepen our brotherly bonds.
That is no doubt
the best course.
[YUKI] Or maybe you could
just give up instead.
Sorry, but, um, what
do you mean, aggressive?
You see, Yuki is my
younger brother,
and I am his older brother.
With that truth in mind,
I declare the following:
Yuki, as I am your elder,
you must obey me!
[YUKI]
Not in a million years!
[AYAME screaming]
Ayame doesn't get it.
Not even a little.
[SHIGURE]
He's not the only one, Hatori.
You still have your whole
life ahead of you.
[CLASSMATE D] How's it
goin', Ms. Mayu‐chan?
[MAYUKO] Hey, show your
teacher some respect.
It's "Ms. Mayuko
the Great to you."
[CLASSMATE C laughs]
Working hard, Ms. Mayuko
the Great? It's a holiday.
Yeah, I sure am. And it blows.
You here for club?
[GIRLS]
That's right!
[CLASSMATE C] Well, see ya,
Ms. Mayuko the Great. Heh.
[MAYUKO] Yeah, yeah.
Be careful on the way home.
[GIRLS]
Okay.
[SHIGURE] Who knows?
You might find someone yet.
[UOTANI]
"She said don't step on 'em!"