[UOTANI]
Man, it's freezing.
[HANAJIMA] I can't believe how
much has changed this year.
[TOHRU]
I know what you mean.
[TOHRU] It seems like only
yesterday that I was living
in a tiny tent all by myself.
Tohru, hangin' out at your
grandpa's place for New Year's?
Well, that's what I
was planning to do,
but it turns out he and the
family are going to Hawaii.
Seriously?
[TOHRU] Apparently they had some
remodeling money left over.
♪ Aloha 'oe! ♪
Hmph. Do they think
they're too good
to watch New Year's specials
on TV like the rest of us?
Does that mean you'll be staying
at Shigure's house
instead, then?
Um. I'm still working up
the courage to ask him.
Hold up.
So you have no idea where
you're actually gonna be
during the holiday?
Nope. No clue.
Then just come to my place.
It's small, but we'll fit.
I promise it won't
be boring, at least.
You're more than welcome
at my home, too, of course.
Oh, no!
I wouldn't dream of imposing
on the two of you
for the entire winter break.
If you're not down with staying
at one of our houses,
we could always grab your tent
and take a little
New Year's trip.
Oh, yes.
Starting a year off by
camping out in nature
does have a certain
appeal to it.
[TOHRU]
I'll be fine.
Spend some quality time with
your families over the break.
[UOTANI grunts]
[TOHRU]
Wow, it's late.
It's gonna be getting dark soon.
We should hurry up and get home!
[TOHRU humming]
[HANAJIMA]
I sense great agitation.
[UOTANI]
Hm?
In her waves.
[sighs]
[KYO]
Why do we even have to bother
replacing these stupid things?
No one's gonna care about
a tiny hole or two.
[YUKI]
Shut up and work.
It's your fault they're beaten
up in the first place.
Why are we related?
[TOHRU humming]
You really having that
much fun cleaning the deck?
Yup!
I love tidying up the house for
New Year's with all of you.
It's like a dream!
[TOHRU lauging]
[YUKI] I honestly don't
think that Tohru Honda
experiences the world the same
way that other people do.
She accepted that we
change into animals
like it was no big deal.
She even seemed
excited about it.
And her life's been much harder
than most high
schoolers' her age.
Yet she's always smiling,
acting like everything's fine.
We've lived together
for four months,
and I still don't
fully understand her.
[door opens]
Ugh. My poor back.
Why do books have
to be so heavy?
I hate that I have
to get rid of these.
I'll just get yelled at
if I ship them to the
main house, though.
[TOHRU]
Hey, Shigure?
[SHIGURE]
Hm?
[TOHRU] Uh... I know it's
terrible for me to ask this
when you've done so much.
The thing is, my grandfather
contacted me and...
...it seems the family's going
to Hawaii for the holiday.
So would it possibly be okay
if I stayed here in your
house for New Year's?
[SHIGURE]
Mhm.
Course, but is that really
what you wanna do?
[TOHRU]
Uh.
[KYO, YUKI]
I'm staying here, too!
I haven't been back
in four months,
so why should I break the streak
just 'cause a new
year is starting up?
If I show up for
the banquet now,
what was the point
of me leaving?
Yeah.
At least make an appearance,
or else you're going to upset‐‐
[YUKI, KYO]
No, I'm not going.
This is gonna be a pain.
[TOHRU]
Are you okay?
It sounds like everyone's
unhappy about something,
but I can't figure out what.
Listen to how unreasonable
they're being!
These fools are refusing to go
to the main house
for New Year's,
and I'm sure I'll be yelled at.
Stop whining like a toddler.
Don't you have any
sense of self‐respect?
But why aren't you going home?
Momiji told me that
New Year's is, like,
a really important
holiday for the Somas.
Hoppy New Year!
You're right about that,
it's the biggest event of
the year for our family.
The whole entire clan gathers
together for the celebration.
And the most significant part
is the exclusive zodiac banquet.
It is quite the affair,
I assure you.
A few years back, Yuki
graced us with a dance
that was the
personification of beauty.
Really? Wow!
I wish I had the chance
to see him perform.
When will you learn to
keep your mouth shut?
One day.
This banquet sounds incredible.
And it's a lot like the one
mentioned in the
old folk tale, too.
You have no idea
how right you are.
Uh?
Cats don't get to go,
so I've got nothing to
do with the banquet.
[TOHRU gasps]
That's so sad. Why not?
[SHIGURE]
It's longstanding tradition
that no little
kitties can attend.
Which means we keep
close to the spirit
of the old story, at least.
How awful.
I'm the one who can't go,
why are you so sad about it?
'Sides, the banquet
isn't why I decided
not to visit the main house.
Oh, no, it's because
poor Kagura
would likely smother
him with adoration.
Shut up!
[YUKI]
There are other reasons.
If we did return,
we'd be expected to
stay until January 3rd.
In that case, you'd be
in this house all alone
that whole time, Miss Honda.
Thanks for thinking of me.
But I would be perfectly
fine here on my own.
If it's such a big holiday
for your family,
you should absolutely go
and have fun with them.
It'll be your first time
visiting your parents
in a while, right?
I'm sure they look
forward to seeing you‐‐
you don't wanna
disappoint them.
Don't worry about me!
I'll take good care of the
house while you're away!
I'll clean and water the plan‐‐
And water the...
Ah! Oh, no! I left the
bathwater running!
You've totally set my
mind at ease, Tohru.
Fine, then.
Well, I guess that settles it.
I'll go.
Have to. After that speech.
[TOHRU] It'll be your first
time visiting your parents
in a while, right?
[YUKI] She's never going
to see her parents again.
[KYO]
No matter how much she wants to.
Guess I can learn to
put up with Akito.
If I must.
I can handle Kagura
in small doses.
If I must.
[SHIGURE]
Hmm...
As far as these two
are concerned,
Tohru's words are the law.
[YUKI]
If she says she'll be fine,
then shouldn't we trust her?
[KYO] Yeah. New Year's is
always the same, anyway.
We just have to suck it
up and get through it.
[TOHRU]
All set?
Make sure you don't lose
each other in the crowds!
We'll be fine.
The streets'll be empty.
Most people are watching TV.
Make sure you lock up.
You should check
the windows, too.
Right! See you
when you get back.
[SHIGURE]
Have a happy New Year!
[TOHRU]
And you guys, too!
[YUKI gasps]
[YUKI]
She'll be okay. I'm sure.
[HATORI] Akito. It's too
cold to be barefoot.
[AKITO]
It's been a long time...
...since I saw Yuki.
You know, a few nights ago,
she left her bedroom
window wide open.
[YUKI, SHIGURE]
Are you a peeping Tom now?
Oh, come on. Get real.
I saw it from the yard.
She could really stand
to be more observant.
She fell down the stairs
again yesterday, too.
She's the kinda girl who'd
run into a brick wall.
Definitely the type who'd die
choking on her New Year's mochi.
[YUKI] Why would you even
imagine something so horrible?
[sighs]
That's enough.
You sound like a couple
of new parents
fretting over their child.
[KYO, YUKI]
Huh?
Look, I get it, you're worried
about Tohru being alone.
But it was your decision
to come to the estate.
What're you talkin' about?
I'm not worried‐‐
she's just fine!
This is ridiculous.
Keep walking.
Oh, now that I think about it,
the paper said something
about burglaries.
There've been a
bunch in this area.
I think the criminal's
still on the loose.
[BOTH gasp]
[KYO]
Crap.
She's such an airhead I bet
she'd invite the burglar inside
from the cold!
[YUKI] She'll probably
even fluff his pillow
and serve him tea,
while asking him to
tell her his life story.
[KYO growls]
[SHIGURE]
I like this game.
Hey, come on. Get a grip, 'kay?
If you stand around in
the street like that‐‐
You could be killed.
[SHIGURE yelps]
Oh. Hi. I did not see you there.
[KYO] Does she always have
to make a dramatic entrance?
[YUKI] Where does one even
buy a cloak like that?
[SHIGURE] Fancy meeting
you on the road! Heh.
We're on our way
home to spend time
with the rest of the family.
I see. So she'll be
utterly alone this year.
[BOTH gasp]
[HANAJIMA] She's never
spent a New Year's holiday
without her mother.
And this time, she
won't have anyone.
Arisa and I both offered
to spend the break with her,
but she just smiled
that smile of hers
and told us it was important
to be with our families.
Who's looking out
for her, though?
Think about it.
All the New Year's specials...
All the performers...
They're basically the
exact same every year,
which must bring back memories.
How will she feel this time,
seeing them without her mother?
[YUKI]
What must she have felt
when she watched us
leave her behind?
I wonder, is she really okay
with how this turned out?
Will she end up
being happy, or not?
[KYO] Did we abandon her?
How must she feel right now?
[BOTH grunt]
[KYO groans]
What are you buffoons doing?
Just go to the banquet.
Your precious Akito misses you.
And what about you?
You'll break your precious
Kagura's heart.
[KYO]
Agh! Screw you!
You can take that insane
girl for all I care.
And you can have Akito.
[KYO]
I'll pass!
[SHIGURE]
Wait, are you kidding me?
Where are you off to now?
[BOTH]
I'm going home.
Really? You, too?
Your dinner's waiting.
Shut up. I don't care
‐‐about the banquet.
‐‐Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I get it.
You planned this.
That whole speech was
just to trick them
into going back for her.
It wasn't a trick.
Not like you're thinking.
My only desire was to do
something nice for her.
And nothing more.
I wish you good waves
in the new year.
She's a clever one.
[YUKI] We've lived
together for four months...
...and I still don't
fully understand her.
[KYO] I missed it.
I couldn't see the truth.
Because she always seems
like she's so carefree.
[YUKI]
She gives an earnest smile
to even the smallest things.
[KYO]
Yeah. She's constantly smiling.
[YUKI] And she always says
what you want to hear most.
This may sound strange,
but your kindness
reminds me of a candle.
It can light up the darkness.
Though I do have one request.
If I forget you, please
befriend me again.
I have always loved
the zodiac Cat!
I'm confusing you.
What I mean is:
I want us to be friends!
[TOHRU] So trust me
when I say, I can see it.
You have a plum on your
back. I swear it's true.
[YUKI]
Why didn't I see it?
[KYO]
Why couldn't I see it?
[TOHRU]
Soma, Kyo, Shigure.
I wanted all of us
to stay together.
Learning about each other.
I wanted it so much.
[KYO]
There's no way she's fine.
She doesn't wanna be alone.
[YUKI] I should've known she
wouldn't wanna be by herself.
[TOHRU]
I want to go... home.
Even if it is selfish,
that's what I want.
To be with all of you!
[YUKI]
I wanna go home.
[KYO]
[YUKI]
I wanna go home.
[KYO]
[YUKI, KYO]
I want to go home.
Right now!
[gasps]
Whoa! Oh my gosh, you scared me!
What happened?
What‐What're you doing back?
[gasps]
Ah! No, don't worry!
I‐I can explain. Oh! I was
cutting onions! Yeah, that's it!
Um, and, you know, it's
that time of year where...
...where you just can't
help but be moved
by the songs people sing
and all of the happy people
that are on TV and stuff...
[BOTH groan]
[TOHRU] Ah! What's happening?
Are‐Are you two okay?
[YUKI] Thank goodness. If we
hadn't realized in time...
[KYO] We almost let her cry
through the new year alone.
Um. Hello?
[YUKI] We're okay. Just excited
to watch the first sunrise.
[KYO]
Yeah, that's right,
but I wanna eat
New Year's noodles first.
[gasps]
[YUKI, KYO]
We're home.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Welcome home, you two.
[SHIGURE]
Honey, I'm home!
[HATSUHARU]
About time.
[SHIGURE]
Hm?
You're the last
one here, Sensei.
[SHIGURE] Ah, if it isn't
my two favorite Ha's.
Nice of you to greet
me at the door.
We have actual names, you know.
One of these days you'll learn
to have fun, I'm sure of it.
What's up? Long time no see.
Yeah, where are the others?
[SHIGURE]
Hmm.
Well, not to make a big
deal of it or anything,
but... they're skipping?
"They're skipping"?
Huh.
I can already feel the heat
of Kagura's fiery rage.
Which is nothing compared
to the bone‐chilling horror
of Akito's quiet fury.
[HATORI]
So, what do we do?
[SHIGURE] Relax. I can
handle Akito myself.
[HATSUHARU]
Sheesh.
And here I was looking forward
to my last fight of the year.
Calm down. Don't you go
breaking houses, too.
[HATSUHARU]
I guess...
...I can understand why
they'd wanna skip, though.
It's easier running from pain,
instead of facing it.
You're wrong there.
I don't think this was about
running away for them at all,
or at least not entirely.
Uh, what're you saying?
[MOMIJI] Shii‐chan!
You're finally here!
The banquet is about to start.
Oh! Momiji. I'm looking
forward to your dance.
[MOMIJI]
Danke!
There's something we
have to deal with first.
Who knows how Akito
will react to hearing
that those two are skipping.
Wait, who's skipping what?
Is someone not coming
to the banquet? Who? Who?
[SHIGURE]
Good evening.
It's a pleasure to watch you
reaping what you sowed... Akito.
[TOHRU gasping]
What's wrong? Why are you
looking at me that way?
[KYO]
I need you to eat slower.
[TOHRU]
Hm?
But I'm pretty sure I'm eating
at a normal rate of speed.
Mochi is best when you
take time to savor it.
Just make sure you're
chewing it well.
You, too? What's up
with you guys?
[TOHRU] Do people really choke
on mochi that often,
or are they just being paranoid?
[phone ringing]
Oh, that's weird.
Who's calling so late?
Whoever it is, they got
pretty crap manners.
What if it's someone
from the estate?
[KYO gasps]
[KYO] Don't tell me Kagura
caused some kind of emergency.
[YUKI]
Did Akito fly into a frenzy?
[TOHRU]
Hello. May I ask who's calling?
[UOTANI]
Hey, Tohru. It's me.
Uo‐chan? Why are you calling
so late? Is everything okay?
Wait, please don't tell me
you ended up choking
on your mochi.
Yeah, no, that's something
only you would do.
Also, how could I call
you if I were choking?
That doesn't make sense.
[chuckles] You've got
a good point.
So what's the matter, then?
[UOTANI]
Nothing. I'm just saying hi.
I was worried you
might be feeling
a little lonely or something.
[TOHRU]
You called to check in on me?
Well, yeah.
Hanajima was saying
stuff about your waves
being agitated or whatever.
Huh?
Nuh‐uh, drop it
right now, Pops!
Our deal was you got one beer
in honor of the holiday.
Oh, yeah. I must've lost count.
Don't play dumb with me!
Trash the can.
Jeez. Hopeless geezer.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[TOHRU] You know,
I truly am a lucky girl.
[UOTANI]
Don't cry, stupid.
I gotta go, but have
a good New Year's.
Thanks. And the same
to you and your family.
[phone clicks]
That was Uo‐chan calling.
She was just checking in
because she was worried
about me for some reason.
Oh. I see.
But that's nice, isn't it?
‐‐Of course!
‐‐Speaking of your friends,
we saw Hanajima earlier on
our way to the Soma estate.
What a coincidence.
[YUKI]
Indeed.
She was really concerned
about you, too, Miss Honda.
That's very kind of her.
Hana‐chan...
I'll make sure you're my first
phone call of the new year.
I'll be waiting.
So, um, are you sure
it's going to be okay
for you to miss the big banquet?
I promise, I'm glad
you're here with me,
but I don't wanna
get anyone in trouble.
No, it's fine.
We'll drop by and wish them a
happy New Year at some point.
[YUKI]
Probably.
Thank you for cooking.
Of course, it was nothing.
[YUKI] Right about now, the
banquet should be in full swing.
[KYO]
I wonder how mad Kagura is.
[YUKI]
Akito must be furious, but...
[KYO]
But...
[humming]
It's so much colder
on the roof.
[YUKI]
Here.
Please be careful.
I will be. Thank you
for giving me a hand.
[TOHRU gasps, giggles]
Look, you guys,
the sun's coming up!
Perfect. Made it.
[YUKI]
I feel strangely at peace now.
I don't feel guilty, either.
[KYO] I had a lot of
reasons for coming back,
but if I'm being
honest, deep down...
So, are you ready?
You only get one chance
for a New Year's wish.
I've already got
mine figured out.
[YUKI]
Deep down...
[TOHRU gasps]
[KYO]
Deep down... all I wanted...
[YUKI]
All I really cared about
was greeting the new
year at her side.
Hey, Kyo, Soma.
I just wanna say
happy New Year!
I'm looking forward to
the next one with you.
The feeling is mutual.
Uh. Yeah, same.
[KYO] This is the year I'm
gonna beat that damn Rat!
[YUKI] Uh‐huh, sure.
Good luck with that.
[TOHRU] It's going to be
a wonderful new year!
[HATSUHARU]
"Yuki was my first love."