[doorbell rings]
[DELIVERYMAN A]
Hello! Package delivery!
[TOHRU]
They're...
They're all animals!
Yeah. Those are some
cute pets you got there.
Now, if you could
please sign here.
[TOHRU]
No! You don't understand!
[DELIVERYMAN A chuckles]
Aren't you a smart
little poochie?
Thanks a lot, ma'am.
Have a good day!
[KYO]
Ugh!
We could've covered if you
jerks hadn't transformed, too!
[YUKI] You're the one who
screwed up first, stupid Cat.
‐‐[KYO] Oh, yeah?
‐‐[TOHRU] And they can talk?
‐‐[YUKI] Clumsy feline.
[barks]
[KYO hisses]
[SHIGURE sighs]
[SHIGURE]
We can either tell her the truth
or make up a story she
won't believe anyway.
As you can see, I'm the Dog,
Yuki is the Rat,
and Kyo Soma over
here is the Cat.
We're all possessed
by animal spirits.
Ten others in the Soma family
are similarly possessed
by the different
zodiac animals.
It's been this way
for generations.
Unfortunately,
it doesn't give us
any especially cool
powers to speak of.
Pretty much all we
can do is communicate
with our respective animals,
and we transform when
our bodies are weakened
or when hugged by someone
of the opposite sex.
We automatically turn
human again after a while.
Completely naked, I'm afraid.
[SHIGURE]
Sorry about that.
I know it must've come
as quite a shock to you.
Now, then, are you
feeling a bit calmer?
I think so, but it's kind
of a lot to take in.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Of course!
That must be why Soma
shoved away that girl
who tried to hug him.
I have to say, that was a
pretty pathetic showing, Kyo.
I mean, you are a
trained martial artist.
Shouldn't it be a little harder
for a girl to sneak up on you?
You really have eyes for no
one but Yuki, don't you?
Don't make it sound like that!
It's not my fault!
You're the ones who let
a girl into this house!
Why is she even here?!
Calm yourself.
You have absolutely no say
in who we allow to
come in the house.
You're an outsider.
[grunts]
Shut up!
Oh, crap.
Is that blood?
[TOHRU]
Huh? I'm bleeding?
[SHIGURE] Oh, dear,
we should get a bandage
on that immediately.
[TOHRU gasps]
[YUKI]
I knew you were a moron,
but I didn't think
you were this stupid.
Out of respect for the
sheer depth of your idiocy,
I'll do you a favor
and fight you for real.
So... please try
not to bore me.
Give it all you've got,
you little girly boy!
Are they...?
Oh, this is normal.
Get them in a room together
and they're bound to go off.
You know, like
fire and gasoline.
Uh, okay, but shouldn't
we try to stop them?
Let them spar.
I assure you,
they'll be done soon.
Yuki will win.
Like he always does.
[gasps]
[YUKI]
Just as I feared.
You were a bore.
‐‐Wow. He went flying.
‐‐It's like the two of you
‐‐are trying to trash my house.
‐‐How badly are you hurt?
Oh, I'm totally fine, really.
Don't worry, it was just a bump.
But is he okay?
[YUKI]
Prob'ly.
Yes, I'm sure he'll be fine.
There, you see?
[TOHRU] I never imagined that
the boy known as "the prince"
would be so tough.
When he's at school, he's so...
[TOHRU gasps]
Oh my gosh, I have to hurry
or I'll be late to class!
I'm sorry for running
off like this,
but it's important to me
to go to school every day,
I hope you understand.
Yes, you did promise
your late mother.
Don't apologize.
Though, I should let you know,
I will have to report that you
witnessed our transformation
to Akito, the family head.
"Family head"?
Wow, that sounds important.
'Kay, I understand.
I guess I should go
change my clothes now.
Of course.
[YUKI] That explains
why you were so quick
to tell our secret.
[SHIGURE]
Hm?
She'll have her
memories altered.
Like those others did before.
No, this is much different.
Back then, there were
so many people involved
that we didn't have a choice.
I should get going, too.
Hey, stupid Cat, you'd better
fix the roof in her room.
Kyo, look after
the place, will you?
Don't you dare think
about running off again
while I'm gone either.
Apologize to Tohru
whenever you see her, too.
[bell ringing]
[UOTANI]
Tohru!
It's not like you to be late.
You oversleep?
Huh? Oh. That's right.
[KINOSHITA] So you admit
you're super lazy.
You should've stayed at home
and gotten more beauty rest.
[BOTH yelp]
[UOTANI] The prince was late,
too, so they're extra on edge.
And suspicious.
[TOHRU] I definitely can't tell
them I stayed at his house.
What a buncha airheads.
Must be nice to be so dumb.
[YUKI]
Miss Honda?
[TOHRU]
Is that you, Soma?
What did you tell your friends?
Our secret, is it safe?
I‐I didn't tell them anything.
Oh, no, were you worried
that I would go and
blab to everybody?
I promise, you don't have
to worry about me.
My mom always told me
that only bad people
spill secrets that have
been entrusted to them.
[YUKI]
No. I'm concerned‐‐
Look, I'll swear you an oath.
We could even seal it with fire
or blood if you wanted to!
[YUKI]
No, listen.
[TOHRU] Mom apparently used to
do stuff like that all the‐‐
That's not the issue here.
[YUKI]
I'm sorry,
but even though you're doing
your best not to tell,
we might end up
erasing your memories.
[gasps]
Well, not literally.
It's more like a strong
form of hypnotism.
[YUKI] A long time ago,
the truth about me came out,
just like it did this morning.
I was playing around
with some friends
and a girl hugged me.
[YUKI]
It was a giant mess.
And in the end, everyone
who saw it happen
had their memories suppressed.
[YUKI]
Akito, am I really so strange
that I have to hide who I am?
[AKITO]
Yes. You are.
A person turning into a rat
is obviously something
no one would understand.
People would be sickened
by your existence,
and they'd begin to
avoid you at all costs.
You would be utterly alone.
Is that what you want?
[TOHRU]
Are you okay?
[YUKI]
I'm sorry.
But I can't go against whatever
Akito says is right for us.
No matter what's decided,
I must go along with it.
That's just... how it is.
Wait. Hold on, I‐‐
[TOHRU]
I'm so sorry!
It was an accident, I swear!
I‐I'd never do that on purpose!
[YUKI] It's okay.
Just as long as no one saw.
[TOHRU]
What I wanted to say was...
...I appreciate you being
concerned about me.
It makes me happy. So, thanks.
And I get what you said.
This is an important secret
I accidentally found out.
Something that could have
a huge effect on you.
So please, I want you to do
whatever will make you and
your family feel the safest.
Sure, the idea of forgetting
does make me sad,
but if that's what I have
to do, I'll grin and bear it.
I do have one thing to ask you.
If I forget you,
please befriend me again.
[TOHRU gasps]
The amount of time we
stay as animals varies.
There we go. All done.
[TOHRU]
Oh. Your tie is crooked.
[YUKI] I'm not great
when it comes to that.
No sweat.
It's lucky for you,
I'm here to help.
[AKITO] People would be
sickened by your existence.
You would be utterly alone.
[YUKI] Miss Honda,
you don't feel... sickened?
Oh, no. I'm all better.
Huh? No, that isn't
what I meant.
[YUKI]
Shall we go?
[TOHRU]
Yeah. Good idea.
[YUKI]
Thanks for that.
[TOHRU] No problem.
I've got a knack for neckties.
[KYO]
Call a pro to really fix it.
For now, you just need to
keep the rain out, right?
[TOHRU]
Oh. Thank you.
[KYO]
H‐Hey!
Y‐Yes?
[KYO] I, uh, can get kind of a
one‐track mind when I'm upset.
So, about this morning...
...I wanted to say I'm so‐‐
[SHIGURE]
Yuki, Tohru, I'm home!
Is that clumsy kitten who lost
another fight still here?
Forget it, dammit.
No. Please. What
were you saying?
[SHIGURE]
It's good news.
Tohru is allowed
to live with us.
So long as she continues
to keep our secret.
Does that mean I
won't be punished?
As long as you stay quiet,
you won't have done
anything wrong.
[TOHRU]
I will!
[TOHRU] Thank goodness!
I get to keep my memories!
To be honest, that plan almost
sounds too good to be true.
Like you two might be scheming
and mixing up Miss Honda
in some plot or other.
Oh, come on. Would I do that?
[AKITO] I'll trust this "Tohru"
person, for the time being.
This might be a
good opportunity‐‐
for Yuki and Kyo, as well as me.
[SHIGURE chuckles nervously]
[TOHRU]
Excuse me.
Um, it's probably a little
late to be saying this,
but I'm so glad I've
gotten to meet you.
The feeling's mutual.
Um, yes. I do agree.
And it's a pleasure to
meet you, too. Uh, Kyo.
You can leave me outta this!
I've got nothing to do‐‐ Uh!
[splash]
[KYO]
What the hell was that for?!
[YUKI]
Go away. Outsider.
[TOHRU]
Well, I guess that's that.
I'll be staying with
the Soma family for now.
This is amazing.
I can't believe you
managed to clean up
such a disgusting kitchen.
Well, I gave it my best.
I didn't even know that
Shigure owned a rice cooker.
Yeah, I had to excavate it.
How does it taste?
I hope all the flavors
are coming through.
Delicious. I haven't had
a meal like this in a while.
Oh, wonderful!
Where is Shigure?
He and that stupid Cat have been
gone for quite a long time.
And you went out for a little
bit earlier, too, didn't you?
[YUKI] Yeah. To my secret
base in the backyard.
What? A secret base? Is it
like some private fortress?
[YUKI] Eh, it's probably not
as interesting as you imagine.
But I can show it to you
sometime if you'd like.
[gasps] Wait, seriously?
That's so exciting!
I saw one once when I was a kid,
but no girls were
allowed inside.
Shut up!
Will you listen to me
for one second, Kyo?
I'm so pissed. Is this
what makes you happy?
Manipulating innocent
people like me?
[SHIGURE]
Slow down!
Sure, I'm enjoying
this thoroughly...
[TOHRU]
Welcome home.
Would you two like
something to eat, maybe?
Hell no!
Don't take your
anger out on her.
And no shoes inside.
Says the man who did laps
around the room in his.
How nice. Is that food for us?
'Scuse me. Why's he upset?
[SHIGURE
It's his nature.
Also, I might've tricked him
into taking a school
transfer exam.
A transfer?
Yep, it's official
and everything.
Tomorrow, our Kyo
will be walking
the same school hallways
as the two of you.
Thanks for the foo‐‐
You're done. Put that
down and get out.
[SHIGURE]
I knew you'd be mad.
Here's the thing:
This is good for him.
He should be going to the
boys' school near his place,
but he hasn't shown up to class
in over four months now.
Apparently, he's been
training in the mountains.
Why training?
All that he wants is to
beat Yuki in a real fight.
They've been rivals ever
since they were kids.
He's an idiot.
Thanks for the food.
Of course.
[TOHRU] I wonder why Kyo
wants to beat up Soma so bad.
Maybe he resents the fact
that he was tricked.
Just like the Cat in
the old zodiac story.
But I get the feeling
it's not my place to ask.
At least not right now.
Especially since I'm
pretty sure that Kyo
doesn't like me
in the slightest.
Just my luck.
I finally get to meet
the zodiac Cat
and everything goes wrong.
[STUDENT B]
Where is he?
[STUDENT C] Look, over there.
The boy with the orange hair.
[STUDENT D]
Think it's his natural color?
[STUDENT E]
He's super cute!
[CLASSMATE A]
So, you're related to Soma?
[CLASSMATE B]
I bet you're crazy close, huh?
[CLASSMATE A]
Tell us everything.
[TOHRU]
He's terrified.
[STUDENT F] Hey, Yuki.
I hear that's your cousin.
Why haven't you
introduced us already?
[YUKI]
Sorry, Senpai.
It's true that we're
technically cousins,
but I've never spoken
to him before.
[TOHRU]
What's with that weird smile?
[UOTANI]
I'm diggin' his carrot top.
Maybe 'cause it kinda reminds me
of the blazing hair your
mom use to have, Tohru.
[TOHRU] Yeah. Now that
you say that, I see it.
I feel them.
His strong waves are exactly
the same as Yuki Soma's.
They're odd. What am I sensing?
It's almost as if the
waves aren't human.
[TOHRU] Whoa. Hana's Wave
Report is totally spot on.
[CLASSMATE D]
Something wrong?
[CLASSMATE C] Hey. Where
are you going? We were ta‐‐
[CLASSMATE C]
Ow, that hurts! Let go of me!
[CLASSMATE E]
Oh my gosh! What is your issue?
[CLASSMATE D]
Get your hands off of her!
Everybody leave me alone!
[CLASSMATES scream]
[CLASSMATE D]
No way. He's incredible.
[UOTANI] Looks like he'll
be fun to have in class.
[YUKI]
Hey.
Would you try thinking before
you cause a big scene like that?
Why do you go here?
The place is crawling with
girls. You're insane.
It's better than
being forced to go
to the all‐boys'
school Akito picked.
I want at least one foot
outside of the Soma cage.
I can't understand why you
want to be inside it so badly.
[growls]
Course you don't!
You'd never understand!
I'm gonna win!
I'll beat you and become
a full‐fledged member
of the Soma clan.
I won't let them ostracize me
anymore, you hear me?
Please don't!
I'm‐I'm so sorry.
But you shouldn't‐‐
If you fight at school, you‐you
could get in trouble, or‐‐
Will you shut up already?!
This isn't any of your business!
What's your deal anyway?!
Stop causing...
That's enough.
...get out of here!
[KYO grunts]
Maximum... anger.
He already hated me, and this
made things even worse.
You really are a hopeless fool.
[KYO]
Aren't you gonna kick me?
Sometimes not getting
kicked hurts more.
[SHIGURE] Your very first day
and you skipped class?
[KYO] Listen, I wanna
leave this house.
It's only your third night here.
Think of it as training.
That'll help you tough it out.
[KYO] I always end up
saying mean things to her.
Every time.
Wait, who?
Oh. You must mean Tohru.
[KYO]
I can't do this, okay?
I'm not cut out for living
so close to other people.
Nah, it's just that you don't
have much experience yet.
Think of it this way:
You can break a table
in half with one punch,
we're well aware of that,
but you're also capable
of stopping that punch
right before it lands.
That's because you've trained.
And getting along with people
takes practice, too.
If you interact with strangers,
you might hurt them, or you
might end up hurt by them.
But that's how you learn,
about other people
and about yourself.
If you don't do that,
you'll never be
capable of connecting.
So keep training and resist
the urge to run away.
Then, one day, when you meet
a girl who says she loves you,
you'll be able to
treasure her completely.
Like such a girl exists.
And what will you
do if she does?
[KYO]
That's a pretty easy question.
I'll start out by asking
her if she's crazy.
Is that so?
[YUKI]
I'm home.
But where's Tohru?
Still at school?
At work.
She won't be done until late,
so I'm thinking of
walking her home.
[SHIGURE]
Yeah. That's a smart idea.
Perverts sometimes
creep around here.
[TOHRU sighs]
[KYO] Stop causing problems
and get out of here!
[sighs]
[TOHRU] When I said
I'd quit being the Dog
and become a Cat instead,
I really meant it
with all my heart.
I can't believe the real
Cat spirit hates me.
[KYOKO]
Just be you, Tohru.
I know I should be, Mom.
This won't bring me down.
‐‐[gravel crunches]
‐‐[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Don't tell me...
Is this... some creepy
forest pervert?
Go away!
[gasps]
Oh. Oh, no.
Sorry, I was just doing
practice swings!
Lucky running into you out here!
Are you going for a walk?
[KYO]
Cut it out.
So, you hit me. Whatever.
Just drop it.
Okay. Uh, Kyo?
[KYO]
Yeah, what?
I was just saying your name.
Well, it sounded like
you were calling me!
Sorry!
[KYO]
No, it's fine.
You can say my name
without needing something.
And I know you don't mean
to cause any problems for us.
And if I piss you off,
you can go ahead and hit me,
I don't care.
[TOHRU]
Am I reading this wrong,
or is he trying to apologize?
Is that why he's
out here? To find me?
[TOHRU]
Hey, Kyo.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
But the honest truth is,
I thought you were a pervert,
that's why I swung
my bag at you!
Me? A pervert?
[TOHRU]
I actually really like you!
I have always loved
the zodiac Cat!
[KYO]
Uh...
I'm serious. I even wanted to
be born the Year of the Cat.
I'm confusing you.
What I mean is, I want
us to be friends!
What'll you do
if she does exist?
A girl who says she loves you.
Ugh. Nothin's good about
the Year of the Cat, okay?
[TOHRU] I think... I might be
starting to understand him,
just a little bit.
He can be awkward
sometimes, yes,
but I think he has
a gentle heart.
He knows what it feels
like to be sorry.
And he's an honest person.
[SHIGURE] Why, Kyo, you
lecherous little deviant!
What gives you the
right to call me that?!
You know, Tohru,
he personally offered to
walk you back from work
so you'd get home
safe and sound.
That was a one‐time thing;
it won't happen again.
[TOHRU]
Okay. But I'm glad you're here.
It's really nice to see you
eating a proper meal with us.
So how is it?
Up to your standards?
What do you want?
Nothing.
You were looking at me.
You're in front of me.
Sure, like you'd gimme
that look for no reason!
Is the food that bad?
It is!
[TOHRU]
Then I'll try harder next time.
[KYO]
I mean. Uh, no.
[TOHRU]
As you can see, Mom,
we patched things up.
And I have a feeling the
days ahead will be fun!
[TOHRU] "Let's Play
Rich Man‐Poor Man."