[WOMAN A]
I heard it was suicide.
[WOMAN B]
Poor thing.
[MAN A] The Cat spirit
must've driven her to it.
[KYO]
Shut up.
[WOMAN C]
The child isn't even crying.
[MAN B] You'd think he'd
show some remorse
for what he did.
Just shut up!
This isn't my fault!
You don't understand!
[KAZUMA]
I do.
I understand.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kazuma Soma.
This isn't my fault.
It's not my fault!
[KAZUMA]
It's okay.
It's okay. I understand.
[gasps]
Kyo, how would you like to
come and live with me?
[SHIGURE]
This is a pleasant surprise.
How've you been?
Fine, thank you.
And I hear that
life as a novelist
has been treating you well.
[SHIGURE laughs]
[SHIGURE]
Oh, I get by.
Ah. Thank you very much.
Of course!
[TOHRU] This must be the man
Kyo told me about before.
His master.
[KAGURA]
Sensei, I'm glad you're back.
It's been so long.
It has. But you've
been well, I hope.
[YUKI]
It's good to see you.
Sensei.
Hello there, Yuki.
You're so much taller than
I remember. You've grown.
[SHIGURE]
Oh, Tohru.
Sorry. This is Kazuma Soma.
The family's martial
arts instructor.
He's taught Yuki, Kagura
here, Haru, and others.
He's Kyo's master.
[TOHRU]
Oh, I didn't realize...
If you don't mind, may I
please call you "Tohru"?
Oh! Yes, please do!
That would be great.
Um. It's nice to meet you!
I've heard a lot about you.
I believe you know of
the zodiac spirits?
[TOHRU]
Uh, yes.
Ah, but how much?
[SHIGURE]
Hey, Kyo.
Maybe you should stop
sulking in the corner
and greet your master.
You haven't seen him
since you trained in
the mountains, right?
Aren't you happy to be reunited?
I, uh‐‐
Is something wrong?
Could you tell me which
room belongs to Kyo?
Oh, sure. You just go up
the stairs and take a right.
I'd be happy to show you.
No. I can manage on
my own, thank you.
[SHIGURE, KAGURA chuckle]
That's classic Kyo.
Totally.
I think I'm missing something.
What do you mean?
[giggles] It's cute.
Kyo's actually really happy
to see his master again,
but he would probably rather
die than let us see it.
Especially with Yun‐chan
hanging around.
[knocking]
[KAZUMA]
Kyo. Let's talk.
[KYO]
That was rude of me.
I'm sorry, Master.
It's okay. I understand.
[KYO]
You're really here.
Welcome back, Master!
[KAZUMA]
It's good to be back.
[TOHRU] So, I guess Kyo's
master isn't one of the Somas
with a zodiac spirit?
[KAGURA]
No.
He is still a member of
the main family, though.
[KAGURA] They say Sensei's
grandfather was actually the one
possessed by the Cat
spirit before Kyo.
I guess, if anyone
can understand
some of what Kyo's going
through, then he'd be the one.
But I've always thought
their connection
was based on more
than just that.
Sensei really seems to love Kyo.
Like a true father
would love his son.
Wow, they must be so close.
[KYO] Does this mean your
training sabbatical
is finally over?
Yes, it is.
I'm afraid I can't afford
to spend any more time
away from the dojo.
Great! So, can I go back
to the dojo, too, then?
That's what you said, right?
For now, you will
continue to live here.
So, what? You're just
gonna break your promise?
I guess you're scared
of Akito, too.
That's not it.
My observations have
led me to believe
that this is the best
environment for you.
Whether the two of you
living under the same roof
was coincidence, or fate,
the fact remains,
she is a comfort to you.
[KYO] Master! Please,
I can't stand it here.
It's like I'm sitting
in a lukewarm bath
and my skin's getting pruny.
Sometimes, I hate it so much...
I feel like I wanna scream.
I didn't ask for this.
I don't need to be comforted.
[KYO]
I hate it.
[KAZUMA]
Now that isn't true.
That's not hate you feel.
[KAGURA] Sensei will be
staying the night, won't he?
Me, too! It's like
a slumber party.
It's not! Go home, would ya?
Aww!
I'm glad he's staying,
but where do you think
we should put his futon?
Maybe he can share
Shigure's room?
[YUKI]
No, definitely not.
[TOHRU]
Uhh.
Well, I guess that
means he and Kyo
will just have to bunk together.
Huh? Why can't he sleep
here in the living room?
[KAGURA]
I'll go ask him.
Come back!
It'll be nice. I'm sure you
have a lot to talk about.
Not really.
Oh, I know!
Um, here's an idea.
If there's time, maybe I could
see you and your master
do some of that sparring
you talked about before.
[KAGURA]
Sensei's gonna stay!
[KAZUMA]
It's time.
I thought I should warn you.
I'm going to remove it. Tonight.
Things may get messy.
[SHIGURE]
I don't doubt it.
Why now? Seems like an
awfully sudden move.
I know.
But today, when I saw
how he looks at her,
I thought, perhaps she's the
one who can open his heart.
Perhaps she will accept him.
All of him.
Either way, I think it's best to
find out now rather than later.
We are running out of time.
[SHIGURE] Even you would
entrust everything to her.
One young girl.
[SHIGURE] Still, you can't
be certain it will succeed.
Even if she does accept him,
Kyo will most likely
reject that acceptance.
And this time, he may
well break for good.
[SHIGURE]
He might come to despise you.
You may never see
his smile again.
Tell me, is that really a
risk you're willing to take?
[KYO]
Ha! Are you kidding me?
How'd this even happen?
You really suck at
cooking, Master.
[KAZUMA]
Yes.
I suppose I'll need
more training
if I want to make
something edible.
[KYO laughing]
[KAZUMA]
Even so...
Even so, I'll take my chances.
On her.
[KAZUMA] Tohru, might you have
a spare moment this evening?
Of course.
[KYO]
Listen, Master,
whatever this is about,
couldn't we have talked inside?
You know I'm no good when
the weather's like this.
My grandfather suffered
the same way.
Apparently, rainy days often
left him feeling weak and ill.
But is it the Cat spirit..
...or is it the spirit
of your true form
that can't stand the rain?
It's time.
To move forward, you must fully
accept who you truly are.
If you cannot do that, then‐‐
I accept it now!
[KYO]
I have for a long time.
Being born with the Cat spirit
meant my life was already over.
And that it's the Rat's fault.
He's the reason
all this happened.
Everything woulda been different
if it weren't for him!
This is all his fault!
He's the reason this happened!
So I'll kill him,
and then I'll die, too!
Then you'll be satisfied, right?
That's what you want!
If I die, then you'll be happy!
I see you haven't changed.
You need to make a choice.
Is this how you wish
to live your life?
Covering your ears...
Closing your eyes...
Burying everything else beneath
the hate you feel for Yuki...
Is that the only way
you can keep yourself
from falling apart?
If that's how you live,
then that's how you'll die.
Lost and alone.
Like my grandfather.
You hate it here.
That's what you said.
But it's not true. You're
simply trying to run away.
You realized you've
grown comfortable here.
This "lukewarm bath"
makes you feel safe.
Except, you're also scared.
You don't want your true
form to be discovered...
...because of what
you stand to lose.
Instead of risking that loss,
you'll run away and
spare yourself the pain.
Therefore, I will take
away your escape route,
and we'll see what happens.
Will you lose what you've found?
There is no turning
back after this, Kyo.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Let's see if your
life truly is already over.
[KYO'S MOTHER]
It's okay.
It'll all be okay...
because I love you.
That's why I don't want
anyone else to see you.
Don't look. Nobody
look at my son.
Don't look.
[KYO'S MOTHER]
It's disgusting.
[KYO]
Don't look!
[AKITO]
Really? This is Kyo's true form?
[KYO grunting]
It's like some hideous
creature from a nightmare.
What's that stench?
It's revolting.
Like the smell of
something rotten.
[AKITO]
So, that's what it looks like.
The true form of the Cat spirit.
Are you... Kyo?
It's disgusting.
[KYO]
She saw. She saw.
She saw me.
It's too late. It's over.
It's... all over.
[KAZUMA] Now you've seen
what Kyo's kept hidden.
The true form of the Cat
spirit that possesses him.
Tell me, does it disgust you?
Frighten you? Repulse you?
[KAZUMA] Will you run
to him... or from him?
[yelps]
[TOHRU retching, coughing]
[TOHRU] I've never smelled
anything so awful.
Like something rotten.
That was him. That was
Kyo's other form.
[TOHRU coughing]
[TOHRU]
I don't understand.
What's happening?
What's the right thing to do?
I feel so lost.
But... even so!
[KYO'S MOTHER]
What's the matter?
Did something happen again?
[KYO'S MOTHER] Kyo, did
Akito say something to you?
It's okay.
It'll all be okay...
[KYO]
Stop.
[KYO'S MOTHER]
...because I love you.
[KYO]
Stop it!
[screams]
[KYO]
I can't... take any more.
[TOHRU]
Kyo, I‐‐
[KYO]
Stay away!
What are you doing here?!
Why the hell are you following
me like nothing's changed?!
Kyo, please‐‐
[KYO]
I said stay away!
What is wrong with you?!
You've got eyes, don't you?!
A nose, too, right?!
We both know I'm disgusting
like this, so go!
Just leave me alone.
I don't need you or your pity!
[KYO]
Please.
Please, no more.
I know.
But... But I...
[KYO'S MOTHER]
I love you.
[growls]
[KYO]
Don't touch me!
Get lost.
[TOHRU coughing]
[KYO]
Idiot! Get out of my sight!
Next time I'll carve
up your face.
I mean it.
[KYO] If I'm going to lose her
anyway... I won't hold back.
I'll hurt her so badly that
she'll never forgive me.
So badly she'll never have
to worry about me again.
I'll wreck everything... so
she'll never want to look back.
I can't take it.
I'm sick of losing people.
Sick of pity.
Sick of being miserable.
Sick of having things
forced on me.
[KYO'S MOTHER] No, honey.
You're as human as anyone else.
You turn into that form
sometimes because of evil magic,
not because there's
anything wrong with you.
You're back to normal
soon after, right?
That proves it.
You're not a monster.
It's okay, I promise.
I'm not scared at all.
[KYO] Liar. You were
scared, weren't you?
[KYO] Isn't that why you checked
dozens of times every day
to make sure the
beads were still on?
[KYO'S MOTHER] I'm so proud
to have you as my son.
[KYO]
Yeah, right.
If you were so proud, why
didn't you let me go outside?
[KYO'S MOTHER]
You're so adorable
I have to keep you
all to myself.
[KYO]
You were ashamed of me.
[KYO'S MOTHER]
Sweetheart, I love you.
I would die for you.
You know that, right?
[KYO] Why did you always
say stuff like that?
How can you love somebody
when you never acknowledge
who they really are?
She loved you.
Your mother loved you more
than anything in the world.
Stop it! You're wrong!
Don't force that "love" on me!
I don't need it.
I don't.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
Let's go home. Please.
We have to go home.
Right now!
[TOHRU] If we don't,
I have a feeling Kyo
won't come back to
that house ever again.
[KYO]
Just go away.
[TOHRU]
No!
[KYO]
Don't you get it?
[TOHRU]
No, I don't!
[screams]
[TOHRU]
I'm scared.
Even though I know
that's your voice,
it doesn't sound like you.
You're in a form I've
never seen before...
...and it scares me.
But... scared or not...
I wanna understand.
If you need to talk,
I'll listen.
If you need to be selfish,
I'll let you.
I wanna help you the
way you've helped me.
If you're feeling hurt,
or scared, or weak,
I want you to tell me,
so I can face it with you.
Because...
Because I wanna
keep living together.
I wanna eat with you, study
with you, worry with you.
All of those things.
Please, I just want...
I just wanna stay
with you, Kyo!
[KYO]
The thing is,
if she didn't love all of me,
that would've been fine.
Or even if...
if she were scared...
...I'd get that.
Because being scared would've
meant she was looking
at the ugly part of me.
But she never did.
Mom used love to avoid
seeing the truth.
To avoid even thinking about it.
But... I wanted her
to understand.
I just wanted her to say
we'd face it together.
To say... she wanted to stay.
[KYO] Even back then,
I knew it was stupid.
A kid's dream that would
never come true.
Because who would ever say
something like that to me?
[KYO]
That's what I thought.
Until...
[KYO]
Tohru.
...you showed up.
[KYO] You showed up and
things began to change.
You started to melt
away the ugly feelings
and dark thoughts inside me.
Bit by bit, day by day...
[KYO] Why would somebody like
you... wanna stay by my side?
[KYO]
Why... would you cry for me?
How can I ask you to?
I know I shouldn't.
I don't have any right.
[KYO]
I know that it's a mistake...
...for you to be here with me.
[KYO] But still... I find myself
wanting to treasure you.
To stay with you forever.
I can't help but wish...
[TOHRU]
"Summer will be here soon."