[gasps]
Ahh. Thanks for the soup,
Tohru. It's divine!
I'm so glad you like it!
Just one more way
you've changed things.
We never ate breakfast when
it was just me and Yuki.
[TOHRU]
Hm? Hello, Kyo. Good morning!
Hey, come and eat.
[YUKI] Better hurry,
or it'll all be gone.
Um, don't you want breakfast?
Not hungry.
[TOHRU]
But‐‐
He can starve if he wants to.
[TOHRU]
I wonder what's wrong.
[slurps]
[UOTANI]
Huh.
[HANAJIMA]
There's only one.
That's a let‐down.
I figured that
the prince's locker
would be filled to bursting.
[YUKI]
With what?
[UOTANI]
Chocolates.
I was expecting a whole
avalanche of 'em
to come spilling out.
[RECIPIENT A]
Oh, yay!
[HANAJIMA]
I believe I know what happened.
What we have here
is a clear case
of the cuckoo phenomenon.
Just as a cuckoo chick will
take over a shrike's nest
and dump out its eggs,
each girl has tossed away the
previous girl's chocolates
in order to draw
attention to her own.
Allow me to present Exhibit A.
Ah! You're right! Wow!
Man, that's low, even
for those cuckoos.
And I will be the hawk
that swoops in to seize
the final sugary offering.
Shouldn't Yuki get at least
some of his chocolates, though?
[TOHRU]
It's February 13th.
Valentine's Day falls on
a Saturday this year,
so today will be a chocolate‐
giving frenzy at school.
[TOHRU gasps]
[TOHRU]
Kyo!
'Sup?
Hey.
[TOHRU gasps]
Please don't!
[KYO grunts]
[UOTANI]
First thing in the morning
and he's already
lookin' to fight.
I'm not so sure.
His waves are more innocent
than usual. It's odd.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
What? No.
He's conflicted about something.
Well, it's got nothing
to do with us.
Just as long as he doesn't
cause trouble for our Tohru.
Good enough for me.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[ADMIRERS grunting, chuckling]
[KINOSHITA]
We shall give them to Yuki!
[IWATA]
We shall!
[CHIE]
No one is more deserving!
[CLASSMATE A]
They will be his!
Girls are really terrifying
this time of year.
They look like a pack
of starving wolves
lying in wait for their prey.
[TOHRU] I feel bad for the
members of the zodiac.
Valentine's Day must be
really scary for them.
[ADMIRER C]
Kyon‐Kyon!
Here. I brought these for you.
Uh. Okay.
Wow. Yuki's not the only one.
"Kyon‐Kyon."
Go, Carrots!
That girl's in love.
So are you givin' them
chocolates, too?
Yes!
And I'd like to give some to
Shigure and the other Somas.
I was planning to give you
guys yours on Monday,
if that's okay.
I look forward to it.
Merci beaucoup!
Way to go, Kyon‐Kyon.
Yeah, man, I'm like,
super jealous!
[KYO]
Is today... Valentine's Day?
Uh. I mean, technically,
it's tomorrow.
[KYO]
I'm going home!
What?
No, I can't. It's not
safe there, either.
Right! I'll go on a trip!
Get out of town.
I'll see you suckers later!
Don't know where you
think you're going,
but your desk is over there.
[TOHRU]
Ms. Shiraki.
Just let me go, you old hag!
What's that?
Sounds like I've got a
student who's in need
of an attitude adjustment.
Maybe dying that orange hair
would help curb your
disobedient streak.
But the good news is,
I came prepared.
Unless you want a makeover,
I suggest you sit down.
[TOHRU]
It seems like something's
really bothering Kyo.
Something more serious
than being afraid of girls.
Maybe he has a bad
Valentine's Day memory.
Uh.
Umm... You look kind of
nervous. What's wrong?
[gasps]
It's Kagura!
My love, Kyo.
I'm here, darling!
[KYO]
Oh, crap! She found me!
[KYO, KAGURA yelling]
[KAGURA]
My love will not be denied!
Figured.
Ah, so this was all about
trying to avoid Kagura.
[KAGURA] Well, it's
Valentine's, after all.
An important day for
couples to spend together.
Not a couple.
Careful. You'll only
make things harder.
Screw this.
I should've fought my way
outta that damn classroom.
So, delivering chocolates?
[KAGURA] No. I actually
came to invite him out.
Tomorrow, okay?
Let's spend the day together.
I wanna give you your
chocolates then, too.
Go out?
[TOHRU] Wow! That sounds
like a real date!
Oh! When you say it like that,
it's kind of
embarrassing, Tohru.
I'm not going. There's no way.
That's where you're wrong.
I said no way, damn it!
Why should I have to go out
on some dumb Valentine's date?
And with you!
[KAGURA]
Kyo...
That was cruel.
Do you always have
to be so hateful?
Please just make it stop.
This is cute and all,
but perhaps you two could
take the flirting elsewhere?
[KYO]
Shut up!
Hold on! I have a great idea!
We'll bring Yuki
and Tohru with us
and make it a double date!
[TOHRU]
Huh?
Nice! I like it!
I know, right? It'll be perfect!
Hey. Wait just a second.
I'm not goin'
anywhere with Yuki!
Oh, wow!
I've never been on a real date,
let alone a double date!
Are you sure you wouldn't mind?
[KYO]
Fine, whatever.
[KAGURA]
I'll see you tomorrow.
Are you excited yet?
[KYO]
Not at all.
You know, Haru told
me something.
He said that you and Yuki are
starting to get along better.
He thinks that maybe if you
get to know each other,
you'll actually become friends.
I hope he's right.
That would make me happy.
Well, bye!
[SHIGURE] Haru's surprisingly
wise sometimes.
Come, now.
Would it kill you boys to
meet each other halfway?
And what do you know about it?
Stop talking like we're supposed
to be friends or something.
Get to know him?
Don't make me puke!
I hate his guts,
and I always will.
All of you should
just accept that!
[SHIGURE] You know,
it almost sounds like
you feel obligated to hate him.
[grunts]
[SHIGURE]
What's wrong?
Are you scared of
what might happen
if you actually got to know him?
Kyo, wait!
Please! Come back to the house!
[YUKI]
Something happen? What's wrong?
Me. I may have been a bit
impatient with Kyo.
Pushed him too far.
Kyo? Where are you?
C‐Can you hear me?
[TOHRU] Back there, he really
did look like he was scared.
Kyo. Are you‐‐?
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
His hatred.
He's using it to
protect something.
But what? Himself?
[KYO]
Forget it.
What happened back
there... forget it.
It has nothing to do with you.
Let it go.
It's okay if you don't
like him. Really.
I mean, I've been hoping you
two could learn to get along.
But... it's fine if you can't.
It's fine if you hate him.
It really is.
[TOHRU]
I can see it, plain as day.
You have a plum right
there on your back.
Soma's great, but the
thing is, so are you.
[KYO]
I don't wanna see.
I don't wanna think
about anything.
Not yet.
[TOHRU] Kyo's heart is
so much more delicate
than he wants people to know.
And so is Yuki's.
A single touch
might bruise them.
[TOHRU] So, I know we
have plans tomorrow,
but it's okay if
you'd rather not go.
I guess I can live with it.
It's just one day.
If you're sure.
[TOHRU grunts]
Ow. What did you do that for?
No reason, really.
Let's just get back.
[TOHRU] The pain they
hold inside, the fear...
Someday, I hope I can
help wipe it all away.
That's what they did for me.
And more than anything,
I want them to be happy, too.
[SHIGURE]
I dreamed about the one I love.
[SHIGURE] And that was that.
It was all over for me.
[phone beeps]
[MITSURU] Sensei, I'm
heading over there now,
so please drop everything
and get that manuscript
ready to go!
Cute. And the "please"
was a nice touch.
[YUKI]
Shigure?
I'm not sure how long we'll be.
Go! You kids enjoy yourselves.
What fun! Who doesn't
love a double date?
Oh, one more thing, Yuki.
What is it?
Don't be a cheapskate.
No splitting the bill, okay?
Wasn't planning on it.
And you be a proper
escort for sweet Kagura.
This is so stupid.
Um, sorry.
Are you sure you don't mind
going over to the main estate?
I can probably just deliver
the chocolates myself later.
Worry not. I wasn't
planning to eat them.
Oh, no, that's not
what I meant!
You just seem really
busy with work‐‐
[YUKI]
No, it's fine.
He'll do it. You just
stay away from the estate.
But, well...
[SHIGURE] Little does he know
she's already been there.
No. Yuki's right.
I'll handle it.
You just leave the chocolates
to me. Enjoy your date.
Okay!
[KYO]
Hey! If we're going, let's go!
[TOHRU]
Right. Coming!
Thanks a lot! We'll see
you when we get back!
[phone ringing]
[SHIGURE]
Sure.
[phone ringing]
Now, get out of here.
[ANSWERING MACHINE]
We're sorry.
No one is available
to take your call.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
[phone beeps]
[MITSURU]
Sensei!
Listen, I know you're screening
my calls, and that's fine,
but don't you dare run
off before I get there!
[static]
[SHIGURE]
Hmm. Interesting.
So that's what she
expects from me.
It would be such a shame
to disappoint her.
[KAGURA]
Kyo!
I was so excited
thinking about today!
I hardly got any sleep at all!
[KYO]
Oh, yeah?
Well, in that case, maybe you...
[YUKI]
Is something wrong, Miss Honda?
Well, it's just, no
matter what happens,
Shigure is always smiling.
So I have a difficult
time telling
whether or not I'm
causing trouble for him.
[YUKI] Not many people know
what's going on inside his head.
He's a mystery to most
everyone but Hatori.
You know, it's funny.
Somebody said, "He's like
a ripple on the water.
A wave that approaches,
then recedes.
It tickles your feet, but when
you reach down to touch it,
it leaves.
He's the kind of man you
can never quite catch."
I always thought that
analogy was too pretty.
If you ask me, he's the
jellyfish waiting to sting you.
[TOHRU chuckles]
[KAGURA]
Yun‐chan! Tohru!
We're going to miss the
beginning of the movie
if we don't hurry.
Oh! Right!
Valentine's!
He may be smiling
on the outside,
but who knows what
kind of things
he's plotting on the inside...
[SHIGURE]
Special delivery!
Valentine's chocolates
from yours truly.
Okay, you're right. I lied.
They're really from Tohru.
[HATORI]
Idiot.
She's a thoughtful girl.
[SHIGURE]
That's an understatement.
She sent some along for
Momiji and Haru, too.
She was going to bring them over
here herself, but I volunteered.
And do you want to know why?
Because she, Yuki, Kyo, and
Kagura are all going out
on a double date together!
That's certainly unexpected.
[SHIGURE]
Isn't it?
Must be Tohru's influence.
That young lady has worked
a Valentine's miracle.
They're probably snuggled up,
watching a movie as we speak.
[ART]
Mogeta, no!
The evil creature can't
get its hands on you!
Stop, Art. It's too
late to save him!
Wait, look! The Mogeta!
This is all wrong!
What's happening here‐‐?
[MOGETA]
Mogeta!
[ART]
[HEROINE A] Don't do it, Artemis
Donpanina Taios, aka "Art"!
[MOGETA]
Mogeta!
[HATORI] I can imagine
her influencing them.
She has the most uncanny way
of softening anyone she meets.
[SHIGURE]
I have a confession.
I maybe‐kinda‐sorta
picked on Kyo yesterday.
He got a bit agitated
and ran off.
Don't wind him up.
But then, Tohru went after
him and brought him back,
and he seemed almost normal.
She has some sort of
tranquilizing effect
on those two.
[HATORI]
You certainly look satisfied.
Things are going exactly
as you planned them.
Why do I detect a note
of criticism in your voice
when you say that?
[HATORI] Like hell you're not
using her, you shameless liar.
You and Akito both.
She's a pawn you two are using
in some kind of elaborate game.
Don't even think about
pretending otherwise.
Do you remember that
morning? The dream?
We all woke from it
crying. You, me, Aya...
For you two, it became something
twisted and painful.
But for me, those feelings
still linger, unfaded.
That affection... that passion,
so thrillingly sweet and sad.
[SHIGURE]
I don't want it to end.
I want it to last forever.
I want to give it form
and make it mine.
I will.
All these years, and that
vow is still right here.
If I have to lie, or manipulate
a few people along the way,
then so be it.
It's a small price to pay,
even if someone gets hurt.
[sighs]
[SHIGURE] I do feel bad
about it sometimes, though.
Mostly, it's when I'm
looking at Tohru.
She's just good,
through and through.
She helps for those two,
but her innocence may
be a bit much for me.
Sometimes she forces
me to realize
that mine might be the
filthiest soul of all.
Granted, I am as
dirty as they come.
It's funny, but sometimes I find
myself feeling jealous of you.
And I wonder if maybe I'm
the most cursed of us.
[door opens]
[MAIDSERVANT A]
Pardon me.
Doctor, it's time for
Akito's checkup.
Ooo, I know!
Why don't I fill in for you?
I promise I'll be very thorough.
[HATORI]
Saw that one coming.
[HATORI] Tell Honda I said
thank you for the chocolates
when you get home.
Sure, sure.
[HATORI] Whatever outcome
you're aiming for...
...you had better be
prepared to lose a tooth.
Yuki or Kyo. Maybe even Honda.
One of them is bound
to punch you in the face
before this all plays out.
Yes, well, that may be.
I don't care for pain,
but I'll take it.
[HATORI] You should know,
I won't be your ally in this.
But I won't work
against you, either.
Right, then. Goodbye.
[HATORI] Shigure.
Don't let Akito catch cold.
[SHIGURE chuckles]
[HATORI]
You're not the only one.
My hands are dirty, as well.
[SHIGURE]
They can have a few teeth.
Bones, if they want them.
[SHIGURE]
That's not what I care about.
Akito.
Shigure. Why are you here?
I came to visit. I've been
wanting to see you.
[AKITO]
Well, that isn't surprising.
[SHIGURE]
Of course it's not.
Since I care about
you most of all.
[SHIGURE]
I will get what I want.
No matter what lies I have
to tell, or who I have to use,
I'll make that dream eternal.
[TOHRU]
Ah. That was really touching!
[KAGURA]
With so many moving scenes!
Especially that one with
Mogeta and the true emperor!
That was my favorite one, too!
Glad you liked it.
So the date's over, right?
Now, now. I know you don't
really mean that, Kyo.
Such a shy boy.
[screams]
‐‐[KAGURA laughing]
‐‐Kyo, are you okay?
Um.
[TOHRU]
Excuse me.
Can we help you with something?
No. Nothing matters now.
It's over. I'm ready to end
my worthless existence!
[TOHRU]
What?
If you have to die,
could you maybe not do it
right in front of my house?
‐‐[TOHRU] What?!
‐‐[gasps]
[MITSURU]
Sensei!
[SHIGURE]
This is my editor, Mitsuru.
Why did you do it? You jerk!
I asked you not to run off,
and then you went
and did it anyway!
That wasn't running off.
I went out for a bit, is all.
How's that not the same thing?!
Mii‐chan, que será, será.
Whatever will be...
Would you like some tea?
Okay.
By the way, Hatori
sends his thanks.
[TOHRU]
Oh! I'm glad!
I was worried he'd
think it was weird.
So, do I get some?
I'm actually making
them right now.
I want them to be
perfect for you.
[MITSURU]
Why aren't you writing?!
There's no time!
Don't you understand?!
Fine, fine.
Sensei, will you please try
to take your work
more seriously?
Don't you care about it?
[SHIGURE]
My work?
Not that much, really.
Certainly not more than myself.
[MITSURU] Then think about
how much happier you'll be
when your manuscript is done
and I leave you alone!
[SHIGURE]
Okay, okay.
[MITSURU] Next time,
I'm definitely, definitely
not going to let you get away!
I'll follow you to the ends
of the earth if I have to!
Now that's a scary prospect.
[SHIGURE]
Go ahead. Catch me if you can.
[TOHRU]
"This is a wonderful inn."