[MOMIJI] I think every
memory is important.
Nothing's okay to forget.
[MOMIJI]
Nothing.
[TOHRU] Shigure, is there
anything you need me to do
around here on May 1st?
I'd like to go out for a few
hours in the afternoon.
Oh! Take all the time you want!
I'll be out on an errand
most of the day myself.
What's the story?
Hanging out with friends?
Yes. It's been a year
since my mom passed.
We're visiting her grave.
[SHIGURE]
Good girl.
The first anniversary, huh?
That's right.
But we're not doing anything
too special for it.
I'm sorry. I can't go.
Uh, no. Please don't worry!
[YUKI] Would it be
okay if I joined you?
You want to?
I'd like to pay my respects.
If you don't mind the company.
Thank you very much.
Mom will be so happy!
And Kyo? Surely you've got
nothing better to do.
You should tag along with them.
[UOTANI] Say what?
The prince is coming with us?
What about Kyon?
Well, I don't really know.
He didn't give
much of an answer.
Oh, man, just think.
Kyoko woulda've had so
much fun with that punk.
I'm talkin' some
hardcore tormenting.
[KYOKO]
Look at this hair, Carrots!
I'm gonna eat you right up.
[KYON]
Cut it out.
Then, right when
it seemed as though
he couldn't take
any more torture,
she'd pull him into a bear hug
strong enough to pop his back.
[TOHRU] That would be
terrible. In so many ways!
It's odd. This
doesn't feel real.
A whole year has
passed since that day?
I know what you mean.
It still feels like she'll
pop out of nowhere
looking just fine.
Apologizing to us because this
was all some twisted joke.
[UOTANI] Sorry. I'm being
a total downer, huh?
I guess it just goes to show
what a badass Kyoko was.
The legend of the "Crimson
Butterfly of Route Seven"
will never be forgotten.
[TOHRU giggles]
[MOMIJI]
Tohru!
[TOHRU gasps, yelps]
Please, you gotta hide me!
But from what?
Classmates. We're playing
cops and robbers.
And I'm the criminal!
There you are.
No use running now!
Tohru, you work today, right?
I'll see you then!
[STUDENT B]
Stop, you thief!
Hey, you guys! I found him!
Second floor, hurry!
Oh, no, not good.
Please slow down.
Watch where you're going.
That kid.
I wonder which one of his
parents is from Germany.
[TOHRU]
Now that I think about it,
I don't hear any of
the Somas say much
about their moms or dads.
Hardly anything at all.
I've never even laughed like
that in front of my parents.
Whoops! Sorry, Tohru!
‐‐[STUDENT B] Gaining on ya!
‐‐Momiji!
Please stop. This could
end up being a total mess!
Look at her.
She's worked so hard.
Even if she's worried right now,
she's still cheerful.
To get to this point,
she must've talked herself
out of countless dark moments.
But I think... if she died,
I wouldn't be able
to smile for a year.
Maybe much longer.
Or ever again.
I might even wish
I'd never met her
so that I wouldn't have
to feel her absence.
[HANAJIMA] She's put in so much
effort to get to this point.
Are you done after we
take these bags out?
[TOHRU]
Almost.
I've still gotta empty the
trash in the breakroom.
I can do that.
Oh, that's okay!
It's fine I'm having fun!
Here.
I really appreciate you
helping me out like this.
[MOMIJI] I told you
not to worry about it!
Is Yuki walking you
home again today?
Yup.
Kyo should be a good friend
and come and get you
every once in a while.
But he's stubborn.
[TOHRU]
By the way, Momiji?
[MOMIJI]
Was?
[TOHRU] I know one of your
parents came from Germany,
but was it your mom or your dad?
My mutti!
And, um, that means...
"Mutti" means "Mama."
Got it, so your mom is German.
[MOMIJI] I've got a picture
of her here. Ta‐dah!
Wow! She's so gorgeous!
[MOMIJI chuckles]
[TOHRU] I can definitely
see the resemblance
between the two of them.
She met Papa‐‐ Oh,
he's a Soma, of course.
Anyway, they met when
they were in college.
Then they got married.
I don't know how he managed to
attract such a beautiful person.
Oh, is that so?
[MOMIJI] And guess what!
I have a little sister, too!
Her name's Momo!
She looks just like Mama.
Huh? I can't believe I didn't
even know you have a sister.
[MOMIJI]
Ja!
She's just in second
grade, though.
Oh, and she's not one
of the zodiac spirits.
You wouldn't believe
how spoiled she is.
She follows Mama everywhere,
like some kinda baby duck.
And she's not very great...
[TOHRU]
He sounds so happy.
[MOMIJI] ...when she does, it's
a little clumsy and jumbled.
It's pretty much
the cutest thing!
Mama and Momo usually come here
to pick Papa up after work.
So they're probably around.
It's so great you all
get to go home together.
Ja, well, that
would be wunderbar,
but Mama doesn't know
anything about me.
[TOHRU]
Uh?
[MOMIJI'S MOTHER with accent]
Oh, Momiji.
That is you, isn't it?
What are you doing
here, of all places?
And so late in the evening?
[TOHRU]
Speak of the devil. It's her!
[MOMIJI chuckles]
My friend works here,
so I came to keep her company.
No one likes to
clean alone, right?
[MOMIJI'S MOTHER]
That's very kind, but remember,
this isn't a playground.
You're right. I'm so sorry.
[TOHRU] Then this must
be his sister Momo.
[TOHRU] Momiji looks more
like their mom than she does.
[MOMIJI'S MOTHER]
Think of your poor mutti.
She'll be so worried if
you're not home for dinner.
Oh, it's okay! I'm leaving now!
[MOMIJI'S MOTHER] Straight
home. Don't take any detours.
[MOMIJI]
I won't!
We should get going, too,
engel. Papa must be waiting.
Thanks for your hard work.
Yeah. Sure.
[MOMIJI'S MOTHER]
Come on, Momo.
[MOMIJI]
Ungluck!
What a pain.
Today is not my lucky day.
I'll have to apologize
to Papa later.
Momiji.
Ja . Like I said,
she doesn't know me.
She forgot. She had
her memories erased.
[gasps]
[MOMIJI] She obviously
knows what my name is,
but thinks I belong
to a different branch
of the Soma family.
Children possessed
by a zodiac spirit
are born two months
before full term.
And that's only the beginning
of their problems.
Just think: You meet someone
you love, get married,
and then you find out you're
going to have a child together.
You want everything
to be perfect.
But then, when you hold
your newborn in your arms,
it turns into a
strange, tiny animal.
Imagine how devastating
that must be for a mother.
To cradle your baby and have it
turn into something inhuman.
The mothers usually
react one of two ways.
They're either extremely
overprotective of their kids,
or they end up rejecting
them completely.
Mutti... fell into
the second category.
She rejected me, body and soul.
She wouldn't even look at me.
When she wasn't sleeping or
hiding, she was always on edge.
Sometimes screaming
hysterically.
Thinking about it now,
I think it emotionally
broke something in her.
Like Kana.
[MOMIJI'S FATHER]
Momiji.
Your mother might not
make it through this,
but the doctor thinks...
it is possible she'll get better
if she forgets all about you.
I know that would
be painful for you.
But I promise to love
you that much more
to make up for losing her.
If you love Mama like I do,
then this is the one way
you can save her life.
[HATORI]
Are you certain?
You're sure you want to
forget about your son?
It's a big decision.
You won't regret it?
You really want to sit there
und ask me such a question?
Then I'll tell you.
I regret that I ever gave birth
to that cursed creature.
[MOMIJI]
And that was it.
I was erased from
Mama's memories.
It wasn't long before she
started getting better.
After two months went by,
she was even smiling again.
[MOMIJI]
Mostly....
...I just hope that I really
was able to save Mama.
[TOHRU]
He's been watching over her
this whole time, hasn't he?
Secretly, from afar...
so she wouldn't see him.
[TOHRU] I bet that day when
I first met him downstairs,
he'd come here to catch
a glimpse of his mother.
[MOMIJI] Anyway, I'm never
going to be like her.
I've decided to live my life
keeping every one of my
memories close to my heart.
Even sad ones.
Or memories that only
ever seem to hurt me.
Of times I sometimes
wish I could forget.
I've promised myself I won't
let them go, no matter what.
[MOMIJI] Because if I can stand
up and face those memories,
if I can learn to accept them,
then I believe one day,
I can become a person
who isn't beaten down by things
that have hurt me in the past.
I want to believe
I'll be stronger.
I want to believe there
isn't a single memory
that it's okay to forget.
And that's why, in truth...
...I never wanted Mama
to forget anything.
I wanted her to
try to get better.
To not give up.
To try and love me.
Which... is just me
being selfish, I know.
So that's a secret.
That's me. I'm the same.
I wanna be like that.
[TOHRU] I wanna embrace all of
my memories, and keep believing,
just like Momiji.
[KYO]
Hey.
Just so you know,
I'm going to the gravesite.
[TOHRU]
That way I won't be defeated.
And someday,
I can find the beauty
hidden in the difficult
moments of my life.
[YUKI] Fortunately
the weather cleared up.
It's been so gray lately,
but this is nice.
I think maybe it's because
Mom is happy today.
After all, she's got
a few new people
coming to say "hi" to her.
[UOTANI]
Tohru!
[TOHRU] There you are!
Thanks for coming!
Yeah, of course.
Perfect weather to
visit a grave, huh?
[TOHRU]
It is!
Why the heck are you
two dressed like that?!
You got a problem with this?
Yes, my dress is
too plain, isn't it.
Are you crazy?!
[YUKI]
Um, excuse me, but...
...that's the kind of coat
biker gangs wear, right?
Huh. You know your stuff.
Yup. This belonged
to Tohru's mom
before she passed it on to me.
It's the esteemed coat
of the Crimson Butterfly.
Uh. Of course. What's that?
That was Mom's name when she
was still an active member.
[YUKI]
Member of what?
[UOTANI] The crew's all here,
so let's hit the road.
[YUKI]
These girls.
[KYO]
Could they be more ridiculous?
Oh, hey. Looks pretty clean.
[HANAJIMA]
Did someone already stop by?
It must've been my grandpa.
See? Look. He knows what
Mom's favorite food is.
[KYO]
Oh, yeah, that guy.
[TOHRU]
Uh‐huh.
What's his deal?
Was he your mom's dad?
No, he's my father's father.
Yeah, our Kyoko didn't
really talk to her parents.
And what about your dad?
Apparently, he caught a really
bad cold, and then he died.
I was pretty little
when it happened,
so I don't remember
much about him.
[YUKI] No wonder she was
so worried when I felt sick.
[TOHRU]
Hi, Mom. It's me and my friends.
[HANAJIMA]
Greetings.
There's not much to do.
The old man cleaned it up
pretty good earlier.
The flowers even look new, too.
[YUKI] Her father died,
and then her mother.
I don't understand.
How is it that she can still
smile and be cheerful?
Why isn't she radiating
despair instead?
I remember the day
when it happened.
A teacher came to get her.
She was obviously surprised.
And after they spoke a little,
she ran from the classroom.
Her two friends immediately
went after her,
and of course, the other
students all gossiped.
I remember wondering
for a second
if maybe one of her relatives
had gotten into an accident.
But I didn't give it
much thought.
At the time, I was
only vaguely aware
that someone named Tohru Honda
even existed in this world.
Yet, now, we live beside each
other in the same house.
And she's always close by.
[TOHRU]
Hey, Yuki!
Look at these flowers.
Aren't they wonderful?
[YUKI]
Somehow, against all odds,
I can't help but smile
when she does.
[TOHRU]
Oh. Not good.
I messed up the arrangement.
[UOTANI] Give 'em here.
Prince, you hold these.
[YUKI]
Okay.
[KYO]
I was wondering...
[HANAJIMA]
Hm?
[KYO] Can you, uh, see
ghosts and stuff like that?
Like, are there any here now?
I'd need spiritual power,
and I don't possess that.
[KYO] What? But that
weird wave stuff‐‐
[HANAJIMA]
Waves and spiritual power
are completely different.
You mustn't confuse them.
When I say I sense waves,
I basically mean human thoughts.
Think of them as words that
pass from brain to brain.
‐‐With no sounds required.
‐‐I already regret asking.
[HANAJIMA] Tell me,
why the sudden interest?
[KYO] No real reason.
I was just wondering.
[HANAJIMA]
Think of it this way.
Living humans are
stronger than the dead.
The waves of those who've left
us are most likely very weak,
so they end up being drowned out
by the powerful waves of those
who still feel the light
of the sun on their face.
The dead can't be heard.
It's interesting.
Right now, it feels as though
your waves are screaming at me.
Why is it that this graveyard
fills you with such chaos?
[gasps]
And guilt.
[TOHRU]
Hey, you two. What's up?
I hope I'm not interrupting.
No, you're good.
[HANAJIMA]
Indeed.
In that case,
please come with me!
We're all set up now.
[KYO gasps]
You shouldn't have a picnic
in a damn cemetery!
[UOTANI]
Huh? Get a grip, loser.
The rowdier we are,
the happier Kyoko is.
And what are we gonna do
if the priest sees us?
We'll just apologize, chill out.
[YUKI]
Still, this feels quite strange.
[UOTANI]
Will you sit down already?
I can't relax with you
hovering over me.
Ugh, fine. Here, you happy?
Hungry? What can I get
for you to eat first?
Whatever.
'Kay!
From what I can tell,
it sounds like you were both
close with Miss Honda's mother.
Yeah, she was real good to us.
Plus, such a big deal
that I looked up to her
before ever meeting
her in person.
[YUKI]
A big deal?
[UOTANI]
Do you not listen?
She was the legendary
Crimson Butterfly!
They say whenever she
rode her motorcycle,
the red tail lights looked like
wings fluttering in the wind.
[UOTANI]
I've been noticing.
Lately, those guys seem like
they're better and better
the more I see
'em all together
The prince certainly seems more
chill talking to mere mortals.
And no matter what Kyon says,
he definitely cares about Tohru.
Maybe one day he'll actually
find some courage
and confess his love to her.
That won't do.
I won't allow someone
to get into a relationship
with Tohru so easily.
What are you?
An overbearing dad?
[HANAJIMA] Something like that.
Besides, I'm half joking.
[UOTANI]
That means you're half serious.
As always, those Soma boys
exude such harsh waves.
Confusion. Chaos.
I couldn't tell you why,
but their minds seem to be ruled
by dark, troubled thoughts.
It's almost palpable.
[HANAJIMA] All humans have
such thoughts, of course.
Those two are plagued by them
to an excessive degree.
As long as that
remains the case,
they probably don't have
the capacity for romance.
And if I were to be completely
honest, they're quite dense,
especially when the
matter of love is at hand.
That goes for our Tohru, too.
But who knows?
Sometimes feelings sprout
for no real reason,
blooming before you
can even realize it.
Oh, dear.
For some reason, thinking
about Tohru getting married
brings tears to my eyes.
I can't help it.
[UOTANI] Don't go getting
ahead of yourself.
[TOHRU sighs]
I don't know that there's
anything more refreshing
than a cup of tea
after a long day.
I had such a fun time
visiting the grave earlier.
And I'm so glad I finally
got to introduce Yuki
and Kyo to my mother.
[TOHRU] You see, Mom, those
two are always helping me out,
even when they don't know it.
I hope you get the chance to
meet Shigure sometime, too.
I want you to know:
Every day I spend with
the people in this house
is a good day.
I enjoy it more and more.
So you can watch over me
without worrying. I promise.
I'm just fine. Okay, Mom?
Did you seriously make tea
and then fall asleep out here?
Hey, you're gonna
catch a cold.
Come on, get up.
[giggles]
[KYO]
Like waking a child.
Hey.
[YUKI] The breeze must've
knocked these down.
[YUKI]
A hat?
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
[HATORI]
"I wouldn't say that."