[footsteps]
[TV HOST B]
Next, tell us about a strange
snacking habit you have.
Starting from the left.
[TV HOST C]
Let me think. Um.
Okay, well, I don't know
how strange it is,
but I like to wrap
rice crackers in ham.
[TV HOST B]
Rice crackers and ham?
That'll add a few inches
to the waistline.
[TV HOST C]
Are you calling me fat?
[TV HOST B]
Who? Me? Never.
[TV HOST D]
Hey, now. He's not fat.
He's just a growing boy‐‐
[UOTANI sighs]
[UOTANI] Okay, now that's
what I'm talkin' about.
Can't have summer without
a nice, cold pool.
[UOTANI sighs]
I am not movin' from this spot.
Why's a delinquent
polluting the school's pool?
Don't her kind usually ditch?
I don't understand why
we should have to share
a pool with a weirdo who dresses
like some bad girl
from 20 years ago.
[KINOSHITA gasps]
[BOTH scream]
[KINOSHITA]
Actually, I take it back.
Wave Girl is the
real weirdo here.
[CHIE]
Dunno, not sure if "weird"
is the right word, exactly.
[KINOSHITA, CHIE]
More like terrifying!
[STUDENT A]
Look at them go!
[STUDENT B]
Those two are really fast.
Find it yet? Your hair‐tie?
No luck. I fear it's
drifted away somewhere.
It's unfortunate.
The pool experience will be
much less enjoyable now.
[laughs]
Y'know, most people would
just call it "swimming."
[TOHRU]
Hana‐chan!
Look what I found!
An extra hair‐tie!
Oh. I didn't realize you
had gone to look for one.
That was very sweet of you.
[TOHRU]
It was no problem.
[gasps]
[UOTANI wailing]
Oh, no, Uo‐chan!
What's the matter?
[TOHRU humming]
[HANAJIMA] I don't understand
what the problem is.
You should be used
to it by this point.
I mean, we see Tohru in her
school swimsuit every year.
Come on, can you
really blame me?
We were stuck with those ugly
things in middle school,
but we get to wear whatever now.
Maybe, but I think
it's adorable.
Hey, I'm not sayin'
that it doesn't look cute,
or it's embarrassing,
or anything like that.
Just... I dunno.
Seeing her in that kinda gives
me the same feeling I get
when old people come into the
convenience store to buy food.
You know what I'm talkin' about?
I mean, it's probably no big
deal to grandma and grandpa,
but I can't freakin'
stand the sight of it.
It's just too damn sad.
And I can't help it.
I start bawling, burst into
tears, right then and there.
[GRANDPA gasps]
[UOTANI]
That's right.
I actually cry while I'm
ringing the geezers up.
[UOTANI crying]
To be fair, it doesn't really
take much to make you cry.
[TOHRU]
Swimsuits are expensive,
so I thought it would
be wasteful to buy one
when this one still fits.
But maybe I should go ahead
and do it this year.
I don't want Uo‐chan to cry
anymore because of me.
Hey, I know!
I have the most
brilliant idea ever!
All right, kids,
we're goin' shoppin'
for Tohru's new swimsuit.
It'll be a present
from all of us,
so everyone's chippin' in.
No arguments.
Huh? You can't go around
making decisions like that!
And anyway, why's it
gotta be a swimsuit?
[UOTANI]
Oh, quit blushing.
Have the rest of you done any
housework since Tohru moved in?
You might wanna try showin' her
a little gratitude
every once in a while.
[SHIGURE]
Swimsuit?
[UOTANI]
Hm?
Indeed. I wholeheartedly
approve.
Summer... here we come!
There, see.
The scribbler understands.
No, he's just a pervert!
Well, sure, buying a
present sounds fine.
But, uh, why a swimsuit
specifically?
Oh, right. I suppose
you three wouldn't know.
The sad fact is,
Tohru's still wearing her
middle school swimsuit.
[KYO]
What is your problem?!
[YUKI]
Disgusting, Shigure.
[TOHRU] I'm ready!
Sorry to keep you wait‐‐
[SHIGURE]
Tohru! You have to, okay?
Please get one.
For all our sakes!
[TOHRU]
One what?
Say yes!
I'll get down on my knees
and beg if I have to!
This can't go on!
It seems that he has a
weakness for Tohru, as well.
[UOTANI]
Mh‐hm.
[UOTANI sighs]
[UOTANI] Deciding on one's gonna
be harder than I thought.
There're a lot to
choose from, huh?
Perhaps a one‐piece
would suit you?
Hey, morons!
What's cuter: Bikinis
or one‐pieces?
[BOTH]
Don't ask us!
[UOTANI]
What are you doing?
Get your butts off
that bench and help.
[KYO]
We're guys.
This isn't the kinda thing
we're supposed to help with.
Oh, yeah? Then why
did you come along?
'Cause someone didn't
give us much of a choice.
[UOTANI]
Come on, Carrots.
I don't get what you're
so embarrassed about.
It's not like I'm asking
you to pick out
panties for her
or something, jeez!
What is wrong with you?!
Keep your voice down!
Ugh! Fine, fine. A color, then.
You can at least pick a color
that looks good
on her, can't ya?
‐‐Blue does.
‐‐Orange.
[BOTH grunt]
Seriously?
What about her makes you think
she'd look good in a
boring color like that?
Give me a break. Anything
would be better than orange.
That's a garish color for
idiots and their idiotic hair.
[KYO]
You're the idiot!
A brighter color obviously
fits her better.
[YUKI] It's too bright
for Miss Honda.
You obviously have
no sense of style.
Not like you have
any either, jerk!
[UOTANI] These two
are like an open book.
How do they not realize?
Are they stupid?
[HANAJIMA]
Pink.
[BOTH gasp]
The answer is pink. P‐i‐n‐k.
She looks good in any color,
but that one is the best.
It fits her.
I'm sure you'd have reached
that conclusion eventually.
Yeah, she's right.
Pink's totally Tohru's color.
Why'd you even
bother to ask us?!
Why not? It was fun.
Besides, there's no harm
in getting a second opinion.
But Kyoko did think that
pink fit Tohru best.
She'd say that she was red,
because she was
the Crimson Butterfly,
and that Tohru's dad, a
straightforward man, was white.
Mix those, and you
get pink for Tohru.
A pink swimsuit's perfect.
Aw, man. She's gonna
look so cute.
You both really love
Miss Honda. It shows.
Helping her seems
to make you happy.
[UOTANI]
Well, yeah.
Like I told you before,
the girl kinda saved me.
Wasn't exactly easy adjusting to
life as a respectable citizen.
Woulda been impossible
without her.
Right. Like you're respectable.
[UOTANI] What d'you mean?
Of course I am.
[ITO]
Isn't that Uotani?
What're you gonna
do about it, Ishi?
[ISHIHARA] Lookin' awfully cozy
in her new social circle.
[TAKEMURA]
Wanna rough her up?
[ITO] She's got some
guys with her, though.
[TAKEMURA]
Idiot.
You think I'm scared of
a couple jerks like that?
They'll just run away
like all the other
useless guys these days.
[ITO]
Got that right.
[ISHIHARA]
But... they are seriously yummy.
[TAKEMURA] Yeah. Not gonna
argue with that one.
[TOHRU]
Uh...
You guys bought this
for me? Like, a gift?
I don't understand.
It's our way of
saying "thank you."
[TOHRU]
But I‐I didn't even do anything.
Come on, just take it already.
Really. We want you to have it.
Please accept, okay?
[gasps]
[TOHRU] This means so
much. Thank you guys.
I will treasure it.
Forever and ever.
Oh, Tohru!
Our Tohru.
[YUKI, KYO]
Uh.
[CLERK A]
Here's your table.
[YUKI] Which swimsuit
did you end up getting?
[UOTANI] You'll find out
when she wears it.
I mean, you'll probably
go to the beach, right?
[YUKI]
Mh‐hm. I hope so, anyway.
We ladies should take a trip
of our own sometime, too.
We should!
I would enjoy that.
You're so close. Like you've
been friends a long time.
Did you meet in
elementary school?
Oh, no. Middle school, actually.
Hanajima, you started at
our school back in what,
eighth grade?
Yes. I had to transfer in.
I caused some minor problems
at my previous school.
[BOTH]
Yeah?
You were still part of the gang
back when we first
met, weren't you?
Sure was. I started running
with them in fifth grade.
[TOHRU] You always went
around with a mask on.
[UOTANI] Don't forget the long
skirts and super‐thin eyebrows.
[HANAJIMA] No mask now, but
the last two are still true.
[UOTANI]
Oh, yeah. Guess you're right.
[UOTANI laughs]
[BOTH]
Should she really be laughing?
Well, I had a real chip
on my shoulder back then,
and it showed.
So on edge.
Like a lion that's gone
too long without a meal.
My teachers didn't know
what to do with me.
Neither did my dad.
Seems like it should be harder,
but going bad's pretty easy.
Before I knew it,
I'd joined a female gang‐‐
running around with
a buncha tough chicks
causing all kinds of trouble.
I hurt people and
got hurt myself.
Did a lotta bad stuff.
You don't even wanna
know the half of it.
Basically, I was a moron.
An idiot of epic proportions.
But still, even an idiot...
can find somebody to look up to.
She pushed aside men
and became a gang leader,
despite being a woman.
Her street name was
the Crimson Butterfly.
Also known as Kyoko.
Tohru's mom.
[TAKEMURA]
Hey, Ishi.
We gonna do something
or just stand here?
Hold on. I wanna picture
of those hotties first.
[TAKEMURA, ITO giggling]
Um. Excuse me.
[CLERK A]
Enjoy your meal!
[UOTANI]
Heck yeah. This looks great.
I'm pretty sure you mentioned
this before, briefly,
but, um, your mom was
some kind of biker?
Yes, that's right!
Before she had me,
Mom was the big‐shot leader
of a motorcycle
gang around here!
Oh, wow. Really?
It's hard to picture that,
knowing her daughter.
Kyoko was special.
Not some wannabe, back‐alley
thug playing gangster.
They say whenever
she rode her bike,
the red taillight
weaving back and forth
looked like a
fluttering butterfly.
She was a good fighter.
And respected the
codes of the street.
Every time I heard an older
member talk about her,
I liked her even more.
That happens to
everybody, right?
You find someone you
view as your hero
and put them on an
untouchable pedestal.
You really love the
Butterfly, huh, Uotani?
[UOTANI chuckles]
[DELINQUENT A] I'm surprised
you haven't run into her.
I'm pretty sure she lives
in a neighborhood
not too far away from here.
[gasps] For real?
[DELINQUENT A]
Yeah.
Way I hear it, she got married
and changed her last
name to "Honda."
I think she's even got a
daughter about your age, too.
Who knows?
Maybe you go to school
with the Butterfly's kid.
Crazy. A daughter?
[STUDENT C]
Watch out. It's Uotani.
[UOTANI]
I have a feeling I know exactly
what Kyoko's daughter
must be like.
A total delinquent badass.
Shouldn't I have noticed
another girl like that, though?
Whatever. I gotta
find this girl.
Then maybe I'll get to meet
the Crimson Butterfly herself.
[UOTANI]
Huh?
[squeaks]
‐‐I'm so sorry!
‐‐ Watch where you're going,
you big idiot.
Yes! I promise I
will from now on!
I will be more careful‐‐
Ah! Oh, no, this is such a
disaster! I am such a klutz.
[UOTANI]
What's with this chick?
[TOHRU] Excuse me! Please don't
step on those notebooks.
Um, did you hear me?
I need these.
...the last musical guest
was the best part.
[TOHRU]
I'm sorry, but if you could just
watch where you're stepping...
She said don't step
on them, numbnuts!
[growls] Get it together.
Stop spacing out and
pick these up already.
Okay!
Screw this school.
Class is bad enough without
havin' to do this crap.
You. What's your name, huh?
[TOHRU]
What? Oh, right.
I'm Tohru Honda.
[UOTANI]
D'you say Honda?
Next thing I know
you're gonna claim to be
the Crimson Butterfly's
daughter.
Yes! I am.
That was my mom's title back
when she was still active.
[UOTANI]
You gotta be kidding.
[TOHRU]
I'm sorry, what?
[UOTANI]
Seriously?
You should definitely come
meet her. She'd love that.
[UOTANI]
Could this girl...
...actually be the
Kyoko's daughter?
Of course I didn't
realize who she was.
She's about as
plain as they get.
And it's not only that...
[TOHRU]
By the way,
feel free to say no, but
could I call you "Uotani"?
[UOTANI]
Uh. Yeah, fine.
[TOHRU]
I'm glad we met, Uotani.
[UOTANI]
She seems... a little...
How do I put it?
Strange.
[KYOKO] Surprise!
How was school today, Tohru?
‐‐[TOHRU] Um.
‐‐[UOTANI] Huh?
‐‐[TOHRU] You're kinda heavy.
‐‐What the heck?
[KYOKO] How lucky am I that I
caught you on your way home?
Hey, listen what
happened to me today.
You won't believe it.
Actually, before that?
There's a classmate of mine here
who really wants to meet you.
[UOTANI]
No way.
Could this person...
really be her?
Oh, is that so?
Who do we have here?
This is Uotani.
[UOTANI] Turns out the
delinquent I admired...
...had changed into
a doting parent.
It was like a punch to the gut.
In that moment,
my hardcore admiration
for her disintegrated.
It's hard to explain just
how disappointed I was.
Which was totally unfair.
I'd created this perfect
image of Kyoko in my head,
what I thought she'd be like,
and then I had the nerve to be
mad because it wasn't real.
I wanted her to be the
person I'd imagined,
not some nice mom.
Pretty selfish.
'Course, Kyoko smiled and
took things in stride.
She forgave me for being selfish
and didn't hold it against me.
Even though I wasn't done yet.
I'm sorry. It's such a mess.
I didn't expect company.
Please, make yourself at home.
[UOTANI] The Crimson
Butterfly is doing laundry?
[KYOKO] Say, why don't you stick
around for dinner, Uo‐chan?
What'd you call me?
[KYOKO] Uo‐chan.
That's your new nickname.
[grunts]
[TOHRU gasps]
Yes, please stay and
eat with us, Uo‐chan!
[UOTANI]
It's already a thing?
I, uh, nah. I'm goin' home.
Oh, come on. You must be hungry.
And nobody cooks
like my Tohru does.
I'm just okay.
[KYOKO] By the way,
what's on the menu tonight?
[TOHRU]
I'm happy you asked!
We're having meat
stewed with potatoes.
[UOTANI]
Great. But I really gotta go.
Oh, wow. I get it.
Your parents are strict.
Don't be stupid.
You can tell they're not
just by looking at me.
Well, that's not
necessarily true.
Everyone's lives are unique.
I couldn't be more
disappointed in you!
The Crimson Butterfly I idolized
has turned into a domestic,
overly‐friendly mom
who can't stop loving
on her dumb daughter.
I can't believe what a pathetic
person you've turned into.
[UOTANI gasps]
[KYOKO]
I just relaxed a bit.
And it feels nice.
[KYOKO]
Huh?
[TOHRU]
Uo‐chan!
Uo‐chan! Wait!
You forgot your mask.
Don't call me that name like
we're friends or something.
[gasps]
[UOTANI] I don't want
anything to do with you.
Run back home and let
your mommy spoil you.
So stupid!
Your life makes me
wanna puke everywhere.
It's her.
[UOTANI]
What the hell?
Why do I feel like
I'm missing out?
Even though they're the ones
who got on my nerves.
I dunno why I'm so pissed.
[UOTANI] Maybe 'cause I didn't
fit into the vibe of that place.
Something there
made me feel so...
...uncomfortable.
[AKIMOTO]
Uotani.
[UOTANI]
Yeah, Akimoto‐senpai.
Tell me, did you meet
the Butterfly's daughter?
[UOTANI chuckles]
I'm over that idea.
I mean, it's such a pain
to go to school anyway.
[DELINQUENT A] Yeah, I hear
you. Totally not worth it.
[DELINQUENT B]
Ya got that right.
[DELINQUENTS laughing]
[UOTANI]
This is the vibe I fit into.
[DELINQUENT A] Who do you
think you are, bitch?!
You wanna die? Huh?
[DELINQUENT B] I'll give you
scars you'll never get rid of!
[UOTANI]
This is where I belong.
[DELINQUENTS laughing]
[DELINQUENT C] Man, my mom
called the freakin' cops on me.
I swear I'm gonna
kill her one day.
My old man told me
to never come back.
[DELINQUENT B]
But he says that every day.
[DELINQUENT C]
Thing is, they're the...
[UOTANI] I need a place where
I can fall as far as I want.
[UOTANI]
Nothing going on today.
Guess I could go home for once.
Your dad's the only
one there, right?
It'd be cool to smother
him in his sleep.
[DELINQUENT C]
At least swipe his cash!
[DELINQUENTS laughing]
[UOTANI]
My mom left us for some new guy.
I was in the first grade.
I've been living with
my dad since then.
[TV HOST B]
Next, tell us about a strange
snacking habit you have.
Starting from the left.
[TV HOST C]
Let me think.
Okay, well, I don't know
how strange it is, but...
...I like to wrap rice
crackers in ham.
[UOTANI]
All he ever does is drink.
[AUDIENCE laughing]
[UOTANI]
I'm used to it, though.
[TV HOST D]
...a growing boy. That's all.
[TV HOST B]
What? He's older than I am!
[TV HOST] Wait till you hear
about his cheese habit.
[UOTANI] You can get
used to a lot of things.
Whether you want to or not.
[KYOKO]
I just relaxed a bit.
And it feels nice.
[TV HOST B]
What's next?
[TV HOST A]
Just wait.
This is going to take you
to another world entirely.
[TV HOST B] Perfect. Well,
it was nice knowing you.
[gasps]
[growling]
Watch it, mister.
Wait, is that all you got?
Was it weird sounding?
Not weird, but it's kinda
missing something.
[TAKEMURA] Yeah, maybe start
with adding more words.
[ITO]
Here, lemme try.
What the hell are you
lookin' at, fool?!
You wanna throw it
down right now?!
Come on, punk, I'll [beep] your
[beep] with [beep] till you cry!
Then I'll take a [beep] and
[beep] in your [beep]...
[ISHIHARA] Whoa, whoa, calm
down! Hang on a second!
Don't you think that's
going a little far?!
It's not proper for girls
to say such filthy things.
Baby. Don't get your panties
in a wad, loser.
What did just you call me?!
Say that to my face,
why don'tcha?!
[TAKEMURA]
Yeah. That's it!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TAKEMURA]
That's the attitude we need.
[BOTH]
Oh.
You wanna piece
'a me, ya idiot?!
[ITO, TAKEMURA]
Ohh.
[ISHIHARA]
Sweet.
Let's go scare some rando
so bad they pee themselves.
[ISHIHARA laughs]
Look, someone's coming.
Ready. Set.
[ALL]
You wanna piece 'a me?!
A foreigner!
[TAKEMURA]
What are we supposed to do now?
Don't be wimps!
We follow through with this.
Let's fight, kid!
[TAKEMURA]
Yeah, you heard her, punk!
Nice one!
[MOMIJI speaking German]
[GIRLS gasp]
[ISHIHARA]
We'll be back!
[GIRLS scream]
[MOMIJI]
Hm?
Huh.
[TOHRU]
"This is for Uo‐chan!"