[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT A] This is the place
I was talking about.
[STUDENT B]
Those look so good!
[TOHRU]
Thanks for stopping by!
[STUDENT G] Man! These
are selling like crazy!
[STUDENT C]
Rice balls were a great idea!
[YUSUKE]
Perfect festival food.
They're only selling so well
because Honda made them so well.
Uh! No, no!
It wasn't a big deal.
[VICE PRESIDENT A]
And the cat ones are adorable!
[KYO]
This feels wrong.
Somehow, I don't think rice
balls are the real reason
we're doing so much
business today.
Stop this! No pictures
permitted without permission!
Yuki clearly doesn't like it.
[TOHRU]
Look at him.
The senpais relentlessly pleaded
for Soma to dress as a girl
for the duration
of the festival,
and he folded in the
face of their demands.
Everybody's been stopping
by throughout the day
to get a look at him.
Boys, girls, even
some teachers, too.
It's really helped to
boost our rice ball sales.
[TOHRU gasps]
He won't look at me.
I hope I didn't make
him angry somehow.
[KYO]
Nah, just ignore 'im.
He gets really insecure
about his face sometimes,
'cause it's so pretty.
No! What should I do?
I didn't realize
he was so miserable.
This whole time,
I've just been thinking
how cute he looks
dressed like that!
Hey, don't sweat it.
I guarantee you're
not the only one.
[KYO]
Seriously.
In that dress, you'd never
know he was a dude.
[KYO chuckles]
[BOY]
Du lieber himmel!
You look like
ein schones Madchen!
Who's that?
[TOHRU]
It's that boy!
What's he doing at the festival?
Wait, you mean you
know who that is, Kyo?
[HATORI]
Momiji.
Don't go wandering off
on your own like that.
Sorry, Harry!
So, you're looking well
today, Yuki. Kyo, too.
‐‐So cute!
‐‐Are the three of you friends?
So cool!
Hey! Guten tag.
I'm Momiji Soma.
Half German, half Japanese.
And this is Hatori Soma.
We're related to your
classmates Yuki and Kyo!
They're in your family?
Uh‐huh.
[TOHRU] I'm so lucky to
meet more of the Somas.
I wonder if these two are
members of the zodiac as well.
Now that we're all acquainted,
perhaps you'd like to tell
me when you became a girl.
Based on the number of
times you've seen me naked,
you know full well
I'm definitely not.
[ALL gasp]
Yuki, does that mean‐‐?
No way.
Now, give me a deep breath.
He's a doctor.
But you don't need to
give me an exam here.
[HATORI] That would be true
if you ever came by
for a check‐up once a
month like you promised.
Every month? Don't tell me that
you're sick or something.
Yuki has some bronchial issues.
He frequently had trouble
breathing when he was young.
Are you Tohru Honda?
That's me! Pleased to meet you.
I see. You really
are a normal girl.
Hey.
[VICE PRESIDENT A screams]
[VICE PRESIDENT A] You shouldn't
climb on that sign,
‐‐it's not safe!
‐‐Why not?
Idiot, what do you
think you're doing?
What if he falls off?
I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
Why are you here?
If you're not thrilled that
we showed up at your school,
you can take it up with Momiji.
He brought home a flyer
and Akito got interested.
Akito has a fairly high fever,
though, so I nixed the idea.
Of course, that just
meant that I ended up
having to come instead.
Relax. I'm not here to do
anything to your new friend.
But let me give you
a piece of advice.
That threatening look
doesn't work so well
when you're in a dress.
I don't need your opinion.
[KYO]
You're such a little pain.
'S it me, or has Tohru been
acting real funny lately?
Maybe it's just because she's
been getting so friendly
with the prince and Carrots.
Yes. And her waves
have changed.
I'm concerned.
[TOHRU sighs]
‐‐[thud]
‐‐[MOMIJI] Owie!
Now sit here and
don't move a muscle!
Kyo hit me!
[MOMIJI cries]
Don't do that!
Oh! Hi, Tohru! How are you?
I came to see you.
Uh. Good afternoon.
So, you're in the
Soma family, too, then.
Ja!
It must've been fate that
brought us together that day.
Wait, do you two
know each other?
We met at Papa's building!
Huh?
Oh, yeah. I like
to hang out there.
Papa's the CEO.
What?! He runs the company?
Hey, you know our secret about
the zodiac spirits, don't you?
[TOHRU]
Uh. Yes.
Hooray! That means it's okay
if I hug you! Here I come!
[KYO] Hold it, Romeo.
We're still in public.
You can't stop me just
because you like her.
I bet you hug Tohru every day!
[gasps]
I do not!
I gotcha!
Did something just explode?
What happened back there?
Tohru?
[KYO, TOHRU gasping]
[VICE PRESIDENT A] Huh?
Where'd that bunny come from?
[STUDENT D] Hey. The little
kid's clothes are on the floor.
[STUDENT E] What? Where would
he go without his clothes?
That's weird.
"Weird"? Well, if that's
the case... I'm weird.
Dressing as a girl,
even though I'm a boy.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YUKI]
Thanks.
[TOHRU]
Thank you so much, Soma.
That acting was a brilliant
diversionary tactic,
and a great sacrifice.
[KYO] You damn brat! Do you even
understand what you've done?
[MOMIJI]
He's scary, Tohru.
So much for guessing
what zodiac you are.
Disastrous.
It's a good thing Yuki thought
fast and distracted everyone.
Hah. He can complain
all he wants,
but I think he likes his
girly features and the‐‐ Ah!
[YUKI] Should we see if I can
make you go even higher?
[KYO]
You damn rodent!
[HATORI]
Ah.
I almost forgot there's
something important
I have to do.
You two, line up
here in front of me.
[YUKI]
Why?
Do as you're told.
What is this about?
I want you to say the first
thing that comes to mind.
[HATORI]
Macaroni and...
‐‐[YUKI] Cheese.
‐‐[KYO] Cheese?
Akito told me to bring back
a nice photo of you boys.
See you.
[MOMIJI]
Tschuss!
Hatori! You get back
here right now!
[YUKI]
This is the worst.
What will Akito say
about my dress?
I've gotta get
out of this thing.
Uh! What?! Here on the roof?
[YUKI] I'm sure I'll feel
better once it's off.
[TOHRU] Sure, but just think,
everyone liked it so much!
[YUKI] Boys don't like being
called "cute," you know.
I'm sorry.
The truth is, I thought you
looked really cute as well.
I didn't want you to see
me looking like that.
So pathetic.
[TOHRU]
Um. Thing is...
Whenever my mother
called me cute,
the word always fill me
with this incredible
sense of happiness.
Because I knew that
what she really meant
was that she loved me.
It was a form of love
between us.
[TOHRU]
Oh, Mom.
I'll never get to hear
her say that again.
Anyway, I think that's
what our classmates meant,
just that they like you.
And they, um... Hold on.
Am‐Am I making this worse
for you by talking so much?
[YUKI]
No.
Actually, what you've shared
makes me feel kinda better.
I guess I could give my senpais
a little more fanservice.
[chuckles]
[YUKI] But first,
can you help me with this?
There's a button
stuck in my hair.
Yeah. Sure.
This design doesn't exactly
look like it's easy
to get off and on.
If you wore it,
I bet you'd look great.
I don't think I could pull
it off. But I wish I could.
Just like a princess.
[YUKI]
You'd look cute.
It's the truth. You'd be
much cuter than me.
I swear.
Thanks for the help.
We should get back inside.
[TOHRU gasps]
I'm so shocked, and touched,
and confused, and...
I think my heart's gonna
beat right out of my chest!
Honestly, more than being
cute or beautiful
or anything like that...
Soma is so cool.
And he doesn't even try.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Thanks to everyone...
[YUKI]
Oh. By the way, Miss Honda.
[TOHRU]
Yes?
About Hatori.
If you ever see him again,
it'd be best to avoid
being alone with him.
Um, why do you say that?
Because...
He's the one who suppressed
everyone's memories
when I got found out.
So I guess... I just want you
to be careful around him.
That's all.
[UOTANI]
Yo, Tohru.
Uh. Oh, hey. Hi, you guys.
Well, I'll head back
to the classroom.
[TOHRU]
So, um, what's up?
Spill it.
Is there something
about the prince
that you're hiding
from the two of us?
[gasps]
[HANAJIMA]
Is it possible
that you and Yuki Soma
could be an item?
No! It's not like that! I just
live with him, that's all!
Nothing weird's going on.
[squeaks]
We'll need you to explain.
[TOHRU] I'm sorry I didn't
tell you what was going on.
But I'm fine now, honest.
They're great people,
so there's no need
to worry about me.
[HANAJIMA]
I don't know that I've ever been
more shocked in my life.
I did notice that you'd
been weirdly chummy
with the prince
and Carrots lately,
which had me confused.
But now I get why.
[HANAJIMA] Perhaps we should
invite ourselves over.
Huh?
That way we can personally
assess the environment.
And make sure it's good for you.
Ooh, that's a killer idea.
Let's go right now.
Hold on.
If they don't expect us, there
may not be snacks on hand.
Okay, yeah, good point.
But I'm still concerned here.
[HANAJIMA]
Agreed.
Fortunately, it's a school
holiday tomorrow.
‐‐Uh. You guys?
‐‐Let's sleep over tonight.
[HANAJIMA] Strike while the
iron is hot, as they say.
Huh?
It'll be awesome.
We'll go straight home after
school and grab our stuff.
And we won't cause any trouble.
Yo, yo.
Evening.
Hello! So glad you're here.
Sorry about this.
I know I didn't give you much
warning that they were coming.
Nah, never you mind.
Shigure, are you
sure about this?
Word around school
is you shouldn't
underestimate Wave Girl.
Que sera, sera.
This'll work out fine.
Don't be so nervous.
[HANAJIMA]
A dog.
Well, hello there.
Huh? Now that's unexpected.
Bad boy. You go back outside.
[DOG barks]
[TOHRU]
Here ya go.
Great. Thank you.
So, old man. I mean, Shigure.
What do you do for a living?
Oh. Me? Well, I'm a writer.
A novelist, in fact.
Wait, hold up, you write books?
Why are you surprised by that?
You live here and didn't know?
What do you call it?
High literature?
Yep. That's right.
Stories like this.
[ALL gasp]
Whoops! Sorry,
grabbed the wrong book.
This here is more what
I'm interested in.
This is just a silly
one I wrote for fun.
Yeah, but that doesn't change
the fact that you did write it!
That is so impressive.
I can't believe I didn't know.
I never dreamed I
might personally meet
an author in real life!
Oh, stop.
[YUKI] Careful. Praising him
will just inflate his ego.
[KYO] I don't know if it's
possible for his head
to get any bigger than it is.
[TOHRU]
Oh, hey!
I just thought of something
that might be fun!
Wait here, I'll be right back.
On that note, I'm out.
Unfortunately, I've got a
prior commitment tonight.
You kids try not to
have too much fun.
So, she's fine.
In fact, it seems she's
fitting in well here.
I'm happy about that.
And I know she only kept it
from us so we wouldn't worry.
Still...
[UOTANI] We swore we'd be
there if she ever needed help.
Anything.
Maybe that sounds
dramatic to you,
but Tohru was the first
friend we ever had.
And in a lotta ways,
she saved us.
I don't expect either of
you to understand that.
I just hate this.
The fact that we didn't know to
support her when she needed us.
[UOTANI] It's like Tohru does
all the work in our friendship,
but can't count on us for
putting in the same energy.
Is it even worth being
friends with us?
[KYO]
Look, you're good.
She's not the kinda girl
who sweats stuff like that.
[YUKI]
Miss Honda.
She deserves the moon, but
would never ask you for it.
[TOHRU]
Sorry for taking so long.
I couldn't find the
cards anywhere.
Let's play Rich Man‐Poor man.
[HANAJIMA]
That's a brilliant idea. I'm in.
Aw yeah. I can't wait to
school coppertop over here.
Not a chance.
I'll beat you, and when I do,
you gotta dye your
hair black, got it?
[UOTANI]
Fine...
Here, do the honors?
Cut the cards for us.
[KYO] This is my natural color,
you bleach‐blonde moron!
Yeah. Sure.
[KYO]
Fight me!
[SHIGURE]
How are you feeling?
Yuki and Kyo seem much happier,
and I'm certain it's because
Tohru is living with us now.
I hope things continue
on a positive track.
I know your real goal.
I assume you think this will
fail, but you're out of luck.
Because you see,
Tohru is a much better
person than you are.
You don't have to say it.
I know I always ask
for the moon.
[UOTANI]
Ugh.
I yelled too much
and my throat hurts.
At least you didn't end up
the poor man like I did.
This is a rather luxurious bed.
[TOHRU] Isn't it?
Shigure bought it for me.
[UOTANI] What is he? Some
kind of "Mister Moneybags"?
Huh? Whoa, Tohru.
I can't believe you
still have that hat.
[TOHRU] Of course I do.
It's an important memento!
[HANAJIMA]
Really? What's the story?
Oh, that's right.
I don't think I ever had the
chance to tell you about this.
It's from when I was a kid.
In elementary school, the boys
bullied me all the time.
One day, they were chasing me,
and I was so scared as
I ran away from them
that I completely lost
track of where I was.
I hid because I was afraid
they would find me,
and eventually, I just sat
there bawling my eyes out.
That's when I saw a boy
across the street.
And he was wearing this hat.
He stood and stared at
me for a little while.
But then he ran off,
without saying a word.
And for some reason
I chased after him.
Like it was on instinct.
[TOHRU]
Wait! I don't wanna be alone!
I wanna go home!
Please don't run so fast. Ah!
[TOHRU] I almost lost sight
of him so many times,
but he'd wait for
me to catch up.
And thanks to this
mysterious boy...
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
...I found myself outside
of my apartment
building once again.
[HANAJIMA]
That's a wonderful memory.
If the two of you met again
later and fell in love,
it'd be an even better story.
It's the type of setup
from a romance novel.
[TOHRU giggles]
I won't hold my breath
[UOTANI]
Hey, it's a small world.
You never know, it might happen.
[TOHRU]
That's true.
If I did meet him again,
I'd at least like to thank
him for what he did.
He's probably forgotten all
about it by now, though.
I bet it was just
another day for him.
But still, he holds a
special place in my heart.
[TOHRU] I think that
boy might've been
someone important in my life.
My first love.
You poor kid.
You even had a rough life when
you were little, didn't you?
Oh, no, I wouldn't
say that at all.
I recently learned
exactly how lucky I am.
And I won't take
that for granted.
I get to live in this
house with the Somas.
I had the most
incredible mother.
And I have not one,
but two wonderful friends
named Hana‐chan and Uo‐chan
right here by my side.
I know you two will
always have my back.
How could I possibly
be ungrateful
when I have people who care?
I can't tell you what
that means to me.
How fortunate it makes me feel.
I love you two.
Look, you're good.
She's not the kinda girl
who sweats stuff like that.
Miss Honda.
She deserves the moon, but
would never ask you for it.
[TOHRU]
All right.
We should probably
be getting to sleep.
They really do get
her, don't they?
Uh. What?
It's true. They see straight
through to her essence.
Her ability to appreciate
what she has in the moment,
instead of always looking ahead
and wishing she had more.
And incomparable friendship.
That's right.
Yours, too.
[YUKI]
Cretin.
I've told you not to drink
straight from the carton.
Oh. Good morning!
‐‐Lay off me, stuck‐up rat.
‐‐I hope you slept well.
[KYO yells]
Oops, looks like you
spilled the milk.
Go and buy more for us.
You jerk!
That's it. We're settling
this right now.
A cat and a rat.
[KYO, TOHRU, YUKI gasp]
Uncanny.
[TOHRU]
Oh, hello! Y‐You're up!
Can I get you something?
Why do you say that?
You know, they're
like that cartoon...
[KYO] That's right.
I forgot they were here.
Still, this seems like
a fun house to live in.
I'd decided that if I came over
and found out it was a bad
environment for Tohru,
then I'd do all sorts of
things to the two of you.
What kinda things?
Like what?
Has anyone ever told you...
that your waves are quite nice?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[HANAJIMA]
Oh, you don't realize it?
Well, that's good, too.
Well, we're counting
on the two of you.
Please look after her for us.
You guys. I'm okay.
But thank you for...
[KYO]
That was like...
[YUKI] ...they were
giving away a bride.
Now, let's have breakfast.
We'll have to come back
and visit here again.
[HANAJIMA]
Yes.
I'd like to investigate the
Soma family's strange waves.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
she's gotta be kidding.
[TOHRU]
Um!
I promise that I'll be
super careful, 'kay?
Your secret will not get out.
Plus, they're both
really good people.
I swear.
Yeah, fine. Have it your way.
Yes, they are your
friends, after all.
[gasps]
[phone ringing]
[TOHRU]
Hello?
[HATORI]
Is this Tohru Honda?
[TOHRU] Uh, yes.
May I ask who's calling?
[HATORI] Hatori Soma. We met
at the festival yesterday.
I'll cut to the chase.
I need you to come to the Soma
estate on your next day off.
[TOHRU]
Pardon?
I have something important
I must discuss with you.
Don't tell anyone about this.
You'll come by
yourself as well.
He's the one who
suppressed their memories.
So just be careful.
[TOHRU]
This isn't good!
But then, Mom did tell me not to
doubt people without a reason.
[HATORI] If you don't show up.
I trust you know what'll happen.
[TOHRU]
Right. I'll be there.
[HATORI]
Good.
And who knows, you may
even get to meet Akito.
[gasps]
[TOHRU]
"Spring comes."