[TOHRU]
It's spring!
And the first day of the new
term is always so exciting!
We are now officially
second‐year students!
Aw, the first‐years
were adorable!
Even if some of them
looked totally lost.
The two of you really missed out
by not coming to the opening
ceremony to wish them well.
‐‐[KYO] Sounds horrible
‐‐[UOTANI] Hard pass.
I'm already suffering
through this hay fever.
Put me in a loud, cramped
room and I'd be in hell.
Stop complaining
and take some meds.
They don't work for me.
Maybe all those drugs in my
rebellious youth were a mistake.
What drugs are
you talkin' about?
I'm surprised the prince
isn't with you.
Well, everyone on the ceremony
committee's really busy today.
Man, sounds like a rough life.
Plus I bet he's getting mauled
by lovestruck
first‐years already.
[SATOMI]
Excuse me.
Senpai, I think I somehow
lost my student ID.
You, too? I don't know what
you want me to do about it.
[SATOMI]
Please help!
[YUKI]
Do you remember the last time
you're certain you had it?
I'll help you look.
Can you tell me your name
and class number?
I'm Satomi Arimori, 15,
Scorpio, blood type B!
My hobbies include
arts and crafts,
and my best feature
is my slim ankles!
[RINA]
I'm Rina Sonomiya!
And lots of people say I look
like I should be in a pop idol!
[STUDENT A]
No one says that, you idiot!
[STUDENT G]
Uh...
I know I should be jealous,
but I feel bad for him.
I wouldn't be surprised
if the prince ends up
student council
president this year.
The current one should
focus on his own issues.
[TOHRU] I don't think Yuki
would really want that.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[UOTANI sneezes]
Here, take this.
[UOTANI]
Ugh. Thanks.
Of course.
[HANAJIMA]
Tohru.
[TOHRU]
Hm?
I picked up some waves
from the adults area
that felt like they
might belong to Shigure.
Oh. Right. He should be here.
There are a couple of new Somas
who're entering the
school as first‐years.
[SHIGURE]
I adore Haru and Momoji.
It's like they're my
younger brothers.
Clearly I'll have to be there.
I'd never be able
to forgive myself
if I missed their
glorious school debut.
Hm?
What? Why those
suspicious looks?
I'm appalled.
Surely you don't think I'm going
simply to ogle high school girls
in their natural habitat?
Besides, I am an artiste.
It's my job to observe the
beauty this world offers.
Idiot.
Hold on a sec. You're saying
more Somas go here now?
[TOHRU]
That's right. Two boys.
You met one of them at
the culture festival.
Kyon, bring the newbies here.
Yes, go. Let's see them.
Why do I have to?
Just send that one instead.
She's already planning
to say "hi," I bet.
Well, yeah. I am.
Yes, but why should we trouble
our dear friends with such
menial errands when you can
play fetch for us instead?
I'm not a dog!
[UOTANI]
Move it, Carrots.
Guys, it's really fine.
I wanted to go welcome
them to school
whenever I got some
free time anyway.
But you can still join me.
If you're not doing
anything else.
What a pain.
Now I have to see
those two idiots
in the outside world
and at school?
Maybe the change of scenery will
make you get along a lot better!
This could be a good thing.
I'll see ya later!
Crazy how hard it is for him
to say no to her these days.
It's entertaining.
[KYO] Have you met a pair
of guys named Soma?
A little blond kid and
one with white hair?
Oh, yes! They're in our class!
‐‐[KYO] Go get them.
‐‐[GIRLS] Sure!
[KYO sighs]
[KYO]
If she wanted to see them,
she could've at least tracked
down their class number.
Sometimes it's like
she's not thinking.
[STUDENT H] Dude, check
her out. Pretty cute.
[STUDENT I]
Definitely.
Looks like she might be
a bit of an airhead, though.
[STUDENT I] Yeah, maybe,
but that's fine by me.
Girls who think they're so smart
can be a pain sometimes.
[STUDENT H]
Heh. Fair enough.
Let's go introduce ourselves.
[BOTH gasp]
[TOHRU]
Huh?
‐‐[BOYS yell]
‐‐[TOHRU] Hm? Hm?
Damn scumbags.
This is what happens
when you space out.
Um, yeah, sure?
You should be more aware of your
surroundings when you're alone.
Otherwise, losers like that
might take advantage of you.
[TOHRU]
Hm? Right. Got it.
When you're alone, not now.
Whenever I'm with you,
you can space out all you want
and I'll make sure you're okay.
[TOHRU]
Right.
I didn't mean that in
a weird way, okay?
[TOHRU]
Hm?
Weird, like how?
Like you'd take it the
wrong way. Course not.
‐‐[TOHRU] Hm?
‐‐[MOMIJI] Hallo!
[MOMIJI]
It's me, Tohru!
[TOHRU]
Hi, Momiji!
[giggling]
Aw, it's so good to see you!
[KYO]
Are you crazy?!
[MOMIJI screams]
[TOHRU] Whoa! Kyo, wait!
Please calm down.
What am I supposed to do?
Look at what he's wearing!
[HATSUHARU]
Yo.
[TOHRU]
Ah! Hatsuharu!
[MOMIJI whines]
Kyo, why you got to
be such a meanie?!
Look around, you do realize
that you're wearing
a girls' uniform, right?
Even this wannabe playboy
put on the right jacket!
[HATSUHARU sighs]
[HATSUHARU] If he likes it,
then what's the problem?
Isn't it so cute?
Yeah! It really suits you.
How am I in the wrong here?
[HATSUHARU gasps]
[TOHRU]
Huh?
Seriously?
I can't believe that's what
you're wearing, Momiji.
And you. No better.
Oh, good! Does this mean you're
done with your committee work?
[YUKI]
No, not yet.
I just came to check on these
two while making the rounds.
Hey, ja, did they tell you?
Earlier, before school, I got
warned not to mess around.
After all, if I crash
into a girl,
I might change in front of them.
So instead, I'm going to play
it cool while I'm here.
[KYO] This is you playing
it cool?! Dressed like that?!
[TAKEI]
Your dubiousness is justified,
Kyo Soma of Class 2‐D.
Your tangerine hair
may be a nuisance,
but a boy wearing a girl's
uniform is unprecedented!
Brazen, even! Not to mention
the length of those shorts!
Shameless!
The teachers may overlook
this travesty, but I will not.
That is my duty.
For I am Makoto Takei,
your trusted student
council president!
And to you, I'm the commander
of the School Defense Force.
Another idiot appears.
What gall! This coming
from an obvious ruffian!
You're practically
jangling with jewelry!
And don't even get me started
on your ludicrous bleached hair!
[YUKI] Actually, president,
that is his natural color.
[TAKEI]
Guh?
Yuki! Greetings!
It's a pleasure to see you.
But back to the vile
matter at hand!
This can't be real‐‐
the roots are black!
Trust me on this one.
I am a scholar and
his hair defies sense!
[TOHRU]
It'd be a whole lot easier
if we could just tell
him the truth.
Now, shall we move on
to the little sprite?
What's the meaning of your look?
Speak up for yourself!
Huh?
[TAKEI] Is this some rebellious
statement on masculinity?
Or is this simply
the sense of self
you'd like to present
to the world?
[cries]
I just... I think this uniform
looks much cuter on me.
Um. Please, sir.
Don't be too harsh on him.
I am not being harsh,
just asking questions!
I'm abiding by common sense
as well as the rules
of this institution
‐‐that I am sworn to uphold.
‐‐[HATSUHARU] Shut up.
[TAKEI]
Eh?
[KYO grunts]
I thought I had shit on my shoe,
but you're what
I've been smelling.
[TAKEI]
You can't speak to me like‐‐
Whoa, Haru.
Why don't I ask you
some questions now.
You think wearing a tie
means you're not a bully?
Or no one's ever been mugged
by a guy not wearing jewelry?
That people with one hair
color can't murder a man?
Just who the hell do
you think you are?
God or somethin'? Huh?
[TOHRU, KYO, YUKI]
It's Dark Haru.
Well? What happened?
Where's your righteous fury?
Lost your voice?
[GIRLS]
President!
Stop it. You can tell he's
got no fight training.
You stay out of
this, ya stupid Cat!
[KYO]
Don't start with me, you idiot!
What?! Don't act like
you're that great!
You ran away from our last fight
with your tail
between your legs!
Is your brain broken? You're the
one who called that fight off!
[HATSUHARU] Oh, let me guess,
you're on this worm's side.
I shouldn't be surprised
you'd think he's right.
[KYO]
Both of you are morons!
D'you want a lollipop?
Excuse me, ladies.
‐‐[GIRLS yelp]
‐‐Don't drag them into this.
I wanna know what ya think.
Take Momiji Soma over there.
He looks fine in that
uniform, right?
Eventually he'll grow up.
But let him enjoy himself.
He can dress like a man later.
Bet he'll be pretty hot.
[MOMIJI]
You want a taste?
[GIRLS]
Yes.
Don't let him brainwash you!
You're unleashing chaos.
Why can't you follow the rules?
It's a rule of fashion to always
wear what looks good on you.
[TAKEI]
Unacceptable!
You're twisting reality to
suit your own desires...
You just don't quit, do you?
Well, okay then. What if it was
Yuki wearing a girl's uniform?
[gasps]
[YUKI]
Mr. President.
Fine.
No, it's not.
End this. Or I am never
speaking to you again.
Come on. It was rhetorical.
Just like your threat.
[YUKI]
Mr. President.
Magnificent.
Stop picturing it!
[grunts]
Please forgive me.
I got carried away.
You are quite the formidable
opponent, Mr. Hatsuharu Soma.
But can you prove to
me that your hair
is without a doubt
its natural color?! Hmm?!
If I have to.
This should be rich.
Undeniable proof?
I highly doubt‐‐ Ah!
Hey, wait! Excuse me!
[TAKEI screams]
Undeniable proof.
I see there is still much
to learn of this world.
[KYO]
He didn't.
[YUKI]
He did.
Fine! You're the
victor on this day!
But each of you will feel
my retribution next time!
[GIRLS]
See you soon, Momiji!
[HATSUHARU chuckles]
What was the reason that
guy showed up again?
[YUKI sighs]
Um, so how did you
prove that that was
your real hair color
in the bathroom?
[YUKI, KYO grunt]
Easy. If you'd like, I'd be
happy to show you as well.
‐‐Uh.
‐‐Don't you worry.
No hugging is necessary
for us to give into‐‐
[KYO] Dark is the one
guy I can't handle.
[TOHRU]
I'm confused.
[YUKI]
It's nothing.
Don't give him a second
thought, Miss Honda.
I feel tired.
[KYO]
You're tired? I'm exhausted.
[bell tolls]
Hey! There's the bell!
[TOHRU gasps]
Question: Would you be willing
to meet some of my friends
before you go home today?
You really mean it?
Ja! Of course I would!
They'll be so excited.
Oh, yeah. I need to
talk to Yuki and Kyo.
Could you two stay behind?
It'll be real quick.
Right.
Well, I'll go on ahead, but I'll
see you when school lets out!
I'm sorry, Tohru.
Oh, it's no problem!
All right, what's
this all about?
It better not be somethin' dumb.
[MOMIJI]
Mhm.
[TOHRU]
Wow, that was kind of a lot.
If it's gonna be like this
in the hallways every day,
Kyo and Yuki are going to
get worn out in no time.
[AKITO]
You look like you're having fun.
[TOHRU]
Huh?
[MOMIJI]
We've got a visitor.
At school.
[MOMIJI]
Akito's here.
[YUKI] I yearned for so much
from inside that dark room.
I wanted... so many things.
[gasps]
[HATSUHARU] Apparently, Akito up
and decided to visit the school.
[MOMIJI] We thought it would
be best to warn you two
so you weren't surprised.
Especially if you don't
want to see each other.
[TOHRU gasps]
A‐Akito. It's you?
That's correct. Tohru Honda.
Ah! I'm very pleased
to meet you!
[TOHRU]
I don't understand.
Why is Akito at our school?
Should we really be
meeting like this?
I didn't expect the family
head to be so young.
Or as beautiful as Yuki.
Wait. This is the person
who hurt Hatori's eye.
[AKITO]
Hm.
You strike me as quite
feminine. Gentle, too.
I'm glad you seem like
such a good girl.
And most importantly,
you're also very cute.
[TOHRU] What? Oh, no,
I'm just a normal‐‐
Ha. Don't get flustered.
I'm just stating the obvious.
Sorry it took me so long
to introduce myself.
I'm rather shy when it
comes to strangers.
I hope you're not angry.
[TOHRU]
No, no, of course not!
That's a relief. So, how
about a formal introduction?
Nice to meet you. I'm Akito.
Head of the family.
Yes! Right!
But please, the
pleasure is all mine.
[TOHRU]
It's strange.
Akito comes off as much
softer than I had expected.
Now that we've met,
I'm hoping we'll be able
to get along well.
Please take care of
Yuki and the others.
[YUKI]
Akito!
[AKITO]
Ah. Yuki!
I was hoping I'd run
into you. My boy.
Feels like a lifetime has gone
by since I saw you last.
Can't believe how grown up
you look. You're taller, right?
[YUKI]
What did you do?
What did you say to Miss Honda?
Nothing. I was simply
paying my respects.
Isn't that right, Tohru?
Wasn't I just
paying my respects?
Um. Yes, that's right.
But, Yuki, now that you're here,
there is a question that's
been weighing on my mind.
What would possibly make you
skip New Year's with me?
Don't you know how
that makes me feel?
Especially when I have been
so generous to you lately.
When you do foolish
things like that,
it really hurts my feelings.
I wonder if this means you
need a little reeducating.
Perhaps some time in your
special room is in order.
You recall those days.
Would you like to repeat them?
Or do you remember
how to be a good boy?
Um. I'm sorry.
But we have to get
back to class now.
You know, or else
we'll be in trouble.
Of course. Forgive me.
I suppose I should
be getting back
to Shigure and company anyway.
They're probably worried.
Yuki, I hope that you're
enjoying your time
at this school.
And remember... it would make
me happy if you visited.
[TOHRU] I shoved my way
between the two of them
without even thinking.
I don't know what they
were talking about,
but... I think Akito
must be... dangerous.
[TOHRU] That look. I've never
seen anything so threatening.
Does the head of the Soma
family hate me? Why?
[YUKI]
Miss Honda?
Yes?
[YUKI] Did Akito really not
say anything strange to you
before I got here?
No! Nothing! I promise.
We really were
just saying hello.
Okay.
[TOHRU]
No.
I can't be worried about
why Akito hates me.
That's not the most
important thing right now.
Hey, Yuki! Let's have some fun!
School's out early today,
so we've got some free time!
And I was talking with Uo‐chan
and some of the others
about hanging out after class!
Let's seize the moment and do
something exciting together.
[TOHRU]
At this moment,
all I want is to banish
the terror of Akito
from Yuki's mind the best I can.
[GROUP] ♪ Rock, paper, scissors,
and these will be our teams! ♪
How'd I get roped in?
And why badminton?
[UOTANI]
Real men don't complain
when they're asked
to play sports.
You're not the one who's gotta
play the game wearing a mask.
No one's making you play!
I don't really know why we're
in groups. Or the rules.
[UOTANI]
Easy. Do whatever you want.
[YUKI]
Uh.
There are no rules
required for badminton.
You serve with every
ounce of strength,
and then you return with
every ounce of strength.
Let's put it this way:
The first one to collapse loses.
‐‐I like this. It's simple.
‐‐[UOTANI] Mh‐hm. Mh‐hm.
That sounds too easy!
Oh, shut up already.
Just make sure you protect
your side of the court.
That's it?
[UOTANI]
This is our game, prince.
Time to take out
Carrots over there.
[KYO]
You think you're so tough!
Whaddaya say? Shall we?
[MOMIJI, TOHRU, UOTANI]
Ready, go!
[SHIGURE]
So, Tohru is ugly, apparently.
Or at least, someone thinks so.
[AKITO]
She's absurdly ugly. So plain.
She seems stupid, too.
I've nothing to fear from
a pathetic girl like that.
Before long, Yuki will
come crawling back,
begging forgiveness.
After all, the boy is
still afraid of me.
And that proves he can't
forget about me, doesn't it?
[SHIGURE]
He was there so long.
Locked in that dark room.
Akito put him through
so much torture.
[YUKI]
Get me out.
Please, get me out.
[SHIGURE] I guess something
like that's hard to forget.
[HATORI] Yes. But Akito
doesn't understand.
Just as there are
people who inflict pain,
there are those who try
to soothe that pain,
in themselves and others alike.
That gives people courage,
if nothing else.
And aside from that,
Tohru is adorable.
Honestly, it's impossible
not to love her.
[HATORI] That sounds
criminal coming from you.
[YUKI]
I yearned for so much.
I wanted so many things.
Parents who would hug me.
A home I'd want to return to.
A place where everyone smiled.
To be someone people
wouldn't leave behind.
Warmth.
A warm life.
A warm person.
[YUKI]
They exist.
They're real.
[HANAJIMA]
The sun is setting already?
I guess time really does fly
when you're having fun.
See you tomorrow,
Tohru. Until then.
How come we're dying...
and she's okay?
[HATSUHARU]
Well, we should head home, too.
I was worried at first...
but Yuki seems fine.
To me, at least.
Thank you. For everything.
[TOHRU] Mom, I met the head
of the Soma family today.
Unexpectedly.
There was something about him.
He struck me as a
very unusual person.
I can't help but wonder if he's
a member of the zodiac, too.
And which one.
To be honest with you,
I felt a little scared of him.
[YUKI]
I guess we can't stay here.
It's getting pretty
late. Shall we?
Yes!
[TOHRU] But after spending so
much time with my friends,
that fear feels worlds away.
Like I'll never feel it again.
[AYAME]
"How have you been, my brother?"