[MITSURU]
Sensei?
I'm here to pick up
your manuscript!
If you'll just hand it over,
I'll be on my way!
Very funny. Pretending
you're not at home again.
Hello?
Come on, you've had
your fun! Sensei!
[groans]
[MITSURU] Please, Sensei!
I know you're in there!
Don't do this to me!
[growls]
[SHIGURE]
Hiya.
[MITSURU] Sensei! Uh,
where are you right now?
[SHIGURE] I got the biggest
craving for takoyaki,
so I took a stroll
to Octopus Dude.
Have you ever tried their food?
[MITSURU]
But today is your deadline!
[SHIGURE]
Is it really?
Totally slipped my mind.
[click]
Oh, no, you don't!
You're hungry? Great!
Because I'm gonna
feed every last one
of your blank pages to you.
‐‐[MITSURU screams]
‐‐[chuckles]
[MITSURU yelling]
Whoops. I'm so sorry!
[RITSU] No, I'm the one
who should apologize
for walking in front
of your leap...
It's my fault. I'm
rushing because Sensei
cares more about downing
street food than his deadline!
He'll be the death of me.
But, sorry, that's
not your fault is it.
I must be going now.
I'm coming for you,
Octo‐sensei!
[TOHRU humming]
[MITSURU]
Tako‐yucky!
Hello there, mi‐‐
[RITSU screams]
[RITSU] The bottom of my bag
broke. This is a disaster!
[TOHRU]
Here.
I'm more than happy
to give you a hand.
[RITSU] No, please, that's
far too much to ask of you.
Nonsense.
It's good to help each other
out when we face problems.
[RITSU]
Forgive me.
See, It doesn't
matter where I am;
I always cause problems
for the people around me.
I shouldn't be taking up
space, or using up oxygen.
Still, even though I feel bad,
I'm making you get on
the ground and help me.
I apologize. Not just to you,
but to the entire world!
Listen, all of
humanity, I'm sorry!
But until then, I'll apologize
to the entire world! I'm sorry!
Wait, are you Ritchan?
[screams]
Am I so horrible that even
strangers on the street
know what my name is?
Of course they do! My cursed
name must be infamous,
so everyone knows to avoid me.
I've been living...
No, I figured...
I apologize for...
Ah. Why are you here, Ritchan?
[RITSU]
Ah! I apologize!
Someone of my low worth
shouldn't have the
honor of visiting you.
I'm just so sorry!
[SHIGURE]
What a rare treat this is.
You're usually so timid.
Not the sort to drop
in out of the blue.
Oh! Yes, sorry for barging in.
And for causing Tohru
so much trouble
because I overloaded my bag.
No. I was happy to help!
And even happier to meet you.
[TOHRU] I was hoping I'd get to
meet Ritchan, the zodiac Monkey.
Who knew she'd end up
being such a pretty girl?
So, then, why the
impromptu visit?
No, this is terrible.
I must be intruding on you.
[SHIGURE]
Mh‐hm.
[RITSU] I'm sorry!
I'll run home immediately!
‐‐You'll never see me again!
‐‐I'm just kidding.
Sit down, it's a joke.
So, what's on your mind?
Well, you see, most of the
other members of the zodiac
had already met Tohru since
she started living here,
so I figured it would
be rude of me
if I didn't introduce
myself to her.
My name is Ritsu Soma.
You know my mother from
the hot spring you went to.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you.
No, the pleasure is all mine.
My name is Tohru Honda.
Ah. Right. It's not
nearly enough, but‐‐
Ooh, you brought a gift? Yay!
Yes.
But I didn't know what
fruit you would like,
so I got you some books
on fruit instead.
I hope you find them enjoyable.
Or not! I'm so sorry.
This must be a terrible
present‐‐absurdly rude.
Well, yeah. It kind of is.
[barking]
[RITSU]
I'm the worst!
I'll go to the market
and get some real fruit.
‐‐All the fruit! Right now!
‐‐Kidding. Sit down.
[RITSU] I knew I shouldn't
have come here today.
Why am I making you put
up with my stupidity?
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Yes, he's right!
I'm excited to meet you,
Ritchan, so don't you worry!
The fact that you came to visit
me makes me truly happy.
I swear it! I'm delighted
that you're here.
[RITSU sniffs]
You're so kind. Thanks for that.
[TOHRU] Wow. She's even more
beautiful when she smiles.
[SHIGURE] I see you still
take after your mother.
The two of you panic so easily.
You're going to be
a working adult soon;
you can't constantly act
on edge in the real world.
I know. I apologize.
With that in mind,
maybe it'd be wise for you
to grow a little more backbone.
Yes, I hope to!
I want real confidence in
myself more than anything.
And maybe one day,
I'll be overflowing with
self‐assurance just like Aya is.
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
Yeah, that's not happening.
Huh, but why not?
Is it because I'm too weak?
Aya's the issue.
He has what you might call
a "superhuman level"
of belief in himself.
[RITSU]
Oh. I see.
Let's start small.
You must know you
apologize far too quickly.
Yes, you're right. Sorry.
[SHIGURE]
Point confirmed!
Here's an idea.
As the first big step
toward a new, better you,
you're banned from
reflexive apologies.
[gasps]
And, Tohru, cheer
Ritchan on, yes?
Uh. Sure, of course!
[RITSU] They're going through
all this trouble for my sake.
What kindhearted people.
Thank you. I will take
on this challenge!
[YUKI]
I'm home.
Ah. Well, talk about your
perfect timing, right?
Yuki will be the first
test you must pass.
But I need to prepare
myself emotionally.
Not true. You got this!
Hey. Ritsu, what're
you doing here?
[RITSU yells]
You're right! The likes of
me shouldn't be allowed
anywhere near your
home, should I?
I'm so sorry! This is totally...
[YUKI]
That's not what I meant.
Hey! Try it again!
[RITSU gasps]
[RITSU]
Y‐Yuki.
You're beginning to resemble
your older brother so much.
[YUKI]
We're done here.
[RITSU] Ah! Did I say something
to make you mad at me?
Not at all.
[RITSU]
No! I'm so sorry!
Ah. Here comes Kyo.
Ritchan, pull yourself
together and try again.
[RITSU]
Huh?
[KYO] Huh? What're
you doing here, Ritsu?
Uh! You're right.
The likes of me
shouldn't be allowed
anywhere near your home,
should I? I'm so‐‐
I came to introduce
myself to Tohru.
[KYO]
Huh?
[RITSU] By the way, I wanted
to say I'm happy for you.
Why?
You and Yuki are living
under the same roof now.
I bet you're becoming
good friends.
[BOTH]
Like hell we are!
[RITSU yelps]
I couldn't be sorrier!
I take it back!
You hate each other!
I knew someone as worthless as
me shouldn't be visiting here!
I'll be taking my leave!
I apologize for staying so long.
For ever showing up!
For ever being born!
Thank you for putting up
with such a worthless person
for as long as you managed to.
I'm leaving now and
I'll never return.
I'm sorry!
No, please stay!
[ALL grunt]
[TOHRU]
Huh?
Wait, I don't understand
this. Aren't you a girl?
And I thought only males
in the zodiac transformed
when I hugged them.
Uh. But you... What's happening?
I... I'm so sorry!
[SHIGURE]
So, here's the deal, Tohru.
Ritchan is actually male.
Be that as it may,
he's worn girls' clothes
since he was quite young.
That makes a lot more sense.
But why wear girls' clothes?
Something about them
makes me feel secure.
In the beginning, I just
wanted to try them on
to see what they'd be like.
Then, once I realized I was
far more at peace in them...
...I couldn't dream of stopping.
[RITSU] Kagura‐chan,
could I have this dress?
[KAGURA] Huh? What,
you mean like to wear?
I'm sorry. I'm so
embarrassed of myself.
No, please, you shouldn't be!
The clothes really suit you.
You're gorgeous!
[SHIGURE]
I think you may be missing
the bigger picture on this one.
[YUKI] Thing is, you'll
be working soon, Ritsu.
Will you wear
girls' clothes then?
I don't know. What if I can't?
Uhh...
[RITSU cries]
[SHIGURE]
Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't you three
get comfortable
and ditch your school uniforms?
[YUKI]
Mh‐hm. That does sound good.
Please excuse me for a moment.
[RITSU]
I have to apologize to you.
[SHIGURE]
Huh?
I agreed to take you up
on your challenge earlier
but then immediately failed.
[MITSURU]
Octo‐sensei!
Were you expecting someone?
Uh! Quickly! Go close the door!
Do it!
Uh, right. Sure.
[MITSURU]
Listen, you coward!
Sensei, I know you're in there.
Don't make me break
down this door!
You can't hide from me
forever! Why can...
Um, so, do you know the woman
trying to break into your home?
[SHIGURE]
Hmm.
Yes, I do. She's what
you'd call a stalker.
What? Really?
She figured out where I live,
and now I live my life in fear.
How fortuitous, though!
Fate offers you a new challenge.
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
Ritchan!
Assert yourself by sending
this obsessed fan away.
If you can get rid of my
stalker all by yourself,
well, then, it will be proof of
your improved self‐assurance!
Are you sure?
Then I'll do it.
I will find my inner strength!
Okay, great.
[chuckles]
Hello?
Stalker? Miss?
[screams]
Sensei?
Uh. Hi, there.
[growls]
That pervert! He's been holed up
inside with some girlfriend!
[RITSU]
No, you've got it all wrong.
I'm related to Shigure!
I'm not his girlfriend!
Ha! You think I'd believe
a bold‐faced lie like that?
[RITSU]
It's the truth, honest!
Stop hiding behind your lover!
You've done it, right?
Tell me it's complete!
We haven't done anything!
Is it good? Huh?
[RITSU]
I have no idea!
[MITSURU]
It's no use.
I can't believe he's not
finished with his draft.
Huh? What draft?
Uh, stalker?
[MITSURU]
Please, Father, Mother,
forgive me for leaving
this world before you.
[RITSU screams]
What's that, miss?
My will.
[RITSU screams]
If the manuscript
isn't finished yet,
there's no way
I can go on living.
Alas, maybe I'll have a copy
of the draft in the afterlife.
[TOHRU]
Y‐You okay, Mitchan?
[RITSU]
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
Would you look who it is?
How are you?
[MITSURU]
S‐S‐Se‐Sensei!
I knew you were in there
hiding from me, but why?
[SHIGURE laughs]
[SHIGURE]
Do you really need to ask?
[MITSURU] Please tell me:
Are you done? Is it ready?
[SHIGURE]
Of course it is. Here.
[gasps]
[MITSURU]
My humblest gratitude.
‐‐I can't believe it.
‐‐Uh, sorry.
‐‐I'm so happy.
‐‐Who is this again?
Oh, you don't know?
This is Mitchan.
She's Shigure's editor.
[RITSU grunts]
I apologize for not
knowing who you are
and what an important
job you have!
I got in your way. I'm sorry!
[TOHRU, RITSU, SHIGURE]
Uh.
[yelping]
[screams]
Are you okay?
‐‐Oh, wow.
‐‐[TOHRU] Speak to me, please!
[RITSU screaming]
[KYO]
Crap! What is he doing?
Hear me, O righteous
gods and Buddhas.
You must not show me any favor
or forgive me of my sins.
Please step back.
What drama.
[RITSU] That manuscript was
more precious to Mitchan
than her own life, and I
destroyed it in front of her.
Only through death may I attempt
to atone for what I've done.
[TOHRU yelping]
Miss Honda, please calm down.
[RITSU] Furthermore,
I've disappointed everyone,
despite the many chances
they've given me.
I'm not worthy of
any more kindness.
Gods, what purpose
do I have for living
if all I do is ruin things?
How can I not be
a burden to others?
Well, you could start by
climbing down from the roof.
Please! Listen!
None of us are upset with you.
You have to come down.
No. You don't understand me.
I've always been this way.
Having a zodiac
spirit for a child
causes people enough trouble.
But on top of that,
I ended up being a crybaby.
A clumsy coward.
My parents were always having
to apologize on my behalf.
[RITSU]
I'm sorry. So sorry.
Mom and Dad, you must hate
always having to
apologize for me.
You probably wanted
a normal child
who could play
without you worrying.
[RITSU]
I think, maybe a person like me
should just give up on life.
There's no reason not to.
Maybe everyone would
be better without me.
And yet, I don't even have
the courage to end things.
I stand here a failure
in every possible sense.
Still, I have the
nerve to stay alive.
[TOHRU] But that's what
takes real courage.
‐‐Miss Honda!
‐‐When'd she get up there?
What's wrong with having
the nerve to live?
Isn't... Isn't that what
makes us human?
Sure, sometimes we get lost.
We cry, or worry,
or we're afraid,
but we feel joy, too!
[RITSU] What's the point
in the end, though?
When I look at my life,
I can't find a single reason
for me to have ever been born.
[TOHRU] Maybe the point of
living is to find that reason.
Somewhere deep down,
I know you must be desperately
looking for your life's purpose.
You might not realize it...
but your heart is searching.
[KYOKO] Oh, Tohru.
I'm so glad I had you.
Now I'm happy every day,
because you're here
with me, making me smile.
[TOHRU] Then, I guess the
whole reason I was born
was so I could make
you happy, Mommy!
[KYOKO chuckles]
[KYOKO] If that's true,
I won't question it.
[TOHRU]
I think that none of us are born
with some predetermined reason
to be alive in this
world, Ritchan.
Because your reason
for living is something
you need to decide or
discover for yourself.
[gasps]
Be careful!
[RITSU]
Oh, no, Tohru!
[TOHRU] And I think...
everyone is different.
Maybe you'll find
meaning in a dream,
or a job that you really
love, or maybe...
...maybe your reason
is another person!
Sometimes your purpose might
feel uncertain or unstable.
You might even lose your reason.
But as long as you're alive,
and you wanna keep looking,
you'll find another one.
[TOHRU]
I get it now.
I'm looking for the
same thing myself.
And my big hope is...
that it's a person.
[TOHRU]
Or, rather, people.
I wanna live for
the sake of others.
That's why, I think it's okay
to have that nerve
to keep on living.
Because if you have
the nerve to live,
you might meet that
special person
who's your reason
to embrace life.
The one who wants you
to be their reason, too.
[RITSU]
I wonder if someone like me
will find what you're
talking about.
I hope I do one day.
[RITSU]
And, yes, I agree with you.
It'd be nice if I could
live... for someone else.
‐‐She's awake!
‐‐Um, are you okay?
Where's the draft?
[SHIGURE]
Rewriting at this very moment.
Sensei, thank you!
But I won't be finished
for another hour or so.
How 'bout some takoyaki?
I'm on it!
It's dark outside. Why don't
you escort her, Ritchan?
Huh? Oh, okay.
[BOTH]
Uh.
[COOK A]
Hope you enjoy!
[RITSU] Again, I'm really
sorry about messing up
those pages earlier.
No, I should be
apologizing to you.
I acted like a fool in front
of someone I'd just met.
Still, that man has no
right to call me a stalker,
even if he was joking.
Does he always act that way?
That was nothing.
He's constantly teasing
me to amuse himself,
ignoring deadlines
and disappearing
whenever I need him.
My, sounds terrible.
[MITSURU] Honestly, I'm not
sure I'm cut out for this job.
I panic too easily.
When that happens,
I can't think rationally,
so I end up causing
trouble for other people.
[MITSURU sighs]
That might be the part
of myself I hate most.
I know the feeling.
I've always been a disaster.
Ever since I was a child,
it has defined who I am.
I think that might
be the reason why...
...I've never had any
confidence in myself.
I don't know why I was born,
so I've felt useless.
But, despite that... I have the
audacity to continue living.
Because... it's possible
that someday,
even a mess of a person like me
will find the reason I'm alive.
It might even be
for someone else.
Someone who needs me.
[RITSU]
Just so you know,
I'm repeating another person's
words, they're not mine.
I don't care who it is that
said it in the first place.
Hearing it makes me feel
like I can keep going!
[RITSU]
We should probably head back
before the takoyaki gets cold
and we have to grab some more.
[MITSURU]
Okay!
So good.
[MITSURU] So, about that
manuscript, is it done?
Here, Tohru, open wide.
I need you to eat faster!
Shovel that octopus down!
Please, use these
delicious treats as fuel
to power your rewrites for her!
Take those words to heart
and become a takoyaki‐fueled
writing machine!
[SHIGURE]
Didn't I mention? It's finished.
Don't worry, you can
thank me later.
Sensei, you angel.
I'm so grateful. Thanks.
Aw, I'm so happy
for you, Mitchan!
Thank you, too. I'm really
glad we talked earlier.
No, don't thank me.
This was all my fault
to begin with.
Say, if it's okay with you,
I was wondering if you might
want to be my friend.
Uh. But are you positive you
want to be friends with me?
Oh, yes. Please!
Maybe you could teach
me to dress better.
I'd love to learn how to
put on a kimono properly
and be more feminine, like you.
[SHIGURE]
Oh, I should clarify.
Huh?
Ritchan's actually a boy.
Ah! I'm so sorry!
I shouldn't have jumped...
It's my fault! I apologize
for my confusing attire...
No, no, it's just that
you're so beautiful,
I couldn't help but
assume with envy.
[RITSU]
Beautiful? You're so kind!
I'm sorry I made you
feel the need...
[YUKI sighs]
Will this ever end?
[KYO]
So stupid.
I can't do much well,
but I'll happily show you
how to wear a kimono.
No problem!
I look forward to it!
It'll be a lot of fun.
[RITSU] Oh! Yes!
I'm excited about it, too!
Honestly, I swear it.
[RITSU] I hope one day I can
look at someone and say,
"I was born for your sake."
[MITSURU] I hope I can tell
someone, "You're my reason."
And I hope whoever I
say those words to...
[RITSU, MITSURU]
...wants to say them back.
[HIRO] "I can't believe
you picked it up."