So what do you
plan on doing with her?
I'll return her to
her previous form.
And I'll monitor her treatment.
It's the best way to
keep him from finding
her. It should be fine.
And by him... you
mean Chaos's master?
That's correct.
He got Ikaros and Nymph, too.
This guy's made the two of them
suffer so much, I'm
curious who he is. I mean...
Who he is doesn't matter.
Tomoki...
Just make sure that she's happy.
That's all I came here to say.
It's the best any of
us could hope for her.
Wait...
I want to thank you...
for truly loving my daughters.
It means more than
you could ever know.
Memory data recovery
one hundred percent complete.
Reactor function
normalization complete.
Auto-repair protocol
terminating, now.
Whew! Wake up, Alpha.
You're back to normal.
Did everything you
did make her better?
Duh, of course. Now that my
wings are back, I've recovered
my information processing
abilities. So this was no sweat.
That's so awesome. Then can you
do something about these next?!
You powered these babies up
all crazy-super-charged earlier!
It was the coolest ever!
Do it again, please! Can you?
Sorry, but I can't.
Huh? Why not?
Just... do it yourself.
You still have a lot of room
to grow. Put forth the effort,
and you might find you're
able to do it without my help.
Effort, huh?
Yeah, I'll put forth effort!
Hey, Ikaros, you're up.
Wait, are you
sure you should be?
Yes... I feel fine. I promise.
And your memory's
back now, right?
He proposed?
Yeah, it's this thing the humans
do on TV a lot where they
promise they're
gonna be together forever.
We'll be together forever. Just
back off before you kill me!
Yeah, so... you
do remember everything?
Yes, I... remember.
That's great.
Well that's a
load off our minds.
I remember. I remember
Master proposing to me.
Good morning. Our
top story today is...
Hey, Ikaros, what's...
Morning, Tomoki.
What the crap?! Why the Hell
are you two here this morning?!
Lighten up.
When are we ever
not here, dummy?
Okay, whatever.
Ikaros, breakfast, please.
Whose house is
this anyway?! Jeez!
I gave Ikaros a pretty stern
talking-to about not doing
anything funny in the bathroom
again. So I should be able to
take my time in here
and not have anyone bug me.
Nothing beats peace
and quiet, that's for sure.
Sorry. Occupado.
Master, I apologize, but I...
well, it's about your proposal.
Take a hike!
And fix that door!
You don't even know
basic bathroom manners?!
How little common
freakin' sense do you have?!
I said I was sorry, Master.
First thing you do
at a bathroom is knock!
I knock?
That's right, genius!
You hit the door like this!
Oh yeah. And don't
forget to flush. Got it?
Yes, Master.
All right. Now that
we're clear on that
I'm gonna need you
to do me a little favor.
Sure has been a while.
Okay. Let's do it.
Of course, Master.
Conversion process
will commence momentarily.
It's Sorami's own
Cinderella. Tomoko!
Hello! Whatcha think? Huh?
Today's the last
swim class of the year!
And I'm gonna
rock their world by
turning into their pool water!
They're real obscure,
you haven't heard of 'em.
So you're gonna be
swimming with us today, Prez?
That's right. They
combined our classes today.
I don't know how to swim,
but with this heat...
even I wanna jump the
heck in and get all wet!
If you can't swim what
are you even doing here?
Here they come! Girls
in swimsuits! I'm gonna just
roll them all around in
my palms a little! He-he!
Nymph! Over here!
Wanna play some Marco Polo?
Water...
What's your deal, Sohara?
It... was like
something touched me.
Water...
Sensei! Is
something the matter?
Must be my imagination.
Water's the
freakin' best! Water!
Water is grabbing my boobs!
This is so gross!
Someone help!
The water! It's in the water!
It's the water. There's
something wrong with it!
Nymph!
Water!
Oh. Flat as a
wet ironing board.
This is definitely Tomoki!
Nymph, give me
a hand would ya?
Here it is.
What the--?!
W-W-Water!
That's what ya get,
Tomoki, you jerk.
Later, dummy!
You really don't think
we should leave it at that?
Personally... I believe a
much more severe punishment
should be enacted
this time around.
Whoo, I reek of chlorine. For
a second there, I really thought
I was going to get washed out to
sea. Oh well! Time to figure out
what I'm going to be turning
into for my next amazing trick.
Coulda sworn I
heard somethin' back here!
When I find him, I'm gonna
give him my special chop!
I'll take pictures!
Crap-sticks! They're after me!
Sensors say Tomoki's
still on school grounds.
Madame President!
The dragnet is in place!
Good, because the enemy is still
close. Go over the campus with
a fine-tooth comb
until you find something.
Anything?
No sign of him down this way.
Balls. I'm trapped.
What about back here?
Double-trapped!
I'll just duck
in here for now.
Is this it? That fabled place?
The place where young maidens
go to "freshen up?" It is!
The girls' bathroom!
This is totally not where I
planned to go, but who gives
a flip! Hell, Tomoko's a girl,
it makes perfect
sense to be in here.
Still, it's kinda weird
not seeing a single urinal.
Whatever. I'm
here and I'm safe!
Time for calisthenics!
And now a deep inhale!
We need these
in the boys' room.
I've been holding it forever.
Girls!
That cockroach Tomoki must've
crawled back under his rock.
Didn't he get flushed
down the sewers or something?
We should be so lucky!
Are they about to?
This is it! Tomoko's climbing
another step towards adulthood!
So what do you wanna do now?
I couldn't do it. Call me
chicken, but some things should
just stay secret. Yeah.
Guess I'd rather hold fast to
the illusion that girls
have that sweet floral scent.
Not good.
That was too close.
Sohara and the others know
Tomoko's really me!
If they see me, I'm dead!
This is getting ridiculous.
Where could he have run off to?
Too bad, huh? I was looking
forward to some violence.
Let's blow it off.
We should just
clean this
restroom and go home.
Good idea.
Wait a second. Someone's in
the stall over there. Excuse me.
We're about to clean the
restrooms. You mind hurrying up?
Why?! Why is this
happening?! No, wait.
Calm down, Tomoki. Ikaros
is out there with them, too.
Which means I can do this!
Is that...?
Morse code?
G-e-t S-o-h-a-r-a o-u-t
o-f t-h-e b-a-t-h-r-o-o-m...
Get Sohara... out of
the bathroom... right now.
Why-are-you-in-ter-
Why are you...
in-ter... preting.
That's Morse Code.
Yeah, so. Just between us
girls... you don't suppose...
Tomoki's behind that
door coppin' a big squat on
one of our cans? Huh?
That's nuts. Not
even Tomo would be...
Tomo, is that you?
Meow... meow...
It's him!
Incidentally, in my pocket
here, I just happen to have a
saw that will cut through any
lock you might come across.
Thank you very much.
Crap! This bites! I gotta
vamoose! And fast! But how?
They're blocking
the only way out! Yes!
Last chance. Over the top!
Oh, yes. I also strung
barbed wire across the
top and electrified it. It's
kinda like a toilet prison.
You're as prepared as Alpha.
Out of options. I'll
have to make a mad dash
for the door! Oh god!
And I told my boys
to shoot the Hell out of
anyone running toward
that exit who isn't us.
But way more merciless.
End of the road! No way out!
Trapped in a world gone wrong!
If I don't get outta here,
I'm a dead man! Or chick!
But how? How do I escape
when every path is blocked?!
Tomo...
Grandpa?
But I don't want
you to go away, Grandpa!
That'll totally suck!
Sorry, kid. But I'm
going to have to get out of
the country for a while.
Maybe a long while.
But why?
Your grandma.
She found out about my
philanderin' ways again.
I can fix that.
I did it before, 'member?!
It's all good.
For any good woman,
it's water under the bridge.
it's water under the bridge?
That's right.
Your grandma's
a good woman, boy!
In time, it's all
water under the bridge!
Think, Tomo.
What are you, right now?
That's it.
There's my way out!
For any good woman,
it's water under the bridge.
That's right! Because right
now, I am a very fine woman!
Only question is, Grandpa,
can I make it under the bridge?
Yes, you can, you sexy bitch.
No time like the
present. Here goes!
We got 'im!
Um, Sohara. What
the Hell are you doing?
Lesson Four...
Sewage water treatment.
One: Sewage water is recovered
from each house's yard
by a special truck.
This is a long and stinky
process that pays very poorly.
Two: It is carried to a
treatment plant for processing.
Three: The dirty water
passes through dis-in-fe--
machines, until it is finally
made into clean water again.
It's at this point that it
is discharged back out to sea
where the process
starts all over again.
And class... dismissed!
Another pain in
the ass day for Tomoki.
Master, I still need to
talk to you about something.
C'mon, Ikaros! I just told you
this morning about the bathroom!
Knock it off!
Oh, right. First, you knock.
Whoa. She really is learning,
isn't she? If I teach her these
things, one at a time, she'll
actually pick 'em up. Cool.
Knock means...
to hit. No problem.
Also, don't forget to flush.
Master?
Ikaros, hey!
Have you seen Master anywhere?
Oh, dear. He hasn't
gone missing again, has he?
I have something
to discuss with him.
Which is?
Well... it's... his proposal.
Okay, Ikaros... why
don't you take a minute.
I want you to
start at the beginning
and tell me
exactly what happened.
I've been getting
flushed out to sea
a whole lot lately, haven't I?
Oh, good.
Don't wanna be late.
What the Hell?
Ikaros!
Will the groom
please step forward?
Do you vow to love and
honor each other, in sickness
and in health... for as long
as you both shall live...
so help you
God in Heaven above?
I do.
Ikaros...
Okay. Time to seal
your vow with a kiss.
Whoa! Back up a sec!
What's going on here?!
It's a wedding, silly.
I got that. But why?!
Well, see, Ikaros told us you
proposed to her. So go ahead.
Make her an honest woman.
Look, I don't know how
this all got outta hand,
but it's clearly
a misunderstanding.
Seriously, I don't ever
remember proposing to you!
That's too bad,
because I thought this
such an opportunity.
It seemed the perfect time
to bring into the
light everything that's
been hiding in the shadows.
Well? Which one you
gonna choose, Tomoki?
Of course... you could always
stay with Door Number One
and marry Ikaros,
here. But sorry.
This chick is
already spoken for!
You're what?
Tomoki?
What the Hell is this?
When do we get cake? They
promised there would be cake!
So sad, nowhere to run.
This is too much fun.
Master, you're
not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
Look! Over there!
Chaos?
Hi there, mister!
Yet another fine mess
falls right in my lap.
I just want my
peace and quiet back!
So I wonder who
Tomo woulda chosen...
if we didn't get interrupted.
I know Tomoki's
happiness comes first, but...
I still think it'd be nice if
things stayed like
this a while longer.
Yeah, with all of us
enjoying our time together.
Together.
Why is freakin'
everyone in my house?!
What? It's our happy ending!
It's like we're
one big family.
I had some free time,
so I thought I'd stop by.
See how Chaos is doing.
So what do you think?
I have to say, the food's good.
Thank you so much, Ikaros.
She doesn't appear
to be hostile at all.
What do you say you become
her master, too, Tomoki?
Jeez, why me, huh?!
One more won't make
any difference to you.
Anyway... you're going to
be Nymph and Astraea's master.
Isn't that the case?
Oh, yeah. I guess so, huh? But
don't go getting the wrong idea.
Just because I'm your
master, it doesn't mean
I'm going to
fall in love with you.
Guess I should
say... Thank you.
Let's go! Alpha! Delta!