Tomoki, wake up!
Run away! Go as fast as
you can! She's coming for you!
Wait a sec. She who?
Of course. You don't
know who I'm talking about.
I mean... Chaos.
Who's that?
What should we
play next... Mister?
That dream again.
'Bout time you woke up.
How come?
It's raining like crazy. We're
so gonna be late for school.
I wonder if
we'll get a typhoon.
Who cares, how's Ikaros doing?
Your reactor is
definitely out of whack.
I'll run a diagnostic, okay?
How're you holding up, Ikaros?
I'll stay home
with Alpha today.
Somebody should
really keep an eye on her.
Get some rest, okay?
Uh... all right.
Fevers suck.
Take it nice and easy.
Well, be good.
Later, guys.
Who was that... boy?
Huh? Oh, man! Good one.
You really had me
going there for a secon--
We're getting torrential rain,
but only in very specific areas.
It gets weirder.
The typhoon itself
seems to be reversing course.
This is, technically
speaking, impossible.
It's now heading due
south... straight for--
Straight for Sorami. For us.
That's just... creepy.
Huh? It reminds me
of that funky-ass dream.
What dream?
With the angel chick.
She wanted me to run
before something bad got here.
Bad, eh? Like what?
I dunno, she
called it... Chaos?
The storm's moving inland.
We really need to check
this out. It'd be a lot more
helpful if the
Angeloids were around.
What's Astraea,
then? Chopped liver?
Astraea?!
Out you go.
That's a good girl.
Aw... Bye, fridge!
Dude, the weather's ass.
I'm staying in here,
where it's nice and dry.
I think that's
probably a good idea.
If Chaos truly is on her
way here, we shouldn't assume
her target is Ikaros.
It might just be Tomoki.
Tomo... Don't ya
think it's kinda weird?
Not having Ikaros and
Nymph in class with us?
I know, I'm as worried
about Ikaros as you are.
Jackpot!
Dripping wet!
Man, this sucks!
Totally soaked, to the bone!
How come our shirts
have to be white?
Ah, what are we gonna do?!
You can see right through 'em!
Dude, this weather rules!
No Angeloids today
and wet schoolgirls?
What did I do
to get so lucky?
Tomoki, you pervert!
I don't get what's happening.
Your auto-repair program
kicked in by itself,
and it seems to be
erasing your
memories of Tomoki.
Who?
Well... they haven't
all been erased yet.
But, there isn't
any way to cancel the
auto-repair protocol.
If I still had wings...
it'd be a piece of cake.
Without 'em, I don't have
that kind of power anymore.
Anyway, your circuits
are all funky right now.
You're staying in
bed today and that's that.
Merging both satellite feeds.
You can see that we're sitting
very much in the
heart of the storm.
Astraea, dear. Status report?
All clear! And it's windy!
This is... from
when we went to the zoo.
And this... is from
the summer festival.
And this...
This is... This... is my
master... Tomoki Sakurai.
He's... My master... I
don't... want to... lose him.
The times he got mad.
The times he was kind.
I don't wanna
forget any of it!
It's been a while.
You! But... you're dead!
I'm back... and
I'm bigger than before.
There, in the darkest
depths of the ocean,
I learned so much about
love! So very, very much!
Chaos, stop it.
Now I'll teach you three about
love! Here's your first lesson!
Astraea!
How did Chaos
survive the ocean?!
Run away!
Go tell Ikaros
to get over here!
I'll keep her
busy as long as I can!
Yeah? Gotcha. On my way.
What? Say again?
I missed that last part.
What about the "Dive Game?"
Listen! Tomoki! Dive into
your dream! Locate Daedalus!
Huh?
Tell her that Chaos has
evolved! She'll understand!
Evolved?
We'll need your help
to save the Angeloids!
Hurry, there's not
a moment to waste!
I'll do what I can!
Found it.
Wait... Does Sugata want
you to jump into a dream?
I didn't quite get
all the sciency stuff,
but it sounds like the
dookie's hitting the fan.
Here, Sohara. Sugata
wants to talk to you.
Hello? Yeah, no problem.
I've typed a whole bunch of
numbers as student
council treasurer.
Sounds like it's
right up my alley.
Think that did the trick?
Well... gotta go.
This is...
Are you... Daedalus?
Oh, thank goodness!
Yeah! Love hurts, doesn't it!
Delta!
Nymph, no!
Chaos!
Time for a little snack...
It's gonna be hungry work,
teaching you all
about love, Nymph.
Please, come in.
What is this place?
Nymph and Astraea!
I know there are many things
you'd like to ask me, Tomoki,
but right now...
you have to trust me.
That's Chaos. A
second-generation Angeloid.
The poor thing's creator
has twisted her psyche.
You have to stop her.
You're the only one who
stands the slightest
chance. If not...
I am so friggin' fed
up with all this fighting.
I'm sick of the drama.
Forgive me... Tomoki.
Not for myself! This
sucks for them the most!
They enjoy peace and
quiet as much as anyone!
Wearing pretty clothes,
pigging out on snacks,
laughing with friends!
That's what they
deserve. Not this!
You're right.
Give me that!
No, Alpha! No way! You
can't fight. You're too weak!
No... I'm all right.
Listen! If you get hurt
any worse, those memories
are gone forever! All of them!
Are we playing tag?
Almost time.
Right!
I asked Daddy to evacuate all
the locals to someplace safe.
Good.
And Sugata...
How's Ikaros holding up?
Is she still all feverish?
Fighting Chaos before, Ikaros
sacrificed the Hephaestus to
send them both to the bottom of
the ocean. She barely survived.
Chaos is undoubtedly
stronger now. But by how much?!
Nymph, when she attacks
you, analyze the pattern.
Right!
I will use my
Artemis missiles to
blast all of her
wing-blades off.
And then you swoop
in. We get one shot.
Lock on to Chaos and hit her
as hard as you can, Astraea.
Got it!
Alpha. Keep your distance.
If she gets her hands
on you, you're done for.
Look out!
Sensei, no!
Are you all right?!
I'll make you a deal.
If we survive this,
we'll play poker...
whenever you want.
Deal!
Pattern of attack...
identified! Sending!
Transfer of attack
data, complete.
Artemis armed. Engage!
My turn!
Gotcha!
Got you!
Dammit!
Such pathetic rejects.
Killed by a newer toy.
My fallen angels
meet a fitting end.
I bring love.
Do you accept it?
Let them go, Chaos. Now!
Just hang on. Here I come.
I'll... save you both.
Alpha! Stop! You're too
weak to go Uranus Queen Mode!
Are you trying
to kill yourself?!
No, don't! That's my job!
Ikaros!
No more playtime?
Your human master's love has
made you weak, just like him.
"Love..."
I may not know what
that is... No. I do know.
Even if I lose all my memories,
and forget my master forever...
I will fight, until
there's nothing left of me!
To defend Master's life,
and his happiness!
It's so dark at the bottom of
the ocean. There was no one to
play with me. It was lonely.
I was a good girl. I taught
the fishies all about love.
I loved the fishies!
Lots and lots!
I loved them to
pieces! And now, Ikaros...
I'm gonna show
you the same love!
So long, Ikaros.
Stop it!
Don't die, Ikaros!
That's an order, dammit!
You have to obey
your master, right?!
Hey, Nymph! Astraea!
Same for you!
I'll become your master,
if that's what it takes!
I'll boss you
around all damn day!
Tomoki...
Because... I don't
wanna lose any of you.
I admit... sometimes...
you drive me effin' crazy.
But every day is
a brand new adventure.
Every day... is awesome.
So don't even think
about dying, any of you!
Yes... Master.
If you're doing this...
just because I got caught...
I am warning you,
I will so kick your ass!
You better mean it, okay?!
You said "ass." Nice one.
Shut up! My love...
is better than his!
You're too late.
What?
My master gave me an order!
Oh... I'm getting weak. You're
hacking my system, aren't you.
Go, Nymph.
Her wings grew back?
But how?! This is incredible!
They're beautiful!
Please be safe, everybody.
And I was so
close to killing you.
You may think being here with
a kind master made us weak.
Nothing could be
further from the truth.
His kindness is our strength.
And now, Chaos... you are going
to witness it... firsthand!
Why are you all lying to me?!
Ikaros, you only sent me down
to the bottom of the ocean
because you love me, right?!
'Cause love is pain.
And there was so much of it,
down there in the darkness. I
was so lonely. I was terrified.
But now, I've returned so
I can love you all right back!
I'm gonna love you
until there's nothing left!
Nymph! Do you read me?!
Loud and clear!
Chaos's post-evolution
attack strength is unknown.
The three of you will have
to orchestrate a group attack
in order to take her out.
What do you have in mind?
Turn up your hacking field
as high as it will go, and do a
one-time rewrite of Ikaros and
Astraea's ability programming.
I'm uploading battle
tactics via your data stream.
'Kay! We'll give it our all.
Hacking field up!
Full power!
What?
Alpha!
Variable Wing Safety:
Release! Artemis: Full Fire!
That won't work twice!
Artemis missiles can track
their target pretty well.
That's why I hacked
into their homing code,
to make sure every one
of 'em landed a direct hit!
Your turn, Delta!
Right!
She can maybe beat
all of us one-on-one.
But together,
we're non-stoppable!
Die, you little...
Bedtime, Chaos!
Aegis: Engage!
That hurt. It hurts,
it hurts, it hurts.
Because... you all
love me so very much!
Please, hurt me some more!
This time, you're goin' down!
Oh thank you, Astraea!
Down, I say!
Thank you! I loved
hundreds of fish and birds to
get strong enough
to come back up here,
but 'til now there
was nobody to love me back.
Yes! 'Cause you're
gonna love me to death!
Love me to death! Love me
to death! Love me to death!
What are you waiting
for, huh? Somebody love me!
Love me until I'm just
a smear in this crater.
Love me to pieces!
It's okay now.
Mister?
Guess you've had
a pretty rough time, huh?
I really wish I had played
with you that day at the park.
I'm sorry.
What's happening?
My chest hurts.
But it's different than
the other hurt. It's warm.
How come? What is
this feeling? It's so...
Thought I told
you to take it easy.
Still... You
rocked today. A lot.
Whoa... Ikaros!
Next time... "Forte Wings
Soaring for Tomorrow"