Watch out...
She is coming... A new angel.
That... dream?
Good morning to you, Master.
Are you awake yet?
Of course I am! Do I have
to tell you every morning
not to scare me like that?!
Stop straddling him, Alpha.
And Tomoki, you
should be awake already.
What's that?
Uh... What do you
want me to say here?
Good morning, Tomoki!
Sohara!
Are you up? We have
school, you know.
Aw, crap!
If Sohara sees me like this,
she'll kill me without thinking
twice about it. What
the Hell am I gonna do?!
Ikaros, you gotta shoot me!
Right now!
Shoot me in the jimmy!
Shoot you in your what?
Tomoki...
Ikaros! Shoot me!
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Eishiro Sugata.
And these here are my assist--
Aw... Sugata...
These are all your
previous assistants,
aren't they? The Pretties?
Anyway, the mysterious
black hole, which appeared
in the sky over Sorami
recently, remains there,
its true nature
still unknown to us all.
However... Last year
during Christmas...
I witnessed the anomaly
with my own eyes.
The New World
does indeed exist
on the other side
of this black hole.
Congratulations!
It's a little rub-on transfer
I had designed. I figure I can
sell these babies off
at a thousand yen a pop.
Like I was going to say,
what we have to do now is
find a doorway that
leads to the New World.
If we peruse human history, we
can see giant structures built
in the distant past that also
depicted paths into a New World.
For example, this is a mural
within one of the pyramids--
Tomo! Come on! You better get a
move on or we're gonna be late.
Here. At least drink
your milk before we go.
You, too, Nymph
and Ikaros. Drink up.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sohara.
Cool. Forget anything?
Nope. I'm all good.
Let's get outta here.
Little refresher.
We live in Sorami City.
It's a small place, about
seven thousand people...
and it's completely
surrounded by mountains.
It's nice. The town isn't known
for anything in particular.
If it was, it'd be the smile
on the old farmer's face.
Or maybe that huge
four-hundred-year-old
cherry blossom
tree that sits on
the gorgeous hill
right outside of town.
That all changed of course...
the day when Ikaros
fell out of the sky.
Not long after that, Nymph
showed up. She pretty much put
the final nail in the coffin
of my days of peace and quiet.
Oh well... C'est la vie.
Lately, I've actually gotten
used to living like this.
Far as I'm concerned, as long
as nothing else goes screwy,
I'm totally cool. 'Cause
nothing beats peace and quiet.
Am I right?
I am so sorry. Dragging you
back into this is the last thing
I wanted. But you have to
watch out... for the angel.
Take good care
of her... Will you?
She's trapped... by the sky.
They've returned?
Yeah, that stupid dream again.
I hadn't had one in a long time,
so I'd almost forgotten
what they were like.
But after so
long without one,
it felt, I don't
know, kinda weird.
Having a weird dream shouldn't
be a big deal to you anymore.
You're old enough to be
experiencing certain feelings--
I can assure you, Prez,
it was not that kinda dream.
Oh gosh, Tomo. You mean
it's those same dreams
you used to have all the time?
I'm sure it's your desire
to go to the New World that's
caused you to have this dream
again. When you repress things,
dreams are
where they pop up.
Nuh-uh!
Somewhere deep in
your subconscious you've
finally started to realize
that you are a member of
the New World Discovery Club.
That's all this is, Tomoki.
No, it's not!
Hey, what if
we did that thing?
Everyone did it all the time
in the Synapse a while back.
Remember that thing?
But... it could be dangerous.
What's dangerous?
What are you talking about?
The Dive... Game.
The Dive Game, you say?
What the heck is that?
Exactly what it sounds like.
It's a game where we would
dive into a person's dreams.
It was pretty popular.
Everybody up there
liked playing it.
What's the... Synapse?
Stop there! I forgot
to mention that all
Synapse-related questions
are strictly forbidden.
Those files are locked
away, classified top-secret!
And you're better
off not knowing.
Better off not knowing?
That's right. So... What
do you think? If you play
the Dive Game, you'll be able
to go inside Tomoki's dream.
You wanna?
Initializing connection.
Ring Gate... Open.
You guys be careful
on the other side.
Be careful of what?
What? You and
Ikaros aren't coming?
You know very well...
that Angeloids can't sleep.
Dreams are somewhat
of a taboo for us.
Master, please, just...
use caution on the other side.
'Kay.
'Kay, here goes! Your next
stop, Tomoki's dreamscape!
Oh, wow!
Just as vast and empty as
I expected his head to be.
Well, what do you
think we should do first?
Well, usually, it starts off
having this blue-haired chick
with wings soaring up to me.
Oh... There she is. Hey, lady!
Or not...
Oh-god-oh-god-oh-god!
Not her! Not her!
You really like 'em
big, don't you, Tomoki?!
Run faster!
Is that a female?
Man! I thought we were dead!
Wow, you've got the
dreams of a crazy person!
No I do not! This is
not my freakin' dream!
I'm afraid... this is the
dream I had last night, Tomoki.
Yeah, slight
miscalculation on my part.
There was nothing slight
about it, you bonehead!
You don't have to be
such a jerk about it.
I made an honest mistake.
I will be such a jerk!
I almost died!
Least I found a nice souvenir.
Made it worth the trouble.
Like what?
Wait. That's a crystal from the
cave we were just trapped in.
Hello, my precious. You
must be worth a boatload.
Once I cash you in, I'll
never have to work again.
Not another
day the rest of my--
Where'd it go?
Did I forget that part?
You won't be able to
bring anything
back from a dream.
Since that's where it comes
from, that's where it stays.
Too bad, so sad.
Okay people, let's
reconnect to Tomoki's dream.
Have a safe trip.
Better'n last time I hope!
What is this awful place?!
You mean this isn't
your dream, either?
Not even close!
Incoming!
Get 'em boys!
Suck on this.
That's right.
Sayonara, bitches.
This was my dream, everybody!
Nymph, help us! We're in the
dream of the one person whose
dreams we should absolutely
stay the Hell out of!
Get us out of here!
Straight into another this time.
Is this one yours, Tomoki?
Oh, no!
Hmmm... Whose is
it this time, then?
What's your deal?
Oh, nothing!
Terrible! Just terrible! We've
landed smack in the middle of
the dream I had last night!
Which means, oh god,
it's that dream!
We should probably
start by looking around.
Why not?
No! They wouldn't!
Wanna take a bath with me,
you twisted little thing?
Sohara...
Tomo, you're
such a little horndog!
You're so hot...
Oh, get your fingers
out of there! That tickles!
What is your problem, creep-o?
How could you possibly
have such a sick dream?!
But... This isn't...
This isn't mine...
What's wrong with that damaged
little head of yours that
it would imagine
such deviance?
Come on up here,
my sexy boo-boo...
I swear. Totally
not my dream at all.
Fore!
Sugata?
Yes?
Sometimes, you just can't
help what you dream about,
am I right?
Am I right or not?!
Yes.
Stop it, you dirty little man!
Get that ass back here, baby!
You know I need some of that!
What are people gonna
say?! Get away from me!
Come on, baby!
Tickets please! Tickets
please! Tickets please!
Can't catch me, Mr. Bear!
Aw! Gimme your
goo-goo ga-ga, honey!
Lemme show you what I mean by
"busted!" Assume the position!
Say my name!
Uh... Check please.
I'm ready to go.
I want you to
listen here, Tomoki.
In life, you gotta
always dream big.
Dream big?
Yes. As big as you can.
Your grandpa here
dreamed big, too, you know.
Yeah, I dreamed
before I left this earth,
I'd take all the girlies
of the world to bed.
Only two billion, nine hundred
and fifty-seven million,
two hundred and
seventy-two thousand,
six hundred sixteen to go!
Grandpa!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
And to think, I was so
close, too. Listen, Tomo...
Be sure to dream. And
when you do... Dream big!
Grandpa!
So, what's the
verdict, your honor?
Can we go to my dream now?
Hold that thought
for one moment.
I have a feeling I need
to check something here.
There's some kind of block
on Tomoki's dreamscape!
Did you say a block?
For a dream, it sure
has a lot of nerve.
But I'll hack this thing!
Master, please stop. The Dive
Game is not meant for humans.
Huh? Why not?
Well, Master... It's...
There we go!
Hacking complete.
This time, I'm absolutely
positive it's Tomoki's!
Right... let's do this.
Whoa, Tomo. This is
what your dream looks like?
I guess we finally made it.
This is wrong!
Wait, we're still not there?
No! My dream is always
on this lush, grassy field.
Not some stark barren void!
I mean, c'mon,
look at this place!