I see. Somehow Tomoki's
dream connected to
this "Synapse" place
you're talking about.
And when it did,
your people sensed danger
and made the decision
to kill Tomoki.
What do I do? It was an accident
but I gave away secret info
while I was restarting. Gotta
think of a brilliant plan!
Ooh!
That was weird, I was
totally talking in my sleep!
What did I say?
I thought
Angeloids didn't sleep.
Oh, poopie, you knew
that? Okay, gimme a sec.
Let's see, I was just, um...
What you meant to say was that
the "New World" is hovering
in the sky above Sorami?
New World? What do you mean?
It's not a New World,
stupid, it's the Synap--
Does the "Rule" refer
to the chinquapin tree
that Tomoki saw in his dream?
Of course not! The Rule's
that big stone thing
with all the
writing on it. Duh!
Oh... Thanks for telling me.
Crap! He got even more secret
info out of me! That's it!
I have no choice!
I have to kill him now!
He dodged me!
Wait! What are you doing?!
That's interesting to hear.
That you've come to our world to
kill our good friend Tomoki. Are
you listening to me, Astraea?
Yes, please forgive me!
Pay careful attention to me now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I've decided to help you out!
Mikako, you've got that look
on your face you get every time
you find yourself a new toy.
You should know, he can be
quite a formidable opponent.
I knew it! You have to
tell me his secret weakness!
Let's see... First things first.
You're going to need to learn
the ancient martial
arts of your new home.
Wow! They've got
so many stands this year!
Give me a bite of
your cotton candy.
I wonder if Tomoki
remembers that time.
Where's Mikako?
I haven't seen her.
Supposedly she's been
out here all day setting up.
Something about an
event for this evening.
Really?
Wanna see?
It's right over there.
Oh, hell no. I remember
this d-bag from last year.
Almost got me killed. I got
a bad feeling about this.
Such a fun festival.
This makes two years in a row.
Let me go! You lunatic,
get your hands off me!
Unclench and relax,
Tomoki. It's not like
everybody's cleaning
their guns so we can have
a shootout in the
woods like last year.
In fact, I've done some
reflecting. Originally,
a festival was a holy gathering,
to showcase the glory of God.
This year I thought we'd be a
bit more dignified and hold...
our first sumo tournament.
Sumo... tournament?
Wra-ssa-lin'.
This is it. The legendary fall
tournament... begins right now!
In round one, we've
got the Madonna of the
shopping district. Daughter
of the stationery store owner!
And with the access she has to
colored pencils, she's sure to
turn the white ring red!
The Pencil Madonna, Makiko!
The grand prize is a
cool ten million yen!
Plus, a once in a
lifetime chance to
share a bath with the
Satsukitane family's geisha!
Guess they found a reason
for me to take this seriously.
And now, walking definition
of "genuine article!"
I will now show you a mask...
the likes of which
has never been seen!
Mask du Pants!
As official representative
of the Satsukitane family
I hereby declare the
first Satsukitane Cup
Fall Tournament
as open! Good luck!
I'm your play-by-play announcer,
gym coach Taizo Matsuyama!
Color commentary
by Eishiro Sugata...
and our special guest, Nymph.
What does sumo taste like?
Sumo is a sport
and this isn't it.
Nope! We're doing
this by American rules!
Right. And we're
bringing it live.
While heavily favored to win,
Sohara and her patented killer
chop will be stepping
in as this year's referee.
And we're sorry we won't
get to see her compete.
Well, this first round is going
to be one for the record books!
Sugata, what's your take?
The data I've accumulated
states that Makiko was in the
amateur wrestling club
during her high school days.
So is it salty or sweet?
It's Makiko with
the first strike.
Oh, and she lands an incredible
tackle, right into the ropes!
Oh, and she's up in the air
for a head-slam to the mat!
And just like that,
we have a pin!
Mask du Pants is
one pathetic wrestler!
One... two... thr--
What happened? She
stopped the three-count
right before she was done!
I honestly don't know.
Noooooooo!
He's groping her!
Oh, the humanity!
Pants is groping Makiko!
I... I... I give up!
Makiko just
threw in the towel!
That's one way to grab a win.
Though he won the match,
the women of the audience are
booing Pants as
he leaves the ring.
Not making any
friends out there.
Gotta come up with something
real killer while I still can.
Nymph! Come here a sec!
Yeah, Tomoki, what's up?
Please, you gotta turn on
your Cool Guy Jamming for me!
If you do, I'll buy you anything
you want later. I swear! 'Kay?
Anything I want, huh?
Okay, I'll do it.
Ladies!
Holy crap, it's Mask du Pants!
So dreamy!
Kick ass. Now the chicks
won't be against me anymore.
I love you, Mask du Pants!
Thanks! And what
color are your panties?
Get bent, cockroach!
What the Hell just happened?
I turned it off.
I turned the
Cool Guy Jamming off!
Why did you do
something stupid like that?!
I hate it.
I hate it! I hate it!
I hate it! I just hate it!
Sheesh, what's up her butt?
Moving on to round two.
In the red corner,
the unsmiling beast, Ikaros!
And in the blue corner, that
guy from the takoyaki stand!
That ten million
yen is mine, baby!
Okay, Ikaros, you got him!
And the referee
halts the match!
I'd call this a very
decisive win for Ikaros!
In this round, Sugata steps in
the ring, who until a moment ago
was sitting comfortably in his
commentator's chair. No way!
He's already in a tight spot!
The man's face is being crushed!
This does not look good!
He's down! Mikako just
wasted Sugata and he was
the one favored
to win the round!
That's a gripping
power of 400 kilos.
Unbelievable, Nymph!
Once your face is caught
in something
like that, lights out!
I had a hunch it would be
like this. Prez sets up some
grandiose prize just to snatch
the whole thing for herself.
Well, I ain't
gonna let that happen!
Hope you're ready in there,
Astraea, because you're up next.
Are you sure about this outfit?
That is the proper costume
for age-old Japanese combat,
worn for generations.
Now, get out there
and jack up
Tomoki something fierce.
I want his face
to look like sausage!
Right!
I'm looking, and I don't
see too many matches left
on tonight's docket.
Sugata, any comments?
It seems Mikako is the
clear favorite at this point.
It would be a shock to
us all if she didn't win.
Seriously, what
does it taste like?
Ladies and gentlemen! It's
time to change things up a bit.
The next round will
be a tag-team match
with four combatants.
The rules are simple.
Whoever wins advances to
the final round
and battles for victory.
Good gravy, folks! We got
an elimination match! Sugata?
Sounds like it. We just
need to know who's competing?
What's this? Are we looking
at a shot of the changing room?
You're here to give these
people a good show, all right?
Go on, give it a shot.
Mother of pearl! Are
you trying to kill him?!
I apologize.
If you have a weak stomach, this
is the time to exit the arena!
'Cause we just don't know
what these two will pull!
In the red corner,
Mask du Pants and Ikaros!
And now it's time we introduce
a mysterious new contender!
Hailing from Mongolia, raised
in a poor farming village,
this secret weapon has
entered the tournament to
support her family! Greetings
from the land of the loincloth!
In the blue corner, the
mysterious sumo wrestler...
Delta Yama!
What are you
doing up there, Delta?
Solly! I no speaky
you clazy ranguage.
The question that remains is who
will be Delta Yama's partner?
Having to stand ground against
those other two, I don't know.
Nymph, would you like
to enter the tournament?
Don't stare at me
like that, you dumb-bug!
This fruit isn't ripe yet!
Soap opera fanatic...
Sorami's idol... it's Nymph!
Time for you to
hop in the ring, Nymph.
I bet Tomoki will be more
than thrilled to fight you.
Maybe I will enter the fight.
And so, the tag-team match
of the century has begun!
At the top, it's Pants
toe-to-toe with Delta Yama!
Look at that! Yama unleashes
a weapon right out of the gate!
I wouldn't really
worry about that.
And she takes herself out!
Gropey, gropey,
gropey, gropey...
This is terrible!
Pants has slipped into the
same obscene
attack we saw before!
No more of that!
Gropey, gropey, gropey...
The referee is
putting a stop to this!
Back off, Miss Ref. It's
not like I'm breaking any
tournament rules here, am I?
Your thoughts, Sugata?
Technically, the move is not
illegal, so not even the referee
can prevent him from performing
it. He's in the clear.
No.
Check out Pants
getting his grope on!
This man isn't letting
up his attack one bit!
His hands are
crawling all-- Whoa!
She's got a sword in the ring!
Master is in danger.
Ejection! Ejection!
Now we're down to
just two combatants.
Seems to be something
wrong with Pants...
I'm not really feeling
it. Not against those.
You jerk!
Whoa! Is that a Cobra Twist?
Actually it's an "abdominal
stretch," also known as
the "grapevine hold."
Well? You give up?
Not yet, baby!
Ha! I got you now!
Ladies and gents,
Nymph has fled the ring!
Which means Mask du Pants
is moving on to the final round!
Thank you very much!
Hey, how's it goin', Nymph?
Sorry about earlier.
It's all part of the show,
so no hard feelings, eh?
My reactor is acting funny
again. I'm an Angeloid,
and yet... I feel as if...
I've fallen... in love.
This is it! Who
will be victorious?
This'll be his last day
on Planet Freakin' Earth!
Take this loser to town, Prez!
Mask du Pants is
taking the whole thing!
M.D.P.! M.D.P.!
The final championship
bout... begins now!
Ladies and gentlemen, the moment
you've all been waiting for!
Today's main event! And here
comes our first finalist...
In the blue corner, the Grinning
Gangstress, Mikako Satsukitane!
President! President!
President! President! President!
Mikako!
And, in the red corner...
The Undertaker of Underwear,
Mask du Pants!
Hooray. Hooray for you, Master.
You pervert!
Go nipples!
Illegal object!
You wanna check inside my pants,
feel free to stick your hand in.
I don't mind if we
break the rules a little.
And now here's a
little gift from me to you.
It's a chain-link
deathmatch, folks.
What should we be
looking for in this fight?
Basically, however Pants decides
to counter Mikako's Iron Claw
will be the determining
factor in this match.
We're now joined by
our guest, Ikaros, who has
completed her matches and
is now petting a watermelon.
Correct.
Whoa! Looks as if Pants
has already been seized!
Well, this is disappointing!
Now, Mikako's victory
is all but assured!
Sesame oil! M.D.P. has
drenched himself in sesame oil!
Huh. Not a bad tactic.
Thanks. Now prepare
for a whuppin'!
Pants launches into
a ferocious attack,
relentlessly grabbing
for Mikako's ample bosom!
But Mikako slips on some
of the spilled sesame oil!
You're mine now!
Tomoki, you have
crossed the line.
Pants is behaving
like a twisted savage!
And look at the ladies.
They're completely mortified.
Behind her is an
electrified chain-link fence!
No joke, Mikako's
really in a tight spot now!
Hold on...
Somewhere during the match,
the referee has disappeared.
Up there.
Everyone look to the sky!
A mysterious masked wrestler
has appeared from nowhere!
Heh! Long as this
chain-link fence is in place,
ain't nobody gonna
stick their no--
Boom! Through the
chain-link with her bare hands!
Flying body press!
Ooh! She's slaughtering
him with a double attack of
flying chops and electricity!
She's reaching, oh,
to catch him in mid-air, oh,
and performs an
Argentine Backbreaker!
I'm... not so sure that
Pants' spine is supposed to
bend that way. His people
might wanna call a doctor.
He won't be able to
stand up again after that.
What's this?
Unbelievable! After
taking a furious beating,
what is it driving this
young man to get back up?
I... wanna soap
you up... all over...
And the referee steps in
to lift the masked wrestler's
hand in the air! But why?
This makes no sense!
Pants is still on his feet!
That's true.
But he's already dead.
So, you alive again?
Who ends up walking
away the winner then?
If he died during the
match, it must be that
mysterious masked wrestler.
Which would be you, Sohara.
I have no idea what
you're talking about!
I was backed into a corner,
too. So why don't we just say
the winner was Tomoki?
Are you serious?!
As a heart attack.
Kick ass! Ten million in prize
money! And a bath with geishas!
If that's settled...
Ladies and gentlemen, presenting
the World Championship Final!
Wrestling is bullshit.
Come on! Let's you and
I play us a little game.
First... Tell me, when
people die, where do they go?
Please... Don't come back
next year. I really never wanna
see you again,
you crazy gun-nut!
Man, a lot
happened in one night,
but the festival
was fun, wasn't it?
Are you sure
that's all you wanted?
I said I'd get you anything.
And I do keep my promises.
'Cause the last time
you had a candy apple,
you said they
were gross tasting.
You remember that?
Course, you cried
over it like a baby.
But I do like them.
Candy apples.
I like them a lot!
Hey, Tomoki, aren't
you going to have one, too?
Nah, I already had a bunch of
takoyaki and other junk today.
You don't eat a
lot of sweets, do you?
Not really.
Next time... "Mortal Combat!
Hot Spring Snowball
Fight at 1.4° Below"