What is love? You and Tomoki
Sakurai, you love each other,
don't you, Nymph?
Well, don't you? C'mon, tell!
Oh... Drat. You can't, because
he doesn't love you, does he?
Of... course! How could he love
a wingless nothing like you?
What a greedy little
Angeloid you are, Nymph.
Tomoki is Ikaros's master.
You had better leave
my Tomoki alone, you tramp.
You know I've
always hated you, right?
No, you're wrong! They
wouldn't say that! Just shut up!
Shut up. Shut up!
High time we took
you to the junkyard.
You can't even fly.
You're such a waste.
No!
Damaged goods.
We're gonna sell you for scrap.
Such a waste!
Broken toy! Such a waste!
No!
Thanks for tagging along.
I know shopping's a drag.
Hey, no sweat. I'll even let
you pick up the bill for lunch
to make it up to me.
Huh?!
So! What's on
the menu tonight?
Croquettes!
Yeah!
Oh, guess what! You're not gonna
believe this, but Ikaros can
go shopping all by
herself now! Crazy, huh!
I'm really proud of her!
Whoa. No kidding?
You remember when Astraea
first showed up here,
how she was always trying
her best to destroy you?
These days, you
guys are pretty tight.
Of course... the one
who's improved the most
has gotta be Nymph.
I mean, when she first showed
up, there was something kinda
scary about her,
wasn't there? And now...
She seems a lot...
I dunno... happier.
Whatever you've been
doing, keep it up.
Huh? What're ya talking
about? I haven't done crap.
But... you know... this peace
and quiet? I am diggin' it.
Ditto.
Sohara and... Master?
How is he here?
Damn it! Ow, let go!
You lying freak!
I'm so gonna kick your ass!
Do you hear me? You are dead!
You... piece of turd!
Shut your trap,
you broken-down toy!
Nooo!
What do we do?
They perfected a
second-generation Angeloid.
"Second-generation" how?
That creature is
far more powerful
than the originals I created.
You invented Angeloids?!
But she... is in a
class totally unto herself.
Huh?
Hi, Ikaros! I was
hoping you'd show up.
I'm not broken! I'll kill you.
Tear you to shreds. Kill you!
Oh, Nymph.
You will pay. Variable
wing safety: disengage.
Enemy located: Target lock.
Artemis missile--
Master...
Damn it! Why can't she see
that she's being manipulated?!
You coward!
Ikaros. Blow Nymph to
pieces. That's an order.
An... order?
Bye, Nymph.
No! Alpha!
Run away!
Hey, now. What's
the big idea, Ikaros?
Did you... just
disobey my command?
I am sorry to
disappoint you, Master.
But I am unable
to destroy Nymph.
What are you?
I am...
Your Angeloid, Master.
Type Alpha. Ikaros.
Now, please order
me as you will.
Well, for punishment...
you can destroy yourself.
Start with your right arm.
Master.
What the heck was that?
You think they're doing
construction
nearby or somethin'?
I gotta head out.
Thanks for the ramen, Sohara.
O... kay?
Gotta... help Alpha.
She needs me.
Gotta help.
Yeah, right. Why don't I
just fly right back there?
"Nymph, I really wanna become
your master," she says to me.
I so fell for it.
How'm I supposed to help
Alpha? I'm not even any good
in a fight. Just a wingless...
Piece of trash!
Why would anyone...
ever bother taking me in?!
Nymph, is that you?
Delta...
Whoa, what happened
to your face?!
Go help, Alpha! She's gonna
die if you don't! Please go!
What? Wh-What are
you talking about?!
She has to be
going through Hell!
And it's all because of me!
Fine! I'm going then! I have
no idea why, but whatever!
Hold it, Delta.
Kill the Beta for me.
That's an order.
Stupid girl. You thought
you had gotten away from me?
You'll remain my toy...
for as long as you live.
What's wrong,
good-for-nothing?
Have you forgotten
what comes next?
This is the
part where you beg,
"Oh please, Master.
Please don't scrap me!"
You have your orders, Delta.
Hop to it. Start by chopping off
her limbs. And after
that, rearrange her face.
I obey, Master!
I don't wanna do this, Nymph.
But Master gave me an order!
I have no choice!
Don't worry about it. It's
okay. Angeloids do what their
masters tell 'em.
Simple as that.
My living here has been like...
a dream. But I'm an Angeloid.
We're not even supposed
to... have dreams.
I'm sorry!
Don't you dare!
Tomoki...
Who says Angeloids
don't get to dream?
Who says an Angeloid can't
tell her master to go shove it?
Who cares about wings?
You're fine without 'em!
Enjoying candy apples,
or having a good cry, or...
thinking zoo animals are cute.
Nothing's wrong
with any of that.
Well... yeah, but...
You're great.
Just how you are.
I am? Really? Tomoki!
Thank you, Tomoki!
Astraea.
That day... at the snowball
fight. I asked if you were
gonna kill me because
you actually wanted to.
So make up your mind!
What is it that you wanna do?!
Delta!
U-Uh... Y-Yes... Master?
Deal with that insect later.
Chaos is still toying with
the Uranus Queen. Go. Slice
our dear Ikaros to ribbons.
Uh... I obey, Master.
I swear... I'm gonna come
back and kill you both!
Knew that blast
wasn't construction.
I got a bad feeling...
that won't be the last of 'em.
That jerk! What's
his deal, anyway?!
Make up your mind! What
is it that you wanna do?!
Ikaros and Nymph
don't give a crap about
the Synapse now 'cause of him!
How'd they fall for that
dumb bug?! Humans are trash!
All they're good for is
smashing and chopping up!
He's so dead! He's goin' down!
Oh, look.
Oh, balls! I'm starting
to like him, too!
Astraea likes someone?
Y-- I mean no! I mean yes,
but I don't "like him" like him!
Quit babbling, Delta! Destroy
the Uranus Queen, immediately!
You listen when I
am talking to you!
Make up your mind!
I am ordering you!
Shut up!
You broke your own chain,
Astraea. Naughty, naughy!
Hey... Can you tell me?
Is that what love is?!
I don't know what
love is! I'm stupid, okay?!
But... just now...
I decided for myself!
What the?!
I don't know...
but I think it's
gonna get bloody.
So that's the second-generation?
Chaos, type Epsilon.
Can Astraea defeat
her in battle?
The Delta... is dumb.
Not the wording I
would have chosen, but--
I boosted her emotive
and combat abilities...
at the expense of
her computational skills.
True. I could have
found a way to give her
something more to
work with upstairs.
But I didn't... because it
wouldn't've made a difference.
Delta's wings are designed
for hyper-acceleration.
She's the fastest
Angeloid in existence.
That's not all. She's equipped
with the Aegis-L Shield.
Wow...
And the hyper-vibration
photon sword, Chrysaor.
My Delta wields the
greatest weapon and shield
of any Angeloid.
She's no tactician,
but in hand-to-hand
combat, she's unstoppable.
You caught me off-guard
for a sec! It's fine.
I'll kill you from far away!
I can't block
these much longer!
Delta isn't equipped with
any long-range weapons.
If Chaos keeps
that distance...
She's done for.
I can't let her win! I finally
made up my mind for myself!
I'm finally doing what I want!
This was fun. But it's
time to say "bye-bye."
Huh?
Sorry, playtime's
over... Chaos.
Ikaros, you're okay!
Aw, no fair. How'd you
get better so quick, Ikaros?
I know! You fixed yourself,
huh! And you did it in the
short time I've been playing
with Astraea? That's so neat!
Your toy is ginormous! But guess
what! Two can play at that game!
Whoa! No way!
Try grabbin' this!
Oh, no! That brat
just cut its arm right off!
I'm not done yet!
Ikaros, no!
You don't wanna play?
Then it's nap-time!
Go!
Increasing speed to Mach
Ten... 11... 12... 13... 14...
Why did you hit
me with your toy?
15... Mach 16... 17...
This is messed up, Ikaros.
Why're you doing this to me?
My master... swims very well.
What?
Angeloids sink like a stone. As
you're about to learn... Chaos!
Current depth.
Twenty-two hundred...
twenty-three hundred...
passing twenty-three fifty.
We're going down to the
bottom of the ocean, huh,
just you and me! I
hope you thought ahead!
I do not intend
to survive. But...
If my death will stop
you! I am ready to die!
Before we break,
tell me a bedtime story.
About what love is.
Yeah! I wanna know what love
is! Please tell me what it is!
Tell me! What is love?!
I do not know.
I can't tell you...
because I do not know myself.
But... whenever I think about
Master... my reactor hurts.
It aches. I can't
help it! But why?!
Why does the mere thought
of it make my reactor ache?!
Is... Is that what
love is? I don't know!
You're crying?
If I were to let you go now...
you'll definitely hurt my
master. The thought of harm
coming to him...
hurts worse than anything!
I die... to protect
my master! That I know!
Aw, Ikaros, no fair.
C'mon, c'mon,
where are you?!
Ikaros!
Astraea.
Huh?
Can you tell me?
Do you know what love is?
Huh?! Well you know
it's--! It's like um...
C'mon you know what it is!
I am sorry. But I don't.
I have never
known... what love is.
I'm just... I'm just like her.
Please. I want
to go see Master now.
'Kay, all done.
Thanks, Sohara.
♪Ouchie, ouchie... go away!♪
There you go,
Nymph, good as new.
I wish you could sing that and
magic me up a new pair of wings.
Nymph, listen. If
you're still bummed out--
In this household, we don't
come through the roof like...
Sugata! I'm glad you're okay!
What's all the
shouting about this time?
Tomoki's new skylight.
...looking for food.
Am I right? Am I right?
Come on! Can't you use the
front door like normal people?!
But, since you're back safe and
sound... I'm gonna let it slide.
Yes... Master.
Next time...
"Shoot-out! Fishing at the
Jumbo Carnival of Dreams"