What's all the fuss about?
Dude... let's go check it out.
Who is that? What
is she doing? Gross.
Oh, Astraea, no.
What were you doing
out there, Delta?!
I was hungry. I had to eat.
Oh, don't worry about it.
But, as long as you're here...
Maybe it's time we made an
addition to the student body.
No way in Hell!
That's just one more way to
stir up trouble in my
life! I won't allow it!
Come on, how about
a one day trial?
And she should join
the same class as Tomoki.
Oh, yes. This will make
a lovely social experiment.
And you'd look adorable
in a uniform, Astraea.
All right, fine.
We don't have much time
before class starts, so Ikaros,
you're up. Show Astraea
where the locker room is.
Yes... Master.
What are you up
to this time, Tomoki?
Yeah, wha-- Tomoki?
It's been too long
since I showed up!
My name's Tomoko! And
that's the quantum converter
Sohara broke a while ago.
Ikaros was nice enough to
fix it for me, so I'm
gonna take it on a test run.
Hi... So... you ready?
What?
It's one of the rules we have
at this school. The first thing
we do with each new student
is conduct a full physical exam.
Oh... Well, if
that's what you do.
That's what we do.
Let's start with your hips.
You mind spinning
around for me?
Okay.
Oh, I'm so sorry
my hand slipped!
I apologize. But since we're
both girls, there's no shame
in a little accident, right?
Yeah, right.
Good, so next
we'll do your bust.
To Hell with her waist!
Boobies! Boobies! Boobies!
Oopsie! My hands slipped again!
Ooh! These suckers might
be as nice as Sohara's!
Hey!
What are you doing to her?
You're such an a-hole! Ahhh!
My name is Astraea.
Of all the foods I've eaten,
rice balls are my favorite.
She has wings.
Oh how cute.
Be nice to the
transfer student.
It's never easy being
the new kid in town.
All right. So the
answer to question two...
So hey, Ikaros. Astraea's
a bit too dumb for this class.
Why don't you teach
her something else,
so she doesn't
slow everyone down?
Yes, Master.
You have three apples
and four oranges.
How many total pieces of--
I eat all of them!
Okay, let's move
on. Seven bananas--
I eat all of 'em!
I still have this nasty poison.
I'll kill Tomoki
this time for sure!
Astraea.
You wanna give these a taste?
You're always hungry, right?
She likes me!
She really likes me!
Don't mind if I do!
It's like a
party! In my mouth!
Finally, class is over.
Time to mosey on home.
Hold it, Sakurai!
You've got detention.
Or, have you
forgotten already...
about your last test score?
So uh... What
are you guys in for?
Spanish class is
freakin' killing me.
I was bored and
this seemed interesting.
You're not here because
you're behind in a class,
are you, Prez?
That's precisely why.
Whoa? What subject would
you have trouble in?
Ethics, of all things.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Still, I'd hate
to be you, Tomoki.
What? Why would you say that?
Oh, goodness. You haven't
heard. 'Cause of this.
"Boys at Sorami High That You'd
Like As Your Boyfriend Survey."
Look at the bottom. Because
that's where your name
seems to have fallen.
Aw, look! He's unpopular,
and he's stupid. Poor dumbass.
What's your guys'
freakin' problem?
You are always peeping
on the girls' locker room.
What makes you think
you'd be popular with them?
So what? You're against me?
Maybe you should go
back to kindergarten
and learn to
not be such a tool.
Sha! As if! I'm still way
cooler than a kindergartner!
I'd be sixth grade, at least!
And you dingbats'd be
lucky to make fifth!
Pretty sure you're
way dumber than us.
No way!
Yes way!
Hey, Miss Ikaros.
I need to know, how do you
read this character right here?
Talk about dumb
enough for kindergarten!
Astraea's behind
on her first day?
Yes, in every subject.
Dum-dum!
You're the dumb one,
ya freakin' cockroach.
Yeah, you lowlife pervert!
What did you call me?!
Sounds to me like we need
to set this record straight.
If you'd like, I can
throw together a little
competition on
the grounds outside.
Hell yeah. You do that.
You dumb chicks'll see
that I really am smart!
I'll show you!
I'll show all of you!
Ladies and gentlemen, it's
time now for the first ever
Smart-Kid Championship
Quiz Show. I'm your host...
known all around town as Eishiro
"New World or Bust" Sugata.
And I am his assistant,
Ikaros, the one who
made up all the questions.
Now then, to explain the rules
of the game. The quiz questions
will be answered by
whoever buzzes in first.
If the contestant answers
correctly, that person's seat
will rise one level higher.
However, a wrong answer
will result in a punishment.
The first to give ten correct
answers... will rise to the top
of the tower and will
be crowned the winner.
And that winner will
receive from our sponsor,
the Satsukitane Group,
these fabulous prizes...
A one-month trip to this
luxurious South Seas island,
courtesy of Satsukitane Tours.
As well as a one-year
passport to their water park
and of course a
signed first-edition
photo collection of
Mikako Satsukitane, Wrestler.
So then, who will
be our winner today?
The stands are packed
with cheering fans..
Tomoki's a cockroach!
You are a dumbass!
Shut up!
It's too bad, but our
own Tomoki seems to have
no home crowd support today.
So, um... What's all that?
What's all what?
All that... down
there below us...
You know, that's
a very good question.
Very good, first question...
It is... a question on ethics.
There is someone on the side of
the road tossing out empty
soda cans. What do you do?
I kill everybody.
What is that?! Octopi?!
The seat opened up and
dropped Mikako down
into a pit full of octopi!
We're doing this?
Yeah!
Had to ask, didn't ya?
Right. Next is an
agriculture question.
Aomori Prefecture is
famous for its apples.
What is the Spanish
word for "apple?"
Man... zanno?
This time, there's
a pigsty at the bottom!
Moving on to math. This
will be a giveaway question.
What is one plus one?
Purple!
What is this? She's
fallen into an eel pit!
You're all so freakin' dumb!
Next question. There's
a girls' changing room
right before your
eyes. What do you do?
I take a peek!
Oh, no! It's a pile of shit!
Tomoki has fallen
into a pile of shit!
Jerk!
Lowlife!
You suck, Tomoki!
The already very, very
unpopular Tomoki is now having
trash hurled
at him by the girls.
As for the correct answer.
That would be "do not peek."
Let's keep going.
The next question is...
And that's how the quiz show
continued. Round after round.
With pretty much disastrous
results for everyone.
Manzann-a?
A big plate of rice balls!
Kill 'em all.
The "Barnyard Sonata."
Well, except for Nymph
who was the only one of us
able to give
any correct answers.
That's the ninth question
Nymph has answered correctly!
Only one more
and she's the winner!
Yeah!
Contrary to that,
Tomoki is doing terribly.
He has yet to answer a
single question correctly.
He's fallen so
much, he's buried.
Well... At this point, Nymph's
victory is all but assured.
On to the next question.
The subject is health
and physical education. Now...
Well, wait, what is this?
Oh, it's nothing.
So the question is...
Sohara Mitsuki of
Second Year, Class C...
has what measurements?
What? Ikaros, what the crap
kind of question is that?!
Does... anyone on
the panel have an answer?
No freakin' way
they do! And I swear...
I sure as Hell
won't be answering it.
In centimeters,
her bust is ninety-two.
Waist, fifty-nine.
Hips, eighty-four.
If you wanna be specific,
her waist measured fifty-eight
until two days ago. But
when I glanced this morning,
it had risen to fifty-nine.
I believe the reason for this
to be the two
pieces of shortcake she
readily consumed yesterday.
He's absolutely right!
Tomoki has answered correctly!
Moving on, now. What time did
Asaka Maiko of Second Year,
Class A take
her bath yesterday?
From 9:57 p.m. until 10:34 p.m.,
for a total of thirty-seven
minutes, or to be more
precise, thirty-seven minutes,
twenty-one point
zero eight seconds.
Incidentally, her
favorite bath powder
is Strawberry Chestnut Splash.
Next question. What color
are the panties of the
three pretty girls standing in
the front row of the audience?
From right-to-left,
white, pink, and polka-dot.
Yesterday, it was polka-dot,
striped, and flowers.
Before that, pink,
white, and a light teal.
Tomoki's correct
answers just keep on coming!
And his seat continues
to rise... along with the
crazed outrage
from the girls below him!
Ladies... and gents...
they're side-by-side! Tomoki
has reached the same level as
our first place holder, Nymph!
It all comes down to this.
Whoever answers the next
question correctly will win.
What's this? Another giveaway?
The next question
is a giveaway question!
One of the previously-asked
questions will be asked again.
Here goes... There is
a girls' changing room
right before your
eyes. What do you do?!
Crap. This thing's over.
That Tomoki
cockroach is gonna win.
I'm gonna be sick!
This is it, ladies. You've
done your best to make fun of me
for being unpopular and
dumb and ugly and whatever.
But in the end, I'm the
one who wins this thing!
Starting tomorrow,
I'm gonna rip into you!
Dummies! Ha ha!
You're so freakin' dumb!
This is it, Tomoki. We
need your answer, please.
My answer is... I do not--
Huh?
What's wrong with him?
Answer, Tomoki.
You can do it!
There is a girls'
changing room...
right before your eyes...
What do you do?
No. That can't be what's
happening. Don't tell me he's
fighting against his
Inner Dude up there!
Don't screw this
up, man! Come on!
It's just a game show!
Lie if you have to, man!
Just give the
right answer, dammit!
Say it, Tomoki!
I take a peek.
I don't peek.
And Nymph is the
winner! Everyone, please,
a warm round of
applause for our champion!
You win.
Several days passed... but
things didn't get much better.
The news about how I blew
the Smart-Kid Championship
got around Sorami pretty fast.
Look, there he is.
You mean the stupid
one we heard about?
Everyone in town started
looking at me like I was
the biggest idiot
they'd ever seen.
Tomoki Sakurai. Today's the day
I kill you 'til you're dead!
Not my fault I'm
more self-aware than them.
I'm so hungry.
Astraea, what are
you doing over there?
Dummy!
You're the last person
who should be calling me that
and you know it!
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
It's like that,
huh?! Rematch time!
What is this thing?
It's just a little board
game... where the truth is
literally laid out for
you in black and white.
Being some mythical
creature from a strange place,
you've never seen
this game before.
No way you're gonna beat
me your first time playing.
Now, you're gonna be
the biggest idiot in Sorami!
You big dummy!
So...
You gonna show me how to play?
Sure... Check it out. Just put
this piece here, surrounding my
white piece here, and
then you flip it to black.
Now what?
Um... Well... let's see,
uh... I guess I'll go here.
What next?
Well, if you put one there,
most of my white pieces will
turn black, won't they?
Yeah, good.
And now what?
Let's see... I put
this piece here and...
I win!
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
Oh, is that right?
Fine! Then... Then
we're playin' this next!
Ten seconds...
Twenty seconds...
Wait a minute! I can't read!
I win!
Dummy! Dummy!
No. This game is boring. I
challenge you to Stick-Man Kick!
Sure. Bring it on, baby!
Check out that killer pass!
Yeah, shot on goal!
Long pass blowin' right by you!
Interception!
Interception denied! Boo-ya!
Uh, guys. This doesn't
seem to have anything to do
with how smart
either of you a--
Take that, dummy!
You're the dummy, dummy!
That's exactly what
they're doing, Sugata.
I just wondered
what you thought.
Here it comes, dummy!
Dummy!
Dammit, Tomo!
Geez, how many times
are you gonna do this?
You will be paying
for that window, you know.
Busted!
Two, three!
Stop! That's not how you play!
Dummy! Dummy!
I lost...
Great! What do you wanna
play next? Old Maid, maybe?
Nah. I'm cool with
being the loser today.
Yep, I said it. I'm the big
loser, okay. Now are you hungry?
You wanna eat before you go?
You're always hungry.
Ooh, Nymph. Nice job. You
arranged the food perfectly.
Hey!
Excellent,
they're finally here.
Jeez, you two, it's
about time you showed.
Sorry about that. We were
just having ourselves
a really killer contest.
Everything is ready... Master.
Raise your glasses. Here's
to our good pal Tomoki.
The biggest moron our fair
town Sorami has ever seen!
Jeez, keep your
voice down, would ya?!
To Tomoki...
Yeah, fine. To me.
I think I'd like
some of that, too.
Sure.
Meat is awesome!
Hey, Astraea. Could you pass
me that? I wanna try some.
Yeah. Here.
Cool, thanks.
Sugata, you're not having any?
I'll eat later.
That quiz the other day sure
was a good time, wasn't it?
Tomoki, you ready
for your revenge yet?
No way, I'm over it.
Aw, Miss Ikaros...
Astraea. Hey...
if you ever faint. Like...
from hunger... come over
here and eat. Anytime.
What'd I say?
Thanks. Even
though... you're dumb!
Hey!
Hey! What the
Hell are you doing?!
Hey!
You're dumb!
Nuh-uh! You are!
What are you doing?!
That's my food!
We're trying to have a
nice dinner. Don't ruin it.
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
Another day in paradise...
Yep.
Dummy! Dummy!
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
At least she
is enjoying herself.
It is a little disturbing
that, unlike Beta,
she has yet to
break her imprinting.
My daughters are so amusing.
What is that?
Ah, there you are... Daedalus.
Funny thing. While following
a bug who recently trespassed
into the Synapse...
I found evidence of you
accessing Tomoki's dreams.
You were also the one who broke
the seal on the Uranus Queen
and ejected her to
Earth, weren't you?
So what if I did?
There's nothing you can do.
Harpy and Gamma's
Prometheus Cannons won't even
dent the barrier I
have established around me.
Oh, I know that. I'm
actually here to deliver
a small message of courtesy.
About the
second-generation Angeloids.
They've been perfected.
Perfected?!
The new model is far
more advanced than that
pathetic first
version you built.
Their destructive power
alone... is unfathomable.
What are you
planning to do now?
What do you mean? That
should be obvious to you.
I'm going to destroy
the Alpha... and the Beta.
Next time...
"Tomoki-Eating Watermelon"