Wake up. Come on, Tomoki!
Please, you have to wake up!
Hey... Been a while.
Tomoki!
Whoa! What's going on?!
Something awful has happened!
There's a... second-generation
Angeloid, and--
They pulled me
out of his dream?!
No, it's worse.
Someone took my place!
It's her. The new model!
Hi, mister. Wanna
play dolls with me?
Who... Who're you?
Come play dolls
with me. It's fun.
But how? Nothing should be
able to penetrate the block on
Tomoki's dreamscape!
This new Angeloid...
Is she really that powerful?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Somebody's been
a very bad dolly!
Cut it out!
Is there something
the matter... Master?
That dream... What the Hell?
So much of the phenomenon...
that science cannot explain...
has occurred near girls
on the verge of womanhood.
During the mid-1800s, the Fox
Sisters founded Spiritualism
in America based on
their odd experiences.
And there were the Cottingley
Fairy photos in England.
These are just two of the
examples of supernatural events
that have taken
place around young women.
Could this correlation be
the work of the New World,
a.k.a. the Synapse? Hmm...
Given the form
The Angeloids take,
that isn't hard to believe.
That said, if one of them finds
themselves in the midst of
such a phenomenon,
they should watch out.
The girl in question might
be nothing more than bait.
Ah, the great outdoors.
Oh, my empty belly!
Tasty! Dead ahead!
Squid?! For me?! Score!
I haven't eaten
in forever! Thanks!
Gotta eat 'em one at
a time, all careful-like,
get all the flavor out of 'em.
Savor each 'n' every one.
Taste that tasty squid!
Look at me! This is
sad with a capital C!
I'm the Synapse's bestest
Angeloid in in-your-face combat!
I'm Astraea!
A Delta type, even!
How come I can't power down
the whole bag at once, huh?!
Wait a minute...
this is all his fault!
Revengeance!
Let's see how much
he likes being hungry!
Bye, Mom! I'll see ya later!
Look both ways
and all that stuff.
Man, Alpha is such a
screw-up. How does somebody
forget to go shopping?
Gimme snacks already!
Oh! Maybe there's still
something good in the fridge?
Guess I'm hearing things...
Brr... Brr... Brr...
Oh, jeez. What are you doing?
I snuck in like a food
ninja when nobody was looking
so I could eat the yummies!
But there isn't anything
yummy inside this fridge.
There's only me! God, why!
Aw, can it! I'm hungry,
and I actually live here!
My tummy! My tummy!
Nymph wants a snack!
My head!
Wait. What about...
Yeah, of course!
What?
Alpha grew 'em all from seeds.
I got a bad feelin' about this.
I mean, Ikaros loves
watermelons almost as much as
she oves the
dummy-bug, right?
You got that right.
She'll stomp our faces
if she finds out. But...
She's not gonna
miss a few of 'em!
O'course not! What Ikaros
won't know doesn't hurt us!
Yum!
Awesome!
Ooh. Let's eat a big one now!
Dummy! Big melons aren't
any better than little ones!
You see? Good thing
I came along with you.
All this ended up
being a lot to carry.
Yes, thank you...
for the company.
And for the recipe, too.
Sure! And speaking of shopping,
I'm really proud of how you can
do it all by yourself
now. Good job, Ikaros!
Sometimes, when Master
does not give me a list,
I still make mistakes.
Well, what do you
still need to get?
Potatoes, for use
in tonight's supper.
Huh? You're buying them all?
I am cooking for four.
Let's see Tomoki,
and then Nymph is there,
and you're eating of course.
Who am I not accounting for?
Master said... "buy for four."
Okay.
Typical Tomoki.
I am totally stuffed.
I am gonna have a food baby.
Yeah, so uh...
We're screwed...
Any bright ideas?
'Cause once... a buncha
flies tried to make her
watermelon patch
their salad bar...
Alpha fired up her
Artemis projectiles
and blasted 'em all to Hell.
That was fun,
huh? See ya later.
Yes. I had a lot of fun today.
I am home.
I think we're in trouble here!
Isn't there something
we can do?! Come on!
Is something wrong?
Wait what about that
hacking thingy you do?!
Can't you tell
the plants to like,
grow more watermelons,
now and stuff?!
I dunno. I've never
used it on plants before.
But... I guess I
don't have a choice, huh!
Why did you make that?!
It's your fault!
Hey! Shut up down there!
Huh? Help! Get it off of me!
I'm melting! Melting!
All that's left of the
dummy is a seed! Look at him!
Yeah! Thanks for
that, Captain Obvious!
Let's plant him
and see what happens!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Nooooo!
Nymph... please open up.
Nah, it's cool.
Don't worry about it!
We're fine. We're all
fine here now, thank you.
Why was Master
screaming, Nymph?
Crap... she's on to us!
Cards, don't fail me now!
Uh...
Delta-ate-'em-all-I-swear!
Why?!
Start talking, dingbats!
Whatever. Not my fault.
Blondie's the
one who started it.
No, I'm not! Liar,
liar, pants on fire!
I wasn't stuck, I was hiding!
Least I wasn't
stuck in the freezer.
And you're so short...
You'd still be in there
if I hadn't gone to the door.
Ah, shut up already!
All this crap went down just
'cause you were hungry, right?
Huh?
I told ya you could come
eat here whenever, didn't I?
So shut up and
eat... you dummy.
Thanks for the food.
Thanks for the... food?
Dumb-dumb!
Hey! You thieving jerk!
Least I'm not a
dumb-dumb, dumb-dumb! Hey!
Great, here we go again...
I'm takin' this, take that!
I will take that! Eat it!
Hey! Leave my food out of it!
So Delta, what
are you gonna do now?
Huh?
Still gonna
try and kill Tomoki?
What do you think I should do?
It's not for me to say.
Master hasn't contacted me,
but I know I'm not supposed to
go back to the Synapse.
You and Alpha seem to be
having a good enough
time down here, though.
So, that wasn't very nice
of you earlier. Why'd you put
all the blame on me?
You ate just as many
"wallermeloms" as I did.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I panicked.
Though, I gotta say Nymph,
for as tiny as you are,
you sure can pack it away.
"Tiny," huh? Come back here
an' call me that to my face!
Hey! Gotta go!
Oh yeah! Sorry, Nymph! You
can't chase me 'cause you don't
have wings anymore!
Neener-neener-neener!
Wait... Where...?
Whatever. It's your own
fault you lost your wings.
You and Ikaros turned
your backs on the Synapse,
so you're nothing
but big ol' traitors now.
I don't get it. Like,
why did they punk out
on the Synapse, anyway?
Wearin' me out. After
all that, I didn't get
a single damn croquette.
Hey. It's me, God. Please
do me a solid and take me away
to a world without
Angeloids. Amen.
Huh?
You want me to
take you there, mister?
Do I... know you?
Want me to take you
away to a world, mister...
without any Angeloids at all?
Aw hey, you're all little
and junk, but you care about
other people. That's
so friggin' adorable.
Anyway. It's getting late.
You should head home.
See ya!
You're nice to me.
I have an idea. Wanna
play dolls with me, mister?
Sorry, Nymph! You can't
chase me 'cause you don't
have wings anymore!
Neener-neener-neener!
I know Delta's too dumb
to mean anything by it...
but without wings, and without
a master... What good am I?
This reject is
good for nothing...
except tossing
on the scrapheap.
It's okay... 'cause Tomoki
would never say that!
Oh, Tomoki... he's so...
Sugata?
Dammit, the bug is fast!
There he is!
Three... two... one... adios.
How does he keep doing that?!
This time... let's aim
for 40 seconds, all right?
Oh. But I'm worn
out! C'mon... call it a day.
Not on your life.
In the words of Sun Tzu,
"Know thy enemy," Nymph. I
have to investigate the Synapse
while avoiding the Harpies.
Yeah, that's cool.
Forty seconds, huh?
Damn that little bug!
Next time he's going down!
We better keep our eyes peeled.
One... two... three...
Hi, Nymph.
Oh, Tomoki. What's up?
Uh, five... six...
seven... eight... Huh?!
Come on... Let's go on a date.
But! Sugata... He's
depending on me to--!
He'll be fine.
No! Wait! Tomoki!
Thirty-seven... Thirty-eight...
Thirty-nine... Forty.
I've hit a bit of a snag.
Just pretend I'm not here.
Oh, no! Our hearts go
out to you, good sir.
As if! Say your prayers,
ya little cockroach!
Quickly!
Oh no ya don't!
Sugata's fine. I'm sure of it.
What's wrong?
Do you wanna... go back home?
That's Master... and Nymph?
What is this...
sensation I am feeling?
Master is my master.
I carry out his orders.
That is supposed to be all.
My reactor. It hurts.
Why they went
AWOL from the Synapse?
That's what you're asking?
Yeah... I thought
you'd know, Sensei,
'cause you're super-smart.
Good call. See,
it's a love-triangle.
Actually... no...
It's a love-square.
Math, my mortal enemy!
Astraea, my dear.
Yeah?
I believe we're in
for some stormy weather.
Not that I
dislike a bit of drama,
so long as nobody
goes overboard.
"Stormy?"
I brought you out here...
'cause there's
something I wanna tell you.
Yeah?
Nymph... I really
wanna become your master.
You dragged me here
for that? Oh, very funny!
I'm dead serious.
Why now?
My wings... got torn off... and
everyone says I was... a reject.
You're so not.
A worthless mistake...
Not to me. You're adorable.
I've always thought so.
From the moment I met you,
I wished you were my Angeloid.
Do you... really mean it?
Yeah. Cross my heart.
Honest?
Then... I'll start the
imprinting process right away.
Good, but before you do, can you
do me one, tiny favor first?
Name it. I'll do anything.
Kill yourself.
T-Tomoki...
Why would you say that?!
I... wanna know what love is.
"Love conquers all,"
doesn't it?
You betrayed
the Synapse for love.
Now... kill yourself! And prove
your love! Prove it to me!
Prove it! Prove it!
Prove your love! Prove it!
Show me! Show me
what love is! Show me!
Of course. Why would
he ever choose me?
Who the Hell are you?!
How dare you
pretend to be Tomoki!
Darn... I guess ya caught me.
I'll just have to learn
about love a different way.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you. I'm the new
second generation Angeloid...
type Epsilon... Chaos.
Nymph, would you tell me, pretty
please? What does "love" mean?
Paradise Song!
Bye-bye, brat!
Nymph... I really
wanna become your master.
That wasn't... fair!
Nymph. I don't
know what "brat" means...
But it doesn't sound too nice.
No way! I hit her dead on!
My master sent me to Earth...
to track down Ikaros...
and rip the variable
wing core out of her.
Master says the variable
wing core is the Synapse's
most valuable technology.
You know... I just don't care
about boring stuff like that.
But I turned myself into
Tomoki Sakurai 'cause there's
something I do care
about, a whole bunch!
Yeah, brat. What's that?
It doesn't make any sense
to me. How come you two
turned your backs
on the Synapse, huh?
Master said you've been
infected by love, but I
don't understand, 'cause we're
not programmed to feel love.
That's why I need
you to tell me, Nymph.
What is love?
Please tell me, Nymph. Before
you're dead. What is love?
What is love? What is love? What
is it? Tell me what love is!
What is it? What is love?
What is love? What is looove?
Please, don't be
afraid. I'm a friend.
The Harpies can't
get to us in here.
Who are you?
What the--?!
It's begun. I knew it.
Next time... "The Song of
the Angel Echoes in the Sky"