Yo. Remote. This is boring.
Here.
Cool. Thanks, Nymph.
Uh... sorry about that.
Just... be more careful, okay?
He responded
that one had nothing
to do with the other,
echoing the sentiment of...
Whoa, what's up? She
looked kinda cute there.
Yeah, she did!
Shut up, you!
Master. Your tea
is ready to drink.
Yeah, uh, thanks.
Oh god! Is Ikaros becoming
aware of her sexuality?!
You need me?
No, I do not! No!
No! No! This is insane!
Lusting after mythical beings?!
There's nothing normal about it!
I've gotta do something
about my overblown libido!
Tomoki, are you here?
Master went into the
mountains this morning.
The mountains?
He was yapping something
about training himself.
Well, he picked
the worst time for it.
Is something wrong?
Dreadfully.
He's been targeted.
Good afternoon,
everyone. Tomoki here.
I've come high into
the mountains to train.
Here I feel I'm at a safe
distance from the mythical
creatures who, lately
have become unusually sexy
for some reason.
Focus, focus...
Master...
Need me now?
Be quiet!
How 'bout now?
Stop already!
And so, I have made my
way to this Zen temple...
in order to gain control
over my earthly desires.
I found him.
The other day, when I was near
the great cherry blossom tree,
an Angeloid I'd never seen
before fell from the sky.
And I'm not quite
sure how I know this...
but I got the vibe that
she's after Tomoki's life!
Tomo!
Deploying wide-area radar.
Identifying enemy
Angeloid type and location.
The enemy Angeloid has already
made contact with Master.
No way we'll make it in time!
Oh, gosh!
Processing return data.
Threat identified as
close-combat model Angeloid.
Type Delta, Astraea.
Target confirmed.
Tomoki Sakurai.
You will be... eliminated.
Oh, never mind, it's Delta.
So, you wanna go eat all the
leftovers in
the fridge with me?
Yes.
What?! At a time like this?!
Are you sure
that Tomoki's okay?
If it's Delta, he's fine.
And what is that
supposed to mean?!
So what's the
deal? Is she weak?
Not hardly. More
like ridiculously strong.
And better than Alpha
in close-quarters combat.
But then?
We first-generation combat
Angeloids didn't come equipped
with all that
much functionality.
Here's an example.
For as much computational
and emotional control I have,
my combat abilities are low. And
because Alpha has computational
and combat abilities, her
emotional control is low.
Make sense?
Now, since Delta is stacked
with combat skills and emotions,
that means her computational
abilities are low.
I see.
Wait. I'm lost.
What are you saying?
Delta... is a
blithering idiot.
Ah, for cryin' out loud.
Another one? Really?
This just has trouble
written all over it.
Young Sakurai, I think
you should move on to
waterfall training next.
Oh... Yes, sir.
Oh, oh, oh! I wanna do it,
too! Over here! Me, me, me!
It makes sense that Ikaros'
master would be like this.
He won't be an easy mark.
The fool doesn't even know
I came here to kill him.
Go ahead... Let your
guard down! You are so dead!
So, so, so...
So... so cold!
Holy crap, are you all right?!
Mr. Priest, where are you?
I need some help!
Hurry! Mr. Prie...
You rang?
Stop it! No! Since when
is your name Mr. Priest?!
Away with you,
worldly desires!
Only reason I came up
here was to gain control
over my stupid desires!
Control... Over...
My... Desires...
Come on, buddy. I'm just
tryin' to help you out here.
Damn it, I am not giving up.
Not giving up, not giving up!
Away with you, worldly desires!
Sensors say Master is here.
You worry too much.
I'm telling you, he's fine.
Of course I'm worried,
he's still my best friend.
Actually, I'm more curious
about what this training is
he's going through.
Why don't you wait
here while I go inside?
Yeah...
It'll give me a chance
to gauge the situation.
All right. I guess if
I don't get rid of these
my desires
will never go away.
Thank you. You've
been so good to me.
Oh, just one more
for the road, girls!
Tomo Sense tingling! Nymph?
Pervert!
Why are... you here?
Sleazebag! You've been
leering at me the way you do
the girls in those
magazines, haven't you?
I can just imagine!
Now... You have to take off your
clothes so I can examine you.
But that needle is way too big
for me to take the whole thing!
Or even worse!
Time for your spanking!
Thank you, Master.
May I have another?
That's what you've
always wanted to do to me,
isn't it, you jerk-face?!
Would you stop hitting me?!
Yeah? Why should I?!
For someone your age,
you've got some nerve!
Maybe your opinion will
matter once you grow up some!
Especially in this region!
Fine then. You wanna see what
I'll look like all grown up?
Why don't you check this out?!
Since Angeloids don't
age, I'm going to use this
pseudo-growth
device to show you.
Now fall to your knees
and gaze upon the fine body
I could develop in five years!
Well? This is how I'd
look five years older.
Check out my huge cans.
No, wait! Not yet!
Aw, yeah. These are
my breasts in ten years!
Close your eyes!
Don't look at me!
I swear they're
gonna to get bigger!
Imagine living this long,
and they're still no bigger.
You sick pervert!
I hate you, Tomoki!
Oh look, Nymph is back.
Hey! How'd it go?
Did you find
anything out about the...?
Did something happen to her?
I will go see
how Master is doing.
After this, I can
get back to training.
But first, just one more look!
Tomo Sense is tingling!
What is Ikaros doing here?
Whoa! What is this filth?!
Have you ever seen
anything so horrible?!
Master? Are such simple
magazines really that dangerous?
Oh, Hell yes! These naked
women gang up to seduce men!
It's awful! Somebody's
hatching some kind of evil plot
somewhere, I tell ya! I'll
deal with these things later.
Acknowledged.
Eliminate all dangers
to Master... Initiate.
Multiple enemies
identified... Targeting...
Commencing elimination mode.
Nice job, Ikaros. You've
done good. Go on home, now.
Yes... Master.
Hey Ikaros, have any luck?
Master was in adequate health
but he did not seem to be
in a happy mood.
Is that right?
Yes.
Oh Tomo.
I'm worried about you.
Wow. You're right, this tree
looks... exactly like the one
we saw in Tomoki's dream.
I wonder what it means.
Ikaros. I hate to ask,
but would you look at this?
Could you tell me
if this acorn is of
the same variety as
the chinquapin tree?
Yes.
Commencing structural
analysis... Fifty percent...
Eighty percent... One hundred
percent. Analysis complete.
Genomes of both
organic substances...
are an absolute match...
Identical species
and variety confirmed.
I knew it. Of course.
Sugata. What
does all that mean?
All of our answers
are in the New World.
Up beyond the sky.
Rest in peace. I'll miss
you, beautiful ladies.
You're gone too soon. So sad.
What is he doing over there?
Look how defenseless
he is right now!
That's a porno mag! Ooh!
If I can pull him even more
off his guard, maybe
I can kill him right now!
Excuse me, sir...
There's an even more incredibly
dirty porno mag over here.
What's this?
Bang!
Oh, my God.
No! Don't close it!
Hold on a sec!
Check it out! How about this?
See? Flashie... flashie...
Nowadays, that kind of
soft-core crap wouldn't even
turn on a middle-schooler.
Fine. Then what do you
think about this, big boy?!
This... this is...
One more page to go!
Damn centerfold!
No! I can't take off any more!
Enough of your futile
resistance, stupid paper!
Dammit! Isn't there anything
around here that can cut this?
Like some scissors
or a box cutter?
Sure.
Oh, thanks a million!
What do you think? Cuts
pretty well, doesn't it?
I can't believe my
desires are so entrenched in
my psyche that
it's come to this.
Here you go, dude.
The priest told me I should
bring this stuff to you.
Thank you.
I gratefully accept this.
You finally let your
guard down, stupid bug.
The food you're
eating is poisoned.
Loaded with vicious
and deadly poison...
that I forgot to put in!
You have to give
me that food back!
The Hell's wrong with you?!
Let go!
Stop! Stop! I can't breathe!
No! Stop wriggling!
Tomo! Tomo!
It's all good!
Grandpa?
Whether they're human,
or mythical beings,
long as they got boobs.
Doesn't matter. They're
all still chicks, right?
It's all good.
I finally get it,
Grandpa. It's all good.
What's that?
Here are the Six Domains. When
a person dies, they are taken to
one of six worlds, depending
on the life they led.
The realms are called the
Hell Realm, the Preta Realm,
the Animal Realm, The Asura
Realm, the Human Realm,
and the Blissful Realm. This is
a path that cannot be avoided...
if one ever hopes
to atone for one's sins.
This is the enlightenment my Zen
temple training has provided me!
Finishing strike! Welcome
to the Six Domains of Tomoki!
Tomoki Hell Realm!
Stop doing that! It burns!
Tomoki Preta Realm!
This... is... so... gross!
Tomoki Animal Realm!
No!
Tomoki Asura Realm!
I can't take any more of this!
Where's the door
out of this place?
Um... what's that?
Welcome... Tomoki Human Realm.
No! No! I said no!
Come on, man. Just look at it.
That's what she said.
What in the world
is that thing?!
Tomoki Blissful Realm, man.
Fine, but what is that?!
No more!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Master.
It is good to see you.
Would you like to take a bath?
Nah, not right now. I'm beat.
Master's spirits are low.
Perhaps I should not have
eliminated those
magazines for him.
Activating card.
Read me...! Read me...!
What on Earth?!
Ikaros...
Master?
You big lunkhead. You
did all this just for me?
Yes... Master.
I am glad. As long as Master is
happy, that is all I could want.
Read me! Read me! Read me!
Master...
Your magazines tell me
they would like a festival to
celebrate their resurrection.
Sure! Paint the
town red! Do it big!
Due to unforeseen contingency...
Circuits shutting down.
Commencing initialization.
Restarting. Reaffirming mission.
Dreams are... an imperfect,
unique phenomenon,
experienced only
by Earth humans.
One year ago, an
incident of uncertain origin
occurred in which the
dream of one human became
connected to the Synapse.
Concluding there
was no immediate danger,
the Supreme Council's
ultimate decision was to
let it pass. Until several
days ago, when evidence was
discovered of humans
infiltrating the Synapse's core.
The core is where
the Rule resides.
The Rule?
Although not acknowledging
any interference with the Rule,
the Synapse Supreme
Council determined that
this action posed
a security threat.
The alert level was
elevated to stage four.
And it was ruled that
it is now necessary to
eliminate human target
Tomoki Sakurai at once.
My mission is to eliminate
Tomoki Sakurai at once...
and determine the cause of...
It appears...
you and I are going to
need to have
ourselves a long talk.
Next time... "A
Proud-Fought Battle"