Peace and quiet.
Sure is nice, huh?
Crap, I just typed in
the wrong numbers again!
Son of a...
Peace... and...
friggin'... quiet...
It's been nothing but love and
tears and battles to the death
around here, lately. I approve
of all the drama, of course...
but I'm not getting
to have any of the fun.
All of this evil... and
nobody here to vent it upon.
Well... nobody...
except you, my dear Sohara.
You look buoyant.
Guess it's that time of year
again. Crazy, huh?
Me and the gang are hitting
up the local shrine for
the summer festival,
just like always.
I can't believe how
relaxed I feel right now.
Yoo-hoo! Tomo!
So... we meet again.
You didn't think that you
were shut of me, did ya?
Gather 'round, time to
unveil this year's event!
Oh yes, but first...
This way, ladies.
You boys'll be thrilled
you decided to come, when you
see what your class president's
cooked up for you tonight!
I present the Yo-Yo Fish-Off!
Huh? What?
Snowballs and wrestling and
live ammo and now this?! No way!
I've said it before and I'll say
it again. Fishing is bullshit!
I suppose I should explain
the rules. Oh, clumsy me...
Thank you...
for that... but... why?
Now Tomoki... remind your horny
classmates what yo-yos are.
Huh? They're, y'know, those
toys that go "boing boing."
Oh yes.
"Boing boing" is right!
Got one!
What the--?!
No!
Y'see? Boing-boing,
just like you said!
Look!
The pool is
swarming with girls!
What's the big idea?!
Noooo!
The rules are very simple.
Everyone breaks up into
two-person teams. Whichever
team reels in the breast catch
will be declared the Yo-Yo
Fish-Off champ. Easy as pie.
Such a shame, though. Tomoki
would have been a shoe-in
to win this one...
but sadly he's already said
he doesn't even want to try.
Tomoko knows what to do
with a rod! Tide is optimal.
Wind:
north-by-somethin'-or-other.
All right, ladies and germs!
On your marks... Get set...
Let's do this!
Here we go!
Class President Satsu-kitane
delivers yet again with
today's Yo-Yo Fish-Off
competition! I'm Mr. Takehara,
the math-teacher-slash-host
who's got everyone's number!
I will provide...
color commentary.
Remember, first place goes to
whichever team fishes
the biggest ta-tas,
a.k.a. yo-yos, out of the pool!
It's chaos in the water as our
melon-maddened menfolk make
a beeline for the boobies!
Oh, no!
We're done for!
Stay away from me!
I've gotta hunch these are
the two teams to watch, folks!
Tomoko and Sugata are fast,
but Satsukitane and that one guy
are right at their heels!
Sure hope my hands don't slip
while I'm measuring the haul!
Good thing it's
just us girls, huh?!
No! Let me go! Let me go!
The little minx has resurfaced
with four more teats to tally!
Ink 'em up!
Ink 'em up! Waaaaaay up!
Thank you. I'll
treasure them forever.
To-mo-ko...! To-mo-ko...!
In she goes! No question who's
the fan-favorite here, folks!
Tomoko and Sugata put
the "jug" in juggernaut
with their fourth
catch of the day!
Yeah! Dream on! You keep
your gender-bent paws off of me!
Go ahead and try it!
You feel lucky, punk?!
Come back when you're
bigger, little guppy.
She released Nymph back
into the wild! Attagirl!
Excellent angling etiquette.
Wouldn't have helped
their score anyway.
Correct.
Stop messing around.
We're running out of time!
Catch us a girl with curves!
Aye-aye!
Now then. Time to
call in the big guns.
Jackpot!
Here juggy-juggy-juggy!
Speak of the devil!
I'm gonna get ya!
Oh, did I forget to mention?
This is a contact sport.
Showtime!
Oh! No! Oh, you got me!
Tomoko went down
in a hail of gunfire!
Is this the end of the road...
Hey! Shake it off,
you gigantic baby!
Meanwhile, Madame President
and the other guy have
landed a pair of backbreakingly
epic sweater puppies!
Oh, Sugata!
Whatever are we gonna do?!
Catching them with a pole is too
slow. Let's switch methods...
mass-harvesting!
Right!
Sugata and me, we managed
to put up a pretty good fight.
But Prez kept bringing
the hurt, like hard-core.
Every time I went to
seal the deal, there she was.
Time was almost up, and we still
hadn't landed any big catches.
Best! Festival! Ever!
He's so rude! Who's he calling
a guppy?! Stupid pervert!
He had to toss
you back, Nymph.
Look at those bug-bites!
What did you just call 'em?!
Nothin'!
Least I can spell "bug-bite!"
Are you having fun?
Oh. Hey, Alpha!
Hey, why aren't they fishing for
your boobs in the pool, Ikaros?
I think that I've...
had enough of water for now.
Yeah... guess so. I mean, after
what you had to do and all.
I'm sorry you were forced to
take a life. But the truth is,
if you hadn't
stopped Chaos, none of us
would be standing here.
Correct.
Any luck?
Yeah, but all bad.
Ten minutes to go, sports
fans! Team Satsukitane's at the
head of the pack!
But the pool's all fished
out! Damn that Astraea for
having epic funbags!
Legend tells of a creature.
A thing that guards the pool.
Those who've laid eyes
on it speak of it with
fear and reverence.
A Leviathan that
glides through the
chlorinated deep...
its bustline
continually growing larger.
Bustline?
She... She's huge!
An omen...!
Are you all right, Master?
Maybe Fate is trying to tell
me... that it's high time...
I cop a feel!
Master...
Launch the boat.
There's no time to
explain! Boobies, ho!
We're taking on water!
Damn! She's not responding!
Go! I'll hold her together!
Right!
Sugata...
If I... If I survive, I swear
I'm gonna propose to Ikaros.
What does that
mean? "Propose?"
I'll bring her...
a bouquet of flowers.
The biggest ever!
Dear Ikaros, I'm sorry.
After this one last haul,
I was gonna propose to you.
But if you're reading this...
I guess... my luck ran out.
Even so... I
don't regret a thing.
I may be gone... but
the boobs that I've seen...
will jiggle... forever!
Forever!
And there's the whistle!
After a white-knuckle night
of fishing, Team
Satsukitane wins it all!
Heading out?
Yeah.
Until next time.
'Til then.
Ah! That's better! So uh...
You sure you don't
wanna cut him down?
Positive!
The whole Yo-Yo Fishing
thing was bad enough,
but what's wrong with Tomo?
Sometimes he treats
me like a piece of meat!
And he told you
he would propose?
It's like he doesn't even
think before he opens his mouth.
Sohara...
What's up?
Tell me... What is love?
Huh?
The entire concept.
I do not understand it.
But... sometimes my reactor
hurts when I think of him
and it gets hard to breathe.
I see... For what it's worth,
I'm in the same boat as you.
I don't understand
it, either. Not really.
It hurts you... but you always
want to be around the person.
Is that it?
It is.
Come on, you.
Ikaros must have
feelings... for Tomoki.
Sorry! Guess I zoned out.
You're proposing, Moota?!
With a
diamond-studded horseshoe.
Umami, let's be
together forever.
That's so sweet.
He proposed?
Yeah, it's this thing the humans
do on TV a lot, where they
promise they're gonna
be together forever.
Together forever...
What's with you?
Oh! The love thing.
Are you still bummed out
about not knowing what love is?
I think Tomoki's got
something that could help you.
Let's see... where'd
it... Ah! Here!
"My First Errand..."
Yeah!
Oh, no... don't! If you keep
chasing me, all my clothes...
The Hell's this crap?
Oh, you naughty,
naughty man!
Oh man, home safe at last.
Where did you find that DVD?!
What the Hell are you doing?!
It's not even mine!
Bad Angeloids! Bad!
Um, Master...
Fine, it is!
Remember when you said...
you were going to propose.
Huh?!
After... the boob fishing.
No-no-no-no-no-no-no-no! I
didn't mean proposal proposal!
I meant, like... uh,
Backpedal! Backpedal!
But. There is something
I have been meaning to give
to the both of you.
It's called an allowance.
And Nymph.
An allowance?
Why not? You
two can handle it.
Sohara was just
telling me how Ikaros can
go shopping
all by herself now,
and I'm sure there's gotta
be stuff you want too, right?
Is this an errand?
No! It's for fun!
This money is yours now. You can
spend it on whatever ya want.
Understand?
Awesome. I'm never gonna run out
of snacks again! Hey, Alpha!
Whatcha gonna do wi--
Why are you petting your money?
I am bonding
with my allowance.
Huh? Something that
would please Tomoki?
Correct.
Oh, I can think of a ton
of things you could get for
Tomo that he would really
enjoy. Pile o'porn, maybe?
Nah! That boy's got enough
smut to last a lifetime.
Save your money, Ikaros. Just
treat him to some together time.
Together...
Um... Are you pissed
at me or somethin'?
It's together time.
Oh great, this rules.
We'll be together forever.
Just back off
before you kill me!
Aw, man. That was close!
Master, did you just say
we would be together forever?
Yeah... Somethin' like that.
Ikaros greeting... Hi!
Pleasing Tomoki,
that's the idea?
Correct.
Well, he's probably
still sore from
our little
fishing competition.
Why not draw him a nice bath,
and then hop on in with him?
Master...
Ah, what the crap?!
Down periscope!
Master did not seem to
like that much. Maybe...
I do have to
purchase him something.
So what kind of purchase
would please Tomoki?
Correct.
Well, what do you think?
Yes, but...
He'll like it.
I guarantee you.
All right then.
I will go buy it immediately.
Somethin'...
I can help ya with?
Yes, please.
These are so good!
Preach on, sister!
Delta! I don't remember
you asking if you could
have any of my snacks!
What's the big deal? You bought
a bunch. There's more than
enough to share! Huh?!
Hey! Hands off!
I'm starvin' over here! At least
I'm not stingy like you are!
What's with all the racket?!
Oh, hey, Tomoki. Here.
Take it. 'Cause it's just
gonna go to waste if you don't.
Thank you.
What the Hell?! When I took
some, you were all like,
"Oink, oink, Astraea!"
Shut up! Jus'...
shut up already!
You're a butthead! How come
he can have some?
I am home.
Hey, Ikaros. Welcome back.
I wanted it, so I...
I get it. They
destroyed your garden,
so you bought yourself that.
Man, it was balls getting eaten
by that watermelon monster.
This was a mistake. I knew it.
This watermelon
is what I wanted.
Whatevs. It's all good. You
took your allowance and bought
something for yourself with it,
just like you're supposed to.
Good job. I'm proud.
Master was pleased with me.
Sugata's idea
must have been correct.
But why? This watermelon...
is something I wanted,
not something
that Master wanted.
Master, did you just say
we would be together forever?
Yeah. Something like that.
Maybe that moment... was
Master's way... of proposing.
It's so sparkly...
And now it's gone. I'm so
deep underwater, I can't move.
No fair.
I wish she would have
told me what love is.
Everything... hurts a lot.
It hurts?!
My reactor hurts.
I can't help it!
Of course! So
that's what love is!
Did that hurt you,
little fishies?
Someone had to show you...
what love really is!
I have to eat you now,
my lovelies, so I can get
big and strong! And once I do,
I'm gonna go back up there...
and show them what love is!
All of them! All of them!
Next time... "Peek Into
the Fantasy Field"