[DELILAH] Here you go.
[ITAMI] So? What did you wanna
talk to me about?
[YANAGIDA] While you were away,
we were approached by a very
interesting visitor.
She asked if we would kill
a flame dragon for her.
[ITAMI] Huh? We can't do
something like that...
[YANAGIDA] Just hear me out.
[ITAMI] I see. So it
destroyed her home village.
Of course that's a real tragedy.
But her request was denied by
the Lieutenant General, right?
What else is there to talk
about?
[YANAGIDA]
The dragon showed up
within the territory of the
Native State of Elbe.
An area that is apparently rich
in oil deposits.
As well as very large uncut
diamonds.
[ITAMI] O‐kay. When am I
supposed to give a crap?
[YANAGIDA] How'd you like
to go on a scouting mission?
[ITAMI] Huh?
And just like before it's the
kind of mission that offers
you a great deal of freedom.
You'd be able to take actions
outside of the initial scope.
[ITAMI] What are you suggesting?
[YANAGIDA]
Look I'm just saying...
That you might find
yourself
on the other side of
the border...
[YANAGIDA] And you might
encounter a dragon.
[YANAGIDA] And you might have to
kill it and come back
with some samples of a few
resources you found.
[YANAGIDA] If something
like that were to happen
I doubt there'd be too much
trouble.
[ITAMI] Yes there would!
You never saw that thing okay,
and I did.
[ITAMI] It was goddamn
terrifying!
[ITAMI] Look if it's an order,
then I'll follow it,
I don't have a much of a choice.
But if I do... I'm not getting
my team killed.
[YANAGIDA] You might want to pay
a little visit
to your blonde elf friend.
[ITAMI] Tuka?
[ITAMI] You okay?
[ITAMI] What's the matter?
[TUKA] Father!
[ITAMI]  What?
[TUKA] Oh Daddy!
[ITAMI] Uh... Tuka?!
[TUKA] You see he DID come back!
Can't believe you would take
such a sick joke that far!
[ITAMI] Tuka?
[TUKA] You're not going to
believe this.
You know what she said?
[TUKA] She said.... She said
that you were dead!
[TUKA] She told me that you
were...
killed... by a flame dragon.
[LELEI] This will allow her to
rest for a while.
[ITAMI] What the hell happened?
[RORY] It was Yao.
[TUKA] What did... you say...?
[YAO] I said that your father
is no longer among us in this
world.
No matter how far and wide you
look,
you are never going to find him.
[YAO] You remember
what happened.
Your village was attacked
by the flame dragon.
And you're the only survivor.
[YAO] Everyone else was killed.
[TUKA] You're lying.
[YAO] You need to wake up!
Tuka your father is dead!
He was burned and devoured
by a flame dragon.
[TUKA]
[RORY]
Yao told Tuka... the truth.
[RORY] The truth that we've all
been
trying to avoid this whole time.
[LELEI] And because we
never did, Tuka never
stopped looking for him.
[RORY] She's been wandering
aimlessly around town.
Sometimes forgetting to eat, or
sleep
[RORY] So every now and then...
we've been using this spell to
help her get some rest.
[ITAMI] Jesus Christ.
[ITAMI] Why would you tell her
that?
[ITAMI] We've worked very hard
to handle this delicately.
What you did was totally
uncalled for.
[YAO] Oh it was uncalled for
was it?
All I did was tell her
the truth.
I understand that you especially
caring toward her and your other
friends here.
[YAO] That you're an
extremely loyal leader.
And that you're willing to break
a few rules
in order to protect them.
Well knowing that fact
I decided to take
advantage of it.
[ITAMI] Is that right... There
are lines you just don't cross!
[YAO] Don't speak to me like a
child!
[YAO] I went to your people
and asked them to kill the flame
dragon.
I begged for their mercy.
[YAO] I offered them
anything they could possible
want in return!
[YAO] But they... but
they turned their backs
on me and my village.
They told me they can't do it.
But then... a few of them also
told me something else.
They told me you might help!
That is why I broke her heart!
And if you want to save her.
If you want her back.
You must tell her that her
father
was murdered by a flame dragon.
[YAO] And exact revenge for her!
[YAO] So what are you going to
do man in green?!
[YAO] Are you going to
abandon your friend?
Or are you going to take up arms
and make things right?
[YAO] If it were a person and
they had killed your loved
ones...
You would hunt them down to the
ends of the earth
and make them pay for what
they've done.
[YAO] But, this is a flame
dragon isn't it?
The rules aren't the same!
[YAO] No one can just go out
there and catch it.
No one can punish it.
[YAO] So what do we do?
How do we seek justice?
Where do we focus such anger?
[YAO] Where am I supposed to
direct this hatred
for the thing that took the ones
I love?!
[YAO] I know I'm being selfish.
I know that.
I'll give you anything.
I'll give you everything.
My heart, my soul. Whatever it
takes.
[YAO] I just thought...
Even if you did it for her,
my people could be saved as
well.
[DIAVO] What?! They're making
Zorzal the Crown Prince?!
[PINA] Yes. His succession to
the throne
has been announced.
[DIAVO] Damn it! But why do it
now?!
[PINA] I don't know.
[DIAVO] Our idiot brother has
lost his mind.
He's going to rise up against
our father!
[DIAVO] He told me I had to
choose which side I was on!
[PINA] He really said that?
[DIAVO] But who would give him
such an idea?
Who put such a stupid thought
into his head?
[DIAVO] Pina...
always remember something.
A giant fool with small ideas is
very dangerous.
[DIAVO] They will destroy
themselves
and everyone else around them in
the process.
[DIAVO] My dear sister.
It's time for you to start
thinking about your future.
[PINA] I only want one thing...
peace between the Empire and
Japan... Brother.
[BOULO]
[THULE] What do you want?
I have received a most
interesting report
from one of the spies I sent to
Alnus Hill.
[THULE] I'll read it later.
Just leave it somewhere okay.
[THULE] Oh, your reward.
[BOULO] If Zorzal is truly the
crown prince,
we both know that the end of The
Empire is imminent.
[THULE] Well it wasn't easy.
I had to stroke his...
ridiculous ego.
[THULE] He's a buffoon.
[THULE] Nothing more
than a mindless teenager
who thinks the entire world
revolves around his tiny
little existence.
[THULE]
That moron will do
whatever I tell him to.
[THULE] There will be no peace
with the other side.
[THULE] It's coming...
The full force of my wrath has
just begun.
[BOULO] Then why do you
keep the slaves?
Simply get rid of what's left of
the Japanese captives
who still sully our great
Empire?
[BOULO] It seems they care about
their people above anything
else.
[BOULO] They would be outraged
and almost certainly attack the
Empire.
[THULE] For their people, huh...
[THULE] That's not enough,
Boulo.
[BOULO] Then what do you think
it will take my dear.
[THULE] It's simple.
Noriko was in the exact same
situation as me,
Yet she was offered refuge.
[BOULO] And who will be
the one to kill her?
[THULE]  Pina will do
nicely.
[YOUNG ITAMI] How could you do
this? You killed dad?!
[YOUNG ITAMI]
She's gone. She's delusional.
She's sick.
She has to be put in the
hospital.
[YOUNG ITAMI]
They're gonna take her away.
There's nothing I can do.
There's nothing...
[ITAMI] It's good to
see you awake.
[TUKA] Hey.
[TUKA] What's the matter with
you, father?
[ITAMI] Huh? Ah...oh nothing.
[TUKA] It's OK.
You don't have to tell me.
[TUKA] It's good to have you
back.
[ITAMI] It's good to be back,
Tuka.
[TUKA] Hey! I'm over here,
Father!
[TUKA]
So where do you want to go
today Daddy?
[ITAMI] Oh, I don't know...
[KURATA] I heard Itami's been
pretending to be Tuka's father.
[TOMITA] Yeah. He's been coming
to work
from her house each morning.
[KURATA] Whoa is she really in
that bad of shape?
[SHINO] It's bad enough that
when she looks at him she sees
her real father.
[TUKA] Well I know a great place
we should go, Daddy.
[ITAMI] How can I say no to you?
[KURATA] Holy crap.
[ITAMI] So Tuka... where do you
wanna go today?
[TUKA] It doesn't matter...
as long as we're together I'm
happy!
[ITAMI] Well that doesn't
help me much.
[TUKA] Love you Daddy.
[HIGAKI] Need you to go
to the Imperial Capital again
tomorrow.
[ITAMI] Am I moving there?
[HIGAKI] Yes.
I need you to do some
more interpreting.
And this time it might
take a little while.
[HIGAKI] Is there a problem?
You've spent a lot of time
there, you know the place.
[TUKA] Okay so... We
told the children that
we're going out of town,
and they got really excited!
[ITAMI] Huh... Yeah?
I told them it was dangerous,
but they didn't care.
Either way it should make for
a great change of pace for them
don't you think?
[ITAMI] I'm sure it will be.
[TUKA]
[TUKA] Okay father. What's the
matter?
[ITAMI]  Everything's
just fine.
[TUKA]
So! When's your next day off?
I wanna go out again! Just the
two of us.
[ITAMI] Yeah... about that...
[TUKA]
[ITAMI] Sorry. But that'll have
to wait for awhile.
[TUKA] Huh?
[ITAMI] I don't have a choice.
I have a job to do.
Since when are you such
a hard working employee?
[ITAMI] Hey don't say that. I
feel bad about it.
[TUKA] I'm not so sure.
[ITAMI] So Tuka. I need to tell
you something important.
[ITAMI] I have to go away again,
and it could be for quite a
while.
[TUKA]
But there's no need to worry.
I promise I'll be back.
It's just that...
I wanted you to know you'd be
here on your own.
[ITAMI] Tuka? Are you...?
[TUKA] No, I'm fine, it's okay,
I can do this.
You just do your job alright?
[ITAMI] You're still here I see.
[YAO] You always a jerk this
early in the morning?
[ITAMI]
[YAO] She's been suffering from
headaches, hasn't she?
[ITAMI]
[YAO] That poor girl is
teetering on the edge right now.
She's so close.
It won't take much to send her
over
and plummeting into the depths
of insanity.
[ITAMI] I know what I'm doing.
[YAO] Ah yes playing
the role of her father.
A twisted ploy so she doesn't
have to face her father's death.
[YAO] But you don't know a thing
about Hodrew.
YAO] You can pretend to be
her father all you want,
but every little inconsistency
you create
only adds to the crippling
confusion
spiraling through her mind.
That's what's causing
her headaches.
[ITAMI] I fully aware of that.
[YAO] This can't go on forever.
The end is coming soon
and you know it!
[YANAGIDA] So Itami.
How long are you going to keep
playing the family man?
[ITAMI] Leave me alone.
[YANAGIDA]
I'm fine with it if you are.
Anyway, the first group of war
prisoners will be returned soon.
[ITAMI]
What about the abductees?
[YANAGIDA] That will have to
wait until next time.
First we need to show
Princess Pina
we've kept our part of the deal.
The rest will involve
further negotiations.
[ITAMI] Alright then. Well I
hope it goes well.
[YANAGIDA] Hey. Are you doing
alright Itami?
[ITAMI] On top of the world.
[YANAGIDA] Yeah... right.
[ITAMI]  I'm sorry. No
I'm not alright.
[ITAMI] Feel like my head is in
a tailspin.
[YANAGIDA] There's a simple
solution for all this.
You could kill the flame dragon.
[ITAMI] And get my subordinates
killed at the same time?
No thanks, Yanagida.
[ITAMI] A mission is one thing.
[ITAMI] But I can't risk other
people's lives
for personal reasons or some
shady agenda.
[ITAMI] The only life I have to
risk is my own.
You undertand that right?
[YANAGIDA] Whatever.
Itami... You let me know when
you change your mind.
[YANAGIDA] I'll be happy to do
all the boring paperwork.
[KURATA] Alright there he is!
[TUKA]  Oh...
[ALL] Cheers!
[RORY] So tell me, how does it
feel to have a daughter who's
older than you?
[ITAMI]
Kinda complicated actually.
[RORY] I imagine so.
[LELEI] You must be under a lot
of distress.
[ITAMI] Well... I'm glad she's
taken a liking to Kurokawa.
[ITAMI] At least I know that
somebody'll take care of her,
y'know.
[TUKA] Hi Daddy!!
[SOCIAL WORKER]
You're asking if taking revenge
can be good for a person.
Well, the natural impulse to
share one's pain can extend to
seeking retribution.
[ITAMI] But that doesn't mean
getting that revenge
fulfills anything.
[SOCIAL WORKER]
It may not be rewarding.
But some are reaching for any
sort of moment,
no matter how unfulfilling, just
to move on.
[DURAN] S'cuse me lad... is
there room for an old man?
[ITAMI] Yes of course.
[DURAN]
That's very cordial of you.
I like to come to find myself
here every night.
[DURAN] Just so you know.
[ITAMI] Uh‐huh...
[DURAN] What is it that
has you looking so glum?
[ITAMI] Not again...
[DURAN] You don't have to tell
me your troubles, lad.
[DURAN] But I beg your pardon
if I can't tell you one of mine.
Is this how your people
fix things?
[ITAMI] Yeah.
[DURAN] They did tell me
I'd be able to run again.
[ITAMI] With some of
the legs they make,
you can run faster
than you did before.
[DURAN] Is that so? Aahh...
[ITAMI] What?
[DURAN] Oh nothing.
I'm just thinking.
You sure you've got
nothing to say?
[DURAN] Oh‐ho...!
I'm certain
they will feel better
after exacting their vengeance.
But their enemy is pretty
formidable.
Given the location
I can't bring a very large unit.
It just wouldn't work.
And if... If I go in small, then
we'd all get obliterated.
[ITAMI] No matter what I do,
I lose something.
[DURAN] You listen here lad.
I think you're forgetting
something very important.
[ITAMI] What?
[DURAN] What you feel in your
heart.
[ITAMI] If I could make
decisions like that
then I don't even have to think
about it.
[DURAN]
Sometimes in life... you must
not make a decision at all,
and just go with what you feel
is right.
[DURAN] I know in your heart
you've probably already decided.
[ITAMI] C'mon don't give me that
look.
[TUKA] Okay...
[ITAMI] I'll be back in no time.
[TUKA] Yeah.
[TUKA] And when you are...
[TUKA] Everything... everything
will be normal again!
[PILOT] Ready for dust off.
[TUKA] Everything...
everything will be
normal again !
[ITAMI] Sorry old man!
I'm not making this trip!
[KUWABARA]  What?!
[ITAMI] Tukaaa!
[TUKA] But father...
[ITAMI] I decided I'm going to
stay by your side.
[TUKA] Can you... do that?
[ITAMI] Sure. Tuka.
We're going together.
[YANAGIDA]
What the hell... Itami...
You unbelievable ass!
You abandon your mission
to go dragon hunting with
one elf girl!
[YANAGIDA] What the hell
am I supposed to tell the brass
to make this absurd
decision of yours sound
half‐way reasonable?!
[ITAMI] I thought that was
kinda your specialty.
You listen to me. You are going
to rejoin the team.
[YANAGIDA] You are going to
finish your mission,
and then take your troops to
hunt the dragon.
Maybe that way, I can...
[ITAMI] Yanagida,
I've already decided.
[YANAGIDA]  Goddamn it
what do you need?
[ITAMI] A transport vehicle,
some backup fuel,
weapons and ammunition,
And probably some food.
Enough to sustain two people for
a week I guess.
[YANAGIDA] One week rations for
two people...
Are you sure that's all the food
you want to bring along?
[ITAMI] Yeah.
[YANAGIDA]  Sure about
that?
[ITAMI] Yeah...
Of course I'm sure.
Everyone else is already...
[ITAMI] Uh Rory?!
[RORY] If you wanted to ask a
girl
to fight a ferocious beast,
all you had to do was ask.
[ITAMI] Uh... We're talking
about a flame dragon here.
Oh don't get me all worked up
before we've even left!
Unless you're just planning on
losing before you even start.
[ITAMI] Uh no...
[RORY] Then you may ask me.
[ITAMI] Well...
[ITAMI] Okay okay I'll ask you!
[ITAMI]  Rory. Will you
come with us?
[RORY] Fine, but it'll cost you.
[ITAMI] M'sure it will.
I'm not sure how I can pay you
back though
I've got something in mind.
[ITAMI]  What are
you doing?!
[RORY]  Signing our
contract.
[ITAMI] Our contract?!
Now if you should go
and die on me,
your soul will be mine.
[ITAMI] Wait what?!
Yanagida.
Add another person to the menu.
[LELEI] Make that four.
[ITAMI] You too, Lelei?!
[LELEI] To increase your chances
of survival...
you'll need some magic.
[YAO] Henceforth my fight and my
body are forever yours.
Just tell me what you need.
[ITAMI] I guess I should have
expected you.
Ah well we could always use a
guide along the way.
[YANAGIDA] So that brings up
the total to five people, yes?
[TUKA] I don't understand
why SHE has to come with us?!
[ITAMI] Don't be like that.
She's on her way home, we're
just giving her a ride.
[TUKA]
[YANAGIDA] You'd rather be
screwing around...
and work when it's convenient.
[YANAGIDA] And somewhere in that
mixed up logic...
[YANAGIDA]
You're surrounded by people...
who volunteer to follow you.
[DURAN] That's a good lad.
[YAO] I'm coming... We're all
coming!
[YAO] Hope is on the way!
[TUKA] Let's go Daddy!
Step on it!
[ITAMI] Ha! You got it!
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
The Flame Dragon Once Again.