[ZORZAL] In the great name of
Zorzal El Caesar,
[ZORZAL] I declare... the
foundation of the office of
Crown Prince!
[ZORZAL] As of this moment,
the Empire is under my command!
[ZORZAL] And our Empire is
vulnerable.
[ZORZAL] After suffering great
losses in so many battles, the
Senate chooses not to fight.
[ZORZAL] Instead wants to
surrender to our foes,
[ZORZAL] They wish to sell out
the freedom and dignity
of each and every one of you!
[ZORZAL] All to protect only
themselves!
[PEOPLE]
[ZORZAL] Their true cowardice
and complacency is showing.
We won't entrust our nation to
weakness. No!
This realm is ours!
[ZORZAL] You are the strong and
noble people of this Empire.
[ZORZAL] You are the chosen ones
that have
successfully ruled this realm
for over 600 years.
[ZORZAL] Now is the time for us
to come together,
We must show what we are capable
of.
[ZORZAL] It is time to overcome
the turmoil around us,
And grow our Empire's strength
and power.
[ZORZAL] Let us all gather
around our flag,
[ZORZAL] And let us all make
history together!
[CROWD] Zorzal, Zorzal, Zorzal,
Zorzal, Zorzal, Zorzal, Zorzal
[ZORZAL] And so... now it's time
[ZORZAL] To begin the war with
Japan
[IMAZU] Well... it looks like
Prince Zorzal's coup d'etat was
successful. Over.
[NYUTABARU] Yes. That's right...
And the Empire's under martial
law,
[NYUTABARU] So leaving the
premises is restricted. Over.
[IMAZU] Is the Vice Minister
safe?
[NYUTABARU] Yes. Jade Palace is
protected under the agreement.
[NYUTABARU] there should be no
need to worry.
[IMAZU] We are in no position to
let our guard down.
See if you can find out
the condition of the Emperor.
Over.
[NYUTABARU] Will do. Over and
out.
[PINA] Did you learn the
whereabouts of Lelei?
[GREY] Yes. Apparently, she is
trying to become a master of the
magic arts.
[PINA] She's in Rondel?
[ZORZAL] Pina.
[PINA] Brother!
[ZORZAL] That girl is a hero of
the entire Empire.
Bring her back safe and sound.
[GREY] Of course, your Highness.
[PINA] Zorzal. May I ask you
something?
[ZORZAL] What is it now?
It may not look it,
but I am a busy man.
[PINA] Would you mind telling me
why you're placing
the pro‐peace representatives
under house arrest?
[ZORZAL] Oh yes of course that.
[PINA] What did you say?
[ZORZAL] The
representatives‐for‐peace
have been receiving bribes and
other gifts from Japan.
[PINA] That's absurd! Do you
have any evidence of this?!
[ZORZAL] Oh I will find proof
eventually.
A definitive source that cannot
be rebuked.
[PINA] Then tell me. What is it
you're planning to do?
[ZORZAL] Nothing at all...
In the absence of the Emperor...
[ZORZAL] I am simply to carry
out my Princely duty as I see
fit.
[ZORZAL] But if you stand in my
way...
[PINA] Will you make a prisoner
out of me as well?
[ZORZAL] That shouldn't be
necessary.
I need you to act as an
intermediary peace negotiator
with Japan.
[PINA] You're continuing with
the negotiations?
[ZORZAL] Of course I am.
But without... resorting to a
defeatist mentality,
[ZORZAL] and after taking
measures to ensure our victory
that is. Understand?
[HELM] Um Prince Zorzal, we have
come at your request.
[ZORZAL] These are the men
I have appointed as my generals.
[ZORZAL] I'm sure you know a few
of them.
[PINA] I do.
[ZORZAL] Very well...
I called you for a simple
reason.
[ZORZAL] Gentlemen do you
have a plan in place...
to fight the upcoming battle.
[HELM] Our enemy is extremely
powerful, sire.
If we approach it as a
traditional fight, we'll surely
lose.
[HELM] We will need to adopt a
more sinister course.
[ZORZAL] Really now. A sinister
course?
[HELM] Yes.
We will gather goblins,
[HELM] And have them attack the
villages near Alnus.
[PINA] What?!
[HELM] And have them attack the
villages near Alnus.
[ZORZAL] Don't you think
that would provoke them.
Our enemy will seek
retaliation and invade us.
[KALASTA] There's no need to
worry about that.
This will be the work of
a group of freelance thieves
and bandits.
[HELM] And we can take it even
further.
Our soldiers could disguise
themselves to look like
the enemy when they are
attacking the villages.
[ZORZAL] Ha Ha. So we make our
enemy look like the bad guys.
[HELM] That way their reputation
will be compromised..
and our people will turn against
them.
[PINA] You should be ashamed of
yourselves!
You are supposed to be a
dignified soldier of the
Empire?!
[HELM] It is the only way we can
fight them.
We can't possibly win otherwise,
Princess Pina.
I think you know that.
[ZORZAL] Very good
[ZORZAL] Proceed with the plan.
[PINA] But you can't!
[HELM] We'll start preparations
right away.
[PINA] Helm... It was a mistake
to have negotiated your release.
[HELM] I have no words to
describe how grateful I am
for your kindness, Princess...
as my former superior.
[HELM] Now leave everything to
us, and get yourself some rest.
[PINA] Diavo! Brother!
[PINA] What's going on?!.. What
is this, where are you going?
[DIAVO] Just keep moving.
[PINA] You answer me right now!
[DIAVO] I'm getting as far as I
can from this place.
[PINA] But you can't!
You must help me stop Zorzal
from destroying everything.
You have responsibilities
as a member of the imperial
family
[DIAVO] I am carrying out
my responsibilities.
I shall stop our deranged
brother by gathering forces
from foreign nations.
[PINA] What? You're inviting
them into the Empire?!
[DIAVO] I'm afraid there's no
other way.
[DIAVO] Get out of the road you
idiot!
[PINA] Diavo. Please think about
this.
[PINA] If you do this our land
and people will be taken away.
[PINA] There will be no Empire
left.
[DIAVO] And if Zorzal's
dictatorship continues.
The empire will fall anyway.
[DIAVO] That bigot needs to be
forced into listening
through a demonstration of
strength.
[DIAVO] That's all I can tell
you now get out of the way!
[PINA] I will not!
[DIAVO] Move or I'll run you
over!
[PINA] If it's for the sake of
the Empire...
I don't care what happens to me!
[DIAVO] Oh, grow up! Hyaa!!
[PINA] Stop! Diavo!
[DIAVO] Ideals aren't going to
help you survive, Pina!
[LELEI] I would like to
introduce you to her properly.
This is Mimoza.
[LELEI] She's a wizard and a
great sage.
She's one of the elders in
Rondel.
[MIMOZA] It is nice to meet you.
So how long has it been, Rory?
[ITAMI] Huh?
[TUKA] You know each other?
[LELEI] I had no idea.
[MIMOZA] We traveled
together awhile back.
[MIMOZA] About 50 years ago,
doesn't that sound right? Rory?
[RORY] Mimoza... You're so...
old.
[MIMOZA] Oh my. Yes, I am. I've
earned some wrinkles haven't I?
[MIMOZA] Sure you're jealous.
[MIMOZA] So I heard that you
went on
a little holiday to the other
side of the Gate.
[MIMOZA] What was it like over
there?
[RORY] Hmm... It was just
lovely...
the streets were nice and
impeccably clean.
[TUKA] Every shop had a wide
variety of products.
And looked like they were doing
well.
[LELEI] I especially liked their
wonderful bookstores.
[ITAMI] Lelei?
[LELEI] They had books from
every field you can think of.
Sold at very affordable prices
even for the commoners.
[MIMOZA] The commoners could buy
books?
[LELEI] In Japan, the ability
to publish books is very
accessible.
[LELEI] There was even a market
with books by amateurs for sale.
[MIMOZA] Oh dear dear. That
would be incredible to have
books for everyone.
[ARPEGGIO] Oh no no no!
That's one thing that can never
ever happen! Never ever ever
ever...
Never ever.
If my magic encyclopedia that I
copied by hand night after night
after night were to go down in
price...
[ITAMI] What is wrong with her?
[Arpeggio rants]
[LELEI] One of Arpeggio's
jobs is a scribe writing books.
She's upset how cheap
they are to make.
And how easy her job is.
[Arpeggio continues]
[MIMOZA] Her specialty
is in mineral magic,
which can be rather pricey
in order to maintain.
...AND if book prices go
down on top of that...
Ugh... How will I pay
for food and rent?
I'll get kicked out if I miss
another payment...
[LELEI] Now don't you worry.
I'm sure the price won't drop
right away.
[LELEI] That would be far into
the future.
[ARPEGGIO] Sure about that?
Welllll why didn't you say so,
you trying to scare me?!
What. Is. Your. Deal?!
Anyway. Like I said...
she's a mineral specialist.
[MIMOZA] Which means she could
really be of help
for your resource survey.
[ITAMI] That sounds great, would
you be up for that?
[ARPEGGIO] Well sure... I would
be happy to help you.
[MIMOZA] Are you curious?
You seem to be very interested
in that picture.
[RORY] Oh no not really.
Glad you came, even if you were
just tagging along.
I've been wanting to give you an
answer
to
the homework you gave me.
[ITAMI] Homework?
[RORY] That's correct.
I gave her a problem to resolve
before we parted ways.
[RORY] To answer why there are
such varied species in this
world.
[ITAMI] Is there an answer to
that?
[RORY] Of course there is.
[MIMOZA] It is because...
[MIMOZA] Of the Gate. Oh dear.
[MIMOZA] The creation legend for
the elves
begins with a man and woman
...who were led by a God to the
Forest of Origin.
[MIMOZA] Now, elves are spread
throughout the realm,
but every tribe has their own
version of the origin story.
[MIMOZA] When you ask the
location
of the Forest of Origin,
...the elves in the
north point to the south,
...and the elves in the
south point to the north.
And it all leads to one
location.
[ITAMI] So... Alnus.
[MIMOZA] That's correct.
[LELEI] So all elves come from
Alnus?
[MIMOZA] Oh well not just elves.
All sorts of species across the
region
claim Alnus as their home.
[ARPEGGIO] And what do you think
about that, Master?
[MIMOZA] I've traveled this
world my entire life
and my research has born much
fruit.
[RORY] And tell me, what is the
answer
you were finally able to
discover?
[MIMOZA] That there are
different kinds of demi‐humans
throughout this world,
and all of them moved here
once the Gate was opened.
[MIMOZA] The GATE remains
dormant for several hundred or
even thousands of years at a
time.
But then, it opens.
And every time it does,
new inhabitants emerge from it.
Sometimes they fight other
species who were here first
[MIMOZA] and other times they're
able to mix peacefully.
They become rooted, and join our
existence.
[MIMOZA] Then, as always,
the Gate goes back into a long
slumber.
That history has been repeated
for as long as time.
[MIMOZA] And we are a part it.
Judging by antiquity and
literature,
We're most likely the most
recent to come through.
[MIMOZA] It makes sense the
Empire regard Alnus as holy
ground...
And why the new foreign visitors
have chosen to set up their base
there.
[RORY] Very well done, Mimoza
[MIMOZA] Oh dear! Thank you
ma'am!
I'm finally free! Oh Thank the
gods!
[ITAMI] Did you already know
about all that, Rory?
[RORY] Yes, for the most part.
It is but God's will in the end.
Demigods like myself only follow
their will
and do our duty to protect this
world.
At times we guide those
exhibiting high potential,
and sometimes we have to
eliminate those who venture
astray.
It's how we maintain harmony for
all who live with us in this
realm.
[LELEI] I don't think I ever
heard that story.
That's because it's MY research
that I spent years studying.
I don't think Kato is very
interested in much history.
[ARPEGGIO] That's what I've been
telling you all along.
Instead of learning from one
person,
staying here allows you to learn
several points of view.
[LELEI] If I stayed here. I
couldn't try for the
rank of master for a very long
time.
[ARPEGGIO] That may be true...
but you'd've learned more.
[MIMOZA] So then...
What is it that you're going
to be presenting Lily?
[MIMOZA] I'd love to hear what
you've been working on.
[ARPEGGIO] What's that thing?
[LELEI] It's a device from the
Japanese.
[ARPEGGIO] Oh God with this,
no one would ever even need
books anymore!
[MIMOZA] Look at that,
it's even more amazing inside.
[MIMOZA] She's incorporating the
knowledge
of another world into the
framework of magic.
[MIMOZA] This might be able to
make even the most
stubborn of old mages shut up
and listen for once.
[ARPEGGIO] My own little sister.
She has completely surpassed me.
I hate this! I've got no money,
and my sister's way ahead of me.
I've been working on my research
for years
and gotten absolutely nowhere.
[ARPEGGIO] Maybe I just don't
have any talent.
[ARPEGGIO] Wait I know! I'll
get married and start a family!
[ARPEGGIO] What kind of man is
Itami?!
[ITAMI]
Yoji Itami. He's an Officer.
And he's also a Lord... Of Elbe.
[LELEI] And an honorary tribal
leader of the dark elves,
Itami holds many titles.
[TUKA] Are you alright, father?
Hmm. So he's an elite noble with
an elf child.
How's that possible?
[LELEI] Um... Don't worry about
it.
[ARPEGGIO] What about his
finances?
[YAO] He possesses a large rare
diamond.
It was given to him by the
people of my tribe.
[YAO] About this big.
[ARPEGGIO] OH! Is he married?!
Itami is currently single.
[BOTH] That's perfect!
[MIMOZA] Oh my oh dear.
[LELEI] No. He is no longer
single.
Itami and I completed the Three
Nights Ceremony.
[TUKA] Ah! When was that?!
[RORY] You'd better explain
yourself!
[ITAMI] What!?
What are you talking about?!
What is the Three Nights
Ceremony?
Our practice of proving
common‐law marriage,
if a man and a woman share a
bedroom for three nights.
[MIMOZA] In other words, it's a
declaration to let
everyone know that you are now
betrothed!
[ITAMI] What?! I don't remember
doing that.
[LELEI] We've slept together
exactly three times.
[LELEI] The first was
at the camp.
The second was in Risa's room.
[LELEI] And the third was
the hotel in Hakone.
That makes three.
[ITAMI] The camp, Risa,
the hotel... I suppose so.
[TUKA] Counting like that,
I've slept with him way more
than three times!
[MIMOZA] Oh, bigamy?
[LELEI] Well you had lost
your mind at the time
and thought that Itami was your
deceased father .
[LELEI] So it really doesn't
count.
[RORY] Itami!
Unbelievable. All this time
and not once did you try
to take advantage of me.
[RORY] Guess you were too busy
getting frisky with every other
girl here.
[RORY] Care to enlighten me,
lover boy?
[LELEI] Arpeggio?
[ARPEGGIO] Defeated yet again.
[ARPEGGIO] My sister has bested
me academically,
financially, and romantically.
It's almost as if have no
dignity as an older sister.
There's only one more thing
left to do.
[ARPEGGIO] Do not hesitate.
This is necessary for the future
of our sisterhood.
[MIMOZA] Ahhhhh.
[MIMOZA] Oh dear, oh my...
[MIMOZA] Oh dear, oh dear ...
[MIMOZA] Oh my, oh dear ...
[ARPEGGIO] Now! Do you admit
defeat?! [MIMOZA] Oh my, oh dear
...
[RORY] As of now, the 13th
Battle
of the Lalena Sisters is
approved.
[RORY] In the name of mee!!
[RORY] The rules are simple:
You are not allowed
to kill your opponent.
That's very important.
There are to be no unsightly
marks to the face.
Or you shall
answer to me, understand?.
[continues]
[ITAMI] What is going on here?
[MIMOZA] These two still like to
fight each other, whoo!
A bit differently from before,
but I'll take what I can get.
[ITAMI] Heh. This isn't good.
[RORY] Are you ready?
[RORY] Begin!
[ITAMI] What is that?
[MIMOZA] You like it...?
Arpeggio uses minerals as a
catalyst,
[MIMOZA] so she can skip the
laws of science
and interfere with the
principles.
[ITAMI] I don't know what that
means,
but I do know that this isn't
any normal sibling rivalry.
[MIMOZA] It is a normal wizard
fight, though.
[MIMOZA] Oh dear.
What an exquisite show of magic.
Oh my.
[ARPEGGIO] Oh No!
[ITAMI] What's that thing
surrounding them?
[MIMOZA] It's a barrier of
magical protection.
[MIMOZA] Protecting one's self
is the first thing the
wizards of the Lyndon Faction
learn
when they are new to the craft.
[MIMOZA] This battle is about
who can break
the opponent's barrier first.
[ARPEGGIO] Stupid idiot
genius...
[ITAMI] Hello, 'scuse me,
Rory...
Don't you think this has gone a
bit too far?
[RORY] If we stop them now,
they'll never reach
reconciliation.
[ITAMI] Maybe, but I don't want
anybody to get hurt.
[RORY] Just shut up and watch
them do their thing.
[ARPEGGIO] My special attack!
Big Sister's Dignity! Hwaaah!
[ARPEGGIO] Craaaaaaap.
[ITAMI] What's happening now?
[RORY] Oh a tie‐breaker.
[RORY] Grey Co Aldo.
[RORY] This is my holy
battlefield
and you have just brazenly
soiled it.
[RORY] You'd better have some
justification.
[GREY] I suggest you and
your people leave this place
as soon as possible.
[GREY] I killed one assassin,
but there will be others
on the way.
[ITAMI] Assassins?
[BOY] Mommy. Where'd our house
go?
[GREY] I received an order from
Princess Pina.
I'm to invite Lelei to the
Imperial Capital,
[GREY] so I came to Rondel to
find her.
[SHANDY] But while we were on
the way here,
we received information that
there
are assassins after her.
[ITAMI] You have any idea who
might've hired them?
[GREY] It's only a speculation
on my part.
So I should probably avoid
saying who I think it is.
[GREY] To be fair.
[SHANDY] Ever since the head of
the flame dragon was hung for
all to see,
Lelei's fame has been
growing in the Imperial Capital.
[SHANDY] Whoever it is..
they don't like sharing the
spotlight with others.
[ARPEGGIO] What do you mean,
the head of the flame dragon?
What the heck does that have to
do with my stupid jerk sister?
[GREY] You mean she didn't tell
you?
[GREY] Your little sister
joined arms with the people
here.
Together they attacked
and defeated the flame dragon.
[ARPEGGIO] Oh yeah right that's
good.
Come on, you're messing with me.
I know she's all
smart and everything,
But she wouldn't be
able
to kill a flame dragon.
Could she?
IS IT TRUE?!
[ITAMI] The dark elves told us
that they would
show the Empire the head of the
dragon,
and let everyone know that it's
dead.
[GREY] Their presentation was
effective.
[ITAMI] But why is it that only
Lelei
is becoming famous for it?
[SHANDY] That probably
has something to do with the
fact
that she is the only one who is
a
citizen of human descent from
the Empire.
[LELEI] I am a member of Lourdo.
I don't ever remember becoming a
citizen of the Empire.
[GREY] The people care not about
such things.
[GREY] You are under no one's
submission
and yet still did something so
great.
[GREY] That is the reason people
have been praising you.
[ITAMI] Okay so it's safe to
say,
whoever's hiring the assassin...
Is jealous of Lelei.
[ZORZAL] Ooh! This is so good,
Furuta!
[RUFLUS] Are you sure about
this?
[THULE] You have a problem
with Prince Zorzal's new
legislation?
[RUFLUS] 'Course not...
But the way it's worded
is rather confusing...
As to what sort of crimes are
enforceable and by whom.
[THULE] That is preciously what
His Highness wants.
[RUFLUS] I understand...
I'll pull some strings in the
Senate. To see it's heard.
[THULE] I take it you'll be able
to ensure
the bill gets the support it
deserves.
[RUFLUS] I will make the proper
arrangements.
Leave it to me.
[ITAMI] The Piper?
[GREY] Yes. He's one of the
assassins
most recently hired.
[GREY] He's extremely deadly,
the two of us would be no match
for him.
[RORY] Given her achievement
of killing the flame dragon, it
is no surprise.
[SHANDY] If you please,
we will need your assistance
with this, Itami.
[ITAMI] No one needs to beg me.
I'll protect Lelei anyday.
[GREY] You're the man in green
I've been hearing about.
[GREY] Why don't the two of us
join forces
and take out these cowardly
assassins.
[ITAMI] I don't think so.
[ITAMI] I've a better idea...
Run away.
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
The Lovers.