[LELEI] Japan's Self Defense
Force
was dispatched to the
mysterious Special Region.
Where peace talks were
interrupted by an earthquake.
Itami and his team rescue
Noriko, a Japanese girl enslaved
by Prince Zorzal.
[LELEI] Now, Itami, hoping to
save Tuka's sanity,
embarks on a quest to slay the
flame dragon that killed her
father.
[DELILAH] la‐la‐la‐la‐la! Out in
the city I roam.
Alnus is my favorite place!
Everything is so easy!
And the food is so tasteee!
The sun up in the sky... it's
shining down on me.
Come and feel the glow of Alnus
It's the place to be!
[DELILAH] Thank you!
[CROWD] Wow! [CROWD] Bravo!
[DELILAH] From Italica?
What? Japanese?
Why would she order such a
thing?
Here I sit, the great queen
of the proud Voglia bunnies
How long must I suffer at the
hands of that monster?
[BOULO]
I am here for you,
as always, Thule
[THULE] How did it go?
[BOULO] Letter was delivered
[THULE] Good. You can go.
[BOULO] As you wish.
[THULE] Now the Folmar's spy
embedded in Alnus will be
killing Noriko for us.
And the traitorous voglia, who's
after my life, will be none the
wiser.
If I make it look like Pina
ordered it,
then the relationship between
Japan and the Empire
will fall apart, and war will be
inevitable.
[THULE] And Prince Zorzal, the
prick who destroyed my tribe,
Will go down in agony, along
with this God‐forsaken Empire.
[DELILAH] Gods and apostles
that protect us from on high.
I dedicate this prayer and
sacrifice all I have to you.
I give myself to the flames of
your will.
Emroy, God of War, Hardy, God of
Hades,
Deldote, God of Pact, Palapan,
God of Vengeance.
My body is your sword of
retribution, that will take the
life of my enemy.
Until I have my revenge on Queen
Thule,
who threw away her pride as a
voglia and betrayed us all,
[DELILAH] I shall not die!
[HIGAKI] So, let me get this
straight,
First Lieutenant Itami received
intel
about an underground
natural resource.
[HIGAKI] leaving Sergeant Major
Kuwabara in charge
while he went alone to
investigate.
Is that what you're telling me?
[YANAGIDA] Yes Sir... The
Ministry is anxious for
information on any strategy
resources.
[YANAGIDA] Considering the
situations surrounding us,
we must find as many locations
as we can before things get
worse.
[HIGAKI] I heard there are
dragons in that area.
[YANAGIDA] I'm quite sure he's
aware of that.
[HIGAKI] Then why would he
choose to go in all by himself?
[YANAGIDA] Because he's an
idiot, sir.
[YANAGIDA] Well... That's... all
the groundwork...
I just need the approval from
the lieutenant general.
[YANAGIDA]
[HAZAMA] Uh...what in the holy
hell is Itami thinking?
[YANAGIDA] Sir...The letter
5‐304 from the Ministry.
Entitled "Strategy Resources in
the Special Region"
is what caused Itami to take
action!
[HAZAMA] Yes yes but... that's
just his official purpose.
[YANAGIDA] Official or not,
First Lieutenant Itami
went to search for resources!
[HAZAMA] Hmm... I see.
Well gentlemen, it seems we have
a dumbass among us.
But we can't just watch him die
can we.
[KURIHAMA] No matter what kind
of soldier he is... he's still
one of us, after all.
[HAZAMA] You're damn right
soldier. He's our dumbass!
Colonel Kamo!
[KAMO] Sir!
[HAZAMA] Put the 1st Combat Team
on standby.
Wait for the Air Self‐Defense
Force's contact.
And support based on their
intel.
We need to back up their search
for resources.
Lieutenant Colonel!
[KAMIKODA] Sir!
[HAZAMA] I am requesting
air reconnaissance.
You're on C. A. P. Prepare to
encounter a Special Region
Class‐A Vermin.
That is all.
[SOLDIERS] Understood!
[SOLDIERS] Let's go, Kurihama.
Alright let's do this.
[KURIHAMA] Let's get to it
[YANAGIDA] How can they just...
prepare a strike so easily?
[HAZAMA] You don't happen to
speak the special region's
language, do you?
I have someone that I would like
you to meet.
After you close your mouth, of
course.
[DURAN] Enter.
[YANAGIDA] Good evening, Sir.
[DURAN] I've been waiting for
you to come and see me.
[DURAN] I'm Duran, King of the
State of Elbe.
[YANAGIDA] It's nice to meet
you.
[DURAN] In my country, a dauphin
is supposed
to administer the government.
[DURAN] I bet they're relieved
I'm out of the picture.
If you would...
Could I trouble you
to send these
to Duke Clemson and Count Watt.
[DURAN] In order to get the Elbe
back in my hands,
[DURAN] I need them to bring
together
the powerful nobles throughout
the area.
[YANAGIDA] We want no part of
your family feud.
[YANAGIDA] You can ask that kind
of favor of the Empire.
[DURAN] Hmph... I'm done with
the Empire.
[YANAGIDA] So if we were to help
you with this,
what do you have to offer us in
return?
[DURAN] If you were to back
me...
You may cross our borders in
order to fight the flame dragon.
[DURAN] How's that sound?
I'm pretty sure we
wouldn't have
any trouble getting permission
from the Prince.
If we sent your head pickled in
a jar.
[DURAN] How delightful of you.
[DURAN] I've heard rumors of one
of your men willing to fight the
flame dragon...
So what is it you want?
[YANAGIDA] Underground mining
rights, and tax exemptions.
[DURAN] Gold and copper are the
sources of our nation's wealth.
[DURAN] Can't give you those.
[YANAGIDA] Then everything
except for the gold and copper.
[DURAN] Wait a minute! Are you
saying that there are other
valuables buried there?
[YANAGIDA] F'you don't know,
it's like they never existed.
Or should I go ahead and start
preparing the salt brine?
[DURAN] Uhhh... Hmph! Fine have
it your way then.
All underground resources
save for those used as currency.
[DURAN] Will that do?
[YANAGIDA] And don't forget the
tax exemption.
[DURAN] You are a canny man.
[YANAGIDA] Thank you. The JSDF
will provide protection for your
safe return.
It's on the way to the flame
dragon. So it'll be no
inconvenience.
[DURAN] Hm.. In that case, I
hereby give you permission to
cross our borders.
I am pleased we were able to
reach an agreement.
[YANAGIDA] Hm. Well as long as
you can keep up your end of the
bargain,
Japan will uphold a friendly
diplomatic relationship.
[YANAGIDA] Damn it!
This is not at all turning out
the way I had planned.
Lieutenant Hazama and Lord Duran
are both working to help Itami,
[YANAGIDA] And now so am I...
[YANAGIDA] That lazy slack!
I hope it rains on his stupid
girl parade!
[ITAMI] It's really coming down.
[RORY] I guess that's a problem
isn't it?
[YAO] The ground is unstable
enough already.
We should probably get out of
this area
before it gets any worse.
[ITAMI] I think you're right.
[SOCIAL WORKER] I am very sorry.
We've been looking for your
family since Ginza.
[SOCIAL WORKER] We assume that
they were also
victims of the tragedy that
befell us that day.
[NORIKO]  Mom, are
you there?
[PHONE] The number
you have dialed
has been disconnected
or is no longer in service.
Please check the number and...
[NORIKO] Dad... Mom...
Hiroki...
[NORIKO]
Maybe it's time for me to die as
well.
[DELILAH] Really.
[NORIKO] Who're you?
[DELILAH] I would feel sorrow
ending someone's life who wishes
to keep it,
[DELILAH] but if that is truly
your desire,
then I shall be doing you a
favor.
[NORIKO] You're going to...kill
me?
[DELILAH] Yes...you shall get
what you wish.
[NORIKO] So be it.
[DELILAH] I'm sorry. I honestly
have no choice.
[NORIKO] I really wouldn't like
to feel pain though.
[DELILAH]  Hmm.
[DELILAH] How should you like it
then?
I don't think I know how to do
this
without it hurting at least a
little bit.
[NORIKO]  You remind me
of a slave I knew.
Her name is Tyule.
[DELILAH]  What did
you just say?
[YANAGIDA] You!
Get away from her!
[SOLDIERS] What was that? It was
outside.
Over there!
[YANAGIDA]
[YANAGIDA] Aagh!
[YANAGIDA] God dammit..
[YANAGIDA] <pained manic
breathing>
[YANAGIDA] Die! You! Damn!
Bitch......
[YANAGIDA] Ach... ooh...
Dammit... aah...
[MUTY] Ahhhhh! Oh my god!
[MEIA] What's the matter with
you?
[MUTY] It's Delilah... She
stabbed Yanagida!
[KIKUCHI] Chef Gaston, can you
confirm that Delilah was indeed
a spy?
[GASTON] I... tried to talk her
out it, but she wouldn't listen.
[KIKUCHI] I understand. Thank
you for your time, sir.
[GASTON] Um Excuse me
[KIKUCHI] Yes?
[GASTON] I guess this means
we're going to be shut down
and banned from the village.
[KIKUCHI] Nonsense.
You have nothing to do with
this terrible incident.
[KIKUCHI] What is this?
Was she in the middle of some
kind of ritual or somethin'?
[MP] Sir.
[KIKUCHI] Uh‐huh.
[MP] I found this. I
thought it might be important.
[KIKUCHI] The Folmar's family
crest.
[KAINE] We already know that you
sold
the great family's parchment on
the black market.
[BARTHOLOMEW] That's not true!
I don't know anything about
that.
[YOGA] Take a close look at
this.
We've discovered two sets of
fingerprints on this paper.
[YOGA] The one circled in red
belongs to Delilah,
[YOGA] And the other...care to
take a guess?
[BARTHOLOMEW]
[PERSONNEL] Folmar's butler...
has confessed.
[PERSONNEL] Those trying to
prevent peace talks
framed the Folmar family
and tried to kill Noriko
Mochizuki
[PERSONNEL] And the one who both
knows of her
and benefits the most would
be...
Uh..it's Prince Zorzal
It takes around 10 days to get
to the Capital.
They will not be aware of their
failure yet.
[IMAZU] So what do you suggest?
[PERSONNEL] We should inform the
Folmars
the assassination attempt failed
and our team is en route.
There we should be able to find
out the source of the leak.
We need to investigate the
people closest to Zorzal.
The 3rd Recon Unit is in the
Imperial Capital right now.
[HAZAMA] That's perfect.
I want you to send new orders to
the unit,
have them infiltrate Zorzal's
camp and start sweating him out.
Someone deceived those under our
protection.
They have spilled one of our
men's blood and they're going to
regret it!
[ALL] Yes, sir!
[ZORZAL] Hey!
[ZORZAL] So! Who in the hell
cooked this ma nuga meat?!
[ZORZAL] It was you wasn't it?!
[ZORZAL] You are an artist!
[ZORZAL] You must be the same
chef from Pina's party the other
day huh?
[ZORZAL] I could never forget
how incredible that meal was.
[FURUTA] That was me.
[ZORZAL] Well excellent...
In that case I have an important
job for you my friend.
[ZORZAL] Come on by the palace
tomorrow. You got it?
[FURUTA] Who's that?
[MAID] I don't know who she
thinks she is?
But I bet she's the prince's
favorite plaything.
[MAID] She sure seems proud of
herself.
[KURIHAMA] Current altitude:
11,000 feet. 10 minutes to the
border.
Cruising at 280 knots. Revised
heading of 1‐9‐0.
[KURIHAMA] Turning now.
[KAMIKODA] Copy.
[KAMIKODA] It's been three days.
We should've seen it by now.
[KURIHAMA] Well when you do,
don't just start shooting at it.
The goal here is to evaluate its
capabilities.
[KAMIKODA] I know.
[KURIHAMA] That thing's one
tough mother.
According to the report, it has
armor as strong as a tank.
[KURIHAMA] And neither the 7F
nor 20mm can penetrate it.
[KAMIKODA] We should've asked
Daddy‐o
to let us bring an ASM or a
rocket launcher.
[KURIHAMA] Yeah well
the thing moves as fast
as a fighter plane.
There's no way we can hit it
with stuff like that.
[KAMIKODA] Ok. We got our bogie!
[KURIHAMA] Confirming target is
a dragon,
Special Region Class A vermin.
[KAMIKODA] If I shoot, I can hit
it.
[KURIHAMA] Easy.
20mm rounds won't do anything.
We don't want to show
our hand just yet.
[KAMIKODA] Roger.
[KAMIKODA] Uh oh. It's mad at
us!
[MIZUHARA] Look how quick it is.
That thing can turn on a dime.
[NISHIMOTO] It can bend its body
freely.
We don't want to find ourselves
in a dog fight with it.
[KURIHAMA] Check it out. It has
hover capabilities, too.
So it can move like a plane or a
chopper. Not bad.
[KAMIKODA] Are you finished
assessing it yet?
[KURIHAMA] Yeah, I think I get
the general idea.
[KAMIKODA] Good ...Then it's my
turn!
[KAMIKODA] Let's see what you
got.
[HEAD OF MAINTENANCE] Real nice
job, ladies.
Urk!
[HEAD OF MAINTENANCE]
Did you want it to disintegrate
in midair or what?
We don't always have these
parts in stock y'know.
[KAMIKODA] A flying lizard was
trying to kill me
with its fire breathing mouth.
[KAMIKODA] That is not a fair
man's fight if you ask me!
[HEAD OF MAINTENANCE] Oh shut
up! That big dumb monster
doesn't know what a fair man's
fight is!
[HEAD OF MAINTENANCE]
And besides it could be a girl!
[KAMIKODA] Uh yes of course,
sir.
[ITAMI] I think this is where we
are now.
We've passed through Tongut,
Hebrae, and Gremina.
[ITAMI] And this morning we left
Metabal,
so... yeah we must be at the
Telilia Plain.
[RORY] Why did you take
such a strange path to get here?
[YAO] Yes I'm sorry.
I was following the rumors I'd
heard
about the movements of the green
ones.
[LELEI] This is the way through
the Korlo Mountains.
The road is wider, but steep.
[LELEI] And this goes by the
Gurban River.
It's longer, but more flat.
[ITAMI] Either way, the road
conditions are not great.
[ITAMI] Lelei, would you help us
out?
[RORY] How much longer will the
magic work on her?
[ITAMI] Yao. The dragon has been
showing up
in the Schwartz Woods, hasn't
it?
[YAO] Mostly in the southern
region including the forest.
[YAO] But, if you really want to
find the flame dragon,
we should make our way to the
Lordom Valley.
[ITAMI] Remember our purpose
is for Tuka to get revenge for
her father's death.
[ITAMI] I'm sorry but we did not
come here to save your people.
[YAO] But there's someone there
who can tell us exactly where
the dragon lives.
[ITAMI]  Well that could
help us.
Then I guess... we should start
heading
towards the Lordom Valley.
[ITAMI] But let me make one
thing clear.
We're not fighting that thing in
the valley.
[ITAMI] Not interested in being
at the bottom of a kill box.
[LELEI] Here we are. Lordom
Valley.
[YAO] Wait here for a minute.
I'll let my people know we have
arrived.
[TUKA] So... Is this it?
[ITAMI] Yeah...
How was your nap?
[TUKA] It was just lovely.
Why would they choose to live in
a place
where's there's hardly any green
around?
[ITAMI] I don't know. But there
must be some reason for it.
[RORY]  Dark elves?!
[KUROW] Who are you and what are
you doing here?!
[ITAMI] Tuka, run!
[ITAMI] Can you hear me?! Run!
[ITAMI] You need to get away
from here now! Go!
[RORY]  That was quiet
impressive.
[ITAMI] Tuka. That's the flame
dragon.
That's the beast that murdered
your father.
[TUKA]  You're a liar!
My father is not dead!
Because you're right here,
Daddy...
[ITAMI] I am not your father,
dammit!
[TUKA] You're not?
[RORY] If it's on the ground, I
can get to it!
[KUROW] Don't hesitate! Keep
shooting!
[LELEI] Come on. Can't get my
aim down.
[ITAMI] Tuka!
That dragon is your enemy.
Put that bastard in the cross
hairs, and pull the trigger.
[TUKA] No!!!!
[ITAMI] Open your eyes! Look!
[ITAMI] Pull..the..trigger!
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
The Battle.