Lelei:
Japan's Self Defense Force
was dispatched
to the mysterious
Special Region.
Where their Emperor has
unexpectedly collapsed
and Prince Zorzal
has taken advantage.
Running from the oppression,
Casel and Sherry seek refuge.
Japanese diplomat Sugawara
accepts them for protection.
Outside the gates, Zorzal's Army
and the Order of the Rose,
are poised for
a fierce battle.
Kill them all!
Attack!
(battle cry)
Take them down!
Ready! Raise your
spears... now!
(death screams)
No! Don't
back down!
You cannot escape!
Surrender! ,/
You must realize by now
that you are outmatched!
(growling, panting)
Sweeper:
(battle cry)
(panting, battle cry)
Uhhh. Morita, sir.
What are you
so upset about?
The citizens of the Empire are
currently fighting one another.
They're at Jade Palace,
with the Vice‐Minister.
We need your permission
to rescue our people
immediately from the area.
Can't do it.
Uh... and why not?
It's not the right time.
The delegates from
overseas would not let up.
We were forced to invite them
to see the Region.
And now the media is hungry.
Chomping at the bit
to publicize any missteps.
It's a disaster over there!
Shirayuri and her people
are in danger
and will to be evacuated
immediately from the premises. ,/
It is not safe.
Oh, they'll be fine.
Ah!
Morita:
It's not like they are
completely defenseless.
This 'Order of the Rose' will
do their best to protect them.
You honestly believe that?
Kano:
Huh... Morita? ,/
(sighs)
Look, how I personally
feel about it is irrelevant.
(grunts)
Besides... the plan
that you are proposing ‐
would involve our troops
occupying the Imperial Palace.
Even if it is only temporary...
our people would immediately
be on us to finish it.
To occupy the Special Region
and end the war.
And we can't do that.
We don't have the intel
to take over the entire Empire.
Then we should come out and
explain that to our citizens.
This is much bigger than
just pleasing our citizens.
With the media presence...
we have whole world watching us.
Okay. So what
do you suggest
for dealing with this
rather sensitive matter?
Morita:
As long as our overseas guests
and the media are in the Special
Region, we cannot make a move.
But once they're gone,
you can do whatever you like.
That is a week away, they could
all very well be dead by then.
Sorry but they will just
have to hang on a bit longer.
You are disgusting!
If the Order's security
does get breached...
Imagine the atrocities that
would befall both our delegates
and the people
within Jade Palace.
If something happens to them,
the blame will be on you.
Yes, as I expect
it should.
Stand down now! Why are you
protecting these criminals?!
This building is bound by law
with diplomatic immunity.
I don't care who you are.
Vifita:
Anyone trying to intrude
will be crushed!
In the name of the Emperor!
I must witness this.
Uh?
I'm sorry, Sugawara... ,/
I hope you don't find my need
to watch this event repulsive. ,/
I knew this was
a possibility
when I chose to
come to the palace.
And that's why...
that is why I cannot dishonor
them by looking away.
They are dying
for my freedom.
Is something
wrong, Sugawara?
I just realized
that my actions...
have caused a great deal
of strife and bloodshed.
Do you regret
your decision?
No. If I hadn't stepped in,
I would have regretted it
for the rest of my life.
Oh, Sugawara...
And I refuse to apologize...
for choosing to save yours.
My decision triggered
this struggle.
I know their sacrifice...
is mine to bear.
Casel:
No matter what
you choose,
You still would have
been responsible
for the consequences
of those crimes.
Marquis Casel!
A person who looks away
from a fight
and chooses the
road of disgrace,
will only find himself
trapped between the fight
and the disgrace.
The only option we have‐
is to choose the path
we can live with
for the betterment
of our conscience.
The Empire has requested that I
become Sherry's legal guardian
and to keep her under
my protection and care
as if she were my own.
In other words, as of today,
I am to be your father.
Ah!
Uh...
(sounds of fighting continue)
Gah...
Fall back! Retreat now!
Komurazaki:
(scoffs) Look at
those lazy bastards...
just sitting around
doing nothing.
That is the true character of
the Japanese Self Defense Force.
You see it, don't you?
When our backs our turned...
When the citizens look away,
this is what they do.
They don't look like
they're slacking off to me.
Ohhhh, that's right.
I almost forgot that you were
rescued by them, weren't you?
I was.
It feels like such
a long time since then.
Okay well... it's understandable
you would give them the
benefit of the doubt.
Right now... my job is to be
a liaison for the press corps,
so I need to do whatever I can
to stay neutral in all of this.
Noriko:
But, what seems
strange to me..
is that the reporters
from Japan...
They're the ones most skeptical
of the JSDF activities.
Because that is our job
as true journalists.
I know the people in
Alnus, seem to accept
and trust their presence,
Komurazaki:
But I believe that's because
the area has been staged
for the benefit
of the media.
I bet other areas might
have different reactions.
It's a shame.
Because most likely...
we will only get
to see the places
the JSDF will
allow us to see.
You seem to be harboring some
sort of preconceived notion
that there is some
kind of hidden agenda.
That manner of thinking
is anything but neutral.
There's no such thing as
a neutral point of view
in journalism.
Speak for yourself.
If that's the case...
how can you believe anything?
How can the media ever
report the truth?
The truth is not
the media's responsibility.
We just need the people
to keep tuning in. Grow up.
Nanami:
Excuse meeee!
Noriko, Noriko!
Would you mind helping
us out please?
Sure... what's
the matter Nanami?
A French news team seems
to have gotten themselves
into some sort of trouble
with the locals.
Okay, let's go.
(chuckles)
I'll just stay here
and take some pictures.
A little photo
expose...
on how the SDF is
spending our tax dollars.
French Officer:
It was my understanding
the negotiations
were already in
progress.
We have yet to be able to
sign a cease‐fire agreement.
At the moment, the Empire's
leadership is refusing
to move forward with
the peace summit.
Well if that's
the situation,
then they must accept
an unconditional surrender.
The issue here is how
they're going about it.
That's right.
And according to our sources,
the Empire has begun a series
of aggressive
guerrilla tactics.
That is definitely going
to be a problem for us.
Is it really a full
600 kilometers
to get from here to
the Imperial Capital?
Did we not provide you with
a map of the Special Region?
It's more like a child's
doodle than a map.
I cannot believe that's
the best map you can offer us.
Meia:
Well, this is it.
Whoa!
U.S. Officer:
Is this of the entire Empire?
How much do you want for it?!
Three hundred eighty
thousand please.
I'll take it!
Oh no you won't!
Ahh!
Sold to the lady
from the JSDF!
(JSDF soldiers weeping)
I am keeping this protected!
Been a while since
we were here in Rondel.
Do we honestly need to come back
to this particular city Itami?
Well yeah of course we do.
You have your conference.
If I were to give up
on my degree,
we can avoid a great
deal of trouble.
But there's no guarantee...
that the assassins will
stop looking for you
everywhere else,
you know.
That's right. Even if
we did go back to Alnus,
they would still
be coming for you.
Exactly.
Lelei, let's go.
(snickers)
Hotel Porters:
Here she comes.
Okay Shandy...
whatever you do,
do not open your eyes.
O‐kay...
Itami:
Because if you do, then you're
gonna be in big trouble.
Right. Okay!
(battle cries)
Gotcha!
It is done!
Not this time fellas.
Hotel Porters:
(screaming)
Rory:
(giggling)
Shandy:
(screaming)
Ah!
Ooh!
Ugh!
Rory:
(giggling)
Shandy:
My eyes! My eyes...!
(sobbing)
I think we're safe now.
No one else seems to be coming
down the corridor, father.
It's all clear.
How are the perps doin?
Fine. They're still
alive anyway.
Wait, don't I
recognize you guys?
They are employees
of the hotel.
(groveling)
Talk to me...
We were tricked into
doing this I swear it!
Then tell us
all about it.
We met someone at the bar
who told us about these guys!
They're not really
who they say they are!
That they are really
monstrous murderers,
out to take the lives of any
merchants staying at the hotel!
And we were told that
they're actually felons
wanted by the police!
You just believed
whatever they told you?
We saw the
warrant ourselves,
and we were given part
of the gold bounty
placed upon their head!
Oh and just like that...
you sneak in their
room and try to kill them?
But we didn't
actually do anything!
We got caught, everything's
fine, no one died right? ,/
(crying)
But you tried.
You were stabbing
knives into our beds.
We're very sorry
Hmm. This sounds like something
the piper would try and pull.
Can you tell us
what he looks like?
Well sometimes he's
a human male,
and other times he's
been an elf woman.
He's even been known
to disguise himself
as a dwarf every
now and then.
But what's most scary about him,
is that he can somehow get
inside people's heads
and turn a regular person
into an assassin.
Even the sweetest,
most harmless little child,
or an elderly person
who can barely get around.
So the piper doesn't like
to get his hands dirty.
Unless we can get rid of
the piper once and for all,
His assassins will never
stop coming for us.
All he has to do
is create more.
So they were just
his pathetic pawns
to use in his sick
little game.
Please! Please...
You must forgive me
for what has transpired here!
Your Holiness, and her
wonderful friends!
I know what they did
was horrible,
But all they wanted to do
was to protect the customers
and reputation
of the hotel!
I'm sure you've lost
your trust in the Hotel Shokai,
But these little guys
are still young,
please allow them to
change their ways!
Oh Harmar!
Harmar!
Oh, please
forgive them!
We forgive them.
But you will need
to better educate them
of these sorts
of things.
This cannot happen in
your establishment again.
Ohh! Thank you,
I promise you, it won't!
Hotel Porters:
We promise!
Yeah well it's the
least we could do, y'know.
I will speak to a
very good friend of mine
who runs an inn.
It's just down
the street.
You can move your things
over there right away!
There's no need
for that, sir.
Harmar:
Huh?
Lelei:
Once someone has
been manipulated,
they are more careful
the next time.
Your hotel is now safe.
Are you serious?
We would like to continue
staying here, please.
If that's all right with
everyone else...
Yes! Uh,
certainly!
I am humbled to serve her
Holiness and her dear friends.
Ugh... hooo...
Do you really think it's
a good idea to trust
those little porter guys?
They seem a bit
shady to me.
It's not easy to
change a mind
that fundamentally
knows murder is wrong.
It's a systematic belief.
The piper is likely skilled
at finding minds that
are easily changed.
Okay then.
So he's got a knack
for finding people
who are morally challenged.
"Morally challenged"?
It means people out there
whose sense of values can
be easily broken or swayed
one way or another.
Such a phrase was not
in the dictionary.
I'll make it a point
to remember it.
You can file it
under "Chunibyo."
People who are able
to get tricked...
will get
targeted again.
Eh?
If we stay here, we can
narrow down our enemies.
The piper will
want to collect.
He will contact
the trolls.
For their "morally
challenged" minds.
Well done.
Now I see why
you forgave them.
We let the little
guys go free...
and then we just wait for
the piper to come calling again.
But how... do we
keep our eyes on them?
By now they already know
what all of us look like.
Well... not
everyone exactly...
There's someone who's face
has yet to be been seen
by the employees, because she
was rolling around on the floor.
Huh?
Oh!
Mm?
Oooh Why did it have
to be so bright?
Oh hey...
(crowd chattering)
(yawning)
What's going on?
Earlier this morning...
One of the bridges was fixed,
allowing a messenger
to arrive on horseback.
Grey:
He told stories of
the flame dragon's head
being hung in the
Imperial capital.
The rumors have quickly spread
that you were the ones
that defeated it.
Not only that, but I have
heard some stories
about Alnus as well.
My behavior has been
grossly exaggerated.
The whole thing
is very embarrassing.
And I was insane at the time.
I can't be held
responsible for my actions.
I don't like that the story
says I played a major role
in the killing
of the dragon,
when I actually did
next to nothing.
The story is getting
rather twisted.
How so?
According to rumor, Lelei is
the one that gave the dragon
the final blow.
Oh...
The people in the Empire are in
desperate need
of a strong human hero that
everyone can rally around.
I can see that.
On the one hand they want to
give Lelei all the credit.
But on the other hand they
also want to take her out.
There something
bothering you? Itami?
When you came to Rondel
from the Imperial Capital,
you had already heard that we
had killed the flame dragon.
But it's only now that
the people in town
are getting around
to finding out about us.
Grey:
Like I said,
a messenger was able to cross
over the bridge just today.
Is there only one bridge
crossing the river
between the Empire
and Rondel?
No. There are at least
three others.
And if we count small ones,
there are a few more.
What about this...
What if someone had them
all destroyed on purpose?
Something must have
happened at the Capital.
Something that they
don't want to spread
throughout the
entire Region.
Have you heard anything
from the SDF?
No we're still too far out
of the network's range
to get a clear
signal through.
But I'll try.
I'll do what I can
to contact 'em.
Ruflus:
I am pleased to report that
we are spreading the word
across the realm...
that you are now leading the
Empire as the Crown Prince.
Good to know Ruflus...
But aren't you neglecting
to tell me about something?
Uh... what do you mean?
His Highness is wondering
about the quality of your men.
He was under the
impression that the people
enforcing the Oprichnina,
were supposed to be elite,
and yet they were
soundly defeated
by a group of
women and old men.
Oh, yes sire!
Uh, uh, for that I'm
afraid I have no excuse!
I have already
dealt with Gimlet,
who was in charge
of the unit.
And I intend to take immediate
action with the new army.
I will be waiting
to hear some good news.
Sir!
The Marquis Casel
is a key player
for those who
support peace.
It doesn't sit well with us
that he is still free.
Thule:
We're counting on you.
What's happening at
Jade Palace is unfortunate.
Princess Pina, what Boses
and Vifita did...
it's still within the wishes
of what the Emperor expressed...
But, well...
The current Senate
wouldn't dare approve it,
because they are under
my brother's influence
at the moment.
I recently heard
something troubling...
that even the royal guards
at the Imperial Capital
were called in
for the Oprichinina.
Then I will be leaving
directly for Jade Palace.
Helm:
Excuse us.
Get out of here!
The Princess is bathing!
I do apologize for the
interruption, my ladies.
But Prince Zorzal has
ordered us to come here.
Princess Pina.
He needs you to come to
his chambers immediately.
Vifita:
It's looks like morale
is still pretty high, Boses.
That's good to hear...
though I wish I could ask
why you would do such a thing.
Do you think we were
in the wrong?
No, Vifita I don't.
But our Order is under
Princess Pina's command.
Our actions can
ultimately influence
how well she will be treated
by the Crown Prince.
Mmm.
All we can do is
protect the palace.
Which is also a fight
for the peace agreement.
We will not only
honor diplomacy...
but we will remain the sword
that protects the will
and dignity
of the Empire.
Right.
Vifita!
The enemy has
returned yet again.
No...
Dear God...
It can't be...
Vifita:
Our comrades are now our enemy?
Boses:
They have 800 soldiers!
No! Almost 1,000!
Zorzal:
Pina.
I'm sure that you are well
aware of what's going on
at Jade Palace,
aren't you?
Pina:
Yes.
I do not want to cause any more
trouble than necessary,
but I also cannot allow
the traitors who fled there
to be free to insult
the Empire... can I?
I need you tell your
Order of the Rose
to stop protecting
the Jade Palace.
Zorzal:
If they do, we won't lay
a finger on the delegates.
We just need them
to temporarily stand aside
until the nation
has been stabilized.
I cannot simply hand you
the Marquis Casel.
It was my mission given
to The Order of the Rose
to protect Jade Palace.
How can you still be
so unreasonable,
Yet so very
predictable?
This country is already
yours for the taking.
Do whatever you see fit.
And I shall do whatever
I like as well.
I'm headed to Jade Palace now.
I bid you farewell!
(gasps)
What in the hell is this?
I am sorry, Pina.
It creates far
too many difficulties,
if you're allowed to leave.
I'm afraid you will need
to remain here for a while.
Zorzal:
But don't worry, you'll be back
out and about in no time.
(seething)
(laughing)
Like I said...
I need you to wait until the
foreign delegates and the media
have returned from Alnus!
We cannot wait
that long.
They are already
under attack at Jade Palace.
Everyone who supports
the peace movement is in danger.
And that will land directly
on Kano's head!
I thought I made it clear
that we will not be accepting
any requests for asylum.
It is our job to clean up the
mess that any of our people
out in the field
have made!
If we stir this thing
up any further...
the media will have a
field day butchering us!
And we will lose the election!
Is that what you want?!
I would rather lose in the
election than regret not doing
what we should have done for our
people in the first place!
It's our job...
to make the
difficult decisions
that benefit the
good of humanity.
Argh...
Alright then fine.
You have permission.
But you... you take full
responsibility for this.
Sir... I will
take it gladly.
(growls)
Kano:
Let's get our people back home!
Lelei:
Next time on Gate:
A Princess in Slave Clothes.