(roar)
(screech)
(screams, fearful reax)
(roar)
[ELDER] This is disastrous.
[ELDER] The moon...
It has gone full cycle since our
troubles began.
Since the flame dragon chose our
forest
to be its feeding ground.
[ELDER] He has brought death
to all our people who chose to
challenge it
and equally to those who went
into hiding.
[ELDER] If this continues,
not a single soul from our tribe
will survive.
[ELDER] It shall be up to you.
[ELDER] The only course of
action that remains
is to implore the ones of
legend,
the ones said to have actually
taken one of the flame dragons
arms in battle.
[ELDER] The green ones.
[ELDER] It is you...
Yao Haa Dushi, the daughter of
our people...
With the greatest skill, wisdom,
and ability to direct the
spirits.
[ELDER] You who have faced
grave misfortune and hardship,
and has now lost your fiancé
and best friend to the beast.
[ELDER] Yet, even among such
devastation and pain you never
lost your way.
[ELDER] We entrust the destiny
of the Dark Elves to your hand.
[ELDER] Endowing upon you the
greatest treasure of the tribe.
[ELDER] I assume you understand
why you ‐ as a woman ‐ were
chosen to be the emissary.
[YAO] Of course, Master.
[ELDER] Then be on your way!
[ELDER] And return to us with
the green ones to help us!
[YAO] Master! I will find these
green ones and bring them back!
And if my body is the price for
the head of the dragon...
[YAO] ...so it shall be!
(run efforts)
[YAO] Oh! They're dressed in
green! That has to be them!
[YAO] Excuse me gentlemen but I
have a dire request to make!
[YAO] I'm certain you are the
people that the elders spoke of!
I need your help...
my people need your help!
[YAO] My name is Yao Haa Dushi!
And I'm with the Dark Elves of
the Schwartz Woods!
[YAO] A few months ago, a flame
dragon appeared in our village
and now my tribe is close to
extinction...
You're the only ones powerful
enough to vanquish such a beast.
[YAO] I'm begging... please!
(uneasy reax)
[SOLDIER] (uneasy) Za... Zaval.
Halu uguluu?
[YAO]
(shopping/street buzz)
[SOLDIER] Uh, how ya doin?...
[SOLDIER] Um gimme just a second
here uh...
[SOLDIER] I can make your
talk... I am a friend.
[SOLDIER] Agulagullu.
[YAO] Un‐be‐lievable...
[YAO] Dammit, nobody here
understands a single word that
I'm saying.
[YAO] Now, wait a minute.
The pervert with the teenager in
the Inn last night
was wearing the same thing!
[YAO] And he seemed to
understand every single word I
spoke to him.
[YAO] Who is he ... I need him.
[TODO] Itami! On your right!
[TODO] Now they're leaving.
[YOJI] Probably just screwing
around.
[YOJI] Fly boys... they must
love it out here.
[TODO] Uh... Why would you think
something like that?
[YOJI] Well! There aren't any
airliners or any traffic up
there.
[YOJI] Yep! Nothing but wide
open skies to explore!
[YOJI] Except for the dragons
and wyverns of course.
[TODO] Yeah. Guess so.
(whining/running)
(hit reax)
[YAO] Hmph. What am I supposed
to do with this?
[YAO] Did he just mistake me for
a prostitute?
Wretched toad. Uh?
Hey sister, hear you wanna talk
to the green people.
[YAO] Can you translate for me.
[MAN] Yeah. Over here. (laugh)
(nasal exhale)
(whining/running)
[YAO] (sigh) Seriously?
[MAN] Well hello there...
I haven't seen you here before.
I'll show you a real good time.
I promise to make it
worth your while.
[YAO] Hm Honestly from this
perspective
I highly doubt that.
[MERC] Huh?!
[MAN] What's going on, sexy!
Got an itch that needs a
scratchin?
(street buzz)
[YAO] Uhhh...This is very
disappointing...
All the men around here are
either depraved or
incredibly useless.
[YAO] I have got to find a way
to get the green ones to listen
to me.
[YAO] Oh! Uh... What's this?
[YAO] What a wonderful market!
There are so many goods here!
[MEIA] You have discriminating
taste there, soldier!
[MEIA] And it's on sale right
nyow!
[SOLDIER] Well, then let me get
one!
[SOLDIER] Me, too!
Thanks you so much, gentlemen!
(gasp)
[YAO] She's actually able to
talk to them!
[MEIA] Myake sure you come by
and see me again okay.
[YAO] I'm sorry! Please talk to
me...!
[MEIA] Huh?! I remember you
from the bar last night.
[YAO] Just now! Were you
speaking
in the language of the green
ones?
[MEIA] Oh, Japanese? Iiiiit's
right here in the red book!
[YAO] Uh... red book?
[MEIA] Yeah "Conversational
Japanese"!
All employees here at the
military exchange get a
copy for free.
It's the same book all
the school children are using
too.
[YAO] Please sell this book to
me!
[MEIA] I'm sorry but I can't do
that...!
Mwe're not allowed to sell them!
[YAO] But please! I have got
to learn their language,
I desperately need to
speak with them!
I've been trying to talk to
these warriors since the moment
I got here!
But none of them can understand
what I say.
[YAO] Please, I'm begging you!
[YAO] I cannot fail my tribe...
! They'll all die...!
[MEIA] Yeah I am super sorry...
but y'know I really don't feel
like losing my job today.
[MP] Hi Meia.
So how're things
holding up for ya?
[MEIA] Hey there! Things're
pretty good!
[MP] Caramel skin. Silver hair.
Tall female with elf ears.
Wearing leather armor...
and a long dark cloak.
[MP] Definitely matches the
description from the report.
[MP] Yeah she does...
Hello there ma'am...
you got a minute?
We really need to talk to you
about a few things, ma'am.
[MEIA] The soldiers are saying
they want to talk to you.
(gasp)
(exhale/inhale)
[YAO] You... wanna talk?
[MP] Um Arvaloo...We'd like to
hear your story...
(shrieks, delighted)
(surprised reax)
[MP] Uh... Will you come with
us...Mangala.
[YAO] Yes! Definitely!
[MP] Right this way, please.
[YAO] Uh‐huh!
[MEIA] That girl needs a lotta
help.
(joyous sigh)
(OM breath catch)
[KATO] Hmph! That was
magnificent, Lelei...
No wonder you're my...
Waaughhhhh!
[LELEI] When I visited the other
side of the Gate...
I found several books about
philosophy.
They've done a lot of research.
(gacking) (gasp)
[KATO] You're growing fast.
I don't have the words.
I'm impressed, Lelei.
Your use of these new
philosophies will create
all sorts of unimaginable
uses for magic.
[KATO] You had to go to a
different world to find some of
these philosophies,
but all the research you've done
with them shall make you a
Master Wizard in no time.
[LELEI] Maybe...but it's not
strong enough.
[LELEI] Oh?
[KATO] Looks like we have a
guest.
[MP] Sorry to just show up
unannounced.
But we were hoping you could do
some more interpreting for us.
[MP] She's here because someone
matching her description
was supposedly strong‐arming men
out of their money.
[MP] The complainant's stories
and hers aren't exactly matching
up,
so we thought you might be able
to make some sense out of this.
[MP] Plus, she keeps saying
something about being attacked,
and that's all we can figure out
with the red book, anyway.
[MP] So, you think you can help?
[LELEI] Yao Haa Dushi. Hello.
[LELEI] They've asked me to talk
to you. Okay?
[YAO] Who are you?
[LELEI] My name's Lelei.
I'm able to communicate with
them.
[MAN] Good god, they're still
swollen!
[MUTY] Excuse me!
[MUTY] I need to talk with you
for a sec.
[MAN] M‐Me?
[MP] Seems like Romeo out there
filed a false police report.
[MP] It looks like we're talking
to the real victim here.
He'll be on his way to
Italica...
he won't be doing that anymore.
[LELEI] So does that mean she
can...
[MP] Uh‐huh...
[LELEI] They're letting you go.
There's no reason to hold you
any longer.
[YAO] Uh! But I can't leave!
My tribe is still being
attacked by a flame dragon!
[LELEI] A flame dragon?
[YAO] It's injured!
He's missing an arm!
I really need to talk to them
okay...
[YAO] I need to talk to the
green ones!
[YAO] Please!
[YAO] I have to!
[LELEI] Do you want me to tell
the Japanese you need their
help?
(gasp)
[YAO] Yes, please!
[LELEI] Is there anything else?
[YAO] Huh?
[YAO] From the looks of things,
it seems you have some influence
over them.
[YAO] I'd appreciate it if you
could say something.
[LELEI] I'll talk to them.
[YAO] That's all I can ask.
[HAZAMA] Miss Yao Haa Dushi.
Sorry... but... we cannot help
you.
[YAO] Lelei what did he say?
[LELEI] He says he can't help...
Yao.
(gasp)
[YAO] No what do you mean?!
[HAZAMA] The problem lies
with the geography of where
you live.
The Schwartz Woods are in the
country of Elbe...
And that's beyond the borders of
the Empire.
[HAZAMA] As a military
organization
we cannot cross that border
right now.
It would be considered an act of
aggression.
[HAZAMA] And that is simply
something we cannot risk
at the moment. I hope you
understand.
[LELEI] You should probably let
it go.
The General does have his
reasons.
[YAO] It's... not like we need
an "army" or anything.
I heard that it was only, maybe
ten of your soldiers
who defeated it and drove it
away!
[YAO] That's all we need!
[HAZAMA] Out of the question!
I will not put my men in such
extraordinary danger!
[HAZAMA] These beasts are
deadly,
it's pure luck they survived the
first time.
(exhale)
[HAZAMA] Look it gives me no
pleasure to refuse to help
you...
but I have no choice in the
matter.
[LELEI] He's very sorry.
[YAO] My village...
[ELDER] To your sincere way of
life
that didn't get lost even
with those misfortunes,
we will entrust the destiny of
the Dark Elves of the Schwartz.
[ELDER] Then go! And come back
with the green ones to help us!
(reax)
[YANAGIDA] Lieutenant Itami..
might be up for it.
[LELEI] He says Lieutenant Itami
might do it.
[YANAGIDA] If it was up to him,
he'd save every last one of
you...
and put you in a display case...
[YOJI] Here we are!
[TODO] Amazing you managed
to put a landing strip here!
[YOJI] Yeah right?... we had to
pick a location
the Empire didn't know very much
about.
[YOJI] Take a look at that.
That's gonna be our ride to meet
with the locals.
[YOJI] A little further down...
We'll be meeting a contact.
[TODO] Oh? Is it someone you
know from the Capital?
[YOJI] Yeah. A friendly named
Hamilton will be there with
her subordinates to help us make
quick an exchange.
[PINA] Hello Itami! Sorry for
the trouble!
[YOJI] Hey... No sweat...
(giggle)
[TODO] And who is this?
[YOJI] Pina Co Lada.
[YOJI] Happens to be the third
princess of the Empire.
[TODO]
[PINA] It's been a while.
The first time since we came
back?
[YOJI] So what is it that brings
you all the way out here?
[PINA] Well, now... Sugawara
said something about
another diplomat dropping in on
us.
[PINA] And I thought I'd make
his acquaintance.
[PINA] Mmm... and uh... (ahem)
[PINA] You know...
I think you might be carrying
something, yes?
[YOJI] Mm? Carrying what?
[PINA] Boses gave you a package
for me!
[YOJI] What do you mean?
[PINA] Whatever you know 'what'!
[YOJI] Oh yeah!
I remember now.
(gasp!)
[PINA] This is it!
This is what I've been waiting
for!
[TODO] What did you get exactly?
[PINA] A work of fine‐art!
[BOSES] We finished translating
the first batch...
They were sent to Princess Pina
in today's shipment.
[PANACHE] And so now... all we
have to do is find out
what books will be in the second
package.
[ROSE] Oh, please!
You must allow me do the next
translation!
[PANACHE] You need to wait your
turn.
[PANACHE] We will assign what
job
everyone is to do when the time
comes.
[NISHINA] Ladies.
The new tea leaves came in to
the café just today.
We think you'll like it.
[ROSE] Oh, this is good! What
are these pastries?
[NISHINA] It comes from Aoyama
in Japan...
and it was created by a famous
confectioner.
[NISHINA] The pastry is known as
a Napoleon.
[BOSES] This is so wonderful.
[BOSES] I hardly believe it!
You have taken something so
tiny...
And you've turned it into
an amazing piece of edible
artwork.
[ROSE] It's deliciouus!
[PANACHE] Sure is.
[NISHINA] 'Scuse me.
(breath catch)
[NISHINA] What are they reading
that for?!
And how the hell am I going to
enter this into my report?
[KAMO] So Nishina's the one
keeping an eye on them...
[KENGUN] He's on butler duty?
[YOGA] I got some chatter that
Yanagida
sent him to a certain restaurant
in Ikebukuro.
[KAMO] What a pain in the ass.
Ugh.
[TSUGE] Hey take a look over
there?
[DELILAH] Here you go!
[LELEI] It's an herbal tea made
from St. John's wort.
[LELEI] It is said to remove
anxiety and depression.
[LELEI] Try it.
[LELEI] Uh.. have some more.
(sip)
[YAO] It feels like...
Like I've been living in a
never‐ending nightmare.
None of this feels real to me
anymore.
[YAO] All I hope.. is that it's
all a dream.
[YAO] Please tell me this isn't
really happening.
Tell me you misinterpreted what
the General said.
[LELEI] I didn't misinterpret
anything.
[LELEI] Everything that I told
you... and what you saw...
Everything was real.
[YAO] No you made a mistake!
Uh...
(inhale, into sob)
(sob/gasp)
[YAO] Please... (gasp) Tell me
it was a mistake...
[YAO] Why...can't they do it?
[LELEI] I'm afraid the
General...
already explained that to you.
[YAO] But my people...
my... people... (exhales)
(tavern/restaurant buzz)
[DELILAH] What in the hell...
[DELILAH] It's like we're at a
funeral or something.
[GASTON] Yeah I heard about the
dark elf...
Supposedly the General told her
that he can't help her with the
flame dragon.
[DELILAH] Think it has something
to do with pissing off Rory?
[GASTON] I doubt it.
I don't think that group had
much say in it.
[DELILAH] So it came down from
the top then.
[DELILAH] And here they are
sitting upstairs about to talk
all about it.
[DELILAH] I really need to start
working on my Japanese
so I can understand what they're
saying.
[GASTON] Delilah... I'm really
not gonna say anything
about this "side" gig of
yours...
but I really don't want to lose
this job, alright?
[GASTON] If anyone starts asking
around...
I'm telling 'em what you're
doin'.
[DELILAH] You do what you gotta
do.
But I'm not screwin' this up.
[KENGUN] So, Yoga. Isn't there
something we can do?
[YOGA] Eh? Unfortunately no.
Ichigaya says...
we can't do anything that could
be considered
a provocative act
to the opposition.
[TSUGE] What do politics have to
do
with a damn dragon, huh?
[YOGA] Well, uh... actually
we were called before the Diet
to talk about fatalities
from the last dragon attack.
[KAMO] If we did do something,
it could go real bad.
They might even call
a vote of no‐confidence
against the Cabinet.
[YOGA] Morita's Cabinet
isn't exactly full of hawks,
either.
[KAMO] What about the big hero?
Itami?
[KAMO] 'Cause you know...
that guy might be up for doing
something.
I mean... he already testified
at the Diet didn't he?
[YOGA] Yeah, he did. He saved us
a lot of grief.
He and the three girls he took
made us look
pretty decent in the eyes of the
politicos.
(reaction)
[KENGUN] That doesn't help
anything.
[KENGUN] A little girl's crying
over there.
[KENGUN] We should be able to
use
just a minimum of force...
and quietly take care of that
dragon for good.
[KENGUN] I mean it shouldn't be
that hard.
[KAMO] What if we send in an
F‐4?
[YOGA] Based on the reports
you'd need to send
a whole squadron after something
like that!
[YOGA] One Phantom won't cut it.
[YOGA] If it were up to me...
I'd use the F‐4 to harass it
and drive it down close to the
deck, about 20 meters.
[YOGA] Then we get the artillery
batteries to lob in
H‐E rounds while it's trying to
regain altitude.
[YOGA] Then, hit it with TOW
missiles from our Cobras!
[YOGA] And you know, a few sabot
rounds
from our tanks wouldn't hurt,
either.
[YOGA] After that, we put some
boots on the ground to confirm
the kill.
[YOGA] Might throw in some high
explosive
to finish it off. Just in case.
(disgruntled reax)
[KENGUN] That's kinda overkill,
don't you think?
[LELEI] I have something to do,
so I need to go.
If you don't have a place to
stay,
make your way to the Co‐op
office.
[YAO] If these officers
have their reasons to
refuse help to me...
What do I do...?
How do I change their minds
and convince them to reconsider
this?
[YAO] Perhaps I can persuade
a lower officer?
Using money...
Or do I try and seduce him.
[RORY] Hey there... not finding
what you need at the bar?
[YAO] Um excuse me.
[TUKA]
Oh! Lelei told me all about
you...
You must be Yao.
[YAO] Yes.
[TUKA] Just gimme a minute
and I'll show you around the
place, okay?
[YAO] Tempt his pockets.. or
tempt his loins?
Perhaps I should try both.
What was his name...?
[LELEI] He says Itami might do
it for you.
[YANAGIDA] Lieutenant Itami...
might be up for it.
[KAMO] He might be up for doing
something.
[YAO] Itami...
[TUKA] Oh...? What did you just
say?
[YAO] Itami...
[YOJI] Take care Your Majesty.
We'll catch up with you later
at the palace if that's all
right.
[PINA] Yes. Yes, Lieutenant.
Thank you for your time.
[YOJI] Nah. It's not like the
only reason
I came here was to deliver your
artwork!
[PINA] Right, sure, I know that!
I think it's safe to say
that your objectives are
the same as mine.
Both of us want the exact same
thing out of this conference...
[BOTH] To get everyone to sit
down for a peace summit!
(half laugh)
Right... and now it's time for
us to head back home.
[HAMILTON] Princess Pina, this
was a lot of trouble.
You could've had it delivered
with everything else.
[PINA] Just look at it.
[HAMILTON] Ehhh...
[PINA] Uh? NO no I don't mean
that!
It's what's on the inside!
[HAMILTON] Is that...
...a record of what he's done?
[PINA] Yes... They did this for
me as a little favor
while they were translating it.
[HAMILTON] The hero who
prevented an invasion...
and saved the people of Japan
from the Empire?!
[HAMILTON] Sir Itami did that?!
[PINA] He did.
Apparently, he was also
in the army
that crushed the Allied
Kingdom's Forces at Alnus Hill.
[PINA] And the same group that
saved
the Coda Village from the flame
dragon...?
He was there too.
[PINA] Oh and... He commanded
the forces
that fought with us at Italica.
[PINA] Who's this man, Itami?
Who is he?
[KURATA] Omigod omigod!
You heard about it, right, sir?
In the Imperial Capital, there
are
a bunch of beast girls and bird
girls too!
[YOJI] Yeah?!
[YOJI] But I thought that you
were
partial to cat girls all this
time.
[SHINO] You guys are the biggest
dorks ever! Cut the chatter!
[BOTH] Nooo!
Nu‐uh..
[YOJI] This is important stuff
we're talking about here!
[KURATA] Damn right it is!
[MARI] Lieutenant.
I forgot... the children
of the refugees from
Coda Village stopped by to see
us before we left.
[YOJI] They did?
[MARI] Yeah... they wanted to
say...
thank you for all the
kindnesses we've shown them.
[MARI] And they wanted us to
know...
they're glad we brought them
here.
[YOJI] They speak Japanese?
[MARI] Yes... kids are some
quick learners...
pretty impressive right?
[KURATA] OW!
Geez, Lieutenant! What
was that for? Oww...
[YOJI] Peace cannot get here
fast enough.
[LELEI] Year 687 on the Imperial
Calendar.
[LELEI] The year that brought
the Empire war and destruction.
And it was only half over.