[LELEI] Japan's Self Defense
Force
was dispatched to the
mysterious Special Region.
[LELEI] Where their Emperor has
unexpectedly collapsed
and Prince Zorzal has taken
power,
[LELEI] Hunting down all those
supporting peace talks with
Japan.
[LELEI] Lelei, while in the
magicians city of Rondel,
barely escapes an assassination
attempt.
[LELEI] She and her friends have
fled
and are now on the move to a new
location.
[LELEI] Itami... um what are you
doing?
[ITAMI] Well Lelei. I'm deciding
which way we'll be going next.
[ITAMI] And today, it's this way
[LELEI] I don't think we'll find
any resources
if we go this
direction.
[ITAMI] That's not exactly our
priority.
Right now, we have to get away
from the assassin, okay.
[ITAMI] Like this... No one will
know which way we're going.
We need to be as unpredictable
as we can.
[LELEI] So we don't even really
know ourselves.
[ITAMI] Bingo that's exactly
right.
[ITAMI] M'kay! Let's get a
move‐on.
[KANO] What the hell is this?
[COUNSELOR GLASSES] Prince
Zorzal
has issued a new law
called the Oprichinya.
Because oppression towards
anyone threatening his power
is becoming stronger
within the Capital.
[KANO] He is turning this into a
reign of terror.
What does... this
Oprichnina Law mean anyway?
[COUNSELOR GLASSES] It's an
ancient political tactic.
It states that "A committee can
vindicate and recover
the sovereignty and
authority of the Emperor."
[KANO] Sounds rather vague, but
gives him power to do
whatever he wants to "protect
the empire."
[COUNSELOR BAGS] That it does.
Pro‐peace representatives and
nobles
are being arrested one
after another.
[COUNSELOR BAGS] Many of which
have asked us
to keep them under
our protection.
Not a chance! There's
no way we can take them in!
If we were to get involved
in this... it antagonizes
the Empire.
[COUNSELOR GLASSES] Yes but...
[KANO] The time will come
when we can make a move.
But until then...
we stay under their radar.
[KANO] Advise our men how to
proceed.
[KAMO] Lieutenant General!
Are you abandoning our
most loyal supporters?!
[KAMO] Call in the 1st Combat
Team.
Send us out on a rescue mission!
[KAMO] We can save everyone from
the Imperial Capital!
[KENGUN] Sir! Order the 4th
Combat Team to go.
[KENGUN] Do it from the air. A
heliborne assault can get this
over with quickly.
[HAZAMA] Just settle down! We're
going to have to wait.
The higher‐ups will ever approve
something like that.
[KENGUN] But sir...
[HAZAMA] Look, no one is telling
us to abandon them.
[HAZAMA] The best you can do is
to keep yourselves ready,
so you can move quickly once the
orders have been issued. Is that
understood?
[BOTH] Yes, sir!
[PINA] I see. The Marquis Casel
is alive and has taken refuge
with the Tuelis.
[HAMILTON] He seems to be safe
for the time being. But it's
difficult to say for how long.
[PINA] There's nothing I can do
at the moment.
[HAMILTON] Sorry Your
Highness...
[PINA] How did I.. become so
powerless?
[SHERRY] Sir Marquis. Would you
like to have a little more soup?
[CASEL] I think I've had enough,
thank you.
[MAID] Sir! Madam!
We're in trouble!
[MAID] It's the Oprichinia. The
"Sweepers" are coming,
they're on the way, they're
almost here at the house!
[SHERRY'S FATHER] Sherry.
You will take care of the
Marquis Casel!
[SHERRY] But what about you and
Mommy?
[SHERRY'S FATHER] Don't worry.
Your mother and I will be coming
right behind you dear.
[SHERRY] OK Father. Please
Casel. Come along!
[SHERRY'S FATHER] If she can
just survive this raid.
The Tuelis will live on.
[SHERRY'S MOTHER] Yes.
[GIMLET] Hello... I'm Gimlet
from the Imperial Protection
Committee.
[GIMLET] You are being placed
under arrest on suspicion of
imperial infringement.
[GIMLET] Submit to us now.
[SHERRY'S FATHER] Submit, huh?
Well.. What say you?
[SHERRY'S MOTHER] Oh hon. Why
don't we ask these nice
gentlemen
if they would like something to
drink?
[SHERRY'S FATHER]
You're so right.
Failing to offer drinks
to our lovely guests...
would be a shame that would
taint our family name forever.
[SWEEPERS] You son of a bitch!
Please. This little stunt
won't buy you any more time.
[SHERRY] Father...
[CASEL] Dear god.
[CASEL] No you can't go back!
[SHERRY] Get your hands off me!
My parents are in there!
[SHERRY] Let me go! Mommy!
Daddy!
[CASEL] Do not let their
sacrifice be in vain!
[GIMLET] This was found after
the fire, it leads to a sewer.
[GIMLET] Casel, and the daughter
of the Tuelis must have fled
through here.
[RUFLUS] Are you saying you
failed to capture who we were
after?
[GIMLET] They set their own
house on fire.
[THULE] Are you neglecting your
duties?
[THULE] Or is it, that all your
talk of undying loyalty is
actually a farce.
[THULE] Deep in your heart,
are you quietly questioning
Prince Zorzal's judgment?
[RUFLUS] No. That is not it at
all.
[THULE] Then prove it. Show that
you put the Empire above all
else.
[THULE] Before I decide to
report your unfortunate blunder
to His Highness.
[RUFLUS] This is the exit of the
underground passage.
Close all the streets within a 2
league radius from here,
and search every single building
inside.
[THE SWEEPER] Of course sir
but...
we don't have enough manpower
for an area that large.
[GIMLET] I pretty sure you'll
find...
that you will only need to
search a few houses.
[RUFLUS] Why do you say that?
[GIMLET] I think if we make
enough noise in town,
[GIMLET] Then The Marquis Casel
will be compelled to make a
move.
[RUFLUS] So we smoke the rat
out.
[GIMLET] And we will purposely
leave a hole
big enough for him to crawl
through.
[RUFLUS] He will emerge exactly
where we want him. Yes.
I like it! Let's implement this
plan of yours right away.
[GIMLET] Right! But there is one
thing... Jade Palace is well
within the 2 league radius.
And it is protected under
Princess Pina's
Order of the Rose,
[GIMLET] If they decided to go
there for help, things could get
complicated.
[RUFLUS] No need to worry.
[RUFLUS] Even though she may be
the princess.
She must follow Oprichnina law,
or she will be considered an
insurgent.
[RUFLUS] Proceed with
confidence.
[SWEEPERS] Will do.
[THULE] Boulo.
[BOULO] Yes, my dear?
[THULE] It's time to make things
interesting.
[BOULO] Anything for you.
[CASEL] I guess I should have
accepted seconds whenever you
offered me earlier.
[SHERRY] I'm hungry too. What
can we do about getting some
food?
[SHERRY] We must eat something.
[SHERRY] I'll go and find some
provisions.
[RED TURBAN] Can I help you?
[SHERRY] I'm wondering if you
can spare something to eat.
[RED TURBAN] Oh yeah and what
can you give me?
[SHERRY] How about two of these?
[RED TURBAN] Sorry, that's not
gonna be enough.
[SHERRY] How about four then?
[RED TURBAN] Hmph... How about
you give me all you've got and
maybe I'll think about it.
[SHERRY] I wouldn't mind that,
but it could cause great discord
within your household.
[RED TURBAN] How so?
[SHERRY] This one was made
for a small child,
so if you were to give it
as a gift for your wife,
you would need 10 more to
complete the necklace.
[RED TURBAN] Then I'll just use
two of them
to make her some earrings
and then sell all the rest.
Maybe so... But women can be
awfully greedy
when it comes to jewelry
from their husbands.
[SHERRY] She would only want
more so that she could
have a beautiful necklace to go
with her new earrings.
[SHERRY] If that happens,
who do you think she would be
pestering?
Just imagine the
insufferable whining.
[RED TURBAN] I uh...
[SHERRY] Perhaps you should
settle
for five of these gorgeous
pearls.
[RED TURBAN] Little lady, how
old are you?
[SHERRY] I'm 12, sir.
[RED TURBAN] You're gonna be a
force when you get older.
[RED TURBAN] Here. This is all I
have.
[SHERRY] Is this from... Japan?
[RED TURBAN] Yes. It is.
I've been working as a footman
over at Jade Palace.
[RED TURBAN] I get some of their
leftovers sometimes.
[SHERRY] Do you know... if the
delegates are okay?
[RED TURBAN] Uh‐huh.
They are protected under
Princess Pina's Order,
as long as they stay inside,
they should be safe.
[SHERRY] Well that's good to
know.
[RED TURBAN] Listen... The
guards there switch
twice a day, every morning and
evening.
[RED TURBAN] When they do...
Their security ends up
shorthanded for a brief period.
What?
[RED TURBAN] Now be safe.
[SHERRY] Thank you very much.
And thank you for giving me the
pearls Sugawara.
It's all to see you again.
Please understand... my husband.
[SHERRY] Um...Marquis.
[CASEL] Yes what is it, Sherry?
[SHERRY] We should go into
exile.
[CASEL] What are you talking
about?
[CASEL] We're completely
surrounded by all sides.
It's not possible to get out of
the Imperial Capital.
[SHERRY] There's no need for us
to try to get out.
There is a foreign entity right
here within the Capital.
[CASEL] You mean the Jade
Palace.
[SHERRY] Yes! It is protected
by a diplomatic accord.
In other words.
No one from the Empire can touch
us there.
[CASEL] But Sherry, would the
Japanese delegates
even accept us into their
territory?
[SHERRY] Right now, we must
throw ourselves at Sugawara's
mercy.
[CASEL] That would
cost him. A lot.
He and his people could get into
a great deal of trouble trying
to help us.
[SHERRY] Marquis Casel.
I am going to get revenge for
the death of my parents.
[SHERRY] But in order to do
that,
I will need great power behind
me.
[CASEL] Sherry please. Listen.
[CASEL] Do you have any idea
what that means.
The consequences.
[SHERRY] Yes...of course.
[CASEL] Looks
like they're going after
the wrong people,
perhaps they'd be better off
catching you first.
[CASEL] Alright, fine. I'll do
it.
I'll share this crime with you,
little one.
[SHERRY] Looks like it has
begun.
If we stay here... we could
cause trouble for those
in this house.
Come.
<laughing into his gross
slurping noise>
[BOULO] Oh so very naive.
[BOULO] Who would lend you a
room
purely out of the sheer kindness
of their heart?
[BOULO] And you, you could have
lived much longer.
If you hadn't chosen to do
business with the sweepers.
[BOULO] Now... it's time for the
dance to begin.
We'll see how far you get.
[BOSES] It looks like
something's happening in town.
[VIFITA] I've already sent
scouts to take a look around.
They should be back shortly.
[YELLOW ROSE A]
I bring word ma'am!
It has been confirmed that The
Sweepers are indeed the ones
causing the commotion
within the Imperial Capital.
[YELLOW ROSE A] It would
appear that they are
hunting down fugitives,
and they are considering
Jade Palace as part of their
sovereign territory.
[BOSES] OK!
Make an emergency call to the
Yellow Rose Unit!
[BOSES] Tell everyone to prepare
for battle!
Stay on high alert!
[YELLOW ROSE A] Right!
[BOSES] Looks like it's going to
be a long night.
[CASEL] Hmm... I guess we have
to
wait until the guards switch
in order to get near the palace.
[SHERRY] We do not have that
kind of time.
We must be brave and vigilant,
and go straight in.
[CASEL] Evening my name is
Marquis Casel,
a representative of the senate.
We need to speak with
the Japanese delegates.
[YELLOW ROSE B] You're The
Marquis?
It's rather late, isn't it?
[CASEL] Yes we have an
emergency.
I would like to speak with them
right away please!
[SHERRY] See? It's working
perfectly.
[CASEL] You are indeed a brave
little lady
[YELLOW ROSE B] Please wait
right here.
[GREY BEARD A] Pardon me Miss.
But you cannot go beyond this
point without permission.
[SHERRY] And why not?
[GREY BEARD A] Under the
agreement the grass area
is effectively the property of
Jade Palace.
[GREY BEARD A] Which means...
The Empire ends right here.
[SHERRY] It's the country of
Japan
[BOSES] I'm glad that you're
unharmed.
[CASEL] Yes we are, fortunately.
But my family and her parents
were not so lucky.
[BOSES] You have my sympathies.
[CASEL] Thank you. Now about our
meeting with Japan?
[BOSES] They said they must
decline...
...and send their deepest
regards.
[CASEL] Really. Just like that?
[SHERRY] Excuse me, but may I
please
at least see my Sugawara?
[VIFITA] Sherry what you are
asking...
is an unreasonable request.
[SHERRY] You don't understand,
he is my future husband!
[SHERRY] And if he knows that
I'm out here...
I'm certain that he will accept
us into the palace!
[VIFITA] You are quite
tenacious.
[BOSES] Knight Captain Vifita.
Will you please find out?
[VIFITA] Right... Yes of course.
[SUGAWARA] Vifita, I thought we
just told you
that we cannot do that.
[VIFITA] Yes I know but...
[SUGAWARA] The Marquis is a
major player
in the push for peace.
Of course, we want to
save him.
[SUGAWARA] But we... we've been
notified by our country that...
[SUGAWARA] If we save one,
then we will have to save two.
[SUGAWARA] If we save two we
save four...
As you can see it would become
endless.
[SUGAWARA] And if that happens,
then the Prince would feel
antagonized,
and this already tenuous
situation will only get worse.
[VIFITA] I understand the
predicament.
But sir... he has a companion
who is very adamant about seeing
you.
[SUGAWARA] A companion?
[SHERRY] Sugawara!
[SHERRY] Sugawara! It's me,
Sherry!
[SHERRY] I'm right here!
Sugawara, let me inside!
[SUGAWARA] Sherry's here!?
[VIFITA] How interesting.
So what she was telling us
wasn't all fantasy was it?
[SUGAWARA] What'd she say
exactly?
[VIFITA] It happens quite often
with girls around her age.
A girl meets someone
kind who treats her nicely,
and quickly becomes obsessed
with thoughts of marriage.
[SUGAWARA] Did she happen to say
that I was her future husband?
[VIFITA] She did.
[VIFITA] I'm sure you wouldn't
attempt
to try and lay a finger on her.
[VIFITA] But well... this sort
of thing
will be extremely hard to deal
with.
[VIFITA] She's royalty. She
believes
she's chosen to be treasured
forever.
[SHERRY] Sugawara! Please
listen!
I want see you, and hear your
voice again.
[VIFITA] She came all the way
here,
trusting in your kindness.
[VIFITA] Risking her life.
Believing in your devotion.
[SHIRAYURI] Are you sure about
this? This what you want?
[SUGAWARA] Look I am a diplomat.
I cannot let my personal
feelings
get in the way of our national
interests.
Well that is the perfect answer
for a diplomat.
But only for a diplomat.
[CASEL] So... I guess they will
not be able to accept us.
[VIFITA] I wish we could help
you. I'm sorry.
[CASEL] No. You are only doing
the job you were given.
[CASEL] Pay it no mind.
[BOSES] The Sweepers? Are here?
[CASEL] It is time.
[BOSES] Allow them to come in.
[GIMLET] Well... If it isn't
Marquis Casel...
so this is where you have
hiding.
[CASEL] Huh. Like you didn't
know already.
[GIMLET] You've done an
excellent job, Boses.
[GIMLET] I'm sure Princess Pina
will be pleased.
[BOSES] Oh really? Why's that?
[GIMLET] Right now, she's found
herself
in a very delicate position you
know.
[GIMLET] How she chooses to
treat this situation
with the Marquis could put her
at great risk.
[GIMLET] Heh.. I almost feel
sorry for the little girl.
[CASEL] She doesn't want your
pity.
You killed her parents.
[GIMLET] Spare me the drama
we lost some of our finest
people as well.
[CASEL] It would seem
that this is our end.
[GIMLET] Let's go child.
[SHERRY] Sugawara! Please! Let
me in!
[SHERRY] Ow! Let me see you!
Sugawara!
[SHERRY] Sugawara!
[GIMLET] That is just about
enough!
[GREY BEARD A] Let the girl go
now.
[GIMLET] If you try to defy us,
you will be treated as a
dissident!
[GIMLET] You're coming with me!
[SHERRY] No! Get away from me!
[SHERRY] Sugawara help!
Sugawara! Sugawara!
[GIMLET] Let's go!
[SHERRY] Sugawara!
[SUGAWARA] Get your filthy hands
off her!
[SHERRY] Sugawara
[GIMLET] Look here it's Mr.
Ambassador.
What brings you out join us?
[SUGAWARA] You will release that
girl to me at once.
[GIMLET] Excuse me? She is a
citizen of the Empire.
[GIMLET] What sort of basis
could a Japanese bureaucrat
possibly have to ask for her
release?
[SUGAWARA] She's mine, and when
she comes of age,
it has been decided... that she
will be my bride!
[SHERRY] Sugawara...
[GIMLET] Heh. That is absolutely
ridiculous.
[GIMLET] Back off!
[GREY BEARD A] You can go, miss.
The ambassador has given his
permission.
[GREY BEARD A] Go! You'll be
safe in Japan!
[GIMLET] Noooo!
[SHERRY] Sugawara!
[SUGAWARA] It's okay...
[SHERRY] Oh... Sugawara. I'm so
sorry.
[SHERRY] I... had to sell the
pearls
you gave me for food.
Please... forgive me
for what I've done.
[SUGAWARA] Don't you worry.
They can always be replaced.
But you are a different story.
[SHERRY] Thank you.
[SECRETARY] We're in trouble,
Vice‐Minister.
Sugawara has acted out on his
own.
[SHIRAYURI] Yes I am aware.
Call Kano. We must let him know
what's happened right away.
[GIMLET] Goddammit! Do you know
what you've done?
[VIFITA] Form a line now!
[VIFITA] Our sworn duty is to
guard Jade Palace.
[VIFITA] No matter the cost.
We must let no one enter these
grounds
without being given permission.
[VIFITA] We will defend it with
our lives!
[ALL] Right!
[GIMLET] You've sealed your
fate!
You are harboring a known
criminal.
[GIMLET] And no 'agreement'
will prevent us from taking them
back! Prepare to die!
[VIFITA] Swords!
[GIMLET] Charge!
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
The Dead line.