[LELEI] A Gate connecting to
another world has appeared in
Japan.
[LELEI] After fighting back the
army that came through it,
the Self‐Defense Force was sent
to the other side.
[LELEI] Yoji Itami, one of the
troops involved in the Battle of
Ginza,
and a helpless otaku, joins the
team.
[LELEI] When they arrived,
thousands of troops were
awaiting them.
[CASEL] My Lord, the Gate
situation is an utter
catastrophe!
[CASEL] I am sorry to report,
but over 60% of the Imperial
Army is gone!
[CASEL] How do you propose we
respond to this situation?
[SENATORS] (harrumphs,
uncertain)
[CASEL] How do you intend to
lead the nation
in the face of such a crisis,
Your Majesty?!
[MOLTO] Steady, Marquis Casel...
no doubt things seem untenable
at the moment.
[MOLTO] And yes, it would appear
the military advantage we had
has been completely obliterated.
[MOLTO] But I believe what
actually troubles you
is whether or not our
subordinate nations
could combine their remaining
strength...
and bring rebellion to the steps
of the capital.
[MOLTO] That's the true threat
is it not?
[CASEL] Huh?
[MOLTO] Every time we find
ourselves in a precarious
situation,
the Emperor, the Senate, and the
people of the Empire unite,
and thus manage to grow even
stronger from it, My dear
Marquis.
[MOLTO] You cannot win every
single battle in a war.
Therefore, I will not hold
anyone accountable for what
happened in this fight.
[MOLTO] And I'm sure that
neither the Marquis nor the
Senate
have time to engage in these
debates...
[MOLTO] ...rather than trying to
keep the Capital
from being surrounded by unknown
enemy forces.
[SENATORS] (approving) [CASEL]
He's conveniently forgotten he
started this.
[GODASEN] What is your plan,
Your Majesty?
[GODASEN] Two days was all it
took for the army
from the other side to cause
such incredible losses.
[GODASEN] On top of that,
they've seized control
of the Gate,
and are now establishing
a foothold on our land!
[GODASEN] We tried to take the
gate after they arrived.
it was a complete disaster.
[GODASEN] But we couldn't even
get close to them!
[GODASEN] I have never seen such
sorcery!
It's as if they read our minds
and cast fire right at us!
[PODAWAN] We must fight!
[PODAWAN] Our vassals must give
us what we demand!
Rebuild our army using their
soldiers!
[SENATOR] That will only make
things worse, senator!
[SENATOR] And only repeat
Godasen's mistake!
[SENATOR] That's right!
We must stand firm!
[GODASEN] Uh?
[MOLTO] Sitting here and waiting
for matters to worsen is not the
answer.
Therefore... we will fight.
[MOLTO] Send messengers as far
and wide as their horses will
take them.
[MOLTO] Tell them we need their
assistance in repelling the
invading forces...
and we need them now!
[MOLTO] Make it so!
Have Godu Rino Gwaban
and all of the allied Kingdoms
rally to us!
It's time to re‐take Alnus Hill!
[SENATORS] Pledge loyalty to the
Emperor Molto!
[CASEL] Your Imperial Majesty...
[CASEL] I fear Alnus will be
another battlefield
littered with the corpses of
men.
[MOLTO] Heh!
[SOLDIER] My Lord!
[SOLDIER] We've spotted what
seems to be
the enemy's scouts at a high
vantage point two hills ahead.
[DURAN] Let them be for now.
[DURAN] I must hurry to the
gathering of kings!
[DURAN] Why isn't the commander
of the Imperial Army coming?
[MESSENGER] We're in the midst
of an offensive
on Alnus Hill, Milord.
It's impossible for the
commander to leave his post.
[KINGS] (concerned)
[DURAN] That doesn't sound
right.
[DURAN] My observers only saw
a modest number of enemy troops.
[REIGOUX] Oh, come now...
Sir Duran the Imperial Army is
holding down the enemy forces.
[DURAN] Are you sure of that?
[MESSENGER] Sire... we only need
one thing from you...
we need you to strike the enemy
tomorrow morning.
[KING OF ARGUNA]
Very well then...!
My army shall be the spearhead
of the attack!
[KING OF MOWDWAN] Hold it!
Let my army take
the lead this time!
[REIGOUX] Now wait a moment!
Let us be at the forefront of
this victory!
[KINGS] (arguing)
[MESSENGER] Tomorrow morning.
Alnus Hill. We'll wait for you.
[KING OF ARGUNA] It shall be a
glorious day.
[KING OF MOWDWAN] Perhaps
but my army's all you will need.
[REIGOUX] A shame. This should
be our time to shine.
[DURAN] The enemy army
has only ten‐thousand men.
We outnumber them thirty to one.
[DURAN] I don't think being
the first into battle
will be very distinguished.
[REIGOUX] So where else would
the glory be?
In being the first to sound the
retreat?
[DURAN] In all my years we've
never seen such a foe.
[REIGOUX] (laughs) Even
Lord Duran, the Lion of Elbe,
can't keep the ravages of time
from catching up with him!
(laughs)
[KING OF ARGUNA] For‐ward!
[SOLDIERS] (war cries)
[DURAN] It is about time we join
them on the battlefield.
[SOLDIER] My Lord!
[DURAN] (surprised)
[SOLDIER] Majesty... the other
kingdoms...
They've departed to
assault Alnus Hill...
And Lord Reigoux is set to join
them.
[DURAN] And where is the
Imperial Army?
[SOLDIER] My Lord... no Imperial
troops...
none have been sighted on the
hill.
[DURAN] What was that?!
[REIGOUX] Why don't I see the
Imperial Army?!
[SOLDIER] They're not here, Sir.
[REIGOUX] That can't be.
[artillery whistle]
[KING OF ARGUNA] Uh...?
[REIGOUX] What is this? Ahhhh!
[DURAN] Impossible! Is... the
hill erupting around us?!
[DURAN] Where's Arguna's king?
Where's the King of Mowdwan?
[DURAN] Where the hell is
Reigoux?!
[LORD] We brought over one
hundred thousand of our own
troops,
but half of them are already
gone...
How can this be happening?
[LORD] What is the Imperial Army
doing and why aren't they here?!
[LORD] No, even the Imperial
Army is no match for this
opponent.
Falling back might be the only
option left!
[DURAN] Retreat is not an option
that's open to us gentlemen.
[LORD] What?
[DURAN] For the realm...
we must strike back!
[LORD] Lord Duran! We have
neither the men nor the
materials!
[DURAN] A night raid might
give us the advantage.
[DURAN] The new moon is tonight.
[DURAN] If we take advantage of
the dark,
and come in from the side of the
hill blocking out the stars,
slowly and quietly...
We should be able to make our
approach.
[CAPTAIN] Don't shuffle about...
be quiet... pick your feet up.
[SOLDIERS] (surprised)
[DURAN] (breath catch) Where is
that coming from?!
[DURAN] (breath catch) No! HAH!
[DURAN] All troops! For‐ward!
[DURAN] Keep moving! Don't let
them hit you!
[DURAN] Go! Go! Go! HAH!!!
[DURAN] Move! Keep going!
[DURAN] Hyah! Follow me!
[SOLDIER] My Lord! Let me help
you!
[SOLDIER] We need more shields!
[SOLDIERS] (reacting to the
starburst rounds)
[DURAN] (growl) Get out! Do you
wanna get hit?!
[DURAN] Goddammit!
[DURAN] How could you...
What did we do... to deserve
this.
[DURAN] Heh! (maniacal laughter)
[KURATA] Did you hear the
report?
Intelligence says they lost 60
thousand.
[YOJI] Plus 60 thousand in
Ginza... 2 army corps worth
of men.
[KURATA] Don't tell me you're
worried about them.
[YOJI] A hundred twenty thousand
people?
[YOJI] Why would they send so
many?
And what kinda country are we
fighting?!
[MARCUS] Your Imperial
Majesty...
[MARCUS] The damage of the
Allied Kingdoms' Forces
is expected to reach over
100,000 dead and injured.
[MARCUS] The defeated armies
have no officers
remaining and are making their
way back home on their own.
[MOLTO] Hmm... Just the way I
conceived of it.
[MOLTO] The potential threat of
our quibbling neighbors
coming to raze the Empire has
successfully been eliminated.
[MOLTO] Torch all the towns and
villages between us and Alnus.
Poison all of the wells and herd
their livestock this way. And
burn the crops.
[MOLTO] That should keep their
armies from eating our food and
water...
then we can plan a
counterattack of our own.
[MARCUS] So it's a scorched
earth policy...
[MARCUS] That causes me worry
about the tax revenue decrease
and inside secession.
[MOLTO] What do you mean?
[MARCUS] Well... there's a
problem, Your Majesty.
A movement is forming behind
Marquis Casel to replace you at
the head of the Senate, Sire.
[MOLTO] (laughs) Can you imagine
how much service
I'll get from the Senate
when I expose this travesty?
[MOLTO] Go ahead and let
the Private Council know
I'll be needing their
services right away.
[PINA] Your Majesty!
[MOLTO] My darling daughter...
What is it?
[PINA] It's Alnus, of course.
[MARCUS] Hmm?
[PINA] It is my understanding
we were soundly defeated at
the Gate...
And that the armies of all our
subordinate nations
were routed on Alnus Hill
just a few days later...
[PINA] What is Your Majesty
doing in response to this
situation?!
[MARCUS] Obviously we aim to
re‐gathering our forces
and create a plan to
counterattack...! (breath catch)
[PINA] Create a plan?!
The enemy is on our doorstep,
we must move now!
[MOLTO] Pina my dear, you're
right. You're absolutely
correct.
However the issue at hand is
that
we do not know much about the
enemy forces occupying the hill.
[MOLTO] Why don't we try this?
Take all of your knights from
the Order of The Rose
and scout
the situation for us.
[PINA] But... Your Majesty?
You want me to take my people?
[MOLTO] Well why not?
You've been longing to prove
that your knights
are doing more than just
marching and color guard.
So... here's your chance.
[PINA] Consider the mission
done... Your Majesty.
[DIRRELL] What in the hell does
Japan think they're doing?
[DIRRELL] They move an entire
division across the Gate,
and then box themselves in
like a bunch of baby turtles for
crying out loud!
[KREARON] Their first mission
statement
regarding this has been to
evaluate politics...
They're only interested in
controlling certain areas.
[DIRRELL] (laughs) Oh my god.
Well they're missing out aren't
they?
[DIRRELL] They've stumbled upon
a goldmine of untouched
resources!
[DIRRELL] Are they gonna just
let it sit there,
that does nobody any good.
[DIRRELL] What about this...?
We've already got guys in
Okinawa, just send them in.
[KREARON] That's not a good
idea, sir.
The other leaders are hoping to
allow Japan to uh...
drop the ball on this.
[KREARON] The thought is to
let Japan simply fail on
their own this time.
[DIRRELL] Interesting.
We don't want to get pulled down
with them.
"Plausible deniability" is a
good friend to have.
[HIGAKI] ...With this is mind...
We need intelligence to decide
future policy.
Investigating their political
base... religious faith...
and what kind of industries are
the most prevalent
in this world are
at the top of our upcoming
fact‐finding missions Lieutent
Itami.
[YOJI] Well that seems
like a great idea...
Best of luck to whatever dummy
gets that job.
[HIGAKI] Congratulations,
"Dummy" ‐It's all yours.
[YOJI] Huh...? Please not me.
[HIGAKI] What?
[YOJI] I can't do something
like that myself.
[HIGAKI] We wouldn't entrust it
to just you.
[HIGAKI] We've already
organized the
six deep recon and surveillance
units we need.
[HIGAKI] And you, Lieutenant,
will command of one of them.
[HIGAKI] Your mission will be
to make contact
with the inhabitants inside the
disputed area...
And if you don't get your ass
shot off,
start a friendly relationship
with them.
[YOJI] Ahhh... sure...
I guess if that's an order.
[HIGAKI] It is.
[HIGAKI] And as much as it pains
me to say this...
[HIGAKI] You are officially in
command of the
3rd Deep Recon and Surveillance
unit!
[YOJI] Yeah...
[KUWABARA] Fall in!
Sir! 3rd Recon... is ready, sir!
[YOJI] Hey, Old School! And
we're...
[YOJI] Uh... thanks for falling
in or whatever.
I'm Lieutenant Itami. So, now...
[YOJI] Oh, god... miss one
train on the way to sexy
Shimbashi and now I'm here...
In a platoon fulla... dudes.
[YOJI] All right... let's get
crackin' folks.
[SHINO] You kidding? This is the
diipshit they sent us?
[KUWABARA] Mount up!
[YOJI] Man it's bright out here!
Just like I hoped it would be.
[KURATA] Oh come on Lieutenant
we've got some beautiful scenery
back home.
[KURATA] I mean, for me,
I was figuring
I'd see freakin' dragons flying
all over the place.
Maybe a fairy or two.
[KURATA] Look at all
the towns we've seen.
Just boring 'ol humans
all over the place?
[KURATA] I'm pretty
disappointed.
[YOJI] Oh that's right, you got
that whole cat‐girl thing.
[KURATA] A cat‐girl, or a hot
little witch, yeah!
I could definitely
go for one of those.
[KURATA] So... what about you...
you got a preference?
[YOJI] Well, uh... magical girls
are cool.
[KURATA] Seriously?!
[YOJI] Emu is smokin'.
[KURATA] Whuh? Your standards
are low.
[YOJI] Hmm? Don't be talkin'
about my waifu like that!
[KURATA] Easy, man! She's
alright.
I can sing her whole opening
theme song!
[YOJI] Really?!
[KURATA] Hell, yeah, sir!
[YOJI, KURATA] When I, feel low!
There's one, place to go!
Mei Com! Mei Com! Mei Company!
It's the, one place Put's a
smile on, my face Mei Com! Mei
Com! Mei Company!
[SHINO] Oh dear God.
[TOMITA] By the way, What are we
doing with gear that's, like,
ancient history?
[TOMITA] I mean our vehicles
seem to be up to date, don't
they?
[YOJI] It's probably a cost
management thing.
They figure, worst‐case, we
might have to
ditch 'em and run like hell.
[TOMITA] So we were given
weapons we can afford to lose.
[YOJI] Besides,
all the new stuff
has all that gadgetry
that needs GPS.
No satellites out here.
So no need for it.
[KUWABARA] We're just bringing
along what we need.
Kurata... There oughta be
a small river comin' up here in
a little bit, all right.
[KUWABARA] Follow along the
banks for a while
and we oughta get a look
at that forest they were
tellin' us about.
[KURATA] Got it, Top.
[YOJI] Well, there's the river.
Looks like you know what
you're talking about, Old Timer.
[KUWABARA] Considering I taught
nearly everyone here how to
land‐navigate, I hope so...
I'd say we better put stakes
down in front of the trees
tonight.
[YOJI] Sounds good.
[KUWABARA] Huh? Hmm? You've
already called back to the rear?
[KURATA] So we're going in,
right, no need to stop.
[YOJI] Well think about it.
If we just plow right in there
then we're gonna have to setup
somewhere deep in the forest.
F'we do that... we could be a
risk...
to any settlements and villages
that're in there.
[YOJI] Y'see we're the
"Self‐Defense Force that cares."
[YOJI] The general and the major
told us to
build a friendly relationship
with everyone we can.
[YOJI] Check this out...
Zavalu, Halu uguluu...?
[KURATA] Yeah I don't know
Lieutenant.
They might think you have a
speech impediment.
[YOJI] Oh shut up!
[KURATA] Hehehe! Huh?
[YOJI] Hang on... I got more
books
and I'm not afraid to use them.
[KUWABARA] What's that?
[YOJI] A Fire?
[KURATA] It's on fire all right.
[YOJI] And it's really big...
what the hell coulda caused it?
[KUWABARA] You gotta see this
one for yourself Lieutenant.
[YOJI] Holy crap!
[DRAGON] (roar)
[KUWABARA] It's like King
Ghidorah with only one neck.
[YOJI] You really are
a classic aren'tcha.
[SHINO] Lieutenant.
[YOJI] Huh?
[SHINO] What would you like us
to do, sir?
[YOJI] Sergeant Kuribayashi...
do you think you could hold my
hand for me?
Your CO is gettin' kinda scary
over here.
[SHINO] Eat it.
[YOJI] Yeah...OK.
[DRAGON] (roar)
[KUWABARA] It's buggin out.
[YOJI] It makes you think...
Why in the hell would a dragon
just burn down
an entire forest with nothing
else around?
[SHINO] Well you know if you're
really
that curious about it Lieutenant
Itami...
I'm sure our new dragon friend
would be happy
to sit down for a quick
interview.
[YOJI] Are you always like this?
[SHINO] Huh?
[YOJI] They told us back
at the Village.
There's a small settlement
inside that forest.
[SHINO] Oh! Uh...
[KURATA] Holy shit!
[YOJI] Hey, Top...
bivouac's gonna have to wait.
[KUWABARA] Got it! We're back on
the move, people!
[TOMITA] There's still smoke
coming from the ground.
[KURATA] It'd take a miracle for
anyone to survive this.
[KURATA] (breath catch) Um...
sir...
[YOJI] I know. Keep moving.
[KUWABARA] Rest in peace...
[SHINO] Lieutenant...
[SHINO] Our first
glance here... there are 32
foundations coming up out of the
ground...
The majority of which appear to
be roughly the size of family
dwellings, sir.
[SHINO] We only found twenty
seven bodies...
the rubble and the wreckage
could be hiding the rest.
[YOJI] Assuming you have three
people in a house...
That gives us one hundred dead
and no survivors.
[SHINO] This is just horrible.
[YOJI] I suppose then that
Dragons in this world
will attack groups of people.
That sounds like something to
tell the General.
[SHINO] Maybe but I'm not sure
the general
is going to like what else we
have to tell him.
Fifty‐cal barely put a dent in
the wyverns we hit in Ginza,
and they weren't breathing fire
all over the place.
[YOJI] A flying tank with
a flame thrower
is not a good thing.
[YOJI] We should see what kind
of recon
we can do to learn more about
them.
[klunk]
[YOJI] What?
[SHINO] Sounded like it hit
something.
what's down there?
[YOJI] Not a "what," ...a "who!"
[YOJI] We need a hand over
here!!!
[LELEI] Next time on "GATE:" A
Flame Dragon.