[LELEI] A Gate connecting to
another world appeared in Japan.
After fighting back the army
that came through it,
the Self‐Defense Force was sent
to the other side.
[LELEI] Itami was put in charge
of the 3rd Deep Reconnaissance
and Surveillance Unit.
The group witnesses a flame
dragon attacking a settlement.
[LELEI] There, they discover a
girl, the sole survivor of the
attack.
[YOJI] (grunts)
[YOJI] Got her!
[KUWABARA] Easy, you guys!
Steady, steady...
[YOJI] We found a person! Hurry
up!
[ALL] Roger.
[YOJI] Eh?
I guess not exactly a person.
[MARI] Her BPs high
enough to move her!
But we gotta get her out of
these wet clothes!
[SHINO] Sorry, but this has
gotta go.
[KURATA] (happy) An elf!
And not just any elf. A blonde
elf too!
[KURATA] Now that's the kinda
thing
I was expecting to find out
here!
[KURATA] (giggles) We hit the
jackpot this time baby!
[YOJI] OK... you're into elves?
[MARI] Excuse me, sir.
[YOJI] So, how's she doing?
[MARI] Her temp's back down to
normal...
She's no longer in critical
condition.
[YOJI] That's good to hear.
[MARI] All right... so how would
you like to proceed?
[YOJI] Let's see...
A dry pair of boots'd be pretty
kick ass right about now!
[MARI] What?
Never mind. no way we
can leave her here...
she ended up losing her entire
village.
We'll classify her as a refugee
and take her with us.
[MARI] Now why did I get the
feeling you were gonna
come up with something like that
Lieutenant?
[YOJI] Eheh... pretty humane
of me don'tcha think?
[MARI] Yeah...
wouldn't go that far.
[YOJI] Huh?
[MARI] I mean, I was thinking
you might've done it
because she was an elf...
Knowing what you do in your
spare time...
it'd be pretty rude of me to
point out now wouldn't it sir?
[YOJI] That's it.
We should head back to Camp
Alnus.
It'll be best to take the road
through Coda Village.
[KURATA] You know what,
Lieutenant...
[KURATA] I'm thinking we'll
probably run into
a dragon again before a
cat‐girl, huh?
[YOJI] Better watch what you
say,.
Or else it might come true,
you know.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Dear God!
The entire village has been
destroyed?
[YOJI] Malu haluu. Uh, Big bird.
[YOJI] Lahoo. Forest. On fire.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Flame dragon!
[VILLAGER] (slow gasp) No way...
[VILLAGER ] Unbelievable...
[YOJI] Mlapalaa, shooting
fire...
Pabla maloo burned to death.
[YOJI] And one girl. We saved...
Yarimila?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Oh?
And she's the only survivor?
That is just awful.
[YOJI] Kalahoo. Can you help?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Mm‐mmm...
We can't care for an elf.
And besides, we need to find a
way
to get out of here ourselves.
[YOJI] Onaha... You leave?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Yes...
Once a Flame dragon gets a taste
of human or elven flesh
it will be back for more.
[MELIZA] (grunt) Come on! We
gotta go!
[HUSBAND and SON] Got it!
[MELIZA] Right!
[KATO] (grunts and groans)
[KATO] Ahhhhhhhhhh!
[LELEI] Um Master we can't load
anything else on the cart.
Lelei...! I need to take my
books with me! Hear me?
[KATO] Lelei... we've got to
come up with something.
[LELEI] Certainly...
The books that have spells
and incantations
should be given
the highest value.
[KATO] That's right! You really
are a genius, aren't you?
[KATO] why is there dragon here
anyway? Most peculiar.
50 years sooner than expected!
What am I supposed to do without
any sort of warning?!
[KATO] Most inconsiderate!
[LELEI] Master we really
need to ride.
[KATO] Pardon me, how could you
be so lewd?
I'm way too old to be riding a
girl as young as yourself.
(laughs) Now, your sister...
she's another story.
[KATO] Boom! Bang! Boom! Yeah!
ACK!!!
[KATO] Hey! magic is the world's
most sacred thing!
It shouldn't be used for trivial
matters AGGGGHH!!!!
[KATO] Well now...
guess we're gonna have to work
on that sense of humor.
[LELEI] If I don't have one it's
because of your teaching.
[KATO] We're not moving...
I don't suppose you overloaded
the cart?
[LELEI] You wanted all of your
books, Master...
you should've expected something
like this.
[KATO] It's a good thing we're
wizards...
let's just magic it out.
[LELEI] "Magic is the world's
most sacred thing ..."
"It should never be used for
trivial matters!"
[LELEI] Your words,
if I remember.
[KATO] Yeah, well...
[LELEI] But in this case I
believe we're out of options ...
[KATO] I'm... sorry.
[LELEI] It's fine. I've gotten
used to it... Master.
Huh? What's going on? Why are we
just sitting here?
[VILLAGER ] Master Kato...!
Lelei...!
The road is being blocked by a
carriage's broken down!
Someone overloaded and snapped
the axle!
[KUWABARA] Let's get this column
moving, people.
[BOTH] Uh... Huh?
[KUWABARA] Hey, Lieutenant!
Look in that book of yours
and tell the Chief we need some
help!
[YOJI] Got it, Old School!
[KATO] never heard a
language like that before.
[LELEI] I've never seen clothes
like that before.
[KUWABARA] Kurokawa. Check
around for injuries!
[MARI] Yes, sergeant major!
[KATO] A woman... who's also a
soldier?
I shall go take a look, Master.
[KATO] Huh? Wait a minute!
Lelei!
(horse in distress)
[LELEI] Life‐threatening
injuries...
[MARI] It looks like she might
have a concussion...
looks like her ribs might be
broken, too.
[FURUTA] Please! It's not safe
here!
[LELEI] You're a healer? Uh!
(panicked horse)
[MARI] Hey! Are you okay?
[LELEI] These people...
[LELEI] ...these people just
saved my life.
[KURATA] Lieutenant...
[KURATA] How long do you think
we're supposed take care of all
these folks anyway?
[YOJI] What's that?
[KURATA] Don't they have some
kind of
noble lords or whatever to look
after them?
[YOJI] Well, I asked about it.
[KURATA] Uh?
[YOJI] I bounced it off the
chief when we were talking.
The lord over this area took his
army with him
and they ended up part of the
body count at Alnus Hill.
[YOJI] We wiped all of them out,
Kurata. All of them.
[BANDIT] I heard everyone in
Coda is bailing out tonight.
[BANDIT BOSS] Sounds like easy
pickins for like us.
[BANDIT] It's not like we got a
lot of guys, man!
[BANDIT BOSS] Well check this
out.
a buncha defeated soldiers
camping out...
they'll jump at the chance to
join us.
[BANDIT BOSS] We offer those
guys a little something,
we can make an army of our own
and take down an entire city!
[BANDIT] And force a lord out of
the area!
[BOSS] Eheh! From leading a
bunch of troublemakers,
to having my own city...
I like it.
[RORY] (giggle) [RORY] Good
evening, gentlemen!
[RORY] I'm so glad you could all
get together like this.
[RORY] And... I am very thankful
for you offering your lives to
charity...
[RORY] The Supreme God... loves
the way
you naughty boys have behaved
yourselves.
[RORY] You should be honored
he's asked you to join him... in
the afterlife!
[RORY] (giggles)
[RORY] You may call me Rory
Mercury.
[RORY] I am an apostle...
of the Dark God Emroy.
[BANDIT] Holy shit it's really
her! It's Rory the Reaper!
[BANDIT] The gown!
The Temple of Emroy's
Oracle Robe!
[BANDIT] Get outta here!
[RORY] No you don't...
[MARI] One‐twenty over eighty.
She'll be up and around pretty
soon, sir.
[YOJI] That's good... but... not
sure she wants to.
[KURATA] So, have any of 'em
said where they're going?
[YOJI] Hmm?
Nope. Not really.
[KURATA] Huh? You're kidding
right?
[YOJI] (sigh) Leading an
evacuation effort,
is a lot more tiring than I
thought it'd be.
[KATO] Ahhh... I really need a
drink of water...
[LELEI] We won't be able to stop
for a while.
[KUWABARA] Comer on. Move it!
Get your backs into it!
[KUWABARA] Move it!
[YOJI] So here's the thing...
If they have to pick a spot
it's gonna be in a place
where the dragon can't get them.
It's the same for any refugee
no matter where you live.
Except for the whole dragon
part.
[TOMITA] It's not gonna work,
sir. The axle snapped.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] If we
stay we're only sentencing
ourselves to die.
Only carry what is necessary.
Leave the rest.
[VILLAGER] Uh... Fine. I get it.
[SON] (crying)
[MARI] So why did you make them
burn it, Lieutenant?
[YOJI] Because they were just
sitting in front of their stuff
and wouldn't leave it behind.
I suppose you have a better
idea?
[MARI] We could have put in a
call for more vehicles.
[YOJI] Take a peek at your map
and
you'll see we're behind enemy
lines already.
[YOJI] I mean they might let a
few vehicles get by,
but if we bring too many in, it
could get real ugly real fast.
[YOJI] They shoot at us, we call
in a strike,
they die, more take their place,
then it's an air strike, and
we've pretty much
failed the mission we were given
to establish peaceful relations
We'd end up escalating the
conflict
trying to help them out.
So we won't be able to get more
vehicles... understand?
[MARI] Guess the major told you
that in advance.
[YOJI] We have to help them
out as best we can...
cause nobody's gonna help us,
got it?
[MARI] Oh? Huh?
[KURATA] What's that?
[KURATA] I see something...
up the road.
[YOJI] Crows?
[YOJI] No... way...
[YOJI] Goth lolita girl!
[KURATA] What'd you say?
[RORY] (giggle)
from where do you fine ladies
and gentlemen hail...
and what's that that strange
contraption?
[YOJI] She looks like trouble.
[KURATA] Yeah...
[MARI] The maids around here
sure are young.
[BOY] She's an oracle!
[BOY] Oracle!
[BOY] Hey, Oracle!
[YOJI] Oracle?
[RORY] And where are you kids
from?
[BOY] Coda Village, Ma'am.
[OLD LADY] We're running away
from our village.
It was attacked.
A flame dragon appeared...
so we evacuated.
It almost looks like they're
praying to her doesn't it?
[YOJI] Do you think maybe that
fancy outfit of hers
has a special meaning or
something?
[RORY] Oh...?
[RORY] So who are these
strangers you're with?
[BOY] They came and helped us
out!
They're the good guys!
[RORY] And you're sure
they're not taking you
against your will?
[BOY] Mm‐mm!
So how is this moving
without any horses?
[BOY] I... don't know. But one
thing for certain
it's a lot more comfortable than
a carriage!
[RORY] Really? More comfortable
than a carriage?
[RORY] Well I would just love
for you to show me...
how "comfortable" the ride is.
[YOJI] Uh... Za...
Zavalu. Halu uguluu? Hehe...
[RORY] (giggle)
(discomfort)
[YOJI] Hey! Hang on a second...!
[YOJI] That is not where you
sit!
[YOJI] Please just move!
[KURATA] How is this happening
to you right now?!
[YOJI] I just need you to get
off, okay!
[RORY] Oh! really?
[YOJI] Don't touch my gun!
That's dangerous!
[RORY] Ehhh?
[YOJI] Keep your hands off!
[KURATA]You're the luckiest guy
ever!
[YOJI] I'm not enjoying this!
[RORY] Oop‐sie!
[KURATA] I'm dyin' over here!
[YOJI] Hey! That thing is
loaded!
I mean it! Get off of
me!
[VILLAGER] Oh, look it's Roche
Hill.
[VILLAGER] I can't believe we
walked so far!
[KURATA] The terrain's starting
to look a little different.
[YOJI] Yeah... we really put
some distance
between us and the village.
I really hope we get this whole
evacuation over with.
[KURATA] A‐men to that, sir.
[YOJI] It sure gets a lot hotter
out here
than it does in Japan, you know?
[YOJI] Wha‐?!
Contact!
[KATO] An honest to goodness
flame dragon!
[KATO] I've never actually seen
one! Wahhahhhh!
[KUWABARA] I know it's the
tradition of the self defense
force to fight for the people,
but we might wanna run!
[YOJI] I need a diversion,
Katsumoto! 50 CAL!
[YOJI] Don't let up! Keep on
shooting!
It's gotta have a weakness
somewhere!!
[YOJI] Watch out, guys!
[KURATA] That thing could fry us
all in a second!
[YOJI] 50 cal isn't making a
dent!
[YOJI] Shit! Come on!
[TUKA] ONO!
[YOJI] Huh?! Well look who's up!
[TUKA] O‐NO!
[YOJI] What?
[YOJI] The eyes! Aim for the
eyes!
[DRAGON] (growl)
(roars in pain)
[YOJI] He didn't like that. RPG!
[KATSUMOTO] Oops... better check
my rear.
[ALL] Just shoot it!
[YOJI] You pulled it!
[YOJI] It's not gonna hit!
(roar of rage and pain)
[KURATA] That... was kind of
awesome.
[YOJI] Well, glad you had fun.
[VILLAGERS] (lamenting, crying,
moaning)
[GIRL] (sobbing)
[KUWABARA] Most of the survivors
have relatives they can stay
with nearby.
[KUWABARA] And a few others
have arrangements for shelter
and lodging.
[YOJI] What about the rest?
Are they sure they're gonna be
able to find something...?
If they're on their own out
there?
[KUWABARA] I hope so,
but we've got a bigger issue to
deal with.
[YOJI] A lot of kids and older
folks...
lost their family... in the last
attack.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] It might seem
heartless,
but we have our hands full
trying to find another place to
live.
We simply can't stretch
ourselves any thinner
adding someone else.
[YOJI] You're leaving... Without
them?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] We thank you.
You'll always have... our utmost
gratitude.
[SHINO] Take care of yourselves!
[VILLAGERS] Thank you!
You were a big help! Be well!
[MARI] All right. So what are we
gonna do with the rest of them?
[YOJI] Well...
[YOJI] Refugees, right?
[YOJI] Don't you worry... it'll
be fine!
[MARI] (half‐laugh)
[YOJI] Eh? Huh?
What're you smiling at?
[MARI] Nothing.
Just had a feeling you'd
say something like that.
See? You do think I'm humane!
[YOJI] Let's mount up, people!
[YOJI] We're heading Alnus Hill!
[LELEI] Next time on "GATE:"
To the Land of the Unknown.