Lelei:
Japan's Self Defense Force
was dispatched
to the mysterious
Special Region.
In Japan, the Prime Minister is
forced to send a rescue mission
to save Japanese delegates
and the pro‐peace nobles,
from the hands
of Zorzal's army.
The Order of the Rose
is outnumbered,
facing 1000s of their former
allies at the Jade Palace walls.
Meanwhile, Itami and his friends
are targeted by an assassin
known as the piper, who is deft
at manipulating people's minds
to do his deadly bidding.
Ruflus:
Our enemies before us
are nothing more
than a group of women
dressing up in knight costumes.
They are merely amateurs
who are playing make believe!
Put them in their place!
(battle cry)
Do not back down,
no matter who the enemy is!
Today we battle to protect
the honor of the Empire!
Turn them away!
Right!
Why do we have to fight
against our own comrades?
Be quiet. If the enforcers
of the Oprichnina hear you,
they will most
certainly kill you.
It wasn't meant
to be like this...
Attaaaack!
Now!
(battle cry)
Hmm...
Nola:
Hello there.
Are you from
the Hotel Shokai?
Her?
You are the only person
that they haven't seen yet.
That's why I would
like you to spy on them.
Listen...
I will be acting as if I have
been manipulated by the piper,
and attack Lelei on the day
of her big presentation.
I would like you to share
this information with her,
so that she will know to wear
armor underneath her robes.
Then what is
she supposed to do?
Lelei will need to lie still
and play dead for a while,
So that the piper
will finally show himself.
He'll need to confirm if his
target is actually dead. ,/
That's brilliant!
And then we can finally
catch this creepy creep!
Mmm‐mmm!
You do remember...
what his face looks like,
don't you, boys?
Yeah of course, we do!
We could never
forget it!
Heh. Very good.
Nola:
You can repair your
reputation if I can trust you
to do this right.
Of course, we will!
I can't believe they were
fooled again so easily.
Goodbye. Be sure
to follow the plan, fellas.
Bye bye!
Are you ready
in there?
Rory:
Yes.
Hey, I see you
have a new robe.
The other one still
has a stain on it
from her fight with Arpeggio
and it won't come off. ,/
It's nice.
Itami:
And this one looks
good on you too.
Mm.
Um excuse me.
It's been four days
since we last saw Shandy.
But it's still probably a bit
too early for us to lose hope.
Hmm.
I'll ask around.
There might be someone
in the market area
who knows where
she could be.
Oh God that
was faaar!
(panting)
Rory:
Shandy?
Wa‐Water...
Sorry, It took so long.
I was following a woman named
Nola, hoping to find the piper.
Is everything alright?
You could have, at least,
tried to contact us you know.
I never really
got the chance to.
So I take it, the porters
came by and offered you
some new
information, right?
Yes. They said that Lelei needs
to wear armor under her clothes.
As I am sure you
guys can guess,
Nola is just another one
of the piper's many instruments.
I thought as much.
We don't know when
he will make his move,
so wearing some sort of armor
is probably a good idea.
And if that
woman shows up,
we will need to get a hold
of her before she's able
to get anywhere
close to Lelei.
I guess you're right...
By any chance...
Did you happen to see what
the piper really looks like?
Yes. He looked just like
the porters said,
He's a scary
bounty‐hunter type.
I followed him all the way
to the town of Pyran, but...
when I turned away for just
a second I lost sight of him.
That trip can take even
the most seasoned traveler
two days each way.
Can't really blame
her for that.
Thank you for
the effort, Shandy.
But all we really needed you
to do was to keep a close eye
on the three porters.
And see who made
contact with them.
What?! So you mean I just wasted
four days for no reason at all?!
Uhhhh.. Well, no,
no, not exactly
You were able to find and
confirm what the piper
truly looks like...
that's big!
Bet you're hungry.
Why don't you get yourself
something to eat.
Sure! Yeah!
(squeals in excitement)
Do you think, we should tell
the porters about this?
No. Let them think what
they think for a bit longer.
I believe they'll be much
more useful to us that way.
What we need
to do right now‐
is figure out when and where
the piper is planning to strike
at the conference. ,/
There are so
many people.
It's very possible that someone
else among us is being currently
manipulated
by the piper.
We need to make an effort to
stay aware of our surroundings.
Yeah.
Arpeggio:
Yoohoooo!
Over here you guys!
Um so why did it take you
so long to get here?
I'm not late, sister.
There's still plenty of time
for me to check in.
As always, you and your
incessant stubbornness.
Oh.
So... I see you
got a new outfit.
Oh my oh dear, Arpeggio.
(giggles)
What do you want,
Master Mimoza?
Wellll.. ,/
I was curious to see if she
was able to get a new outfit
ready in time.
I know you were up all night
hemming your old robes
so she'd have
something to wear.
Gah!
Seriously, Mimoza!
I thought I told you
never to mention
anything about
that, come on!
Oh my dear girl...
I'm so very sorry!
Conference Staff:
If you are already registered,
then please go ahead
and get in line.
So Arpeggio...
How many people will be
receiving their degrees
at the end of
this ceremony?
Not sure. Every year
is a little different,
sometimes everyone passes
and sometimes no one does.
Why d'you
wanna know?
I suspect the piper might try to
manipulate someone into thinking
they need to get rid
of the competition
in order to secure
their own degree.
Oh that's not going
to happen here.
All of these people aspire
to become honored specialists
in each of their
chosen fields.
They are our most valued
and respected magicians.
What if the research you
had been working hard on
for so many years was
stolen from you...?
and not only that, but that
the perpetrator was going to
present it to the community as
if it were their very own?
Uh?
Itami:
Furthermore, what if
that thief was standing
right in front of you as if
nothing was happening?
Well, I would... I would
beat that fraud to a pulp...
It's time to put an end to this!
Itami:
Hold it right there.
You don't understand!
That little swindler,
she stole all of my research!
Old Sage:
There's no way
a little girl that age
is ready to be a master
of the magic arts!
She's taken everything
I've worked so hard for! ,/
I think there's some information
you may not be aware of.
Will you please take
this gentleman away
and explain that he has been
fooled along with everyone else?
It would be my pleasure.
Old Sage:
Wh‐what's going on?
Where are you taking me?
Lelei:
You saved me.
Thank you very much.
Hmm. Sure.
We'll be on top of the security,
so don't worry about it.
Good luck!
You can do this.
Presenting Sage:
And uh, well, uh, therefore,
the uh, data shown on this
particular chart explains
the cause of the retrograde
movements of the planets
Old Master:
Oh shut up!
(scream)
Which backwoods
camp‐town are you from?!
I heard that crap
from my great grandpappy!
Mokri's ridiculous
theory of the sun
is more convincing
than that, you imbecile!
Get out of here you
good‐for‐nothing amateur!
Go work in
the stables!
You embarrassed
us and yourself!
(high‐pitched screaming)
Oh, now I see.
The white robes do give the
presenters ample opportunity
to be humiliated.
Mm.
Hm?
I'm going to
be just fine.
Good. I'd much rather protect
you in clean robes anyway.
Presenting Sage 2:
That being said, if we can solve
the cause of the distortion,
We will be able to finally
uncover the secret origin
of our world.
Thank you for your time.
Ah. Very good.
Well. Guess that means
it's your turn, Lelei.
(crowd whispering)
Damn. Couldn't they have waited
'til after the presentation
The porters sending her signals,
so that means it must be Nola.
I'm too late!
(gasps)
Nola:
(screams)
Uh... how did they all know
to use their magic?
Uh, their was a rumor
going around town
that Lelei was being
targeted by an assassin.
So everyone was
ready‐and‐waiting
to take immediate action.
(chuckles)
Aw... Man I wish the SDF
could do stuff like that.
Alright then...
well, now that it's safe.
Best of luck
with the rest.
Ah!
Itami:
Lelei!
Helm:
Princess Pina.
What are you doing in here?
Leave me alone.
I have some bad news
I'm afraid.
The Crown Prince would like you
to change into your...
new clothes.
(gasps)
Kengun:
(frustration‐building groans)
What is the hold up?!
Jade Palace is going
to be taken before
we can do anything to help!
Do you think that
I don't know that?
We just need you
to hold back.
Hazama:
I'm sure we will
get the order soon.
They have only 300 people,
Most of which are women,
children, and the elderly.
Yet, you sit here coddling
your sad beleaguered army,
while our enemy
celebrates in comfort?
Yes. I apologize,
mistress.
But the morale... of the
Imperial soldiers has soured.
And I'm afraid that‐
I'm not here to listen to your
sad and feeble excuses.
Prince Zorzal is
eagerly waiting
to hear the news
of your victory.
Understood.
If you need to gather
more soldiers, then do so.
But if you continue
to allow these traitors
to act freely any longer,
You will be branded a coward
of impotence and dishonor.
Do you understand?
Our soldiers are beginning to
show serious signs of fatigue.
How much food do we have left in
stock?
We never imagined we
would have to barricade
ourselves for so long.
There can't be much
in there to sustain us.
Our rations are thin.
We can use the well in Jade
Palace for drinking water, ,/
but I'm afraid we
will soon be out of food.
Boses. What are
we to do?
If we can somehow
convince Japan,
Then we will take everyone
we have and force our way
through the enemy line.
If we do survive,
where would we go?
Italica.
(gasps)
Good idea!
The Yellow Rose Unit and the
foot soldiers are already there.
If we join them, we would
have a chance of turning
this thing around.
Yes. But I'm
worried about Pina.
She's at the mercy
of her brother.
Huh?
He couldn't harm her‐
she's a protected member
of the royal family!
If we're going to leave
the Imperial Capital,
Then we will need to make sure
we can rescue Princess Pina
and get her
to safety.
But sneaking into the
Imperial Palace is no easy task.
I mean do we even know exactly
where she's being held?
We don't. We have to wait
for Hamilton to make contact.
Yellow Rose Soldier:
They're attacking!
The enemy's attacking!
(scattered commands shouted)
They're not giving us
any chance to recuperate.
It's tough for
the enemy as well.
Until we make contact
with the Princess,
we must do what
we can to stay alive!
Right... I understand.
(struggling)
Stop it! Stop it!
Are you listening to me?!
(struggling continues)
Don't leave me here!
You have repeatedly
ignored the advice
your brother has
graciously given you.
Instead choosing to interfere
with his royal activities.
Thule:
Therefore, you are to be
judged... by Oprichnina law.
You're nothing but
a Voglia bunny!
I don't really care what
you think of me, Princess.
Did you know that's
the exact same room
where I was
once held captive?
I think it's a very
nice room Princess.
And it will suit
you perfectly!
Oh! And. Yes.
I have a message for you from
the great Prince Zorzal.
He has something very
important to tell you.
(chuckles)
(door creaks, slams)
Zorzal:
You lose, Pina
Lelei. Lelei.
Hey are you alright?
Huh?
(sighs)
(gasps)
What the?!
N..NO! She's wearing
armor underneath?!
Hmph.
What did they say?
Her thesis went well,
but there's just too
much drama, right now.
So they informed us
that they're going to be
holding on to her degree
until everything else
settles back down.
Huh... That's too bad.
Did you see anyone at
the conference that
may have been the piper?
Mm‐mm. No I did not.
And besides‐
whoever Shandy
says she saw,
may not be the
actual piper anyway.
Most likely, he would have kept
himself well hidden from view.
I don't believe you!
If she was going to wear
armor under her clothes,
you should have
let me know about it!
But‐ you're the
one who told us
that she would need
to wear armor, remember?
That was all you.
Oh?!
I would like you share this
information with her,
so that she will
know to wear armor
underneath her robes.
Uh?
Uh...
Oh, I'm such an idiot!
It's a good thing that
the person fooled was
a fool themselves, huh?
I mean why would we not do
anything when we knew she was
going to be attacked?
Because knowing what's
coming is your best defense.
It was rather foolish of you
to not go for her neck.
Uh, Tuka...!
(whimpers)
Shandy...
why would you try to do
something like this?
It is what must be done to save
the life of Princess Pina!
Huh?
Hm?
How would attacking Lelei
possibly do anything
to save the Princess's life?
Because Prince Zorzal wants
Lelei out of the picture‐
he wants to
see her dead.
Mmm.
So I guess I thought that if I
were to offer him Lelei's head,
then it would demonstrate
Princess Pina's
allegiance to him.
I see what he did.
He used your loyalty toward
Pina to manipulate you.
Look I didn't need to be
tricked or manipulated, okay?
I know more than anyone
the incredible danger
that Princess Pina is in.
Prince Zorzal's dictatorship
has gone out of control!
Shandy:
I just...
(fighting tears)
I fear for
her very life.
I cannot believe that they would
actually attack Jade Palace.
If we don't do
something quickly,
Princess Pina will be
judged by the Oprichnina.
Knight‐Lieutenant Grey,
if you feel as indebted
to Princess Pina as I do,
you would kill Lelei yourself!
Why the hell would I do that?
That's an absurd way
to try to fix things.
And besides... even by
a pure tactical viewpoint,
Rescuing the Princess is
a much more plausible
approach to all this.
There's no way we'll be able
to just sneak into the Palace
without confronting one
of the royal guards.
Now listen to me.
If we want to
stop the piper...
Then we must do so by finally
putting an end to the man
who's pulling
the strings.
You seriously want us
to kill the Crown Prince?
If you want to
save Princess Pina,
this would be the most effective
way of getting it done.
By the way, Itami.
Were you ever able to get
in touch with your military?
I should be able
to get a signal
if I go to the
outskirts of Rondel.
But... it hasn't
been working very well.
We need to stay
one step ahead.
So I took advantage
of the newly repaired bridge.
And called for a messenger.
Messenger:
Excuse me, sir!
Aaah! What do you
have for me?
Messenger:
Something terrible has
happened to the Princess!
Grey:
What?
(gasps)
Yessir, I Understand.
Huh?
Let's do it!
Squad Leader:
About face.
Soldier:
Yes, sir!
Squad Leader:
Prepare for inspection.
Chute, secure!
Equipment secure!
Weapons check!
Ammo check!
Automatic wire...
Soldier:
Automatic wire, check!
Squad Leader:
Alright. That's it,
gentlemen! All green!
Get on board!
Radio:
To all units in
the Special Region...
this is from Headquarters.
At 06:03 tomorrow morning,
the Dispatch Joint Task Force
will be parachuting down
to the southwest Empire,
and initiating
an airborne assault.
Our goal is to rescue the
Japanese delegates residing at
Jade Palace and asylum seekers,
harboring the seeds
of peace with the Empire.
We have to hurry...
to the Capital!
Lelei:
Next time on Gate:
Paratroopers