[LELEI] Dispatched to the
Special Region,
the 3rd Deep Reconnaissance Unit
led by Yoji Itami
saved the town of Italica from
bandits.
But on the way back to Alnus
Hill,
they encountered Princess Pina's
knights,
the Order of the Rose.
[LELEI] Itami was taken captive
and his subordinates forced to
retreat.
[LELEI] Itami's fate now lies in
Pina's hands.
[SHINO] Hmm...
[SHINO] I dunno guys...
he could totally be dead
already.
[KURATA] Hey, come on Sarge
you're not supposed to say
things like that.
[SHINO] Seriously, Kurata.
They were really roughing him up
when we drove off.
[TOMITA] Be patient, guys...
wait for the sunset.
[KURATA] Aw, maaan...
[PINA] What the hell have you
done?
(hard breathing)
[PINA] (hard breathing) You
idiots...!
(confused exhale)
[PANACHE] Your Majesty...!
What have we done to make you
this angry?
[PINA] Don't you get it?
[HAMILTON] Master Itami!
(breath catch)
Say something. Are you okay?
Master Itami?
[HAMILTON] Talk to me, please!
[YOJI] (flops)
[HAMILTON] Aaahh!
[PINA] We have broken the treaty
on the very first day.
[GREY] They can use this as a
reason to restart the war.
I wouldn't put it past your
father to do that...
But we don't know if these
"Japanese" would do the same
thing.
[PINA] If they did, it would all
be over very quickly.
[GREY] At the very least...
Boses and Panache didn't go
overboard and kill the guy.
Maybe come forward and apologize
for what they did.
[PINA] You want me to just
grovel before them?
[GREY] I don't think you want a
fight...
all things considered.
(breath catch)
[SHINO] What?... What'd you say?
[KURATA] The lieutenant doesn't
have anything to worry about?
[SHINO] That is not what you
said!
[TOMITA] Kurata said that
Lt. Itami happens to be a
Ranger.
[SHINO] Huuhhhhhhh?!
You're joking... there's
no freakin' way
in the world a jackass like that
has a Ranger Badge!
[LELEI] Hmmm? What's wrong with
Itami
having one of these Badges? Zit
a bad thing?
[SHINO] Look, it's not like we
give 'em out to just anyone!
You gotta be really tough to go
through the training!
And then you gotta be able to
prove you can accomplish
something afterwards!
It's s'posta be a goddamn honor!
(gasp)
[SHINO] Rangers are total
badasses!
[SHINO] And the Lieutenant is
not a badass.
(giggle)
[RORY] So that means he must be
stronger than he looks.
[TOMITA] All right... It's time
for us to get moving people...
[MILITIAMAN] Ah, this sucks...
I don't care if they're
Imperial Soldiers or not.
They're so full of themselves it
makes me sick!
[MILITIAMAN] Easy.
C'mon you don't want these guys
hearing you, do you?
[MILITIAMAN] Yeah, whatever,
man. Hunh?
[MILITIAMAN] It's the Apostle
and her friends.
[TUKA] Oh? (giggle)
Oh ye spirit of slumber...
Take these souls with you...
Allow them to experience your
peace and harmony.
(zonked)
(snoozes, flops)
[TOMITA] We're clear.
(rousing)
[MOMU] Are you awake, Master
Itami?
[YOJI] Huh? Where am I?
[MOMU] You are in the mansion of
House Folmar.
[YOJI] The home of the Count...
[YOJI] Which would mean that I'm
back;
they brought me all the way back
to Italica.
[YOJI] Ehhh... Those are cat
ears. Uh...
[PERSIA] Hmm?
Is sommmmething wrong?
[YOJI] Uh... Oh, no... I was
just kinda wondering
what the heck is going on.
[KAINE] There's no need to
worry.
We've been ordered by the
Princess to give you the best
service possible.
All you have to do is ask one of
us and we will take care of you.
Also... regarding the Knights
who mistreated you...
they've been severely
reprimanded.
[KAINE] Your actions have given
this town a new life...
and for this we are eternally
grateful, My Lord.
[YOJI] Ohhh... y'know don't
mention it.
[KAINE] To assault the savior of
Italica
in the way they did is
unforgivable.
As such, if you wish to reduce
this town to rubble
I will assist you in doing so.
They certainly deserve it.
[KAINE] But please... I ask that
you spare our mistress the
Countess.
[KAINE] Please don't make her
part of your retribution.
[YOJI] It's okay. I'd never do
something like that.
I'm not that kind of guy.
[KAINE] Thank you for your
generosity.
It's definitely appreciated.
[YOJI] Ah... (gulp)
[YOJI] Sure... It was nothing.
[KAINE] These four are your
personal nurses...
feel free to ask them for
anything while you're
recovering.
[MAIDS] Count on us Master...
we are more than happy to serve
you.
[KAINE] As I said.... Just ask
them for anything you need.
[YOJI] Yeah... will do.
(gasp)
[KAINE] What's happening?
[MAMINA] Someone's at the
back door...
It sounds like they're trying to
force their way in.
[KAINE] More than likely... it's
Master Itami's people.
[KAINE] Show them the way in and
bring them here.
If it's someone else, then you
know what to do.
[PERSIA] Yes, M'yam.
[YOJI] Ah... Ohh. 'Scuse me...
can they really uh...?
[KAINE] Can they handle
themselves?
Mamina's a voglia warrior
bunny...
and Persia is a very adept
cat‐person.
[KAINE] Aurea is a medusa...
[KAINE] ...and Momu is human.
The late head of the family was
very open‐minded,
and actively made a point of
employing species of all
varieties.
You could go as far as to say
it was an "interest" of his.
[YOJI] Now that... sounds like
the type of guy
I could get along with.
[AUREA] Itami you have a very
similar smell to the late
Master.
[SNAKE] (menacing sound)
[MOMU] Hey! You cannot just say
things
like that to our guest okay!
[AUREA] Okay...
[KAINE] Medusas use their hair
to drain the life from their
adversaries.
[KAINE] Aurea knows better but
you'll still want to watch
yourself.
[YOJI] Eh... OK.
[MOMU] And... ahhh....
[YOJI] Ahhh... Uh?
[KURATA] Lieutenant!
Are you all right?
[YOJI] Hey guys!
[SQUAD]
[PINA] Boses... Panache...
You have attacked an
officer of the Japanese Self
Defense Force...
You treated Master Itami in a
less than hospitable way
and endangered his life.
This is a violation of our
treaty.
[PINA] These people possess
the power to fight off
a Flame Dragon.
So imagine what would happen
if they decided to declare war,
wouldn't be good I can assure
you.
[PINA] The Empire would fall!
[BOSES] Yes.
[PINA] It is on you...
to make them forget this ever
happened.
You're going to need to offer
that man your body.
(gasp)
[PINA] I know it's degrading,
but you will do whatever it
takes.
[BOSES] I am a daughter of
nobility, Your Majesty.
And I understand what it takes
to protect the realm.
I will do what must be done...
If that is what it comes to.
Uh... ma'am! Corporal Takeo
Kurata reporting milady!
[KURATA] 21 years old, single!
My hobbies are anime and
doujinshi!
And I'm totally single.
[PERSIA] Uh?
[KURATA] 100 percent single!
(giggle)
[MAMINA] The way you fought
those bandits was awesome!
I really mean it! I totally saw
everything!
[SHINO] Nah... it wasn't that
great!
[LELEI] These snakes of yours,
how do they shed?
[AUREA] That's kind of a secret.
[SNAKE] (hiss)
[MOMU] How do they make the
fabric like that?
[TUKA] I don't know what kind of
loom they used...
but it's extremely stretchy and
really comfortable.
[KAINE] To have you here today
Your Holiness,
is truly a great honor.
[KAINE] The mercy of the Mighty
Emroy
is a wonderful thing to behold!
[RORY] (annoyed) Something like
that.
[KURATA] Ah‐haaaa!
[PERSIA] Mwell, meow. How's the
tea?
[KURATA] Oh! It's the best tea
ever!
[PERSIA] Rowl!
[YOJI] Well now... looks like
we're comfortable.
[TOMITA] I don't think we're
gonna need
to be calling for a dust‐off
anytime soon.
[KATSUMOTO] Guess the Sergeant
Major
can take the night off and we'll
call him later.
[YOJI] Yeah... let's just call
tonight a cultural interchange.
(steeling herself)
[PINA] It's on you... to make
them think this didn't happen.
You're gonna need
to offer that man your body.
(several uneasy breaths)
[KURATA] Say cheese!
(laughter)
[BOSES] Uh... Wha‐
[KURATA] Oh. This is a good one.
[SHINO] And you can take a
picture with this.
[RORY] Takes pictures of what?
[chatter]
[YOJI] Oh, wow... and they let
you in?
That's kinda hilarious Tomita.
(big laugh)
[TOMITA] It wasn't that funny.
[BOSES] I don't believe this.
[BOSES] I am the second daughter
of the honorable Count Palesti!
[BOSES] The nerve of this man.
This pig has no idea what it
took for me to lower myself!
[YOJI] Huh?
[BOSES] (swing)
[YOJI] Ahhhhhhhhhhhh!!!
[PINA] All right...
What's... wrong with his face?
[BOSES] Um that was my doing
Your Majesty.
(wail/gasp)
[PINA] Oh dear God...!
How do I explain this?!
[TOMITA] Well, Ma'am...
if it's all the same to you
we'd like to take our leave
now...
and you just do whatever you
need to.
[LELEI] He says that whatever
you want ... s'fine.
[PINA] This is not good!
[PINA] Uh.. the sun's almost up!
Why don't we sit down for
breakfast!
We can talk it out. Get to know
each other better!
[KURATA] Uh we appreciate the
offer, Milady...
the thing is... Our government
has called the Lieutenant
back home...
to report to some of our
lawmakers.
[LELEI] Itami is returning to
Japan
to testify to their Senate.
[PINA] To their Senate?!
[LELEI] That's correct...
that's why they are in such a
hurry.
[PINA] Huh... The Japanese have
a senate...
[PINA] So then... ...then that
means...
[PINA] Depending on what he
tells them,
[PINA] They could have their
military do something in
retaliation!
Something.. horrible... (gasp)
[PINA] Wait!
[SQUAD] (reax)
(reax)
[PINA] I... want to...!
(uneasy)(gasp)
[PINA] I would like to... to
accompany you to Alnus Hill!
[YOJI] What's that?
[PINA] I must speak
with your superior...
and apologize to him... for
violating the treaty.
[PINA] Is that possible Sir
Itami?
[YOJI] Come with us?
[BOSES] Princess...?
[PINA] Mm‐hm.
[KURATA] Take it easy Persia!
I'll be back soon!
[PERSIA] MyI'll be waiting for
you!
[KURATA] I love you!
[YOJI] I guess the princess
is really coming with us,
isn't she?
[TOMITA] Sir... a message from
the major...
"he said we can bring them in."
"And treat them with all due
courtesy."
[YOJI] Yeah, yeah...
just let him know what our ETA
is willya?
[YOJI] Move out!
(uneasy)
(breath catch)
[BOSES] Uh... Princess! I can
see it!
[PINA] You mean we're already
there?
[PINA] That was fast.
[PINA] What are those staffs?
Is every soldier in this
army a Wizard?
[LELEI] No, ma'am. They're not
using any magic. Um...
Those are weapons they call
"rifles".
[PINA] Those are weapons?!
[LELEI] This is how they work.
A small amount of fire is
ignited within the cylinder...
forcing out a small stone at
high speed...
[PINA] Every single Japanese
soldier has a weapon like that
one...
[LELEI] Yes...
It's part of their basic
teachings.
Every Japanese soldier is
trained to use one...
apparently quite well.
[PINA] They don't even have to
be in the proximity
of their enemy to take them out.
[LELEI] It's the reason
the Imperial Army fell.
(nasal inhale, pensive)(gasp)
[PINA] First their flying
steel... and now steel
elephants.
[PINA] They really are...
Creatures from another world.
[PINA] Why have they come here?
What do they want from us?
[LELEI] The Empire stepped on
the griffon's tail.
[BOSES] Mind your mouth, girl.
Do not speak so casually
when the Empire is on
the verge of collapse.
[LELEI] My tribe roams
where it pleases, Knight.
[LELEI] We've never answered to
the Empire.
[PINA] I suppose you can rule a
nation by force...
[PINA] But you can't control
what they think
no matter how hard you try.
[PINA] Lieutenant Itahmi...
Since were both here,
could I have a moment to speak
with you? Uh?
[YOJI] Uhhh... Sorry, no...
I really need to attend a few
briefings
about all this
meeting‐with‐the‐government
stuff. Hehe.
Sgt. Kuribayashi should be able
to help you I'm sure!
(gacking)
[BOSES] Princess?
[PINA] I lost my chance
to tell him how peaceful we are.
[HAZAMA] Sorry for the wait.
[LELEI] This is General Hazama
from the Self Defense Force.
[HAZAMA] Please, go ahead and
have a seat.
Well now... having you here is a
bit unusual so...
there must be something you
wanted to discuss with me.
[PINA] Regarding the treaty...
I'm afraid things have gotten
off to a rough start...
And I would like to apologize
for that.
[LELEI] She is sorry.
[HAZAMA] Itami's report was very
thorough...
You hadn't communicated with
your inferiors yet.
[PINA] (erk!) It's true...
but we've taken care of that.
[LELEI] It's true.
[HAZAMA] We're currently using
you as an intermediary
between our government and those
running your Empire.
If this is causing you any
problems
we'll be more than happy to
reconsider terms of the treaty.
[PINA] The treaty's fine
as it is! I don't think any
changes are necessary.
[YANAGIDA] Can you clarify
something for me...?
Part of the report said
your knight over there
really gave him the business.
[PINA,BOSES] (gasp)
[YANAGIDA] Covered the poor guy
in bruises and scratches...
[YANAGIDA]  I found it
hilarious.
As you might expect Itami was
naturally embarrassed
and tried to pretend it never
happened.
[YANAGIDA] Or course it kinda
made me wonder
if perhaps he said or did
something out of line.
[PINA] (nervous laugh)
[LELEI] Allow me to clarify...
Did Lt. Itami do something rude
to make you strike him?
[BOSES] No... no sir, he didn't.
[LELEI] Very well...
what did he do to make you
want to hit him?
Create a situation where you
needed to defend yourself?
Tell us in detail, if you would
please.
[PINA,BOSES] (uneasy sounds)
[LELEI] He'd like to know.
[HAZAMA] All right Yanagida,
I think that'll be more than
enough.
Don't you see how
nervous you're making them?
[YANAGIDA] Sorry, sir.
[TUKA] What? You really
want me to go
to the other side of the GATE?
[YOJI] That's right. You know
what this world is like...
so I would like you to talk to
them about it.
[YOJI] We'll be leaving
tomorrow... and staying for two
nights...
We're gonna be back before you
know it.
[TUKA] So you'll
be going as well?
[YOJI] Yeah I've gotta go.
Oh and Lelei's coming...
She'll interpret for us.
[TUKA] OK, Father... what would
you do now?
[YOJI] What?
[TUKA] Oh. No no it's nothing.
So it will make you happy
if I go to the other side and
speak to your government?
[YOJI] Well not just me.
It's more like all of us'd be
happy.
We'd all really appreciate it if
you went with us. M'kay?
[TUKA] Well... If that's the
case, yes, I'll go.
[RORY] Wait just a minute!
(grunt) [BOTH] Huh? Hm?
[RORY] You cannot seriously be
considering
going to the other side without
taking me.
[YOJI]  Now hang on...
Ehh?
[KATO] Yoohoo! I wanna go too...
[YOJI] Huh?
[YOJI] (big stretch) Ah! I'm
beat!
Making sure the ammo gets back
to the armory...
Breaking down the guns and
cleaning them up...
taking all the vehicles to the
wash rack and
getting all the mud and dirt off
of 'em.
They are gonna run me ragged.
[YOJI] Huh?
[YOJI] What now?
[YOJI] Wait a second... it's
winter there isn't it?
[YOJI] I gonna make it to that
convention
if it's the last thing I ever
do!
[YOJI] It's getting kinda late,
don't you think?
[LELEI] Uh, Itami... May I get a
ride back to camp...
I'm so tired...
[YOJI] You've been interpreting
this whole time?
'Splains why you're tired.
[YOJI] But well... I don't think
I can check out a car this late.
[YOJI] So, why don't you just
stay... oh..
(snoozies)
[YOJI] I'll take that as a yes.
[YOJI] Ah! Oh crap! Uh uh!
I definitely do not need to have
Kurata seeing me like this! Mph!
[YOJI] I should probably get
something to eat.
I wonder if there's any dinner
leftover.
[BOSES] Your Majesty... Do you
think it's possible they
would use this incident to start
a war with the Empire?
[PINA] No. If they wanted to do
that...
they'd never have let us come
here in the first place.
Not to mention how civil the
general was today.
[BOSES] Why then...?
[PINA] I'm not really sure...
These people are so different
from us...
I honestly have no idea what
they're fighting for.
I don't get it.
[PINA] But I could find out...
[BOSES] Your Majesty... you
can't do that...
[PINA] We must go with them...
[TOMITA] You sure this is okay,
Lieutenant?
[TOMITA] Come on, sir. Isn't she
a little much?
[YOJI] Absolutely, but I got
permission.
[YOJI] Besides... do you really
want her
going off here while we're away?
[TUKA] Why are we wearing such
heavy clothes?
[LELEI] The soldiers are saying
that
it will be much colder when we
get there.
[YANAGIDA] I do apologize...
The paperwork took a while...
but we're done.
[YOJI] Huh?!
[YANAGIDA] These two are flying
under the radar,
if you get my meaning,
Lieutenant.
Keep an eye on them for us.
[YOJI] Are we just showing up
unannounced?
[YANAGIDA] People already know
they're going to be there.
This is directly from the
General.
He wants all of our guests to
have a proper welcome.
[YANAGIDA] Treat the Princess
like you would any ambassador.
And a quick tour around Tokyo
wouldn't hurt.
[TUKA] This is the gate to the
other world.
[RORY] Oh how exciting.
[LELEI] We're not going to the
other side to have fun, Rory.
[RORY] Speak for yourself, kid.
[BOSES] This is it.
[PINA] Yes...
[PINA] The country on the other
side...
[PINA] Come. Let's go.
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
Japan, The Other Side of The
Gate