[LELEI] Japan's Self Defense
Force
was dispatched to
the mysterious Special Region.
[LELEI] After arriving in the
secret village of the dark
elves,
[LELEI] Itami and his friends
team up with Yao and her people
to fight the vicious flame
dragon.
[LELEI] Many were killed, but
they were able to defeat the
dragon.
[LELEI] Tuka who was traumatized
by the death of her father was
saved from her own insanity.
[HIGAKI] Chief of Special Region
Dispatch 3rd Deep Recon
Surveillance Unit,
[HIGAKI] First Lieutenant Yoji
Itami, You are suspended for two
weeks.
Relieved from your rank,
[HIGAKI] and confined to
Special Region Headquarters.
[ITAMI] Yeah... I figured as
much.
[HIGAKI] You're a disgrace.
You abandoned your subordinates
and acted solely on
your own accord.
[ITAMI] I was prepared for the
consequences.
[HIGAKI] Sir?
[HAZAMA] Now to receive your
honors!
What?
[HIGAKI] Did you say honors?!
[HAZAMA] Commendations are
bestowed upon you
by the Minister of Defense,
For saving the
Japanese hostages!
Also, from the King of Elbe,
you have been given a letter of
appreciation...
And granted a
title of nobility.
You also received another letter
of appreciation...
[HAZAMA] from the tribal leader
of the Dark Elves making you an
honorary tribe member.
[HAZAMA] You've earned some sort
of ownership of a girl named
Yao.
I hope I can trust you will not
abuse this.
[HAZAMA] But now for the true
topic at hand.
[HAZAMA] First Lieutenant
Yoji Itami,
[HAZAMA] You are to be in charge
of all research projects
concerning resources in the
Special Region.
[ITAMI] Research projects for
resources?
[HAZAMA] You are hereby
permitted to walk freely
throughout the Region
searching for usable assets.
You can hire the 'team'
you've assemble
as your regional guides.
[HAZAMA] Once your suspension is
over,
you are to report
immediately to said mission.
[ITAMI] Yes, sir! Thank you,
sir!
[ITAMI] I was actually hoping to
relax a little bit.
[ITAMI] So how's it going over
there, uh?
[LELEI] I'm trying to
focus...Don't speak to me right
now.
[ITAMI] You look like you might
be getting the hang of it.
[LELEI] Maybe a little.
[ITAMI] I think you have a knack
for this.
Especially compared to the rest
of the girls.
[RORY] Um excuse me?!
[ITAMI] Ha! Now... you just keep
going straight till we get to
Rondel.
[LELEI] Understood.
[ITAMI] The city of magic, huh.
It'd be real nice if we could
get there by noon.
[LELEI] The streets to Rondel
are narrow and can be congested
with travelers.
[LELEI] It's safe to assume that
it will take some time.
[RORY] By the way... how long
would it take to get to Bernago?
[ITAMI] Isn't Bernago the place
where uh...
[RORY] That's right. It's where
Hardy's temple is located.
[RORY] I'm wanting to tell her ‐
to her face
she will never in a million
years have me as her own.
[YAO] If possible..I'd like to
go too.
[ITAMI] Maybe, we could go in
between Lelei's presentations
for the conference.
[LELEI] That wouldn't be a
problem for me.
[ITAMI] Tuka, is there anywhere
you want to go?
[TUKA] Are you kidding?..
You just took me somewhere
horrible
that I never wanted to go to in
the first place, remember?
[TUKA] Remember, father?
[ITAMI] Yeah sorry about that.
[TUKA] No need to apologize.
[TUKA] I appreciate what you did
for me.
[ITAMI] You're quite welcome
Tuka.
[ITAMI] Hey we totally defeated
the flame dragon, ...didn't we
guys?
[LELEI] Rondel has a longer
history than the Empire.
[LELEI] The city's origin is the
school that was constructed by
the gods of learning,
Elran and Lah, Back when they
were still demigods.
[ITAMI] Wow. You can feel the
history of this place. And
man...
[ITAMI] Most of the people look
like they're just kids.
Guess that makes sense given
that there are so many students.
[LELEI] One of the Rondel's most
distinctive traits...
...is everyone's irrational
attitude towards life.
[LELEI] We should be able to
find a hotel around here.
[ITAMI] Oh! I could use a nap!
Let's go!
[HOSTLER] It's an honor to
welcome friends of her
Holiness...
Do make yourselves at home.
[HARMAR] Welcome Apostle, and
all who are in service to the
God of Emroy.
Tis an honor beyond our highest
expectations.
Welcome each of you to Hotel
Shokai.
[ITAMI] When did we...
become an entourage to her great
Holiness?
[LELEI] Keep it quiet.
The higher our status, the
better we will be treated here.
[ITAMI] I guess old po‐dunk
towns are all the same,
no matter what dimension.
[HARMAR] Welcome to the city of
Rondel.
We've prepared the very best
accommodations for you.
[HARMAR] Our staff here will be
in charge of showing you to your
rooms...
as well as taking care of your
every need.
[HARMAR] Please rest assured
you will be in excellent hands
with them.
They're the best we have.
[ITAMI] Ah... well that's great.
[HARMAR] Are you here to
accompany
this young lady on her magical
appointments?
[HARMAR] We'll see to it that
it's as pleasant as possible.
Now please make yourself
comfortable.
It is Room #2 at the south end
of the third floor.
[ITAMI] Excuse me.
[HARMAR] Hm?
[ITAMI] What about my room?
[HARMAR] Oh, yes Manservant.
Your quarters are right across
from hers. Room #3
[HARMAR] It's a tool shed, but
it's convenient for you to
receive orders and run errands.
I thought it useful.
You're welcome.
[ITAMI] Well crap. Oh well so
much for my honorary nobility.
[ITAMI] May I come in?
[RORY] Of course.
[ITAMI] Wow...now that's a fancy
outfit.
[TUKA] You look like a great
scholar!
[YAO] Is it customary in this
city to wear things like this?
[RORY] Only custom for certain
people.
Anyone trying to become a master
mage will wear this in Rondel.
[ITAMI] Master, you say? Is it
like a college professor?
[LELEI] Yes in your system...
that would be very similar.
[LELEI] Do you think... this
fits me?
[ITAMI] Yeah.. suits you very
well. You look great.
[LELEI] If my presentations at
the conference are not accepted,
then those in attendance... will
throw ink all over my robes.
[LELEI] And from then on, I
won't be allowed to take it off
while in the city,
[LELEI] Nor will I become a
master.
[ITAMI] You study very hard and
excel at everything you do.
[ITAMI] You'll be just fine!
[HARMAR] Goodness.
Your garments!
[HARMAR] Are you telling me this
young lady is going for the
title of master?
[ITAMI] Oh and I'm not a
manservant either!
Could you please remember that?
[LELEI] That's the hall where
the conference presentations are
to be held.
[LELEI] The city council hall is
over there.
[LELEI] And over here is the
District of Research and
Development.
[ITAMI] I assume this must
be where the great teachers are.
[LELEI] They stay secluded.
[ITAMI] Huh? Secluded?
[LELEI] Yes
[explosion]
[RESEARCHER A] No!!! That was
all of my research!
[RESEARCHER B] Someone! Please
make it stop!
[RESEARCHER C] Augh! It's the
papers I wrote my new formula
on!
I've been working on that for
months!
[RESEARCHER A] Oh my god
not again! Not again!
[RESEARCHER B] Everything is
soaking wet! What have you
done?!
[RESEARCHER C] Unbelievable! No
no noooo!
[LELEI] As I said.. they stay
secluded.
[ITAMI] Oh. I gotcha.
[MIMOZA] Yes?
[LELEI] It's Lelei.
[MIMOZA] Aah! Ahhhhh!!!
[LELEI] It's been a long time.
[MIMOZA] Oooh! Oh dear! Oh my!
Oh my! Oh dear!
[MIMOZA] Is it really you...?
Lily!
[LELEI] Um It's... Lelei.
[MIMOZA] Is that right...
Well, I think Lily is a little
bit cuter.
[MIMOZA] We'll just change it to
Lily starting today.
[LELEI] No, thank you.
Wellll, well now please do come
in, all of you please!
[MIMOZA] Welcome everyone!
[TUKA] Uh. She's very cheerful.
[ITAMI] That's putting it
mildly.
[MIMOZA] Here. Let's look at
this, I see, I see...
Oh! that's what happened?
[MIMOZA] Ah this is great, Lily!
[LELEI] My name is Lelei.
[MIMOZA] And here I thought
you were way too young
to try and achieve a master's
title,
[MIMOZA] but as far as I can
tell from Kato's letter,
your achievements are
outstanding.
[LELEI] You heard from Kato?
[MIMOZA] Yes!
[LELEI] May I ask,
where is Arpeggio?
[MIMOZA] She just left to go
shopping.
Oh! By the way, Lily...
Would you mind helping me?
We need some chairs for all the
guests.
[LELEI] Um my name is Lelei.
[LELEI] Are you okay?
[MIMOZA] Oh dear.
I'm so very clumsy.
Oh dear. Just look at me.
[ITAMI] Are you alright?
[ARPEGGIO] Mimoza?
[MIMOZA] Yes?
[MIMOZA] Oh Arpeggio..
oh my oh dear... I'm so sorry.
[ARPEGGIO] What tha!
I told you not to make
a mess of things
while I was gone!
[MIMOZA] Oh dear oh my....
[ARPEGGIO] Ah! Honestly!
I will clean all this up,
just get out of the way alright!
[ARPEGGIO] Please, just stay
outside for a while.
[MIMOZA] Listen. While you were
out,
Lily dropped by to see us!
Uh‐huh.
[ARPEGGIO] Lily? Who the heck's
that?
[LELEI] Ugh. It's Lelei.
[ARPEGGIO] Uh. Oh. MMhph.
[ARPEGGIO] Mimoza.
Would you please get
us a table
at our regular restaurant.
[ARPEGGIO] I will be there
shortly.
I have a sister
who is about to test
for master mage,
[ARPEGGIO] Meanwhile her older
sister
will still be working towards
her doctorate.
My younger sister is flirting
around with attractive men
while her older sister
still has no experience at all.
My younger sister, who
apparently gallivants with the
rich and famous
while her older sister struggles
to get by.
And oh yes, a little sister,
who travels with elves and
divine apostles!
She's so greeeat.
We certainly have lots and lots
of catching up to do!
[ITAMI] Lelei... Is she by any
chance...uh...?
[LELEI] Yes.
She is my... sister. Arpeggio.
[MIMOZA] Oh dear.
[PINA] This is a fine day.
I can't believe we finally made
it this far.. Sugawara.
[SUGAWARA] Yes...The peace talks
between the Empire and Japan
are finally set to begin.
[PINA] It's good. Once the talks
finally move forward...
I think my work will be done.
[PINA] I will be able to fully
indulge myself in studying the
arts.
[PINA] Oh by the way, Sugawara?
[SUGAWARA] Huh?
You seem to have a young admirer
with an interest in you.
[PINA] Those pearls are
impressive.
Looks like you may have won the
heart
of the Tueli's daughter with
such expensive gifts.
[SUGAWARA] Let's take it easy.
Y'see in my country...
it's not proper for an older man
to treat a young girl as we
would a woman.
[PINA] Oh that doesn't mean
anything in our world.
You should know that.
[PINA] That girl has
a crush on you.
[SHERRY] Sugawara! Sugawara!
[SHERRY] The fruit that grow on
that tree over there are really
great!
[SUGAWARA] I'm very sorry...
but I am busy right now Sherry.
[SHERRY] Sugawara! Did you see
all the food over there?
[SUGAWARA] I'm sorry... but I
have a very important meeting to
attend.
[SHERRY] Sugawara! You wanna
take a walk with me?!
[SUGAWARA] Aah... I'm very
sorry... but I need to stay here
right now.
[SHERRY] Sugawara!
Sugawara!
[SUGAWARA] Listen Sherry. I
can't play with you tonight
okay.
My work must come first. Please
understand.
[SHERRY] You really shouldn't be
so unkind to me.
Because in just four short
years...
I will become a most suitable
woman for you to marry.
[SHERRY] This would be a
wonderful opportunity for you
to introduce me to your
country's vice minister.
[SUGAWARA] And why would you
want that?
[SHERRY] To say hello!
It's important to
meet important people,
especially if they work with my
future husband.
[SUGAWARA] Excuse me.
[SHERRY] I'm just messing with
you.
Take a look around.
The guests from the Empire...
None of them are going anywhere
near the Japanese delegates.
[SHERRY] All they know about
Japan...
is it's a mysterious country
with great military power.
[SHERRY] They're afraid of you
above anything else.
[SUGAWARA] You're right.
[SHERRY] That is not
an ideal position
‐ for either you or your country
to be in.
We need to improve relations.
[SHERRY] How can we talk peace
if we can't hold a conversation?
[SHERRY] Please understand...
I'm more useful than you might
think I am.
[SUGAWARA] Vice Minister
Shirayuri.
This is the daughter of the
Tuelis.
[SHERRY] It is a pleasure ma'am.
[SHIRAYURI] Nice to meet you.
I am Vice Minister Shirayuri.
[SHIRAYURI] You're so young.
And yet you can speak fluent
Japanese already?
[SHIRAYURI] That's very
impressive.
Tell me, who taught you to speak
so well?
[SHERRY] Sugawara of course!
He has been a very kind and
patient teacher
helping me learn so many things!
[SHERRY] Look he even gave me
this beautiful string of pearls.
[SHIRAYURI] Oh?
[SHIRAYURI] Listen Sugawara...
I hope you haven't done anything
that might create an
uncomfortable situation.
[SUGAWARA] Please Miss Vice
Minister
give me a little credit
here for god's sake.
[SHERRY] Oh I was wondering
about something, Miss Shirayuri.
[NOBLEWOMAN] I'm very interested
in women's fashion over there.
Must be fabulous.
[SHIRAYURI] Then you must be
extremely disappointed to see
what I'm wearing.
[NOBLEWOMAN] Not at all, you
look splendid in that outfit.
[SHERRY] So... I think that went
well.
[SUGAWARA] You were right.
Thanks to you, they are feeling
much safer around us.
[SUGAWARA] Thank you very much
Sherry.
[SHERRY] Oh. It was nothing.
Anything for my future husband.
[SUGAWARA] Oh God... what have I
gotten myself into?
[THULE] The ceremony will begin
soon, Your Highness.
[ZORZAL] Quiet!
[THULE] Apologies, sire.
[ZORZAL] Augh! These
ridiculous peace talks
were never
supposed to happen.
I did everything I could to
derail this.
[ZORZAL] I even made it look
like that Japanese whore's
assassination
was ordered by my own sister!
[THULE] I know sire...
I'm sorry...
[ZORZAL] Don't apologize Thule,
I'm not blaming you.
You're just the messenger.
It's not your fault the
assassination attempt failed.
[ZORZAL] But there'll be no more
tricks from now on.
We're going to need support
in case something happens...
We'll need more numbers to see
this through.
[THULE] Yes.
[ZORZAL] I'm at a loss.
I don't have clue what I could
possibly do anymore anyway.
[THULE] But you are the next
rightful heir. Your Highness.
[ZORZAL] That's exactly it.
I am but a step away from the
throne.
It's maddening being so close to
the Emperor
without being able to take it!
Hmph.
He is such an idiot.
[THULE] As well as so easily
manipulated.
[BOULO] I'm here for you.
What would you like me to do
next?
I have gathered some fresh
elites to join our cause.
[THULE] They'll have to wait for
now.
They will have their chance soon
enough.
There's... something I want you
to prepare for me.
[BOULO] Anything.
[CHAMBERLAIN] Ladies and
Gentlemen, Presenting:
the great Emperor Molto, Prince
Zorzal, and Princess Pina!
[SUGAWARA] The first is The
Emperor Molto,
behind him his children Prince
Zorzal and then the Princess.
[SHIRAYURI] That's Prince
Zorzal?
[PINA] What're you doing?
[ZORZAL] Guys! I'm so glad
you all made it back.
Helm, you are safe!
[HELM] Yes..Your Highness!
[ZORZAL] Kalasta.
I hope you're well.
[KALASTA] Yes thank you my
Prince.
We are all very grateful!
[ZORZAL] I'm glad
you made it too, Mudra!
[PINA] Zorzal! We're in the
middle of a ceremony!
[MOLTO] Pay it no mind, Pina.
[MOLTO] Allow him to
congratulate
those who have returned to us.
[MOLTO] We shall continue with
the ceremony, please.
[CHAMBERLAIN] Yes, sir, of
course.
[CHAMBERLAIN] Japan, who has
returned
our prisoners of war to us,
Has sent their esteemed
delegates!
[MOLTO] Have them come forward.
I would like to greet our
guests.
[CHAMBERLAIN] Representatives
from Japan,
please come before the Emperor!
[SHIRAYURI] I am honored to meet
you, Your Majesty.
[MOLTO] I appreciate you two
coming all this way.
We are honored to have you here.
I welcome you, as the Emperor of
our great land.
[SHIRAYURI] Thank you, your
majesty
[HELM] Your Highness!
This is an utter embarrassment!
[KALASTA] I know that it was
all for our safe return,
But the Empire is making peace
with these people
under inauspicious conditions.
[ZORZAL] That day of my
humiliation was sheer agony...
[ZORZAL] It was the day I chose
not to resist...
[ZORZAL] I chose to appear as
though I was incapable
to avoid being purged...
[ZORZAL] But...THOSE DAYS ARE
OVER!
[SUGAWARA] Is he directing this
anger
toward the Emperor?
[BOSES] Oh you look exhausted,
your Grace. Y'okay?
[PINA] Yes I am.
His Majesty has at last approved
the peace negotiations with the
delegates.
[PINA] My dream is finally
coming true.
[PINA] No matter how tiring,
the path toward peace is now
under way.
[SHANDY] I am glad you have
finally found a place
where you can feel at ease,
Princess.
[PINA] I think I deserve
this moment. Uh‐huh.
[MOLTO] So the flame dragon has
been slain.
[MARCUS] Yes, your majesty.
We are still at a loss as to who
was responsible.
This was merely dropped at the
gates.
[MOLTO] We must find this hero..
[MOLTO] Does anyone in
attendance
...know of the warrior who
defeated this great beast?
[PINA] Your Majesty!
[MOLTO] Yes what is it, Pina?
Do you know... something about
this victory?
[PINA] She does. She can
tell us who was responsible
for the killing
of the flame dragon.
[PINA] Go ahead.
[SHANDY] Sire! A man named
Itami,
and Rory, Lelei, Tuka, and Yao.
It was all five of them who put
down the dragon!
[MOLTO] Rory the Reaper?
[SHANDY] Yes! It was! It was Rory
Mercury...
the divine apostle of the God
Emroy!
[MOLTO] Well that I can believe.
[MOLTO] If she was indeed there
helping them...
then the besting of the flame
dragon is understandable.
[MOLTO] Although... it does
surprise me
that an apostle would involve
herself
in something like this.
[MOLTO] But I guess that means
the glory goes to the gods.
[SHANDY] Well. It was Yoji
Itami...
who led the team on the attack,
sire.
[MOLTO] Itami?
[PINA] The same man
who was in charge
when Prince Zorzal...
was beaten...
[PINA] By a young girl.
[MOLTO] Oh, yes of course.
So you're saying our enemy was
involved in the killing?
[MOLTO] And what about the other
members?
[SHANDY] Tuka is an elf from the
Forest of Lodo.
[SHANDY] And Yao is a dark elf
who lives in the Schwartz Woods.
[MOLTO] They're of so many
breeds and races.
[SHANDY] Yes. And the last was
Lelei la Lalena,
a disciple of the sage Kato.
[SHANDY] From the Coda Village.
[MOLTO] Ohhh! A disciple of Old
Master Kato.
[MOLTO] Then I take it she is
human.
[SHANDY] Yes. Right.
She's a descendant of Lourdos,
[SHANDY] but recently settled in
the Coda Village,
so we can rightfully call her a
subject of the Empire!
[MOLTO] Oh? S'that so?!
Well that is excellent news to
hear! Pina...
[MOLTO] I give you the task of
finding this heroine, Lelei.
You are to bring her back to the
palace for me, my dear.
[MOLTO] I would like to reward
her.
This is a wonderful thing, is it
not?
[PINA] It is!
[MOLTO] Very well then.
So it is ordered
to bring her here.
[SUGAWARA] He seems very happy
about it doesn't he?
That one of his own subjects was
involved.
[SHIRAYURI] It's the same in any
country I guess.
We would have similar feelings
in Japan as well.
[SUGAWARA] I suppose so.
[ZORZAL] What in the hell is
going on here?!
What makes her so damn special?!
[ZORZAL] Why is my father
pandering
to offer praise to some dirty
commoner?!
[ZORZAL] I AM THE CROWN PRINCE!
[HELM] Your Highness! You must
set this right!
[KALASTA] We cannot sit back and
watch this happen!
[HELM] Your Highness!
[PINA] What's wrong with him?
[MOLTO] Everyone!
[MOLTO] To our noble Empire...
and to all its people!
[GUESTS] To the Empire!
[GUESTS] No! Your Majesty!
[PINA] Father!
[BOULO] An elixir from the
Haryo.
It has a most... satisfying
effect.
[PINA] Father!
Wake up! Father!
[PINA] AAgh!!
[LELEI] Next time on Gate:
The Dangerous Sisters