Lelei:
Japan's Self Defense Force
was dispatched
to the mysterious
Special Region.
In order to stop the piper
from creating more assassins,
Itami and his friends head
to the Imperial Capital,
where the Order of the Rose
and the Imperial Army
are raging in battle.
With the number of innocent
victims mounting,
the Japanese government has
finally given the order
to initiate a
critical rescue mission.
We've been ordered to
attack the Imperial Capital
and occupy the target at once!
Our objective is to rescue our
people being held at Jade Palace
Hazama:
as well as protect those
who support peace
who are seeking asylum.
To get this done,
timing will be everything!
Kengun:
We must complete the entire
mission by 1800 hours!
Soldiers! Prepare
to sync your watches now.
In ten seconds!
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one. Mark!
JSDF Superior:
During the Ginza incident,
we saw our citizens being
captured by the Special Region.
But, at the same time,
there are political leaders
in their local government
seeking to negotiate
a peaceful path with us.
Their lives depend on
the success of your mission.
With bravery and honor,
I expect that you will
do your duty efficiently
and make our country proud.
Let this be my order.
This is Saber.
At the ready.
Radio:
Target locked.
Saber:
Air defense facility
is destroyed.
(dragons roar)
(dragons death rattle)
Radio A:
There is no threat over
the Imperial Capital, over.
Radio B:
Roger. Now to proceed
to phase two.
You there!
Send a messenger now!
Uhh... ah!
Uh... oh!
(strained death rattle)
This is Assassin.
It's done.
Assassin:
The west gate
is now under our control.
We will continue
to stay alert.
Tomita here.
I'm with Kuribayashi
at the top of the tower.
Don't advance
too far.
We will attack with
the Special Forces...
and 4th Recon Unit.
Soldier:
Let's go!
The enemy has
reached the west gate.
Ahh!
Side gate is clear.
Soldiers:
Ahhh!
(death screams)
Kuwabara:
Status!
Nishina:
Clear!
Katsumoto:
Kurata:
Clear!
Kuwabara:
Room is clear!
(chuckles)
I'll leave the rest to you guys.
Soldier:
Six minutes before jump!
Ready?! Let's go!
Sir!
Superior:
What?
Sir!
Stand up!
Radio:
Convoy No.1. The course
is clear. Ready! Ready! Ready!
Jump away!
We're green!
Superior:
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
That's about it.
Line's clear!
See you when
it's over!
Aah!
Ah!
Zorzal:
What are those?!
Your Highness!
That is the enemy!
They're raining down
from the sky!
Look at 'em all!
My Prince! We must
prepare a counterattack!
Ah...
Your Highness!
Uh...
Yes you're right!
We can defeat them!
We have a higher number
of men than they do.
We should be able
to overpower their forces.
Reporting sir!
An enemy unit has already
taken over the west gate!
And there are several
more enemy soldiers
waiting on the
other side.
Argh! We are not
ready for this!
Huh?
Damn it, what in the hell
are the guards doing over there?
They're going to come
looking for us, sire!
(frightened groans)
Your Highness.
I sincerely hope you're
not thinking about
running away from
your throne.
What? No no of
course not!
You are the all powerful
ruler of the Empire.
If you were to flee,
the Empire would forever
be lost to the hands
of foreign intruders.
(growls)
Hmph! You needn't
worry about that.
They will never
take it from me.
Very well.
It pleases me to hear that
you're going to remain here.
Even if the enemy were
to breach the Palace,
I know that you would be brave
and fight back.
Because you proudly
stand for everything
that this country
represents!
How you go,
so goes the Empire.
Ah...
I know! I am well aware
of my position!
I'm sorry... if I was
being out of line.
I am certain that you will
make the right decision.
Radio:
Landing coordinates
are three‐one‐zero.
Landing zone "Sakura."
Wind direction
is three‐zero.
(death screams)
Emperial Soldiers:
(battle cry)
Assassin here.
A large number of enemy soldiers
are approaching the west gate.
Assassin:
This is not good!
What do you see?
They're down there
by the corner.
Let's move out!
Recon 1:
There's a large
number of soldiers
waiting to cross the bridge.
Recon 2:
I see it. It's gonna be
trouble if they cross.
(helicopter overhead)
Ah. Here they are.
Ok, We'll take
over from here!
Roger that!
Good luck, we're gonna
get the evacuees to safety!
This is three‐one. I can see the
enemy unit at Bassoon Prison.
Look to be moving towards
the Palace. Over.
Radio:
Four‐zero, roger.
What're they doing?
Why aren't they making
any moves this way?
Ah! They're here!
Go straight ahead.
Jade Palace in two miles.
Right, copy, that!
Unit Leader:
Confirming the target!
Shino:
Don't push! Follow
the person in front of you!
Listen there is enough
transportation for everyone.
There's no need to worry!
I don't get it,
why can't we just leave
all the nobles behind?
Oh you know
better than that.
The men‐in‐green have provided
everyone here with so much.
I would say it is time we
repay them for their kindness.
Misery:
And we do that
with kindness ourselves.
Oh hey there
Mrs. Cicero!
Kuribayashi.
I can't tell you
how happy I am
to see you here!
Oh thank you so much!
Ahhh... Alrighty then.
I'm just doing what I'm told.
Oh thank you so much!
Ahhh... Alrighty then.
I'm just doing what I'm told.
Ma'am?
Oh?
Would your husband
happen to be with you?
Yes. He's right
over there, dear.
I know the SDF has our best
interests at heart...
But judging by the looks
of the current situation ‐
Are you taking us over?
Has the empire been defeated?
No, ma'am. ,/
All we've been ordered to do
is see to your rescue
and provide safe passage
out of the area.
We're taking all of you
to Italica!
Climb in and make room
for everyone.
We have a lot of
people to fit in.
We'll be leaving
very shortly.
We'll use the
west gate exit.
(horses whinny)
(screaming)
Itami, please
be careful!
Do you honestly
need to drive so fast?
You're scaring
us, Daddy!
You need to stop driving
so fast slow down!
Yao:
Itami!
No!
Nobody... is going
to die on my watch!
Reporting sir!
The 401st Company...
has secured
the landing point.
We're all green
and good to go.
Airborne 12th Company
has taken over all routes
to the Capital.
The road is clear.
All units have begun
evacuating the civilians.
Everything is going
according to plan.
The Airborne 11th Company should
be arriving at Jade Palace
just about
any moment now.
Grr...
(long breath)
(death screams)
Fan out to the right.
Our targets are the
officers wearing black.
Take them out and the
rest of their soldiers
will be in disaray.
We will provide any needed
support. Now fire away!
(battle grunt)
(death rattles)
The commander is really
getting into this.
Yeah well it's our first real
battle in the Special Region.
Just about everyone
out here's excited.
Unit Leader:
Get down!
Gah! Uhh...
Shit! Medic! Medic!
I need some help over here!
Calm down!
Keep him still,
and do not remove that arrow!
Unit Leader:
He'll have massive bleeding,
if you just yank it out.
(battle cries)
Keep firing men!
We can't let them
break through the barrier!
(death screams)
(screaming continues)
(cowarding pant)
Unit Leader:
Well done, men!
Excellent job!
(panicked panting)
You're not getting away from me!
Boses!
(panic intensifies)
Burn in Hell!
Ruflus:
(echoing death scream)
Radio:
Jade Palace is now secure.
Send in the last order. Over.
Huh?
You're gonna
be okay!
Radio:
Located the VIPs.
They're all safe
and accounted for!
Jade Palace is
under our control!
Roger. All units,
damage report.
Remain on
high alert. Over!
Radio 1:
Roger.
Radio 2:
Shirayuri:
Welcome gentlemen
we're glad you came.
Kengun:
We will begin an
evacuation immediately.
Miss Vice Minister,
do you have anything
you're bringing with you?
No thank you
I'm fine.
Good to see you again,
Colonel Kengun.
It's good to see you, too.
You look well.
(clears throat)
All of the civilians
are on route.
The entire Capital
will be cleared.
You will need to have safe
passage.
Have you secured
yourself a way out?
I have.
Then I have a favor
to ask of you.
Oh?
I would like...
the Order of the Rose...
to accompany you
out of the city.
Uh... I guess that's ok.
Once we are clear
of the area...
We go to the lands
of Count Folmar.
Understood.
And another thing.
We have a lot
of wounded soldiers.
They're in need of help.
And with our
limited resources...
We will have to
leave them here.
And it looks like they
won't be able to move
on their own, either.
Those men
are soldiers.
We will take them with us.
As if they're our own. ,/
You're a good man...
Colonel.
Huh?
Uh... I have
an idea sir.
I think maybe we can get
them out on the Chinooks.
Kengun:
Not bad. We'll transfer people
with serious injuries by air,
and the ones with
light injuries by land.
Soldier:
Sir! We're ready
for the transfer!
Everything will be fine.
If we hurry, we'll be able to
just make the rendezvous point.
Good. Well then...
I wish you
the best of luck.
Wait what?
Okay Vifita!
I leave the rest to you!
Where are you going?!
And what do you mean
"the rest"?!
I am off to rescue
Princess Piña.
I can't leave her!
I'll be back!
Hmm!
What! Are you crazy?!
You cannot do this alone!
Yah!
(panting)
Hmph... What the hell do you
think you're doing, you idiot?!
Boses, wait!
Uhhh...
Vifita:
We'll be back! Wait for us
at the rendezvous point!
Uhh... What...
just happened...?
Helm:
Reporting.
The dragon knights' camp has
been completely destroyed.
There were no survivors.
Kalasta:
Every last one of the
Opri‐chi‐nya member
has been killed.
And Ruflus was part
of the deceased!
Tch. What purpose
did they serve?
So Thule!
Yes, sire?
I need you.
I need some ideas.
Your Highness. You cannot allow
our enemies to go unpunished.
Gather all of your
remaining royal soldiers...
and send them to take
down Jade Palace.
Yes of course.
Send the soldiers
to Jade Palace right away!
I'm sorry...
But that's impossible.
Your guards are already on their
way to the Imperial Palace.
If we were to give them
a conflicting order
at this point...
It would cause
mass confusion.
Shut your mouth, shut up!
Yes, please
forgive us sir!
Look. If you can't
move the soldiers
that are already on route,
Then send the ones
that are already here.
Zorzal:
Have them move
out immediately!
Sir!
Oh!
Oh! Marquis Casel,
it's you!
You're alive!
Mercifully we managed
to escape to Jade Palace.
But it was close.
What happened to all
those who were captured?
Well those who stayed quiet
are still alive,
but the ones who spoke out ‐
not so lucky...
Just as I had feared...
My debt is paid.
Thanks, JSDF.
You on the horse!
Stop right there!
I am acting
commander, Boses.
Here on behalf of
the Order of the Rose.
I demand to see
Princess Pina right now!
That woman
is a traitor!
She's not allowed
in the palace!
Boses!
(battle cries)
Vifita:
Come on!
Princess Piña!
Vifita:
Get up!
Princess Pina!
Boses:
(crying)
If you die, it will all be for
nothing! We have to go back!
That should just about do it
for all the civilians!
Job well done.
We're the last ones here!
Good. It's time.
Move out!
Why are we still here, sir,
why haven't we left yet?
I have no idea, soldier.
But I'm sure the
Colonel must have a plan.
(growls)
Soldier 1:
Yeah... but still...
Soldier 2:
An enormous cavalry
is approaching!
Dammit! This doesn't
look good!
Kengun:
Prepare to fire!
Target the leading pack
of the chasing cavalry!
Distance, 200 meters!
Short, quick bursts!
Do NOT hit the girls
in front! Fire!
Fire!
(death screams)
Kengun:
Keep firing! Step back
to the second line!
(battle cries)
I gotcha.
Mooove! Don't leave
anyone behind!
Everybody hop on!
(exerts force)
Argh!
Everybody's on!
Get moving!
(angry yelling)
We almost didn't
make it, guys.
We did cut it
pretty close.
Uh... excuse me
Excuse me!
Oh... I'm sorry miss.
I'll uh put you down.
Princess Pina!
Colonel Kengun!
You must help the princess!
I am very sorry.
But I fear there is nothing
we can really do at the moment.
(gasps)
But, that can't be...
Boses:
Princess!
(sobbing)
Where's Itami?
He could get it done.
Helm:
The enemy soldiers
have rescued all the
pro‐peace representatives
held at Bassoon Prison.
They recruited the people
of Trouble Town to help,
and got them out of
the Imperial Capital.
The losses to our forces
are catastrophic.
I'm very sorry,
your Highness.
Now Thule...
Yes?
I've got to come up
with a way to fix this.
It's quite simple.
You'll inform the
remaining citizens,
that your Imperial Army
has repelled Japan.
You mustn't let them know...
that this was a defeat.
(seething)
But be sure. This will not be
the last time we see of them.
I know this ‐ Because we have,
in our possession,
the very key to
controlling the peace
talks to however we see fit.
Pina:
(pounding door)
(crying)
Someone please!
Let me out of here!
I can't stay here any longer!
Is anyone here?!
Answer me!
Say something!
Please... Someone...
Pina:
Help me...
Lelei:
Next time on Gate:
Thus They Fought