[LELEI] After the Self Defense
Force established a base
at Alnus Hill in the Special
Region...
Itami took Lelei, Rory and Tuka
to Japan
as representatives to
testify before the Diet.
[LELEI] And, just as they were
about to return home,
[LELEI] A huge crowd had
gathered to give them an
incredibly positive reception.
[LELEI] Now,
it has been almost 5 months
since the Empire first made
their attempt to attack Japan.
[LELEI] But since the Battle of
Italica,
A peaceful environment has
spread around the military
base at Alnus.
[LELEI] As ideas and goods
have been more regularly shared,
natives of the region have begun
staying around the camp at Alnus
Hill.
What was initially a refugee
camp has turned into a
flourishing township.
[LELEI] Meanwhile, Princess Pina
Co Lada,
who witnessed the strength of
Japan with her own eyes,
returned to the Imperial Capital
with a resolution to hold peace
talks.
[LELEI] Japan's Ministry of
Foreign Affairs sent
Koji Sugawara to join her in the
dialogue.
[LELEI] Both sides are now
preparing
to hold classified negotiations.
[HAMILTON] Today, you have a
luncheon with Lord Cicero.
And later, a dinner party at
Marquis Ducie's.
[HAMILTON] And between those,
you'll be having a meeting with
Shandy.
[HAMILTON] Were you up all night
again, ma'am?
You know you'll only end up
getting sick
if you keep doing
this to yourself.
[PINA] I know.
[PINA] However... the fate of
the Empire is too closely
dependent on the peace talks.
I'll get all the rest I need
once this is over.
[PINA] What's this?
[HAMILTON] The list of captives
we want released.
[PINA] Why are there fourteen?
I thought they were allowing us
to ask for the release of 15.
[HAMILTON] Don't you remember?
You told me to keep the list
trimmed down to 14, milady...
to leave room for Lord Cicero.
[PINA] Oh, yes... of course I
did.
[HAMILTON] Ma'am, are you sure
that you're okay?
[PINA] Let's assume for a moment
that I'm not ... could you step
in?
[HAMILTON] Oh no. Sounds awful.
[PINA] All right then... I'll
keep going.
Let's go. Sugawara is waiting.
[YAO] So this... is Alnus...
(laughing, talking, eating,
joking)
(exhales)
[SUGAWARA] Hmm... I think I
might fill up rather quickly.
[PINA] It's like I told you
already.
You don't have enough stomachs
for this.
[SUGAWARA] I guess not...
good thing the PX has plenty of
antacids for sale.
[PINA] Well that sounds helpful.
Cicero Lah Maltus.
His family is very important to
us... They're among the Empire's
founders...
Of course they have a strong
influence in the Senate.
[PINA] He has... a strong voice
among those pushing for war.
Since the devastating loss in
Alnus,
the Imperial Army is still
trying to recover.
[PINA] Meanwhile, the Senate is
still divided on how to use it
once we do recover.
Of course.. there's the group
that wants to use force...
they'd prefer to fight.
They will be standing behind the
Emperor's call to battle no
matter what.
[SUGAWARA] And the anti‐war
group...
I understand they're the
majority in the Senate, correct?
[PINA] That's right.
They want to restrict the power
of the Emperor,
who started this
reckless war...
They're moving to take command
of the Army away from the
Emperor
and form a militia controlled by
the Senate.
[PINA] And once that happens...
They hope to bring an end to
this, with Japan going back
through the Gate.
[SUGAWARA] So then they want us
to leave...
[PINA] They do.
And they'll jump at any
opportunity...
To do this without any more
violence.
[PINA] And so we... need to
convince one of the hawks to
change his mind.
[PINA] ...someone with
influence.
[PINA] Lord Cicero.
This is... Japan's diplomatic
envoy... Mister Sugawara
[SUGAWARA] Hello Lord Cicero...
I'm Koji Sugawara, it is a
pleasure to meet you, sir.
[CICERO] Well, now... Japan
huh...
[CICERO] You'll have to forgive
me, but I've never heard that
name before.
What kind of country is it?
[SUGAWARA] Well where
should I begin...?
The weather's nice... the water
and forests are beautiful.
[CICERO] Well...
isn't that lovely.
[CICERO] Must be a real nice
place to... visit.
[CICERO'S WIFE] Honey stop it.
[SUGAWARA] Allow me to present
you with some gifts from my
homeland.
[CICERO'S WIFE] Oh?
[SUGAWARA] We would be honored
if you accepted them.
These items were all created
by some of our finest craftsmen.
[CICERO] I must apologize for
being rude.
Your country seems to possess
excellent technology and
craftsmanship.
[CICERO] However... I still
don't know quite enough about it
just yet.
[CICERO] Where exactly is Japan
located, Mister Sugawara?
[SUGAWARA] Japan is the country
on the other side of the Gate,
sir.
But there's a little issue...
we're currently at war with the
Empire.
[CICERO] Oh is that so?!
All of you need to get out right
now!
[CICERO] The rest of this should
be discussed in private.
What were you thinking?!
You held negotiations in
secret...
...and then you even invite one
of their emissaries here?!
[CICERO] There are consequences
to this!
What do you think the Emperor
will do when he finds out?!
[CICERO] That goes for you too!
Don't think you'll get off...!
We're now in this together!
[SUGAWARA] Indeed.
[CICERO] You telling me my
nephew's still alive?!
[SUGAWARA] He is a prisoner of
war in our custody.
(gasp)
[CICERO] A prisoner of war?
[SUGAWARA] Yes.
The Princess has been
handling negotiations
on behalf of your
Empire.
Thanks to her he should be
released shortly.
[CICERO] In exchange, I suppose
you want me to represent
your interests in some formal
capacity.
[SUGAWARA] Not at all, sir the
Princess has already
volunteered.
(breath catch)
[CICERO] I see then.
You don't want me getting in the
way of your talks.
[PINA] I'd love for you to join
me...
I need to give the same
good news to the Ducie family.
I'm sure they would enjoy your
company, Senator.
[CICERO] To see Lord Ducie...
Yes well... I do seem to
remember their family's forces
joining the battle.
[CICERO] I would be most
delighted to go along with you,
Princess.
All I'm asking, is that you take
care of my nephew.
(street/shopping buzz)
[YOJI] Wow. Look at this place,
it's really gotten busy, hasn't
it, Old School?
[KUWABARA] It used to just be
the PX here...
And now they've gone and built a
little town around it.
[YOJI] Yeah, well I'm sure it
has something to do with the PX
being chock full of a bunch of
Japanese products that these
people have never seen before.
[KUWABARA] Yeah, I know... It's
kinda like a side market.
People are making a killing
selling all this stuff to the
nobility back home.
[YOJI] Is that what's going on?
Well that's kinda cool.
[YOJI] A lot of this makes for
some pretty sweet souvenirs,
don'tcha think?
[YOJI] Besides a little free
trade is a good thing for
everyone.
[KUWABARA] I wouldn't say
everyone, sir.
[YOJI] Huh?
[KUWABARA] We keep building
more and more streets and
buildings...
and that means we need more
people out here.
[KUWABARA] It's barely working
as it is...
we're lucky Princess Myui
decided to loan out her maids
to help run all this.
[KUWABARA] it does have its
negative effects as well.
[YOJI] What do you mean?
[KUWABARA] I'm not a
prohibitionist
but look at this...
way too much free time, sir.
[KUWABARA] It can lead to bad
habits...
and a lot of our young guys have
a taste for bad habits.
[YOJI] A soldier needs to unwind
after a hard day.
[YOJI] But, if things get too
out of hand I'm sure you know
how to straighten the goofballs
out.
[KUWABARA] Yeah.
[DELILAH] Hands off the tail,
asshole!
HYAHH!
(hit) (impact/roll)
[DELILAH] Who the hell do you
think you are?!
[DELILAH] This ass is for show
not for trash like you to try
and grab and smack
you got it you little pint sized
twerp!
[DWARF] Watch your mouth
bitch...
You're messing with the wrong
dwarf.
[RORY] Well hello there little
fella,
would you mind if I messed with
you?
I'm sure that you're aware
who I am aren't you...
[DWARF] Uh... Emroy's girl...
[RORY] Look at that you got it
on the very first try!
Guess I'll give you a chance to
get out of this alive!
But if you're still interested
in getting messed with then I
will happily oblige!
[DWARF] I'm good! I'm good! I'm
gone!
[RORY] Heh. Typical.
[YOJI] Out on patrol, Rory?
[RORY] There've been
a lot more people
coming in and out of town
lately...
many are idiots like Stumpy
who can't keep their hands
to themselves.
[YOJI] You're doing great.
[RORY] Are you going in to eat?
[YOJI] I was actually about to
meet someone for a drink.
[DORA] Here you go!
[YOJI] Huh.. Tuka?
[RORY] Uh... oh...? Tuka!
[RORY] Looking for someone,
dear?
[TUKA] Yeah... kind of...
something like that.
[RORY] Aw do you have a
boyfriend now?
[TUKA] Oh don't be silly, Rory!
[YOJI] Is she really doing this
every day now?
[MARI] Yes.
[MARI] Every day about this
time,
she starts wandering around
looking for her dead father.
[MARI] How long are we going to
let her keep doing this.
(grunt)
[YOJI] We can't stop her.
(exhale)
[RORY] Do you really think
she needs someone
to force her into dealing with
this situation?
[MARI] Well yes of course she
does...
you can't... deal with the
future
if you're always dwelling on the
past.
[MARI] And well if she keeps
this up...
she'll end up losing her grip on
reality right now.
[MARI] No one... should live
like that.
[RORY] Suppose I see where
you're coming from...
(nasal exhale)
[YOJI] Look, Kurokawa...
If we all told her the truth...
that her father is dead and
she's searching in vain.
What good do you think that
would do for her?
(react)
It could very well send her
to a place much darker than
this.
And as her doctor...
you're the one who'd
have to be there for her.
And you just don't
have the time...
won't be long before we're
called back through the Gate.
[YOJI] All of us will be gone..
and Tuka will be left here to
deal with it all by herself.
[MARI] OK, so you favor doing
nothing?
[YOJI] I do... if we
can't care for that girl
until the very end...
then let her be.
[MARI] Very well, sir.
I need to get ready for
tomorrow. G'night.
[KUWABARA] I'll walk her back to
the barracks.
(nasal exhale)
[RORY] Less sulking, more
drinking... okay, sweetie?
[RORY] Aah... Nine hundred and
sixty years of this...
[YOJI] Huh?
[RORY] It's been a long time,
but it's gone by so quickly.
I've met so many people along
the way.
So many joyful greetings,
and so many bittersweet
farewells.
[RORY] Eventually I guess I've
grown less attached.
[YOJI] Well yeah, sure.
It's certainly made you a lot
tougher than most.
[RORY] Yes it has... so maybe
you shouldn't be so cold
hearted.
[YOJI] My heart's been asked to
handle more than I'm used to.
It's not big enough to be kind
to everyone.
[RORY] You know nothing.
[RORY] That is your problem...
your heart should only be opened
to one single person.
[RORY] You'll fare better with
the girls if you do.
[YOJI] You don't, say?
[RORY] Look I've been a girl
for 960 years okay?
And every girl wants to be the
only one.
[YOJI] Heh...
You may be tough but you
can be quite the softie.
[YOJI] That's gotta be the
nicest thing I've ever heard
from someone called "The
Reaper."
[RORY] Ruling over death
is the same as ruling over life.
Death, after all,
is the end of life.
And in order for you
to die with grace,
Your life must have been lived
with respect and honor.
[YOJI] So respect for life is
the key to death... Huh.
[RORY] Right.
[RORY] Dora! Another one,
please!
[DORA] Coming up!
[YOJI] You might wanna
slow down...
you're gonna wind up drunk.
[RORY] Too late for thaat!
Will you take care of me baby?
[YOJI] Take it easy... people
are looking at us!
[RORY] Oh come on Itami, you
think I care about them?
(exhales nervously)
[YAO] What kind of place is
this?!
(surprised)
[YAO] What do you think you're
doing, serving alcohol to a
child!
(snoozy sounds)
[YOJI] Hey, wake up, Rory.
They need to close up.
[RORY] Mm... I can't drink any
more.
[YOJI] Yeah. Well you shouldn't
anyway.
(grunt/lift)
(happy)
[RORY] Ah! Could you be gentler
with me, please?
[YOJI] Goodnight, Rory...
[RORY] Wait.
[YOJI] Whut...wahhhh!
(grunt/exhale)
[RORY] I need you to stay with
me. Please, Itami?
[YOJI] I guess for a bit.
(annoyed)
[RORY] Okay... Who are you...!
You think you can
just waltz in here
and ruin the spectacular plans
I had for this evening, huh!
[YOJI] Uh what plans're you
talking about, Rory?
OW!
[YOJI] Whahhhhh!!! Wh‐What was
that for?!
[RORY] You stay out of this.
[YAO] My name is Yao Haa Dushi.
[RORY] Hmph! Yes, and you're a
dark elf...
And I'm betting you're around
three hundred years old, yes?
[WOLFBOY] Oh dear god a dark elf
and Emroy's apostle are gonna go
nose‐to‐nose.
[SCARFACE] It's gonna be a
bloodbath.
[RORY] Alrighty then...
what exactly did you come here
for?
[YAO] Well child... I'm a
daughter of Dehan
in the Dushi Clan living in the
Schwartz Woods.
I have been told that the
"green ones" come to this inn...
and I would like to speak with
them if I could.
[RORY] The green ones?
[YAO] Yes.
But first things first...
Why are you giving this little
girl alcohol?!
Taking advantage of a child
will have severe consequences.
[RORY] Please save me from this
debauchery!
[RORY] That dirty heathen has
been forcing me to drink with
him!
[YOJI] Huhhhhhh?!
[RORY] He's coercing me!
Telling me to drink
or he'll hurt me!!!
[YAO] You miserable son of a
bitch.
[YAO] I will make sure this
hurts!
(fakey cry)
[YOJI] You're messed up Rory!
[YAO] Now don't you worry,
little one. This filthy pig is
going to pay the price.
[YAO] Uh?
[YOJI] Gotta go!
[DELILAH] Hey buddy!
I'm putting this on your tab!
[YAO] Good.
You're safe now child.
The evil's gone... Hmm?
[DELILAH] Your "innocent victim"
took off through the window.
[YAO] Uh...? Whatever for?
Huh... And after I tried
to help her out, too...
Well that was rather rude.
[DELILAH] Yeah, yeah...
you're gonna drink?
[YAO] No, I'm here to find
someone...
[DELILAH] Yeah, well, the green
guys aren't here right now.
[DELILAH] I'm trying to run a
business...
If you're not going to drink,
then you gotta go.
[YAO] All right... I'll have an
ale.
[DWARF] Hey, kid... you said
you were lookin' for the green
people, right?
[YAO] Yes.
[MEIA] Mmwhy is it you're
lookin' for them?
[YAO] There's something I need
them to do for me.
[CUSTOMER] So why do you think
Rory the Reaper was putting on
the little kid act?
[CUSTOMER] Don't know but the
elf had no idea
she had one of people she was
looking for right in front of
her.
[DWARF] Maybe the green people
won't be able to do what you
want 'em to.
[MEIA] He does have a point.
[YAO] Why is that...
I heard that the green ones are
a band of honorable warriors.
[YAO] If that's true, they
wouldn't abandon people
in their time of need would
they?
[YAO] I'm also prepared to pay
for their help.
[CUSTOMER] God! Lookit the size
of that thing!
[CUSTOMER] You could buy
yourself a kingdom
with a diamond like that!
[CUSTOMER] I could work over a
thousand years and never earn
that much!
[CUSTOMER] I'll do whatever you
want miss!
[CUSTOMER] Back off, buddy! This
bounty is mine!
[CUSTOMER] No. I'm doing it!
[CUSTOMER] Forget it, man!
What do you need, my lady!
[YAO] Hmph. Yeah well, I'm
sorry, boys...
but I don't think any of you
have what it takes.
[CUSTOMER] What?
Oh I got what it takes!
[CUSTOMER] How do you know?!
You haven't even told us the
task!
[YAO] I need someone to kill a
flame dragon.
[CUSTOMER] A
...flame...dragon...
[YAO] That's right. It's already
injured.
Who here is willing?
[YAO] If you find this reward
insufficient...
[YAO] I shall include myself as
part of the payment.
[ALL] There's no way I'm getting
involved in that.
Are you gonna try it?
[CUSTOMER] A flame dragon...?
Hell. No...
[ALL] Yeah, best of luck to ya,
little lady!
Heh...No kidding. I'm not
getting myself killed.
[CUSTOMER] Hope you find those
green fellas,
they're the only ones nuts
enough for that!
[YAO] I must've missed them.
[DELILAH] Call it a night, okay.
[YAO] Guess I will.
[DELILAH] You got a place to
stay for the night?
[YAO] Won't be a problem...
[YAO] The spirits of the wind
sing their songs out here.
[YAO] And the water and the air
are especially calm and pure...
as is the land healthy, green
and lush.
[YAO] This is a good place.
[YAO] Just a little longer...
[YAO] Everyone... please hold on
a little longer.
(growls)
(fearful, screams)
(roars)
(jet engine roar)
[KAMIKODA] How about this?!
You think you can catch me,
Nishimoto?!
[KURIHAMA] He got behind us!
Break to the right!
[KAMIKODA] Shit!
[KAMIKODA] There! I got your ass
now!
[NISHIMOTO] I don't think so,
rookie!
[YAO] Yes, there they are...
I've found the green ones!
[YAO] At long last...
we will finally receive the help
we need.
[YOJI] Textiles... dishes and
pots and pans
and all sorts of kitchen stuff.
[YOJI] Oh wow. You even got sake
in here.
[YANAGIDA] I'm pretty sure no
one will mind
if you went ahead and took one.
[TODO] Um I think I'll mind.
All the stuff in these
containers are like
ammunition and weapons for us
diplomats, okay?
[YANAGIDA] Oh are you trying to
tell me
you've never once skimmed a
bottle or two for yourself?
[TODO] I'd never do such a
thing.
[YANAGIDA] Ah, and this funds
the operation.
[TODO] Yeah. We managed to
collect
some local currency from the
Alnus co‐op.
[TODO] From some grocery sales.
And now we'll be able to
put it to good use.
[YANAGIDA] Should be highly
effective
in stabilizing and growing a
developing country.
[TODO] Yeah, something like
that.
Depends on the country,
right...?
This definitely beats
strong‐arm tactics.
[YANAGIDA] Yeah whatever you
say...
they already saw what happened
the last time they threatened
us.
[TODO] And that is why you are
never gonna be an ambassador.
We don't need to create
any more unnecessary trouble
[TODO] For now, I'll just focus
on getting
more peace‐minded people to the
table.
[YANAGIDA] Itami. Make sure it
all gets through.
[YOJI] Yeah! We got this, okay?
[YOJI] Right!
The capitol's next, so strap in!
[YAO] A little more faith,
everyone!
[YAO] Soon... I will bring the
green ones,
and our salvation, back home!
[LELEI] Next time on "GATE:"
Itami Might...