[LELEI] The Self Defense Force
was sent to the Special
Region...
[LELEI] ...where they created
shelter for refugees from the
Coda Village.
[LELEI] In order to support
themselves,
the refugees decide to sell the
valuable scales of wyverns
slaughtered at the Battle of
Alnus.
They set off to Italica,
along with the 3rd
Reconnaissance Unit
led by Lieutenant Yoji Itami.
[KUWABARA] We're on Thessalia
Way right now.
[KUWABARA] And so I'm guessing
this over here must be Italica.
[KUWABARA] You're wondering
what this is, right?
[LELEI] Mm‐hmm!
[KUWABARA] It's a compass...
[KURATA] They used to call him
drill‐sergeant‐from‐hell.
Now he's going all grandpa over
a cute little witch with silver
hair.
[RORY] Interested huh?
[RORY] That's the kind of girl
you like, isn't it?
[YOJI] What are they doing back
there?
[KURATA] Sir.
[YOJI] What's going on?
[KURATA] We've got a plume of
smoke on our two, Lieutenant.
[YOJI] OK... does the road take
us anywhere near
where the smoke's coming from?
[KURATA] Yes it does...
we're gonna go right through it
if the map's correct.
[YOJI] Alright so this
is the second time
we're running into
a column of smoke.
[KUWABARA] That should be
Italica.
[YOJI] Heads up everybody
let's be sure to keep our eyes
open.
[LELEI] Smoke's black... must be
trouble.
[YOJI] D'you know what it's
from?
[LELEI] Looks like it's...
man... made...
It's a...? It's a flower.
[KURATA] A flower?
[YOJI] I think she means
"fire..."
"Fi‐re."
[LELEI] Fi‐re...
[YOJI] Let's all stay awake out
there people and keep moving...
And remember... watch the sky as
well as the ground.
[SHINO] Three‐two, wilco.
[YOJI] What's your deal?
[RORY] There's blood in the
air...
[PINA] Their middle's weak!
Break it, now!
[BANDITBOSS] Son of a bitch...!
Re‐treat!
[PINA] Norma! Hamilton!
Are you alright?!
[HAMILTON] Alive and
accounted for, ma'am!
[NORMA] Uh‐huh...
[GREY] Hey well what about me?
You didn't even bother to ask
whether I was injured or not.
Hurts my feelings.
[PINA] After all these years
I know you better than that
Grey.
[HAMILTON] Your Majesty...
why did we come
all the way out here
to fight a bunch of crazed
blood‐thirsty bandits?
[PINA] We didn't have a choice!
They raised the alarm...
letting everyone know
they had armed forces trying to
storm the walls!
I thought it was the army from
the other world!
[PINA] We did what we were
supposed to:
rush to their defense!
And what did we find?
Soldiers from the other
kingdoms turned rogue!
[PINA] Listen to me! You don't
have time to lie about!
The bandits will be coming back!
It's time to bury the bodies...
and reinforce all the gates!
[PINA] The rest of my people are
coming!
But they're still three days
away.
If you can hold out that long,
the Order of The Rose
will avenge your fallen in
battle!
[PINA] Three days!
[BARTHOLOMEW] Your Highness...
With all due respect...
[PINA] What is it?
You want to surrender?
[BARTHOLOMEW] 'Course not.
Still... I'm hoping there's
a way to settle this without
bloodshed.
[PINA] There certainly is...
open the gates and let them in.
[PINA] And after that... prepare
to give them everything.
[PINA] Let your men be shackled.
Let your women get raped.
[PINA] Leave all the decisions
to them
and allow them to do as they
please.
Just let them ravage and enslave
everyone...
It'll be the first step toward a
beautiful relationship.
[BARTHOLOMEW] You speak
facetiously.
[PINA] Of course I am, I'm
trying to illustrate a point.
[PINA] I know it's not an easy
thing to think about...
But pretending it's not as bad
as it really is...
will not help you...
you will lose everything.
[KAINE] I hope you enjoy.
[PINA] Hmm. It lacks in flavor
and sufficiency.
[KAINE] When one is physically
spent...
eating extremely rich foods
can actually shut the body down.
[PINA] Oh really?
You've dealt with a situation
like this before?
[KAINE] Of course. I am a native
of the city of Rosa.
Which is now a loyal part of the
Empire.
[PINA] Very well.
I shall be resting in
your guest room.
[PINA] Bring me any urgent
messages right away.
[KAINE] As you wish, Your
Majesty.
[PINA] Oh and uh... what will
you do
if I don't wake immediately?
[KAINE] I have a nice cold
pitcher of water
to pour on you if it comes to
that.
[PINA] Fine, that should work.
[PINA] There aren't many true
soldiers here.
The bravest militiamen are
always among the first to die.
Morale is getting low.
[PINA] My first battle should
have been glorious...
[PINA] But this... this is
pathetic.
[YOUNGPINA] Listen!
Today... all of you are members
of the order!
Knighthood is a privilege!
Nothing less than an honor!
Live up to your title with your
heart and soul!
[GIRLS] Yes ma'am!
I'd like to introduce the man
behind our training.
He is Master Grey Co Aldo.
[YOUNGPINA] Well, sir...?
What should be our first course?
[GREY] Now let me see... I'd say
we begin with
the basics, which would be the
march.
[YOUNGPINA] Left and right and
left and right and left
and left and right and left and
right and left and right
[YOUNGHAMILTON] Oh. Oh?
[YOUNGPINA] Hamilton! If you
can't march,
then maybe you need to find
something else to do!
[YOUNGHAMILTON] Let me try
again!
[YOUNGPINA] Yeah, yeah. Fall
in.
[YOUNGHAMILTON] Yes, ma'am.
[YOUNGPINA] Good grief.
[GREY] It's only her first day,
Highness.
[GREY] So tell me something...
Are you truly serious about
making this an order of
knighthood?
[YOUNGPINA] Of course, I am.
Now I'm aware something like
working with me
must be beneath you and all.
[YOUNGPINA] I know my father
ordered you,
I'm sure you have better things
to do
than babysit the concubine's
princess.
[GREY] A concubine huh...?
Well... My birth wasn't
glamorous either...
if you don't mind my saying so
Princess.
Perhaps you and I have more in
common than you think.
I guess it's good to have
company.
[YOUNGPINA] Master Grey...
Hmm! All right then.
Wear us out!
[YOUNGPINA] Train us like you
wanna kill us!
[MOLTO] In the name of Emperor
Molto Sol Augustus ...
The Order of the Rose is hereby
called into duty.
[PINA] Damn it!
Honor guard, honor guard.
Time and time again, that's all
we ever do!
[PINA] Goddamn him...
we have to be more than just
ornamentation for his parades!
[GREY] Patience Your Majesty.
Someday... we'll need to be
ready
when your father calls upon the
Order.
[MOLTO] Why don't we try this?
Take all of your knights
from the Order of The Rose and
go scout the situation for us.
[PINA] But... Your Majesty?
Scout the battlefield for you?
[MOLTO] And why not?
You've been longing to prove
that your knights
are doing more than just
marching and color guard.
So... here's your chance.
[PINA] Consider the mission
done... Your Majesty.
[PINA] My Order of The Rose
is finally sent to the
battlefield. And yet...
[PINA] The enemy?!
They're here?!
[GREY] We're not entirely sure
of what's going on out there.
[GREY] You might want to take a
look.
[PINA] What the hell's that?
[HAMILTON] Whoa... What's that
carriage armored with?
[PINA] Is that...... made of
iron?
[NORMA] Identify yourselves!
If you're not our enemy come
into the open now!
[PINA] That staff of hers...
only a Lyndon Wizard can wield
one.
[PINA] And an elf...?
If they know how to combine
their powers
it could end up being a serious
problem.
[PINA] Rory Mercury's with
them?!
[HAMILTON] Ehhh?!?
[GREY] Rory the Reaper.
That's definitely not good.
[PINA] I... I saw her performing
her rituals a few weeks ago.
[GREY] Why would an apostle of
Emroy
choose to join a band of
brigands?
[PINA] Well. It wouldn't really
surprise me much.
[GREY] What?
[PINA] The Gods' decisions
seem to be acts of whimsy
sometimes.
[GREY] I wouldn't say that
around the Oracle
if I were you, Princess.
[PINA] Perhaps. But even the
Gods can be damn fools.
[GREY] (groan) Oh holy hell
I did not just hear that!
[HAMILTON] So what're we going
to do? They're on their way.
[PINA] If these bandits already
have Rory the Reaper on their
side...
then we need to consider the
city already lost.
[HAMILTON] That's true...
[PINA] That being said...
we still don't know if they're
truly our enemy.
[PINA] What do we do?!
[PINA] Okay... if this group is
not our adversaries...
[PINA] ...we certainly want them
to join us!
[GREY]
[PINA] Welcome to Italica,
friends!
[PINA] Ah, ah...!
Oh did I... that was me huh?
[GIRLS] Uh‐huh.
[KUWABARA] Lieutenant.
You there? Lieutenant!
Lieutenant! Come in!
[TUKA] What is wrong with you?
What kind of a person just
shoves a door open without even
looking?!
[PINA] Eh?! Uhhhh...
[TUKA] Even dwarves and pixies
are more careful!
[TUKA] What are you? Some kind
of goblin?
[RORY] Hello there... you're not
dead yet, are you?
[YOJI] OK, then... I guess they
decided to let us in.
[KUWABARA] 3‐1, Chief!
Are you there?! Come back.
[YOJI] Uhh... 3‐1.
[KUWABARA]  Glad you
finally woke up...
I almost decided to move in.
[YOJI] Yeah... gimme a minute
before you do anything crazy.
I need to look around.
[KUWABARA] You got it.
[YOJI] So uh... Which one of you
fine folks is in charge here,
anyway?
[PINA] Wha...?! Wait what...!?
[HAMILTON] Everyone! You are in
the presence of Her Majesty...
the Third Princess Pina
CoLada...
Show some respect!
[YOJI] Huh?
[LELEI] The Princess?
[YOJI] Pina Co Lada?
[PINA] This is the fortified
city of Italica,
where the Thessalia and Ahppian
Ways come together.
[PINA] Which makes it extremely
vital for trade.
[PINA] This city and the
surrounding area was governed
by the family of Count Folmar
for generations.
However, the Count took ill
recently and passed away,
leaving a political power
struggle between his daughters.
[PINA] The two oldest were
married into other families,
but there was still a custody
battle.
They had a third sister Myui.
She happens to be the only
legitimate successor of the
Folmar family throne.
[YOJI] I guess that kinda thing
happens here in your world too
then, huh.
[LELEI] Itami... wait
did you just understand what she
said?
[YOJI] Uh yeah a little...
I'm starting to pick up bits
and pieces of your language...
here and there anyway.
[YOJI] Maybe I got special
powers when I hit my head...
[PINA] And then...
the Empire decided to send their
divisions through the Gate.
[PINA] All of our nobles
were ordered to send troops
from their kingdoms to join the
Empire in the fight.
In the end none of them made it
back here.
[PINA] Public order in the city
has deteriorated.
With no soldiers or anyone
skilled
in public service, it's complete
chaos.
[PINA] The Mistress of The
Folmar Fiefdom
is sitting on the other side of
this door.
She is Princess Myui... Folmar's
Countess.
[YOJI] Oh? That kid?
[LELEI] If I remember
correctly...
she'll be eleven this year.
[PINA] She may be the head of
the family...
but she's never been taught
the violent art of leading an
army.
[PINA] So for now...
I'm commanding what's
left of her militia...
until she can.
[YOJI] Okay I understand.
[PINA] Let me get this
straight...
You are offering to help us
defend the city.
[YOJI] Yeah... I don't think any
of the merchants here
are in the mood to buy dragon
scales right now.
[PINA] Very well then...
I'll assign your forces to
occupy and guard the South Gate.
[KUWABARA] Fall out!
[ALL ] Roger!
[HAMILTON] So they're the "men
in green"
we've been hearing about.
The ones who defeated the flame
dragon.
[PINA] Looks like they are.
[HAMILTON] Are you sure it's
safe?
Should we let the rest of them
inside the walls?
[PINA] We're not in a position
to be picky with our allies
right now.
[PINA] If they say they're here
to help
then we must believe them.
[HIGAKI] What are you talking
about!
You've got orders to get back
here, dummy! Right now!
[YOJI] Yeah... but it looks like
we're
getting caught up in a little
squabble, sir.
[HIGAKI] And who the hell
authorized you to do that?!
I need you back here, without
getting shot!
[YOJI] It's funny you should say
that...
So if it isn't too much trouble
I've got a teensy favor to ask,
sir.
[YOJI] See what I see?
[KUWABARA] Yeah. Scouts from the
looks of 'em.
Two battalions behind
'em, too.
Not sure if they're comin' here,
though.
[YOJI] Yeah I doubt they're
bringin' the party to us.
[KUWABARA] Probably not...
600 guys isn't enough to attack
the whole city at once.
And they'll stand out against
that limestone on the northern
cliffs.
I'd say the best concealed
routes...
are gonna be on the way to the
west or the east gates.
[KUWABARA] And of course...
you know where that puts us,
dontcha.
[YOJI] Yeah... just sittin' here
on our butts.
[YOJI] We are playing the decoy.
[YOJI] This gate was already
damaged during their prior
engagement.
So, her assumption is that if
they see
just the twelve of us here,
they'll attack.
And then run into her secondary
line
once they get past us.
[YOJI] That's what her plan is
anyway.
[KUWABARA] Do you really think
that they would go for that,
Lieutenant?
[YOJI] Well this is where
the Princess wants us for now.
So we'll just sit here, twiddle
our thumbs
and see who's dumb enough to
drop by.
Oh, yeah... Tell her we don't
need that bonfire, either.
[TOMITA] Is that the last one?
[MARI/KURATA] Yeah, Top!
[SHINO] Lieutenant. [YOJI] Hm?
[SHINO] Here... it's getting
dark.
[YOJI] Thanks...
You're the best.
Furuta. See what we can
do
about keepin' the bad guys on
the other side.
[FURUTA] You got it, boss.
[RORY] Itami, dear?
[YOJI] Huh?
[RORY] Why are you helping the
princess of an Empire
that attacked your homeland?
[YOJI] To protect the people of
this town Rory.
[RORY] You really meant that.
Wow.
[YOJI] Of course I did. I mean
why wouldn't I?
[YOJI] Dammit! C'mon get on
there!
[RORY] Let me have a look at
it...
I'll keep it steady.
[YOJI] I'd appreciate that.
Do you care about
what's going on?
[RORY] Emroy is a god of battle,
you know?
Where death and destruction
come with the territory.
[RORY] But there is... motive...
It is the most important thing.
[RORY] If your purpose isn't
righteous...
...then deception will sully
your soul.
[YOJI] Well since I wasn't lying
when I said I want to help
I guess there's no problem.
But I do have another reason.
[RORY] Hmm?
[YOJI] I wanna show them
different way...
that we're not this big enemy of
theirs...
I want the Princess to
understand she can talk with us.
[RORY] I like it!
I really really like it!
[RORY] Your fear!
[YOJI] Huh? Fear?
[RORY] I can feel it
coming off of you!
You'll burn into her soul I just
know it!
[RORY] I am wholly looking
forward to helping you
in the upcoming battle, sweetie!
[RORY] It's been so long since I
could let loose...
this should be superb! (giggle)
[YOJI] That's not exactly
what I meant.
[NORMA] Here it comes!
Flame arrows inbound!
[NORMA] Archers! Counter‐volley!
Get a message to the Princess!
We've made contact with the
enemy at the Eastern wall!
[PINA] They're at the East
Gate?!
[RORY] Why way over there?!
[RORY] We were supposed to
fight them right here! (pouty)
[KURATA] I got 0311...
they couldn't have timed it out
any better could they.
[KUWABARA] Those bandits out
there
used to be regular Army...
they still know a thing or two.
[YOJI] Has anybody from the East
Gate asked for us?
[KUWABARA] Nope. Nothing yet.
[YOJI] Oh‐kay...
[NORMA] Pick them off the wall!
Don't let an arrow go to waste!
[NORMA] It's a magic user!
[FARMER] I got this!
[BANDIT] I gotcha!
[BANDIT] Y'like that! The rest
of this should be easy!
[NORMA] Did these fools come
here
just to die in a meaningless
battle?
[PINA] So this is war.
[PINA] I've imagined its reality
so many times ‐
but I had no concept of it's
true horror.
[BANDIT] Get it open!
[PINA] Stay calm...
[NICOLA] You...
You sons of bitches!
[PINA] Someone...! Stop him!
[GUY] Follow Nicola...!
Kill them all!
[GREY] No!
[PINA] It can't be... this has
to stop!
[WOMAN] Where are all the
others?!
[WOMAN] Where are the men in
green?!
[PINA] Even if I were to call
for them they'll never come.
[PINA] I already put them at the
South Gate
as a sacrifice for the rest of
us!
[KUWABARA] Well? Boss?
[YOJI] Yeah, I know. I know.
[YOJI] C'mon Princess...
What're you gonna do?
[LELEI] Next time on "GATE":
Ride of the Battle Goddess.