Lelei:
Yoji Itami. Age 33.
He and all around him agree,
he's a hopeless fanboy.
This is his story:
My hobby is the most important
thing I have in my life.
So know this, if gonna ask me
to make some sorta choice,
the answer is the same.
Itami:
My otaku life always
comes first.
Good to see
you back, sir!
So. Everybody
alright back there?
Yeah!
Itami:
Hey‐hey! Good
to see ya Chief.
Again, we are saved
by the men in green.
We are very grateful.
(laughs)
It's just part of
the job description
Oh!
It's been
a while, sir
I just made contact
with Alnus.
They said they would
be able to accept all
the people you picked
up along the way.
I appreciate the help.
S'not important.
Now, we need to move on
and discuss the purpose
of your visit.
As I'm sure
you're well aware...
we have just conducted a
large‐scale rescue mission.
So it will be
very difficult
to get support for
another mission publicly.
That's not a problem. This is
a personal request of Grey's.
He's Pin's subordinate.
And I've accepted the task, sir.
Looks like you've
already made up your mind
with or without our
help haven't ya.
Come in!
Huh?
Reporting!
Uh...
ah! Uh...
Reporting!
It's good to see
you back... soldier!
What the heck's
going on?!
Aw!
You didn't think
you were going
on this mission
without us did ya?
I'm a little hurt
I didn't get a call
when you were about
to get into a fight. ,/
Remember, I'm always
here to help.
Just let me know
what I can do okay?
We're here to assist
wherever you need us
You know you can
always count on us, sir.
Aw.. you guys're
the best!
Let's do this!
Ah...
Alright. So here's
what we're gonna do.
We need Rory and Lelei
in the Palace.
I will disguise
myself as a footman
and walk them through
the front gate.
Kurata and Kuribayashi follow
Tuka, and infiltrate the rear.
Tuka, I want you to
use your slumber magic.
Tomita, you and the old man
will cover our escape.
No problem, chief
Kurokawa and Yao
will try to find the Emperor.
I'm sure he will need
some medical attention.
Got it, how are we
supposed to get inside?
Heh. You are going to be
hiding inside the wagon
that I will be pulling.
Once inside, we'll
split into groups.
One for the Princess,
and one for the Emperor.
Once they're safe we're
gonna meet with Kurata,
and then we'll all drive
like hell outta there.
And to cover the guards
at the palace exit...
we'll have Tomita
and the old man.
We should probably
take an LAV for this.
Yes, it has an M2.
I can handle the
hand‐to‐hand combat!
Heh. Well, the
main objective will be
to rescue the prisoners, but...
If that dumbass prince
does something stupid again,
have at it.
(growls)
Yes, sir!
But, Sir. Why would
they let you in?
Even with Rory and Lelei
accompanying you.
I'm sure they must be watching
out for the JSDF presence.
Oh they won't...
I won't be going in
as a man in uniform.
Itami:
They won't even see us comin'.
It'll be a walk in the park.
Itami:
(struggling)
(engine revving)
I never said...
that I would push this thing...
all the way by myself!
Man... you guys are worthless!
My grandmother could
push harder than this.
And she's been dead
for thousands of years.
I thought this thing was
supposed to feel lighter
with the
engine running?
Well we can't
move too fast,
or it end up
looking suspicious.
You don't have
to worry about that!
Uh hey there, skinny.
That looks like
a pretty heavy load.
Where you headed?
We have been summoned by the
Prince to the Imperial Palace.
Villager:
So you carrying some
precious cargo or something?
That's gotta be
some rough work.
Itami:
You have no idea...
(giggles)
State your
business.
Guard 1:
The Palace is
under strict guard.
Guard 2:
We cannot allow anyone
through without permission.
I am Lelei la Lalena‐
I'm from the Coda Village.
The Prince has requested
our presence here.
Please tell him
we've arrived.
We've been told he
would like to speak to us
about defeating
the flame dragon.
Oh, so you're
the ones?!
Please... Please
excuse us, my ladies!
Here's our
invitation.
Right!
Guard 1:
Hey, footman!
Don't be an idiot.
You can't leave your wagon
blocking the gate!
Bring it inside!
Yes, sir! But I...
Come on in, please!
Right this way!
Make yourself
at home.
Rory:
Thank you,
darling.
Hey! You guys?!
(groans)
Do I still have to drag this
by myself? Who's plan was this?
Hang in there.
You got this, chief.
Ahh! Ahh!
Ah!
What do you
want from me?
I think you already
know that, Princess.
The Order of the Rose
were only following the orders
given by the
Emperor himself.
So are you saying that allowing
the enemy to get inside
the Imperial Capital
was the Emperor's idea?
Huh?
Helm:
Are you feigning
ignorance?
(hysterical laughter)
What's so funny?
Your knights helped the enemy
infiltrate our lands.
You created the
situation we're in!
If that isn't treason,
then what is?!
Tell me, if they're
not guilty,
then why would they
flee the Capital?!
Helm:
They're running away because
they have something to hide!
(laughs)
Do I really need to
spell it out for you?
It's because they know
that if they stay,
they'll be treated
like this.
If you run away, you're a
traitor.
If you don't, then you're just
a traitor who's up to something.
You're arrogance
won't change anything!
You have given us
up before we've even
gotten started, Princess.
Prince Zorzal.
What do we do with her?
Rory:
They look so peaceful.
Almost... dead.
Lelei:
Every guard in the hallway
should be out for awhile. ,/
This is Itami.
We're inside.
Itami:
How's it going
over there? Over.
This is Kuribayashi.
We have made it into the Palace.
Shino:
Tuka put the guards
to sleep. Over.
(chuckles)
Hello...
Who are you?!
I do apologize for just
showing up like this.
I am a dark elf
from Lordom Valley.
I have a bit of business
with the Emperor.
Hold it, how'd you
get in here?
Don't come any closer
or I will use force, lady.
(chuckles)
Oh... is that so?
Mari:
Freeze.
Ha!
I'm sure you realize what
happens if I pull this trigger.
I guarantee you
it's not pretty.
Drop your weapons
if you want to stay alive.
Very good.
What am I do with you?
I have complete faith that you
would never even think about
abandoning the Empire.
But it is a fact that the Order
of the Rose assisted the enemy.
I know nothing of that!
That's enough. ,/
That's not even what
I care about anymore.
My priorities have
recently changed.
What I want now is
to defeat our enemies!
And be an
all‐powerful ruler!
If they wish to proceed
with the peace talks,
they will have
to come here.
Zorzal:
So don't worry.
Until then, I will
need you alive.
And by the time they arrive
we will have regrouped...
and prepared ourselves
a counterattack for them!
We've been taming a giant ogre
just for the occasion!
They can attack us whenever
they please. Bring it on!
Rory:
Oh really?
Oh!
Rory:
Oh really?
(gasps)
Rory:
(giggles)
Hmm...
(horrified scream)
It's been a long time,
Crown Prince Zorzal.
(gasps)
Itami, you're here!
Princess Pina. We are here
to rescue you.
Oh! Stay Away! ,/
You there! What are
you guards doing?!
Do not let them
come anywhere near me!
Your elite
soldiers outside
decided to take a
little nappy poo.
Right now, the only people who
can protect you are right here.
Rory the Reaper...
is ready to accept whichever
one of you is up for it.
(excited giggles)
Hey.
You have some
wise soldiers.
(growls)
You are going to die!
Ogaaaare! Get in here!
Come and tear
these bastards apart!
(monsterous breathing)
Huh?
Huh?!
Ah!
Zorzal you've lost
your mind!
I no longer
have a choice.
Zorzal:
Kill them!
(thunderous roar)
(roaring continues)
(pained roar)
(excited giggle)
(ecstatic moan)
The bigger the foe
the better it feels!
(angered roar)
(maniacal laughter)
Grr... ah!
(pained roar)
(ecstatic moan)
Mmm...
(pained roar)
(agonized roar)
(giggles)
(agonized roaring continues)
Looks like it's
almost time.
Your Highness,
We'll be leaving now.
Guh!
Um one more thing.
Our objective for today,
involves making sure
you and your men
never go after
Lelei again.
Oh and to rescue
the royal princess.
Come on. Time to go.
Itami, I...
Heh. Remember we're the
self defense force that cares.
The good guys.
Hold it! It's not over
between you and me!
Let's go! Just the two of us,
I'll take you all by myself. ,/
Wha‐
No matter where you are,
you'll always be
within our sights.
You step out of line
and we will drop you.
Itami:
I'll say it again.
You will stop going after Lelei.
And you'll give
us Princess Pina.
Otherwise, next time,
a bullet is going right
through your skull.
Do you understand what
I'm telling you?
Uh...
Alright... let's go.
Hey Chief!
You need a ride?!
Right on time!
Uh Rory... You don't
have to sit on my lap!
Plenty of room
in the back!
Oh. What?
But we'll be picking up some
other people too, right?
I don't like
being crowded.
Oh come on! I see nothing
has changed has it?!
I am not enjoying this!
Now. What's the status
of the others?
Okay so...
Kuribayashi's already
engaged in a firefight.
There aren't really
all that many of them,
but Tuka's magic
won't last much longer.
Kurata:
And as for Kurokawa...
This is Kurokawa.
We have the Emperor with us. ,/
His vitals
are looking good!
Roger that!
(battle cries)
Get out of the way!
Move it you dummies! ,/
Getting hit by a
car really hurts!
Ahhh!
Tuka, Kuribayashi!
Get in the back!
Kurata!
Kurata:
Moving out!
Itami:
Kurokawa. We just collected
Tuka and Kuribayashi.
We're on our way
to get you.
Mari:
Roger that.
When they get here, we'll be
able to move the Emperor.
I understand!
It's my
greatest honor...
to protect Princess Pina
and Emperor Molto.
If necessary,
I will gladly be the bait!
There won't be
any need for that.
You can trust we will
take care of them.
Great! Everyone's here!
Hang on this is
gonna be close!
(nervous groan)
All:
(scream)
(screaming continues)
Kurata:
Aagh! We're not gonna make it!
Ahh!
Grr... what WAS that?!
Gotta clear passage
for you, Chief!
(panicked panting)
Don't shoot on the city streets.
We don't want any of the stray
rounds to hit the civilians!
Tomita:
If we can get through the castle
gate, then we can stop them.
Kuwabara:
Well... then we better make it.
You hear that?!
Yes, sir!
Hooah!
Sweeper:
Don't let them through!
Dammit! They're
moving too fast!
Tomita:
We're at the west gate!
Keep advancing.
Itami:
Copy!
(battle cries)
These guys don't ever give up!
Special Forces:
Ready to fire.
Archer:
Fire!
(soldiers screaming)
(struggling)
That took care of 'em!
Yeah we did it!
I love it when a
plan comes together!
(relieved sigh)
Princess Pina.
Hi, Hamilton.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Your Highness...
If anything awful would have
happened to you,
I would have just died!
I'm sorry if
I frightened you.
Pina:
Oh father...
I appreciate this.
I can't thank you enough
for rescuing the Emperor.
I take it ‐ he was
the top priority.
I guess it's blind luck
you found me as well.
Not at all.
My primary objective
of this mission
was to get you out and
someplace safe, Princess Pina.
After that, if we were able
to find the Emperor,
then we were
to extract him.
Saving the Emperor
was secondary?!
Itami:
Yes. That came as a
direct order from my boss.
That if we're going in
to save the princess,
then we would need to rescue
the Emperor, as well.
What's the
ulterior motive?
We need to be seen
as an alliance.
If you are joined by
the Emperor and the
pro‐peace representatives...
Then we can show that there is
only one traitor within
the Imperial regime.
Your Majesty!
Father!
Are you all right...
Your Highness?
Yes. Despite the
exceedingly bumpy ride.
I do believe that
I'm doing rather well.
I'm glad you're OK.
And the Senate representatives
have all been successfully
evacuated to Italica.
Itami:
At our current speed,
we should get there tomorrow.
On horseback that always
took us several days,
but with this contraption
our world has gotten smaller.
Truly incredible.
Father!
Zorzal is trying to create mass
confusion within the country.
Stop him! Please speak with him
and make him listen to reason.
There's no point in my
going back to the capital.
Your brother won't even
pretend to listen to what
I have to say anymore anyway.
No, I think it's best if we go
along with Japan's plot.
What plot?
Civil war is
now inevitable.
Pina... I'm making you the
Crown Princess of the Empire.
What? You want me?
Yes, my dear.
I want you to be
the voice to establish
a legitimate government,
And to lead the opposition
against your brother.
No, father! I cannot
go against him!
It will be up to you.
The choice will be yours
to do what you think is best.
Molto:
You can seek to
make peace with him,
or you can divide the
Empire in two.
The time is now. You are
the one to decide our future.
Tell me... where are we
planning to go, Your Highness?
To the Northeast for now.
We'll figure out the rest later.
But, sir. If we leave
the Imperial Capital,
We will lose control
of the country.
(growls)
Shut your mouth!
(gunshot)
Oh!
(whimpers)
It's Furuta here.
Prince Zorzal is escaping
with the nobles and the
pro‐war representatives.
He's leaving the capital.
I'm not sure where yet.
Following them will be too risky
so hang tight for now.
I'm going to keep
my distance. Over 'n out.
What she up to?
Thule:
I endured the life
of a prisoner
to take revenge for my
country that they destroyed.
No matter what
the cost may be.
I vowed the Empire be
obliterated.
That was my only wish,
and I have finally achieved it.
But.. why?
Why is it that
I can't stop crying?
Godammitah...
This cannot be
happening to me...
(gunshot)
(cowers)
I swear to you...
I will have my revenge!
Lelei:
Ten days later, a grand
ceremony was held in Italica.
Princess Pina was named
the Crown Princess,
and a new, legitimate
government of the Empire
was officially founded.
My dearest daughter Pina,
From this day forward...,
I do hereby...
entrust the Empire's
government to you.
The realm is yours to rule.
Take good care...
of our country.
Your time is now... Pina.
(fighting tears)
My heart and soul...
are true to the Empire.
And I swear... I will lead
this country to prosperity,
in peace with Japan!
This is so great!
I was hoping
for a happy ending!
Are you actually crying?
Not cool dude!
Huh? Whatever, this is
the greatest day ever!
(sobbing)
Hey, baby...
Are you ok?
Yeah.
Well, what is this?
Oh!
(chuckles)
We've been seeing
each other...
We're kinduv a thing now ‐
Ever since I was sent back
to Japan awhile back.
I couldn't say anything before,
but we're expecting a baby...
And... we've recently gotten to
know each other as well.
We kinda overcame uh...
the language barrier.
You got hurt because of
my personal vendetta.
Yes, I did.
You better take care of me...
until I get better.
I think I can do that.
The love between Sugawara
and I... will last forever!
Yeah, uh... And it will
all be totally legal I swear!
What?! When did
all this happen?!
This is
not fair!
Hey! Why does everybody suddenly
have a sweetheart except me?!
Because you're easily fooled
and a little bit nuts.
That wasn't niiiice...
Oh... Wait!
I just realized the chief
isn't here to celebrate.
Where... is he?
Yeah he's not here.
Uh... No shit.
Okay soo...
You know how he feels
about all his otaku
hobbies and everything?
Well he sorta
had somewhere to be.
Yeaaaahhhh... I'm back, BABY!
It's been too long.
Can't believe it's been a year!
Finally the event
I've been dreaming about!
OHHHH! I love you!
(kisses the cover) ,/
Sorry, Princess Pina!
I just... I just could
nots let an opportunity
like this pass me by!
Event Staff:
The doujinshi exhibition
and sales is cancelled!
Itami:
Hoo‐hoo‐haa‐haah!
I'm finally here!
And if we don't put
an end to it right now...
THEY'LL SHUT DOWN
THE COMIC'S CONVENTION!
Man, I things have been
a little bit crazy lately.
But I'll just leave
that in the past.
Because what's really
important... is the future!
Guh! Ahhh!
That hurt...!
Why are you guys here?!
It's not very fair if you're
the only one having fun, Daddy.
Itami, will you please
take me to the bookstore?
How did you get here?!
We asked the delightfully
mustachioed Hazama for
permission to visit.
But only under the strict
condition, that you would
take care of us.
Uh What?! Why does
he hate me?
Look here. I'm sorry but
I have some important business.
Please, just go
back to Alnus.
(crowd chattering)
Male Bystander 1:
Is that who
I think it is...?!
Male Bystander 2:
Oh my gosh!
Hey Rory!
They're really real!
Hey!
Hey there!
Wow, that's really Rory!
Gotta get her autograph!
(crowd intensifies)
Hey look over here!
Lemmie get a picture!
There are so many
people here!
And the crowd is growing.
Of course it is,
I'm sure we'll get lots of
attention everywhere we go.
Oh God... This is going
from bad to worse...
Hey! You there!
What's going on?!
Wait! This is
just uh... I swear!
Whatever it is, you're gonna
have to come with me!
Huh?
Don't worry, son.
Uh... I'll take
ya someplace safe, 'kay?
Uh yeah, no thanks.
Officer:
Just get in the car.
You're gonna be fine.
Is this Hell...?
When I, feel low!
One place to‐
AAAAAAHHHH!
Eh...?
(panicked whimpers)
Is that you?! What in the
world are you doing in there?
Itami:
(sobbing)
I just... all I wanted to do was
buy some doujinshi comics!
Itami:
(sobbing)
WHY!
Lelei:
This is the story
of two worlds...
mysteriously connected
to one another.
And the path that brought
those two worlds together.
A path that
was to be know as...
All:
The Gate.