[HAKKAI] You were so lively
not that long ago.
All good things must come
to an end, I suppose.
[GOJYO retching]
What's wrong with you two?
You've been puking your
guts out for miles.
[HAKKAI]
Altitude sickness most likely.
It appears we've already
climbed over 11,000 feet
above sea level if
you can believe.
Can you not drive like
a bat outta hell?
Can you not bark orders at me
until regaining your
ability to walk?
[GOKU] I don't get it.
I feel fine.
Alas, some people have
especially weak constitutions.
Lest we forget, Sanzo is
only a human being.
That said--
[tires screeching]
[GOJYO groans]
Jeez, Hakkai!
Spoke too soon.
Seems those of us part demon
have our upper limits as well.
You're kidding me.
Well, well, if it ain't
the Sanzo Genjo Party!
Who'd a' thought these
high-end bounties
from the east would
scuttle their butts
all the way to no-man's land?
Aw, c'mon, seriously?
[GOKU] Why I gotta be
the only one not sick?
Hey, Hakuryu, can you move?
[HAKURYU chirps]
I'm gonna keep these yahoos busy
as long as I can. I need you
to throw it in reverse
and make like you're
leavin' me for dead.
[GOKU yells]
[DEMONS yelling]
[HASSAN]
Look out, kid!
[GOKU gasps]
[DEMONS groaning]
[HASSAN]
You a'right?
Yeah, sure. Thanks.
[HASSAN] You fellas aren't
from around here, are ya?
No, uh, we're travelers.
My buddies are kinda...
[HASSAN] The altitude gets
to everyone at first.
Part of the reason it's so
dangerous 'round here.
Tends to leave folks
vulnerable to attack.
[MAN 7A] Hassan!
Take a look at these robes!
This guy's...
A Sanzo priest?
Oh. Yeah, that's right.
But... He seems sorta young,
don't'cha think?
Could be he's just a beggar
done up in fancy dress.
Get your hands off of me.
We'll lead these guys
to HQ. Watch your backs.
Wait, you sure?
Come with us to the temple.
We've got some medicine
for the altitude sickness.
That'd be nice, but who
are you again?
The Kouten Corps.
We're Sanzo Sharak's
support squad.
Good to meet'cha, gents.
[GOKU]
Whoa. It's like a secret base!
I'm good.
Can you walk on your own?
Huh. That concoction they
gave us worked like a charm.
[GOJYO]
If you don't mind wantin'
to rip your own tongue
out afterwards.
[HASSAN]
Sanzo Sharak.
The pilgrims have been brought.
[gasps] A chick?
What?
[SHARAK laughs]
Pleased to meet you.
Sanzo Sharak, 28th in Arhat.
Yeah, Sanzo Genjo,
31st in China,
at your service.
You've traveled quite a ways.
Allow me to welcome you
and your companions to the West.
I didn't know Sanzo
priests could be--
Shush.
They certainly came out
with their guns drawn.
Was that a dad joke?
[SHARAK] I've locked in on
the dark aura's source.
It's what we expected.
[SANZO] The Gyumaou Resurrection
Experiment, right?
[SHARAK]
Right.
You'd think as the
highest-ranking
priest in the West I'd be in
a position to do something.
March into Houtou Castle
and shut it down.
But lo and behold,
the Sanbutsushin say no.
Apparently, it's important
to sit on my ass here,
protecting locals from demons.
Was this region hit hard?
Ha. You even have to ask?
Couple of nights after
the initial incident,
demons went to town, literally.
The devastation was immense.
Smaller settlements got lucky,
but all the larger ones
were totally decimated.
There's a hot zone
to the west of us.
One of the highest
concentrations
of demons in the region.
Villagers unfortunate
enough to call it home
live in abject terror.
Hardly ever venture
more than few feet
from their doorstep.
It's our job to protect them.
We patrol regularly to make
our presence known,
trying to maintain some
aspect of law and order.
At the end of the day,
the Kouten Scripture
I'm sworn to defend
till my dying breath
is what governs our resistance.
[HASSAN] Chang'an, huh?
Must've been a rough journey.
I'm more n' little impressed
you're still alive.
No disrespect.
Do you mind if I enquire
to the frequency
with which this temple
is set upon by demons?
[HASSAN]
Oh, uh, actually,
the building is protected
by an invisible barrier
generated from
the Kouten Scripture.
Demons can't get in.
Shields nearby towns, too.
You're telling me
Sanzo Sharak can project
a force field that big
all by her lonesome?
That's impressive.
[HASSAN] Well, to be fair,
she uses mediums, too.
Wait, what's that mean?
[HASSAN]
Think radio waves.
The altar fittings scattered
across the region
act as receivers.
See, the bell in our
shrine emits holy power,
artifacts in other shrines
boost the signal.
The relay's strong enough
that demons can't get through.
Our temple's safe, the
surrounding villages are safe.
You get the idea.
Yes, indeed. So I presume
that's why Sanzo Sharak
isn't permitted
to leave the area?
There are five
Founding Scriptures
of Heaven and Earth.
My predecessor carried two.
Maten and Seiten were entrusted
to Sanzo Koumyou.
There ought to have been four
of our kind in this generation.
One of them was
killed by a demon,
eaten while trekking
through the desert.
Sadly, he carried
the Uten Scripture,
now in possession of
Gyumaou's followers.
Word has the Seiten
Scripture that was stolen
shortly after Sanzo Koumyou died
has also fallen
into their hands.
By my reckoning, I believe
there are three of us
left alive to carry the
remaining scriptures,
are there not?
One of them has had
a change of heart.
The Muten Scripture was
bequeathed to one Sanzo Ukoku,
who, well, who now resides in
Houtou Castle of all places.
He's a bio technician on
the Resurrection Project.
What? No.
[SANZO] His true motives
for aiding the demons
is as yet unknown, but one
thing is beyond a doubt...
[SANZO]
He's no longer one of us.
What I'm hearing is
that there are only
two scriptures the enemy
doesn't have in their grip.
The Maten Scripture
currently in my possession,
and the Kouten
Scripture in yours.
Seems we're the last holdouts.
Huh. Sobering thought.
Damn it.
The five scriptures together are
said to have immense power.
Enough to create new worlds.
Makes sense.
So, the only reason demons
consistently attempt
to infiltrate the temple is
to grab the Kouten Scripture
and dissolve the
barrier protecting us
and the surrounding villages
from their attack. Great.
[SANZO] Three scriptures
are more than enough
to do some damage.
As long as Ukoku
is on their side,
harnessing that power
won't be an issue.
Whatever made him feel
the need to join them,
we won't shame our title.
We'll keep what's left
out of their reach.
Roughly two years ago,
the Sanbutsushin told me
they'd ordered the heir
of the Maten Scripture
to travel West
and subdue Gyumaou
once and for all.
He was a monk ten years
my junior, they said.
The youngest to ever
hold the title,
let alone the Seiten Scripture.
So, now it's been made
off with by demons, is it?
I was half expecting you
to bite it on the way here.
Congratulations.
You and you buddies have
been on one hell of a trip.
Job well done.
[SANZO]
Hmph.
We're just getting
to the good part.
[gasps] Oh, no.
He's been in there a long time.
Well, I'm certain they have
much to discuss.
It isn't every day that
such high-ranking priests
get a chance to talk shop
with one of their own.
True that.
Not to mention it's been forever
since Genjo's been alone
with the fairer sex.
[GOKU]
Can I just go and check on him?
[HAKKAI]
Don't you dare.
I'll have you know
that Sanzo Sharak
has transcended
gender in service
to a profoundly higher calling.
[GOJYO]
Whatever, dude.
Don't stand there all stoic
and try to act like
those rough-edged girls don't
make you tape it down,
if you know what I mean.
No. Uh, well, sometimes.
--[smack]
--[BOTH yelp]
In case you were wondering,
we can hear every word.
What possessed you
to agree with him?
Oh, good. So you're
little chat is at an end.
[GOJYO grunts] What is it about
priests that make 'em think
they're above romanc--? [groans]
I have to admit, Genjo,
your followers are a rather
amusing bunch.
[SANZO] Feel free to
take 'em off my hands.
Amusing is about all
they're good at.
Help you?
Nah. I'm good. Just glad we
made it all the way here.
What?
So, I'm assuming you've
got some sort of plan.
Whatever you fine gentlemen
might need in terms of food
or weaponry, we're more
than happy to supply.
Some modest provisions
and an updated map
of the area would be nice.
Hassan.
We do have a fairly
recent map lying around,
I just wouldn't swear
to it accuracy.
The incident did a real number
on the local geography.
We haven't strayed
far enough West
to make revisions since then.
That will have to do,
though I wonder if we could
impose on you for an evening's
lodging as well?
I'd just as soon let you
rest here for three nights.
Oh, yeah. We'll throw
in some more
altitude sickness
medicine for ya, too.
I'm not chokin' down
another dose of that crap.
Is it that bad?
Uh. No. Wanna try some?
See the look on Hakkai's face
after he takes a sip?
He loves it.
Um. Yeah. I'm good.
Thank you, we'd be
ever so grateful.
Wouldn't want another
bout of altitude sickness
to make us all sitting ducks,
would we now?
Sanzo Sharak!
There's black smoke
rising from Osk village,
just south-southeast from here!
A fire no doubt.
Yes, but there's something
very suspicious
about it, Your Holiness!
We think demons may have set
the blaze from outside!
Yo. Guys. Outta the way.
Would one of you be so kind
as to show us there?
Sure. Just follow our lead.
Sharak, wha...?
[SHARAK]
Gun it.
Looks like you're ridin'
in the back this time.
[GOJYO laughs]
Welcome to the club, jackass.
I wish I could guarantee
your safety,
but the road does
look rather rough.
Huh. Guarantees aren't my thing.
Neither is playing it safe.
[HAKKAI]
Good to know.
You have got be kidding me.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go!
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasping]
[laughs] The nerve of these
imbeciles to put up a barrier!
Maybe barbequing
'em alive'll will teach
their neighbors a
valuable lesson in--
[yelping]
[gasps]
[DEMONS scream]
You have no idea
what you're in for.
Waltz into my territory,
will ya? I don't think so!
[HAKKAI]
I hear a power ballade.
Anyone else hear power ballade?
Uh! No one said anything about
Sharak herself showing up!
W-Wait a second.
Isn't he that outlaw
from the East?
Sanzo Genjo!
Wow. Didn't know you
were such a celebrity.
Good for you.
[SANZO]
Not all it's cracked up to be.
Don't be jealous, sweetheart!
You're as popular as he is!
Two Sanzo priests equal two
scriptures, which means
we get a sizeable bounty,
and you get to be dead!
[SHARAK]
Yeah?
Should'a cashed in on that
one-way ticket to hell!
[DEMONS groaning]
[GOKU yells]
Word of advice:
never turn your backs
on the supporting cast.
We're important, too.
[DEMON 7M groans]
--[HAKKAI grunts]
--[DEMONS groan]
Hey, Sharak,
whaddya say we use this
opportunity to save
the villagers trapped
inside, yeah?
[SHARAK]
Cover me.
Damn it!
Oh, I get it. She's more
important than me, huh?
Way to stroke my ego, pal.
[GIRL 7A cries]
Are you hurt?
[MAN 7F]
Sanzo Sharak!
[MAN 7G]
Thank heavens! We're saved!
[SHARAK]
All of you, evacuate! Now!
The demons are
being taken care of.
Anyone able-bodied enough to
help the infirm, get on it!
[GIRL 7A gasps]
Don't cry. Focus on making
it out of here alive.
[MAN 7F]
Your Holiness!
There are too many
wounded for us to move!
Has my squadron not
arrived here yet?
Is there anyone else that
can't make a run for it
on their own?
[MAN 7G] Uh, there's
another one over here!
[GOKU]
Got 'em!
[SHARAK]
Let's go! Everybody, follow me!
Hold the children close,
keep 'em covered!
[MAN 7F]
Uh. Okay!
[DEMON 7R groans]
[gunshot]
Looks like the villagers
are already headed this way.
[GOJYO]
Can we be done, please?
Hey, what're we waitin' for,
Sanzo? Clean house!
Don't talk to me
like I'm your maid.
[TOWNSPEOPLE scream]
[SHARAK, SANZO]
Om! Manihatsumeiun.
Makai Tenjo!
Ra sati unu is!
[DEMONS gasping]
[MAN 7H] The villagers
whose homes were lost
have been moved out
of harm's way.
The fire's been successfully
extinguished.
The rebuilding effort will start
first thing in the morning.
[SHARAK]
Thank you. Well done.
Ugh. I tell you to rest
then turn right around
and put you to work.
Eh. We're all in the same boat.
No rest for the wicked,
am I right?
[SHARAK]
Yeah.
Here I am, able to
single-handedly carve a chunk
out of the demon hoards,
and I'm forced to stay put.
Something tells me they're
finally catching on.
You could've put a stop to
this mess all on your own.
But channeling
your strength 24/7
to boost the Scripture's power?
Must be exhausting.
[SHARAK] You don't know the half
of it.
Ideally, I'd like to spread
enough receivers
to extend the barrier throughout
the entire region.
Trouble is...
[HAKKAI]
I see your problem.
By doing so, you'd potentially
feed into the idea
that demons don't exist.
[SHARAK] If we were talking
natural selection,
that'd be one thing. But the
"mess" we're in is man-made.
The wholesale elimination
of one side
would have consequences
impossible to foresee.
Count on it.
Well, that's a relief.
The last high-ranking priest
is actually a decent person.
Don't'cha think, Sanzo?
There a reason you're aiming
that question at me?
Is anybody else, like, confused
that we have two "Sanzos" now?
I mean, is it like
a job title or what?
I'll admit it's a trifle odd.
We might as well have
been referring to you
as "general manager"
this whole time.
If we're going that route,
call me CEO.
Long as you don't expect
us to use "Genjo."
Way too awkward.
What about "Joe?"
[GOKU laughs]
Lame!
[HAKKAI]
I have to agree.
Why not something fun like
"Chief," or "Hoss"?
[SANZO] Here's a better idea:
"Idiot's Bane."
[laughs] Oh, my. Say what
you will, Genjo sweetheart,
your friends are nothing
if not entertaining.
Please don't encourage them.
'Scuse the interruption,
friends.
We're handing out rice
to the refugees
if you'd like to help us.
Hey, there's a decent square
meal in it for ya.
Ooh! Count me in!
If there's any way we
can be of assistance,
consider us on the task.
[HASSAN]
Appreciate it.
Tell you what: when we're done,
let's grab a drink.
I got the good stuff.
Hey, Sharak.
Mind if I have a word?
[GOKU]
Do you guys have soda?!
[HAKKAI] Much obliged.
One gets so tired of butter tea.
[HASSAN] So, uh, what were
you and that Genjo fella
talkin' about earlier?
Work, for the most part.
I'm not sure whether
you realize this or not,
but combing two or more
scriptures in unison
is capable of forging entirely
new fighting techniques.
I knew that.
Never seen it done
before, though.
[SHARAK]
That makes both of us.
Why do you suppose Sanzo
priests are so spread out?
Our masters like to keep
things predictable.
Today, Genjo and I
accidentally evoked
our powers at the same time.
We were standing at
a safe distance.
So, you felt the same thing?
I did. Strong, but subtle.
Like the scriptures
were resonating.
[SANZO]
The Maten and Kouten in tune.
Imagine if we were
standing closer.
What sort of new power would
their intertwining give rise to?
The Founding Scriptures
of Heaven and Earth.
Not everything they can
do is necessarily good.
Meaning we ought to
follow the time-tested
wisdom of tradition and
keep the pieces separated.
Better safe than sorry.
Still, though, aren't you a
little curious? I mean, c'mon.
[SANZO]
Hm?
Nothing.
[SANZO]
No. You said what I'm thinking.
[SHARAK] You and the men'll
start rebuilding
tomorrow morning, yeah?
If you need more resources
or manpower,
I can probably convince
our guests--
[SHARAK]
Don't.
We're perfect for each other.
[HASSAN groans]
How many times do I have
to drill it into you skull
not to look at me
like a woman?
Aw, c'mon! Why you always
gotta be that way?!
I don't care if you're a
high-ranking priest or demon,
how if feel is how I feel!
[SHARAK]
How you feel is absurd.
[sighs]
[GOKU] You're really
into Sharak, aren't ya?
[gasps]
My bad. I got lost on
the way to the bathroom
and heard voices coming from
in here, so, I thought, yeah.
[sighs] No, it's fine.
And, the bathroom's
just down the hall.
[GOKU]
Hey.
If you're worried about Sanzo
and Sharak becoming a thing,
I don't think it's like that.
[HASSAN] Mm? Wha--
What're you talkin' about, kid?
[GOKU]
I've known him for a while.
Since before we set
out on this journey.
Here's the deal:
we're definitely his friends
and everything,
it's just he's a priest.
Noble calling, sure. But lonely.
'S gotta be.
I'm sure Sharak could
tell you all about it.
Sanzo's special.
There aren't a lot of
people who can relate
to what he's been through.
The chance to meet
someone who knows
where he's coming from,
someone who'll let him unload
all the stuff he keeps
bottled up. That's rare.
Guess what I'm sayin' is that he
only sees Sharak as a friend.
Well there's no denyin' he's a
lucky man to have you as one.
[gasps]
[HASSAN] Me an' Sharak met way
back in her training days.
I've been head-over-heels since.
[HASSAN]
'Course she's out of my league.
I told myself I'd make do
keeping her safe,
just to stay close.
You see how that works.
I can't keep it together when
she talks to another man.
Forget about one she can
genuinely relate to.
I'm an idiot...
[GOJYO]
What's takin' him so long?
I need to piss so bad
my teeth are floatin'.
Well, given how difficult
this building is to navigate
he may very well
have gotten lost.
[GOJYO]
Ugh. I'll go look for him.
[gasping]
[HAKKAI]
Are you okay?
[GOJYO]
No, yeah. Heh.
Just been a while since
I've indulged. Heh...
Your neck!
[grunts] Yeah, what about it?
Oh. Never mind.
Thought I saw something.
[HAKKAI]
Where did that come from...?
Forgive me for what
I'm about to do.
I'm sorry! There was
no other choice!
[bell tolls]
[SHARAK gasps]
[SANZO]
Hm?
What the...?
Somethin' wrong?
[SHARAK] Impossible.
The Kouten Barrier.
It's been broken!
So it begins.
[SHARAK] Episode eight:
"Barrier." Don't miss it.
[GROUP]
Ura Sai.
[ALL eating]
[GOJYO, SANZO, HAKKAI groan]
[GOJYO]
Why do I keep eating?!
[GOKU groans]
[SANZO, GOJYO]
Delayed reaction!
[HAKKAI]
Off we go!