[MAN 6A gasps]
What just happened?
[MAN 6B]
The child decimated them!
[MAN 6C]
Impossible! It can't be!
Don't hesitate, you idiots!
Strike! He must be
brought to heel at once,
else he bring misfortune
to all of Heaven!
Seize him!
Seize him immediately!
[MAN 6A]
Yes, sir!
You're coming with us--!
[MEN groan]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[KONZEN]
No... Goku.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
Wh-What the hell's
going on here?
What do we do?
The diadem. It was some
kind of power limiter.
Without it, there's nothing
keeping him in check.
[KENREN]
In check?
You're telling me this
is Goku's true form?
[KONZEN gasping]
Demon. God. Say what you will.
He's, not even a human being.
[TENPOU] Look there, on his
torso, the symbol of chaos.
Legend has it the bearer
possesses strength
equal to heaven.
Goku is the Seiten Taisei.
[SOLDIERS whimpering]
Don't back down from him!
Protect me, you cowards!
[LI TOUTEN screams]
No. No, please!
Stay away from me!
I beg of you!
I've had enough of this shit!
Get a hold of yourself!
Nobody wanted this!
Least of all from you!
You need to blow off
some steam, monkey boy?
Come on. I can handle it. Heh.
[GOKU growls]
[ALL gasping]
[KANZEON] Quite the party
going on in here.
[KONZEN]
Kanzeon Bosatsu.
Good effort, but in case
it's not evident,
the shrimp's out of your league.
What can we do?
His power limiter must be
restored, the question is how?
[KANZEON laughs]
Restored?
Huh, I rather thought we'd
just annihilate him.
Go on, shrimp. Let's see
what you're made of.
[GOKU yells]
No! Don't!
[yelling]
Lively one, aren't we?
[KANZEON]
Forgive me.
[KONZEN grunts]
[panting]
[KANZEON chuckles]
[KONZEN groans]
[KANZEON chuckles] You must've
dug deep for that one.
Clearly, I underestimated
the size of your balls.
So, that's how it is?
[KANZEON] How long before
the little monkey
stops likening you to the sun?
[GOKU]
Wow! Your hair is so shiny!
[KONZEN] It's the only
part of me that is.
Sorry.
[KONZEN] You're more like
the sun than I am.
Yeah. That's how it is.
[KANZEON chuckles]
[LI TOUTEN laughs]
You've signed your
own death warrant!
Defending that beast after what
he's done is high treason!
All who flagrantly defy the
will of Heaven must perish!
I'm afraid you've chosen
to stand on the losing side,
Douji Konzen!
Ha! Great. You heard 'im.
What's your take, Field Marshal?
Indeed.
I'm sure there are better people
to ask than a fool like me.
Guys, no. What're you doing?
But then, if we're all fools,
I suppose there's no point
not walking the walk.
You come up with that yourself?
Nice turn of phrase.
No, just a little saying I
appropriated from Earth.
Konzen, can you carry him
while running?
Are you patronizing me?
Kill them all! Now!
None of them leave here alive!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
No! Stop!
Stand down!
Damn you both!
Think what you're doing!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[MAN 6J]
The Dragon King!
[MAN 6K]
Goujun!
[GOUJUN]
Field Marshal Tenpou.
Sorry for the clichéd tactic,
but desperate times call
for desperate measures.
Now then.
Would you all be so kind
as to get out of our way?
[KONZEN]
Goku...
Wake up.
What've you done, Konzen?
Why would a man of your
standing pit himself
against Heaven's military?
It wasn't political.
I simply didn't care
for what was going on
and felt I should do something.
Where do you go from here?
What could you possibly
have in mind?
The army's resources
are considerable,
they will stop at nothing
to crush the four of you.
All this madness over a child.
[GOUJUN]
You've spent your life insulated
from the horrors of battle.
What are you capable of?
That is, apart from dying.
I only wish that I knew.
Regardless, all I can say
for sure is our situation's
gone past the point
of diplomacy.
Konzen, no!
[GOKU panting]
When we met...
...you were the first one
to reach out your hand,
weren't you? Remember?
You're such a pain in the ass.
Look at me. What am I
gonna do with you?
I couldn't let go of
that hand if I wanted.
Konzen.
Now what?
Seems our hostage has
compelled them to hold off
for the time being, but...
Well, they're bound to
resume sooner or later.
Yup.
[door creaks]
[KENREN]
Goku?
You sure it's a good idea
for him to be up right now?
Hey, buddy. How ya feelin'?
Kenren. Tenpou.
Please promise me
you're not gonna go away.
I don't think I could handle
it if what happened
to Nataku happened to anyone
else I cared about.
It's just, we should be
with the people we love,
and for me, that's you guys.
Always. Us four.
We're together forever, right?
Cool. Let's cinch it.
Stick out your pinky finger.
What for?
Seriously? Just do it.
You'll see.
There, that's how it's done.
Feel me? It's a pinky promise.
This way, you know
it's for real.
A pinky promise.
Okay. I suppose it's official.
Looks as though we're going to
be together for a long time.
The plan is for us to
head down to Earth.
It won't be easy.
Depending on how things go,
we may have to split up
for a little while.
If it comes to that,
don't worry.
We'll meet again.
Just look for us beneath
the cherry blossoms.
Kill them! Forget about capture!
Leave no stone unturned!
Show no mercy!
All impurities must be
torn out by the root!
[BEASTS roar]
Uh, anyone know what these
things are supposed to be?
Given the equipment,
I can hazard a guess.
These poor devils were
artificially made.
It's quite possible we're seeing
early prototypes
for Prince Nataku.
I see what you're sayin'.
These are the failed experiments
that led to his creation.
[GOKU gasping]
I'll keep 'em busy for ya.
We'd be most grateful.
[BEASTS roars]
[KENREN]
Don't take this the wrong way.
[BEAST 6A groans]
[KONZEN]
Kenren!
[GOKU]
What's he doing?!
Run away!
Dramatic, huh?
[KENREN]
Go on. I'll catch up.
Yes. We'll see you soon.
[TENPOU]
Okay. Quietly, please.
[MAN 6L]
Where are they?
[MAN 6M] They couldn't
have just vanished!
All right. We're as far as I go.
You're on your own now.
If you'll excuse me.
I've business to attend to!
[BOTH gasp]
[MAN 6L]
It's the field marshal--!
[groans]
[MAN 6N] There's one of them
now! Rush the traitor!
Don't let him get away!
[MAN 6O]
Kill him! Kill him!
Tenpou! [gasps]
But, he's...
Let go. This isn't right!
We can't just leave them,
they're our friends!
Yes, they are.
[GOUJUN] How can you smoke
at a time like this?
Seemed like an opportune moment.
If you ask me, it really
brings out the flavor.
How ya doin', Goujun?
So we let you go
and you pay us back
by followin' us down here.
I didn't know you were
that into me.
Look, it's over.
Don't try to be cute.
Surrender. You--
[gunshot]
[KENREN]
Surrender my ass.
We both know you're here
to finish me off.
I'm right here. Bring it.
What? This a staring contest?
Come on, man.
You're the Dragon King,
act like it for once.
Don't taunt me.
You're terrible at it.
[KENREN]
Well, well. Lucky you.
I'm outta bullets.
I'm sorry, old friend.
Why are you smiling?
Seemed like an opportune moment.
[screams]
[BEAST 6A growls]
Goujun!
[BEAST 6A roars]
Jump through the vent!
Now, before it's too late!
Yeah. No thanks, sorry.
I have a little bit of
an issue with heights.
Personal philosophy.
I'm a practical guy.
I don't feel alive 'less my feet
are touchin' the ground.
[GOUJUN]
You're an imbecile.
Ha, ha. Trust me, I'm aware.
[BEAST 6A growling]
[KENREN] Look at you,
you're just tryin' to survive.
[KENREN]
Hell. Aren't we all?
Hey. No worries.
Totally feel ya.
We gotta do what we gotta do,
right? That's life.
Survival of the fittest.
If you leave a scrap,
I'm gonna be royally pissed!
Don't be shy. Eat, damn you!
[KENREN]
That's it. Don't hold back.
Livin' ain't for the faint
of heart, big guy.
Go on. We all have to show
our fangs once in a while.
[KENREN]
Atta boy.
[TENPOU] Ugh, I could
really go for a smoke
right about now.
Suppose I should've
grabbed a fresh pack
when I had the chance.
[TENPOU]
Huh. Speaking of.
I wander how many packs of
instant ramen I have left?
Never changed that light
in the bathroom, did I?
How much left before
I'm done with that book?
[MAN 6S groaning]
[TENPOU]
Aw, my glasses.
Could've sworn I had spares
lying around somewhere.
What ever happened to them?
They'll turn up eventually,
I'm sure.
On a shelf, perhaps,
waiting to be found when they
come to clean my room.
[coughs]
[TENPOU]
That should do for now.
I must be going.
[TENPOU]
Sorry to make you wait.
Yes. Perfectly fine,
though unfortunately,
my glasses broke.
Well, that might've
been my fault.
Mind if I borrow your
lighter for a moment?
[TENPOU inhales]
[exhales]
[TENPOU]
Huh? Ha, ha. Nothing.
I was just thinking how good
this cigarette tasted.
[KONZEN] In all of Heaven
there's only one path
down to Earth.
A dimensional gate
used almost exclusively
by the military.
It's hidden deep within
the lowest level
of the royal palace.
[footsteps]
[KONZEN]
Kenren and Tenpou bought us
the time necessary to reach it.
They're heroes. But me?
What am I going to do
for someone like him?
[KONZEN gasping]
I only see two guards.
Tenpou must've held
out long enough
to severely thin their ranks.
He did it for nothing.
[KONZEN]
Goku.
Let's give ourselves up.
Quit running.
If you say we're sorry they'll
have to forgive you,
won't they?
I wanted the four of us
to stay together. I...
Listen to me very carefully.
You can't give up hope.
Kenren and Tenpou fought for
this chance for a reason.
We're not giving up now.
We owe it to them to see
this through to the end.
[KONZEN]
My mind was made up.
Never again would I look away.
And besides, we made
a pinky promise. That's big.
[KONZEN] Never again would
I be ashamed of who I was,
or how I looked in your eyes.
Right.
[MEN groaning]
[GOKU grunting]
So heavy!
There it is.
Heaven's only connection to
Earth. Right in front of us!
[GOKU]
Konzen!
My, my. How tragic.
Freedom was just within reach.
[GOKU]
Konzen!
Dear boy.
Seiten Taisei, I believe
they called you?
A legendary creature
possessed of great power
neither god nor man?
I'm inclined to believe them.
Imagine the form Nataku
might be reborn into
if I had your body to work with?
[KENREN]
Atta boy!
[LI TOUTEN]
Hm?
[MAN 6V]
Status report, sir!
The other traitors
have been felled.
One in the eastern block
of basement level 30.
General Kenren
of the Western Army
and Field Marshal Tenpou
are confirmed neutralized.
Mission accomplished, my lord!
Wait, but what does that mean?
What did you do to them?
Where are they?
[GOKU whimpers]
Feel me? It's a pinky promise.
This way,
you know it's for real.
Okay. I suppose it's official.
Looks as though we're
going to be together
for a long time.
You lied to me.
[KONZEN]
We'll meet again.
Just look for us beneath
the cherry blossoms.
It was all... a lie!
[LI TOUTEN]
What the...?!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[gasps]
[KONZEN grunting]
[KONZEN] Earth is just on
the other side of that light.
[groaning]
No! Konzen!
Don't worry about me. I'm okay.
Focus on the dimension gate.
[GOKU gasps]
It's open! We made it!
[KONZEN] Earth is waiting
for you, my friend.
Can you run?
[GOKU]
Yeah!
[KONZEN]
I'm not a fool.
There's no guarantee of
hope beyond the light.
I've known that
from the beginning.
It's possible only
pain awaits you.
But if there's even
a chance at happiness,
I will do everything in
my power to get you there.
[LI TOUTEN] Miserable vermin.
I will not be mocked!
[GOKU grunts]
[KONZEN]
Damn it! We've got to move!
[laughs]
Hope is a lost cause!
Run as fast as you can!
The light will always
be beyond your grasp!
[gags]
[GOKU]
Almost there!
No!
We can make it! Don't give up!
Goku!
[KONZEN] Aren't cherry blossoms
the same everywhere?
[KENREN] Nah, depends on
where they live.
[KONZEN] Is that a fact? I'll
have to see them for myself.
[GOKU grunting]
[door creaking]
Konzen!
Don't stop! You have to
keep moving! [groans]
[GOKU]
No! [grunting]
Open, damn it!
--[KONZEN] Leave it be.
--[GOKU screams]
Never!
--[KONZEN] Please.
--I won't leave you!
[KONZEN]
Goku!
Think back.
When me met,
you were the first one
to reach out your hand.
Konzen.
[KONZEN]
The next time we meet,
I'll be the one reaching
out to you.
Listen to me.
We will meet again.
[KONZEN]
Just remember,
I'm not the sun. You are.
[GOKU grunting, cries]
[NATAKU] In the end,
we all dream of someday
reaching the light.
The question is,
will it have been worth it?
Go... ku...
[KANZEON] A few days later,
the royal garden's
cherry blossoms,
meant to bloom eternal,
fell softly to the ground.
Some say the petals
were trying to follow
Goku and his friends.
[KANZEON]
My goodness.
How long do you plan
on staying there?
[KANZEON] The child lay
were Konzen left him,
huddled before
the dimensional gate.
He'd scarcely moved a muscle
since seeing my nephew die.
There he waited like a stone.
By rights,
you ought to be dead.
A normal body would have
succumbed to starvation.
Come, that's not what
you want. Or is it?
You are not Seiten Taisei.
You are Goku. No one else.
The only name you'll
bear is the way
Konzen saw fit to give you.
"He who sees
what others cannot."
I trust you see how it is you
come by the luxury of despair?
You were brought here
on the back of sacrifice!
Waste that sacrifice and
disgrace not only yourself,
but the death of your friends!
[screams]
[KANZEON]
You've endured so much pain.
I speak for those who cannot.
Konzen, Tenpou, Kenren.
I knew their hearts.
Let me be their voice.
They loved you.
Never doubt it for a moment.
[screams]
[KANZEON]
Five hundred years of solitude.
Such was Heaven's
justice for the boy.
Every last vestige of paradise
was erased from his mind.
He would remember nothing.
Yet for all that, one memory
refused to be cast out.
[KANZEON] Why it persisted
I can only surmise.
Though something tells me
his name played a part.
Five centuries have
since passed.
Nataku is nowhere to be found.
Something is stirring.
I can feel it.
[HAKKAI]
I'd say it's time we get going.
[GOKU grunts]
[KANZEON] After the calm,
comes the storm.
[GOKU] Episode Seven: "Kouten."
Watch without fail.