[GOJYO]
Read 'em and weep.
[PLAYERS]
Ooh!
[FINE LADIES giggle]
[LADY 2A] We've got a card
sharp on our hands, ladies.
[YAKS mooing]
[GOJYO gasps]
[GOJYO]
What is that smell?!
Ugh! And what the hell
are these things?
Commonly referred to as yaks.
Or, even-toed ungulates,
to be precise.
Classed as order Artiodactyla,
family Bovidae, I believe.
I wasn't asking for
an encyclopedia entry.
[yawns] Oh, man.
You gotta love how
warm these babies are.
Especially with
how cold it gets.
If I wanted warmth,
I'd cuddle with a hot lady.
Preferably in a four-poster bed.
Hey. Stop whining.
You sound like a little bitch.
Matter of fact,
go back to sleep and
never wake up, okay?
Sanzo, my man.
[SANZO]
I'm not bumming you a smoke,
so don't bother
asking me for one.
[GOJYO] A-Ah! C'mon,
what if I say please?
[SANZO]
Um, no.
[GOKU, HAKKAI]
Harsh.
[GOJYO]
I love how we're treating
this whole crazy journey
like we just stepped
out for cigarettes.
Kinda sucks there's
nothin' but mountains
as far as the eye can see.
It's the only available
scenery for quite some time,
so get used to it.
[GOJYO] What about India?
How much longer?
I'm not really sure.
That said, I'm fairly confident
it can't be much further.
You'll notice we've been
encountering a lot of demons.
Lady Gyokumen's Gyumaou
Resurrection experiment
is to blame.
It's created a dark aura
spreading from the West
like a plague, decimating
everything in its path.
Inciting demons to violence.
[HAKKAI] Of course people
fear for their lives.
We ought not be
surprised if villages
in the region are
less than hospitable.
They gotta do what
they gotta do to get by.
'S not like they have
much of a choice.
Okay, so look,
not to be that guy,
but I have a hard
time believing this
is gonna have a happy ending.
It's not like things'll
just snap back to normal
after we slay the final boss.
If you want out, leave.
Gimme a break.
Heh.
Like it or not, gentlemen,
we're basically stuck together.
[GOJYO]
Believe me, I know.
You think I'd be hanging
with a bunch of guys
if I had a say in this?
[SANZO]
Keep talking, I'll kill you.
[GOKU yells]
I'm dyin' of starvation!
And I'm dying of thirst!
"What a shock,"
said absolutely no one.
Way to ruin the mood,
monkey boy. Bravo.
Ugh. He's got a point, though.
We're out of cigs,
we're out of water.
if we don't stop off
somewhere soon and restock,
we'll shrivel up and blow away.
[HAKKAI] There should be
a village not far from here.
[GOKU screams]
Could you not scream
in my ear, please?
--It's kind of annoying.
--[GOKU] Look! Just up ahead!
[HAKKAI]
A rather substantial lake,
at least, according to our map.
I suggest we replenish
our water supply
before heading to the village.
Ah!
Not to your liking, I take it?
Ugh! What the hell?
It tastes like salt!
That would be
because of the salt.
A rather high concentration
of it, evidently.
Huh. Great.
So much for
quenching our thirst.
[HAKKAI] We'd be fools
to drink it, that's true,
but on the bright side,
we'd be hard-pressed to drown.
What's that supposed to mean?
If we swam, we could drown.
Ah, but you see,
a high concentration of salt
in the water lowers
our specific gravity.
Essentially meaning, we'd
float on the lake's surface
like driftwood.
[GOJYO] Great, so we can relax
while we die of thirst.
[GOKU]
It's so pretty, though!
[GOJYO]
Shut up.
[MAN 2A]
S-State your business!
[GOKU]
Uh--
Are you human beings or demons?
Well, uh, last
I checked, I'm human.
These three, though?
I'm not so sure, to be honest.
What?
[MAN 2B]
Wha...?
[MAN 2C]
I knew it!
[DEMON 2A]
Lookie here!
Well if it isn't the Sanzo Gang!
Ugh. Here we go.
Why can't demons ever open
with something original?
Excellent question.
It is somewhat alarming
how taken their kind
seem to be with cliché.
[yells]
[DEMONS groan]
Right. Damn it.
What a time to be
outta cigarettes.
All that movin' around's
made me even hungrier.
What are you?
You can't be human.
[MAN 2A] That lake is the
source of our prosperity.
This village refines
and distributes salt.
It's our chief export, you see.
[MAN 2A]
We're a thriving community
by any reasonable standard.
Demons don't dare attack such
a robust population directly.
However, they do ambush
our transport wagons
from time to time.
Lately more than ever.
Who are these clowns
and why are they here?
[MAN 2A] Travelers, sir.
They staved off a demon attack.
You don't say.
A priest and his
entourage headed West.
All right, let's lay it out.
Demons have attacked
enough drivers the
last few months
that it's cutting into
our bottom line.
You fix our problem,
we fix yours.
You need lodging and supplies,
we need a safe trade route.
Whoa, wait a sec.
We're not here to cut
a deal with you people.
We're here because
this slippery bastard
said he'd take care of us
as a thank you for saving him!
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
What? You don't
think that's fair?
Look, pal, nobody
asked you to help.
You stepped in and played
hero on your own terms.
Fact is, 'less you're willing
to scratch our backs,
we got no incentive
to scratch yours.
Who says we're the
right men for the job
you're lookin' to fill
in the first place, huh?
Let's go.
[HAKKAI] Very well, Lord Mayor.
We graciously accept.
[GOKU, GOJYO]
Huh?!
Who died and made you king?
Look, if we need
stuff that badly,
just charge it to the card!
Regrettably, our line
of credit doesn't extend
to regions this remote.
Please be joking.
[HAKKAI] It's not so much that
our credit is bad, per se.
More that none of the shops
here have card readers.
Which wouldn't be a problem
if we weren't so low on cash.
So, getting food...
Would have to wait for a while.
--What about smokes?
--[HAKKAI] You'd survive.
Like hell I would!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
we have to tighten our belts.
I'm not wasting what
little cash we have
on things we don't need.
[GOJYO]
Yeah, well, I need cigarettes!
[HAKKAI] I have a stick of
chewing gum if that will help.
Are you in or out?
I don't have all day to
haggle with you punks!
[MAN 2A] I think we could've
handled that more delicately.
[GOJYO]
Tactful guy, your mayor.
What's done is done, gentlemen.
Not to be glib, but apparently
the Great Sanzo's reputation
precedes him no further
than our line of credit.
We've got no food,
no water, no cigarettes.
What the hell else
were we supposed to do?
No worries. It's settled.
Let's find some grub--ooh!
Maybe a fancy restaurant!
[MAN 2A]
Excuse me!
[GOKU]
Hm?
Just to clarify, demons
will likely be waiting
in ambush for our latest
shipment of salt.
We'd like you to
protect the wagon.
Ride along with the driver
as security staff.
When is it heading out?
[MAN 2A]
This afternoon.
I'll be loading
the wagon myself.
You'll need to leave
as soon as I'm done.
Wha...?
Suppose it can't be helped.
My associates and
I will tamp down
the terms of our
service while we wait.
Uh-huh.
How 'bout I leave
that crap to you guys.
I'm gonna have a look around.
[GOKU]
Me, too!
[SANZO]
Get me a nice room. With a bed.
Wait, how can anyone's who's
slept as much as you have
still be tired?
Well, sleep's supposed
to help you grow up
big and strong.
He's not a child!
Naps don't cure
male pattern baldness.
I will kill you where you stand.
[HAKKAI] Okay, okay.
Everyone do what they will.
Nap, explore, etcetera.
Just be back when
it's time to push off.
[GOKU]
Yay!
[GOJYO, SANZO]
What are you, five?
Yo, gramps.
Where's the nearest place
I can buy some smokes?
New in these parts, I see.
Not a lot of folks wearin'
those sorts of clothes.
'Kay?
There's a tobacco shop
just around the corner there.
Lucky me. Unusual
cigarette you got.
Is it a specialty brand?
You could say that.
Locally produced here in town.
Go ahead. Treat yourself to one.
Don't mind if I do.
[CHILDREN laughing, yelling]
Okay, go!
[CHILDREN gasp]
[GOKU]
Oh. Sorry. Did I weird you out?
Huh? Mm-mm.
[GOKU] What kinda game
ya playin'? Can I join in?
Sure! Why not?
We can always use
another player.
[GOKU]
What're the rules?
[BOY 2B]
That's their side, this is ours.
--[GOKU yells]
--[CHILDREN laughing]
[knocking]
I'm sorry.
I really hope I
didn't wake you up.
I brought you this.
Um, it'll keep you warm.
Great. Thanks.
So, where're you from?
If you don't mind
my asking, of course.
[SANZO] City in the
East called Chang'an.
Chang'an?
[SANZO] You're welcome to look.
Just don't touch it.
Is it true what they say
about you and your friends
protecting the salt wagon?
'Cause, the demons
have been getting
really bold these days and
it's nice to have someone
around who can, well, y'know.
[GIRL 2B chuckles]
[CHILDREN laughing, chattering]
[GOJYO] 'S not a Hi-lite,
but... Eh. It'll do.
[GOJYO]
Hey. How you doin'?
Oh, son of a...
[WOMAN 2A]
Pardon me. Is everything okay?
[GOJYO groans]
It's nothing.
I'm just reachin' for something.
Don't mind me, ma'am.
You sure?
Run along. I'm okay.
Just dropped my smoke.
[WOMAN 2A]
Smoke?
No need to worry.
I can handle it, really.
What a coincidence.
I happen to run a tobacco shop.
Well, whaddya know?
Hah! Isn't this the
craziest coincidence?
Tell ya what. I'll
stop by later, yeah?
Do me a favor, though, huh?
Can you just go
wait in the shop?
I'll be along as soon
as I'm done here.
Okay. But, uh, you
look a little stuck.
[GOJYO]
I see why you would think that.
[GOKU]
These are delicious!
You really think
they're that good?
[laughs] Best I've ever had!
Can I please have another, miss?
Sure, go ahead.
Heh. Eat up.
Take as many as you want,
my kids are sick of 'em.
Whatever. They're too dry.
It's not our fault
if you don't know
how to make stuff right.
Shut your mouth.
Sorry to impose.
I crash your game, next you
bring me to your house
and now I'm stuffin'
my face like an animal.
It's no big deal.
We could all hear
your stomach growling.
You needed food.
[GOKU] Hey, um, are all
these kids yours?
[MOM 2A]
Uh, oh, not exactly, no.
See, their parents...
well, their parents were killed
by demons and they needed
someone to care for them.
Poor dears had nowhere
else to go, so...
[GOKU]
I get it.
Hey, um...
D'you, like, have a
name or somethin'?
I'm Goku!
Ah! Goku's an awesome name!
Punctuality isn't
their strong suit.
Kou! Kou!
Well, Mother.
[DOKUGAKUJI]
Ah. There you are.
Dokugaku.
I'm, sorry to disturb you,
but Lady Gyokumen
wishes to see you.
Very well, then.
[KOUGAIJI] You're telling me
Ni Jianyi has disappeared?
Precisely.
And what's more, the
Resurrection Experiment
is stalled until his return.
Though, given that we still
lack the Founding Scriptures
of Heaven and Earth,
delay was inevitable.
If I expect the
fruits of my labor
to see the light of day,
I first require you to find
the missing scriptures
as soon as possible.
Yes, but, our priority should be
the Maten Scripture
currently in the possession
of Sanzo Genjo,
wouldn't you agree?
[KOUGAIJI]
Not an easy bounty, that one.
How many more demon causalities
are you comfortable with?
Dozens? Hundreds?
Oh, my.
I can't say I care
much for your tone,
particularly given how
often you've suffered
the pangs of defeat.
[BOTH growl]
[MAN 2D] Looks like your friends
had better things to do...
I guess.
I have a decent grasp of
why at least one of them
decided not to show up.
But the other two surprise me.
So be it, then.
I should be more than capable
of handling this job on my own.
I'll take all the
help I can get.
This salt's an essential
part of our livelihood.
Lots of people gave their
lives keeping it safe.
I've seen my friends die.
Demons come out of
nowhere on this route,
wreck havoc, make off
with the goods.
Still, danger or no danger,
this stuff is precious.
It has to make this journey.
No matter how high the
cost. Is that right?
[gasps] Stop the wagon.
[MAN 2D gasps]
[donkey brays]
[HAKKAI]
Wait right here, please.
[DEMONS laughing]
Huh?
[DEMONS scream]
[DEMON screams]
You bastard!
I regret to inform you,
you won't be going any further.
Ha! Like hell!
[yells]
[DEMON 2JJ]
He--He's too strong!
[DEMON 2K]
Don't be a coward!
It's only one guy!
[HAKKAI] A modest group
like this won't be hard
to dispatch on my own.
However, if what the
villagers say is accurate,
there should be twice this many.
It's a trap!
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[DEMON 2M]
Die!
[DEMON 2N]
Give us your salt!
[DEMON 2M groans]
Yeah, I know. I'm late.
What're you gonna do, right?
[DEMONS yell]
[DEMON 2Q groans]
Where the hell were
you? We had a deal.
Where the hell
were you, asshole?!
[HAKKAI] If anyone has the
right to ask that question,
it's me.
Sorry, I was just
havin' a smoke.
I was gettin' a bite to eat.
I overslept a little.
[sighs] One of these days...
Oh, well. Better
late than never.
Things were just about
to get interesting.
[yelling]
[MAN 2D screams]
[MAN 2D yelping]
Tch.
[groans]
[yelps]
[GOJYO] Got here just in
the nick of time, didn't we?
[HAKKAI] I took care of
the first wave for us.
[GOKU screams]
So much for their
precious cargo.
Nice job, Sanzo.
Way to think it through.
Yes, well.
Our young friend's life
is far more valuable.
[brays]
[HAKKAI]
And the donkey's.
So, yeah. You slayed
the marauders,
but you compromised
our shipment.
Sorry, fellas, the deal's off.
We hired you to protect
the salt, not lose it.
No food or shelter for you,
and I want you out of
my village by sundown.
[MAN 2A]
But, Lord Mayor--!
[MAYOR 2A]
Shut it!
Hey.
"I'm not bumming you a smoke,
so don't bother
asking me for on--"
[gunshot]
Whoa! What's wrong with you?
That could'a blown
my head off, asshole!
I know.
Now quit whining and
give me a cigarette.
Here, have at 'em.
[GOJYO] Those aren't yours
to give, monkey boy!
What? Aw, 'cmon.
Don't be stingy.
You have more 'n
enough to go around
My. Your haul looks
quite delectable.
They certainly gave you
the lion's share.
Yeah. I am one happy camper
right now, believe me!
[HAKKAI]
The villagers were generous.
All things considered,
we lucked out.
I dare say perhaps dying from
starvation isn't in the cards.
[GOKU]
That mayor guy was a jerk,
but the people were super nice.
[GOJYO] If it hadn't been
for them, Sanzo's little stunt
would've had us all
working pro bona.
[SANZO]
Shut your hole, water sprite.
[GOJYO] I've said it before
and I'll say it again:
it's like we're goin'
out to buy cigarettes.
Unbelievable.
[GOKU]
Episode 3: "Sky Burial."
Don't miss it.
[HAKKAI]
Ready, and...
[GOKU, HAKKAI, GOJYO, SANZO]
Ura Sai!
Why's anybody think this is fun?
Uh! How'd you get here?
I'm, uh, wondering that myself.
A'right! Let's do this!
[GOJYO]
Yee-ha!
What the...?
You swine!
At least have the decency to
put on a proper bathing suit!
That's your problem?
Here I come!
Wow. Awkward.
Ready, and...
[GOJYO, SANZO, GOKU, HAKKAI]
Ura Sai.
[GOJYO] Good, good.
Just keep walkin' forward.
[GOKU]
Like this?
[GOJYO]
No, hang on. You're veering.
[GOKU]
Ready?
[GOJYO]
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no!
[GOKU]
How 'bout now?
--[GOJYO] Yes-- No!
--[GOKU] Now?
--No! Wait, no! Wait!
--Here? Now?
--Damnit, stop moving!
--Like this? I'm gonna swing!
Whoa! Hang on! Uh--
Ah! Ha...
Is it just me or is
this really tough?
He's not really asleep, right?
[SANZO]
Okay. I'm impressed.
[GOJYO]
Ready, and...
[GOKU, SANZO, GOJYO, HAKKAI]
Ura Sai!
[yelling]
[groans]
So good!
Guess it's edible.
What are you waiting for, Gojyo?
[GOJYO]
I hate you guys.