[HAKKAI yelps]
[GOJYO groans]
[GROUP groaning]
[SHARAK]
He's too much for them!
Very well, then.
My mission continues.
This is bad.
The kid's got some skills.
Ha, ha. Hey, he's
our replacement.
Hurt my feelings
if he didn't.
Indeed. Since we're being
pushed to the wayside,
it might as well be by
someone competent.
Still, though.
We're not going anywhere
if this is all you can do,
short round.
[BOTH yelling]
[GOJYO, GOKU yell]
[HAKKAI gasps]
Incoming!
[GOJYO, GOKU groan]
'Kay, that might've been a
little too close for comfort.
[GOJYO] Ah! How does
so much friggin' power
come outa one tiny,
little dude?
He doesn't even care if
his buddies are in the way!
We should count ourselves lucky
they're the only
things he's hit.
His destructive power
is immense.
Yeah, so everyone
watch your asses.
Gee, thanks. Kind of
already put that together
for ourselves there, chief.
Good talk, though.
[SANZO] Hey, if you've got a
plan for not being blown
to rock dust, I'm all ears,
pretty boy. Lay it on me!
Whoa! Come on, you two!
Not the time to be jerks!
[HAKKAI]
I'd formulate a solution myself,
but considering the range
of his attacks...
[GOJYO grunts]
[GROUP groaning]
Hassan! Roshu!
[HASSAN, ROSHU]
Ma'am!
[SHARAK grunts]
[ROSHU groans]
You okay?!
[GOKU growls, screams]
[GOJYO]
Think fast!
You little...!
[GOJYO]
Damn it!
[HAKKAI grunts]
[SHARAK chants]
You're good, right?
I'm fine. Get off.
[SHARAK groans]
Heads up!
[GOJYO, GOKU grunt]
[SHARAK groaning]
[GOKU grunting]
[SHARAK]
How are they still standing?
[yelling]
[GROUP gasps]
Come on!
Let go of me!
[SANZO chanting]
Makai... Tenjo!
He didn't even flinch!
[chains clinging]
I've got you now!
Whoa there, nice try!
Excellent! He's in
point-blank range!
[SANZO groans]
[gunshot]
Makai Tenjo!
What the Hell is he doing?
[GOKU yells]
Wait, is it over?
Ah. Ha, ha! Piece of cake!
[laughing]
[panting]
Piece of cake my
water sprite ass.
Monkey boy can't even
stand upright.
Now, now. Don't tease.
He fought well.
None of us is light on
our feet at the moment.
Hey, speak for yourself, wuss.
That'd prob'ly land harder
if you weren't wheezing.
I'm surprised you're alive.
[SANZO] Funny. I was gonna
say the same thing.
I'd help you boys with
your wounds, but...
It's all I can do to keep from
falling on my face right now.
Quite all right, friend.
Don't mind us. We'll be up and
about in no time, I'm sure.
[HASSAN]
What about him?
[SANZO]
Good question. He's not dead.
--[explosion]
--[GOKU yelps]
[GOJYO]
Crap...
[HAKKAI]
He took the full brunt
of Goku's attack head-on,
and yet...!
You will be neutralized.
[whimpering]
Goku!
[NATAKU]
Go... ku...?
[laughs] Classic! I wish
I could'a seen it! Wow!
You told me I was awesome!
No one's ever said that
before! It felt good!
Huh. When you said we play
again, it felt even better.
Nataku.
All I wanted... was to
tell you my name.
It's Goku.
[NATAKU] Much as I longed to,
I could never break free.
In the end,
we all dream of someday
reaching the light.
The question is, will it
have been worth it?
[NATAKU]
We shall see.
[sword clattering]
[gasps]
[screams]
Target confirmed.
Must be... eliminated.
Target confirmed...
Must be eliminated.
Target confir--
[hammering]
We don't have nearly enough
men posted at the outer gate.
Send some over, will ya?
[MAN 12A]
You got it.
[HASSAN]
Roshu.
Yes, sir?
Don't push yourself too hard.
C'mon, let those
wound heal first.
Thank you, but,
all due respect, sir,
you're wounds are a
lot worse than mine.
[laughs]
[MAN 12B]
Sharak? Sharak?!
[HASSAN]
Hm? What's up?
[MAN12B]
Looks as though Genjo is awake.
I figured Sharak would
want to be told.
[footsteps]
So, different day,
same old story.
[SHARAK]
What's on your mind?
[HASSAN] Apparently Genjo's
regained consciousness.
Has he now?
You sure it's cool to be up?
Don't worry about it, eh?
He only looks stiff
because he's old.
Dude's not injured,
just has arthritis--
[gunshot]
How'd you like me
to paralyze you
from the waist down
with a bullet?
Awake for five minutes and
already you're shooting at me?!
I dreamed about it the
whole time I was out.
So, I'm in your
dreams now, am I?
I dunno what's worse.
Your fantasies or your aim.
Wanna make my dreams come true,
by all means keep flappin'.
I'm this close to putting a
bullet between your eyes
so I can just hear
the air escape.
--[gunshots]
--[GOJYO] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You could actually
hit me this close!
[SANZO]
...that's the whole idea.
They seem back to
their old selves, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Back in the saddle?
I came to see how you all were.
Seems things've
returned to normal.
We appreciate you provided
us with a room
in order to convalesce, madam.
Truly, we're in your debt.
Oh, please. It's the
least I could do.
Without you, the death toll
would have been much higher.
Is this a good time?
Sure.
True, the loss of life could've
been a lot worse.
What I don't get, though.
What was that boy doing here?
You mean Prince Nataku, yes?
[SHARAK] I understand
he'd been ordered to stop
the Gyumaou Resurrection
Experiment in your place, but...
Why then would he
show up here to fight?
And, why suddenly
fly back to Heaven
after a brief skirmish
with the four of you?
Who can say, really?
Maybe his batteries
needed to recharge.
His retreat did
seem rather hasty.
Oh! Know what?
I think he was hungry!
He needed food.
[stomach growls]
[GOJYO] Yeah, thanks for
playin', but ya know,
not everyone's slave
to their stomach.
[GOKU]
You got something better?!
[HAKKAI]
Calm down, gentlemen.
[SHARAK]
So, what's next?
If you'd like to rest,
you're more than welcome
to stay here as
long as you need.
Nah, we'll go.
[SHARAK]
Westward?
Yeah.
Very well.
If nothing else,
this incident has certainly
taught me my limits.
The Kouten Scripture
enables me
to protect people,
but not everyone,
and not without a price.
I envy you.
I'd quash the dark aura's
source with my bare hands
if Fate so permitted. Alas,
my duties lay elsewhere.
Though I wish I could go.
I have the utmost faith in you.
[HAKKAI, GOJYO chuckle]
[GOKU laughs]
We've piled your ride high with
plenty of supplies for the trip.
Thanks. We appreciate it.
You're too kind.
I prob'ly shouldn't ask...
[SANZO, GOKU]
Hm?
But do you have to leave?
You could stay here with us
for a little while longer
and help out till things
calm down, right?
What's it gonna be next time?
Bloodthirsty demons, Prince
Nataku come back for more?
I can't guess.
Sure'd be nice to have you
all here with us, though.
Sharak'd be pleased.
I don't know about that.
I think she'd prefer us
to fight where she can't.
No, you're right.
I'm just being a fool.
Be careful out there.
Right back at'cha.
Thank you for all you've done.
Especially for all the
delicious grub! [laughs]
[GOJYO]
Ugh. More mountains? Seriously?
Don't worry.
We're stocked up on that
altitude sickness
concoction of theirs.
Nausea ought not to
plague us too terribly.
Unless you try to drink it.
Aw, don't sweat it, man.
If you get sick and
can't take the medicine,
I'll just shove it down
your throat. No worries.
That'd be great.
You're a real friend.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, you all right, Sanzo?
You need a dose?
'Cause I could help.
I'm good.
[SANZO]
Hakkai.
Yes?
We're making a pit stop.
I suppose we are.
[MAN 12C]
Come no further!
You do not have
permission to be here!
Turn back now!
The audience chamber
is forbidden to anyone
not expressly summoned
by the Sanbutsushin!
You're aware of the rules!
Aw, ease up, fellas.
Don't be all stingy.
We're in a bit of a hurry,
so if you wouldn't mind moving.
[MAN 12D]
You can't!
Look, guys, it's fine.
We'll just apologize later.
Not on your life!
Every monk,
regardless of rank, is...
Is bound by the same code!
[MONKS gasps]
Step aside.
Hey, uh, Sanzo Genjo,
31st of China.
Requesting an immediate
audience with Your Graces.
Come on, freaks: time's
wastin'. Scene's up!
What is the meaning of
this base outrage?
You are the first mortals
ever to presume
requesting an audience with us.
Impudence. It's unthinkable
that such a high-ranking priest
would stoop to threaten
others of his own order.
Pardon me. But, it
sounds as though
you're accusing us of
stepping out of line.
What?
Technically, since we don't
work for you anymore,
it's kind of hard to tell which
rules still apply to us,
ya feel me?
Wait a second. I don't remember
really following them
in the first place.
Uh, be quite, Goku.
That's quite enough, thanks.
How dare you.
[sighs] Enough of
this foolishness.
State your purpose here.
Me and my posse are going West.
We're putting an end
to the Gyumaou Resurrection
Experiment.
[NEUTRAL ASPECT] Your intentions
play absolutely no part
in what we decree.
[ASPECT] The honor of
subjugating Gyumaou
has been given over
to Prince Nataku.
Our decision is final.
I don't really give a damn.
Real sorry, guys. Decrees from
Above don't mean shit to us.
It's time for us to finish
what we started.
You're mad!
I just thought you'd
like to hear it from me.
Excuse us, please.
[BOTH]
Glad you got to see me, suckers!
Oh. Yeah. Wait. I forgot.
Don't even think about
yanking our credit card.
[window opens]
I take it they've left?
They won't have an easy time.
[SAITAISAI]
Not if they're continuing West.
Oh?
True, they've successfully
quelled the war god prince.
But I suppose, given your
prophecy, their luck
will take a turn for
the worse sooner or later.
That'll probably keep
things entertaining enough
to hold my interest for a while.
That is deception.
Generations canter by.
You in your eagle's nest
have seen countless Sanzo
priests come and go.
Surely You must know
the stars as well as I do.
I sincerely doubt whether my
prophecies are of any use.
Come. Would you not agree?
Well, now, one can't be so sure.
Only this much is certain--
shots have been fired.
I'm starvin',
you guys! For real!
Soon you're gonna have
to shoo the flies away
from my wasted away face!
[SANZO]
Good.
Jeez. Give us a break.
You just stuffed your face.
Patience, please. We only
have so many rations.
I'll tell you what: we'll grab
something in the next town.
Great. Sounds like a plan to me.
Unless the floating heads back
there froze all our money.
That's true. I imagine we'll
only know for sure
when we use it. Until then,
let's think positively.
[GOJYO] Easy for you to say.
You're not a smoker.
God. You're worse than
the monkey boy.
Can you give us a rest from
your whining for ten seconds?
Yo! Kiss my ass!
I'm gonna die.
[GOJYO] Okay! We get it.
Thank you. Shut up.
[DEMON 12A]
Ah-ha!
[tires screech]
[DEMON 12A] Well, if it
isn't the Sanzo Party!
Ha, ha, ha!
Heads are about to roll!
Aw...
'Kay, this is startin'
to get on my nerves.
Ah...
[GOJYO]
Son of a...
Uh, seems like a lot.
Yeah. They've painted
themselves into a corner.
Quantity over quality.
[HAKKAI]
An obvious strategy,
I'll grant you, but
undoubtedly effective.
[GOKU] So, um, how're we
handling this?
You don't have a snowball's
chance in hell
against an army this size!
Surrender now and--!
[GOJYO]
Let's do this!
[DEMONS yelling]
Ugh. This is such a
royal pain in the ass.
Maybe we should've
head home after all.
[GOKU]
Seriously? Come on!
Rather anti-climatic
after the spiel
we gave the Sanbutshusin,
don't you think?
Lame'd be a better word.
[GOKU]
"Lame."
[HAKKAI]
Moot point, either way.
We wouldn't be likely to
make it back in one piece.
And for that matter,
how do we get there?
What d'you mean?
We don't have a map?
[SANZO] Sure, but the
landscape keeps shifting.
Why do you think
we're always lost?
Damn thing'd be better
off as toilet paper.
And here I thought you
were just a shit navigator.
Go figure.
Yeah, me, too.
Both of you are gonna get shot.
At this juncture, comrades,
going back would be just as
troublesome as forging ahead.
Best stay the course.
Right. And there's probably
demons waiting in ambush
whatever direction we go with.
Seems to me like a
damned-if-we-do,
damned-if-we-don't scenario.
Hey. Sanzo's the boss. What now?
I'll give you one guess.
[SANZO]
The only way out, is through.
[GOJYO, GOKU, HAKKAI, SANZO]
Ura Sai.
Kinda havin' a hard time
believin' it's over.
Yeah. I'm there with ya.
Huh. Who'd have thought
it'd go so fast?
[HAKKAI] How humbling to ponder
the blur this has been.
[HAKKAI] Anyone else
feeling a touch nippy?