[TENJIN] Over and over, the
sacred rites are repeated.
Where is the wellspring of life?
From whence does it flow?
And, more importantly,
where does it end?
[GOJYO]
Ah, damn it! Son of a...!
Was this seriously the only way?
[HAKKAI]
How many times must I tell you?
I'm sorry! It's not my
fault a mountain range
blocks our path to the West.
Come on, nothin' wrong
with a little hike
every now and then, right?
[SANZO] This isn't exactly
my idea of a hike.
Strikes me more as a
rock-climbing expedition.
Do what?
You'll have to talk louder.
I can't hear ya.
[GOJYO] Just tell me
the path isn't like this
the rest of the way.
My palms are chaffing!
[HAKKAI] The West was quite
unpredictable enough
before bizarre phenomenon began
reshaping the landscape.
Maps just can't keep up.
[GOKU] In other words,
how 'bout you quit bitchin'?
Take a page from Sanzo's book--
he's barely said anything.
'Cause the poor bastard
can hardly breathe,
in case you hadn't noticed!
It's all he can do
just to hold on--!
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
That could've hit me!
I didn't do anything.
What makes you think
you're worth the effort
to draw a gun?
Then, where'd the
shot come from?
[DEMON 3A laughs] Well,
if it isn't the Sanzo Gang!
We'll be takin'
that scripture now,
and of course, your lives.
Huh?!
You really have
to do this right now?
Get a clue, jackass.
We're kinda preoccupied
at the moment!
I'd say they have
a fairly decent grasp
of the situation
we're in, actually.
[GOKU]
Well? What are you waiting for?
[DEMONS yell]
Idiots! Don't just
stand there! Attack!
[GOJYO]
Whoa there, tiger.
Givin' a little too much
attention to my buddy there.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
getting jealous.
That'd be a rather
fascinating dimension
to explore in a crime drama.
Popularity's not all it's
cracked up to be, guys!
Is it just me or are
we gettin' hounded
at every turn lately?
It's a shame they
insist on attacking
regardless of how
polite we try to be.
[DEMON 3M groans]
[SANZO] Maybe I'm paranoid,
but I call that being stalked.
[HAKKAI] Isn't there some
old sutra about everyone
having their 15 minutes of fame?
[GOKU] Wait, I'm wasting my
moment in the sun on this?
[GOJYO] Some of us get
a lot more than 15 minutes.
[GOJYO]
Okay...
[growls]
[DEMONS yelping]
[GOJYO]
Man, that's gross.
They're feeding
on demon carcasses?
[GOKU gags]
[TENJIN]
Don't worry.
As you observed, they're
only nourishing themselves
on the dearly departed.
[HAKKAI]
A demon?
Forgive my asking,
but, are you the one
controlling these birds?
[TENJIN chuckles] Goodness,
no. I'm just a caretaker.
They have minds of their own.
You see that little
village down there?
Not so long ago, this area was
reserved for sky burial rites.
[GOKU]
What is that s'posed to mean?
[SANZO]
You know how people are interred
or cremated after they die?
It's kind of along those lines.
Some customs dictate the
recently deceased to be left
out in the open so birds
can pick at their remains.
Talk about leavin' a
bad taste in your mouth.
You know, funeral rites
offer a great insight
into a given culture's
relationship with death.
Sky burials may seem
barbaric at first,
but in reality, its symbolic
of life returning to nature.
Indeed! What an
unadulterated pleasure it is
to meet someone who understands!
Would you gentlemen
care for some tea?
My abode isn't much to look at,
I know, but I live alone.
[gasps] Thank you,
but we really must be--
[TENJIN]
This way! [yelps]
Perhaps some other time?
I'm afraid we're
in a bit of a hurry.
[TENJIN]
Okay.
[GOJYO] All right. So we're
in demand. I get it.
But d'you ever think
we'd be invited
to tea by a demon?
[GOKU] Wouldn't'a hurt
to take him up on it.
You might not have had problem,
but a priest sitting
down with a demon
wouldn't go over well.
You have a point.
One wonders how
the fellow manages,
particularly living
within a stone's throw
of human habitation.
[SANZO]
Who knows?
[GOJYO]
More importantly,
one also wonders where
we're gonna sleep.
Just sayin'.
Another good point.
I had a look around on
the way in but didn't see
a place we could stay the night.
[MAN 3A]
Um.
Pardon me, I couldn't help
but notice your robes.
You wouldn't be
priest, by chance?
Yes indeed!
As a matter of fact,
the man sitting before you
just so happens to be
the noblest priest
in all of Shangri-la:
Sanzo Genjo!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Ah! We'd be ever so grateful
for a reading of scripture,
your holiness!
Give us your blessing?
[WOMAN 3A]
The people of this village
are unshakably devout,
I assure you!
That is encouraging
to know. Thanks so much.
But, I'm afraid your village
doesn't appear to have an inn.
If only there was some
place to rest our bones.
[MAN 3A] We'll prepare a
room for you without delay,
good sirs! Our village
may be humble,
but it is not inhospitable.
[HAKKAI]
That would be most kind of you.
Hakkai.
I know, I'm sorry.
But we have to play the cards
we're dealt, do we not?
Incidentally, I'm counting
on the two of you
not to spoil the illusion.
[GOKU]
Um, what illusion exactly?
[GOJYO] This isn't a con job.
He's really a priest.
[SANZO chanting]
[BOTH]
Convincing. Nice.
He's had plenty of practice.
We owe these young men
a debt of gratitude.
Yes, that we do.
Perhaps now our
misfortunes will be over.
What'cha talkin' about?
Well, you see.
There've been a number
of disappearances lately.
Fellow villagers vanishing
without a trace.
[WOMAN 3B]
I blame the birdman.
He lives on the mountain and
is always up to no god.
What a coincidence.
I understand sky
burials used to be
a common practice in this
region. Is that true?
[MAN 3C] Until recently,
humans and demons lived
side-by-side in
perfect harmony here.
And then the demons went mad.
Burrying our dead
atop the mountain
became too dangerous.
We had to start putting
them in the ground.
[MAN 3C] The carrion birds
are now tended to by a demon
that used to live
among us as a friend.
He's obsessed with them. There's
no rhyme or reason to it.
Of course, it's only
reasonable to assume
he's connected to the
string of disappearances.
[GOKU] Hm. I'll admit he
might've been a little off,
but I didn't get a crazed
killer vibe from the guy.
[MAN 3B]
Wait!
You've actually crossed
paths with Tenjin?
That's one way of
putting it, I guess. Sure.
There you are!
I'd expect nothing less
from the noble Sanzo Gang!
Imagine being so bold
when encountering a demon
in this day and age!
Yes, well, you know.
[MAN 3B] Surely his grace
would agree to confront
the demon and get to
the bottom of things?
[MAN 3C] Better yet, he can
kick him off the mountain
and give our village some peace!
Bless you, sir! Bless you!
Of course.
[TENJIN]
I beg your pardon?
I'd never do the villagers harm!
Delicious!
I owe the villagers
a vote of thanks
for letting me live there
as long as they did.
Oh, and, uh, I happened
to be a vegetarian.
[HAKKAI] Ah. Even so,
you're also a lightening rod.
Your neighbors are
an apprehensive lot.
They'll lay all kinds of
misfortune at this door.
Toiling under a
cloud of suspicion
can't make for a happy life.
Why don't you just pick up
and move the hell
away from here?
'S not like the birds need you
to take care of 'em, right?
[TENJIN]
Maybe not, but I don't choose
to remain here for them.
The ritual of sky burial is an
important part of our culture.
Life returning to
nature is beautiful.
Doomed to live and
are in turn consumed.
An unending cycle through
whose weft and warp
the whole of creation
is threaded.
See, I remain on this
lonely mountaintop
to preserve a vital sacrament.
Awaiting the day when Shangri-la
is once again in harmony.
I need no other purpose
in life than that.
So, that's all
you're interested in?
Uh--
[screams]
C'mon, what're you doing?
Knock it off! This is my food!
You know better
than that, Tenba.
Leave him alone.
You are aware you're
pickin' a fight with a bird.
[TENJIN]
This isn't like him. Huh.
It's unusual for him to even
approach anyone but me.
[GOJYO]
Eh. Wild animals are attracted
to other wild animals,
am I right?
Who you callin' a wild animal,
ya stray water sprite?
Water sprites were
never domesticated
in the first place, you moron!
May I ask why the bird
seems to live here?
[TENJIN] He can't fly
very well on account
of a broken wing.
Poor thing's a lot
younger than he looks.
[HAKKAI] I can understand
taking care of one,
but tending so many
must be exhausting.
How on earth do
you feed them all?
[TENJIN] It isn't as easy
as it used to be.
Since things started
changing for the worse,
there's hardly enough food for
me, let alone a whole flock.
I feed them scraps of
livestock when I can, though.
[SANZO]
Tenjin and Tenba.
Both words mean
"the teachings of Buddha,"
if I'm not mistaken.
Oh, my. You're
knowledgeable of other
religious practices, are you?
I envy the sense of perspective
you must have, my friend.
[GOJYO] You wouldn't know
it by lookin' at him,
but he's kinda smart.
[SANZO] Somebody must really
wanna return to nature.
[MAN 3A]
Tenjin! Stop! You can't!
[MAN 3A] Please! Relatives are
forbidden from seeing!
Don't do this to yourself!
Tenjin!
[TENJIN chuckles] They're in
fine spirits today, aren't they?
A full belly makes the
return flight a joy.
[GOKU]
Return flight? Oh, sure!
You don't keep all
these birds here,
they're going back
to their home, huh?
Where is home for so many
birds as big as these guys?
[TENJIN]
Excellent question.
Where do we go when we die?
[GOKU]
Hm?
[TENJIN]
Our souls, I mean.
When someone you love passes on,
what happens to their spirit?
Where does the soul travel
when parted from the body?
[GOKU] Yeah, I, uh, don't know
much about souls 'n stuff.
I've never really thought
about it. Could be anywhere.
To be honest, I think it's
more important to focus
on the life right in front
of you than to worry
about what happens after
it's all over, y'know?
[GOKU]
Huh.
Well said.
Can't waste our lives dwelling
on the sweet hereafter. Ha, ha.
Sorry to pose a
question so grim.
[GOKU]
What was that about?
My chest feels heavy,
like I'm trapped under a rock.
[HAKKAI]
What do you think, Sanzo?
[SANZO]
About what?
The villagers are
convinced he's responsible
for the recent string
of disappearances.
I don't know whether
I agree with them or not.
Me neither.
We gave him a warning,
that's all they asked.
What happens from here
on out isn't up to us.
[GOJYO]
What's this?
[TENJIN]
When someone you love passes on,
what happens to their spirit?
[GOKU]
What's wrong with me?
Why'd I feel so weird
when he brought that up?
We live, we die. Why worry
about what happens after?
[SHEEP braying]
[WOMAN 3C]
Yes, yes. I know.
[brays]
Goodness gracious. Settle down.
What are you so
worked up about--
Guess we'll have to make
do with an old hag.
[DEMON 3P]
Beggars can't be choosers.
We get too cocky,
they'll be on to us,
and there goes our meat.
[GOJYO] Li'l role-play with
a feisty cougar, eh?
No disrespect, fellas,
but she doesn't seem into it.
[HAKKAI] They've been
quietly kidnapping people
one by one so as not
to stir the village
into an outright panic.
Good way of drawing
out the food supply,
unless of course someone catches
you in the act red-handed.
Who in the hell
are you chumps...
[SANZO]
Pretty convenient setup.
Anybody notices
a neighbor missing,
they'll just chalk it down
to the crazy ol'
hermit on the hill.
[GOKU] Smart. 'Least, that's
what you wanted us to say.
How long you guys think
you were gonna
get away with this?
Screw you!
[SANZO]
Goku.
My bad.
[GOJYO]
Have at 'em.
We figure it's best to let you
people dole out justice.
Bear in mind, they're on
the verge of starvation.
We ask that you refrain
from judging them harshly.
Such wise and
compassionate souls!
May each and every
one of us aspire
to follow your example!
[WOMAN 3B]
Thank you so much!
If there's anything we can do...
[SANZO]
Hakkai.
...only say the word
and it's done!
Well, actually.
Virtue is its own reward.
Heh. What he wants is sleep.
Uh. But, if maybe
you think about
apologizing to the birdman,
that'd be something kinda
nice you could do for us.
That's true.
We're not trying to
gloss over the fact
that we treated him
unfairly or anything.
But a demon's a demon.
We're not comfortable with
one of them living so close.
[MAN G]
Hear hear.
[ROOSER crows]
[yawning] I could definitely
use another hour.
Gojyo, any idea where Goku is?
Tellin' me he's not here?
[HAKKAI] I thought he stepped
out to relive himself,
but that was a while ago.
[SANZO]
Nothing to worry about.
He's probably just
wandering around.
Dear me, no.
The young lad definitely
had a purpose in mind.
Said he had to head out early.
Huh?
[WOMAN 3C] Something about
telling someone something.
Idiot kid.
He must've gone up the hill.
I thought he had
a troubled look.
Tenjin's riddle must've
really gotten to him.
[GOJYO] Stupid monkey, trying
to use brains he ain't got.
[GOKU] Tenjin! You
still asleep? It's me.
Is he here?
[GOKU]
I smell incense.
Hello? Tenjin?
Whoa. What's this place?
All kinds of stuff in here.
Toys, stuffed animals,
a hand mirror.
That looks like a
little girl's barrette.
Did these things belong to
his family or something?
Why's it like
they're on display?
[TENJIN]
Goku?
Ah! Sorry.
I didn't mean to barge
in without permission!
It's all right. No harm done.
Good to see you,
it's just so early.
I wanted to tell you somethin'
'fore me an' the guys left town.
I know it's kind of early,
but I just couldn't wait.
[TENJIN]
Well, then.
Why not come inside
for a bit of tea?
I'm sure Tenba would
enjoy the visit.
[GOJYO]
Ugh.
How long does the
monkey boy need?
[HAKKAI]
I must confess,
I'm not a fan of him
going off on his own.
[GOJYO]
Eh, he'll be fine.
Tenjin's gotta be the
least threatening demon
we've ever run across.
Plus we've already bagged
--the real kidnappers, so...
--[WOMAN 3D] Excuse me.
--I think you dropped this.
[GOJYO]
Oh, thanks. Didn't realize.
Seems an odd thing
for you to own.
How on earth did you come by it?
I don't own it, just found
it on the hill yesterday.
Figured some kid
from the village
must've lost his mitten and
be in bad with his folks.
[MOTHER 3A]
Um, might I see?
I thought it looked familiar.
This belonged to my son!
Forgive me for prying.
May I ask where he is?
[MOTHER 3A] There was an
epidemic several months ago,
it claimed my
darling boy's life.
He was a little-bitty thing,
only six years old.
We buried him with his mittens.
How could this end up on--?
What's up?
[SANZO] You people have
been interring your dead
since the sky
burials stopped, yeah?
That's right.
We made a cemetery
just outside of town.
[SANZO]
Take me there. Now.
[HAKKAI] Gojyo, I think you
need to go up the hill.
Somebody gonna tell me
what the hell's goin' on?
[SANZO]
Round up some men.
Have them bring shovels.
[HAKKAI]
You're sure about this?
[SANZO] If I'm wrong, I'll
recite the appropriate sutra.
[TENJIN] You caught the guys
behind all the disappearances?
That's a relief to hear, though
it's difficult to be happy,
given how many people
lost their lives.
I know. But, hey,
look on the bright side!
At least your name's
been cleared.
That's something, right?
Is that what you came here at
the crack of dawn to tell me?
[GOKU]
Not just that.
Ah! Hey, hey! Easy there, Tenba.
You're crowding
my personal space.
[laughs] Well, look at that.
Who'd have thought my son
would make himself
a new friend so quickly?
[GOKU] Tenjin. D'you
used to have family?
The stuff in your shed
looked like it might'a
belonged to people close to you.
[TENJIN] Ah. Yes, you mean
the random bric-a-brac
my feathered friends make
a habit of bringing here.
Birds can't resist
anything shiny.
[GOKU]
Got'cha.
I can return 'em to the
villagers if you want.
[TENJIN]
U-Uh...
'D be hard to do it yourself,
them being scared
of you and everything.
Lots of valuables
in there I'm sure
they'd like to have back.
How kind. Such a
good boy, you are.
[MAN 3E] They're gone!
The bodies have been taken!
[MAN 3F] We just buried
this one last week!
What it heaven's name
is going on here?
[HAKKAI]
Birds that eat only dead flesh.
There's not much room for doubt.
[HAKKAI] This is how Tenjin
kept his charges fed.
I can't believe he'd
defile the sanctity
of the grave just to
carry on a lost tradition.
The dead aren't just
props for a pet cause.
Wha...
[TENJIN]
Let me tell you about my son.
My beloved wife died in agony
bringing him into this world.
[GOKU]
What's going on?
[TENJIN]
All for nothing.
He was born with a heart
condition that would play a role
in his own death.
I was there. I saw it
with my own eyes.
The insatiable birds
picking at his corpse.
The villagers
butchered his remains,
ripped him open like
a sacrificial lamb.
There he lay,
face down in the dirt,
the birds pecking and clawing
until the only trace
of what had once been my son
was clean, white bone.
You cannot imagine
so magnificent a sight!
Tenba's soul reclaimed
by the earth.
Nature's glorious plan
come full circle!
Until that moment,
I'd never truly appreciated
the beauty of death.
[GOKU]
My whole body's gone numb.
[TENJIN] It was then
that I realized my purpose--
to carry on that grand,
empyrean ideal
and sanctify the soul's
journey back to its source!
I have been burdened
with a mission divine!
[TENJIN yells]
[GOJYO]
Real poetry there. Bravo.
Hell, I'd have believed
you if you hadn't
gone and named a bird after
your dearly departed son.
You're insane.
There's no "mission divine,"
you're just blinded by grief.
Shut up! His death
meant something.
[GOKU]
Tenjin.
[gasps]
[GOKU] I thought about
what you asked yesterday.
What happens after we die?
Honestly, I have no clue.
But whatever's waiting
on the other side,
wherever our loved ones
go once we've said
our last goodbyes, they're
still with us in a way.
In our hearts.
So as long as they're
memory's alive,
they're not lost.
Tenba. Please don't fly away.
No! Don't leave me! Wait!
[GOJYO]
You're an idiot, you know that?
[GOKU]
Sorry. I shouldn't 'a gone.
[GOJYO] You said it yourself,
it's more important
to focus on the life
right in front of you.
[GOKU]
Yeah. I know.
I just...
I just couldn't stop thinkin'
about it for some reason.
I had to talk to somebody.
[GOJYO] Well, from now on,
leave that sorta BS
to people with half a brain.
'Sides, it's not like the big
questions are goin' anywhere.
[GOKU] I love you guys.
You know that, right?
[GOJYO]
Are you gonna start crying?
[GOKU]
Tch! Cut me some slack,
I'm tryin' to have
a moment here!
[GOJYO] I just saved your
ass! Cut me some slack!
[TENJIN grunting]
[TENJIN]
Ah.
I see, you've brought
the whole gang back, huh?
Bear with me, son.
Soon. I promise.
That's a good boy.
[GOJYO] Episode 4:
"Nataku." Don't miss it.
[GOJYO]
Ready, and...
[GOKU, HAKKAI, SANZO, GOJYO]
Ura Sai!
[SANZO]
Hm.
[toilet flushes]