[SHARAK chanting]
[DOKUGAKUJI]
A fellow spirit steered me
from my collision
course with death.
Kou...
[DOKUGAKUJI] I will not let him
walk his path alone. Ever.
Where he goes, it is
my duty to follow.
[SANZO grunts]
[KOUGAIJI] What's the matter?
Why not use the Makai Tenjo?
There's no sport killing
you if it's this easy.
For heaven's sake are you
really that defenseless
without your friends?
Get up and do something!
Heh. Sorry I'm not
more engaging.
There's no sport using
my best trick against you.
[KOUGAIJI]
Is that a fact?
Then I trust you'll
excuse me if I put an end
to this farce
out of sheer boredom!
Don't hold back!
This may be your
one-and-only chance!
Engokuki!
[MONSTER 8A roars]
[yelling]
[DEMON 9B yells]
What's with these guys?
Every time I smack one down,
five more show up.
Wait a sec. Aren't you...?
What are the odds?
You're that kid from
the Sanzo party.
I remember you now!
Wasn't your name all weird?
Somethin' kinda flashy.
It'll come to me...
Is it Zuccini the Magician?
That can't be ri--
[ZAKURO] Zakuro! Also known
as the master of illusion!
Ring any bells?
What are doing all
the way out here?
Well, I, uh,
might've experienced
a reversal of fortune.
[ZAKURO]
After helping you,
word spread that
I was a traitor.
I was even rumored
to have joined you!
My fellow demons hunted
me like a dog.
I was an outcast!
I will shake this pariah
status whatever the cost.
They will respect me.
If I must fight
alongside my kinsman
wherever they choose
to strike, so be it!
Oh, wow.
You really have fallen
on hard times.
[ZAKURO] And it's your fault,
captain obvious!
Hang on.
If you're here, that means
it's a safe assumption
Sanzo Genjo himself can't
be very far away.
Actually he's at the Kouten
compound for now.
[ZAKURO]
That speeds things up, then.
I'll defeat him,
storm the temple,
pilfer the Kouten Scripture,
and leverage it to win
my people's trust!
Huh?
But, first things first:
I'll deal with you.
Do not resist.
Look into my eyes!
But, I...
[GOKU gasping]
All too easy. Observe!
That fearsome weapon is as
flimsy as a wet noodle!
[screams] How'd you do that?!
Oh, dear. You're drowning
in a sea of flames!
[ZAKURO]
Formidable as you are in combat,
caught in my spell,
you are no more than a
mewling infant! [laughs]
[GOKU]
That's cheating!
No one breaks free of my power!
Ugh. Very well, let's plunge you
headlong into the briny deep!
Magic!
[GOKU grunts]
I don't think so!
[ZAKURO gasping]
Come on. 'S that all you got?
Make it difficult!
Uh. Wh... Where's your friends?
Genjo's at Kouten.
What about the others?
Are they at his side
defending the temple,
or did they scramble to
the outlying villages?
You expect me to tell you?!
Not that it really matters.
At the moment, you're all alone.
No one will come to your aid
in the midst of
such a barren land.
What?
[ZAKURO] From the desert,
there is no escape.
This is your prison.
Here you will stay
forever. Alone.
That's not true.
[GOKU]
Where am I?
I don't know.
Probably doesn't
make a difference.
When you're in the dark,
what's the point of
whining about the sun?
Honestly.
This could be the
deepest dungeon
in the whole universe
for all I care.
Freedom. Loneliness.
What do those things mean
in a place like this?
[DEMON 9F]
Die!
Just keep croppin' up,
one right after another.
How many more of these
morons are there, seriously?
[MAN 9A] Fire! Don't let
them get any closer!
Keep shooting!
[DEMON 9G grunts]
[gasps]
[DEMON 9H chuckles]
[DEMON 9I yells]
Lookin' a little pale there.
There's no real point trying
to save somebody else
if it winds up gettin'
you killed, am I right?
Don't worry about me.
[DEMONS yelling]
Bastards!
[ZAKURO chuckles]
[ZAKURO] No one's coming.
You're trapped for all time.
Resign yourself to your fate.
Eternal solitude.
[ZAKURO]
There you'll sit, forever.
While you contemplate
loneliness,
I'll be heading to Kouten.
I'd better be quick.
Wouldn't want Kougaiji
beating me to the punch,
now do we?
[GOKU]
Kougaiji?
[ZAKURO]
You hadn't put it together yet?
He planned the attack.
This was his brainchild
from start to finish.
[ZAKURO] The outlying villages
were a distraction.
With the bulk of Sharak's
forces defending them,
he could lay siege
to the temple.
[ZAKURO]
Sanzo Genjo is strong,
but without his loyal followers,
Kougaiji could subdue
him in a single blow.
[GOKU]
San... zo...
Sure, I'll take you with me.
It's not like I have
much of a choice.
What?!
Oh, yeah. Totally knew that.
My friends will always
be there for me.
Sometimes life drives
a wedge between us,
but deep down, in our hearts,
we're together!
[ZAKURO gasping]
Impossible!
[ZAKURO]
Why isn't it working?!
[groans]
[GOKU] Kougaiji's behind this!
I have to hurry!
[DEMONS groaning]
[HAKKAI] The dark aura robs
demons of self-control.
[DEMON 9L groans]
[HAKKAI] This far out West, its
effects are more pronounced
than we've seen elsewhere.
Staggeringly so.
[HAKKAI] Gojyo being
half demon, half human,
it's difficult to predict
what affect
his exposure will have
on him. However...
I know what it is to go berserk.
The terror of it.
[HAKKAI]
Friend, foe, total stranger.
You bear your fangs at everyone.
When I was in the throes
of bloodlust,
Gojyo was there to check me.
[HAKKAI] Will I be able
to return the favor?
[DEMONS groan]
[HAKKAI]
Am I powerful enough?
Can I stop him?
[horse whinnies]
[footsteps]
[MAN 9B]
It's Goku!
We have to get back to the
temple! There's no time to lose!
[KOUGAIJI]
That's it. It's over.
[gasps]
[SANZO]
I though you wanted to end this.
Way to be a hypocrite.
If that's all you can manage,
killing me isn't in your future.
What's the deal?
Not to be facetious,
but frankly I expected better.
[KOUGAIJI] He's shielding
himself with the scripture!
[KOUGAIJI] You're mad!
Why would you go that far?
[SANZO]
You really have to ask?
I think the real question here,
is why wouldn't you?
Impossible!
He shouldn't be able to move!
[SANZO] You could've
finished me, you know.
That move was enough to
put me in the ground.
Trouble is, it skewed
slightly off target
instead of hitting me dead-on.
I was essentially helpless,
yet you hesitated
just long enough
to let my instincts kick in
and dodge the strike.
Dumbass.
Silence!
[SANZO] That's always been
your problem, hasn't it?
You don't commit.
You always second-guess yourself
when what a bad guy needs
to do is go all-in.
It's why you'll never stand
a chance of defeating us.
[yells]
Shut up!
Genjo!
[SANZO]
What the...?
What powerful aura is this?
[SHARAK chanting]
[yells]
[DOKUGAKUJI grunts]
You're not gonna lay so
much as a finger on her!
[DOKUGAKUJI]
You protect her nobly,
but I do this for my master!
[KOUGAIJI groaning]
Ah! What the hell's that?
[DEMON 9O] I don't understand.
Where's this energy coming from?
It's outside!
[DEMON 9O gasps]
Wait, is it that kid?
Enemy threat present.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Sixteen meters north
by northwest.
Two humanoid types.
[SANZO] Is he a demon?
No, I don't think so.
Get out of there!
Elimination.
[KOUGAIJI, SANZO grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
Kou!
[KOUGAIJI]
What's happening?
His aura is scorching.
I can feel it.
[KOUGAIJI]
Who are you?
Enemy threat.
[KOUGAIJI growls]
Elimination.
[KOUGAIJI groans]
Kou!
[DOKUGAKUJI] I still remember
the first time we met.
[DOKUGAKUJI panting]
[DOKUGAKUJI] You looked just
like my little brother.
[DOKUGAKUJI]
Those piercing violet eyes.
That crimson hair.
[yells]
[DOKUGAKUJI] That cold,
tough-as-nails attitude.
Act, really. Largely trivial
similarities, I suppose.
[yelling]
[DOKUGAKUJI] And yet,
you most certainly saved me.
Whatever path you
saw fit to walk,
we would gladly follow you
to the ends of the earth
without a thought.
Our true leader!
Kou. I owe you my life.
You are my everything.
My guiding light.
My fate.
[SANZO] He's not demonic.
His aura is too strong.
What is he, then?
Surely not a human being.
[NATAKU]
Target chosen.
Power level confirmed triple A.
Likely a relation of Gyumaou.
Probably the son, Kougaiji.
Implementing failsafe strategy.
Ensuring death.
Uh! Kou!
[DOKUGAKUJI] No more.
I won't run from myself.
[KOUGAIJI gasping]
[chanting]
[HASSAN grunting]
[NATAKU]
Enemy status: unknown.
For the time being,
I will return home.
[SANZO]
Hey.
What the hell are you?
[NATAKU]
I do not know.
[GOKU] Whoa! What in the
world happened here?!
Sanzo! Where are you?!
[SANZO]
Stupid monkey. Late as usual.
--[SANZO grunting]
--[thud]
[GOKU]
Sanzo!
What's go--?
[GOKU gasping]
[MAN 9C]
She did it! She really did it!
[MAN 9D]
The chant's done!
Great.
So we can all relax and head
back to Kouten now, yeah?
[HAKKAI]
Indeed.
Sharak completed
the incantation.
Hopefully that means
Sanzo is all right.
[HAKKAI] Now that the
barrier's been restored,
we should be safe.
If Gojyo's body undergoes
further change, however...
Who can say?
[HAKKAI]
This is less than ideal.
His proximity to the dark
aura may prove him
to be more demon
than I suspected.
[HASSAN panting]
Nice job you did there.
Huh. Don't be an ass-kisser.
That's my line.
What the...?
[GOKU]
Huh. Weird.
I was about to call
him something.
[SANZO groaning]
[GOKU gasps]
Sanzo!
[TALCHIE]
The stars are never wrong.
What happened?
This isn't real.
[TALCHIE]
Hard as a man may struggle.
Desperately as he may wish.
Be they high or be they low,
all forms of life
are fragmentary.
Eventually the rut will cease.
[TALCHIE]
Try though they might--
from Shakamuni's hand,
there is no escape.
[groaning]
[KOUGAIJI]
Hey, Dokugaku. Wake up!
[KOUGAIJI] How did he do it?
How did he drag me this far?
It'll be all right.
I'll, summon a flying dragon!
[DOKUGAKUJI]
Beautiful beyond words...
That crimson, so deep,
so utterly captivating.
It drew me.
Seems I saved you this time.
[door creaks]
[DOKUGAKUJI]
What am I saying?
Bit late in day to
put things right.
[KOUGAIJI]
Damn it, stop trying to talk!
Hey, Kou.
I wanted just to say thank you.
You gave my life meaning.
Wish I had better words.
I'm sorry.
That's all I could
think of at the moment.
Please! Don't do this.
Just stop!
C'mon, don't cry.
[GOJYO]
I'm not crying.
Screw you.
[KOUGAIJI cries]
[screams]
[GOJYO]
Episode ten: "Imperial Order."
Don't miss it.