[NARRATOR]
Shangri-la.
[NARRATOR] A land where
harmony exists side-by-side
with chaos, science with magic,
and human beings with demons.
Alas, the delicate age-old
balance has begun to erode.
A dark aura encroaches
from the West,
sowing evil in its wake.
The soil has withered,
demons have turned violent,
human beings live in fear.
A utopia, once upheld
by the twin pillars
of Faith and Civilization,
lay in ruins, swallowed
whole by darkness.
[gasps]
[DONKEY whinnies]
[gasping]
They're behind us! Hurry!
[MAN 1A yelps]
[DEMON 1A] We were tryin'
to be covert, but no,
you just had to notice us.
Is it me,
or do humans seem
paranoid these days?
Don't you give me that look!
Where does a filthy
animal like you get off
snarling your teeth at us?
[gasps]
What's it gonna be?
Wanna die like your buddy here?
Or d'you fancy a deal?
Your life in exchange
for showing us the rock
your village is hiding under?
Go! Run for it!
[panting]
I see. Right then.
Suit yourself.
Death it is.
[DEMON 1C yells]
[RANDOM DEMON 1A groans]
[DEMONS gasp]
[DEMON 1E] What the--?
Where'd these guys come from?
Get out of our way!
[SANZO]
You talkin' to us?
You're the assholes
blockin' the road.
[RANDOM DEMON 1C]
Oh, shit.
[DEMONS groaning]
[yells]
C'mon! Let's go!
How? Wait? Who are you?
[stomachs growling]
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
Uh...
[MAN 1A]
Okay.
[MAN 1B]
Damn it. What's wrong with you?
Why would you bring
outsiders here?
Have you two idiots forgotten
the position we're in?
I didn't have a choice.
They saved our lives. I had to!
Our donkey was
killed in the fight
and these men were good enough
to let us load our
things in their car.
[WOMAN 1A] But, they look
so seedy. How old are they?
[MAN 1D] Word has it some
great priest is heading out
West to slaughter demons.
Could be they have
something to do with him.
[WOMAN 1B]
You're talking about the one
they call Sanzo, right?
I mean, I hear he travels
with a entourage,
but aren't they supposed
to be the picture
of nobility and grace?
[MAN 1B]
Who cares?
Can we focus on clearing
out of here, please?
It's only a matter of time
before the demons find us.
--[gasps]
--[MAN 1C] Exactly!
[snoring]
[TAMURO] That smell.
Is it from being on the road?
They reek.
[HAKKAI]
Terribly sorry.
You were kind enough to feed
a group of total strangers,
and we fall asleep.
[GOJYO]
I can't remember the last time
we had a proper meal,
let alone a decent nap.
[TAMURO] It's fine.
You guys saved my dad, so...
Where'd you come from?
[HAKKAI]
Chang'an.
[TAMURO]
Chang'an?
Way out East. Quite the place.
Biggest, liveliest city
in all of Shangri-la.
Nowhere quite like it.
Surprised you managed
to get this far in one piece.
Whew. Yeah, 's been
pretty rough this time.
I thought I was
a goner for sure.
Hah! From what? Starving?
You've survived a helluva
lot worse than this.
I'm gonna have me a bath.
But, we've imposed
on them quite enough.
[TAMURO]
It's no trouble.
The adults may not
like it, though.
You're probably all right
if you can stay quiet.
If you make too much
noise, they beat you.
See? We're in trouble now!
Yeah? So why are you blaming me?
Ah, guess they prefer things
on the peaceful side.
Seems a little tucked away, too.
Not many villages around here.
Populated ones, at least.
The few we saw looked
like they'd been raided.
[TAMURO] Most of folks
cleared out of this region
a while back.
[GOJYO]
Huh. Now that you mention it,
we have been running into
a lot of demons lately.
[GOKU]
Gee, ya think?
'S why my clothes
are all torn up.
[TAMURO]
Remember the drawbridge
you crossed to get here?
We only use it when
we absolutely have to.
Demons would've found us
ages ago if we left it open.
Still, though...
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
Damn shame.
As you can see,
we tend to be suspicious
of outsiders nowadays.
Been living in fear so long,
we've forgotten how
to be hospitable.
Hardly turn a light on
once the sun goes down.
It's a modest place, sure,
but we were cheerful
once upon a time.
I'm sure you were.
It's fine, We won't
get comfortable.
We have some business
to attend to.
Yes, well. Uh.
In any event, I'm afraid
I have to ask you gents
to stay with us
till tomorrow morning.
And why is that?
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
We only let the drawbridge down
at sunup and dusk. I'm sorry.
We just can't risk
demons getting in.
[TAMURO] Dad. They'd like
a bath, if that's okay.
[TAMURO'S FATHER] Ah. S'pose
you could use one, eh?
Be my guest.
[HAKKAI] I suggest we
split off into pairs.
Whoa. Hold on a sec.
So, I finally get to take a bath
and you're saying it has
to be with one of you?
[SANZO]
I'm bathing it alone.
You three knock yourselves out.
What?
How do we pick who's first?
Rock-paper-scissors?
[GOJYO, SANZO]
Hey.
[HAKKAI]
Ready? One, two, three!
[GOKU]
Ah! This feels amazing!
'Least they have hot water,
even if I have to share it
Huh. Look at this.
Hakkai should cut my hair.
Jeez. Gotta say, this
place is a lot different
than what I'm used to.
Hey! Cheer up!
At least the food's
delicious, right?
Ugh. Is that really
all you ever notice?
[GOKU]
What'd you expect?
We're in the western
part of Shangri-la.
Things are supposed
to be different.
Speaking of which,
how much further to India?
[thud]
[WOMAN screams]
[GOJYO, GOKU scream]
What's the matter with you?
Uh, they asked us to be
quite if you recall.
Help! There was a ghost!
What?
There! She was at
the window! I swear!
[REI] ♪ The peaches
grow so brightly. ♪
♪ So flavorful and
strong standing there, ♪
♪ underneath all
the tall trees. ♪
--♪ Sweetly longing for... ♪
--Her name's Rei.
She hasn't always been
like that. Her husband died.
We basically treat her
like a nuisance now.
[MAN 1D] What have we you
told you about singing?
[RANDOM MAN 1C]
You have to be silent!
[TAMURO] The thing about
her husband, though...
He didn't just die--
he was murdered!
Demons attacked him on the road.
He was on his way back
from a supply run,
just like my dad.
Talk about being between
a rock and hard place.
He was so close to the village.
When they attacked, he led 'em
straight to the drawbridge.
We all heard.
We all knew he was in trouble,
but do ya think we
lowered it for him?
'Course not.
Well, can't say I blame them.
If they'd given him a chance,
he might still be alive today!
We're monsters!
We sacrificed one
of our own people!
This place. I hate it with
ever fiber of my being.
[HAKKAI] That's the anger
talking. He doesn't mean it.
Deep down, he understands
the demons are responsible.
[SANZO]
Hey. Put some clothes on.
You're scaring the locals.
Are those men naked?
We were fools to let them in.
--[GOKU] Uh...
--[GOJYO] My bad.
[REI]
♪ In the shadows, he wait-- ♪
[MAN 1D]
I told you to stop singing!
Darling, please!
Don't be so harsh!
We have to be silent!
It's the only way to survive!
The demons find this place,
that'll be it for us!
Do forgive me, Rei.
I feel for you, honestly,
but we're all suffering here.
Her husband was a damn fool.
Tamuro's father made it
back alive, didn't he?
[MAN 1D] What's done is
done. It was him or us.
[GOKU]
An actual futon!
Yeah, sorry the
room's so cramped,
but it's all we've got.
There's nothing
to apologize for.
[GOJYO]
Think fast!
Hey, four walls, a ceiling
and a nice futon?
What else could we need?
I'll make certain my friends
settle down presently.
Thanks. Get a good night's rest.
See you boys bright n' early.
Thank you again, sir.
Good night.
[GOJYO] He-He-Hey! Flashy bit
o' craftsmanship, huh?
You could say that,
though I believe a
better word is exotic.
We may still be within
the borders of Shangri-la,
but this region is
a world unto itself.
[SANZO]
Yeah.
Goes to show how far
West we've traveled.
The dark aura's influence
around here is strong.
The sheer number of demons
we keep running into
in these parts is
all the proof I need.
Feels as though we're
behind enemy lines,
fighting for our lives.
So, I'm guessin' this is
your way of telling us
to prepare ourselves.
Thank you, but,
given things lately,
we kinda get the point.
[GOKU]
Seriously, though. I'm stoked!
Everything's so different here,
it's hard not to be!
It's like we're on
a journey for real!
[SANZO] What the hell
are you talking about?
We've been on the
road for two years.
Being a monkey sure
does have it perks.
The water they use here
doesn't agree with me.
Yeah, you don't wear
diarrhea sprite very well.
I'm not a diarrhea sprite!
I have a sensitive
stomach! Shut up!
Okay. Settle down.
We have an early day tomorrow.
Anybody who oversleeps
gets left behind.
[GOJYO]
Oh, come on!
Don't spread out like
you're the only one
with futon privileges!
You're not a king.
[SANZO]
No. I'm Sanzo.
[GOJYO]
Wow.
[REI] ♪ The peaches
grow so brightly. ♪
♪ So flavorful and strong
standing there, ♪
♪ underneath all
the tall trees. ♪
♪ Sweetly longing for our song ♪
♪ Who do I spy,
standing there, ♪
♪ In the sha-- ♪
--[TOWNSPEOPLE screaming]
--[crashing]
[RANDOM MAN 1A]
Help!
[ROOSTER crows]
[MAN groans]
No, they're here!
[gasps]
[RANDOM DEMON 1K] I see you
in there! C'mon, open up!
Who the hell is that?
We're in big trouble!
Demons have overrun the village!
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
What?
Weird.
I could've sworn this
door opened inwards.
[GOJYO] You're disturbing
my beauty rest!
This way, please.
[yelling]
[GOKU yells]
[DEMON 1M groans]
What the...? Who're they?
Just some guys you've
woken up two hours too soon.
You maggots have no idea
the bloodbath you're in for.
[DEMON 1S]
Pure white robes.
Silver pistol.
Intensely purple eyes.
Golden hair.
Oh, no.
Attended by three
demon-like followers!
Could... Could it
possibly be...?
[DEMON 1S]
The Genzo Sanzo Party?
They come from the East.
Wherever they go,
it is said mountains
of demon corpses
darken the sky in their wake.
They're the most ruthless band
of outlaws in all of Shangri-la!
It's them! We're
totally screwed!
Ah! No! It's not possible!
They vanished ages ago!
Last I heard, they're
supposed to be dead!
That's kind of a
rude thing to say.
Well, damn.
Ya know, I thought it was
strange none of these lowlifes
were cursing our name
while we slaughtered them.
We are rather filthy.
It's difficult to
recognize anyone beneath
so many layers of dirt,
or so I imagine.
You're kidding, right?
[REI]
♪ ...peaches grow so brightly. ♪
♪ So flavorful and strong... ♪
Easy, fellas.
Put down your weapon.
Fun's over.
Somebody help her!
[DEMON 1H] One false move
and the songbird gets it.
Something tells me a
holy man wouldn't want
a woman's death
on his conscience.
Ugh.
Again?
How many times have we
been in this situation?
Well, there you have it.
Villains are always
true to form.
I'll say that much for them.
[DEMON 1H laughs]
Well, whaddya know?
I had a feeling this crazy
bitch would come in handy
if I let her live
long enough. All right!
Enough with the singing!
Let go of her!
[WOMAN 1E]
Tamuro! Don't!
Is that it?
We stand around like last time
and watch one of our own die?!
[MAN 1F]
What choice do we have?
She reaps what she sows, kid.
Far as I'm concerned,
it's her fault
the demons got here
in the first place.
To hell with her!
[TAMURO growls]
What is wrong with you?!
Don't you know
what she's singing?
Listen to her!
She's not just spouting off
some random nonsense!
[REI] ♪ For so long, the tree
stood so proud and strong ♪
♪ as the proudest man... ♪
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
The festival.
She's singing our festival song!
[TAMURO] Every last one of us
lives in fear of demons.
Rei's no different.
Her grief just drove her to
madness. But still, here she is.
Passing our song
on to the children.
She's still in there!
Some part of her doesn't
want it to be forgotten.
Some part of her
looks to the future,
to a time when--when we can
sing like in the old days.
[TAMURO'S FATHER]
I'm sorry.
It's wrong of us
to cast her off.
We were all just so
focused on getting by.
What becomes of a village
when it forgets its own song?
When its children can't play,
or its people laugh?
[SANZO] Look, none of
this really has anything
to do with us,
but we do owe you one.
Hospitality goes
a long way, after all.
If you want us to do
something, say the word.
[DEMONS panting]
Ugh, poor thing.
I... I was dead wrong.
Bring her back!
Save Rei, I'm begging you!
[DEMONS groan]
[SANZO]
There's a lesson here, I think.
Wherever you go, whoever
you're dealing with.
Look close enough and
you'll see that, deep down,
the same hearts beats
in all of us.
[GOJYO] Ha! Nice. Couldn't've
said it better myself.
The more things change, the
more they stay the same, huh?
We've got a problem
on our hands, people!
The two demons that got away
are making a break
for the drawbridge!
They'll get away!
We can't let them
walk out of here!
Oh, god! If they bring
back reinforcements,
we're done for!
All the other demons will
know where to find us!
[gasps] Hakuryu!
[HAKURYU chirps]
Welp. Thanks for the grub!
Oh, and the futon!
Sorry to duck out
unceremoniously,
but time is of the essence.
Oh, don't worry.
We'll take care of the runaways.
It's the least we could do.
There goes an odd bunch.
Who'd they say they were again?
Oh, yeah. I dunno.
Let's call 'em The Squall.
[DEMONS panting]
[DEMON 1AC]
You've gotta be shittin' me!
We don't stand a chance
against those guys!
They're unreal!
[engine revs]
[DEMON 1AC gasps]
--[screams]
--Son of a--!
[DEMON 1AC]
Go! We can make it!
[DEMON 1AD] Let's see
the bastards catch us now!
Good luck!
Brace yourselves!
[DEMONS scream]
[GOKU] ♪ The peaches
grow so brightly. ♪
♪ Flavorful and strong ♪
♪ Blooming sweetly
in the orchard... ♪
[GOJYO]
♪ Blooming sweetly. ♪
[BOTH] ♪ Who do I spy,
standing there, ♪
♪ beneath the
tallest tree-- ♪
[SANZO]
Stop singing.
[HAKKAI] To be fair, that tune
does get suck in your head.
[SANZO]
Which I why I asked you to stop!
[GOKU] Ow! You never
let us have any fun!
[GOJYO] Like I said,
the more things change...
Anyone else feel like
we're stuck in a loop?
[HAKKAI laughs]
That's one way of looking at it.
What you call a loop some people
might refer to as our style.
So, uh, the sun
rises in the East.
Just like you predicted,
Talche. Nice one.
[TALCHE]
The stars do not lie.
The sun's path is eternal.
Forever and ever unchanging.
It rises in the East. Always.
Then sinks Westward.
To Earth.
It falls and the land
is engulfed in darkness.
Is that another one
of your prophesies?
Nay. Providence.
[SANZO]
Episode Two: "Cloud Mirror."
Don't miss it.
[GOJYO, GOKU, HAKKAI, SANZO]
Ready, and Ura Sai!
[singing fevtival tune]
Okay. Star Festival, huh?
Its exceedingly hard
to keep proper track
of what day it is when
you're out on the open road.
We mustn't lose sight of
the bigger picture here,
wouldn't you agree?
[GOJYO] "I wanna eat all
the meat buns." Shocking.
Does everything have
to be about food?
[GOKU]
Maybe! So what?
I noticed you wrote the word
"debauchery" on yours, Sanzo.
Wry as ever.
Every man wants that. Shut up.
Cheap dream if you ask me.
[GOKU]
Hm? How come Gojyo gets two?
I didn't write that, I swear.
[SANZO] Give us a break.
Who the hell else would?
[GOKU] Mm. Wait.
I take it back. This is...
--[car horn honks]
--[HAKURYU chirps]
[GOJYO, GOKU, HAKKAI, SANZO]
Ura Sai.
[GOKU singing festival tune]
[GOKU]
Where's yours, Sanzo?
If you can't
get it for yourself,
what's the point of wishing?
Stubborn as usual.
Let me just write
one for you, then.
"I wish my male
pattern baldness--"
[GOKU singing festival tune]