[GOKU]
What? Aw, c'mon!
But it's been several days now!
How come you guys won't
let me see him?
He's so sick he can't
have visitors anymore?
[LI TOUTEN'S WIFE]
I'm afraid so.
At least for the time being.
It's important Nataku
get plenty of rest.
I hate turning you away,
but there it is.
Okay.
Nothin' you can do about it
if he's not feelin' good.
Oh, well. Do you mind
giving him this for me?
Whenever someone's sick you
gotta give 'em flowers, right?
Um, traditionally...
Thanks, miss!
One more thing!
If it's not too much trouble,
tell him the kid
who's been comin'
around is named Goku!
[LI TOUTEN'S WIFE grunts]
[TENTEI] The mayhem enveloping
Earth knows no limit.
Overlooking such chaos tempts
a blemish on our prestige.
I order you and the forces
at your command to sortie,
Prince Nataku.
Do you accept?
Sire.
[KENREN]
Objection.
[NATAKU]
Mm?
Who speaks?
[KENREN] General Kenren
from the western army.
I answer to the Dragon King
of the western sea.
[SOLDIERS chatter]
[TENTEI]
State your business.
[KENREN]
Beg your pardon, Tentei.
Can't help but notice His
Highness Prince Nataku,
tough as he is,
hasn't quite healed
from his tangle with Gyumaou.
With all due respect,
I request that my
forces be dispatched
to fulfill this mission
in his place.
Outrage!
[NATAKU] It's him. He was with
that boy the other day.
[LI TOUTEN growls]
Are you arrogant enough
to suggest yourself
equal to Prince Nataku?
Not at all, Tentei.
Just a better option than
the "soldiers" who hide
behind him in battle and expect
to have their asses kissed.
Kenren. That's enough
out of you.
[LI TOUTEN] I'll thank you not
to underestimate
his considerable
prowess, General.
Soldiers or not, my son
is an incomparable warrior.
Him being wounded
is of no concern.
He faces battle without care
for the cost to his person,
even unto death!
Isn't that so,
my little war god?
[NATAKU]
Yes.
[TENTEI]
You may take your leave, Nataku.
Sire.
[thump]
[NATAKU]
Thank you.
It's settled.
There's nothing more
to discuss here.
Let us escort the good general
to a place of self-reflection.
Bosatsu.
What in Heaven's name
are you wearing?
[KANZEON] Something I found.
Lovely, don't you think?
[JIROSHIN]
"Found"?
Yes. An indelicate soul
thought nothing
of tossing it in the garbage.
[KENREN]
Aw. You came down to see me.
I've always known you
for a hotheaded imbecile.
But to push it so far...
Never a dull moment, huh?
We gotta keep things lively.
I'm your superior officer.
Why wouldn't you ask
for my help?
If I'd made our case
to the Tentei,
you might've had a prayer.
Like it would'a
made a difference.
Besides, why deny me the kick
of speakin' my mind?
'S my second-best talent.
Was it worth getting pummeled
and thrown into a dirty cell?
Eh. 'S not that big of a deal.
Gettin' roughhoused
ain't got nothin'
on Nataku's parting jab.
Hell of a thing seein' a kid
his age act so tough.
I'm not sure what hurts worse--
his fist or his attitude.
He's a stout one, all right,
but that façade hides more
n' his fair share of pain.
What do you mean he was relieved
of his duties as general?
The demotion didn't
last a fortnight.
Tenpou appealed to the higher
ups and had him reinstated.
Being a field marshal,
he outranks Li Touten,
much to his chagrin, of course.
Then again,
we are speaking of a man
more than happy to use his
son's title for personal gain.
I doubt that'll be
the end of it.
[KONZEN grunts]
But... No one told me of this!
Why would you expect
to be apprised of
something so trivial?
[KONZEN] Meaning I'm the only
one not in the loop.
The brass are up to something.
The army knows it, and here
I am, out in the cold.
This is bullshit.
Brat.
[gasps]
[KANZEON] Information doesn't
come of its own accord.
One must make an effort.
How long before the
little monkey stops
likening you to the sun?
[TENTEI] Most commendable,
Prince Nataku.
Yet again, word of your
courageous deeds
reaches far and wide.
[LI TOUTEN] Sire. We are
unworthy of such praise.
Our most humble thanks.
[NATAKU]
You didn't lift a damn finger.
[TENTEI] You are free to leave
our presence. Rest well.
Yes, sire.
[GOKU]
Nataku!
[gasps]
Hey, hey! Over here! It's me!
It's good to have you back!
[gasps] You're that kid.
Uh. Father?
[LI TOUTEN]
Do not acknowledge him.
That precocious child is
a heretic born of Earth.
Kill him.
He will weaken our
standing in the court.
His very presence
poses a threat.
We must have done with him.
Strike before it's too late.
Heaven cannot bear
two disgraces.
Where you goin'? Nataku, wait!
C'mon, there's no way
you've forgotten about me!
Hey Nataku!
[footsteps]
[KONZEN]
Was he excited to see you?
Not exactly.
Is something wrong?
[KONZEN] Quit sulking
already and go to bed.
It's not the end of the world.
[GOKU]
I'm not sulking.
What do you call it, then?
[GOKU]
I dunno. I just...
I think Nataku hates me.
I mean, he recognized me.
I could see it in his eyes.
If he didn't acknowledge you,
I'm sure he had his reasons.
[GOKU]
What kind of reason is there
for ignoring your friend?!
Besides, the first time we met,
he's the one who talked to me.
I figured he was just
lonely or something.
Poor guy. I get it.
I was alone for a long time.
I know how it feels.
When I get lonely, it's kinda
like my chest gets heavy.
[KONZEN] Goku. Perhaps taking
you in was a mistake.
You don't belong in Heaven.
[GOKU gasps]
[KONZEN] This is no place
for someone like you.
A lot of shady characters
will try to use you as a pawn.
Just as they use Nataku.
[KONZEN] Get some sleep. I'll
talk to Kanzeon tomorrow.
It's better for everyone
if you go back to Earth.
She'll understand--
What're you doing, Goku?!
[GOKU]
Stop it! Let go!
Calm down and listen to me
for once in your life!
[GOKU] I have been listening!
You're wrong!
Tenpou would never
use me as a pawn,
and neither would Kenren!
I don't understand,
why would you tell me
I don't belong here?
I know you're mad
at me all the time,
but you just gave me a name!
[groans]
Konzen. I'm sorry!
I swear I didn't mean to
hurt you! Are you okay?
Konzen?
Listen to me. Quit likening
me to the sun, okay?
What's that mean?
I don't shine.
I seldom radiate warmth.
I just take advantage
of being different
to give my life some meaning.
I can't talk like Tenpou,
or fight my way to hell
and back like Kenren.
But you know what?
Here lately I find myself
thinking an awful lot
about I can do.
Your fault, actually.
You're talkin' funny.
Did you hit your head?
Look, the bottom line is:
forget what I said.
You're not going anywhere.
Okay!
[GOKU]
So, uh...
True story.
The first time we met,
I thought you looked pretty.
I'd never seen anyone like you.
Thought to myself, "look at him.
If he'd just smile
he'd be even prettier."
Doesn't really suit you, though.
Wow. You have a death wish,
don't you?
[GOKU]
That night,
Tenpou and Kenren
dropped by out of nowhere.
They wanted us to
look at a tree?
[TENPOU]
...look absolutely gorgeous.
Flowers in the moonlight.
You guys have nothing
better to do?
[TENPOU] Well, there's
no call to be rude.
Earth has many foods,
but without a doubt,
among the finest and
most indispensable
of its fare is ramen.
Konzen makes me ramen sometimes,
but it turns out really gross.
Tastes like feet.
[TENPOU]
I should make you some.
[GOKU]
Please!
[KENREN] All right, little man.
How's your tree-climbing?
Excellent! Ha! Last one
to the top's a rotten egg!
Hey, don't break your neck.
I'm gonna laugh when you
fall on your ass, you drunk.
Talk to me.
Uh?
[KONZEN]
Is it possible for two war gods
to reside in Heaven at once?
[TENPOU] So it's crossed
your mind, too, I see.
Multiple war gods existed
alongside each other
at one time. However...
...if perchance our
friend is elevated
to share the title with Nataku,
Li Touten would most certainly
see him as an interloper,
and act accordingly.
Moreover, you would be
the guardian of a war god.
Pitting you and the secretary
in direct competition.
[GOKU] Seriously. The cherry
blossoms were amazing.
I wish Nataku could've been
there, he'd have loved it.
Sorta made me sad.
Here's a golden idea:
why don't you worrywarts
stop talkin' shop
and enjoy the saké?
Yes, yes. We know.
Duly noted, thanks.
I hate to be the one
to point this out,
but the flowers here
aren't half as beautiful
as what they got down on Earth.
Aren't cherry blossoms
the same everywhere?
[KENREN]
Nah. Depends on where they live.
[KONZEN] Is that a fact? I'll
have to see them for myself.
[gasps]
[KONZEN groaning]
Oh! My bad! Sorry!
[KENREN laughs]
Nice catch, Konzen!
I think we found
what you're good at!
[KONZEN] Of all the places
you could've landed,
did it have to be my head?!
[GOKU]
I said I was sorry!
[KENREN]
You chose to sit there.
[KONZEN]
Excuse me?!
[TENPOU]
Goku must weigh over 200 pounds
with those shackles on.
The branch was bound to snap.
[laughs]
[GOKU]
I was with the people I loved.
We were all laughing.
Not much, I s'pose,
but all I ever wanted.
It was wonderful. I could've
lived like that forever.
[LI TOUTEN sighs] Dear child,
again you've been injured.
It must hurt. You poor thing.
Nataku. My treasure,
my sole reason for existence.
My pride and joy above all else.
[NATAKU]
The moment we're alone,
Father's words are tender,
encouraging.
[LI TOUTEN] I am you.
We are one and the same.
[NATAKU] This is the side of him
that frightens me most.
Though, I don't tremble.
[LI TOUTEN] Nataku.
I am nothing without you.
Nothing.
[NATAKU]
I freeze, unable to move.
This is all I know of love.
[TENPOU] Not long after
accepting my post
as field marshal,
colossal demons
began appearing on
Earth in droves.
An onslaught of epidemic
proportions.
Try though we might,
their numbers proved
more than Heaven's
forces could handle.
[TENPOU] We mustn't
underestimate Li Touten.
He's a most ambitious man
who soared through
the ranks on the strength
of his singular mind.
His great weakness is
a failure to endure
the acrimony foisted
upon him by the peerage
for having dared come
from a ruined family.
He hates his betters.
Crushing them is his obsession.
[TENTEI]
Who is this?
[LI TOUTEN]
One permitted to kill, my liege.
I give you the war god,
His Highness Prince Nataku.
[TENPOU]
So it went.
You're familiar with the
boy's work in that vein
since he was admitted
into court, I presume.
This is purely
speculation, but...
...it is my belief that
Nataku's true identity
is a secret between our Tentei
and the upper echelons.
Only they know.
I think Li Touten created
him, artificially.
The boy functions as a weapon.
Gossip is currency in
the trenches, of course,
but one persistent
rumor intrigues me.
Our soldiers say he's
half god, half demon.
We would never sanction
such a thing.
Indeed. And yet it has been.
Evidently Heaven required
a warrior so fierce
they deigned to do
the unthinkable.
A need Li Touten was only
too happy to fill,
perhaps even one
he manufactured.
What are you saying?
[TENPOU] Battle upon battle.
An overtaxed military.
Convenient, wouldn't you say?
[TENPOU] I can't speak to
the man's ultimate goal,
but I know beyond
a shadow of a doubt
he'll do whatever he can
to rid himself of Goku.
Our friend jeopardizes
his leverage.
Nataku himself
might do the deed.
[GOKU]
What deed?
[TENPOU, KONZEN gasp]
[KONZEN]
Goku.
What are you guys talking about?
Nataku's supposed
to be my friend.
You don't think he'd...
He'd never try to hurt me!
Wait a minute! Ugh! Idiot!
Goku, hold on please!
[GOKU]
I don't believe it!
He wouldn't!
We're buddies! He told me!
We're gonna find
hiding places together!
Wait! Hold on!
I'll just tell him my name!
That's it!
[KONZEN]
Come back!
[KANZEON] How long
before the little monkey
stops likening you to the sun?
[KONZEN] Look at me.
What am I good for?
I can't even keep up
with a child!
Damn it! I'm useless!
[MAN 4C] War god,
Prince Nataku, come forth.
[footsteps]
Looks like the Prince's army
is being dispatched again.
Guess we get to sit back while
he does all the heavy lifting.
Good having him around,
isn't it?
[KENREN] Where do they get off
acting like this is okay?
Rotten sons of bitches.
[TENTEI] We leave this
imminent subjugation
in your capable hands,
Li Touten.
[LI TOUTEN]
Sire.
[GOKU]
Get off of me!
[MAN 5C]
Who is this kid?
[MAN 5D]
Quit struggling!
Nataku! It's not true, right?
They think you wanna kill me,
but you'd never do
something like that!
This isn't good.
[LI TOUTEN] Hmph. It would
appear you know too much
for your own good. Listening
to Tenpou, were we?
Neither here nor there.
Do it now.
It's time. Kill him.
Bastard!
[LI TOUTEN groans]
You're the one responsible for
this! If he wants to hurt me,
it's 'cause of what you've
been saying to him!
What the...? Hey.
Step away from
my father at once.
Filth. This man is my master.
Whatever he says,
whatever he does,
he is the sole reason
for my existence.
Those who would harm him
forfeit their lives.
Die!
Kenren!
Get outta here!
I see the general hasn't
learned his lesson.
Well, no matter. Go ahead
and kill them both.
Kenren, no!
Stop it, Nataku!
Why are you doing this?!
[KENREN] I can't let them fight.
It's too dangerous.
[KENREN, NATAKU grunting]
I asked you to stop.
Please, stop!
[TENPOU]
What is going on?
Yes, Nataku! Do your worst!
Obey me!
[TENPOU]
Vile man.
Pardon me.
[TENPOU gasps]
[LI TOUTEN]
Heh.
[TENPOU groans]
Tenpou!
We get it,
you make bold choices.
If we wanted an end
to this madness,
I had to do something, didn't I?
Huh. Guess we're all-in now.
I think it's safe to say
we've crossed the point
of no return, yes.
[NATAKU chanting]
[KENREN grunting]
[GOKU]
Kenren! Tenpou! Are you okay?!
[KENREN]
He's too strong.
This is the power of a war god!
For Heaven's sake,
rein the prince in!
We are in the presence
of the Tentei!
What difference does it make?
What?!
You're behaving as though
I ought to give a damn.
Make a run for it, Goku!
--[GOKU] No!
--Do it!
[LI TOUTEN]
Kill him.
Kill him. Kill him. Kill him!
[NATAKU whimpers]
[GOKU] Nataku, all I wanted...
was to tell you my name.
It's Goku.
[NATAKU]
Someday,
I'll show you all the
great hiding spots!
Raspberries grow in one of 'em!
Goku. Huh. Nice.
[NATAKU]
Someday...
[KONZEN grunting]
[KENREN gasps]
[TENPOU gasping]
[MAN 5F]
What is the meaning of this?!
Stupid kid.
We need a medic, now!
How could this have happened?
[NATAKU gasping]
[gasps]
Goku. There's something
I want...
I want to tell you...
Huh?
That tree... over there.
If you look way up high,
there's a bird's nest on top.
You see it, right?
[GOKU]
No. I don't. I... [cries]
Nataku, c'mon. I don't
know where to look!
Wake up and show me, please!
Unhand my son! I won't
have him desecrated.
[TENPOU]
Li Touten.
[LI TOUTEN] Fear not.
The war god still has his uses.
[gasps] Son of a bitch.
You pushed him past
the breaking point
and still you don't get it?!
Why couldn't he have
a normal childhood?!
What was the point?!
Why twist him so badly he'd
rather die than disobey you?!
[GOKU yells]
Goku!
--[MAN 5G grunts]
--[GOKU yelps]
Let go! Let go of me!
No! Don't!
The hell're you doing?!
Restrain the traitors!
Hold them back!
Goku. Goku!
[GOKU yells]
[ALL gasp]
What is this?
[KANZEON] Rather ferocious
little thing with golden eyes.
I thought you'd like to
come see for yourself.
G-Goku?
[KENREN]
Episode six: "Promise."
Don't miss it.
[KONZEN]
Ready, and...
[GROUP]
...Ura Sai.
Uh, man. Earth is hot as balls.
Shouldn't he be here by now?
[TENPOU] Sorry. Took me
a while to get ready.
[KENREN]
Hm?
Uh...
[GROUP]
Ura Sai.
Somethin' wrong?
Not precisely, no.
I just think our uniforms
could use some pizazz.
Like how?
Well, to begin with,
we should think cosplay.
[KENREN]
Eh... no.