Hey! Cut the BS already, huh?
What's the deal with you lately?
You tryin' to start somethin'?
Screw work-shopping your
joke delivery, jackass.
Learn how to lie.
[GOJYO groaning]
Let go of my hair!
Hold up, Gojyo.
You've got something
on your neck.
Like, a weird-looking mark.
Initializing deployment now.
So, yeah. That's, um,
a demon mark, I guess.
Did he have to know?
No point trying to keep
it under wraps.
What he knows doesn't
change the reality.
[GOKU] Man. When'd you go
berserk? Was it recent?
Nobody's gone berserk!
Son of a bitch.
Why'd it have to pop up
somewhere I can't even see?
Oh, god. Please tell me
it doesn't look lame.
Well, actually. It's kind
of swirly. Like, ice cream.
Yeah. That's it.
Or maybe frozen yogurt.
Let's not over-generalize.
It's more like an
artesian gelato cone.
You guys are not helping at all!
Damn it. Of all the times
for this stupid thing
to make an appearance.
[SANZO] It was bound to happen
sooner or later.
You're half demon,
there's no denying that fact.
Hakkai called it if you ask me.
Simply put, the further
West we've come
the more susceptible you are
to the dark aura's power.
Wait, but how come his ears
aren't all pointy and stuff?
He doesn't look like
a demon to me.
More like one of those gym bros,
with a tribal tattoo.
[GOJYO] What tribe, exactly?
The Ice Cream Men?
Look. It's fine. Any way you
slice it, I'm not a real demon.
We have no idea what it'll do.
I'm a half-blood, so it'll
probably be half-assed.
[HAKKAI]
Precisely my concern.
The effect will manifest
in ways we can't foresee.
It behooves us to
plan for catastrophe.
Wow, man. 'Preciate the
vote of confidence.
We get canned, now this crap?
Next you'll be tellin' me you
agree with the Sanbutsushin.
Not so long ago I'd have said
you were crazy for thinking
that. I wish I still could.
We've come so far, though.
[HAKKAI] Like it or not,
we've been summarily
relieved of our mission.
There is no earthly reason
for us to proceed further.
Especially if you're at risk.
Why plunge forward
into the unknown
if we don't have to?
Ah, so now I'm a liability,
is that it?
What about you,
Mister Mansplain?
If we're talkin' about
who might go ape shit.
Last time I checked, you and me
were in the same boat.
As a demon I'm a known
quantity, more or less.
Besides, this is your first
encounter with the aura.
That's a factor.
I see. You're good
and I'm not, huh?
Bravo! Way to be
a selfish prick!
[HAKKAI]
Oh, I'm selfish now, am I?
Better than an irrational prick.
Hey! Knock it off,
you two! I mean it!
Fine.
I suppose I'll just come
right out and say it.
If the worst-case scenario
happened, heaven forbid,
I couldn't be the one
to put you down.
[gasping]
[HAKKAI]
Let's assume you do go berserk.
What happens when we cross
the point of no return?
Sanzo could kill you.
No doubt he'd oblige you
with a bullet
between your eyes
without much ado.
In which case, he and
I would be at odds.
I wouldn't just stand there and
watch him pull the trigger.
Let's assume Goku or
myself had to be put down.
Could you let Sanzo do
what was necessary?
[HAKKAI]
You're not wrong.
We are in the same boat
as far as being subject
to the aura's influence.
But given that,
shouldn't we play it safe?
Why should our friends
contend with two liabilities?
What a well thought-out
and compelling argued opinion.
[GOKU]
Sanzo!
Well, thank you, but to
be fair, in the end
I'm every bit as selfish as
Gojyo accuses me of being.
Weak, pathetic. Whatever you
have a mind to call me, really.
Sanzo and I have our
own ways of dealing
with worst-case scenarios.
To each his own when the
chips are down I guess.
[inaudible]
[gasps] Kanan!
[HAKKAI] I'd have given
anything to see her live.
Anything.
But dwelling on regret
gets us nowhere fast.
Believe me.
[GOJYO]
Eh... Whatever.
You really expect me to shrug
my shoulders and be all like
"yeah, you know what,
good point.
Best be on my
way now, losers?"
Never crossed my mind, honestly.
I know you too well. Being
reasonable isn't your forte.
[GOJYO]
Seriously?!
Then what the Hell have
you been babbling about
for the past five minutes?!
You act like the worst-case
scenario's already happened!
[HAKKAI] You're missing
the point entirely!
That's enough.
Both of you, get out
before I go berserk.
Excuse me?
[SANZO]
I'm done listening to you bitch.
If you're gonna throw a fit
over what's on your neck,
go home to Chang'an and start
a frozen yogurt stand.
You're holding us back.
Piss off.
Awkward.
Your talent for verbally abusing
us never ceases to amaze me.
Well, too bad your attempts
at being cavalier
aren't as convincing.
We all know out of all
of us the one person
in the group that needs
a healer is you.
I'll take my chances, dumbass.
[GOJYO] Where do you get off
talking to him like that,
you glorified eunuch?!
[SANZO]
I wonder...
[GOJYO groans, coughs]
[SANZO] If you were worth
wasting the ammo,
I'd blow a hole in your head.
[GOJYO]
That's it.
Insult the guy who's got a way
better hairline than you.
[GOKU]
Ah!
You're dead.
[GOJYO groans]
Oh, is that a fact
now, cue ball?
[SANZO groans]
[GOJYO]
Piece of...
Easy! C'mon, are you
just gonna sit there?
If they want to act like idiots,
let them get it out
of their system.
What?! They can't keep
going at it like this!
They'll destroy each other!
Cut it out!
[SANZO]
Shut up!
Stay out of this, monkey boy!
You jerks! Why'd you
go and do that?!
[GOKU groans]
Now I'm ticked!
[GOKU, GOJYO, SANZO grunting]
[GOJYO, GOKU, SANZO]
What the...?
[ALL groan]
[GOJYO groans]
So, in his language that
means "get the Hell out."
Learn something new every day.
[engine revs]
Seriously, you guys.
When did Hakuryu get to
be the levelheaded one?
[laughs]
Talk about perspective.
At this rate the four of
us are cruisin' to fulfill
that prophecy what's-her-name
spewed out.
Much as I respect divination,
that's not my idea
of a good time.
[HAKKAI]
Forgive me, but...
...may I bum a smoke?
[SHARAK]
These demons...
They're not like the others we
tend to run across nowadays.
They'd never harm a soul.
I, uh, can't help but notice.
There aren't quite as
many of you now.
[MAN 11A]
Yes.
Our population has
decreased by half.
Faithful as we try to be.
Our kind can only resist
the dark aura for so long,
and even then it's a fight.
Strong though our
brothers were in belief.
They fought, and they lost.
Far be it from me to ply
you with false hope.
But certain steps are
currently being taken
to extinguish the dark
aura at its source.
With luck, your struggle
to keep the madness
at bay won't have
been for nothing.
Endure as best you can,
my friends.
Your vigil's end may
be in sight.
[gasping]
That's encouraging news!
We can all hold out a
little longer, right?
[SHARAK]
And him?
The child, Prince Nataku,
Heaven's war god?
What if he comes back?
According to Genjo, he singles
out demons mercilessly.
And suppose their kin who've
succumbed stage a raid?
This village would be helpless.
Strengthening the barrier
would be wise.
If you'd prefer, I'd be more
than happy to give it a boost.
Thank you! That'd be wonderful!
Your kindness and
generosity allows us
to thrive in our own humble way,
despite the misfortune that
has befallen our comrades.
Because of you, Sharak,
we live in peace.
Thank your own
considerable strength
before you thank my kindness.
[BABY coos]
[laughs]
[SHARAK]
I can't have children of my own.
Motherhood wasn't in the cards.
This is the next best thing.
I fight out of love.
For our neighbors.
For their children.
[SHARAK]
I swear by the Kouten Scripture,
I will fight for them
to the bitter end.
[gasps]
What?
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[VILLAGERS scream]
[SHARAK]
Everyone okay?
[WOMAN 11C]
Help!
[gasps]
[MAN 11D]
Uh... What's going on?
[ROSHU]
Everyone stay calm!
Son of a bitch, who is it?
Who do you think?
The war god.
[HASSAN]
Huh?
[NATAKU] Confirmed.
Thirty enemy combatants.
They will be dealt
with accordingly.
[SANZO]
Cooled off yet?
Yes. Quite a bit, actually.
Apologies for the fuss.
Uh!
[GOJYO] Why you gotta say
it like a grandma?
[HAKKAI sighs]
A simple "I'm sorry," then.
[footsteps]
Thank you for puttin' us
in our place, old buddy.
We'd be screwed without you.
Mind stickin' with us
a little longer?
[honking]
Hey. Don't worry, all right?
I'll give 'em a stern
talking-to.
Uh, 'scuse me. When did
you get put in charge?
[GOJYO] Guess this explains
why you've been acting
all cagey with me
the past few days.
What I don't understand is why
you wouldn't just say something.
I don't know. I suppose I was
waiting for the right moment.
Knowing about the mark
might've pushed you
over the edge.
I didn't wanna chance it.
Emotional unrest is a trigger.
Give me a little credit,
will ya? I mean, c'mon.
You really think
I'd lose my cookies
over some lame-ass
tribal tattoo?
You're no more susceptible
than I was.
Still...
Knowing the change is
underway can twist you.
In the midst of battle,
for example.
You begin to wonder
what your capacity
for bloodshed really means.
You start thinking,
"maybe I'm already a demon.
Maybe it happened
right under my nose."
I didn't want you
to agonize about--
[GOJYO]
All the more reason to tell me.
This isn't about who's goin'
to the dark side or when.
It's about who's gonna
bring us back when we do.
Everybody's got their
own bag of rocks.
I'm not about to let
mine pull me away
from the folks I depend on.
"Bag of rocks."
I like that. Sums it
up rather nicely.
[GOJYO] I know, right? I'm
kind of a worda-magician.
Kudos for wearing it lightly.
[explosion]
[SANZO grunts]
[GOJYO]
Uh!
[HAKKAI gasping]
[GOKU]
Huh?
What was that?
Over there!
They will be dealt
with accordingly.
A kid?
Yeah, but surely he can't be?
It's, quite an honor
to meet you.
I'm Sanzo Sharak, 28th
in Arhat. At your service.
I'm addressing Prince Nataku,
I presume?
Human beings have ten
seconds to declare
their intentions to flee.
No exceptions.
Those who do not will be
considered enemy combatants.
Seems a bit extreme.
I was informed by the
Sanbutsushin of your duties.
Pardon my associate.
He and the others present,
human and demon alike,
are of absolutely no harm to
anyone, let me assure you.
I understand showing them mercy
may run afoul of your orders,
but I'm willing to accept
responsibility--
Your ten seconds are up.
[SHARAK grunts]
[NATAKU]
Executing orders.
[VILLAGERS scream]
Stop this! What are you doing?!
[chanting]
No, Sharak!
Target locked.
[VILLAGERS scream]
You psychotic little brat!
Let me make our case!
Don't shoot him!
Right!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[MAN 11E screams]
Wait! If you try to make
a break for it--
[NATAKU]
One hostile, fleeing on foot.
Eliminate him.
[SHARAK gasps]
What the...?
[MAN 11E screams]
Sharak! What are
you waiting for?
Give us the order!
Fire!
You're kidding me!
[EIJIN gasping]
[gasps]
[SHARAK]
Whatever he is,
clearly we've made an enemy
of something horrible.
Hassan. Eijin. Roshu.
Sharak's got your back.
Understood?
[ROSHU grunts]
[EIJIN grunts]
Understood.
Humans are hereby advised
to choose their fate.
Leave at once or die.
Not much of a choice,
is it? Heh, sorry, kid!
What are you?
[yells]
What we lack in numbers,
we make up for in skill.
To underestimate
the Kouten Corps,
is to gamble with your
own fate. Aum!
[VILLAGERS whimpering]
Wait, come back!
[EIJIN]
On it!
[MEN groaning]
[HASSAN]
Eijin!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
What have you done?!
I repeat myself.
The humans among you
who fail to withdraw
will be treated as targets.
[SHARAK] He's a soldier,
just as Genjo said.
This attack isn't an
expression of his will.
He isn't driven by
his own momentum.
No. He's only a puppet.
A machine programmed to kill.
Target locked.
[gasps]
[GOJYO] Ah. Thought we heard
somebody starin' some shit.
Who went and threw a party
without invitin' us?
Didn't figure we were
the type to crash?
The weirdos are here.
Good on them for timing.
Come on down.
I'd explain,
but it'd take too long.
Oh, that's quite all right.
I'm fairly certain we
have the gist of it.
This must be our replacement.
Greetings, Prince Nataku.
Best of luck thwarting the
Resurrection Experiment.
We've heard great
things about you.
[SANZO]
Sorry for the late introduction.
Names Sanzo Genjo,
31st in China, at your service.
These are my boys.
[GOJYO]
What's with you?
[sighs]
It's nothin'. I'm good. I
thought maybe I knew this guy,
but there's no way
we could've ever met.
Huh?!
Humans are advised
to take their leave.
Withdraw or die.
No.
Two new enemy
combatants confirmed.
Wait, what the hell?
If I heard correctly,
we've been identified
as the enemy.
If that ain't luck,
I don't know what is.
We're under no
obligation here, guys.
Friendly or not, keeping
these demons safe
isn't our responsibility.
That said...
No, we get you.
This little bastard's
the whole reason
the four of us got the axe.
Yeah, gotta admit,
I'm curious to see if he's
the better man for the job.
I do hope that Your
Highness will indulge us
with an unflagging
show of strength.
Please tell me this isn't
turning into a grudge match.
[SHARAK]
Careful.
This might come off
like you're picking
on someone a fraction
of your age.
Standby Shifting priorities.
These four will be neutralized.
They're so fast!
[HASSAN]
All that in the blink of an eye?
[GROUP gasping]
[GROUP groans]
Hey, this kid's really
not all that bad.
[SANZO]
If the beam had hit us dead on,
we'd be a pile of ash right now.
Ah, as I suspected,
they're shikigami.
How 'bout you quit pulling
backup outta your ass?!
[yells]
Damn it! How many's he got?
I don't know,
but they keep coming!
Battle pop quiz for you, Goku.
How do you vanquish a shikigami?
Oh, um, you...
Break their medium!
[HAKKAI]
Very good.
And if by chance you
can't find their medium?
[GOKU]
Take out their spell caster!
[GOKU gasps]
[HAKKAI yelps]
[GOJYO]
Ah!
[GROUP groaning]
[SHARAK]
He's too much for them!
Very well, then.
My mission continues.
[SANZO]
Final episode: "Haiten."
Don't miss it.
[GOJYO]
Ready, and Ura... Sai?
Well, this is rather exciting,
don't you agree?
Whatever. If he put
something weird in here,
I'll shoot him in the face.
Wow! No idea what spice
this is, but yum!
Such a marvelously
refined broth, oh my!
Huh? The hell's going on?
What? What's wrong?
It's way too heavy.
What are you talking about?
It's delicious!
It's not heavy, wait,
you mean literally.
Ah, allow me to shed
a bit of light. Here.
[GOJYO sighs]
--[GOJYO grunts]
--[pop]