[IMAOJI]
Hey, we're here.
So, what have we got?
That's funny, I thought it was
your job to figure that out.
It's not like I called
you guys out here
for a field trip.
So are those the drugs?
I've definitely never
seen this drug before.
Wonder if it's new.
Where's the owner?
Locked up.
He was arrested 'cause he went
berserk downtown last night.
Question him if you want to.
We've got him at the precinct.
[IMAOJI]
I can go.
Great, thanks.
And you know what?
I think we should have Kotaro
take a look at this.
[SUGANO] You managed to get
Mr. Hiyama to introduce you
to the next STAND candidate?
I gotta say, that's impressive.
A best‐selling author, huh?
Must be nice having such
fancy connections.
[IZUMI]
Oh, stop.
You're coming with me this
time, anyway, aren't you?
[SUGANO]
Sorry!
Do you think maybe you
could ask one of the others
to go with you today?
I've got a bunch of
reports piled up, so...
[chuckling]
Not him.
Try the narc guys.
[IZUMI] They've been wrapped up
in another case all morning.
I guess there was a guy
arrested who had some kind of
new drug on him.
Mr. Asagiri's covering
it on your end.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Well, why not go by yourself?
Only option, really.
I didn't think I was allowed to.
Mr. Aoyama said to
bring someone with me.
[HATTORI]
Hm?
[IZUMI]
Mr. Hattori.
Oh, Makoto Tsuduki. Huh.
Isn't he the king of sappy,
tear‐jerker novels?
Sosei.
You're a big fan of his, right?
[ARAKIDA]
No. Shut up.
[IZUMI]
Um, gotta say...
Surprised you're a romance fan.
Can we not?
Right! New subject.
Uh...
So... I've been wondering
about something.
Mr. Tsuduki is this genius
novelist who keeps writing
one crazy hit after another,
despite the fact that
he's so young, right?
And then you've got his
younger brother, Kyosuke,
who's a popular actor,
and he's also listed as
a candidate for STAND.
Is it typical for the police
to ask novelists and actors
to aide them in
their investigations?
They seem like
odd choices to me.
One of STAND's primary
goals is to try to explore
new ways of solving cases
that have never been
considered before.
I hear you on the actor thing,
but as far as Master Tsuduki‐‐
Ahem.
As far as Mr. Tsuduki
is concerned,
they're considering him
to potentially help
profile suspects.
Interesting.
Oh, right!
I forgot Mr. Tsuduki actually
used to write crime novels,
didn't he?
Yeah, he did.
Now, the police even consider
him to be a reliable resource.
Great! I'm excited.
I hope he'll agree
to help us out today.
Look, calm down.
This isn't a game, okay?
I'm sorry.
Anyway, we don't know how
reliable he'll actually be.
The police could be wrong.
Didn't you research how many
series he's writing now?
[IZUMI] But I thought I read
about some rumors recently
that he's possibly
considering retirement.
Could've sworn...
So you're one of those, huh?
A person who believes rumors?
I'm not.
You were really planning to
meet him using unsubstantiated
information like that?
You need to do better.
Of course.
Oh, man.
He's even scarier today.
[IZUMI]
Um, my name is Izumi,
and I have an appointment
with Mr. Makoto Tsuduki.
[CONCIERGE 3A] We've been
expecting you. Go on up.
[bell rings]
[MAKOTO]
Yes?
[IZUMI] Hello, I'm here on
Mr. Hiyama's referral?
My name is Izumi.
[door opens]
I'm Makoto Tsuduki.
[IZUMI]
So, basically,
we were just hoping you
might be willing to utilize
your exceptional observation
skills and ability
to read people to
help us with our work.
I'm sure you'd like some
time to think it over,
and I understand.
But if you could
just let us know‐‐
[MAKOTO]
That's enough.
I said that I've
heard quite enough.
That sounds excruciatingly
tedious to the point
that it makes me
feel physically ill.
And if you believe you
can distill my abilities
down to something as commonplace
as "reading people,"
I can only imagine what
you're going to say next.
I'm sorry.
I know you came all
this way to see me,
but I'd like for you to go.
Um... Little help here?
Look. I'm sorry
if I insulted you.
I want you to know
that's not even close
to what I was going for.
But listen, I can't just
up and leave now that I know
that's what I've done.
Is there any chance of
convincing you to consider
hearing me out again?
There are two reasons
I can't take on this request.
The first is work‐related.
I'm rather busy right now.
And due to certain
personal reasons,
I may be ending all
of my current series.
[IZUMI, ARAKIDA gasp]
[MAKOTO] So, since I'll most
likely wrap them up soon,
I'll need to do everything
I can to ensure that I can
come up with endings my
readers will be satisfied with.
I simply have no time to
take on a side job right now.
As for the second reason,
that one's rather personal.
In my experience,
narcs are incompetent.
I don't trust them at all.
Quite simply, as long
as narcs are involved,
I have zero intention
of cooperating.
[ARAKIDA] You know, you need
to work on your game face.
You looked openly
disappointed in front of him.
Yeah, I know.
I just never expected
him to be quite so blunt.
It was hard to hide my shock.
Mmm, yet you managed
a parting shot.
Pretty audacious, leaving those
papers and telling him
you'd be back.
So weird.
He is ending his series.
Well, what if he does?
It's work.
If it became too personal,
he'd probably keep seesawing
back and forth.
[IZUMI]
Right.
[IMAOJI] These are the
drugs we confiscated.
Down at the precinct,
I questioned the guy
who had these on him.
He kept swearing up
and down that these pills
are perfectly safe because
they "aren't addictive."
Huh? Seriously?
And that makes them safe?
Where'd they come from?
He refused to tell us.
Kotaro. How's the
analysis going?
It's going.
There was one thing that
concerned me, though.
It's familiar.
It has similar components to
another drug in our database.
Enough to be striking.
The street name is "Plus."
Haven't seen it for a while.
It made the rounds
maybe ten‐odd years ago.
Interesting.
What type of drug is it?
[YUI]
That's unknown.
Wait, what?
All we had were the results
of its component analysis.
By itself, that's not
complete or sufficient data.
There might be more detailed
information kept elsewhere,
who knows.
But that's all I've got.
Hmm.
All right.
Yui, continue the analysis
and keep us up to speed.
Natsume, think you could
take another look
through the database?
[NATSUME]
Huh?
[SEKI] Go through the entire
thing and make sure there isn't
any other information
concerning Plus.
C'mon, that's a needle
in a haystack.
Kotaro already said he
couldn't find anything!
[YUI] Aren't you a firm
believer in getting off work
on time?
Then you'd better believe
we're gonna work you as hard
as a racehorse while
you're on the clock.
Hey!
[SEKI chuckles]
[IZUMI]
Um...
I was just wondering if there
was something I could do
to help.
[AOYAMA] Your scouting duties
should be your priority.
[AOYAMA]
Izumi.
I guess it didn't go well today?
I mean with Tsuduki.
Not really, it was
kind of discouraging.
[AOYAMA] Sorry I haven't been
able to help you out lately.
No! Don't worry!
I'm doing fine.
And Mr. Arakida was even kind
enough to call me audacious!
That's something!
[AOYAMA chuckles]
[KYOSUKE] You had no right
to decide on your own!
[MAKOTO]
Actually, I had every right.
[KYOSUKE]
Why are you always like this?
Fine!
[IZUMI chuckles]
Oh, I see, so you're
the one who came earlier
and left those STAND
documents with him, huh?
Must be cool, being a narc.
It is, thanks!
[KYOSUKE] Heh. There's no need
to be so nervous, Miss Rei.
"Miss Rei"?
You can feel free
to call me Kyosuke.
I prefer things less formal.
Oh, no, did I
say something weird?
Nothing like that. I swear.
Just thinking how you're
nothing like your brother.
Get that all the time.
I mean, he's actually talented.
That's not what I meant!
[KYOSUKE laughs]
Yeah, I know. I kid.
Sorry you had to overhear
our drama earlier,
and for screwing up your
meeting with my brother.
Oh, it's fine. Seriously.
He was never gonna
welcome me back, anyway.
So are you familiar
with my brother's novel
BeingInLoveInthe
CenteroftheWorld ?
They're turning it into
a live‐action drama,
and they've just offered
me the leading role.
That's amazing.
[KYOSUKE] But my brother's
refused to agree to it
being made at all.
Apparently, it's because he's
planning on quitting everything,
so he doesn't want to deal
with an adaptation now.
But he shut it down
so quick, it pissed me off,
and that's why
I went to see him.
So, I guess you really
wanted that role, huh?
Of course.
It's not like offers to star
in one of my brother's works
come around every day,
so I was really excited.
And then he didn't even
discuss it with me.
There's obvious concern there
about him finishing his books,
but he keeps telling me
not to worry about him.
I'm his brother, though.
So, of course I'm going
to worry, you know?
You two are close, then?
We've always had
a pretty special bond.
It's really nice.
[IZUMI]
A little sister.
[phone chimes]
Already?
[knocking]
Oh, hello.
What are you doing here?
Well, I just... It's...
[door opens]
[KYOSUKE]
Miss Rei?
Oh, both of you!
Think you can take over here?
I really need to get back
and finish some work.
[KYOSUKE]
Sure.
Sorry.
[KYOSUKE]
Are those... for Sara?
[IZUMI]
I'm sorry about this.
For researching your sister
without permission, I mean.
It's fine.
You just surprised me,
that's all.
It's not like we were trying
to hide her or anything.
Guess she's already
out for the day.
Too bad. I'd like
to introduce you.
She's a great kid.
[IZUMI]
So, she was in a car accident?
[KYOSUKE]
Yeah.
It happened 16 years ago.
She's been in this
state ever since.
She's on meds to
keep her comfortable,
but they make her sleep
most of the time.
[car skids, crashes]
The guy who was
driving was a junkie.
According to the officer who
was in charge of the case,
when the accident happened,
he was right in the
middle of an overdose.
As for the aftermath...
I guess you could say
it was "complicated."
The identity of the suspect,
the drugs he was using.
Everything in the case was left
unanswered and unsolved.
They basically acted like
the incident with Sara
never happened.
Believe me, my brother
hates the misuse of drugs
just as much as you guys do.
It's just...
...that narc didn't help
our family at all back then.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, you don't need
to apologize, Miss Rei.
But, uh, it might be hard
to get my brother to join you.
He's not the type
to ask for help,
which usually works out fine,
'cause he's able to do
most things on his own.
My brother doesn't
rely on anybody.
In fact, I don't think
I've ever felt like
he's needed me, either.
Weird, right? Heh.
Kyosuke.
[IZUMI]
The "Anonymous Case." Wait.
[MAKI] Have you heard of
the "Anonymous Case"?
This is that case where
Mr. Maki was kidnapped
as a child!
But, why am I getting hits
for this when I searched
for drug cases?
"Summary of the Anonymous Case.
A victim who seemed to have died
under suspicious circumstances
was found in the city.
It has been rumored that
this case may have involved
drug smuggling.
At the time, the Ministry
of Health, Labor and Welfare
had their eyes on a certain
drug smuggling organization.
The people at the top
of this organization
are influential figures
in the medical field.
"There are rumors that even the
Kujo Family has ties with them."
Kujo.
There are so many
candidates that have
some kind of history
with drug cases.
I'm overthinking it, aren't I?
[IZUMI]
Mr. Tsuduki? It's Izumi.
Anyone home?
[thud]
Excuse me.
Mr. Tsuduki?
Pardon me. Uh‐‐
But today...
[IZUMI]
Hey. Hold on.
Wait, what?
[IZUMI]
What do you think?
Should I call an
ambulance for him?
[KYOSUKE] Oh, no.
If he's asleep, it's fine.
I'll have him get
checked out tomorrow.
Overworking, anemia,
lack of sleep.
I can think of a ton of
reasons why this would happen.
I'll head over right
after I'm done filming.
But until then, would you mind?
[IZUMI]
Of course.
I feel so helpless; is there
anything else I should do?
[KYOSUKE] Um... Wait,
today's Thursday, isn't it?
That means he might get
a visit from his publisher.
I'm sorry about this.
[IZUMI]
That must be it.
This is...
[door opens]
[IZUMI]
You're awake!
Thank goodness!
Sorry for coming in
without permission.
Although, I did contact
Kyosuke when I found you.
What time is it?
Oh, you don't worry
about your manuscript, okay?
I already handed it over
to your publisher for you.
Listen, why would you
push yourself this hard?
[MAKOTO]
That really doesn't concern you.
Well, Kyosuke was
worried about you, too.
And forgive me,
but he also mentioned
that you wouldn't discuss
anything about your work
with him, ever,
and it made him sad.
You're not actually
quitting, though, are you?
What are you talking about?
When I went into your office,
I accidentally
saw your computer.
Oh! I totally didn't read
it that carefully, though!
But you read it?
I'm so sorry.
Doesn't matter.
Not like it's something
that shouldn't be read.
I noticed.
It did seem like a pretty
drastic departure
from the rest of your work.
[MAKOTO]
Of course it is.
I'm writing an
adventure novel for kids.
A kid's novel?
Although...
I'm fairly certain that's
not what society wants to see
from me.
The truth is...
I've wanted to write something
like this for a long time.
Something I want to write, not
something I'm forced to write.
When we were kids,
they would always
smile at my stories
and tell me how much
they loved them.
Every time I wrote anything,
it was only for the two of them.
[IZUMI] Sounds like you and
Kyosuke have a lot in common.
You both love your brother
and sister very much.
Of course I do.
More than anyone
in the whole world.
[KYOSUKE]
My brother said that? Really?
[IZUMI]
Yes.
[KYOSUKE] This is the first time
I've seen him asleep in a while.
Even when we were younger,
it was a rare thing.
Takes me back.
My sister and I were
obsessed with the stories
my brother would write.
They were our favorite things.
We really loved them.
You big idiot.
Are you sure?
I could make something for
him to eat when he wakes up.
Get outta here.
Sadly, he prefers sweets over
something nutritious, anyway.
Oh, okay then.
Well, take care.
Yup, same to you!
Do me a favor.
Tell your brother I take
it back and not to worry
about STAND for now.
I kinda think
he wants you and Sara
to be able to read that book
as soon as possible.
Somehow, you keep
managing to see
the most desperately
embarrassing sides of us.
We are so lame.
[IZUMI laughs]
You care about
your older brother,
and there's nothing
lame about that.
When you gave me that
slightly embarrassed smile,
I felt like I saw
you as a child.
You really don't look
at all like your brother.
He always has such
a serious expression.
Although, his gentle nature
and his rare, kind smile.
They're just as beautiful
as the worlds he creates
for the people he loves
most in the world.
Well, guess I'll be going.
Is everything okay?
[KYOSUKE]
Miss Rei, why not choose me?
I'm one of the candidates
for STAND too, right?
Aren't I... enough?