[phone chimes]
[HATTORI]
Hmm.
[IMAOJI]
Are you kidding me?
We still can't get a warrant?
[SEKI] They said we don't have
enough for probable cause.
Even if we're right,
our evidence is circumstantial,
so good luck fighting
that decision.
We'll just have to
catch him in the act.
We need to confiscate the
goods as they change hands.
Are you sure?
I'll take responsibility.
First, we need to find out
exactly where this deal
will take place.
Who the hell are you guys?
Kotaro Yui, with the DCD.
We need your assistance
with our current case.
My name is Natsume.
Hope you can help us.
We're trying to track
down Mr. Soma Kujo.
Huh? Like we would
let you see him!
[SHINDO]
Wait. Track him down?
You mean he's not here?
What's goin' on?
No luck.
Hiyama still won't answer.
I see.
[OTANI] If any one of
us gets into trouble,
it's up to the individual
to get themselves out of it.
That's always been
our rule, hasn't it?
If he wanted our help,
he would have said so.
But he didn't,
so he doesn't need us
to go looking for him.
[keyboard clicking]
[phone chimes]
[AOYAMA]
Izumi.
[phone rings]
Have you guys
found anything yet?
[YUI] Well, we looked through
Soma Kujo's computer.
There's a meeting
with a supposed buyer
scheduled for later tonight.
South district. Midnight.
The sixth warehouse
down at the wharf.
Midnight.
Got a location. We have to go.
Let's hurry!
Yes, sir!
[IZUMI]
That must be it.
Let's go.
[car approaches]
Well, well. Looks like
the whole gang's here.
Mr. Hattori!
In the flesh.
I was under the impression
your warrant request
was declined.
Well, plans change.
You know our boss
is incredibly reliable.
Oh?
But tell me,
what brings you here?
Really? Do you think we
came here to have fun?
I'm sorry, we don't have
time for idle chitchat.
Then go ahead and take
care of your business.
Don't let us keep you.
STAND operates under
its own jurisdiction.
Unlike you at the DCD,
we have the option
to move freely in
cases such as this.
Does that mean you would
be willing to help us?
Yeah, you can count on us.
At least for today.
So, Izumi in front.
Arakida, you go that way.
[IZUMI, ARAKIDA]
Yes, sir.
[ARAKIDA]
Izumi.
[IZUMI]
Mr. Arakida.
It doesn't look like
there's anyone over
on this side.
I didn't find anyone, either.
Over there.
That's Takaomi Hiyama
and Soma Kujo.
The others have
taken their positions.
Let's go!
Hmm. Well, that was
certainly a dramatic entrance.
[KUJO]
How can we help you gentlemen?
[AOYAMA] Start by telling us
what you're doing here.
[KUJO] I don't feel obligated
to explain that to you.
[AOYAMA]
If you want to stay silent,
then I'm afraid we'll have
to search your belongings.
I'm sure you won't mind.
Do whatever you need to do.
Pardon me, please.
[KUJO] I'm not sure what
you're looking for, but...
It's not here.
I'm sorry you've
wasted your time.
Is that so?
You realize we're aware of
the drug trafficking route
run by the Kujo Family?
We have evidence that
you were going to conduct
a deal today.
If that's not the case,
we would like to know
what is going on here.
And you know, with so
many of us involved
at this point, even if we
come up empty‐handed tonight,
we will have to report
this to our superiors.
As I'm sure you're
both already aware,
if you choose not to speak
up and clear your names,
things might get
inconvenient for you.
Oh, I'm sure they will.
You'll see to that.
Very well, then.
Yes, we came here
to meet with someone.
Though he probably
won't show up now.
[AOYAMA] Why set up a
meeting in a place like this?
That was his request.
Who is "he"?
What's the meeting for?
A former attendant.
He was previously employed by
Soichiro Kujo, my predecessor.
I wanted to see if he could
give me more information
about Plus.
The Kujo Family
is not responsible
for its distribution this time.
But its composition is
very similar to a drug
that the former head
was involved with.
So that means...
It's the same formula as before.
My predecessor's
unfortunate legacy.
My goal was to find
the current distributor
and take care of
this problem at once.
"Take care?"
What are you talking about?
Do you mean to say you
weren't benefiting from it?
Don't insult me.
I wouldn't stoop so low
as to rely on that trash.
Sorry?
[KUJO] The last person
to care so much about
these drugs was my predecessor.
They are no longer a part
of the Kujo Family's
business dealings.
As the head, I will make
amends for those actions
moving forward.
[HIYAMA]
It's true.
I can confirm all of it.
He's been looking
into his predecessors
and trying to uncover
their misdeeds.
I've been assisting
him with this.
If that's the case,
why didn't you tell us about it?
If you had just
explained everything,
you wouldn't have been
considered a suspect.
[KUJO] I don't want
the family's former evil
known to the public.
I sought the truth in order
to protect the Kujo Family now.
That's my responsibility
as head.
I don't expect
your understanding.
Whether or not
you choose to believe
everything I've just told you
doesn't matter in the least.
But, we all know there's
not a single reason
that I should be
apprehended here.
[IZUMI]
It does matter.
It absolutely matters.
You know that.
[IMAOJI]
Aoyama.
[AOYAMA]
What is it?
Plus!
I see.
I guess I should have known.
They resented me after all.
[KIRISHIMA] What do you mean
we can't see him?
[NATSUME] We found drugs
in the trunk of Mr. Kujo's car.
That's not something
we take lightly.
He and Mr. Hiyama
are being questioned now.
Unfortunately, we can't
allow you to see him
until that's over.
[KIRISHIMA] Mr. Kujo would
never do something like that!
How do you know someone
didn't try to frame him?
While we can't say for sure yet,
we do think it's a possibility.
You do?
Hey, we're supposed to
keep that on the down‐low.
And if that is the case,
we'll find the true
suspect no matter what.
I understand that you're
worried about him,
but please.
Know that we'll get
to the bottom of this.
So we now know how you feel,
but what does the Ministry
think about that theory?
All things considered,
it's hard to believe that Kujo
will get a fair treatment
in this circumstance,
framed or not.
Why should we trust
you to handle this?
So, how'd it go?
[SEKI] I told them that
the way we found the Plus
seemed unnatural. Too careless.
I suggested that somebody else
might have planted the drugs,
but that's not what
they wanted to hear.
Well. That's not surprising.
The Ministry and the MPD
had to agree to let Kujo
skate for a while
so they could watch him
and eventually take
down the whole family.
But they'll have to change
their approach now,
considering how convoluted
this has all gotten.
With an important witness
to the Anonymous Case
like Soma Kujo in custody,
they can cover it all up
and make sure none of
this sees the light of day.
I guess as long as
they get what they want,
how they do it doesn't matter.
At this point, even if he
was framed for the drugs,
Kujo's going to
take the rap for it.
[HATTORI]
So.
What are you guys
going to do, then?
Got the component analysis back!
What we confiscated
from him was Plus.
No doubt.
[IMAOJI] Now the trick is
figuring out if Mr. Kujo lied
and really did have
them in his possession.
Or if he was framed.
[IZUMI] Honestly,
I don't think it was his.
[NATSUME] Yeah, you said
that to the Kujo Family, too.
Be careful. There's no point
in giving false hope.
That's not what I was
trying to do, though!
Now, now.
Okay, so, Natsume, can I
assume from what you've said
that it's your opinion
the drugs were Kujo's?
Hard to say.
On one hand, considering
we've been investigating him
for so long, it seems
hard to believe
he could end up going down
for such a stupid mistake.
Yeah.
And till the trunk opened
at the warehouse,
I'd believed that it was
possible he was in the clear.
And you, Sosei?
I only have a guess,
so I can't say for sure.
So, what do you think?
Well, if he really isn't guilty,
then I guess I'm wondering
who would try to frame him.
The way Mr. Kujo reacted,
he might've had an idea.
Currently, I'd say that
our most obvious suspect
has to be whoever it was
he was going to meet there.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're talking about
someone framing him
as if he's some kind
of victim here.
But even if he's innocent
of this one thing,
the Kujo Family
has a shady history.
[SUGANO] Yeah, Kujo actually
admitted that, too.
Well, then something
is definitely off.
Don't you think it's
pretty dangerous to simply
take his word on
something so important?
I understand what you're saying,
but I still don't think
he's lying about this.
Going with her gut.
We need to make this
decision extremely carefully.
I mean, we're dealing with
the Soma Kujo after all.
Tell me, the car
you were using tonight,
is that how you
usually get around?
Correct, and it wouldn't
be easy for a third party
to access it, but not
impossible, either.
[AOYAMA] Any idea who might've
planted the drugs on you?
There are plenty of
people who may hate me
or hold some kind of grudge.
If you can't be
more helpful than this,
then I'm afraid I'm going
to have to arrest you
tomorrow morning.
That would be pretty convenient
for you, wouldn't it?
[AOYAMA] Good, you get it.
I'll skip ahead.
It's true.
I couldn't care less if
you're actually innocent
or not in this case.
But I certainly don't believe
you're squeaky clean.
I know far too much
to ever assume that.
Even if you're choosing
not to dirty your hands,
personally, you committed
to keeping the family secret
when you became the head
of the Kujo Family.
I'm not going to let
you sit here and claim
to be completely innocent.
You said you'd protect
the family, right?
I wonder if you really
understand what it means
to make amends.
[KUJO]
Do you truly understand?
Do you even have a concept
of how many businesses
and enterprises we have?
If the Kujo Family is shaken,
then there's no doubt it
would have a ripple effect
on this country's
entire economy.
Protecting the Kujo Family.
That really means
protecting everyone working
under that name.
I understand that not
everyone sees it that way,
but I plan to do my job
as the head of the family.
[AOYAMA] Are you saying
that's more important
than trying to make things
right with all of those victims?
Correct.
This is what I've
resolved to do.
It's the justice
that I believe in.
[IMAOJI] So, if we set
everything else aside,
and we keep our focus solely on
what just happened today,
I think all of us
can agree that there's
a high possibility
that he was framed.
A very high possibility.
If we set everything
else aside, then yes.
Should we let him go, then?
Well...
I think keeping him here
would be a good option, too.
It's a chance to find
his other possible crimes.
This could be pretty
beneficial to STAND
in the end.
Yes, I guess that is an option.
[IMAOJI] But then,
wouldn't the truth get twisted?
I don't know if that's
something we want to risk.
[SUGANO] I mean, yeah,
you've got a point.
[ARAKIDA]
What about you, Izumi?
Why are you so intent
on protecting Kujo?
The thing is...
I'm very aware he could
be involved with the drugs,
and that it would be
beneficial to keep him here.
I do get that.
Mr. Kujo might not be
completely in the clear.
But what I think is
that he has his own
sense of justice.
And right now,
I think all he's trying to do
is see that justice through.
I think we can
all relate to that.
Mr. Kujo's sense of justice
comes from a different place
than ours does.
I won't try to argue that.
But if someone's simply
believing in his own justice
and trying to seek
that out for himself,
and then that person
ends up being blamed
for something he didn't even do,
I don't know. I just don't
think I can let that slide by.
My goal here is to
never turn something right
into something wrong.
It's like Imaoji said before.
If the truth keeps
on getting twisted,
then we might lose
something important
along the way.
That's the last thing I wanna
do on a case like this.
[NATSUME] You're earnest
to a fault, aren't you?
You really are, Rei.
[YUI]
But that's necessary.
Especially with this job.
As we know.
Yeah.
Going after a suspect
is a detective's job.
I won't argue with that.
Okay, so basically,
we've decided to go
catch the person
who's actually
behind this, right?
[HATTORI]
Well, aren't you a lively bunch.
[SUGANO]
You!
[IZUMI]
Mr. Seki! Mr. Watabe!
Good work today.
Well, you heard
what he just said,
so you should be able
to guess what's coming next.
You'll clean it up later.
Right, Watanabe?
You mean Watabe.
Did you seriously just
get my name wrong?
But yes, I'll keep the
higher‐ups off your backs
for a while.
Here on out,
STAND and the DCD
will be working together
as a team.
[HATTORI] Our main objective
is to arrest the suspect
who framed Soma Kujo.
You aren't going home
until we catch them.
Just keep that in mind.
[GROUP]
Yes, sir.
Now, then.
It's going to be a long night,
so how about I grab
us something to eat.
Only thing open now
is a convenience store,
so what would you like?
Hey, thanks, I really
appreciate that.
I'd like a caramel macchiato
with an extra shot, please.
Oh, and make it soy.
Something filling.
Preferably containing glucose.
That I can eat with
one hand, please.
That s'posed to be a riddle?
So, uh, are we allowed
to request anything
we want to eat right now, or?
[WATABE] Yeah, sure. As long
as you remember I'm going
to a convenience store.
So, is this what
the DCD is usually like?
[IZUMI laughs]
No way.
It's never this lively in here.
First, we're going
to need to find whoever
that former attendant was.
Yes, I agree.
That's already
being taken care of.
[KAGURA] Well so far, it appears
that this former attendant
really doesn't want to be found.
There's so little
information that I'm afraid
it's gonna take some
time to track them down.
You know you're happy
they're relying on you.
Well, that goes for you, too!
Sure does.
[phone rings]
Izumi here.
[KANAME]
Miss...
Kaname?
[KANAME]
I'm sorry to call so late,
but have you heard from Go?
He's not at the house.
Ever since we learned
of Mr. Kujo's arrest,
Go's been acting really weird.
Then there's that night.
It's been bugging me.
Okay. I'll be right there.
[KANAME]
Miss?
[IZUMI]
Mr. Aoyama?
Would it be all
right if I were to leave
for just a little while?
[AOYAMA]
What happened?
I found out that
Mr. Miyase is missing.
May I please go look for him?
Well, I don't know,
do you think that should
take priority right now?
[IZUMI] It's just that I'm the
one who asked for his help.
So, if in doing that
it ended up making
him feel trapped,
I can't possibly abandon him.
Please, sir.
[AOYAMA]
All right. Then go ahead.
Thank you, Mr. Aoyama!
[IZUMI]
We wanted to protect something.
And we wanted to save someone.
We hesitated countless
times and we stumbled.
But even then,
we still kept running,
firm in our sense of justice.
I don't always know
the right answer,
but I don't regret the fact
that that's how I got here.
No matter what conclusion
may await me now.
So he's...
[ARAKIDA]
He's dead?
Yes, we just received
word from Revel.
The imposter was
quite convincing,
but definitely a fake.
He disguised himself
as the former attendant,
then used his assumed identity
to get close to Soma Kujo.
That seems like a
really roundabout way
of doing it.
I mean, they went
through so much trouble,
but then if we hadn't shown up,
it all would've
been for nothing.
Wait a minute,
where did we even get
the information about
the deal tonight?