[IZUMI] The media has been
reporting that Makoto
was actually arrested.
The press is being ruthless
with both Makoto and Kyosuke.
I thought... Isn't there any
way you could at least announce
that he wasn't arrested?
I'm begging you!
I'm sorry, Damsel, but you
don't get a say in this.
I mean, after all,
this is our job, you know?
Specifically, it's STAND's job.
Why didn't you‐‐
[HATTORI]
Why didn't I tell you about it?
Isn't it obvious?
It's 'cause you're nothing
more than a scout, kid.
You're an outsider.
Mr. Hattori got it right about
me and that's the worst part.
At some point,
I think I let myself believe I
could be a real asset to STAND.
I mean, as more
than just a recruiter.
I thought maybe my body's
resistance to drugs
would end up being like
a superpower for the team.
You work hard,
and you never give up.
I believe you take
this job seriously.
But, you're dangerously naïve.
Anyone can see how
badly you want to be
a real part of STAND,
but right now you
would just be a burden.
[WATABE]
Hey.
I heard that Rei's scouting
duties have been put on hold.
Yeah.
I was only notified
about it this morning.
So, now, the higher‐ups
are going to be the ones
in charge of scouting for STAND.
She's been ordered to go
back to her normal duties
till there's a new
candidate for the position.
Wow, did you tell her?
Yeah, I did.
She just gave me a smile.
Said to give her all
the work that she hadn't
been able to do lately.
Noble as ever.
Well, if that's the case,
maybe I'll go ahead
and ask her out on a date!
I could even use some PTO!
Slow down there, kid.
Why don't you head on home?
Li'l protective, Dad?
Aw, you old softie.
[SEKI]
Please stop calling me that.
[WATABE chuckles]
Scouting duties put on hold.
That means she must've
done something wrong,
don't you think?
If it has anything to do with
her going to the MPD yesterday,
then I feel totally responsible.
I keep thinking that maybe
I should've stopped her.
But, she honestly
seems to be doing okay.
I thought she'd be
more visibly upset,
but she looks pretty normal.
I'm sorry, but are you
two completely blind?
Look!
Her shoulders are bent
six more degrees than usual.
The sides of her mouth
are also 2.2 millimeters
lower than normal,
and her conjunctiva
are slightly bloodshot!
Curse all of you! What if
Izumi's insanely rare DNA makeup
ends up changing from all
of this emotional stress?
I mean, seriously, what if
all her hair falls out?
[NATSUME] Any chance I could
get you to stop being a weirdo?
Well, this is interesting,
who would've thought
you'd ever bother
to give me a call about work.
So? What brought this on,
then, Asagiri?
Look, don't even worry about it.
You can rest assured that
my feelings toward you
haven't changed a single bit.
What a coincidence.
We actually agree on something.
[ASAGIRI]
Well? How is she doing?
Why are you asking me?
She can tell you herself.
[AOYAMA sighs] So this was
your department's doing.
[ASAGIRI] What do you want
me to say? We're doing our job.
If that's the case, then what
are you so concerned about?
Rookie or not, she'll be
able to understand that.
[ASAGIRI]
I'm not concerned about it.
I mean, you're her
mentor, right?
Worrying about her is your job.
Huh?
[line beeping]
[AOYAMA]
Time to shut things down.
Oh, right.
I'll finish this up real quick.
Might want to it hurry up.
Get going before they
drag you out with them.
Huh?
You all ready to take off?
I'll go ahead and make
the reservation.
Yeah, I think so.
Thanks for that.
[NATSUME] Should we invite
Mr. Watabe, too?
Yeah, Sure, I don't see why not.
[AOYAMA]
Don't push yourself.
Hiding your feelings isn't
going to help anything
in the long run.
They won't go away just
because you ignore them.
If you want to move forward,
you'll need to face
them head‐on.
I, uh...
Go on, I'm listening.
It's rough, you know?
No control.
Not being able to help.
I mean... I couldn't
do anything about Makoto.
I couldn't even help Kyosuke
out when I wanted to.
I may have this
unique condition,
but it doesn't make
any difference.
Mr. Arakida saw
through me completely.
Everyone was only humoring me,
and I was so oblivious.
At this rate, I really
am just a burden.
I'm so pathetic.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry, this is awkward.
I've said too much.
Know what, though?
My heart doesn't feel
as heavy as before.
So thanks for listening.
I appreciate that.
[NATSUME]
Rei!
You 'bout done for the night?
Oh, I, uh‐‐
Izumi's already gone.
‐‐[NATSUME] But...
‐‐[AOYAMA] She's not here.
Well, then I guess
it's just us tonight.
Sounds like it. C'mon.
[IMAOJI]
Hey. Kotaro, hurry up.
[YUI]
Right.
Um, what was‐‐?
[AOYAMA]
I'm sorry if you wanted to go,
but if we'd gone
to drink with them,
I couldn't guarantee that
you'd come home with me.
[AOYAMA]
What are you doing?
Come on in.
But... it's just that
it's already pretty late.
I would hate to be a bother
or anything like that.
[AOYAMA]
Lock that door behind you.
[IZUMI]
Wow.
This place is amazing!
[AOYAMA]
Are you hungry?
[IZUMI]
Uh, yeah. I actually sort of am.
[AOYAMA]
I'll whip something up.
Really?
You seriously put all of
this together just now?
I mean, look at
this presentation!
Don't mention this
at work, okay?
Are you kidding?
This is so good!
Even these sides
are totally delicious!
Thank you so much for this.
For going through the trouble.
[AOYAMA]
Go ahead and eat up.
Then, once you're finished, I
have something to show you.
Hey, you know me, all business.
You didn't think I
only brought you here
to cheer you up, did you?
What are all these?
[AOYAMA] Those are the
results of some research
I've been doing for a while,
into an incident
involving a harmful drug.
Harmful in what way?
Well, there was this
certain pharmaceutical company
that was manufacturing
a new drug.
But it was never completed
because there were problems
during the clinical testing.
Those problems were significant
enough not to move forward.
There were participants
in the clinical test
who had some pretty sudden
and terrible side effects
during the trial.
Dizziness, nausea.
In some cases, test subjects
even had seizures.
I can see why it
wasn't completed.
Yeah. Sadly, the company
acted too late,
and the victim list
grew far too quickly.
Just one after another.
Sixteen years ago.
It was 16 years ago?
Wait a minute.
Then, were those
two car accidents...?
What are you saying?
[IZUMI]
Sixteen years ago,
Kyosuke and
Makoto's little sister
was involved in a car accident.
Apparently, the driver
was under the influence
of some kind of drug.
And also,
I encountered a major
accident 16 years ago
when I was just a little kid.
A nature park.
A car crashed into it.
In the amusement park.
Yes. That's exactly
where it happened.
In the amusement
park in the forest.
I'm familiar.
I know the incident well.
[IZUMI]
Mr. Aoyama...
Why are you doing this?
What made you decide to
start looking into this case
on your own?
Because the Aoyama
Trading Company,
my dad's business...
Turns out, they were
directly involved in funding
that new drug.
Aoyama Trading Company?
That huge... [gasps]
Wait, does that mean you're...
You're actually the son of...
[AOYAMA]
Yeah.
Hold on. There's something
I don't understand.
Neither of those were reported
as drug‐related incidents.
Not the park nor the accident
with Kyosuke's sister.
That's because there's
more to this story.
In order to avoid an enormous
amount of reputational damage
to the company,
they put a different spin
on the whole thing.
Both of these incidents
were dismissed
as being mere traffic
accidents, nothing more.
And they made it
look like the new drug
was never created
in the first place.
So that means...
[gasps]
[KYOSUKE]
It was complicated.
They never found
answers for any of it.
The case was left unsolved.
It was a cover‐up?
[AOYAMA] There aren't many
companies who can make it
so an incident never happened.
Look.
[IZUMI] The Omori
Pharmaceutical Company?
[AOYAMA] The one who
ordered the cover‐up.
It wasn't just a random
Omori employee,
but the top shareholder
and head of the Kujo Family.
The secret's still being
kept by this guy right here.
Soma Kujo, current family head.
[AOYAMA]
That man's got a bad reputation.
Don't go near him on your own.
[IZUMI]
The "Anonymous Case." Wait.
[MAKI] Have you heard
of the "Anonymous Case"?
I overheard the detectives.
It's weird. They kept
saying "Anonymous." Why?
[IZUMI]
Wait. Is all of this connected?
Sara's accident and the
incident at the amusement park
in the forest, and the
incident involving Maki.
They had the same root cause.
They're all drug‐related.
[AOYAMA]
One more thing.
What's this?
The component analysis of Plus?
That drug that was
just confiscated?
[AOYAMA]
Yeah.
And here's the component
analysis of the drug
Omori Pharmaceutical
created all those years ago.
[gasps]
They're the same!
Does that mean...?
This was the
prototype of that drug.
And now it's resurfaced again
after ten odd years, as Plus.
Somehow, the drug that killed
all those years ago is back.
Who would have access to data
that should've been buried
in the cover‐up?
The same people who were behind
the drug's initial creation
and who also happen to have
the means to distribute it.
Soma Kujo.
[AOYAMA] The rumors of him
presiding over drug deals
may be unconfirmed, but they're
still worth looking into.
Even though it
wasn't intentional,
if something they unleashed
into the world turned deadly,
they should still have to
take responsibility somehow.
So should I. Both of us.
Wait a minute, what do you mean?
[AOYAMA]
What I saw that day...
Seeing those children
hurt and their parents
screaming in fear
as they cried for help...
All the adults were
in such a panic.
None of them even
saw me standing there.
Even though I was
just a kid, I thought,
"This was all our fault."
I didn't want to face it,
but I knew in my gut that
my father had a direct hand
in making those things happen.
Sadly, though, I knew there
was nothing I could do
about it back then.
But it never sat right with me.
I felt angry and powerless.
I've never forgotten it.
Eventually, I began looking
into this case in earnest.
That got me interested in other
cases involving illegal drugs,
and so, before I knew it,
I found myself
in my current job.
I could've ignored it,
of course.
It's very clear.
Some people would rather keep
this buried and forgotten.
And I'm aware
people will get hurt.
But I don't care.
I'm moving forward.
My conscience demands
that I settle this.
And until I can do that,
I won't be joining STAND.
[IZUMI] I guess that's your
justice, Mr. Aoyama.
You told me before, remember?
"The other side of justice
is another side of justice."
You're going to see
that it's served,
even if you end up seeming like
the bad guy to someone else.
I wish... I could make
a difference like that.
Every time I try to do anything,
I feel like I'm being told
that my help isn't needed.
And it hurts!
No, that's not right.
It's just so frustrating!
I want that.
To see my justice through.
The same way you do!
[AOYAMA]
You want to help?
Now that your scouting
duties are on hold,
you have some time, don't you?
But you‐‐
You've already gotten so far
doing all of this
research on your own.
[AOYAMA]
Like I said before.
You have a strong
sense of justice.
I admire that.
I already wanted
to ask for your help.
That's why I told you
this to begin with.
So, what do you think?
[IZUMI]
Well, I think...
If there's anything
at all that I can do
to help the people who've
been hurt by this incident,
especially my friends...
That's what I want to do.
I'd be honored to help you.
[IZUMI]
Hey, everybody.
I'm so sorry that
I've worried you.
Aw, we wanted to go out
drinking to cheer you up,
but now you seem fine.
Huh, looks like your eyes
aren't even bloodshot any more.
You seem to be
in perfect condition.
[chuckles]
Hey, good job, Aoyama.
Guess I won't need
that PTO after all.
I mean, I've got to admit.
This is something.
I'm impressed.
You managed to gather so
much information off the clock.
Seriously.
But now, we might
really be able to uncover
where Plus came from as well
as its main distribution route.
And in the process,
we'll probably find out more
about the Anonymous Case, too.
You know what that means.
We could discover the
reason they created STAND.
I mean, the real one.
Not to be a party‐pooper,
but finding too much could
lead to our destruction,
you know?
Well, I'm pretty sure it's too
late to turn back now, so...
Not to mention, of course,
that our damsel here
has said that she wants
to continue moving forward.
[IZUMI gasps]
Um, please don't call me that.
[SEKI]
Izumi. We're on your side.
That's really the point.
If this is the path
you've chosen,
then we're gonna
walk down it with you.
Thank you.
Really. Thank you all so much.
[phone chimes]
Excuse me!
I mean, I decided to
help Rei because I liked her
and no other reason than that.
This doesn't change anything.
Right? Kagura?
Who, me?
You know I'll do my job
as long as I get paid.
I don't care.
Why can't you ever
just be honest?
Shut up, you.
Play the game. It's your turn.
[phone chimes]
[IZUMI chuckles]
[IZUMI]
These good people.
They're all around me, and they
say that they're on my side.
They even claim that
nothing will change that.
It's as if it's been raining
for a really long time,
and I've just been
keeping my head down,
fighting the cold.
But when I looked up,
I was treated to
a different view.
There was light piercing
through the clouds.
And one day, the sky
will be blue again.
I choose to believe that,
and to keep looking up.
[HIYAMA] So the guy we were
wary of apparently has his eyes
on you after all.
And on top of that,
it looks like he's recruited
that scout that I
mentioned to you before.
Listen, now that STAND
is also looking into
the Anonymous Case, you should
probably be more careful.
I know. I really should.
Especially if I want
to see this through.
[KIRISHIMA grunts]
Going to see Mr. Kujo?
Why, is he not
feeling well again?
[SHINDO]
He's been pretty busy lately.
We just need to
make sure he's at least
been taking some supplements.
I'll do my job, no matter what.
[KIRISHIMA grunts]
Of course.
If anyone ever
threatens that man,
I'm good and ready to
protect Mr. Kujo with my life.
But you're the doctor here,
and that means illnesses
are your department.
[MIYASE] Heh. You sound
like you're having fun.
Oh, that sucks.
I totally thought that was food.
[MIYASE] The geraniums
I was growing out back
have bloomed magnificently.
Mr. Shindo. Mr. Kujo
is actually free right now.
He's already off the phone?
Touching base with Mr. Hiyama
as usual, right?
Wonder what they talk
about during their chats.
You're telling me you
actually care about that?
As long as we're in this house,
Mr. Kujo must always be
the most important person
in our lives.
Always.
No matter what secrets
he may be hiding.
[IZUMI grunts]
Whoa, is that the time?
I should really get myself home.
[phone chimes]
Who could be‐‐ [gasps]
What? What is this?