[KYOSUKE] I'm one of the
candidates for STAND too, right?
Aren't I... enough?
Are you able to take some
time off on the weekends?
Sure. Usually, anyway.
So, um, if you'd be
up for getting together
to talk about STAND,
we should do that.
During the week works, too!
It kinda defeats the purpose
if you're working, though.
See, I'm attempting to
ask you out on a date.
Oh, now I get it.
What?
C'mon, go out with me, Miss Rei.
[SHOPKEEP 4A]
Come on in!
[WAITER 4A]
Sorry about the wait!
All right!
Beers all around, guys!
'Cept for Rei here,
and her shochu.
Thanks for the round!
Really?
You're starting off with shochu?
Yeah, why, is that weird?
Are you not really sold
on your salad yet,
or what's going on with that?
Oh, I was just studying
the presentation‐‐
Er, I mean, never mind.
Okay. I think it's time
to raise a glass!
Good work this week, everyone!
[GROUP]
Bottoms up!
How's Mr. Tsuduki doing?
Is he any better?
It sounds like he's
doing just fine now.
The doctors said it
was from overwork.
So, you're getting
the hang of scouting,
and you're even taking care of
people in all your spare time.
That's my Izumi.
Take it and run, girl!
Yui, would you please stop
playing with the drinks?
[YUI] It's an important
experiment, I'll have you know!
Okay, and, done!
Why? What did I do?
Wait, so, STAND's already
acquired Section One,
isn't that right?
Mr. Hattori, Mr. Asagiri,
Mr. Arakida,
and Mr. Sugano, I think?
Right. And you've
made great contacts.
You've met all four members
of Revel, for instance,
and the Tsuduki brothers, too.
You've even managed
to gain their trust. That's...
Well, I'm impressed.
Uh, thanks for that.
I appreciate it.
[AOYAMA chuckles]
So, I guess you're holding
off on scouting Mr. Tsuduki
for right now?
We'll have to try some other
candidates for the time being.
Maybe his brother?
Yeah, you should!
This is him, right?
Mr. Young Heartthrob,
Kyosuke Tsuduki.
His fans call him "Kyon."
Ah! That guy!
I literally heard him called the
"ratings prince" the other day.
You've already made contact
with him, haven't you?
Izumi?
[IZUMI]
Okay, I'm new at famous people,
but is it normal for them
to call you awkwardly
throughout the day
and ask you to dinner
and flatter you
and stuff like that?
[GROUP]
Huh?
Hold on, is that
creep hitting on you?
[IZUMI] No, that can't be it,
he's just teasing me.
Gimme a break. He's going
after that body of yours!
Not everyone's the
same as you, Kotaro.
Anyway, what kind of monster
would put his hands on Rei?
[IMAOJI] No, this actually
concerns me a bit.
Rei is a lovely young lady,
and he's an entitled
celebrity who's been around.
She could have
the best of intentions
and still be blindsided
by someone like him.
[SEKI]
Izumi.
I've got a buddy
in Community Safety.
They have a really good
self‐defense spray.
I'll get one of them for you.
Just do your best not
to be alone with him.
[NATSUME]
Okay, thanks, Dad.
Don't do that.
Mr. Seki is coming
from a good place.
If this guy's pushing
you that hard,
does that mean he's
decided to join?
Well, no.
The truth is, he won't
agree to join STAND yet
because he's afraid I won't
go out with him if he does.
So why not just
date the guy already?
[IZUMI]
Stop! You can't be serious!
Hey, don't let these
guys get to you.
'Course, it would help if you
kept dating STAND prospects
down to a minimum.
[NATSUME]
Now, now.
No need to worry.
If anything happens,
we'll save you.
Or, more accurately,
most of us will anyway.
‐‐Not it.
‐‐What a shock.
[IZUMI laughs]
[IZUMI] Oh, is that
an article on Makoto?
[ARAKIDA gasps]
What's your problem?
Don't sneak up on me like that!
[IZUMI]
Sorry, I said I was coming in.
I'm so glad he decided to
make an announcement about it.
Like it matters to me.
[SUGANO]
Oh, come on.
Give it up!
Don't act like you haven't
been grinning at that article
since yesterday!
[ARAKIDA]
Sugano, I will hurt you.
[SUGANO]
Ooh.
[IZUMI giggles]
[IZUMI]
Mr. Asagiri.
I was asked to deliver this.
They've got you running
errands between
your scouting?
Just helping out.
They're all so busy
with that mystery drug case.
That must be rough.
Oh! Hey, why don't we
go grab some lunch?
It's time for my break, anyway.
Natsuki, don't you
still owe me a report?
[SUGANO gasps]
[ASAGIRI]
If you're hungry,
have one of my favorite
noodle bowls.
Now. Have a seat.
Right, that looks great, thanks.
Glad that's all settled!
Have a good one!
Thanks, I appreciate that.
Izumi.
Maki! What a surprise!
What're you doing here?
Covering for Hatori.
Looks like you're taking off.
Are you headed home?
[IZUMI]
Mm‐hmm.
Well... Guess you've got
perfect timing, then.
[KYOSUKE]
Hey there, Miss Rei!
[IZUMI]
Kyosuke?
[KYOSUKE]
You surprised?
My brother isn't Revel's
only client, you know.
Nah, I'm kidding.
I was actually just asking
Kei a little bit about you.
Oh, that's why he
said that about timing.
You keep turning
me down via text,
so I thought I would
ask you in person.
You're off tomorrow, aren't you?
Got any plans yet?
Well, uh...
Sara's birthday is
coming up, so I thought...
Would you mind helping me
pick something out for her?
Maybe?
Y'know? I'd be happy to!
It's so crowded around here.
You'll be okay?
Never fear!
No one ever sees
through my disguise.
Let's go!
[KYOSUKE] I picked out the
perfect present, thanks to you.
[IZUMI]
I'm glad I could help!
Oh, wow. Look over there!
Those look amazing!
Come on, let's split one!
[IZUMI chuckles]
What is it?
Just you.
You look like you're
having so much fun.
Because I am having fun.
We're on a date, right?
I'll be honest, all I was hoping
for was that you'd finally
have a chance to step
out of work mode
and enjoy the day with me.
I think you accomplished that.
I can't remember the last
time I had this much fun!
You mean it?
Awesome!
[GIRL 4A]
Doesn't he look like Kyon?
Oh, wow, he does!
Busted. Let's bail!
Oh, man.
Sorry to make you run.
I kinda panicked!
It's fine.
That was kind of
a close one, huh?
Too close.
In that moment, all I
could see in my mind
were cheesy headlines about
some steamy new love affair.
Though now that I think of it,
if the headlines were about
you, I wouldn't mind much.
There you go with
the teasing again.
Miss Rei. Come on.
You know I'm being
honest with you.
Look, it's just so complicated‐‐
[KYOSUKE]
It's my brother, isn't it?
[IZUMI]
The thing is... He's...
Your brother is a potential
STAND candidate.
And you are, too.
That's true.
Which means, as soon as
my brother joins STAND,
this'll all be over and
you'll instantly forget me.
Life's brutal, man.
Or, I might just join
immediately if you could
look me in the eye right now
and tell me you like me.
[IZUMI]
I'm not saying that!
[KYOSUKE]
Aww.
[laughs]
Hey, hey, hey.
Watabe, man of the people,
has brought you treats again!
Uh, what's up?
[WATABE] So finding information
on this mystery drug
is even more difficult than
you thought it would be.
It's baffling that we
still don't know what it is
or where it's coming from.
Kotaro's running the
component analysis
and we'll have that soon.
And Natsume's looking into
"Plus" since it was so similar.
Come to think of it, does
anyone know where he is?
Maybe he went to
wash up or something.
By the looks of it,
he was here all night
Your hands are
full, aren't they?
Yeah, I haven't really
been able to help out
with that case at all.
That's only because you've
been busy with your own work.
You're far too nice, which is
why he keeps messing with you.
[WATABE]
Am I missing something?
Who do you mean?
Rei here has an admirer.
Kyosuke Tsuduki keeps
asking her to go out.
But it's not like they're
real dates or anything.
Wow.
First some socialites
and now a big actor.
Turns out you're a pretty
smooth operator, Rei!
No, I'm not!
[YUI]
Figured it out!
I've finally got the component
analysis for the mystery drug.
It's not just similar to
the Plus that circulated
15 years ago.
The drug we've been
studying is Plus.
How can we be certain, though?
Wasn't the data we had
on Plus incomplete?
[YUI] I'm gonna let
Natsume explain that.
[NATSUME] I did some initial
digging but came up empty,
so I ended up getting some
documents from the MPD.
Which I'll need back since I'll
be getting rid of them later.
Does that mean...?
[WATABE laughs]
Excellent work, Natsume!
Honestly.
You can scold me another time.
Basically, the main problem
was the fact that
the component analysis
results had been hidden away.
Which is weird, right?
I found them stored alongside
the other top secret files.
They were considered
classified data.
Only a select few from
a certain agency
could even get
access to them.
And it was STAND.
You're sure?
[NATSUME]
Security was tight.
I just barely managed
to get the analysis out.
I'm pretty sure what this
means is that Plus is involved
in some cases that
STAND will be dealing with.
Did you know
about this, Mr. Seki?
No.
[AOYAMA] It seems strange
to me that anyone would have
drug‐related data
other than the DCD.
[NATSUME] Not to mention
that it was top secret.
Something's fishy.
[YUI]
I'm just speculating here.
But with STAND,
that agency might have
some ulterior motives
that we're
completely unaware of.
[SEKI] For now, Aoyama
and I will deal with this.
We've been able to uncover
something about this drug,
which is great progress.
Aoyama and Imaoji, find out
where it's coming from.
Sure.
Yui and Natsume,
find out everything you can,
both on this and on the drug
commonly known as "Plus."
Roger that.
[phone ringing]
[IZUMI]
Excuse me.
What's going on, Kyosuke?
[KYOSUKE]
Miss Rei! It's my brother!
He was taken by the police!
[IZUMI gasps]
[IZUMI] Oh, he went with them
to be questioned voluntarily?
That's good.
I thought he'd been arrested.
Sorry. I kinda panicked.
[IZUMI]
It's all right.
I would have done
the same thing.
[KYOSUKE] The police had sent
him summons to come down
to the station, but apparently
he had been ignoring them.
If he declined again, they
were gonna issue a warrant
on suspicion of concealing
evidence or something.
They thought your
brother might be hiding
some kind of evidence?
Pertaining to what?
They weren't willing
to tell me anything,
but I did overhear
the detectives.
It's weird.
They kept saying
the word "anonymous."
Anonymous?
Could it be the
"Anonymous Case"?
Is Makoto involved in that?
Who knows. I have no clue.
Never heard of it before.
But...
There's just no way that
my brother did anything bad,
you know?
I mean, he's the kind of guy
who always does what's right.
Always.
And I'm so proud
of him for that.
I never did stand a chance
against him, though.
He's the son that my
parents were proud of.
I was always just a runner‐up.
Everyone I've ever liked
has wanted him instead.
That sounds hard.
Sorry, what am I talking about?
Just ignore me. It's nothing.
Can I tell you something?
I like you, Kyosuke.
You're a nice guy, and
a pretty charming one, too.
Wait, you really
think I'm charming?
[IZUMI]
Mm‐hmm.
Well, thanks.
I don't know what's going on,
but I'll help you if I can.
I'll look into this for you
and see what I can find out.
I owe you one, Miss Rei.
[IZUMI]
Yes. I'm heading back now.
Thanks.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Izumi here.
[MAKI] Hey, I heard Tsuduki
was taken away by the police.
[IZUMI]
So, you already know.
Sure do, and I heard
they were questioning him
about the Anonymous Case.
[IZUMI]
Well...
Listen, don't worry
about me, okay?
We're gonna be looking
into this matter, too.
Though we obviously won't
be asking the police
about it directly.
And Makoto?
He'll be out soon, won't he?
[MAKI] If it's just standard
questioning, then, yeah,
they shouldn't hold him for
days or anything, but still.
You should know, those brothers
are headed for trouble.
[IZUMI]
What's going on?
What is this?
Kyon's big brother was taken?
Wow! Crazy!
[NEWSCASTER 4A] There's no
formal word from the police,
causing much speculation
amongst fans.
Speaking of Mr. Tsuduki,
his younger brother
is currently working as
an actor and has become
a bit of a success himself!
Yes, and one can only
wonder if this might begin
to affect his work.
Who knows how this
could affect the ratings
for his current TV drama?
[ARAKIDA sighs]
[HATTORI] My, my.
Listen to that heavy sigh.
I can't blame you.
They're not holding
back on Mr. Tsuduki.
[ARAKIDA] Nothing else big
in the news right now, either.
You concerned?
[ARAKIDA]
Shut up.
I think you're worried
about the new damsel.
She's such an empathetic soul.
I bet she's probably
a mess right now.
I guess she finally
won you over, too, Sosei.
How surprising.
Oh, please. I've barely
even acknowledged her.
[IMAOJI]
Welcome back.
How'd it go?
Oh, I just followed
up on a few leads,
but I didn't find anything.
I don't know why he was
looking at the Anonymous Case,
and I couldn't discover how
he might've been involved.
It's so strange.
Interesting.
It is unusual that no other
details have been released.
So, I'd bet Section One
has some kind of gag order
about the case.
Or maybe, only a select
few from Section One
even know about it at all.
[IZUMI] Yes, that's what
Revel thought, too.
I asked if they thought there
was anything we could do
about all the awful,
negative comments.
But for now, they said they'd
just have to deal with it.
Hey, look, you should
probably get some rest, Rei.
You look a little pale to me.
Nah.
Were you taking those
back to the library?
I'll take them for you.
You have got to relax.
No good will come
from you panicking.
Hey, Rei!
There's about to be
a press conference
with Kyosuke Tsuduki.
For all the trouble
and the confusion,
I am truly sorry.
So, as my agency has
already announced,
it's not true.
The reports of my brother,
Makoto Tsuduki,
being arrested are false.
Right now, he's cooperating
with the police.
He's gone along with
all of their questioning.
I can't talk about why
he's being questioned
because it will affect
their investigation.
[REPORTER 4A] But is he
really just being questioned?
[REPORTER 4B]
He's a crime novelist.
You don't think he got tired
of writing about criminals
and decided to
become one himself?
[REPORTER 4C] Isn't it possible
that your brother was involved
in a crime and you
just had no idea?
No, it's not.
I firmly believe in Makoto.
He's awkward, but he loves us.
I'm proud of my brother.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, but I
really need to go!
Did you need something?
I came here regarding
Makoto Tsuduki.
The media has been
reporting that Makoto
was actually arrested.
The press is being ruthless
with both Makoto and Kyosuke.
There's been so much
speculation going around
that it's getting
out of control.
I thought...
Isn't there any way you
could at least announce
that he wasn't arrested?
I realize that I may
be out of line,
but those two are truly
suffering right now
due to the awful treatment
they've been getting. Please‐‐
Ms. Izumi.
[IZUMI]
I'm begging you!
There's nothing to talk about.
Please leave.
I'm sorry, damsel, but you
don't get a say in this.
I mean, after all,
this is our job, you know?
What do you mean?
Well, more specifically,
it's STAND's job.
[IZUMI gasps]
[HATTORI]
That's right.
Though it's publicly known as
Section One's investigation,
it's actually STAND that's
holding him right now.
Why didn't you‐‐
[HATTORI]
Why didn't I tell you about it?
Isn't it obvious?
It's cause you're nothing
more than a scout, kid.
You're an outsider.
[IZUMI] The sound of the cold,
driving rain fills my ears.
The belief that I'd been
progressing on this path
was completely shattered
with a single word.
If the guidepost I'd seen
in the distance
and the light within my heart
were both mere illusions...
Oh, hey.
[IZUMI]
Then where am I headed?
Where am I supposed to go?