[ONLOOKERS chattering]
[RESPONDER]
This way!
[MOTHER sobbing]
[RESPONDER B]
Can you hear my voice?
[ONLOOKER]
Someone please help!
[VOICE]
Are you okay?
[MPD BRASS] This brand‐new
investigation agency is intended
to specialize in the
unsolved drug‐related cases
that are increasing
in prevalence recently.
We call it "STAND."
You are the elite few chosen
to establish this force.
Ministry of Health, Labor and
Welfare Drug Control Department
and MPD Investigation
Section One,
we're counting on you.
[MOHLW BRASS] Seki.
I expect you'll be responsible
for scouting additional members.
With all due respect, sir,
the department I already
work in is pretty new as it is.
It might be kind of difficult
for me to take that on.
But STAND will require
the best of the best
to operate at its
full potential.
We need someone to recruit
qualified members of the police,
the DCD, and
civilians to join us,
regardless of their
current assignments.
It's an extremely pivotal role.
Needless to say,
we would feel much better
if you'd accept the job, Seki.
As I'm sure you can tell,
this guy isn't interested
in moving up the ranks.
Well, if it's of any help,
I know someone else
who'd be perfect as a scout.
[MPD BRASS]
Rei Izumi?
I know that girl.
Isn't she the enforcement
official put on probation
for botching a premises
check a few days ago?
We can't afford to
trust a rookie like her
with such an important position.
[AOYAMA]
Forgive me, sir.
But you're wrong.
She's got the right ideals,
and she'll always make
sure justice is served.
But most importantly,
she has a talent that's
hard to come by in the DCD.
As her mentor, I will
personally vouch for her.
She's exactly who we need.
[IZUMI sighs]
Hey, good morning!
Uh... No one?
[NATSUME]
Good morning, Rei.
I'm glad you escaped.
Escaped? Don't say that.
[NATSUME]
Here, want some coffee?
Uh... Oh, yes.
Thank you so much.
So, uh, now what?
Mr. Seki and Mr. Itsuki
haven't arrived yet.
I'm sure you want to get
the lecture out of the way,
but you'll just have to wait.
[IMAOJI]
Natsume.
Don't tease the
poor girl to death.
Anyway, morning.
Oh, sorry.
I gave her your coffee.
[IZUMI gasps]
Uh...
This is yours? Take it!
Heh! No, please, ladies first.
You pulled an
all‐nighter, right?
Why don't you cut
down on the caffeine
and get some sleep instead?
No, thanks. I'd prefer not
to take naps at work.
Is he okay?
He was saying he
couldn't sleep because
he was thinking
about you, Izumi.
Something along those lines.
Don't twist it.
Sorry.
He meant that he was worried
while you were on probation.
All of us were,
to tell you the truth.
It's good to have you back.
[door opens]
[IMAOJI]
Ah, here they are.
I take it the meeting went well?
[SEKI]
Mm‐hmm.
Rei. Long time, no see.
Mr. Seki.
Please accept my apologies
for all the trouble I caused.
As of now, my probation's
finally been lifted.
[SEKI]
Right. I'm glad.
[papers shuffle]
What's wrong?
You're looking kinda down today.
Ta‐da! It's everyone's favorite,
as a little surprise present
from yours truly.
It'll be great.
That came from
Henri Charpentier.
They call it "The Shortcake."
You mean you're
familiar with it, Itsuki?
It's famous.
So am I dumb for not knowing?
Oh, that's right.
Watabe. Don't you have
to get back to the MFA?
Aw, let me hang out!
Did you forget what a big
help I was in that meeting?
Hey. I know.
Why don't we make
some more coffee?
Sure!
So, it's not police or DCD.
But a brand‐new agency,
and they're calling it STAND?
Yeah, they're planning to
put together an elite team.
That's the rumor, anyway.
And to think they're considering
some civilian candidates,
as well. I'm surprised.
It sounds like it's gonna
be a pretty intense job.
Since we're discussing it...
Izumi.
Huh?
[SEKI] There's something
I'd like you to do.
Really? What's that?
It's a list.
Read it carefully.
Those are all
candidates for STAND.
From this point on,
you'll be the one responsible
for scouting new members.
[IZUMI]
Huh?!
Hey. That's a smart choice!
I wish you could have
heard the glowing reviews
you were getting
from Aoyama, here.
We expect great things.
Work hard, okay?
Hey, watch it.
[WATABE chuckles]
But... Sir, I‐‐
Refuse?
No. I'll do it.
Try your best.
Hurry up and eat, then.
Now that you're on
board, we've got no time
to waste.
I have to take you somewhere.
[IZUMI] All right.
But can I ask where we're going?
[AOYAMA] Take a look
at that again. Closely.
I'm not entirely uninvolved
with this assignment.
I'll do everything
I can to support you.
[IMAOJI]
This worries me a little.
Not only is she the scout,
but once STAND gets to work,
she'll be on the front lines
for any related missions, right?
Yeah, being that close to these
unsolved drug‐related cases.
Things are certain to get ugly.
She must be scared.
[SEKI] Aoyama knows that.
But it's done.
[YUI]
Nevertheless...
There's no one better
suited to it than her.
It's the right choice.
[IMAOJI]
Yui.
[NATSUME]
How long have you been awake?
[YUI] Izumi's a super‐rare
case, remember?
Most types of drugs don't
have any effect on her body.
Which is bound to come in
handy for her sooner or later.
Don't look around so much.
Oh, right, I'm sorry.
Excuse us.
Oh, Mr. Aoyama, it's you.
What brings you here?
And who's she?
[ASAGIRI]
Oh, great.
It's our favorite narc
from the DCD.
I don't recall inviting you.
Asagiri.
I see you're still just
as exhausting to look at
as you ever were.
You don't have
much right to talk.
Okay, guys! That's enough.
Let's relax.
So, then...
I guess this is the girl.
Right. Izumi, meet Asagiri.
That's Sugano.
You remember their
names from the list?
They're both
candidates for STAND.
[AOYAMA]
Mr. Hattori hasn't returned yet?
[ASAGIRI] At this point,
I'd be surprised if he ever did
come straight back.
Who's Hattori?
Oh, he's the chief
of this section,
and he'll be the one
directing STAND, as well.
Yup!
I know nothing's
been decided yet,
but since he's our boss
and everything,
we're pretty much
guaranteed to get the job. Oh!
Actually, here's another
candidate now.
[SUGANO]
Hey, Sosei.
You wanna meet the girl
everyone's been talking about?
Or not?
Hello. I'm Rei Izumi.
I'm with the DCD.
Honored to be working
with you sir.
[IZUMI]
Huh?
[SUGANO]
Aw, Sosei.
No, wait. Come back‐‐
‐‐Thank you‐‐
‐‐This isn't a game.
If they interfere
with your work,
then don't wear high heels.
I don't have time to babysit
someone who's unqualified.
Do better.
[IZUMI]
I'm sorry.
[AOYAMA] Don't worry,
he talks to everyone like that.
Arakida's kind of a lone wolf.
Want to quit?
Of course not.
I decided to do this job,
so I'm going to see it through.
And this time, I‐‐
You already paid the penalty
for your past mistakes,
so you might as well
move on now.
You have to.
[IZUMI] I got distracted
by something else,
and I ended up interfering
with a premises check.
Someone with my experience
should know better.
Arakida may have hurt
my feelings before,
but everything he said was true.
I blame myself.
Completely.
I'm sorry!
This is so unprofessional
of me, isn't it?
I'll stop talking!
Well, we've got some extra time.
What you did that day
wasn't a mistake.
It was right.
If there's one thing we
know about you, Izumi,
then I would say it's that you
have a strong sense of justice.
The choice that
seemed right to you
may not have been best from
someone else's point of view,
but that doesn't make it wrong.
The other side of justice
is another side of justice.
[IZUMI]
"The other side of justice
is another side of justice?"
[AOYAMA] That's a saying
I learned back when
I was a rookie.
I took that wisdom to heart,
and I swore that I would always
do what I believe to be just.
Even if other people
may think it's evil.
That's what this job is.
Right.
[AOYAMA]
So, yeah.
You weren't to blame
for what happened.
Mr. Seki might've said this too,
but if one little rookie mistake
spoiled the whole thing,
then it was doomed
from the start.
[IZUMI]
Is that true, though?
Yes.
We're all a team.
Thanks.
I really appreciate that.
[AOYAMA]
Shall we?
[IZUMI]
Sure!
Here goes.
[IZUMI]
Good morning.
I assume you're
on break right now?
[ARAKIDA]
Obviously.
I'm sorry, but I haven't had
a chance to introduce myself
properly yet.
No, thanks.
I promise it won't take long!
Wow, harsh! That poor girl.
She seems like
she's trying so hard.
[IZUMI]
Please wait!
Why would I, when you
have no business with me?
Your assignment is to scout
new members to join STAND,
isn't that right?
Well, I'm already
going to join it.
But I plan to keep as much
distance as I can from you.
So quit following me around.
Listen. I intend to
see this job through!
And I don't know if
I'll be able to do that
if I don't have support
from you and the rest
of Investigation Section One.
That's why I need you
to acknowledge me, Arakida!
[ARAKIDA] You know, I heard
you had an unusual condition.
They normally wouldn't
trust a rookie like you
with that position,
but they made an exception,
because your body is
immune to certain drugs.
People around here see
you as a little princess
in need of protection.
And if that's who you
really are, then no,
I can't acknowledge you.
[HATTORI] Oh, you must be
the new Damsel of the DCD.
Hello there, sir.
[HATTORI]
Thanks for the coffee.
[HATTORI] Are you thinking
about what a jerk I am
for letting you pay?
Not at all!
Your face tells me you are.
You're rather easy to read.
So. How'd you like Sosei?
Do you think that
you can tame him?
What? I'm not sure I follow‐‐!
[HATTORI] Well, you're probably
gonna need the qualities
of a lion tamer in order
to get anywhere with him.
That's all I'm saying.
A lion tamer, huh?
They're strict on others
as well as themselves,
but they can be gentle too.
Even if they may seem harsh.
You giving up?
No way!
Good.
I'm glad you're enthusiastic.
While I've got you here,
let me give you some advice
in exchange for the coffee.
Hey, tell me something.
Have you decided on
who your first recruit will be?
[IZUMI] I don't quite feel
like I fit in at this party.
But still, he's here.
[IZUMI]
Who is this?
[HATTORI]
Takaomi Hiyama,
head of the Hiyama group.
One of Japan's
largest financial firms.
Oh, right,
he's a huge celebrity!
[HATTORI] Well, apparently
there's another side to him
that the public
doesn't know about.
He leads a quartet of highly
efficient celebrity informants.
It's a team that goes
by the name of Revel.
Informants?
If you can convince
them to join your cause,
then I expect things will
go a lot more smoothly.
Like they say.
"He who controls the information
holds all the cards."
But can I find him?
Of course you can.
If you know where to look.
[IZUMI]
Like where?
[HATTORI]
Uh, if I had to guess...
I'd try a fancy gala.
[IZUMI]
It's him!
‐‐[IZUMI gasps]
‐‐[KIRISHIMA] Wait, sir!
[IZUMI yelps]
[KUJO]
I'm sorry, are you all right?
Yes. Pardon my clumsiness.
Go and get her a
new outfit, please.
Oh, no!
You don't need to!
It's really not that bad.
[KUJO]
But...
Don't worry.
It's my fault.
I'll be more careful.
Well, if you ever need
anything, just give me a call.
Now, excuse me.
[MIYASE]
Here, miss.
[IZUMI]
Um, thanks, I appreciate it.
[AOYAMA]
Izumi?
[IZUMI]
Mr. Aoyama!
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
I came to meet up
with another candidate
for STAND named Mr. Hiyama.
What are you doing here, though?
I thought you were working
on a different case today.
Did you say anything to
that man who approached you
just now?
Uh... No.
I just kind of bumped into him.
Let's see...
Kujo. Hold on. Is he‐‐?
Another one of the
STAND candidates.
That man's got a bad reputation.
Don't go near him on your own.
[CROWD gasps]
[fire alarm]
Is there a fire?
[ARAKIDA]
Sir! Come with me!
[IZUMI]
Mr. Arakida?
What brings you here?
Where's the client?
He's safe with Sosei.
There's one problem, though.
It looks like he ran
into the DCD.
What?!
[ARAKIDA]
What are you up to?
[AOYAMA]
That's my line.
What the hell's going on?
These gentlemen with me
have been hired to act
as my bodyguards.
You see, the Hiyama group
received a serious death threat
a few days ago, so we're
exercising extreme caution now.
But who would do that?
And why?
Well, when you're in the
business of selling information,
it's not really unheard
of to make a few enemies
along the way.
It's possible that whoever
sent the death threat
could be responsible for
starting the fire, as well.
Just try not to interfere!
‐‐[ASSAILANT yells]
‐‐[HIYAMA grunts]
[ASSAILANT grunts]
I'll get him!
Hey!
Izumi! Don't be rash!
[IZUMI grunts]
[ASSAILANT chuckles]
Have a nice nap.
[IZUMI]
Chloroform?
[ASSAILANT grunts]
Damn!
Who the hell are you?
You're mine!
[IZUMI]
Mr. Arakida!
[ASSAILANT grunts]
Suspect is immobilized.
[AOYAMA]
Izumi!
[IZUMI]
Right here, sir!
You're safe?
[IZUMI]
Yes, and Mr. Hiyama?
He's fine.
[IZUMI]
Thank goodness.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[ARAKIDA] We caught the suspect,
and Hiyama's all right.
Excellent news.
[ARAKIDA]
You. Tell me the truth.
Did you know that she
would be on the ship?
[HATTORI]
"She?"
Rei Izumi.
Ah.
Sounds like you've
changed your tune.
[ARAKIDA]
Did you put her up to it?
She's an intriguing person,
as I'm sure you agree.
Well? Feel like
being friends yet?
Don't toy with me.
It's just...
She's so reckless,
I can't bear to watch her.
[HATTORI] Does that mean
you'll help her out?
[ARAKIDA]
Yeah, I guess it does.
[IZUMI] I'd abandoned
my heels back there.
It felt weird to be barefoot
in such a nice dress.
I thought about how
absurd I must've seemed.
All scraped up and
disheveled, with messy hair.
Anyone would have thought
that I looked like a disaster.
But, for some strange reason,
instead of being embarrassed.
I was kind of proud of that.
I felt like I could do my
best again tomorrow, too.
Like someone had given
me a gentle push forward.
[OTANI]
Ah.
So that's the princess
everyone's talking about.
[phone buzzing]
Hello? Yup, Hiyama's
completely safe.
Guess what?
I found someone interesting.