Stay calm.
Remember, this is your job.
Right.
[MIYASE] You must be
Ms. Izumi and Mr. Aoyama.
Welcome.
We've been expecting you.
Well, then.
Please, come this way.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
[knocking]
[MIYASE]
Our guests have arrived, sir.
[KUJO]
Show them in.
Thanks. Hello.
I do appreciate you coming
so far to see me today.
I'm Soma Kujo. It's a pleasure.
[IZUMI]
I, um...
I want to apologize for
the trouble I caused you
at that party on the ship.
No.
I should apologize for
inconveniencing you, as well.
Now...
Lovely to see you again,
but I have a feeling you didn't
come here just to reminisce.
Let's get to it, shall we?
Thank you, sir.
We'd like to discuss you
possibly joining an agency
called STAND.
A joint effort of the
Ministry of Health, Labor,
and Welfare's DCD,
and the MPD's Investigation
Section One.
First, let me tell you more
about STAND's goals.
So essentially, STAND's primary
function and objective
is to look at unsolved
drug‐related cases.
We want to solve those cases
in an unprecedented way.
Rather than being held back by
more conventional restrictions,
we're looking for talented
people from various fields.
Quite simply, since you're
the head of a notable
pharmaceutical company,
we feel you'd have
a lot to offer us.
Your knowledge and connections
would be invaluable.
We'd be very grateful if you'd
seriously consider joining us.
[KUJO]
I see.
That's a rather
interesting story.
I understand what you're asking,
but, as you've already
mentioned yourself,
I have a very
important position.
Not only must I protect
Omori Pharmaceutical,
but I must also do
everything in my power
to protect the Kujo Family.
So, please.
I'm going to need you
to give me one solid,
compelling reason why
I should help you out.
Go ahead.
Okay.
I mean, just like
I mentioned before,
with your knowledge and expert‐‐
[KUJO] You know that's
not what I'm asking.
Let me be direct.
There are plenty of people
who have high positions in
pharmaceutical companies.
I wouldn't even mind
introducing you to some.
But I need you to tell me
why you've asked me.
I'd like to know why I
personally should help you
with this goal of yours.
[IZUMI]
Well...
The heads of the Kujo family
have been executives
for Omori Pharmaceuticals
for generations.
Also, I've heard that you're
now ambitiously attempting
to manufacture new products.
There are people in the DCD
who have been studying
drugs for years,
but we don't have an expert
on creating them.
To my knowledge, we couldn't
hope to do any better
than you.
Omori Pharmaceuticals
is our top candidate.
As far as the knowledge
and techniques STAND
is searching for right now.
I understand.
However...
It sounds like you're asking
the wrong person for help.
I'm an executive of the company,
not an expert in the field.
From what you've said, I'd
think you'd be far better off
scouting one of my researchers.
But what STAND
needs is much more
than the knowledge
of just one individual.
Omori Pharmaceuticals
could provide‐‐
Another reason I can't.
The company isn't
actually my property.
Would you like me to
introduce you to someone
more suitable?
I'd be happy to do that for you.
[AOYAMA]
If I may interject...
Though she represents
their interests,
Izumi is not an official
member of STAND.
Her sole purpose is
to recruit candidates.
It's not her job
to choose who to scout.
Of course, if you prefer,
we could ask our supervisor
why you were selected for this.
But if that's the case,
we'll have to request
more of your time later once
we've received an answer.
We don't have a
problem with that,
but I know you're a busy person.
Do you think that
will work for you?
Hey! Watch yourself!
[KUJO]
Very well.
Let me cut to the chase.
I have zero interest
in this deal.
You're clearly intelligent,
so I'm sure you
can figure out why.
If that's why you're declining,
don't you think this
will actually put you
in an even worse position?
That's not really for you
to decide, though, is it?
If it's her job to scout people,
then what does that make you?
He's a candidate,
just the same as you.
That means he's a
potential STAND member.
He's not an outsider.
[KUJO]
You're wrong.
If he's not an
official member yet,
he's as much of
an outsider as I am.
However, if he were
here representing
his family's company,
that'd be different,
as they've helped us out a lot
over the years.
I'd have a little more time
to catch up, in that case.
But as it is...
I have quite a few
engagements to get to.
No, please wait!
I happen to agree with Aoyama.
If we end things like this,
it will put the company
in a worse position
and that won't do you
any favors at all.
Okay? I'll come by again.
Please see yourself out.
[AOYAMA]
Let's go.
[MIYASE]
Thanks for your work today.
So, how did it go?
From all appearances,
it seems at least Mr. Shindo
has had quite enough.
If they're going to stand
in the way of my goals,
then sadly, I can't ignore them.
So that's where
we find ourselves.
I see you haven't changed.
Ever since that day...
Honestly...
I'm getting pretty sick of all
these additional annoyances
coming up.
If the stress gets to him,
his condition gets worse
and that means more work for me.
[KANAME]
You're probably fine.
I highly doubt that
scout stood a chance.
I'm sure he won't be interested.
[SHINDO]
She might've had a tiny chance.
[KIRISHIMA] I kinda
like gutsy girls like her.
But the guy...
I didn't like that dude
one single bit.
The way he was looking at
Mr. Kujo... it pissed me off.
Is that what your
animal instincts say?
Koya's instincts are good.
Surprisingly reliable.
Just forget about them.
[KIRISHIMA]
That's right!
If they show up again,
I'm just gonna pound 'em
and send 'em running
back outta here!
So, you're saying it took
you two and a half hours
to get there and then you
only stayed for 15 minutes?
[IMAOJI]
That must've been rough.
Well, look at this this way,
at least you got to
take in some scenery
and tour a beautiful
mansion, right?
[IMAOJI]
Natsume.
He is the current head of
the infamous Kujo Family.
I guess it's not surprising
that he's got his guard up.
What about the other
residents in that household?
Is there any chance of
getting through that way?
Those four. Is that them?
[AOYAMA] Yeah, we only
got to meet these three,
but they also seemed
rather guarded.
Maybe they aren't
the way in, then.
Huh.
[NATSUME] Rei, didn't you say
you struck up a friendship
with one of the employees there?
[IZUMI]
Mm‐hmm.
But, it was almost
as if we were meeting
for the first time today.
He seemed completely different.
[IMAOJI]
What should we do?
This one's an order from above.
We'll just have to keep trying
until we get through.
Well, her title as
the STAND recruiter
should keep you in
the door and help you out
at least a little bit, right?
That's true.
And this will put us
directly in contact
with the material witness
in our current case,
which is more than
we had before.
Yes, exactly.
Go ahead and set up our
next appointment with them.
Right!
Mm‐hmm. Mm‐hmm.
Love seeing that enthusiasm.
And because you
youngsters are so motivated,
I brought you a gift.
Today's snack is
Mille‐Feuille Spécialité
from Mille‐Feuille
Maison Français.
Oh, thank you so much.
[IMAOJI]
I'll go make tea.
[NATSUME]
Let me help you with that.
[WATABE]
I'll take one, too, thanks.
[SEKI] Don't you need
to get back to work?
[IZUMI] We're still waiting for
our next appointment
with Mr. Kujo.
So in the meantime,
I gathered all the information
I could on the Kujo Family.
I was hoping you guys might
be willing to help me out.
So, you're trying to get
in to scout Mr. Kujo?
[IZUMI]
Yes.
[OTANI]
Let's see.
Hey, now.
Hatori.
[OTANI]
Hmm.
This is pretty good.
According to this data,
everyone has very different
occupations and backgrounds.
It's weird.
I can't seem to figure out
why they're so willing
to band together for Mr. Kujo.
I'll take any information
you can find.
Is there anything
you can tell me?
Izumi, we really‐‐
[OTANI]
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but we don't know
much about the Kujo Family.
I think that Hiyama might
be the only one of us
who does.
When the Hiyama Group was
in some trouble in the past,
believe it or not, Mr. Kujo was
the one who helped them out.
Hatori!
She doesn't need to know that.
[OTANI] It's not like people
don't already know.
Mr. Hiyama and Mr. Kujo have
that kind of a connection?
Wait a minute.
Is that why Revel can't give
me information on the Kujos?
Is that the reason?
I'll let you figure
that out yourself.
Apologies.
I'm going to get a drink.
[KAGURA] Hey, could you try
not to look so disappointed?
It makes me feel like
we did something wrong,
and I hate that feeling.
It's exactly like Hatori said.
Sorry.
I really don't think
there's much we can do
for you this time.
Even if you wait,
the answer won't change.
But then, what should I do?
What the... don't look at me.
[IZUMI]
Excuse me!
They live so far
from the bus stop.
I'm tired already.
[KIRISHIMA yells]
[IZUMI]
Mr. Kirishima?
[KIRISHIMA]
So you're back, huh?
I'm not letting you
get away this time!
Ha. I get it, you take
no sleepers, huh?
Sleepers?
Ya got guts! I respect that!
[IZUMI gasps]
[KIRISHIMA]
Oh, no you don't! Bastard!
[KIRISHIMA roars]
That makes 120 wins,
two losses, and one draw.
[KIRISHIMA]
Go.
You're a worthy proponent.
What in the world...?
[KIRISHIMA] How long are
you gonna sit there?
Your butt, it's gonna get dirty.
Oh, right.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
I guess I should also
thank you for saving me.
I won't let you see Mr. Kujo.
I bet you don't even have an
appointamentary thingie, do you?
Oh, no!
You see, I actually came here
to see Mr. Miyase today,
not Mr. Kujo.
Miyase?
Yes!
I have something
I wanted to give him, so‐‐
[gasps]
Oh, no...
Make sure you just
talk to Miyase.
[door opens]
Where's Miyase?
I think he's with Kiyoshi
in Mr. Kujo's room.
Really?
I mean, Mr. Kujo is here today?
You won't be seeing him.
That's fine!
It's just that I didn't
think he'd be home, is all.
Well, he's‐‐
He's working from home today.
Oh, I understand.
Hey!
I told you not to talk
to anybody but Miyase!
[IZUMI]
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
[SHINDO]
I'd say it's anemia.
He should be all right
if he takes it easy
for rest of the day.
But he needs a full examination.
Make time in his schedule.
Yes, understood.
[knocking]
Hey, you've got a visitor.
Me? Who wants to see me?
[IZUMI]
Here you go.
I'm really sorry
that I got it so dirty.
But what's inside is still fine.
[MIYASE]
This is...
[IZUMI] I want to thank you for
everything you did for me
at the party that night.
It was bothering me that
I'd kept it for so long,
so here it is.
Well, thank you.
It's kind that you thought
of returning it to me.
I, um...
[MIYASE] I don't like
the look of those clouds.
Let's get you a car.
It's okay.
[KIRISHIMA]
I'll take her back.
Sorry about this.
It's really all my fault
for not being able to take down
that deer bastard earlier.
[IZUMI]
Not at all!
Thank you for letting
me see Mr. Miyase.
Mr. Kirishima?
You should stop poking your
nose into Mr. Kujo's business.
I admit, it doesn't really
seem like you think
Mr. Kujo's a bad guy like all
the others have before you.
But you still have some
doubts about him, don't you?
Am I wrong?
What are two you doing here?
This is no place for
idle chatter, you know.
[KIRISHIMA]
I know.
Let's go.
[IZUMI]
Is he...
Is Mr. Kujo not well?
[IZUMI]
Um...
Would you please tell him that
I hope he feels better soon?
I'm sure he's incredibly busy.
It must be hard
for him right now.
Well, it doesn't look
like it's going to let up
any time soon.
[SHINDO] There's no way
you'll be able to drive in this.
[KIRISHIMA]
Oh, yeah.
Whenever it rains around
here, it's irreplaceable!
You mean inaccessible.
You should just stay the night.
This place has plenty of guest
rooms that barely ever get used.
[IZUMI]
Wait! I couldn't possibly!
Don't wanna?
Would you rather
sleep in my room?
[IZUMI]
No way!
Uh, Koya, I'm not so sure.
How come?
Seriously, it's not like
Mr. Kujo's so heartless
that he'd just throw
her out in this rain.
Um, so, what am I‐‐
I'll go and let Mr. Kujo know.
[MIYASE] I'm afraid we've
been using it as storage.
I apologize for the mess.
If you need anything else,
please let me know.
This is perfect, but I'm
sorry for inconveniencing you.
It's fine.
Now, If you'll excuse me.
That definitely could
have gone better.
[IZUMI]
Is this...
Where the heck is the bathroom?
And why didn't I ask
where it was before now?
[KUJO]
Understood, of course.
Thank you, yes.
We're also looking
into the matter,
but considering my position,
my hands are pretty much tied.
Right. Yes, I know.
I'm not about to get picky now.
I'll go ahead and take
care of the sales records
concerning that drug
as soon as possible.
[IZUMI gasps]
[floor creaks]
[KUJO]
Hm?
No, you can go on.
[IZUMI]
So... Mr. Kujo is...
[MIYASE]
Ms. Izumi?
Huh?
[MIYASE]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[IZUMI]
Thank goodness.
So, then...
I guess you really are the
person I met the other day.
[MIYASE chuckles]
My apologies.
I can't believe this
awful weather.
So... I guess the storm
woke you up, too?
Tell me, can I help you?
Mr. Kujo...
What kind of person
is he, exactly?
To everyone here, I mean.
Well, it's complicated,
but I guess you could say
that when it comes down to it,
everyone here owes him
a great debt of gratitude,
and we've all made
the decision to be here
of our own free will.
Therefore...
I'm committed to seeing
my job through,
no matter what happens.
That sounds intense.
Do you mean...
You think something
actually will happen?
Does Mr. Kujo...
Does this household
have some kind of secret
it keeps from the world?
Forgive me for asking,
and please believe me
when I say I don't want
to suspect someone
you and Mr. Kirishima
look up to so highly.
But...
I can't look away from the
truth no matter what it is.
[MIYASE]
Very well.
Why don't you follow me?
[keyboard clicking]
[IZUMI]
So, are you... hacking?
[KANAME]
Yeah, something like that.
I'm only doing it because
Go here asked me to.
But if we get caught, this is
definitely gonna cause
trouble, isn't it?
I'm terribly sorry for
dragging you into all of this.
It's just...
I really want to prove
Mr. Kujo's innocence.
[KANAME] And you think she'll
be able to make that happen?
Well, what do you
think about that?
Can you do it?
[IZUMI]
If I'm honest...
...I don't know yet.
I still have no
clue what's wrong,
or what's right,
for that matter.
The thing is...
...I don't actually
know who holds the truth
I'm looking for.
Right now, I just need
to see with my own eyes.
I've got to determine
what's really true.
And that's why...
I need more information.
[KANAME]
Here you go.
Looks like data
regarding some drug.
[IZUMI]
Square. Plus‐0.
Could this be the one?
The experimental drug that
Omori was manufacturing?