[SEKI]
Plus‐0?
Its official name is SQUARE.
In the sample photo we received,
there were two tablets
in one set.
Well, the good news is,
we can pretty much confirm
just from the reports Izumi's
gathered that SQUARE
is what Plus was
directly modeled after.
Which means,
we can be fairly confident
it's the new drug
Omori Pharmaceuticals
was in the process
of developing.
Wait, if we already
know that the data needed
to create Plus came
from the Kujo Family,
then doesn't that mean
we've actually caught
Mr. Kujo red‐handed?
See, I believe in Mr. Kujo,
and my mind won't
change on that.
Miss Izumi.
Knowing all of that,
would you still be willing
to take my hand?
[IZUMI] All of that is
exactly why I asked
for your help, Mr. Miyase.
Very well, then.
I'll help you however I can.
[SEKI] I dunno what, but the
brass is plotting something.
And let's not forget the
fact that all the candidates
for STAND seem to be tied
to the Anonymous Case
in one way or another.
That's right.
I've been trying to figure
out why STAND was created.
Aoyama has, too.
But we haven't found
anything so far.
The more we look into
the agency's history,
the more it feels like they're
trying to hide something.
[HATTORI] I gave you
fair warning, didn't I?
But you still poked your
nose where it doesn't belong.
So you were the one
who sent that threat,
Mr. Hattori?
[HATTORI] I really thought that
would keep you from getting
too involved.
But I didn't figure
you would join forces
with someone involved
with the Kujo Family.
And now, you've even started
investigating STAND itself.
Honestly, you just won't
listen to anyone, will you?
You want to find out what
STAND is trying to accomplish.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Well...
In that case, you'll
definitely need to learn
some backstory on the suspect
from the Anonymous Case.
So, pop quiz for you,
Damsel of the DCD.
Tell me, when justice
is taken too far,
how do you know where
it should end?
Huh?
[COP A]
Make the BPA a priority.
Do we have an ID?
Kumi Mochizuki, 22 years old.
She's been a staying at this
hotel for the past three days.
[HATTORI]
Masayoshi, look at‐‐
[IDA]
Over here.
The victim had track marks
on the inside of her elbow.
They're probably from drug use‐‐
[IDA]
Yeah, here.
Have forensics analyze this.
I'm going to contact the chief.
He all right?
He seems upset.
Well, it's a
drug‐related case now.
Ah, that would do it.
I've heard he's still pretty
bothered by what happened
to the victim in that
car wreck incident.
[HATTORI] Once upon a time,
there was a certain detective
in Investigation Section One
named Masayoshi Ida.
He especially resented any
case that involved drugs.
How's he doing today?
[IDA]
Hey, there.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
It's fine.
The hotel case is closed
and suspect is in custody.
No other pressing
matters for now.
It's closed, huh?
It's hard for you.
Why not let go?
There are people
suffering out there.
I want to protect as many
as are within my reach.
That's what justice is for me.
We should get going.
[HATTORI] Ida's lifelong
ambition was to ensure that
there would be no more victims
of drug‐related crimes.
To that end, he was
working with someone
in a different field
who shared his vision.
His name was Yuki Hibiya.
Hibiya was in the
middle of developing
a new drug at the time.
A drug they thought would
help them achieve their goal.
Apparently, Ida was personally
supporting Hibiya's work.
[HATTORI] To see them together,
you would think
they were close friends.
Then one night,
I got a call.
[phone rings]
Hello?
[IDA]
I killed him.
Masayoshi?
[IDA]
Yuki. He's dead.
Yuki is...?
Did you say that you killed him?
[IDA]
Sorry.
[HATTORI]
Where are you right now?
[IDA]
We had the same goal.
But this was, it had to be,
a sacrifice for justice.
Masayoshi!
[line clicks]
Yuki! Yuki!
Stay back.
[COP B]
This one is pretty gruesome.
[COP A]
Who could do that to someone?
[MPD BRASS 1A] The victim has
now been identified as
Yuki Hibiya.
The suspect is Masayoshi Ida,
a member of the MPD.
He's taken a hostage
and is currently at large.
This case must absolutely
be kept quiet from the media.
Make sure you conduct this
investigation carefully.
We have no leads.
We need to settle
this, and fast.
I'm worried about
the kid who got taken.
Hey, this has to be a mistake.
Ida wouldn't do something like
this without good reason, right?
[COP A]
Don't start.
[door opens]
There have been reports
that a man resembling Ida
was spotted in a
neighborhood in Kita Ward.
We suspect he's hiding in
an empty house in that area.
We're moving in on him at once.
You all have clearance
to take your guns.
Hiding out?
[COP A]
Hey! Are you all right?
[COP B]
We've secured the hostage.
He appears to be unharmed.
‐‐[COP C] Where's our target?
‐‐[COP A] Damn it!
He's gone again?
[IDA]
Good work, kid.
Masayoshi.
[IDA]
How's the hostage?
[HATTORI]
He's just been recovered.
[IDA]
I see.
I'm surprised you found me here.
You may have made
some mistakes, but
you're not careless enough
to leak your location.
That place was a decoy.
This was the only place
it made sense for you to go.
Where the other investigators
wouldn't think to look.
So you tried to find
a building that could see
her hospital room.
Good instincts.
[HATTORI]
No, you did this intentionally.
It didn't matter where
you were as long as I was
the one who knew
how to find you.
Oh?
You had plenty of time to visit
her again before you left.
If there was any reason
at all for you to stay
in the city, it would be me.
[IDA] I have to say...
I'm proud of you.
I doubt you want to
hear that from me, though.
Listen while I smoke.
That's all I ask.
I'll start from the beginning.
As I know you're aware,
Yuki and I were working on
a solution to rid the world
of drug‐related crimes.
And to make that happen,
we were developing our own drug.
SQUARE. A new tool for justice.
One that would help cure
junkies of their addictions.
That was our dream.
If it had been completed,
it would've been
the first step to limiting
incidents involving
substance abuse.
I always said Yu was
a genius for coming up
with that idea.
So obviously he had my support.
Omori Pharmaceuticals
was on board
to get production
started on the drug,
and for a while it
looked like everything
was going off without a hitch.
But problems arose
during the clinical trials,
and production
was quickly canceled.
Although it appears now
that all those records
have been wiped.
Yu secretly transferred the data
and continued his research,
but then suddenly
said he was quitting.
It was the day of that storm.
Why quit then?
He said that some bad
people were after him.
Watching him.
So then he wanted to destroy
the data on the drug
before it fell into
the wrong hands.
He ran away.
His idea of justice ended
when his own wellbeing
was threatened.
[HATTORI]
And that was worth killing over?
Like I said before.
This was a sacrifice
for the greater good.
You know,
a former detective shouldn't
say things like that.
I know the MPD is trying
to keep this under wraps,
but at the very least,
I wanted you to know
the entire story.
Well, see ya.
Hold it!
Ida!
I'm sorry.
[HATTORI] That was the
last time any of us saw Ida.
Police have kept him, Hibiya,
and the SQUARE incident quiet
to the public ever since.
It's been 15 years.
[HATTORI] And that's
the whole truth of it.
Now that you've heard all this,
I bet you can put the pieces
together and find the answers
you've been looking
so diligently for.
That means that...
STAND was established
to investigate unsolved cases,
and that much, at least,
is still true.
However, the reason the
Anonymous Case was prioritized
is because the MPD's top
brass needs it gone ASAP.
They would have to make it
so the case never happened
to hide that one of their
own was responsible.
That's their motive?
Imagine the backlash over
a detective being involved.
Can't blame them for wanting
to avoid a public scandal,
I guess.
It doesn't happen
all that often,
but this is actually
pretty standard procedure.
But knowing all that,
how are you still willing
to give STAND everything
they need to close this case?
Are you...
You want to know
if I'm helping them
with their coverup, yeah?
You're still so naïve.
Regardless of what
the brass wants done,
I have my own motives here.
I'm gonna find Ida and
make him pay for what he did.
And to make that happen,
I don't mind following
orders from above.
At least for now, anyway.
And is that what
justice means to you?
Why?
Why would you explain
all of this to an outsider
like me?
I wonder... Why would that be?
There's something
you need my help with,
isn't there?
I want Makoto Tsuduki to talk.
[HATTORI] As you know,
we've had him in custody
for questioning for a while now,
albeit somewhat forcibly.
That would be because he's
deeply involved with Ida.
His little sister, Sara,
was the victim of an accident
caused by someone on drugs.
Ida was the detective
assigned to that case.
Even after the investigation
was completed,
Ida continued to make
regular visits to check in
on the Tsuduki brothers.
Makoto more often than Kyosuke.
Naturally, we think he
knows things about Ida
that we don't.
He might even have some
idea of where we can
find him now.
And you haven't been
able to get it out of him yet.
But there's no guarantee
that Makoto would have
that information in
the first place, is there?
He hasn't told us a
single thing the entire time
we've had him in custody.
Not just about Ida.
I mean he hasn't said a word
to us about anything in general.
Do you really think
someone with no information
would intentionally
keep quiet for that long?
I know Makoto Tsuduki
is hiding something.
Sadly, despite our best
efforts, we're empty‐handed.
And that's where you
come in. Understand?
I don't think I'm
the person you need.
I know you're
investigating Plus,
and I think this could help.
Why not? It's a win‐win.
Have you figured out
that the base for Plus
was SQUARE, the drug Ida
and Hibiya was producing?
Uh, well...
[HATTORI] Then you already have
everything you need to know.
If Tsuduki will talk,
we'll be that much closer
to solving the Anonymous Case.
And if you're lucky,
you might be able to dig
a little deeper into
both Plus and SQUARE.
How do you figure that?
When Ida disappeared,
he took some things that
Hibiya didn't get to destroy.
In fact, one of the
items that disappeared
along with him was a flash drive
from Omori Pharmaceuticals.
It contains the research and
clinical trial data for SQUARE.
It's a special kind of device.
Whenever it gets plugged
into a computer,
the location of that
computer is revealed.
A few years ago,
we happened to pick up a signal
from that specific flash drive.
It came from the Kujo household.
[HATTORI]
We followed up on that lead.
We found out that
someone had seen Ida
near the Kujo Family
household around the time
of the Anonymous Case.
The bad guys Hibiya
was so afraid of...
They had to be the Kujo Family.
That's strange, though.
How would they have gotten
their hands on the data?
[HATTORI]
Doesn't matter.
We know right now
that Plus was created
from the data that
was on that flash drive,
and it's thought to
have been distributed
through the Kujos'
personal route.
What you're trying to uncover
is very closely connected
to what STAND wants.
I really don't think
it would hurt for us
to work together.
I do think it's a
tempting opportunity.
But I'm not sure how I can help.
Am I the right person for this?
Oh. Modest, aren't you?
And that's even after you've
managed to tame
‐‐our little Sosei.
‐‐[IZUMI] Huh?
Not to mention it
looks like you've gained
Revel's trust, too.
Especially Maki's.
Maki's trust?
I'm hoping you can
win over Tsuduki
in the same way and
finally get him talking.
I'm not sure.
[HATTORI]
Just remember from here on out,
everything is extremely risky.
I can't take
responsibility for you,
and your life will be in danger.
Are you still
prepared to do this?
As long as people are
suffering from drugs,
I'll do anything.
I want to save as many
as are within my reach.
I don't know if that's
what real justice is or not.
But, if there's something
I can do right now
to help anyone, anywhere...
...I'll always be ready for it.
Well, all right.
You're definitely not
like them, are you?
Very good.
Then I guess I ought
to make up my mind, too.
[IZUMI]
When justice is taken too far,
how do you know
where it should end?
I wonder how
Mr. Hattori has felt,
having to live with
this case for so long.
You know she is definitely
hiding something, right?
Maybe.
[phone chimes]
Hey, this is huge,
you have to hear this!
What is all this fuss about?
[SUGANO] I just ran into Mr.
Hattori and he said he was
going to negotiate directly
with the upper brass.
Negotiate?
Are they finally going
to address this shoddy
filing system?
It's about time
somebody brought this up.
That's not it.
He's going to have Rei
go talk to Makoto Tsuduki.
[ASAGIRI]
Very well, then.
Are you‐‐? You're not
even a little surprised?
[ASAGIRI] That just means he's
finally taking this seriously.
[NATSUME] What? Mr. Hattori
was the one threatening you?
Izumi, he didn't try
anything weird with you, right?
No. I'm perfectly fine.
Just give me a second
to explain, okay?
[YUI] I insist on examining
you this instant!
Behave yourself.
Do you think Rei
will be all right?
It's starting to sound
like she stuck her nose
into something pretty heavy.
I can't say that I'm
not worried about her,
but I heard from Hattori
and he apparently
has her back in all
of this, as well.
Can't believe the MPD
had something like this
happening behind the scenes.
We're starting to see it now.
The truth about STAND.
[IZUMI]
STAND. SQUARE.
The Anonymous Case.
All the separate little
fragments are starting
to form a clearer picture.
One coherent shape.
And the last few pieces
of the puzzle
are only just out of reach.
We're so close now.
But I'm afraid that once
all of those pieces
finally do fall into place,
a difficult truth is
going to be revealed.
And when it does,
someone is going to get hurt.