Thank you for the help, children.
I really appreciate it.
You may have more hands than the rest of us,
but it'd still be a stretch for you to
carry all this lab equipment by yourself.
Exactly. Now, it's a one-trip job!
No wonder you were both elected class officers.
So reliable!
Thanks, but you really could've done this without us.
Couple of quick trips back and forth.
I supposed I could've, yes.
But the more the merrier, eh?
I have a question, sir.
Yes?
Are you starting to feel at home?
Like, with all of us?
Wow. I can't believe you're really asking him that.
Put in those terms, I'd say I feel
incredibly at home as your teacher.
That's strange.
Really?
Well, yeah.
A creature like you taking any interest whatsoever
in a group of junior high kids isn't
exactly something you see every day.
I mean, you actually teach us, so it's borderline cool.
Just takes getting used to.
Yeah, no kidding.
Then there's the whole assassination thing.
A vital part of my role, I'd argue.
Target, teacher. We ought not separate the two.
Did he seriously just dodge
three knives while prepping lab?
Hey, Maehara. You okay?
Eh.
They should know by now that
was too obvious. Am I right, Teach?
All right, boys and girls, let's begin!
Whoa! It's bright red!
Ta-da!
And that's how we extract the
coloring from processed foods.
I'll, uh...
I'll just take the leftover samples, thank you.
Excuse me.
Wait! We bought those for ourselves!
Is it me, or did he just use this lab to
support his junk-food habit between paychecks?
My question's why a super organism has to
live on a teacher's salary in the first place.
Eh?
I, uh...
Well, uh...
Go on, speak up, Okuda.
What can I do for you?
Umm!
Poison, sir! Would you drink it, please?!
Well, she doesn't beat around the bush.
I'm sorry. Is this weird?
It's certainly a very straightforward
assassination attempt, I'll give you that.
See, the thing is, sir, I'm not very good at being
sneaky. I mean, everyone else is so good at this stuff.
But, me? What I'm good at is chemistry!
And I put my heart and soul into this mixture!
All righty, then.
Um, Okuda?
Points for throwing in, but no one's that stupid.
Your heart and soul?
Don't mind if I do, then!
This-This is!
Is it really gonna work?
This might be it!
Or he could just grew horns.
Quite a kick.
Sodium hydroxide, I believe? Good try, Miss Okuda.
If I were human, I'd most definitely have bought the farm.
Oh, I see.
Shall I try the other two we have here as well?
Yes, please!
Right! Down the hatch!
He grew wings this time?!
Wow, he's starting to look kinda fancy.
Thallium acetate. Interesting.
Let's see what the last one does.
Uh-oh!
Not sure I wanna see this!
That's boring.
This just keeps getting weirder and weirder.
I don't like this look. It's creeping me out.
So poison turns him into an emoticon?
If you hate me, I understand.
But please, don't hate assassination.
What's that even supposed to mean?!
Also, young lady. As your teacher,
I can't overlook the fact that you
handled toxic substances unsupervised.
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Why don't we work together on a poison
that has a little bit more of a kick?
Uh, sure!
Doesn't seem like that's gonna
end in success if you ask me.
Might get some good notes out of it at least.
Heads up!
I got it!
Yeah!
All right, that's what I'm talking about!
Hey there, big boy. How's tricks?
It's an absolute sauna in here.
Ugh. Aren't you on fire?
That's not the word I would use, no.
Look, save this act for the target. Back off.
Ugh, I swear, you're such a killjoy.
If you're gonna cut it here
as a teacher, pull it together.
I thought we had discussed this.
For your information, it's not an act.
It's hotter than hell in this dump.
How do they expect these kids to function without AC?
I've tried to put in several requests for renovations,
but the funds aren't there. Or so I'm told.
Seriously?
Damn it!
Everyone saw, right?
That was a clean hit!
Can't be helped. It's how things are here.
Okey-dokey.
We're ready to add it to the ethanol, I think.
Now, be extra careful. Don't breathe in the fumes.
Got it!
It's a shame your enthusiasm for
chemistry doesn't extend to other subjects.
Heh. Everything else seems to go over my head.
Especially when it comes to language arts and stuff.
That's why I'm here, I guess.
I never know the right thing to say.
The words don't come out or I get 'em all turned around.
Tell me to express myself and I seize up.
Hmm...
It's okay. I don't mind so much.
At least with math and science,
there's always a right answer.
Everything's spelled out for you.
They're concise.
No double meanings, no weird feels.
No worrying that someone'll take your words the wrong way.
It makes perfect sense.
I see the appeal.
Tell you what, Okuda.
I have a special homework assignment just for you.
Remember, though. Safety first.
Um...
Okay, so he really asked you to bring the poison to class?
Yeah! He said the stuff in this
flask should work like a charm!
He even drew a manga of the safety guidelines
for proper use and storage. I'm impressed.
Going the extra mile yet again.
I know he's unconventional and all,
but giving us the goods on a poison that'll kill him?
Nice, right?
I think it's his way of encouraging me.
I'm good at chemistry, not words.
He says to focus on my strengths!
Good morning, everyone.
Here's your chance. Go give it to him!
Here it is, sir.
Just like you asked.
Ah! Nice work.
Well, here's to your health, children.
Salud!
Thank you, Okuda.
Thank you very much indeed.
This concoction is precisely what I needed to level up.
Wait, you... I don't...
Pyuu.
He melted?!
You didn't think that was a poison, did you?
On the contrary. I had you whip up a
special tonic designed to increase my fluidity.
In liquid form, I fit comfortably
into the tightest nooks and crannies.
What are you doing in there?
Best of all, I lose none of my speed!
Go ahead! Try to beat me! Come on!
This is messed up, dude!
What in the world did you give him?!
You tricked me! That's not fair!
Hmm... Fair?
Verbal deception is a vital part
of the successful assassin's toolkit.
Huh?
What are you talking about, sir?
Approaching the target so naively
is a good way to fail in your mission.
Even the deadliest of poisons is useless
if one can't persuade the mark to drink it.
Nagisa. Say you wanted to poison me.
How might you go about it?
Huh? Well, lemme think.
I'd probably put it in something you liked.
For you!
For me?
Then I guess I would offer it to you as a gift.
Excellent.
You see, to deceive someone you
have to get inside their heads;
know what they respond to. Use language creatively.
In poisoning, as in life, the
key to success is communication.
Imagine that one day, you make an
Earth-shattering scientific discovery.
How can it benefit mankind if
it stays locked inside your head?
Knowing the right thing so say
can make all the difference, right?
Right! Thank you, sir!
Nice move, Teach. Turn the tables, huh?
No kidding.
Leave it to Koro-sensei.
To him, even a student trying to poison him is still,
first and foremost, a student.
We're a long way off from being able to kill him.
He's just that good.
Quit dragging your feet.
We show up late again, there's no telling
what kind of messed up stuff they'll make us do.
Yeah. Last time we had to clean out the flower beds.
Heh. Man, that blew.
Those friggin' things are the size of a house.
What are you bitching about?
We did all the work.
I was moral support!
This sucks!
Somebody explain to me why
we're the only students in school
who have to put up with this crap!
Surprise!
Hey! Is that Kunudon?
Hello! It's me, Kunudon!
Hooray!
Today, we're going to talk about underachievers!
Here, we like to give them a special place all their own!
A place called E Class, where they
won't bother the good boys and girls!
Wow! What a great idea!
Now we don't normally like it when E Class students
set foot on the main campus. But we do make exceptions
for school assemblies, when we invite them
to take a stroll down the mountain on their lunch break.
Ahh! The stupid bridge is out!
No way!
Who's the genius who told us this was a shortcut?!
Okajima!
Discipline is key! 'Specially for E Class slobs.
And nothing instills discipline like lining up
inside the gymnasium for special assemblies, kids!
Discipline!
Why are there snakes?!
Look out, Okajima!
Come on, maggots, get in gear!
Give me a "sir, yes sir!" Now!
Sir, yes, sir! Hooray!
Why are there falling boulders?!
Oh! Crap! Look out, Okajima!
Whose big idea was it to poke the beehive?!
Look out, Okajima!
He's, uh, not having a very good day, is he?
Hope the poor guy's all right.
Me, too.
Ugh. Can we be done with the rocks
and the bees and the things trying to kill us, please?
I'm glad Okajima was around
to take the brunt of it for us.
Hey. Anyone hurt?
I think we're mostly okay.
Good. No rush.
In fact, at this rate, we're making fairly excellent time.
Wait for me!
Way to ditch me, jerks!
Hey! Professor Bitch!
No one said anything about a class trip during lunch.
Yeah, no offense, Professor, but you look wrecked.
You try running through nature in heels!
Mr. Karasuma? Where's Koro-sensei?
We told him to wait back at the
old campus for security reasons.
It wouldn't do for the other students to see him.
I'm all alone. A shunned Sensei.
Well. The main campus isn't much further away.
Are you ready?
Yeah...
That sincerely sucked.
Well, at least we're not late.
No idea how that happened.
Hurry up, people!
We've got to get in line before they start!
Okay.
Hey, Nagisa!
Uh?
Wow, look at you guys!
I'm surprised you made it!
Must've been a heck of a trek rollin' down the mountain!
Once a month, there's an all-school assembly.
And even here we get treated like the lowest of the low.
Not something we look forward to,
but... not a lot we can do about it, either.
You are the cream of the crop.
This nation's shining elite. Never forget that.
I am proud to be your dean.
But!
Don't get too comfortable.
No. Let E Class remind us of the perils in that.
Now, now! It's unkind to laugh at their expense!
Hey, Nagisa. Why isn't Karma here?
Because he's ditching.
What?
Is he out of his mind?!
It's not like he doesn't know he'll catch hell
for blowing off assembly, he just doesn't care.
Wish I had the grades to get away with that.
They'd probably just throw me out.
Yeah, ain't that the truth.
If I may say so, sir,
this method is remarkably effective!
It shows in the percentage of students from our academy
who go on to top universities. E Class aside, of course.
We are pragmatists here.
Realists. Young people must be
prepared for the world as it is.
Sadly, the best way to ignite their potential
is to let them see it extinguished in others.
Very sound reasoning.
Yes, of course it is.
Whether in school administration or assassination,
I pride myself on adherence to logic.
Now we'll have an address by the student council.
Student council members, come up to the podium, please.
Who's that?
Never seen him before.
He looks way too cool to be a teacher!
I'd like to take this opportunity to introduce myself.
Oh. Hello.
You too?
Wow! Cool!
Yeah.
Hey. Check it, Mister K.
We decorated the thing we keep our knives in!
So stylish.
They're "totes adorable," yes! Now put them away!
We're supposed to keep this on the DL.
The other students can't know!
Oh, sorry.
I think he's the new E Class teacher.
Looks like he's big on the hands-on approach.
No fair. Why can't the regular teachers be that hot?
I mean, seriously, is there some kind of rule?
Whoa! Who's the boobalicious foreign-looking chick?!
Five minutes ago she was down on all fours,
but damn, look at 'er work it!
Slow down. I'm dying!
Quick recovery, huh?
Don't tell me she's an E Class teacher, too?
So jealous...
What are you doing here?
Don't even try to pull rank on me.
I'm an educator just like you are.
So you're finally embracing your role?
Or, I just need an excuse to scope out the student body.
Me-ow. Said nobody ever.
Oh. That's right.
Nagisa. The octopus isn't around. Talk to me.
Gimme some Intel. You're still keeping a record of
all the ooey-gooey bastard's vulnerable points, right?
Let teacher peek at your notebook
and I'll make it worth your while.
Uh. I, uh, haven't added anything
to it since the last time you looked.
Please, sweetheart. You and I both know you're
keeping the good stuff all to your lonesome.
Actually, I've shared every...
Ugh. Come on now, kid.
Dish. Or I'll smother you.
Stop it, Professor Bitch! I can't
breathe through your enormous ta-tas!
What a teacher.
What a... bitch.
What the hell? Are you kidding me?
The End Class douche bags aren't
supposed to get any special perks!
Oww!
Okay. All the upcoming student council events
are detailed in the handouts you've just been given.
Uh. Hang on. How come we didn't get any?
Uh, excuse me, sir?
E Class didn't get the handouts.
Oh. Wow, really? That's kind of bizarre.
Huh. I'm so sorry. I thought for
sure we printed enough for everyone!
Guess E Class will just have to
memorize it off their neighbors'.
That works out for the best, really.
I mean, you people could use
the mental exercise I'm guessing.
What a little prick. Somebody ought to...
There you go, Isogai.
Seriously?!
That should take care of it, I think.
All of you have a copy of the handout now, correct?
Yes, Sir!
Never mind. We have some. My mistake, sorry.
You what?! But, I... How did you...
Okay, who's the wise guy? Who killed our fun?
I mean. Ahem! As I was saying before.
Um, if you'll take a closer look at the events schedule,
you'll notice we have quite a few things packed...
I thought we agreed we couldn't
let the other students see you.
What part of "state secret" do you refuse to understand?
Relax. My disguise is flawless.
No one suspects a thing.
Looks like somebody got a little lonely.
Can't say I blame the guy.
Hey. Was that teacher standing there a second ago?
I dunno, what's with him bein' all big and, like, wriggly?
Yeah. And what's with the hot one trying to stab him?
Is that a thing? Can she do that?
I can get him, let go!
The other one's got her in some kind of hold.
That class is crazy.
Oh well. I'll say this much for her, she never quits.
We're gonna run on ahead, Nagisa.
Cool. I'll grab a drink and catch up with you.
Yo, Nagisa.
Uh?
You proud of yourselves?
Acting like you're havin' the time of your lives?
Laughing during assembly.
Not cool.
You bums ever hear of respect?
If I was in E Class, I'd keep
my head down and my mouth shut.
Yeah, and I sure as hell wouldn't have a reason to laugh.
Hey. Watch it with that look, I'm warnin' ya.
Hmm?
This whole stupid system is a travesty.
Easy does it.
The boy can handle himself.
My students know how to deal with bullies.
Something you wanna say, scumbag?
You want me to kill your ass?!
Kill? You're kidding, right?
You're really gonna kill me?
Heh.
Like you've got the balls to try.
Go right ahead.
Dude, what... What was that all about?
Damn. He's a psycho.
What did I tell you?
They have more self-respect than to roll over for a bully.
Huh...
Interesting.
An E Class reprobate presuming to shove his betters?
Hmph. What nonsense. This behavior is unacceptable.
It would appear a few tweaks are in order.
Assassination can wait.
For now, my priority is the status quo.