Our infiltration of the Fuma Denjo hotel is underway.
We're closing in on the antidote. Hopefully.
Time is running out. Unless we make it to the
top floor, and soon, our classmates might die.
Seem fairly average for a pro, if you ask me.
And is breaking glass supposed to
be intimidating? 'Cause I can do that.
But I wouldn't call in reinforcements as an opening move.
But then, I'm not especially
threatened by "a bunch of amateurs."
Ah...
All right. Put your money where your mouth is.
If you insist.
Nice try, kid. But, as weapons
go, hun, I'd have gone with harder.
I guess I'll have to do without.
Uh...
This dude's grip could crush a grown man's skull
like an egg. He gets his mitts on me, it's game over.
Heh. The odds are definitely not in my favor.
Nothing unusual about that.
But in the end, this is just like any other game.
Just like school.
Uh.
Whoa...
Oh, wow. He's blocking like an expert!
Those are your defensive moves,
are they not, Mr. Karasuma?
For assassins, self-defense doesn't often come into play.
I don't recall having actively taught him any of this.
There's no denying it, though.
These moves are how I handled their attacks in class.
Damned impressive. This kid's a natural-born fighter.
A cut above his peers, even in a classroom of assassins.
I can dodge him all day,
but if I move in for a hit, this prick's gonna grab me.
Hm? What's the problem? Evasive maneuvers ain't
gonna win this. You have'ta come in for an attack!
Oh, you don't say?
And what if really all I'm tryin' to do is
keep you occupied? I mean, my buddies are kinda
hopin' to sneak by, so, maybe I'm just bein' clever.
Aw, relax. I'm pretty underhanded on the best of days.
But this is one fight I wanna win fair and square.
No tricks, no cheating, no holdin' out.
Just you an' me. Now, like men.
Be my guest, hun. I like the cut of your jib.
See, this is what I've been talkin' about!
Two equals, mano y mano. A real battle to the death, hun.
Hm?
There's my in!
Say goodnight, you little punk.
Oh, no!
Sorry, kid.
You're underhanded on the best'a days.
I'm underhanded, like, every day.
You son of a bitch!
He wanted to fight you like a
man and this is how you respond?
Oh come on. This ain't the place
for that, kid; get over it, hun.
Look, you can't get hung up on ethics. I'm an assassin.
This biz don't reward folks who play by the rules.
Hun, if you got a canister of gas?
Use it. If he was all that, he'd have done the same...
Uh?!
Uh... You.... Ah.
Guess great minds think alike.
Now what was it were you saying about me being "all that?"
How di... How did you not... breathe it in?
I... I sprayed you... at point blank range.
You should be paralyzed, hun.
C'mon, Terasaka! What are you waiting for?
I'm gonna need duct tape and every free
hand we got to hold this crazy bastard down!
Yeah, all right. Fine.
You've been yankin' this creep's chain all along, huh?
Fair fight, my ass!
Stay on guard while you're taping him up.
He's incapacitated, but he might be
strong enough to spring back before too long.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Handy, right?
Lifted it off that Smog weirdo a while ago.
Still, disappointing it's a "one-time-use" type-a deal.
How did you see it comin'?
You must've held your breath when I sprayed you.
How'd you know to do that when my hands were empty?
No way you could've told I had anything on me! Ugh! Hun.
That's the whole point.
With you, I was on guard
against everything but bare hands.
Hun.
As far as I know, you probably were
lookin' forward to an honest fight.
But you're also on someone else's
payroll, so you don't get to choose.
You'd've had to stop us by any means necessary.
I would've done the exact same thing in your shoes.
In a way, my mistrust was a compliment.
He's really good.
Yes, he is. And he's changed, for the better.
The anguish of defeat had never
darkened Karma's door. Finals provided
our cocky comrade a much-needed reality check.
Failure humanized the perspective of his former foes.
He suddenly found himself among their number.
His picture of the world altered drastically,
leaving him with a healthy respect for those around him.
He was able to foresee his adversary's moves
because he didn't underestimate his abilities.
Something he only learned through his previous failure.
We must see our opponent, not
as an obstacle, but as a person.
Toiling in the shadow of defeat, we taste true victory.
It is a pleasure to see you
take the lesson to heart, Karma.
I'm very excited about what your future holds in store.
Hm. Hun, hats off to ya. You're nothin' to sneeze at.
I may be beaten, but it was a pleasure to know that you...
Oh, we're not done.
No, I'm just getting started.
Mm?
What in the hell are those s'posed to be?
Mustard and wasabi.
You never know when you're
gonna need 'em to shove up a nose.
You do what?
Part of keepin' my guard up meant I had to play nice.
But, hey, now what we've got
you all bound up, I can let loose.
You'll wanna hold still or that special
clip's gonna rip your nostrils off.
Now let's see. You've got your jalapenos,
your hatch chilies, your ghost peppers,
those are a kick in the balls, right?
And a pinch of garlic for hearth-health.
Well, hun, what cha think?
Show us that samurai willpower?
So, uh. I notice Karma's still a sadist.
I'm very concerned about what his future holds in store.
Who walks around with this stuff in their bag? Ugh.
Can we keep movin', please? Someone'll spot us.
'cause you stick out like a sore thumb.
Ha, ha.
Attention. The terrace is just up these stairs.
Might be tricky. This is the club floor.
Correct.
The Executive Floor can be accessed via
the staircase just off the lounge area.
Unfortunately, the back entrance has a manual lock on it,
so we'll need to detour around
and through the bar to open it
and let the others in.
So we're flying by the seat of our pants.
A bar's the last place we belong.
Koro-Sensei and Mr. K, you hide here.
Leave the tricky part to those best qualified.
We'll unlock the door to the VIP stairs.
You fellas might be out of your dept in the club,
but us girls'll do just fine.
Yeah we will!
No way. I'm sorry, it's too dangerous.
Ah. Well, plan B?
Huh?
Ah...
Huh?!
Uh?! Uh... huh?
So awesome.
Yeah!
You can thank the CEO.
No kidding.
Thanks for the executive suite, mom and dad.
And all the douche-yachts rubbin'
shoulders with me to get at your money.
This shit is depressing. Lamest vacay ever.
Oh, be a man already!
You're here to protect us, not use us as a shield!
Get in front!
I can't! Don't make me do this, please!
Stop it.
You look fabulous!
That's right. This is my life.
Quit whining. You're deep undercover.
We talked about this.
You won't arouse suspicion this way.
Did you have to say "arouse?"
Relax! It's all part of the plan.
It is?
You look stunning!
No, I do not!
Don't be so casual! Tart it up.
Whoa, wait! Are you my pimp all of a sudden?
Where'd this outfit come from anyway?
Next to the pool.
Consider it an anonymous donation.
Uh!
Hottie alert. First time I've seen her on the club scene.
This place is disgusting.
Let's unlock the door before some tool tries to hit on us.
Don't even.
You're milking this moment for all it's worth.
Yo!
Uh!
How you doin', shortie? Papa wants to buy you a drink.
Anything you want, heh, heh! My treat. For reals.
Go on, Nagisa. Don't be an ice queen.
Wha... I thought we had a deal!
The deal is we act natural. Now get in there!
We'll swing back around for you.
Ah... How did my life get to this place?!
Nagisa's a really cute name for a girl.
Anyway, I'm Yuji.
Okay, let's make a break for it.
I think we go up the side stairs. Let me check the map.
Right. Should be just up ahead a little further.
Hey, hey. What's the hurry, doll?
You girls look like you could use a little company.
Ugh.
Is this what I have to look
forward to every time we go out?
Look, bro. I hate to disappoint you...
Yada?
Hiya boys. Wow, you two are stacked.
Look, we'd love to chill, but our
daddies keep us on a short leash.
Yeah, I know it sucks, but what're you gonna do?
Helicopter parents.
Huh?! Tha... Th... Th... That's a yakuza pin!
Not just any yakuza pin!
That's the emblem of the relatively small
but absolutely terrifying Shuei Syndicate!
Sorry we bothered you!
Okay, bye! And that's how you
separate the men from the boys.
Why do you have a yakuza pin?
C'mon, drink up! I'm buyin'!
We're livin' large tonight!
Uh! I'm too... Uh, I mean,
I don't like the way alcohol tastes.
Keep it together, Nagisa.
Hold his interest long enough to give
the girls a chance to unlock the door.
So what brings you to this place? Your friends?
Your mom and dad?
Mom and dad?
As if the two of them would give me the time of day! Hey!
Wanna know a secret? Don't
tell anyone, but my dad's on TV.
Like, uber famous.
You'd know 'im if you saw 'im, trust me.
He's huge. Paparazzi hound him all the time.
Dude can't get away with jack.
'Least not in public! One time, he was tellin' me
about this anchor chick he kept fondling under the table
when they'd cut to commercial.
That sounds skeezy. Does he brag about stuff like that?
Damn it. Way to go, dumbass.
Real smooth. Can't you make an impression
without bringing up the old man? I'm so lame!
Uh, smoking's really bad for you,
'specially that stuff.
Heh. What're you, the surgeon general?
Come on, it's cool.
People just need to loosen up every once in a while.
My teacher calls this a gateway substance.
Says it puts unsuspecting kids on the road to addiction.
Recreational drugs aren't the answer to life's problems.
Yeah, well!
What's your teacher know about my problems?
Guys have it rough.
We gotta be cool twenty-four-seven just to score!
You try bein' somebody when all people
do is compare you to your celebrity dad!
You girls. Y'all don't have a clue how it is!
All you have to do it put on a li'l
makeup, walk into a club and take your pick!
Uh...
I can't speak for most girls,
but the ones I know have a lot more on their minds.
Oh! That's from Professor Bitch's pin collection!
That woman is something else.
Yakuza overlord, horse breeder.
Any pin you can think of, she's
got it and knows how to walk the walk.
Wow that line of work totally
fascinates you, doesn't it, Yada?
You're always picking her brain about different stuff.
Yeah. It's like Koro-Sensei always says about our
"second blade." And, Professor Bitch has more than two.
I like an extensive skill set.
See whatever job she's dropped into, she has a strategy.
That's what you call serious life-competence.
I bet one day when you grow
up, you'll be exactly like her!
Never thought I'd respect a girl with huge melons.
Wow! Kaede's made a real breakthrough, everyone!
Okay. There's the door.
They have a guard posted, though. We didn't count on that.
Not to be that girl, but I
think we might need a man for this.
Well, damn. Okay, Kaede.
Go and rescue Nagisa.
Sure!
Get a load of that face.
Something tells me we'd be better off not engaging.
Hell, even if we could take this guy,
he won't go down without makin noise.
Nagisa!
Uh. Oh, hey there.
Well, uh, it's been nice, but, yeah.
Gotta go!
Seriously? We just started talkin'!
We'll do it again sometime.
Damn it! Do somethin', bro!
She's slippin' through your fingers!
Don't leave me alone like that again!
Yeah, yeah, whatever. Look, we've have a problem.
Just what we need. At least tell me I can ditch the dress.
Not so fast, ladies!
Uh?!
You can't leave! Nah!
Not till you've taken in my signature dance moves!
Really?
This is it. I've got 'em!
No girl can resist the charms of my sweet moves!
Well, what do we have here? A regular tough-guy, huh?
Who me? No.
Shut it!
I'm sorry, man! It was an accident!
This jacket's worth more 'n your life!
Where do you live?
Look, please! I don't want any trouble...
This could be our chance.
You're gonna pay to have it cleaned, understand?
You can cut me a check, or I
can take it out of your ass now.
Wait! My dad's good for the money, I promise!
Just don't beat me up, I'm beggin' ya!
'Scuse me, Mr. Yakuza?
Yeah?
One, two.
Mr. Bouncer, we have a situation here.
I think this man's had one too many tequila shots.
Someone's gonna trip over the poor guy.
Thanks for pointing it out.
Upsy-daisy, leight weight. There we go.
All right, girls. Go for it!
You take those "signature moves"
back to the dance floor, okay?
You didn't see anything.
If you're anything like me, you probably feel humiliated.
It is hard being a guy if you
think it's all about playin' it cool.
Don't try so hard. Just do you.
You really think so?
Word to the wise for the whenever we meet again.
The coolest thing anyone can do is be themselves.
Mission accomplished!
That was some rather questionable
territory you had to navigate.
No one got hands-y with you, I hope?
Mm-mm.
We held our own.
Oh, you changed out of your dress. That was fast.
Not fast enough.
What's bothering you?
Nothing. I feel so stupid. I mean, let's face it.
You girls didn't need me in there.
I didn't contribute anything.
You were comic relief, dude! That's big!
Delete that immediately!
You did a lot, Nagisa.
I know one person who's better off 'cause you were there.
Uh...
Not gonna lie. That dress looked good on you.
Historically, an assassin who can pull off
either gender is a huge asset in the field.
I don't like where this is going.
He's right. 'Cept I'm not so sure I buy you as a dude.
I'd really appreciate it if we dropped the subject!
We're trying to be stealthy. Keep your voice down.
Right. Yes, sir.
We're in this operation's final phase.
Talk to me, Ritsu.
Yes, sir. The VIP floor is just around the corner.
The guests here don't rely
solely on hotel security, though.
They make it a point of bringing their own.
Man, these guys look like they
eat rent-a-cops for breakfast.
I'm demoralized.
You think they're in league with our target, or what?
I mean, technically they could anybody's minions, right?
Like it even matters.
Either way, we're gonna have
to take 'em down to get through.
Excellent point, Terasaka.
And to that end, the weapon you're hiding in your backpack
will more than suffice.
Tch. Great. You have X-ray vision in this form, too?
You'll have to take both guards down at
once to keep 'em from calling for backup.
Kinda figured as much, thanks.
Kimura, help me out.
I'll wait, you get out there and lead 'em this way.
Dude, are you crazy? How'm I s'posed to do that?
You figure it out!
I've got a good idea, if you're not a wuss.
Help you, kid?
Oh, wow!
Not a single active brain cell in sight! Nope!
Just two big dumb walls of meat wearing clothes!
Somebody really ought to call animal control. Sheesh.
Come here!
Why you runnin'?
Guess that did the trick!
Who the hell is the little piss-ant?
And why's he so fast?
Let's do it!
Right behind ya!
Hey wait, why stun guns?
Well, I bought 'em to see if they'd
be any good against the octopus.
But I never thought I'd be usin' them on actual people.
Those cost a fortune!
How'd you afford equipment like this?
Uh, I came into some money.
Odd jobs, mostly. Nothin' special.
Hang on. I've seen these guys before.
Expertly done, Terasaka.
I don't believe it would be remiss
to rifle through their pockets, do you?
Huh?
A bit of due diligence and one can find
the most useful of items on such gentlemen.
Real guns?
That's correct children. Chiba? Hayami?
I think you two should be the ones to have them.
Alas, Mr. Karasuma hasn't yet sufficiently
recovered from his encounter with Smog to handle a gun.
The reality of our situation is this:
you two are our best sharpshooters.
That's kinda out of left field, sir.
That said.
I'll allow no killing. That I won't.
Do not underestimate your skill. In the right hands,
a firearm is all the more
impressive for not causing injury.
I can't believe this... live ammo.
But, even when we had air guns, we froze.
Shall we proceed, children?
If our experience thus far is anything to go on,
the enemy's presence here is relatively modest.
By even the most conservative estimate,
we've thinned their ranks by half.
Yeah! That's what I'm sayin'!
Who's he got left?
Okay, team. Proceed with caution.
The next stage of infiltration is
the VIP-only emergency staircase.
There's an empty concert hall on the eighth
floor we'll have to sneak through to access it.
This whole affair is leaving a bad taste in my mouth.
Thought I was hired to snuff
out some kind of "super being".
How'd I get roped into playing cat-and-mouse
with a gaggle of pimply-faced twerps?
Disgusting. Oh, well.
I have just the thing to wash that taste out.
Huh?!