"Oh, sexy guy. It's a miracle!"
See?
Simple.
Icebreakers like this guarantee a good first impression.
Now, I'm sure we all know someone who's absolute
crap with small talk. Ha. Maybe we are that person.
The trick is to put yourself in the shoes of your target.
Kimura, throw me an ice-breaker, quick!
Uh.
Hey, there?
No, no!
You're just shifting the burden of conversation.
If you want a meaningful response, the other
person has to feel you're pulling your own weight.
Try coming at them guns blazing
with an interesting observation.
Okay?
Conversation is a challenge for
the best of us, and that's okay.
Don't think in terms of finding
the right words. Let them find you.
Just let the conversation flow.
Finesse it like a full-tongued kiss.
Ugh!
Teaching is such a pain in the ass!
At least the students are finally taking a shine to you.
Oh, yeah. Sure. 'Cause that's a load off.
Come on, I'm an assassin.
I'm supposed to be killing people,
not hunting octopus with brats.
And while we're on the subject of tentacled pervs...
the son of a bitch is staring at my tits!
Sipping tea doesn't make it classy!
Have I mentioned how much I
admire your "perky" teaching methods?
Shut your face!
Stand down. You know he's just pushing your buttons.
Yeah, well...
I'll push his buttons!
Hmm...
Hm. She's feisty today.
Huh. Can't imagine why that might be.
I have better things to do than
twiddle my thumbs in this dump.
If I could just bag the squirrelly bastard.
A snare trap?
Who the hell?!
You catch me off guard, Irina.
Watching you babysit bunch of kids.
It's like TV comedy show.
Sir. Why are you here?
What's going on here?
This is your only warning, pal.
Let her go.
Don't worry about it.
She knows how to handle herself.
Right.
So, uh.
Have we met each other somewhere, or is it just me?
We haven't met in person.
But you know my reputation.
I do freelance work for government.
As matter of fact, I'm the guy who arranged
to bring Irina Jelavich into
the mix. I'm human resources man.
Lovro the Assassin!
One of the most dangerous men who's ever lived.
Now retired.
Trains assassins and books
gigs for them all over the world.
Makes a killing. No pun intended.
At the crucial moment, he came through for us,
Jelavich is his protégé. But why is he here now?
This Koro-sensei fellow happen to be near?
I think he's in Shanghai picking up some almond jelly.
Left about a half-hour ago.
Should be back any minute.
So rumors of his speed haven't been exaggerated.
Well. Good. Glad I came when I did.
You run along home, Irina. I'll take it from here.
It's clear you're out of your depth.
Don't get me wrong:
on undercover jobs, you're the best.
Once your cover's been blown, however.
Well, let's face it, you're no Charlotte Corday.
You have to give me a chance, sir!
I can do this! I know I can!
He's fast.
What have I always taught you?
Everyone has their strengths and their weaknesses.
A good assassin knows when to go home.
Congratulations!
You're exactly half wrong and half right.
Hey, hey. Cool it, Game Show.
Another ridiculous nickname?
Are you determined never to call me Koro-sensei?
It's you.
I agree.
As an assassin, our beloved Irina is nothing special.
Frankly, she's crap.
No one was asking you!
Having said that, she belongs here.
She is, in fact, a perfect fit for this class.
Huh?
To prove my point, I propose a kill-off.
Let us see which of you passes muster.
Who is the better assassin?
The rules are simple.
Whomever kills our friend
Mr. Karasuma first is the winner.
Excuse me?
Why the hell am I the target here all of a sudden?
It has to be you, silly.
I'm un-killable.
Here. You have all day tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
So it's to be a pretend assassination.
Why not? Heh.
There are worse ways to pass time.
Suit yourself.
Is this your idea of sticking up for me?
Heh-ah?
Shut up! I know what this is:
you're hedging your bets on me
because you think I'm easier to
manage than some new schmuck, right?
Well, if you don't think I've got what it takes to kill
Karasuma and you, somebody's in for a rude awakening!
Huh...
So there it is. Expect a few disruptions today, and
hopefully it won't interfere with your studies too much.
Just carry on as normal, all right?
Eh...
Poor guy.
He just can't catch a break.
Yoo-hoo!
Hm?
Excellent work today!
I'll bet you've worked up quite a thirst. Aww!
Have an ice-cold beverage!
Here, go ahead and knock it back.
It tastes like a rainbow!
She drugged it.
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
Probably some sort of muscle relaxant.
Immobilize and stab, oldest trick in the book.
Uh!
What do you take me for?
No man in his right mind would let
you close enough to give him a drink.
Well. Why don't I just put in here so
you can take it at your leisure... Ow!
Oh... Ohh!
Pick me up, Karasuma!
Carry me piggyback? Please?
Have some self-respect. This is sad.
You okay, Professor Bitch?
Hey, no offense, but that little
ploy wouldn't have fooled anyone.
My options are limited, okay?
I can't seduce someone who knows my M.O!
Chalk it down to occupational hazard!
It's like a paid escort trying
to put the moves on her old man!
He knows her too well for her charms to land their mark!
That's sick!
Damn it.
I'm racing against the clock here.
When Lovro's got a target in his
sights, it's only a matter of time.
He strikes like a thief in the night.
What do ya think?
Exhilarating being the kill-ee, isn't it?
Oh, it's a barrel of laughs. Wait a second...
Exactly what happens if I manage to dodge them both?
Huh... I hadn't thought of that.
I suppose in all fairness, you'd be the winner.
What do I win?
How about I agree to stand stock-still
in front of you for an entire second?
You may shoot and or stab me at will.
Don't tell the others, though.
We don't want kickoff a feeding frenzy.
The pot might be a little too
rich to keep everyone honest.
Hmm...
Whatever you say.
Heh?
Head-on?
With all due respect, my friend,
how straightforward did you think this was going to be?
You've got skill, but frankly the years haven't been kind.
Until recently, I was in the Elite Special Force.
He is tough one.
If Lovro can't get his hooks into him,
what the hell chance do I have?
Hey, wanna win? Step up your game.
You've only got today.
Hold on a sec, why are you scared?
Don't worry about it!
Just do your best, and try not to lose!
FYI: With a good knife,
I can strike five times in a second.
So, should be fun.
Sir, you... your hand!
I suppose I can't expect to kill today in this condition.
What kind of talk it that?
Nonsense! That's what it is!
You can do this! Think positive!
Even if I wasn't a relic.
Even if I could kill that man.
You'd still be out of my reach.
Same goes for Irina when you get down to it.
If I can't do it, neither can she.
Very well.
If giving up is your choice, don't let me stop you.
But at least stick around to support your protégé.
After all, whatever else one might say about her skills,
she's certainly proven herself a
capable wielder of death before.
Hm.
Once upon a time, yes.
Level with me, okay?
Do you honestly believe I can
take down someone like Karasuma?
Of course.
I can't speak to what you may or may
not have learned at the feet of your guru.
But based on what I've seen you accomplish since
you've been here, I'd be a dolt to think otherwise.
Case in point.
The lingerie you ordered yesterday!
If that's not initiative, I don't know what is!
Uh! Perv!
If you want others to believe in you,
you've got to believe in you. Show them what you've got:
Karasuma, this Lovro fellow, the children.
Hm.
Yo. Have a look at this, man, it's Mr. K.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. He's been eating his lunch
out there a lot lately for some reason.
While he's smackin' on his sandwich,
the spider move in for the kill.
Looks like Professor Bitch is gonna go for it.
Mind if we talk for a sec? You an' me?
What now? I'm aware this is a pretend
assassination, but I'm done screwin' around.
Huh.
She has a knife, I see.
Surely she knows he can smell the ruse from a mile away.
The woman's a fool.
Aw, come on.
Don't be such a stick in the mud.
I'm a girl willing to do whatever it takes to stay here.
You know that about me.
No more screwin' around.
Unless that's what you'd prefer in exchange.
One good turn deserves another, yeah?
You just call the game, love.
It's as simple as that, huh?
If I take her knife, this nonsense will be over.
All right, fine. Jab me.
Just be quick about it, though.
You're a good sport.
Mr. Lovro,
you've been Miss Irina's teacher
for some time, have you not?
Hm?
You've noted her communication skills,
her versatility with words?
To watch her pass that on to her
students is to watch a master at work.
She's fluent in ten languages because
she's fluent in the ways of people.
When she finds the right words,
there's no one she can't reach.
And nowhere, I suspect, is she in more
command of her particular gifts than here.
What do ya suppose she's been up to?
Gott im Himmel.
'Kay.
Ready or not, here I come!
Son of a...
Didn't see that coming!
Man, this is hot!
Yeah! Who's the bitch now?
She's building the skills to kill me in
much the same way she'd acquire a new language.
Methodically, feeling out the terrain,
drilling vocabulary, so to speak.
One look inside her bag and
you'll see there's no room for doubt.
This is definitely a woman with a plan.
Say goodnight!
Take it easy, huh?
Great.
If this comes down to strength, I'm boned.
What am I s'posed...
Karasuma?
Let me kill you.
Pretty please?
Pretty sure it's bad form for a killer to beg permission!
This is ridiculous!
Oh fine.
Better to get it over with than
spend all day listening to you whine.
You go, girl!
She won!
Callin' it! Professor Bitch was the first one to hit him.
It's not like I lost anything.
Koro-sensei was full of it.
He'd never just stand there
and let me take pot shots at him.
You have to respect a pupil
willing to challenge the master.
Especially when the deck is stacked against her.
Imagine what the children get out
of seeing her rise to the occasion.
Yes, that feisty, can-do spirit is an example for us all.
When push comes to shove,
if there's any chance of assassinating me,
her being here is essential to it.
Sir, I...
You're the worst student I've ever had.
But, as a teacher, I don't hold a candle to you.
If you can kill 'im.
Do it.
Absolutely! Yes, sir!
I did it!
Harsh. Arrogant. Foul-mouthed.
But when you see her in her element,
she's a pretty damn good teacher.
Hey! The hell's with the suit of armor?
Nothing in our little bet prohibited basic self-defense.
You're in a good mood today, sir.
Afterschool plans?
As a matter of fact, yes.
I'm flying to Hawaii for a blockbuster premier.
This particular movie
I've been chomping at the bit to see for ages!
Seriously? Wow. No fair.
What's Mach Twenty good for if I can't
be first in line for an international hit?
Sonic Ninja?
It's a big comic book movie.
They've been hyping it since last year.
Don't worry, I'll give you all the gory...
Okie-dokie, then.
I'd best be on my way.
Koro-sensei! Wait up!
We wanna come with you. Please?
Oh-ho! Fans of the franchise?
Oh, yeah.
We've been waiting for the sequel for, like, ever.
I'm a little surprised you're into comic books, Karma.
It's actually not my thing.
I really dig the director, though.
It's his first genre film.
I'd like to come, too. If you don't mind.
I hope I'm not bothering you.
Um.
No offense, Ritsu, but what are you doing in my phone?
I took the liberty of uploading
myself into everyone's mobile devices.
This way communication between students
is streamlined, and I'm fun-sized!
This version of me is called Mobile Ritsu!
Someone else that can do almost anything.
If it's not too much trouble, I'd love to know
what it's like soaring through the air at Mach Twenty.
I can even take aerial photos for Koro-sensei's dossier!
Well then, children,
let's go to the movies! Brace yourselves for a flight
through the stratosphere at super-sonic speed!
Okay.
I know we asked him on a whim,
but I'm kinda having second thoughts.
What'd we just sign on for?
Yeah, well.
If we survive, maybe next time
we'll think of safety first.
Oh now, don't be afraid.
I'll accelerate gently so as to not shock your systems.
Uh, okay!
Wow!
Check it out: The Pacific Ocean!
All right.
I'm surprise there's not more wind or whatever.
It is because you're using
your head to deflect most of it?
Excellent powers of observation, Nagisa.
The secret, you see, is my aerodynamic skin.
Normally, my head is soft and squishy.
When exposed to high pressure,
however, it hardens like a shell.
That's how I can withstand the
effects of Mach Twenty speed.
Did you know that something very much like
my skin plays a role in your day-to-day life?
Uh.
To explain,
let's explore the concept of dilatancy...
Is he giving us a lecture midflight?
This could be your best chance to assassinate him, Karma.
He's distracted juggling two things at once.
Except I don't wanna die.
We're over open water at the speed of
sound; physics doesn't support that plan.
Koro-sensei has us right where he wants us.
We've got no choice but to listen and learn.
And that is how bulletproof vests are manufactured,
utilizing the fascinating science behind dilatancy.
I've made you that much smarter, and in
the time it takes to catch Sonic Ninja.
We're really here.
We're in Hawaii, and we know what "dilatancy" is.
Man, it's freezing in here.
It's an island thing.
They're all about cranking the AC.
Let's bundle you up so no one catches pneumonia.
Here!
Hmm.
This is so cool! I've never been to a movie theatre!
Hey. Don't they cut out a bunch
of stuff for distribution overseas?
We gettin' the real deal here?
Where's your sense of adventure?
It shouldn't be all that different than what
we see back home once it comes out over there.
And if it is, so much the better.
It'll be like seeing the same
artwork from different angles.
Here. My tentacles can be used as earphones.
I'll offer a running commentary as we watch
just in case any nuances of
this version go over your head.
Now, sit back and enjoy the show!
Wow.
This... is so... awesome!
Hi-yah.
Evil doesn't take a vacation. No one...
A brooding hero trying to save the world.
Kids my age eat this stuff up, but what about Koro-Sensei.
Is he really into the whole super hero thing?
This would be even better in 3D.
Oh my god!
Nevermind.
Kill me if you must.
But first, behold my true identity.
My brother?
What a cliffhanger.
They really know what they're doing;
I'll go nuts waiting for the next installment!
I don't know. I feel like the filmmaker
copped out making the bad guy the brother.
Oh... Well.
If you want to find out how the
series ends, I can calculate it!
I'll just make an algorithm of every movie ever made!
Give me a couple minutes.
Nah, I'm good, thanks. Between the two of you, wow.
Huh?
Long-lost siblings!
Can you imagine?
Merciful heavens, how cruel fate can be!
Well, what do ya know? Guess it really got to him.
Damn, my bad.
He's been blubbering like that all the way from Hawaii.
Thank you for taking us with you, sir
G'night.
Yes, yes. Goodnight, children.
Be careful on the way home.
Oh, and I'd like you to write a
detailed synopsis of the film in
your own words for class tomorrow.
Whoa!
You're giving us homework?
Small price to pay for a free trip to Hawaii!
What's up?
Something on your mind?
It's just been an interesting day is all.
We got flown to Hawaii at Mach Twenty
and given a lecture on natural
science over the Pacific Ocean.
Ahh, we lead a weird life.
Personally, my favorite part of the whole
experience was watching Koro-sensei protect you.
I've never seen anything like it.
Did you realize he was using his tentacles
to fend off dust particles and debris?
When you think about it.
We saw the world through Koro-sensei's eyes today.
Hmm...
The more I get to know the guy,
the more I feel like his everyday life
is something we can't even comprehend.
Stiff upper lip, old boy.
No more tears.
I'm needed at Mimura's for a one-on-one math tutorial.
Well?
Did your eyes follow his course?
Good.
Then you can kill him.
You mean... him?
Yes.
Your brother.
Though as of tomorrow, he'll also be your teacher.
Now.
It's time to reap vengeance
for what's been done to our moon.