Hey, Nagisa. You figure out who all's in your group?
My what?
It's mine and Isogai's job to keep track
of who's with who, so let one of us know.
Hm?
You look confused.
She's talking about next week's trip.
Of all the...
Who in their right mind schedules a class
trip this early in the year?! Unbelievable!
I cannot say that I approve.
Then why are you dressed like that?!
Geisha? Really?
It's actually kinda hot!
Guilty as charged.
Yes, all right, I'll admit it.
I'm as excited about this excursion as you.
First midterms, and now a class trip.
We have a pretty full calendar.
I mean, for assassins at least.
Everyone's aware next week is our
big, overnight field trip to Kyoto, yeah?
Well, not to put a damper on the fun,
but you're still on the clock.
So, are we supposed to try to kill him there?
That is the idea.
Kyoto is a very large city, a lot
more cosmopolitan than this area.
For your safety, you'll be touring in designated groups.
Koro-sensei will divide his time between you.
There are a lot of good sniper nests in the big city.
We plan to have sharpshooters
posted just about everywhere.
Lead your target into the crosshairs,
and the reward money will be parsed out
between you and the lucky marksman.
So stick to the sniper-friendly routes
and keep those eyes peeled.
Yes, sir.
So we're splittin' up into groups, huh?
Hey, Karma. Do you wanna be with us?
Count me in.
Uh, you're gonna behave yourself, right?
No funny business?
No gettin' into fights and all that stuff?
Yeah. Sure. Don't worry, dude.
When I stir up trouble out of town, let's just say...
I know how to keep witnesses from reporting it.
Oh, great! And now he's part of our group.
Way to go!
Eh. What can I say? We've been friends for a while.
So... Who else?
There's me, you, Sugino, Kayano, should be two more.
Yep. Got it covered! Okuda's in!
Still one shy.
You think our number six should be a girl, too?
Heh-heh! No sweat. I foresaw this and took the liberty
of enlisting someone very special.
Ladies and gentleman, class idol, Kanzaki!
Ohh! I'm totally for it!
Nice girl, Kanzaki.
Doesn't exactly stand out in a crowd,
but everyone in E Class is nuts about her.
Good addition to the group, I think.
Thank you for letting me join!
I'm flattered.
Uh, yeah.
Cool. So where in Kyoto do we wanna go?
Good question.
Oh! You're all so cute.
Excited to walk the city streets, boys and girls?
Ah, so young and naïve.
Yeah, well, you can just stay here, Professor Bitch.
You can water the plants while we're gone.
Where should we go on day two?
I vote Higashiyama.
Remember, we have to think about assassination.
But there's so much cool stuff on this route.
Oh, no! If you bastards think
you're gonna deal me out of this trip, think again!
What?!
You know, you're kinda giving us mixed signals here!
Oh, I'll show you mixed signals, copper top!
Huh?
One for each of you!
What are those, sir?
They're field trip guidebooks!
What the hell?
They're more like dictionaries!
Just a little something I threw together last night!
Including all illustrations of
every major tourist attraction,
the top 100 local souvenirs and where to find them,
travel self-defense techniques from basic to advanced,
oh, and best of all: the first
edition comes with a model of Kinjakuji!
You are WAY too excited about this trip!
Koro-sensei likes E Class to be prepared.
If the way things have been
going lately is any indication,
this is going to be an educational trip.
I'm actually kinda stoked!
Whoa. Man, look at those lucky jerks,
gettin' to ride first class.
And as always, we're stuck in coach.
Yay for us, right, guys?
Now, now, boys and girls. Try not to look so sour.
Rules are rules, you know how this works.
The student handbook states those of us with the
highest grade-point average get dibs on school funds.
Oh-ho! Is that the putrid stench of
abject poverty filling my nostrils?
Pardon me, boys.
Everyone having a glamorous day so far?
Um, Professor Bitch?
Why are you dressed like the paparazzi should care
who you are?
When it comes to womanly wiles, a
femme fatale pulls out all the stops.
Besides, travel is no excuse not
to look devastatingly fashionable.
You stick out like a sore thumb.
Go change. You're a chaperone, not a runway model.
Oh, come on, lighten up!
What's wrong with a little style?
These kids are going to the city.
Shut up. Get changed now.
She's a more of a child than we are.
Maybe killing rich dudes for a
living disconnects you from reality.
An excellent place to corner him.
Yeah!
Huh. Has anybody seen Koro-sensei?
Was he even at the train station?
Holy...
Not to pry, but is there some reason
you're stuck to the window?!
Uh... I was stocking up on munchies
at the terminal and lost track of time.
It's all right, I'll just stay here till
we reach the next stop. Cloaking engaged!
Nothing to see here. Just some random
clothes and luggage stuck to the side of a train.
Worst. Camouflage. Ever.
Whew...
Who knew traveling incognito would be so exhausting?
Goodness me.
Might be a little easier if you
didn't bring such a big suitcase.
No offense, but you weird people out as it is.
And while we're on the subject, broadcasting
that you're in disguise defeats the purpose.
Truth? It's a lame disguise anyway.
Nobody's buyin' it.
Hey, Koro-sensei.
Try these.
Can't have your nose going AWOL all the time, right?
Wow! A perfect fit!
Custom carved to complement the contours of your face.
You're welcome.
It's whatever, just a little hobby of mine, no big.
Whoa! That's cool, Sugaya!
Isn't it awesome how when you travel
together you see a whole other side to people?
Mm-hm! I don't know what we'll learn about each
other on this trip but I'm ready to be surprised.
Hey, guys, I'm gonna make a run to the main car
and get us some drinks. Anybody else feeling parched?
Uh, can I come with you, please?
Me, too!
Isn't this cool?
I love how space age it feels.
Sorry. Excuse us.
What school you s'pose they're from?
Kunugigaoka.
How'd you like that? A train full of smarties
from one of the best schools in the country.
Tell me another. Come on, her?
She don't look smart.
Hey. I have an idea.
Once we're in Kyoto,
whaddya say we have some fun with these dweebs?
Nice!
So, bullet trains actually give him motion sickness?
You'll probably feel better if
you lay down in our room for a while.
Perhaps later... I need to pop
back over to Tokyo for a moment first.
Koro-sensei forgot his favorite pillow.
How is everything you own not in that bag?!
Any luck?
It's gotta be in there, you worked so hard on it, too.
Mm-mm...
I admire your going through the trouble
of putting together an itinerary, Kanzaki,
but if you can't locate it, don't fret.
I have just the solution.
These handy dandy guidebooks contain everything
you could possibly need.
She made the itinerary so we wouldn't
have to lug those things around!
I distinctly remember putting it in my handbag.
I wonder if I dropped it somewhere.
So, uh, tomorrow is your free-study
day in Kyoto, everybody got that?
Hey! Shut your traps and listen for a second!
Heh! Those jerks from Kunugigaoka
are really gonna try to squeeze
all this sight-seeing into one day?
Nice spot. For assassination, I mean.
Don't you think, Nagisa?
If the snipers can see it, sure.
What a bizarre field trip, right?
Maybe. But you gotta admit it's fun.
Whatever we do, we have to get
green tea warabimochi dumplings!
That's a great idea!
We could put poison in them!
That's twisted!
Not for us, silly. For Koro-sensei.
Not too shabby.
We could take advantage of his sweet tooth.
That'd be a waste of a perfectly good local treat!
Now if only we could find a poison
that didn't give him special powers.
Not to be that guy, but I gotta tell ya:
I was sorta hoping we could
put the whole assassination thing
on hold while we were here.
We're in Kyoto, people!
What do any of these sites have to do with assassination?
You'd be surprised.
Hold on, the Ryoma Sakamoto?
This is where Omiya used to be.
The inn where Sakamoto was cut down by assassins in 1867.
That's right.
And just a little further down is Honnoji Temple.
Though it's moved a few times since they built it.
Oh, yeah. Oda's death counts as an assassination.
Just think, in these few city blocks
a slew of high-profile assassinations went down.
Sure, Kyoto's always been the heart of Japan,
but it's also a Mecca for professional killers.
I never thought of it that way.
Guess you could say we're on an "assassination vacation."
Throughout history, tons of
targets have been neutralized here,
targets whose lives the world
still feels the repercussions of.
As far as that goes, Koro-sensei
is definitely in good company.
Cool! Next up is Yasaka Shrine!
Uh-huh.
Mind if we take a break first? I could really go
for some sugar-loaded Kyoto coffee right about now.
Yay, sugar!
Talk about off the beaten path.
Gion is a ghost town this far in.
Yeah. Places like this put a cap
on the number of visitors they allow,
so you don't catch many people just wandering around.
Secluded, lots of good hiding places.
That's why I made sure to put in on the itinerary.
It's ideal for assassination.
Good job, Kanzaki! You really do your homework!
I vote this is where we do the deed!
"Ideal" is right.
It's also a great spot for kidnappers to ply their trade.
Huh?
I hope you don't take this the wrong way,
but, something tells me you gentlemen aren't tourists.
Don't try to be a hero, carrot top.
Hand over your lady friends and wa...
Y'see that? What did I tell you?
To hell with 'em. Without any witnesses,
it's basically a free-for-all, so go nuts!
Hey!
Hm?
I'm gonna gut you like a pig!
Strong words for a guy kissin' the sidewalk.
Let go of me!
No! Stop!
What did we tell you?!
Leave him alone!
Bring the car around.
Yeah, that's right. Don't mess with us, dweebs.
They crawled out of the shadows like monsters.
Only these thugs are something far worse than monsters.
They're high schoolers.
Nagisa! Sugino!
Oh, thank goodness! Are you two okay?
You all right, Okuda?
Those guys didn't do anything to you, did they?
It's okay, I'm fine.
Sorry, I didn't know what to do, so I just hid.
Don't sweat it. You did the right thing.
Huh?
I think it's safe to assume
those guys are pretty hardcore. We could go to the cops,
except they're the type who
know their way around the system.
Which is fine.
'Cause I'm the type who likes to handle these things
personally, if you know what I mean.
Okay. Dude, how do we even find them?
I gave our buddies a call and they're in.
We're gonna have ourselves a
li'l commemorative photo shoot
with you gals. Feel free to scream.
No one'll hear ya 'cept for us.
You. I seen you somewhere before, right?
Sure I have. Last summer in Tokyo.
Saw ya in that arcade. Don't deny it.
My boys spotted you first,
told me to be on the lookout for a party girl.
We was gonna kidnap you then, but...
I guess you lucked out and gave us the slip.
Who'd 'a thought you were gonna go
to the school for geniuses? No judgment, though.
I get it.
The higher you are on the ladder,
the more you wanna take a swan dive.
Don't worry about a thing.
Professor Ruin's gonna take all
night teachin' you to dive like a pro.
"When a Group Member has Been Abducted?"
I'll just say it, what kind of
"guidebook" covers this stuff?
The sort of guidebook an insanely
thorough teacher writes, apparently.
There's even a section on how to deal with
seeing overpriced Kyoto souvenirs for cheap
in boutique shops back home.
It's like he's walking us through every possible scenario.
"Cheering Up Your Lonely Self
After Seeing a Lovey-Dovey Couple."
Specifically "On the Banks of the Kamo River."
But that's not even a thing!
Well, at least reading this calmed us down.
I for one feel pretty confident about what to do.
So that picture...
Not gonna lie, it's kinda comforting
to know even you went through a phase.
Never would've imagined.
Yeah.
My dad was crazy strict. Always on me about
doing well in school and building up my resume.
It was so suffocating, you know?
I just couldn't deal. So I'd ditch the uniform,
glam myself out, and hang where no one knew who I was.
Felt like therapy.
So stupid. Where did I expect to end up, right?
It's E Class for me.
But now, I don't even know where I belong anymore.
Sounds to me like you'd be right at home with us.
Grades and all that pointless
bullshit don't mean jack here.
We eat elitist scum for breakfast.
Nothin' sweeter 'n knockin'
stuffed shirts down a peg or two.
The only thing that matters is having a little fun, right?
You're a jerk.
I see how it is!
Little Miss Perfect thinks she's better than me!
This is exactly what I'm talkin' about, you uppity bitch!
When we're done here, you go back to whatever fancy hotel
you're in and tell whoever asks that you were
just out singin' karaoke and lost track of time.
Stick to that story, and no one gets hurt.
Once we're all back home in
Tokyo, we can all hang out together.
Maybe we'll scrapbook, do something artsy
with the "vacation photos" we're about to take.
Ah. Speak of the devil.
My photographer buddies are here.
School Trip Guidebook, page 1,043.
"What To Do When a Group Member Has Been Abducted."
"If there are no leads on the perpetrators
think back to any colloquialisms,
accents or linguistic quirks
that might indicate whether said perpetrators are local.
If not, and the perpetrators were wearing
school uniforms, refer to page 1,334."
Here we are.
If the perpetrators are in school uniforms, you might be
dealing with a rival school out causing trouble.
You found us!
What the hell?! How'd you even know where to look?!
"Being unfamiliar with the area, the culprits
will opt to stay within a narrow perimeter
after the initial kidnapping, somewhere secluded
but not far from the scene of the crime.
If this is the case, consult page 134."
"My Mach 20 bird's-eye-view map of popular
and or likely abductor hideouts may help."
That guidebook is straight-up amazing!
There's nothing Koro-sensei didn't think of!
No kidding, right? Definitely worth lugging around.
We should take one with us everywhere.
You're getting all this from a guidebook?!
All right. So what's it gonna be gentlemen?
Fight or flight?
We'll go easy if you back down now,
but after all you've put us through,
you're not gettin' out of this unscathed.
That's a promise.
Heh...
Uh...?
Actin' all badass.
You Junior High kids crack me up.
Why don't you say hello to some friends of mine.
See how far that attitude gets you with them?
They...
Say hello to them if you like.
Be advised, though, they probably won't to hear you.
It's Koro-sensei!
Sorry I'm a little late to the festivities.
I figured it'd be best to let you handle this on your own
while I searched elsewhere, just to cover all the bases.
Um. Sir? Why exactly are you wearing a veil?
Violence is always regrettable.
I'd rather you not associate
my face with what I've just done,
or what I'm about to do.
Good work following the
instructions in the guidebook, Nagisa.
I'm glad I had the foresight to provide them.
Hold on! This freakazoid's your teacher?!
That's the biggest load of bullshit I ever heard!
Such language.
I'll thank you not to use it in front of my students.
I, I didn't even see what he just did!
And unless you can move faster than me,
you'd be smart to keep your filthy hands off them, too.
Wow.
So even the teachers they hire
at that damn school are special.
Prolly get off by lookin' down
on us like the other kids do.
Well, look down on this!
I think you have the wrong impression.
The school these boys and girls attend is special, yes.
But they're considered the outcasts.
Their class is the target of merciless scorn.
Even so, bleak as their situation may seem,
they stay commendably positive.
Never would these children dream of pulling
others down to their "level" out of spite.
They're not privileged,
they simply work hard. And there's the moral for you.
As the old saying goes, in clear waters or murky,
fortune favors the fish who swim upstream.
Okay, boys and girls, let's take care of business.
These misguided young rascals are in desperate need
of a lesson in proper field
trip etiquette, wouldn't you agree?
How are they behind us all of a sudden?!
What the hell did they just whack us upside the head with?
You know...
I'm starting to think we picked
the wrong kids to mess with.
Man, for a while there I didn't
know what was gonna happen.
Should've just left me alone with the ringleader,
I'd have taken out the trash
before the bastard knew what hit him.
We get it, you're a scary dude.
I'm just glad we're okay.
How you holdin' up, Kanzaki? You good?
Sure. All things considered.
I must say, you're handling this quite well.
Huh?
Most folks would've been traumatized
by what you just experienced.
Yet, you've shaken it off without batting an eye.
In fact, I daresay the whole ordeal has empowered you.
What do you know? I guess it has.
Thanks for coming to the rescue!
Don't mention it.
Why don't we carry on with our field trip, boys and girls?
Aw, dang it.
We never got to try out our assassination plan.
Well, it really isn't the time or place for that now.
Whatever. We'll just try it tomorrow.
Best of luck to you.
When your target is also an outstanding teacher,
it's the definition of "between a rock and a hard place."