Let's begin, shall we?
Begin what, exactly?
Studying for midterms, of course!
Dun-dun-dun! Whoa, look out!
I'll be making this period a
high-speed enhanced Midterm Study Hall!
My doubles will provide special
one-on-one attention. Drilling everyone individually
on the areas where you need improvement most.
Man, this is balls.
He's seriously gotta wear a different headband
for each subject?
Gimme a break, man! Naruto's not even on the test!
Look at him go!
Is it just me, or is he getting faster?
I mean, six doubles for Japanese, eight
doubles for math, three for social studies,
four for science, four for English.
One for Naruto.
A Koro-sensei for each of us.
And not that long ago he was doing well
to split himself up into four or five.
Knife down, Karma!
No sneak attacks during Study Hall!
This is very difficult, so try
not to disrupt my concentration!
Doesn't all this spread you a little bit thin, sir?
I, uh...
I mean, just thinking about it, makes me feel tired.
No worries there.
I have a double outside on R&R duty!
How does that help?!
He's been leveling-up like crazy these days.
I wonder.
Is he just prepping to destroy the Earth, or what?
if you're an assassin,
he's a tricky target.
There, are you starting to wrap your head
around the material, Nagisa?
Yes, sir.
And if you're facing midterms,
he's the best damn teacher you could ask for.
Consider this deceptively simple cube.
If I wished to align the colors
quickly and intuitively.
What might be the best way to go about it?
Any ideas?
The answer?
Uh?
Pry them apart and reassemble.
It's as easy as that.
Why, Koro-sensei. It's an honor.
Uhh?
Apparently this gentleman
is supposed to be the principal here.
Believe me, he is, which also makes him our boss.
So good of you to come all this way, sir!
Any chance we could discuss a
teensy little hike in salary,
if I'm not being too forward, of course?
I've added a few extra versions of
myself to help with the workload...
Forgive me for not visiting sooner.
I meant to pay my respects before now,
but one gets sidetracked.
Mr. Karasuma and the Ministry of Defense
have painted quite the vivid picture of you.
Yes, vivid indeed, though I don't pretend to understand
the situation in every particular.
Nor do I feel especially qualified to comment.
However I will say this, if I may be so bold.
You seem to be torn between embracing the role
of savior or villain.
Savior? Villain?
But no matter.
Such things aren't for men like myself to resolve.
I'm hardly in a position to save the world.
That job I must leave to hands more capable.
So barring harm to my school,
your assassins may deal with you
as they will.
I've been given plenty of incentive to turn a blind eye.
Thank you for your cooperation.
That's a very reasonable attitude, principal.
I find that quite attractive in a man.
You flatter me, madam.
That said.
Though I'm happy to give you carte Blanche
to do what's necessary,
I must think of the future, should the Earth survive.
In other words.
What becomes of my school if Koro-sensei is assassinated?
Not to put too fine a point on it,
but E Class must continue to serve its function
in the grand scheme of things.
Interesting. So rock-bottom grades
and students with zero prospects
serve a "function," do they?
Oh, yes.
Are you familiar with the so-called Worker Ant Theory?
It tells us that in any group, 20 percent will work hard,
20 percent will be idle, and the remaining 60 percent
will fall somewhere in between.
Now, imagine a group without a middle ground,
where hard workers comprise 95 percent of the population,
and lay-abouts only five.
If the lazy worker ants are stigmatized,
the ratio is perfectly feasible.
Those who under normal circumstances fall into
the average category, better themselves
to avoid being associated with the ostracized class.
Very logical.
And, of course, unless the five percent is kept down,
the incentive for the other 95 disappears.
Just today I received an alarming complaint
from a D Class teacher.
It seems a student of yours glared threateningly
at two upperclassmen, such that the upperclassmen
feared for their lives.
I have no doubt the confidence to do so
stems from their attempts to assassinate you.
And perhaps that's to be expected.
The issue, though, is that an E Class student
dared to defy his better.
Obviously I cannot let such insolence stand.
As his teachers, you are expected to
remind the student in question of his place.
Oh, and Koro-sensei?
You have one second to solve this puzzle!
What?
You just spring this on me out of the blue?
Whoa. What the hell is going on?
Your speed certainly lives up to the hype.
I can see why most attempts on your
life would be an exercise in futility.
But bear in mind, my friend.
In the grand scheme of things,
there are many problems for
which speed is of no use at all.
Now, if you'll kindly excuse me.
Ah!
Oh.
Hi there! I look forward to your midterm results.
Best of luck to you.
Uh...?
Huh... "Best of luck," the guy says.
And just like that...
I revert from assassin back to an E Class nobody.
As a target,
Koro-sensei is practically invincible.
Amateur and professional assassins alike
have their work cut out trying to off him.
But as a teacher, he's vulnerable to the
whims of people higher up on the food chain.
People like Kunugigaoka Academy principal,
Gakuho Asano.
A shrewd man who, in the first decade of his tenure,
single-handedly hoisted this school to top-tier status.
Essentially, if you teach here there's no
getting around his personal vision of order.
That goes for us and for you.
Good morning, everyone!
As you might guess, today, I
thought I'd make even more of me!
This is getting ridiculous.
Thinking caps on, let's begin! Even
the afterimages are getting sloppy.
It's like he's turning into a parody of himself.
Uh, Hey, Koro-sensei?
No offense, but isn't this going to wear you out?
Wear me out? P'shaw!
E Class must continue to serve
its function in the grand scheme of things.
Look at the poor guy, he's totally down for the count.
I say we try our luck!
Not that I don't appreciate it, but
why's he teaching us so hard anyways?
To get those test scores up, why else?
If I do that...
Koro-sensei!
Look at my grade! This is awesome!
We owe it all to you, Koro-sensei! Thank you!
I'll never try to kill you again!
Oh, sir! Please!
I need help with my grades, too!
I'll never have to worry about you
trying to kill me again! It'll be sheer bliss!
Uh. I mean, the whole helping
us study thing is nice and all...
but, the reward money we get for assassinating him
is nothing to sneeze at.
Let's face it, who needs to ace a midterm
when you've got that kind of cash tucked away
in your bank account?
Money isn't everything, people!
Aw, c'mon, you gotta cut us some
slack here, we're the End Class.
Yeah. Assassination we can strive for.
But academics? Seriously, why bother?
I see. So that's how it is, then?
Hm?
How what is, sir?
Do you know what I think?
I don't think you appreciate
what it means to be an assassin.
Everyone. Schoolyard. Now.
What's his deal, making us all stand out here
like a bunch of goobers?
I dunno, maybe something we said
put him in a mood.
All right, children.
Love or hate the E Class system, as a remedial process,
it can work.
Imagine placing within the top 50
of 186 students on midterms.
Make that a reality, and securing a former teacher's
permission is all an E Class student needs
to return to the class from which they were ejected.
But given the conditions
we're forced to work under, the personal setbacks
that landed each of you here are difficult to fix.
That's why most E Class students
are convinced that returning to the main campus
is no more than a pipe dream.
Don't tell me to hurry up, I'm not a child.
Sorry, Koro-sensei asked me to bring you.
Ms. Jelavich.
I'd like your opinion as a professional assassin.
All right, what do you wanna know?
Now, let's say you've been given an assignment.
Do you have only one plan going into it?
Hm? 'Course not.
If my profession has taught me anything,
it's that Plan A almost never comes off like you'd expect.
There are just too many variables.
A good assassin has backup plans
on hand for any contingencies.
And Mr. Karasuma, what about you?
Hm?
When teaching knife combat strategies,
do you believe the first strike is the only move
of any importance?
The first move is important, but so's the follow-up.
Never assume the first strike will hit.
Because when your opponent's trained, you have to be ready
to deliver the next strike with at least as much precision
and skill as the first, or, better yet,
carry a second blade.
If you have a point, sir, I think we're missing it.
Listen to your teachers, boys and girls!
Backup plans are the cornerstone of confidence,
and a confident assassin is a successful one.
The same goes for life in general.
You strive for assassination but not academics?
You've heard the old saying, right?
Don't put all your eggs in one basket!
Well, that's exactly what you're doing here!
Now. Suppose I left the classroom for good.
Suppose some other would-be
assassin out there managed to do me in.
What would you be left with?
What would you strive for then?
Or are you satisfied with being outcasts?
A word of advice from your Koro-sensei,
you walk a fine line.
Those who can't wield a second blade
aren't qualified to be assassins!
What the...
Holy crap, guys, check it out! Is that a tornado?
Hmph. What a showoff.
There.
Our schoolyard needed a good leveling.
Not to mention a few weeds cleared.
I am a superior life-form,
capable of destroying the Earth.
As you can see, flattening out this little corner
of it was a cinch.
Cast your nets wide.
Show me your backup plan, that crucial second blade.
Otherwise, I'll be forced to conclude no would-be assassin
here is worthy of me.
And I won't just have a mind to leave,
I'll flatten this entire campus as I go.
A "second blade"? So how long've we got?
Not very. Until the end of tomorrow.
The midterms are upon us, class.
I want all of you to place in the top 50.
Whether you realize it or not,
we've been sharpening those second blades all along.
The main campus relies on dull, rote-learning methods.
I, to put it mildly, do not.
You have what it takes.
So wield those blades with confidence!
Take your midterms by the gills, smiling,
your heads held high!
Be proud! Be bold!
And never forget, you are assassins!
You are E Class!
Okay. Ready or not, here we go.
Hmph!
Midterms are administered on the main campus,
even for us. Basically, to E Class,
they're just an away game. Not much else.
Our knife isn't nearly enough to take this thing out!
How are we supposed to tackle question four?!
I expected this.
The midterms they give in this
school have always been a beast.
Damn it. You're kidding me! I
don't even know where to start!
This question's gonna eat me alive!
I'm dead meat!
Did you really mean that crap?
You're gonna take off if they don't all
place in the top 50 on their stupid midterms?!
That's right.
Well, way to be unrealistic!
These kids have the worst grade-point
average in the entire school! Are you nuts?!
I wonder sometimes.
Either way, wherever they've ranked before,
they're my students now.
When backed into a corner,
the first order of business is assessing your options.
If I've taught them nothing else,
I've certainly taught them that.
Come now, we've covered this.
The poor beast isn't as terrifying as all that.
Start by observing that fin.
On closer inspection, it's just that, a fin.
Next, look over each part of the question
with the same attention to detail,
and piece together what you find.
Voila! A trivial adversary indeed!
Now use that trusty blade to fillet it.
Of course!
Huh?
Take the problem one part at time.
That's the trick.
Just like Koro-sensei's been teaching us all along!
This question...
is dead meat.
So's this one.
And this one.
And this...
And all of a sudden...
poised to strike...
a question we weren't ready for ambushed us from the rear.
Not to rock the boat, but this is ridiculous.
You gotta help me out here.
However I look at it, this test seems rigged.
I don't know what to say, sir.
You ought to have received proper notification.
Perhaps there was some sort of
communications flap on your end?
But there's no point in coming to the main campus,
I can tell you that.
The communications flap wasn't on our end, buddy.
Besides, what constitutes "proper notification?"
Two days before midterms, you decide to broaden the scope
and that's supposed to be enough time for us
to cover everything?
With all due respect Mr., uh, Karasuma,
is it? You don't understand. We're a prep school.
This sort of thing happens all the time.
Our students are expected to cram.
That's been our policy for years.
In fact, when it was decided to include new material
on this midterm, the principal
himself lectured our students
on those subjects personally.
It was wonderful. You should've seen it.
Unbelievable.
Is there nothing this man won't
resort to in the name of his own ideals?
They've put us in a hell of a spot.
If Koro-sensei leaves, we're screwed.
We lose everything.
I take full responsibility.
Clearly, I underestimated this
school's dedication to the status quo.
Forgive me if I can't bear to face you.
Uh...?
Have it your way.
Keep your back turned if you want.
Just makes it easier for us to sneak up on you.
I am in no mood, Karma!
This whole situation has me very de... Uh?!
So they added questions to the stupid test.
Big deal.
Seriously?
Hold the phone, you got a hundred in math?
Your method worked like a charm, Teach.
You gave us everything you had and at the moment of truth,
it mattered.
So what if the midterms decided to cover new territory?
I was ready. Don't worry, though.
I'm not going anywhere. You see, this is where I belong.
Normal Class has nothing on assassination.
So. Where are you gonna go, huh? Where do you belong?
You plan on using the fact we didn't all make
the top 50 as an excuse to tuck your tail and run?
'Cause you're not fooling me.
I think you're just scared that
one of us is actually gonna kill you.
You could've just told us.
Not like we'd blame you for being afraid.
Next time, consider being more
straightforward with how you feel.
Even if how you feel is all, "oh no, I wanna run away!"
No one is running away!
'Kay. So what's the deal?
The deal is we get our revenge on
this school two-fold during finals!
Children! This is no laughing matter!
There's no denying we hit a wall on our midterms.
The same wall that's always
closed us off from everyone else.
But for once, I'm kinda glad to be behind it.
Not just glad. Proud. Proud to be in E Class!
Who puts E class in the corner?
Nobody puts E Class in the corner!