"First, you take the planet Earth,"
"round and blue and green."
"And floating over Tokyo, you drop a giant bean."
"Put another one in Sichuan, China... what a sheen!"
"Taking off from Dubai to Hawaii at Mach Twenty,"
"leave contrails as you fly."
"Double back across the Southern Hemisphere"
"over the Philippines once again to ol' Dubai."
"And then! Back to Hawaii, drawing lines of latitude"
"every 25 degrees along the way."
"And there you have it:"
"Koro-sensei!"
See? Simple! Now you try it!
Are you kidding?!
Here's the hitch,
your target is a junior high school teacher
chaperoning students on a field trip to Kyoto.
As you're probably aware, he's not human.
Now, I don't mean to call your skills into question,
but on this assignment, be ready for anything.
They call me Red Eye.
I'm a hired gun. A sharpshooter.
Wowza!
The open-air design really lets you feel this baby move!
This is how you travel by train!
Zipped along at a bracing 25 kilometers per hour,
and no queasiness!
Says the guy who can break the sound barrier.
Just a little more.
And we'll be right in the sniper's line of sight.
Incidentally.
It's a popular tourist stop on the Sagano Tram line.
The Hozu River Bridge.
All right, folks.
Now's the time to snap those pictures.
Hey! Check out the boat, Koro-sensei!
Coolest thing ever, huh?
Ooh, let me see!
Nice!
He's waiting on the banks.
Our high sign is when Koro-sensei leans forward
to get a better look at the boat.
One time, in the Middle East,
I shot a man at twenty clicks during a sandstorm.
Beautiful day, clear line of sight.
Easy mode. Yeah.
If that wasn't a headshot, I'm a monkey's...
He blocked my bullet with a piece of yatsuhashi?
Oh dear.
There seems to be a sliver of bone in my om-nom.
That could've turned out ugly.
Urgh! Impossible!
A high-spin round stopped dead
by a tiny piece of local, ooey-gooey goodness?!
How fast do they expect me to be?
Hmph. Okay.
Now I understand the price on this guy's head.
Mr. K was serious we he said my target wasn't human.
This is gonna be fun.
Be gone with thee, foul wastrel!
Your presence doth desecrate mine eye!
How dare you address me thus?!
Let us teach this man humility, brothers!
Awesome!
Their swords move so fast you can barely see them!
These men are highly trained in
the subtle art of stage combat.
Did I mention that I'm an aficionado of Edo-era swordplay?
Whoa!
Heads up!
Watch out, sir! Don't stand so close!
Okie dokie.
The actors are guiding the target nicely.
Good. Everything's going according to plan.
That's right, eyes on the show.
Huh?
Where the hell?!
Oh, come on! Really?!
How's everyone okay with this?
I come to thine aid.
Blood-soaked sakura blossoms are an evil flower.
I will not abide them.
He even knows the lines?!
I can't hit him like this! The actors are in the way!
Gah, I hate actors!
He's been clocked at Mach Twenty,
and his defensive techniques are unconventional.
But don't let that throw you off.
Yeah. Unconventional. Moving on!
This son of a bitch is dead.
I stake my name on it.
You're late, sir. What took you so long?
So sorry!
I got swept up into a samurai drama.
I was the star!
I totally believe it.
Y'know, we finished Kiyomizu Temple like forever ago.
Then what do you say we scope
out Ninehnzaka Street for souvenirs?
Yeah, right. Like you'll buy anything except junk food.
Okay.
Perfect place to draw a steady bead on him.
From Yasaka's five-story pagoda, it's a straight shot.
Here, Koro-sensei, try this blotting paper!
It's super cool.
I'm not sure I care for you to see what it'll pick up.
C'mon, it's supposed to be fun!
Okay, guess we're doing this.
He pores over his tchotchkes at the foot of Sannenzaka.
And while a student distracts him...
Booyah! Smack dab in the temple!
This is ridiculous! A piece of paper?!
See? This is exactly what I meant.
Look at all these secretions.
There's enough mucus here to stop a bullet.
Hmm?
Ah. Nagisa's group is calling. Excuse me. Hello?
Tell me where you are.
Damn. What in god's name is this thing?
His speed's insane, his defenses impregnable.
It's like he's factory-made with the
express purpose of being un-friggin'-killable.
Red Eye here.
It's me.
Oh, hey Mr. K.
I'm afraid you'll have to pack it in for today.
No more attempts.
The next group you were supposed to work
with has run into some unforeseen issues.
Something about a gang of high school thugs.
Target is disregarding the itinerary to go to their aid.
Yes, sir. Understood.
To be honest...
this bastard makes we wanna throw in the towel anyway.
I've been a sniper for eight years.
And not once have I failed to
see a mark's blood in my scope.
Not once. That's how I got the name Red Eye.
Kinda strange when you think about it.
Nothing particularly red about my eye.
Here you go.
It's a special blend of spices from Sannenzaka.
Thank you. 'Preciate it. You really shouldn't have...
What in the hell?!
Sorry to disrupt your plans;
some of my students were in a pickle.
Not to worry, it's taken care of.
Everything's shipshape now.
So I thought I'd take this
opportunity to drop by and say hello.
So you knew the plan and you
were just playing along for kicks?
You're one scary customer, you know that?
No wonder the government's
paying a fortune to keep you secret.
So, uh... Let's cut to the chase, huh?
If you're gonna kill me, go right ahead.
Death's an occupational hazard.
I know what I signed up for.
Just eat it!
You don't really think I'm going to kill you?
When you've gone to so much
trouble making this an enjoyable trip?
On the contrary, I'm here to thank you.
My students did some very impressive research
on this region. Yes, as a means of pinpointing
an ideal spot for assassination, but still!
They steeped themselves in geography, local
customs, tourist highlights, history, all of it.
As a matter of fact, their efforts brought
them closer to this city's charms than a teacher
might otherwise dare to hope.
They've really come to understand another place
and its people; to expand their minds with travel.
What ultimately brought them
to that milestone? Assassination.
Here you go.
Under the circumstances, I'm as
proud as punch to be their target.
I'll be damned. You're as crazy as you look.
Still. I can tell you care about those kids.
Wish I'd had a teacher like you back in the day.
Wait, what do you mean you're quitting?
Yeah, sorry.
I suddenly feel like just being a tourist for a while.
Life tends to pass you by in the sniper's nest, ya know?
It's time I expanded the ol' color palate.
Eye's gettin' tired of red.
Now, let me see.
What hue should I set my sights on tomorrow?
Hot damn!
How the hell are you dodging all of those?!
This is actually starting to get embarrassing.
Look at the way she handles that
joystick, smiling like it's no big deal.
Oh, wow! I had no idea.
I mean, who knew you'd turn
out to be such a video game pro?
I've kept it secret. My family's super strict.
They don't approve of me wasting time on stuff like this.
Lately, though, I feel like I'm over
caring so much about what they think.
Well what anybody thinks, really.
I used to get so stressed about how other people saw me.
I always second-guessed myself.
But then Koro-sensei made me realize.
It's all about doing the best with what you have.
Being true to the person you are on the inside.
Not a side of Kanzaki I expected to see.
I wonder what she and Kayano talked about
while those creeps held them against their will.
It's like, I dunno, like they've bonded.
They blew you up!
Yeah, that'll happen.
A-ha!
Hey, good save, man.
Almost every sniper who saw the
specs on this mission turned it down.
The one guy we thought was a shoe-in
quit halfway through the assignment. Damn.
So much for our Kyoto gambit, I suppose.
Who else wants some?!
Hey, Mr. Karasuma, quick game?
Aw, what the hell.
No more horning in on their field trip.
This is supposed to be their time, after all.
You got it, but I'll warn you.
I'm pretty good.
I'm just gonna say it. This place is a dump.
Why we gotta sleep in two big
dorm rooms separated by gender?
The kids in all the other classes
get put up in their own fancy suites.
Personally, I think it's more fun this... way...
Hey. What are you guys doing?
Shh!
What does it look like we're doing?
Tryin' to sneak a peek!
What?!
Wait, that supposed to be our job!
It's nobody's job.
Either way, who can resist?
Look at the way that outfit is hung.
That can only mean one thing.
You're a clever guy. You get what I'm saying.
We wanna see what he looks like naked.
This may be our only opportunity.
Does he have a proper body or
is it tentacles all the way down?
And it's not creepy 'cause we need
all the Intel on Koro-sensei we can get.
Can we all agree that this isn't the least bit sexy?
Is he a chick?!
Oh, hello, children.
Are you taking a bubble bath in a public restroom?
We're not s'posed to add anything to the water, sir.
Worry not. This is just my mucus.
Huh?
On contact with water, it works up a
nice lather and acts as an exfoliate.
So is that a pro or a con?
Yeah. Fascinating.
But you let your guard down, sir,
and we're blocking your exit.
You'll come slopping out of that tub eventually.
And when you do, you'll have to walk by us.
We may not kill you, but we'll see you naked!
This simply will not do!
A-ha!
What the hell is that?!
Jellied broth, my dear! Now, if you'll excuse me.
All righty, then.
Well, that was lame.
Can we peep on a woman next time, please?
Travel sure brings out another side of people.
I know I'm learning a lot.
Sucks we still don't know what Koro-sensei
looks like under his clothes, though.
Can we go back to the room now?
Kanzaki's in the top spot.
No surprise there.
Well, yeah. Everybody likes her.
I know.
Pretty slick of you to pull her into our group, Sugino.
I was hoping me an' her would have a
chance to talk a little on this trip?
But with all the crap that went down, no dice.
Sucks to be you, man.
Better luck next time, I guess.
Dudes, you're killin' me!
Can we just focus on who has the hots for who?
Don't ask me to choose!
I can't do it! No! No!
You're exempted.
What about you?
Which of the class shorties is your top pick?
Huh? Uh... I don't really know.
Ah, c'mon, Maehara. You gonna ask you gotta tell.
Sorry. No can do.
A gentleman keeps his secrets, fellas.
Bitch move, man!
When I think how popular dillweeds
like you are, it drives me crazy!
Sounds like a party in here.
Karma! Great timing!
Which of the girls in our class do you like?
Hmm...
I believe I'll have to go with Okuda.
Dude, you're kidding. Really?
Huh. Interesting. But why Okuda?
She's a demon with chemistry.
Think of all the concoctions she could brew up
to enhance my shenanigans. It'd be a match made in heaven.
Yeah, heaven. Sure.
Hey, guys. We're agreeing to keep
these ratings just between us, yeah?
Of course. We're not stupid.
So absolutely none of what we're saying leaves this room?
If this information got out, we'd have a real problem.
Don't mind me. Just passing by.
Oh, no he di'n't!
Kill him!
If I can't get the low-down on juicy
gossip like this, what's Mach Twenty good for?!
Ew. Who wants to talk about boys?
Ugh, c'mon. That's what girls
talk about on trips like these.
Don't be a party pooper.
I'll start! I have a huge crush on Mr. Karasuma!
Honey, there's no one here that
doesn't have a thing for that man.
I'm talking about boys in our
class that we think are hotties.
Aww...
Whatever, I'll get the ball rolling.
Isogai and Maehara are half decent, I guess.
Gross. You don't seriously like them?
Why not? Maehara plays the field, though, so
I'd never actually go out with him or anything.
Isogai's class monitor, so he's, like, upwardly mobile.
I don't know. Karma's the
cutest of the bunch if you ask me.
Too bad he's such a psycho.
True...
Come on.
I don't think he's that bad when you get to know him.
Hey, 'least he's quiet most of the time.
Yeah, so are wild animals.
Who'd you pick, Kanzaki?
Uh... I don't really think about it. No idea, sorry.
Oh, please! Liar!
Don't be a prude! Spill it!
You know you have your choice!
They all worship you!
Tell us!
Seriously, you guys!
Knock it off!
Okay, girls. Settle down.
I'm supposed to tell you lights out,
so, I dunno, at least pretend to be asleep?
Wow, way to chaperone there.
We all know you're gonna stay up jibber-jabbing.
Just keep the antics to a dull roar, okay?
Hang on, how come you get to drink beer? Meanie!
I'm an adult, sweetie. Adults get to drink beer.
Why don't you stay up with us?
You could tell us some "adult" stories!
Huh?
We'd probably get more out of 'em than your usual classes.
Why, you trashy li'l ginger...
Now, now.
Don't get bent out of shape.
Huhh?!
No way! You're only twenty?!
You look great, it's just, you're so... "experienced".
I know, right?
And the whole black widow vibe.
Ladies.
I wouldn't have gotten far in
this line of work if I wasn't...
Who the hell just called me a black widow?!
Delayed reaction much?
Whatever. Point is, if I teach you nothing else.
You should know sex appeal is skin deep
and by the time you get it, it fades.
In a place like the one I was born
in, you learn that all too quickly.
Professor Bitch actually said
something profound for a change.
Feels like B.S.
I heard that, you hussy!
Oh, just ignore her.
Tell us about all the rich men you seduced and killed!
That's what we're dying to hear!
Yeah! I totally second that!
Hmph. Well, if you insist.
Be warned, my life story might
be a bit spicy for girls like you.
It all began at the tender age of seventeen.
I don't think so, pal!
You got a lot of balls helping yourself to our girl-talk!
Aw! But I wanna hear your stories, too!
Why can't an impartial observer get in on this action?
Ha! You never tell us about your love life!
You wanna sit there and listen,
fine, but give us the goods!
She's right. It's only fair, you know.
We know you've got a romance in there somewhere!
You like giant boobs!
You must at least have a crush on somebody!
Oh no, he didn't!
Catch him, make him sing, and cut his throat!
There he is!
Come on!
Rats! Caught in a pincer attack!
You guys still trying to kill him?
Assassination doesn't have a curfew, huh?
Hm?
That was a little too close for comfort!
Would you mind telling me what all that racket was about?
Nothing.
The students wanted me to open up about my love life.
Your what?
Oh, I assure you,
my past is positively riddled with romantic encounters.
I haven't enough fingers and
toes to keep count of them all.
Fingers and toes, huh?
I assume you're referring back to a time
when you had hands and feet?
Sorry. I didn't mean to go there.
I wouldn't want to talk about the past in your shoes.
A wise observation, Mr. Karasuma.
It's bad manners to ask after
the number of one's appendages.
Even while traveling together.
This has been such a great trip, right?
It's like we've all really gotten to know each other.
That's true.
Hm? Is something the matter?
I was just thinking.
You know how our trip's mostly over?
Even though it feels like we just got here?
I'm kind of starting to feel the same way about life.
We're just learning about the
world, and it may be over soon.
Yeah...
And even if the world isn't over by March,
this class will be.
Right...
I wanna live big, to experience everything,
to be a top-notch assassin.
I just want my life to have purpose, you know?
Hm. I hear you.
For now, I'd settle for just
one more school trip like this one.
Me, too.
Tonight, the curtain falls on our adventures in Kyoto.
What a trip.
Tomorrow, it's back to life at Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Back to our Assassination Classroom.
So, no luck neutralizing him on the
field trip to Kyoto either, I take it?
This is most unfortunate, Mr. Karasuma.
The fault lies entirely with me, sir.
I will redouble my efforts.
Need I remind you that May is almost over?
Our deadline is fast approaching.
It will be here before we know it.
Precisely.
Why not just fire a missile at the school
and flatten the whole confounded thing?
We've been through this.
Far too much collateral damage.
And there'd be no guarantee he wouldn't escape the blast.
You recall what became of our trying
to hit him over the Pacific, don't you?
He reassembled the missile fragments and handed them back.
Hey, nice try!
So what are you saying?
That there's no surefire way to kill him?
Worry not, gentlemen.
Several allied nations have pooled
their resources to arrive at a solution.
The fruits of their labor are most interesting.
In fact, we've already received
consent from the Ministry of Defense.
Joining the so-called Assassination
Classroom will be two very special additions.
Cutting-edge science has vested both
with veritably superhuman abilities.
One still has a few kinks that need to be worked out.
The other was put on standby while you were in Kyoto.
Oh, yes, Mr. Karasuma.
There is quite a surprise waiting for you back at school.