[KIRIHA]
You haven't forgotten, have you?
The range of an obi.
One jou and one shaku.
Heh. It seems your
body remembers, at least.
[KAZUYA grunts]
Sure does.
Glad to hear it. Now let's
talk about our opponents.
The range of Sunao's sword
should be fairly short.
A single ken at most.
[KIRIHA] The obi's greater
range should give us
a strong advantage while
attacking from a distance.
However, Sunao has two
abilities that change that.
[KAZUYA] Empty Blade.
And Ground Tracer.
[KIRIHA]
Precisely.
Those attacks can hit
at a range of four ken.
That gives them
the reach advantage.
Also, it's a tough matchup.
By virtue of my
spiritual nature,
I'm all but impervious
to normal blades.
But a sword tsukumogami
is a different matter.
All else being equal,
Kotetsu's steel blade will
tear right through my silk.
So they have the
upper hand then.
Not only is their range greater,
they're stronger up close too.
Is that the gist of it?
Yes. However, we've a plan.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[SUNAO grunts]
Those were good,
strong, strikes.
[SUNAO, HONAKA grunting]
[HONOKA]
Hm... Excellent work.
[SUNAO]
Thank you for sparring with me.
[HONOKA]
No prob. It was a nice workout.
So. How good do you
think your chances are?
I have absolutely
no chance of losing.
Their weakness was
made glaringly clear
from our first fight.
What's more, my training
with Kanaka has taught me
most of that
obi's techniques.
Regardless of whatever plan they
might come up with this week,
I will overpower them.
[HONOKA chuckles]
Brash as ever, I see.
[KOTETSU whimpers]
Pardon, but would you mind
if I said something?
I would. You can see that
I'm in the middle of speaking
with Honoka.
Right. And I'm sorry, but...
it's just that--
And you're also as ugly towards
your tsugumomo as ever.
What's up Kotetsu? Talk to us.
[KOTETSU gasps]
Ma'am!
He pales in comparison to Sunao,
but Kazuya Kagami is
still a malison cleanser.
He's been tested against a god,
just like we were.
I'm just saying we shouldn't
underestimate him.
Are you accusing me
of arrogance?
[KOTETSU gasps]
I'm sorry!
[SUNAO] Their local god, Lady
Kukuri, is a water goddess.
She would've tested Kazuya
with her own powers.
Her water powers.
The obi tsukumogami has
always excelled at defense.
I'm sure her wall weave
worked just fine
against a Water Impact.
However, if Kazuya tries a
wall weave against me,
he'll just be trapping himself.
When I cut into it, he'll
have no means of escape.
I need a tsugumomo
that follows orders,
both swiftly,
and without question.
What I don't need from
my tool is opinions.
I understand.
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Projection.
One of several abilities at
a tsukumogami's disposal.
By expending spiritual energy,
they are able to create and
control copies of themselves.
♪
[KAZUYA]
"Duel."
[KAZUYA screams]
[KIRIHA] Don't be so prudish!
You'll make me catch a cold. Ha!
[splashing]
[KIRIHA sighs]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KIRIHA] How are you still
embarrassed after all this time?
Sorry, I just prefer to
be alone when I'm naked.
[KIRIHA sighs]
Okay, loser boy.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KIRIHA] Before this duel,
I need to tell you something.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KUKURI]
Yup! You got it!
I agree to oversee
this duel for you two.
But I can't have either
one of ya gettin' hurt
or kickin' the
bucket on me.
Therefore...!
We'll use these!
Magic dildos?
Is this really the time?
[KUKURI]
Heck no!
Ahem! These here are
enchanted water dolls.
People aiming to become
malison cleansers
have had duels for ages.
But if we'd let 'em kill
and maim each other,
we'd be screwed.
We use these to cast an
invisible barrier of water
around the contestants.
Any damage a fighter would take
is transferred to the doll.
That said...
[KIRIHA] That said, Kukuri's
magic is only designed
to give protection
to you humans.
Kotetsu and I will both
remain vulnerable to damage.
[KAZUYA gasps]
It's alright. That's what
our projections are for.
My projections are not as
powerful as my true self,
but I can regenerate them as
long as I have the energy.
My real obi is also
capable of recovery.
[KIRIHA] But that consumes
a great deal of power,
and will limit my
maneuverability.
If your control of the projected
obi wavers in that time,
we'll naturally lose.
With your current skill,
you can project two obi.
Including the true one,
you have three at your dispense.
You should consider carefully
when deciding which to deploy.
But should the need arise,
don't hesitate to use the
real one. To use me.
[KAZUYA]
Uh-huh...
[KIRIHA] What is it? You seem
like you have something to say.
Alright.
If the real obi were
to get damaged, then,
that would mean you'd
be getting hurt, right, Kiriha?
[KIRIHA]
Mm.
[KAZUYA] I realize that
I've let it happen before.
But the idea of putting you
in harm's way on purpose?
I can't stand it.
Know what? I'll do both.
I'm gonna win this duel,
and protect you too.
If I work hard enough,
I'm sure I'll pull it off.
It's important
that we win this,
but nothing matters more
than keeping you safe.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KIRIHA whimpers]
What?
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[KIRIHA]
Who do you think you are?!
[KAZUYA yelps]
I do the protecting here,
understand?
[KIRIHA growls]
Focus on the task at hand,
you insolent little whelp!
[KAZUYA]
Why?!
[KIRIHA] To bed now.
We must be rested.
[KAZUYA whimpers]
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya?
[KAZUYA gasps]
You've come a long way.
And in but a week's time.
I have?
Aye. You've done quite well.
How to reward you?
Here's a thought.
I know how shy you can
be about these things,
so I give you permission
to grope me in my sleep.
Why would you think that I'd
be into that kind of thing?
--[KIRIHA snores]
--[KAZUYA] Fondling.
[KANAKA laughs]
I really don't think
it's that funny.
[KANAKA chuckles]
Of course not, I'm sorry.
So, what's going on?
[KAZUYA] Well, Kiriha's never
exactly gentle with me.
But she was seriously
brutal today.
We were talking about
the duel tomorrow
and she blew up
out of nowhere.
Not sure if I agree that
it was out of nowhere.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[KANAKA]
The thing about Kiriha
is she's always been
protecting people.
That goes for you, me,
and her previous wielder.
t's been especially true for
you though, hasn't it, Kazuya?
And then you went
and turned the tables.
I'm sure that startled her.
Heck. It might've
taken her breath away.
[KAZUYA]
So... she wasn't mad then?
Kiriha's really quite
a sweetheart. Don't you agree?
[KAZUYA]
Huh? Yeah. I guess so.
I certainly hope
you'd guess so.
After all the naughty things
you've done with her.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[KAZUYA gasps]
First this, then that,
and to top it all off--
No! I...
[KANAKA]
And not just with her, either.
You've been a busy boy.
[KAZUYA yelps]
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya.
[KANAKA] You know, most boys
your age stick with porn.
Hey! Cut it out with
these weird illusions.
You're freaking me out!
You're definitely making those
illusions yourself, buster.
I mean we are hanging out
in your dream, aren't we?
[KAZYUA gasps]
I really made them myself?
[KAZUYA] Okay. Then I should
be able to get rid of them.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[DUDES]
Kazuya.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[yelps]
[KANAKA chuckles]
Nicely done.
Someone in your position
is gonna need at least
that much willpower.
I guess so.
[KANAKA] Still. You may as
well experiment with her.
Experiment?
[KANAKA] That's what I said.
You know Kiriha wouldn't mind.
I'm sure she'd be quite
gentle in that context.
[KAZUYA sighs]
I think so too, but...
[gasps]
[KAZUYA] I love the way things
are right now. You know?
[KAZUYA] Kiriha, Kukuri,
Kokuyou, and Chisato.
They're great. I really enjoy
just being around them.
If something more
happened with any of them,
I feel like that might
change things too much.
[KANAKA]
Huh... Yeah, I see your point.
[KANAKA gasps] Looks like dawn.
I'd better get going.
[KAZUYA] See ya later,
previous malison cleanser.
Right. Catch ya later.
The previous malison cleanser.
Wait. I thought that the
previous malison cleanser
was my mother. But if my mother
was suppose to be the previous
malison cleanser, then wouldn't
that mean that she's...
Wait... no...
[KANAKA]
Don't hurt yourself, kiddo.
That thought's been sealed away,
so you can't connect the dots.
Take it easy. It'll come back
to you one of these days.
And until then? I'll be waiting.
[KAZUYA gasps]
It was just a dream,
macho men are not your thing,
it was just
a dream, it's fine!
[KAZUYA, KIRIHA]
Tsugumomo!
[SUNAO, KOTETSU]
Tsugumomo.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[SUNAO grunts]
[KUKURI]
The bonds are made.
From here on out, any injury
one of you would get will be
inflicted on these
dolls instead.
There are three ways
that this duel can end.
The water doll's power only
works on this hallowed ground,
so if ya leave, ya lose.
The main two ways to win are
by breaking your opponent's
water doll, or getting
them to surrender.
Those are all the rules
we've got, so keep 'em in mind.
All right. The malison
cleanser of Kamioka
has been challenged
to a duel for his title.
And the Incarnation
of Hakusan Myouri,
Kukuri-hime no Ookami,
has agreed to preside.
I'm sure you'll both
fight with honor.
[SUNAO] To become a malison
cleanser like my brother.
And to surpass Kanaka,
who stole my vendetta,
I have trained and trained,
pushing myself to the
limit since I was a child.
But this boy...
[SUNAO]
It just "kind of happened?"
Yeah, pretty much. Well,
Kukuri ordered me to do it,
so I didn't have a choice.
But, whatever. So it goes.
[SUNAO
This brat didn't work at all
to become Kanaka's successor.
He didn't even want it.
He's my foe alright.
It's my duty to teach him that
things won't always be so easy.
[KOTETSU]
Suou lost his life because
I was too weak to protect him.
If we lose this battle too,
it'll be because of my weakness.
Again...
I can't let it come to that.
[KAZUYA]
Ignorant and unprepared.
That's what I was when I first
became malison cleanser.
But I've grown since then.
If I have to inflict malison
on the people around me,
then I have to be the
one to protect them.
This is my duty. More than
anyone else can claim.
And besides...
Kotetsu? My tool is
none of your concern.
[KAZUYA]
Why be so mean to him?
[SUNAO]
Because he belongs to me.
And when I own an object,
I use it however I please.
[KAZUYA]
Tsugumomo are more than tools.
They're our partners. We have to
beat Sunao to prove that true.
Alright. We've waited
long enough.
[KIRIHA] Time we paid them
back for before, Kazuya!
[KAZUYA grunts]
Combatants at the ready...
[KUKURI]
Begin!
[KAZUYA grunts]
[SUNAO]
Why's he moving forward?
Dummy Weave!
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunting]
[SUNAO] That thing again?
I'll tear it to shreds.
[KIRIHA] Get ready, Kazuya.
Do it just as we planned.
Right!
[SUNAO]
Empty Blade!
[SUNAO grunts]
[KOTETSU]
Are you alright?
We got her!
[KIRIHA] A glancing blow.
Stay wary and hold this range.
We're ill-matched
against that sword,
but her empty blade is
just a projection technique.
It's weaker than the real blade,
and far easier enough
to defend against.
What's more, we know
she needs time in between
attacks to recharge. Once we've
parried her next strike,
we'll use that time to counter.
[HONOKA] Seems your boy's
waiting to riposte. Clever.
[KUKURI]
Huh?
Honoka. You came.
Yeah. Thought I'd send
an avatar, at least.
Huh. I heard he was
a worthless coward.
Completely lacking in skill.
But the kid's putting on
a surprisingly good show.
They make nice rivals,
don't ya think?
Yeah, I do.
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunting]
[SUNAO] He's figured
out my range exactly.
As long as he has those
dummies to block my strikes,
he can dart in right
after to counterattack.
[KIRIHA] She's starting to
catch on to our strategy.
Then let's change it.
Tangle Ball!
[SUNAO]
I've never seen this technique.
[SUNAO grunts]
[KOTETSU]
We should step back
until we know what
they're planning.
Shut up! Retreating is
for losers.
[KAZUYA shouts]
[SUNAO]
How'd it change that fast?
[SUNAO shouts]
Whoa. That's impressive.
They've got her on the ropes.
Huh. This seems a lot more
one-sided than it ought to be.
[SUNAO pants]
[HONOKA sighs]
Wait. Don't tell me.
[KOTETSU] He's changing
his tactics and obi weaves
too quickly for you
to dodge on reflex.
Let's retreat for now and
come up with a plan.
Don't be such a damn coward.
I'll face him head on,
take everything he's got,
and prove I'm stronger.
Is just what she'd be thinking.
[KIRIHA]
Sunao seems to want more.
Why don't we oblige her?
Tangle Ball!
[KAZUYA, SUNAO grunting
[gasps]
[SUNAO grunts]
Crap.
[KIRIHA] We still have momentum.
Press your attack!
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunting]
[KUKURI chuckles]
Looks like Kazuya's got this.
Whatever, they've barely
even started fighting!
[KUKURI chuckles]
[KIRIHA] She's blocking
everything we throw at her.
Still, a sword's
offensive by nature.
If she can't attack,
she can't defeat us.
[SUNAO exhales] So this
is what they came up with.
Not bad. But it won't be enough.
[KIRIHA] She'll be
expecting us to counter now,
so keep it quick, alright?
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunting]
Empty Blade.
Second Sword.
[gasps, shouts]
Kazuya!
Nice one!
Two in a row?
[KIRIHA grunts]
Run. Get out of her range!
[SUNAO]Ground Tracer!
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
It's past her max range!
[KAZUYA pants]
[KIRIHA] We need to change
our plan. Keep running!
[KAZUYA]
Right!
[SUNAO grunts, gasps]
[SUNAO]
A stone?
Archery Weave!
[SUNAO shouts]
Looks like the tables
have turned, doesn't it Kukuri?
They've barely even
started fighting.
Their plan was to exploit
the cooldown time
between Sunao's
ranged attacks.
Let's see if they can adapt it.
She's firing consecutive
strikes, and at greater range.
Is she doing what I think?
Yup. By reducing
the power of each attack,
she's able to chain
them together
and extend their range.
Which, I have to say,
requires a great deal of skill.
Kazuya's still got plenty
up his sleeve, you'll see!
Yeah, yeah.
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunting]
[KAZUYA]
I've gotta try something.
[KIRIHA]
Wait! The second strike!
[SUNAO shouts]
[KIRIHA yells]
[KAZUYA gassp]
Kiriha! That was the real one.
[KIRIHA]
I'll be fine.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KIRIHA] Our old tactics won't
work anymore. What now?
[KAZUYA gasps]
We lost a projection.
[KIRIHA] And we won't get
it back 'til I recover.
[SUNAO, KAZUYA grunt]
[KIRIHA] Imbecile! Why didn't
you defend with a shield weave?
[gasps]
[SUNAO shouts]
[SUNAO] They're in range
of the real sword now.
Let's see him shield weave
his way out of this.
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya! What are you doing?
[KAZUYA] I need two
obi for a shield weave.
But with one projection missing,
that would mean blocking
with the original.
And if I do that, Kiriha will...
Don't hesitate to
use the real one.
I'm gonna win this duel.
And protect you too.
I won't hesitate to use you.
But I won't let her hurt you.
I know what to do!
Obi Hand Weave!
[KOTETSU]
We've never seen this!
It doesn't matter!
[BOTH gasp]
Huh?
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
Obi Hand Weave: Watershed!
♪
[KAZUYA] Now that we've endured
Sunao's initial assault,
the battle heads
towards its final stage.
We're giving this fight
everything we have.
Find out who wins
in the final episode.
Tsugumomo, Chapter 12:
"Partner."
Don't miss it!