We're training? You mean now?
Precisely! You are
a malison cleanser.
The job requires fortitude.
I'm gonna pass. I had P.E.
today, so I'm pretty tired.
You lazy fool! Obi Torture!
Please no!
What's the matter? Are you okay?
I'm fine, but ever
since our last battle,
I've been unable
to use my powers.
[KIRIHA] What's worse is
that I've been cunsigned
to this fragile body.
Should an amasogi
like the hair monster
or the book beast appear,
I'd lack any means
of fighting it.
Despite myself, I must make you
fit to be malison cleanser.
I'll teach you the art
of wielding an obi.
Hop to! We'll start
with jogging.
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Malison Atonement.
When a human's desire
gives rise to an amasogi,
its destruction will bring
proportionate misfortune
to the host.
[KAZUYA]
"Training."
I'm an indoorsy guy.
This is too much
for me. I can't--
Shut up!
Your training's just begun.
Stop acting so pathetic!
Now stay still while
I climb on your back.
[KAZUYA]
What? I can't carry you!
[KIRIHA]
If this is your limit,
you stand little chance
as a malison cleanser.
Now... it's time we proceed.
[KIRIHA] Frankly, I was
astonished by your prowess
during our fight with Kukuri.
I never imagined you
would be such a natural.
Yeah. I did pretty good.
[KIRIHA] Let's see you
demonstrate it once again.
Um...
Care to start with
a shield weave?
All right.
Obi Shield Weave!
[KIRIHA] What are you doing?
Give it some focus, will you?
Also, you have to project two
obi for the shield weave.
Go!
Yeah, okay. But, uh...
How?
This is embarrassing.
Not only did you
fail to project,
you can't even use a
single obi with skill.
Where did the skill
you displayed
against Kukuri come from?
I-I dunno. Maybe it
was just a fluke.
[KIRIHA]
Ugh. We'll head home for now.
[KAZUYA]
Thank goodness.
[KIRIHA] You'll be running, of
course. With me on your back.
[KAZUYA whining]
Listen, I've something
to tell you.
Huh?
To use one well,
it's essential that you
understand the nature
of a Tsugumomo.
The same logic would
apply to any tool.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, I get it.
[KIRIHA] Most Tsugumomo are
able to manifest as humans.
Do you know why?
Let's see...
I guess it helps them
interact with people.
That's incorrect.
[KAZUYA screams]
The vast majority of Tsugumomo
are born from human tools.
And without someone
to wield them,
even powerful magic tools
are virtually useless.
[KAZUYA]]
Uh.
I see.
So in your human form,
you're able to wield
yourself without help.
[KIRIHA]
Precisely.
However, this form does
have its limitations.
[KIRIHA] How would you
describe my body, Kazuya?
Uh, well, it's very small.
But it's also pretty
soft and warm,
and, I dunno, at the moment,
it smells like shampoo.
[KIRIHA]
Right.
The point is that when
Tsukumogami take human form,
we take on all the weaknesses
that go with that form.
We become beings of flesh.
With skin, muscle,
bone, and organs.
That is to say that any injury
which would be fatal to a human
can also kill one of
my kind in human form.
Not to imply that I'm
invincible otherwise.
If I'm damaged beyond repair
as an obi, I will surely perish.
[KAZUYA]
I guess that makes sense.
But what do you mean when
you say, "beyond repair"?
[KIRIHA] I've never really
tested my limits as an obi.
But I do know I can recover
from minor cuts and tears
with relative ease.
Cool.
By the way, Kazuya.
What's up?
I see that you're equally
pleased with this form.
[KAZUYA yelps]
It's just a
physiological reaction!
[KIRIHA]
Vex me though it may,
Tsukumogami cannot
exist without humans.
The energy that empowers
and sustains us
comes from the bonds
we form with our owners.
Until our battle at the shrine,
I had not accepted
you as my owner.
Once I'd burned through
all the power I had stored,
I was forced to draw
from my very life force,
which is why I've been
reduced to this form.
Kukuri also reverted
to a smaller form.
It's likely her power
has waned as well.
That makes sense.
[KIRIHA] There is still
much to explain, but,
before that, I will train you
in what obi techniques
you can currently manage.
Say what?
[KUKURI]
Whaddaya mean we can't
fix it without money?
The logical conclusion
is that these carpenters
lack faith in your divine power.
We'd do it for free
if we could, miss.
But building supplies
are expensive.
We gotta make ends meet.
[KUKURI grunts]
Come on.
Don't ya know that I'm the
goddess of this whole region?
There's gotta be some
way you can help!
[CARPENTERS gasp]
Well, just for you,
we've installed a few
stopgap measures.
Give us a call once you've
got some cash, 'kay?
[KUKURI] Uh! Get back
here, you cheapskates!
It's a shame we don't
have any Tsugumomo
that are skilled at carpentry.
Lazy buncha cowards!
[KOKUYOU]
For the time being,
we'll just have to endure
things as they are.
[KUKURI whines]
Look, I did it!
Too sloppy! And it
took you too long!
Like this!
[KAZUYA]
Okay.
[KIRIHA]
Up. Do it again.
[KAZUYA]
Ugh... Fine.
Look, I did it!
You took too long. And your
work is quite sloppy.
There's little chance that
it would pass muster.
[KUKURI whines]
[KOKUYOU]
Like this.
Oooh!
[KOKUYOU]
The rain seems to be picking up.
[KUKURI]
It sure is.
Come on!
I did it! At last,
the pudding will be mine!
[KAZUYA] Wait a sec, you used
both hands, didn't you?
How dare you accuse me
of such a crime.
It's not gonna hold!
We must stand our ground.
If we can just get this
last board in place--
[KUKURI screams]
Aww... Dadgummit.
Huh? Is something the matter?
Not at all. Something
wonderful just happened.
My shrine. My poor, poor shrine.
Please, hold it together.
[KUKURI] Where the heck are
we supposed to live now?
There's no need to panic.
I have a place in mind.
Nice dodge, you damn imbecile!
Again! Keep your
distance this time!
--[thudding]
--[KIRIHA yelling]
What am I looking at?
I am training his
sense of range.
An understanding of distance
is essential in battle.
The obi extends exactly
one jou and one shaku,
you must understand
that to use one.
Now you're too far
away, you coward!
A jou and a shaku is
equal to 4.17 meters.
Once he's become practiced
at dodging a weapon
with that same range,
he'll know how far his
own strikes can reach.
Sure. Seems kinda basic.
Isn't this a waste of time
for someone like him?
He seemed to know how to use ya
pretty well back when we fought.
I honestly thought
he might beat me.
[KIRIHA] Bad news. Apparently,
that was beginner's luck.
Wha--?
[KAZUYA grunting]
[KIRIHA] This is the most
he's managed since then.
We've a long way to go.
He's totally useless.
What do I do?
Oh no, I really screwed
the pooch makin' him
the malison cleanser, didn't I?
It doesn't really matter.
What's done is done.
Welp. You keep on training.
I'll just head on back
to the ol' shrine.
Hold on. Where are you going?
Hakusan Shrine's in
the opposite direction.
[laughing]
Well, hey!
On the plus side, you can play
with the other kids anytime!
Can it, you! This is
all your fault, anyway!
Oh goodness, if the local
god's reduced to this state,
then there's bound to be more
supernatural trouble soon.
You don't have nothin'
to worry about.
Let's see here.
The Yagokokoro malison
density forecast says
this week has a projected
low of 0% and a high of 10%.
So nothin's gonna
happen too soon.
Well, that's a relief.
[snickers]
[KAZUYA]
Tsugumomo !
[KOKUYOU, KUKURI]
Tsugumomo .
[KAZUYA groans]
Why would the student
council have called for me?
[KIRIHA] Don't just stand there,
let's get this over with!
We've got training to get to!
Hi, it's Kazuya.
[TADATA]
Oh, good. Come in, please.
You asked for me?
Indeed I did, Kazuya.
I am the Student Council
President, Tadata Tadataka.
It's been some
time, hasn't it?
No offense, man,
but I'm pretty dang sure I've
never talked to you before.
Don't recognize me?
I'm not surprised.
How about if I do this?
Is it coming back yet?
[gasps]
You're the person who got
possessed by that wig monster!
[TADATA chuckles]
I'm terribly sorry about that.
I fear my feelings for you may
have gotten the better of me.
And just so this is clear,
I'm not sexually
attracted to other men.
I'm just attracted to you!
That's right!
You're the only one!
Can't say I prefer that.
Just how long is
this going to take?
Hey! Get back in the bag.
Stop flirting and get
to the point, Tadata.
It's good to see
you again, Kiriha.
And your new look is very cute.
Uh, you two know each other?
We do.
She found me after the incident,
and told me all about
how amasogi work.
Just state your business.
[KAZUYA]
The Tabletop RPG club?
[TADATA]
Not a club. An association.
The problem is that they
want to become a club.
And they're acting
like jerks about it.
[KAZUYA]
Huh? What do you mean?
Did they do something wrong?
[TADATA] Apparently, they've
staged a hostile takeover
of the Social Studies club room.
I sent someone to
reprimand them,
but he came back crying
about a monster.
[KAZUYA]
A monster?
[TADATA]
Right.
I was hoping that you two might
know how to deal with this.
Oh-ho.
An intriguing group of people.
Hey, Osamu.
What are you doing here?
I was just heading to
a Manga club meeting.
By the way, I don't believe
I've made this young
lady's acquaintance yet.
Me?
Why I am Kazuya's master,
Kiriha. Nice to meet you.
I feel compelled to tell you
that these things are best left
in the realm of fantasy, Kazuya.
It isn't what you think.
It's gone! The club room.
It's supposed to be right here!
That is strange, isn't it?
There's no doubt in my mind
that the Social Studies club
used to be right there.
Okay.
Well, if this reacts
to it, we can be sure
that an amasogi's
involved somehow.
Ugh!
You do know this malison
forecast is from two months ago.
[KUKURI]
What?
Aw, crap, I forgot that I never
bought the newest volume.
[KIRIHA] This calls for
an immediate retreat.
We are in no shape
for battle right now.
Can someone explain
what's going on here?
After we've left.
[OSAMU]
Hm?
This shouldn't be possible.
This was the hallway
we came from.
[door opens]
I've been waiting for
you, Mr. President.
[TADATA]
Nakajima. How did you--?
Doesn't matter.
All you need to
know is that today,
you'll be officially certifying
the Tabletop RPG club.
I took the liberty of filling
out the form for you.
I'm not signing that.
You haven't fulfilled
all the qualifications!
[KAZUYA]
Tadata.
Couldn't you just lie
for now and say--?
Vacate that club
room immediately!
I assumed that diplomacy
would fail with you.
If you won't give in,
then I suppose we'll have
to roll for initiative.
[laughing]
My minotaur is ready to fight.
[MINOTAUR roars]
[NAKAJIMA laughs]
[ALL gasp]
This is not a fair fight!
Work them over gently,
my dear minotaur.
That didn't feel gentle!
Will you please just
sign the form, Tadata?
What kind of class
president would I be
if I negotiated with terrorists?
Oh, no.
The science room is open. Hurry!
We can get out
through the veranda.
[gasps]
[KIRIHA] That's no door.
It's only a drawing.
As are the windows!
This room was only a trap.
[NAKAJIMA cackling]
Somebody failed their
perception checks!
Running is no longer
an option, Kazuya.
Use your head. We're
dealing with an amasogi.
Understanding it might
be the key to victory.
Let's see.
That notebook.
I think that it must
be the amasogi.
It has the power to manifest
anything that's drawn inside.
Good. So what's next?
If they come from drawings,
let's try and erase them.
[NAKAJIMA laughs]
[TADATA]
Now!
Take this!
Clever of you, attempting
to wash my minotaur away.
However!
It's not enough.
My creation can easily tank
such a miniscule attack.
In that case... how about this?
A fire extinguisher?
He's whiting out my sketch!
No! My poor minotaur!
Let's run for it!
[TADATA]
Right!
I should be able
to erase this too.
Well done!
Just barely had enough left.
[TADATA, KIRIHA gasp]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Another wall? Why?
[NAKAJIMA laughing]
A skilled GM makes contingencies
for unruly parties.
Give up, or get TPK'd.
There's nowhere left
for you to run.
Why don't you just give up and
sign the paper, Mr. President?
That's odd. He's redrawn the
arm that we erased earlier.
But it's shoddy draftsmanship.
I highly doubt that it will
prove to be functional.
I don't disagree, but
we're still in trouble.
Look over to the right.
[KAZUYA]
A fire extinguisher.
[KIRIHA]
Yes, but it's in a bad spot.
I've put the three
of you in danger.
Apologies. I'll
settle this myself.
[KAZUYA]
He didn't do anything.
This happened because
malison is drawn to me.
Hold on, Tadata.
You shouldn't have to give
in to this guy's bullying.
[TADATA] I don't want to,
but we're out of options.
[KAZUYA]
Not yet we aren't.
Kiriha!
I'm ready.
Tread carefully.
You don't have much health,
and I don't see a cleric.
[MINOTAUR roars]
[KAZUYA] An understanding of
distance is essential in battle.
I'll get close,
but not too close.
The range of an obi:
One jou and one shaku!
Wha--?!
[KIRIHA]
Good work, Kazuya!
I try.
Now eat foam!
[OSAMU]
I see.
[whines]
[OSAMU] So this entire
debacle was caused
by a magical being
called an amasogi.
It came from this sketchbook,
and it was by completing
a drawing he'd prepared
in this sketchbook that
Nakajima was able
to generate that monster.
Hey, that isn't a toy!
Should the drawing be erased
or torn out of the sketchbook,
the creation will disappear.
Listen to me.
Yeah, what is it?
If someone other than
you destroys the amasogi,
you'll have to pay a
malison atonement,
so end this yourself.
[KIRIHA]
Good. That settles that.
Well, Nakajima, the two
of us have a lot to discuss.
Let's go to the student
council office.
[NAKAJIMA]
I think not!
You idiots!
He had another page.
There's nothing for it now!
Are we done for then?
[OSAMU]
No need to worry.
Osamu?
I can simply sketch a
more powerful beast.
Huh? Didn't we have
him tear that book up?
[OSAMU] Suspecting something
like this might happen,
I swapped his sketchbook
out with my own.
Now then, how best to
dispose of your minotaur?
I'm tempted to draw
up a magic girl.
But it's probably best to go the
more straightforward route.
This is check.
Do you like it?
It's a flare dragon.
That's mate.
So he traced it?
How do you mean?
You place a piece of paper over
the drawing you intend to copy.
Then you shine a
light from below,
and draw over the newly
visible lines by hand.
I copied my minotaur
from the art
in one of my tabletop
RPG rulebooks.
Which would explain why
that arm you redrew
was so sloppy in comparison
to the rest of the monster.
Uh-huh.
Seems a waste that you
only made monsters with it.
So many options.
Hey, Kiriha.
You wouldn't mind if I drew
a quick sketch of you?
You wha...?
[OSAMU] In your future
form, to be precise.
You know, I hadn't agreed yet.
She's bodacious, with ten times
more curves than the original!
The hell are you doing?
Destroy that
abomination at once.
Now, now.
Just look how beautiful
you're gonna be someday.
Mind your manners,
you worthless slave!
She's ten times
more sadistic too!
Go on then.
[KAZUYA]
So in the end,
the sketchbook amasogi was dealt
with at the hands of its host.
[whimpering]
[IMAGINARY KIRIHA]
Yes.
[KAZUYA] An amasogi has
plunged my entire school
into a dating sim universe.
And the culprit's objective
is a... Chisato ending.
Tsugumomo , Chapter 6:
"Memories and
Childhood Friends."
Don't miss it!