[FEMALE TV HOST A] Next up,
we have a self-proclaimed
shock comedy genius.
Give it up for Eko!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[EKO mumbles]
[EKO chuckles]
[KIRIHA laughs]
[KAZUAKI]
Excuse me.
[farting noises]
[KAZUAKI chuckles]
[KIRIHA groans]
[KAZUAKI grunts]
[MALE RADIO ANNOUNCER A]
Bottom of the third,
tied 3 to 3 with
Kaneda at bat.
[KIRIHA laughs]
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Pudding.
The intoxicating aroma of
perfectly caramelized sugar.
The gentle sweetness and texture
of the marriage of egg and milk.
The faintest hint of vanilla
tickling the nose with--
♪
[KAZUYA "A Certain Day in
the Kagami Household."
[KIRIHA laughs]
[KIRIHA growls]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[sighs]
[KASUMI sighs]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[KIRIHA]
Hm!
Pudding.
[KIRIHA gasps, screams]
[screaming continues]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[KIRIHA gasps]
[gasps]
Kazuya!
Pretty please.
[KUKURI]
Cabbage!
[KIRIHA]
Potatoes.
Well done!
Come now, what's the matter?
I think you know!
[KAZUYA sighs]
[KIRIHA laughs]
Come n' get me!
[KUKURI]
Stop running!
[BOTH gasping]
[KIRIHA, KUKURI giggle]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[inaudible]
[KIRIHA chuckles]
[KIRIHA]
Hm!
[KUKURI]
Huh?
--[KAZUYA] Hm.
--[KUKURI giggles]
[KUKURI]
Hm... Hm!
[KUKURI giggles]
[KUKURI gasps]
[KAZUYA]
I'm home!
[KUKURI giggles]
Welcome home babe!
[KUKURI]
Would you like some dinner?
A bath first, maybe?
Or should we just...
[KUKURI giggles]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[KAZUYA groans]
[KIRIHA whistles]
[screams, cries]
[KIRIHA]
♪ I really want some pudding. ♪
[KIRIHA CHOIR]
♪ Love how it's jiggly. ♪
♪ Want to chow down
on pudding! ♪
[KIRIHA CHOIR] ♪ Love how
it melts in my mouth! ♪
♪ I'd put my life on the line
for a spoon full of pudding! ♪
Pudding. Pu...
Do not imitate her.
[KIRIHA]
♪ Pudding. Pudding. ♪
♪ All of the pudding
in the whole world. ♪
Poor girl must
really love pudding.
Where are her parents?
[KIRIHA]
♪ Oh, how I want some. ♪
Second verse.
Cut it out!
[KIRIHA cheers]
[KIRIHA hums]
[KUKURI gasps]
[KUKURI whimpers]
[KUKURI]
♪ Mizu Youkan, youkan, ♪
♪ mizu youkan, youkan. ♪
♪ [Shall we eat Youkan? ♪
[KUKURI giggles]
[KIRIHA]
Something wrong Kukuri?
[KUKURI nervously chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[DUDES gasp]
We thank you for
shopping with us.
[KUKURI]
Kokuyou!
[DUDES]
Jiggle. Jiggle...
Good evening.
Uh...
[MALE RADIO ANNOUNCER A] Looks
like he's squaring up to bunt!
Wait, there it goes!
Look at it fly!
A home run bunt!
[KIRIHA] Pu-Pu-Pudding.
Pu-Pu-Pudding.
My name's vanilla
custard and when you
mix me with caramel,
I'm delicious!
Nothing beats the
taste of pudding.
Nope, nope, nope!
[KAZUYA]
We're back.
[KUKURI]
We're home!
[KOKUYOU]
We've returned from the store.
[KIRIHA]
Bought that stuff you asked for.
[ALL]
Thank you for this meal!
[KAZUAKI] Right, I thought
so too. No way, what?
[KIRIHA]
Gimme that!
[KOKUYOU]
Delicious.
[ALL]
That was really tasty.
[KIRIHA]
Pudding, pudding, pudding!
[KIRIHA shouts]
[KIRIHA giggles]
So good!
[KUKURI gasps]
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[KIRIHA]
Pudding, pudding, pudding.
[KUKURI]
Mizu youkan!
[KIRIHA]
Pudding. Pudding!
[KUKURI]
Mizu youkan!
[KIRIHA]
Pudding. pudding!
[KUKURI]
Mizu youkan!
[KIRIHA, KUKURI]
Thanks for the treat!
[KIRIHA]
Tsugumomo!
[KAZUYA]
Tsugumomo.
[KAZUYA
"The Super Popular Fragrance."
[KIRIHA chuckles]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[CHISATO]
Oh, Kazuya.
[KUKURI]
Kazuya.
[FEMALES giggle]
[KAZUYA] How did I get myself
into this insane situation?
Well, it all began this morning.
[KAZUYA, CHISATO gasp]
[KAZUYA]
Shirou? What's going on?
Hey. Kazuya, Class Rep
and Osamu. How's it hangin'?
What the hell do you
think you're tryin'
to pull here, Shirou?
This ain't right!
You've been our
MCS from day one!
[MACHO VOICE A]
Motenai. Champion! Shiramine!
[ALL]
What gives?
[SHIROU]
Hm? How's this? You love it.
Shirou, you naughty boy!
Do it to me too, Shirou!
[SHIROU]
Mm? Sure thing.
--[FEMALE STUDENTS chatter]
--[SHIROU chuckles]
[CHISATO]
In.. a... ppropriate!
How dare you defile
this place of learning?
This harem must
disperse at once!
[FEMALE STUDENT B] Shut up,
you four-eyed square.
Stop trying to ruin our
polyamorous fun time!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Yeah you tell her!
[FEMALE STUDENT D]
Go away, loser!
Hey, there's no need to
fight over me, ladies.
I've got enough love for
every last one of you.
[GIRLS giggle]
To the best of my knowledge,
no girl has ever had eyes
for our esteemed Shirou.
Strange that he would
become so popular overnight.
I highly doubt this phenomenon
has a natural cause.
[KIRIHA]
Correct! It's supernatural!
This is certainly the
work of an amasogi.
Come on, Kiriha! I asked
you to stay in the bag.
Like, for the seventeenth time.
[KIRIHA] Curb your tongue,
you craven oaf!
[KAZUYA screams]
[KIRIHA] How would anyone
notice me amidst this commotion?
We checked the
malison forecast.
It indicated that we were in
for some denser malison
over the next few days.
So I was expecting something
like this to come up.
Now, Kazuya,
it's in times like these that
malison cleansers are needed.
Let's see you in action.
Okay, well what do I do?
[KIRIHA]
Think for yourself.
Alright. I'll try that.
[GIRLS moaning]
Hey! Hey, Shirou!
[moaning continues]
[KAZUYA]
Hey horn-dog!
[SHIROU] Hm? Oh, did you
need something?
[FEMALE STUDENT A moans]
I'm somewhat occupied at
the moment. Can't you tell?
I know that you used
some kind of magical tool
to make all these
girls like you!
[SHIROU gasps]
A tool?
Don't think he should've
revealed that
in front of everyone.
That idiot.
Love you get like this isn't
the real deal! It's artificial.
It's nothing but an illusion!
With this tool...
...this chick magnet...
...I could have...
...a harem.
[MALE STUDENTS gasp]
A harem?
Listen Shirou! You have to
destroy this thing immediately!
My newfound studliness
is all natural!
The girls took a while to start
noticing my charm, you idiot!
It's definitely not
that I started using
some magical cologne!
Sure it's not.
Shot himself in the foot.
[MALE STUDENTS] Cologne that
makes girls want you?
[MALE STUDENTS growl]
[SHIROU yelps]
Oh, no.
[MALE STUDENTS]
Hand it over.
[MALE STUDENTS shout]
[GIRLS scream]
Damn. We've no choice. Kazuya!
[KAZUYA gasps, grunts]
[MALE STUDENT A]
Where's the stuff?
[MALE STUDENT B]
We want girls too!
[MALE STUDENT C]
Harem, harem!
Back off, jerks! No way
am I giving this up!
It belongs to me!
[KAZUYA]
Obi Strike!
[MALE STUDENTS shout]
[SHIROU grunts]
Must keep the precious.
Sorry about that, guys.
Kazuya... I fear that
this is far from over.
[MALE STUDENT C]
Must get popular.
Uh...
They're acting pretty strange.
Did the amasogi turn
them into zombies?
[KIRIHA] The desire that spawned
the amasogi seems to resonate
quite strongly with them.
They are not in
their right minds.
[MALE STUDENTS growl]
Go away! Leave me alone!
[KAZUYA] We're getting
out of here, Shirou.
[MALE STUDENT D]
Give...
[MALE STUDENT B]
...us...
[MALE STUDENT E]
...the spray!
[whimpers]
[MALE STUDENT F]
Want... girls.
[MALE STUDENT G]
All the girls!
[KIRIHA]
To think that a single amasogi
could frenzy them like this.
How desperate are these losers?
They're desperate. Sorry Shirou.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[CHISATO gasps]
They're up ahead too!
[MALE STUDENT I]
Must procreate.
[MALE STUDENT J]
Make me a stud!
[MALE STUDENT K]
Harem! Harem!
Follow me.
[MALE STUDENTS groan]
[SHIROU grunts]
[SHIROU] Don't worry baby.
Daddy's gonna keep you safe.
[growling continues]
[OSAMU]
This way!
[SHIROU]
Ow!
[MALE STUDENTS groan]
[ALL pant]
Man, that was rough.
We should be able to
wait them out in here.
[MALE STUDENT F]
D-D-Dirty boy. Get clean.
[MALE STUDENTS groan]
[MALE STUDENT L, F]
Girls! Girls!
[CHISATO screams]
[KIRIHA] Don't panic, Kazuya.
Cast these beasts to the abyss.
[KAZUYA] Sledgehammer Weave!
Spiral Weave!
[MALE STUDENTS shout]
[KAZUYA]
So... Care to explain?
[SHIROU]
Fine. It started yesterday.
Thank you, but no.
[SHIROU gasps]
Kay. But why not?
[MISAGO]
Well, two months ago,
you liked that
third year, Suganuma.
Then one month ago,
it was the first year Miwa.
Followed by Suzuki.
[SHIROU gasps]
[MISAGO]
A week ago, it was Akashi.
And then just three days ago,
you told Shirai from
Class 4 that you liked her.
Here's a tip for you.
A girl wants a boy who has eyes
for her alone. Bye Shirou.
[SHIROU gasps]
Damn. The hell was that?
It was like she knew my
entire friggin' history.
Just who is the asshole
telling everyone
about all my attempts?
Damn it all!
Looks like I drenched myself
in this crap for nothing, then.
So much for "The
Hot Guys' Cologne
that makes all
the girls want you."
[SHIROU]
Hm? What's this?
"If you wanna score,
then here's your ticket.
This cutting-edge cologne
for hot guys only
will unleash your pheromones.
One spritz and all
the girls'll want you."
[gasps]
"Drench yourself and you'll
be a go-go girl magnet!
Caution: May make
you too popular."
Oh, this is just the
stuff for me!
Price is no object, that sexy
elixir must become mine!
[SHIROU squeals]
I'm comin' at ya ladies!
[giggles]
[SHIROU] Tch. Welp.
I should've known better.
[sighs]
What a rip off.
Guess I'll pick up
the Weekly Boingy:
Heavy Breathing Special
and head home.
[COLOGNE]
Let's not be hasty.
[SHIROU gasps]
[COLOGNE]
Why give up so soon?
[SHIROU gasps]
[COLOGNE]
Try me one last time.
[SHIROU] So yeah.
I listened to the creepy voice.
Sorry for trying.
That's quite the story.
If we don't keep our distance,
we'll likely fall under the
spell's effect as well.
Be careful.
Thanks for the warning.
If you don't destroy
this thing yourself,
you'll suffer a
malison atonement.
It's basically
like poetic justice.
You'll handle it, right?
Yeah. I understand.
[SHIROU grunts]
[GIRLS giggling]
Touch me, Shirou!
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
We love you!
We had a good run.
[KAZUYA]
Shirou.
I get it, man.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
You're bad Shirou.
[KAZUYA]
Shirou!
Fine, I'll do it!
I have plenty of regrets
but you aren't one!
[ALL gasp]
[KAZUYA screams]
It's way too much!
What the heck have
you done to me, Shirou?
[LADIES shouting]
[KAZUYA]
Help me!
I'm home!
[sighs]
[gasps]
Welcome back home.
Why are you in such a rush?
Goodness. Look at
the state of you.
Just took a bit of a fall.
I'll go take a bath
and clean myself up.
Huh?
[KAZUYA sighs]
[KAZUYA]
What a relief.
Now then...
[KAZUYA] Dang. I brought this
along without thinking.
What should I do with it?
Guess I'll just talk
to Shirou tomorrow.
[KASUMI]
Brother!
[KAZUYA stutters]
[KASUMI]
How's the water in there?
[sighs]
It's just right!
[KAZUYA]
That was scary.
Thank goodness
she's normal, at least.
[KASUMI]
Kazuya?
What's up?
You wouldn't mind...
if I joined you?
[sighs]
C'mon, quit jokin' around.
[gasps]
[KASUMI giggles]
[KAZUYA shouts]
Kasumi, your clothes!
[KASUMI] Well, I can't
bathe with them on, can I?
That is true, but...
[KOKUYOU] Good evening, sir.
I shall wash your back tonight.
[KUKURI] We've decided
to join you as well.
[KOKUYOU]
To demonstrate our gratitude.
[KUKURI]
So there's no need to thank us.
[KOKUYOU] Now, Kazuya.
Let us clean one another.
[KUKURI] Y'know, Kazuya,
sponges aren't really needed.
If we rub our bodies like so,
we'll all get clean.
Help me!
[BOTH]
Hold it right there!
Back off girls, Kazuya is mine!
Shut up nerd, he's mine
and you know it!
Wow, this is starting
to get even weirder!
[KASUMI]
Kazuya. You've gotten so big.
I want you to know, I'm proud.
[KAZUYA whimpers]
[KOKUYOU giggles]
What's wrong?
You seem to be
stiffening up on us.
[KAZUYA whimpers]
[KUKURI] Doesn't all
this feel good, Kazuya?
I bet it does, huh?
Come now. What's wrong? Hm?
Surely you can handle more.
[CHISATO giggles]
Kazuya. That tickles.
[KOKUYOU] We can put it
between these. Like so.
[CHISATO]
It's twitching so much now.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KASUMI] My. Look at
the mess you've made.
[KUKURI] Wow. Doesn't look
like he's done yet.
[KAZUYA shouts]
[CHISATO]
It's so warm, Kazuya.
[KIRIHA] Move aside.
Let me have a go at him.
[KAZUYA shouts]
[CHISATO]
There, there.
[KASUMI]
Ooh, how do his tears taste?
[KAZUYA]
That just happened.
Three times. With all
of them watching.
Now, then. We must
decide who goes first.
[KAZUYA whimpers]
First at what?
You should know by now.
The order in which we
will be deflowering you.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Rock, paper...
[ALL]
...scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[KAZUYA] Sorry, Shirou.
There's only one way outta this.
Hope it doesn't screw
you over too bad.
I'm pretty tired!
[glass shatters]
[school bell rings]
[STUDENTS groan]
[MALE STUDENT F] My eyes.
Oh, god, they're burning.
[KAZUYA] This was Shirou's
malison atonement.
Though its his classmates
that suffered most.
For one full week.
Our classroom was like a
landfill of diapers and eggnog.
What's going on here?
♪
[KAZUYA] There've been several
sightings of a female student
who shouldn't exist. We start
digging into what appears to be
a haunting, only to
discover a different truth.
Tsugumomo,
Chapter 9: "Letter."
Don't miss it!