[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Kamioni.
Born from regrets that reside
in the hair of the departed,
these powerful amasogi can
manipulate their hair at will.
♪
[KAZUYA]
"Letter."
[KUKURI]
Water Pressure!
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya!
Obi Shield Weave!
[KIRIHA]
Good! Now reweave it, quickly!
[KAZUYA]
Uh, okay.
Crap. How'd it-- ?
[KIRIHA grunts]
Untangle it already!
[KAZUYA]
Got it!
Obi Strike!
[KUKURI]
Too slow!
Uh...
[KIRIHA] It took you far too
long to change patterns.
On a scale of one to ten,
you were trash.
Well, he can't become
a master overnight.
[KIRIHA]
Do not coddle him!
Get up, punk. We're doing
drills 'til sundown.
[KAZUYA groans]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[OSAMU] You seem quite
tired today. Are you sick?
Nah, I'm fine. Kiriha's been
running me ragged, that's all.
Don't pass out.
School's important too.
[KAZUYA]
No promises.
[SCHOOL P.A. chimes]
[TADATA]
Kazuya Kagami, Osamu Osanai,
and Chisatoe Chikaishi
of Class 2-2.
Please report to the
student council office.
[ALL gasp]
A summons from Tadata.
I don't feel like he would ask
for the three of us, unless--
Unless something weird happened.
[TADATA]
Ah. Come right--
--[crashing]
--[TADATA shouts]
Hey, are you alright, man?
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[TADATA chuckles] Took a bit
of a spill. My apologies.
Now. Care to sit?
Oh, no you don't!
You aren't brushin' that off!
[KIRIHA]
I can explain.
Huh? Well go ahead, then.
[KIRIHA sighs] Tadata lost
his hair a few weeks ago.
This is his malison atonement.
You'll recall that Tadata's
desires gave rise to an amasogi.
A pseudo-kamioni,
to be specific.
Had it been able
to fulfill his desire,
or had he destroyed
it himself,
that would've been
the end of it.
But I killed it for him,
and so he must atone.
I am as smooth as a
baby from head to toe.
Wait. So then, if my
amasogi had been destroyed,
would I be hairless too?
Happy cancer awareness week!
[CHISATO gasps]
You're jumping to conclusions.
These atonements do vary, based
on the nature of each amasogi.
And so you know, the more
powerful the amasogi,
the more dire the atonement.
That makes sense.
Yes. Kiriha tells me that
this shouldn't last forever.
I've decided to be patient.
Now then. The reason I called.
--[door creaks]
--[GIRL A gasps]
Where?
[GIRL A screams]
That's the gist of it.
The reports come from former
students of class 1-5.
They claim they were
confronted by this girl.
She appears when they're alone,
demanding something.
That's what you
called us about?
Don't waste our time.
Simply warn the girl
to stop lurking about
and be done with it.
[TADATA] Right. I forgot
to mention a key detail.
That girl, Eiko Nago.
She died two years ago.
[TADATA]
And so,
I would like the four of
you to investigate this.
Look, we're not ghost hunters.
True. But to the best of my
knowledge, ghosts don't exist.
With that in mind,
it stands to reason that
there's an amasogi at work.
It makes sense that
we'd look into it.
[OSAMU] Well, we can
start by asking around.
[KIRIHA]
Aye.
I heard she jumped
after school let out.
Didn't leave a note or anything.
I remember her being
really shy and reserved.
But then, a few days
before she passed on,
she started acting really
outgoing and cheerful.
I wonder if that's what she
was really like. You know?
She was in a fan club for this
one boy named Yuuichi Nishina.
Also, she mentioned
a little sister once.
Told me all about how smart
and athletic she was.
[BOY B] Really man? Why are
you people bringing this up?
[OSAMU]
Who else did?
Think her name was Nanako?
She was just some morbid first
year with the Newspaper club.
I wish you guys would just
let us forget about all this.
I see.
[TADATA] We don't exactly have
a wealth of strong leads.
It's a tough subject
to bring up.
We should try and
find some members
of this fan club she was in.
And we might compare notes
with this Nanako Nanakai
from the Newspaper club.
[NANAKO] You must have
some comment. Anything will do.
Please, Yuu. I need to know
what really happened.
I quit the club before
it all happened.
I don't know anything, okay?
And why did you quit?
What was going on?
I told you. I don't know!
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Excuse me.
You're Nanako, right?
I hear that you're doing a
story for the newspaper.
Um, yeah, but who are you?
An actual ghost in
our little school!
I always watched those shows
where they go into the
haunted orphanage or whatever
and now I might get to meet
a real live ghost in the flesh!
Well they aren't alive
and they don't have flesh,
but you know what
I mean, right?
Are you into ghost stories too?
Yeah. They're fine.
That girl you were
just speaking to.
She was with the
Yuuichi Nishina fan club?
She was. I was hoping she'd be
able to give me a lead, but--
[KOSAKABE screams]
[KAZUYA, OSAMU]
Huh?
[KOSAKABE gasps]
[NANAKO]
Yuu! You're not hurt, are you?
Look in there.
[ALL gasp]
That's her. Eiko.
[EIKO]
Where is... it?
Where is the letter?
[KIRIHA]
Capture her, now!
Yeah. On it. Obi Binding!
[NANAKO gasps]
--[gasps]
--[KIRIHA] It's a kamioni.
Brace yourself!
Obi Shield Weave!
[KIRIHA]
Here it comes. Stay focused!
Okay... Obi Strike!
Huh.
She ran away.
[KIRIHA grunts]
Too slow! I've seen
glaciers move faster!
[KAZUYA]
Sorry. I'm sorry!
Speaking of supernatural,
did you just fight with
an obi sash and then
turn it into a girl?
Interesting that the apparition
mentioned a letter.
That was a kamioni
we saw back there.
Regrets can sometimes linger
in the hair of the deceased.
That gives rise to them.
So it isn't like the
one that Tadata made?
[KIRIHA]
Not exactly. Tadata was alive,
and that hair was but a wig.
His was what you might
call a pseudo-kamioni.
This is still
an amasogi, right?
So doesn't it need a
living host to exist?
Yes, it does. A living
human with a wish
that resonates with
the regrets of the dead.
So if we exorcise this
monster ourselves,
someone'll face a
malison atonement.
That's right. But this kamioni
must have an objective.
And if that turns
out to be revenge,
then we'll have to
thwart it somehow.
I'm sure you're listening.
Get up, Yuu. We need help.
Tell us anything and
everything you know.
Alright.
[KOSAKABE] We were just a
bunch of dumb freshman.
There was this boy in our
class and he was really cute.
We all bonded
over liking him.
That's how the Yuuichi
fan club started.
We got along on
the understanding
that we'd share him. All of us.
But then, Yuuichi actually
took an interest in Eiko.
Things got awkward after that.
[KOSAKABE] It was too
much for me, so I left.
I can't say for sure, but I got
the impression that they
started bullying
Eiko pretty badly.
Sakumi was the
group's leader.
[KOSAKABE]
Actually, I heard that she was
the first person to
see Eiko's body.
We should track down the whole
fan club. Especially Sakumi.
By the way, I think we
should assume that
the amasogi's
looking for them too.
Nanako said she would try and
help us warn them about that.
[knocking]
[ALL]
Huh?
[TADATA]
Come in.
[SECRETARY A]
Excuse me, sir.
I have the details you
requested on Eiko Nago.
[TADATA] You have my thanks.
What'd you find?
Well not only did
she have a sister,
her sister is actually
enrolled at this school now.
That's peculiar. I'm fairly
certain that I have
the current student
roster memorized.
There's no Nago in it.
Yeah that's the thing.
Her parents got divorced,
so her surname is different now.
Here's her profile.
[TADATA gasps]
[KIRIHA] Hurry, Kazuya.
Weave it just like I described.
I'll try. Obi wheels?
[KAZUYA yelps]
[SAKUMI screams, whimpers]
[NANAKO]
Tsugumomo!
[EIKO]
Tsugumomo.
[SAKUMI whimpers]
Please. Don't hurt me.
[screams, grunts]
[EIKO]
Where is the letter?
I-I don't know. I never
saw a suicide note!
[KAZUYA]
Let her go!
[SAKUMI gasps]
We made it just in time.
I know you're here, Nanako!
I know your last name
used to be Nago.
And I know what you're doing.
You're trying to find out what
happened to your sister, right?
[NANAKO]
Glad you understand.
You could've killed someone.
I don't think that the
ghost would've killed her.
No one else knows
where the note is.
[NANAKO] I wanted so badly to
know why. Why she jumped.
So when a lock of her
hair took on her form,
I felt like she sent it
to help me find the truth.
[KIRIHA] Strange. If it has
access to Eiko's memories,
the kamioni should know
why she killed herself.
We've seen it speak.
Why wouldn't it just tell her?
Any ideas?
[KIRIHA] Nothing specific.
But there may be another link
between the sisters'
wishes and regrets.
Nanako. So, what's all
this talk about a letter?
It's all this mindless
husk will say.
The key to finding out
what she was thinking.
Sakumi.
[gasps]
[NANAKO] All it asked you
about was a letter.
You called it a suicide
note on your own.
[gasps]
[NANAKO]
Just tell me where you hid it.
Why would you...
[whimpers] I just wanted
them to get together, okay?
He really liked her.
It was obvious.
But she didn't
want to betray us.
So, she started avoiding him,
despite herself.
We only messed with her
so she'd leave the club.
At least, that's what
we told ourselves.
Honestly, we did it out
of jealousy. I'm sorry.
So you bullied her. Is that the
reason why my sister's dead?
That can't be true! The day
she died, we all talked.
She really let us have it.
Said everything she'd
been bottling up before.
She seemed different. Stronger.
She told us she was gonna tell
Yuuichi how she felt and left.
Later, when school let out,
I saw her heading
towards the roof.
After a minute. I decided to
follow her up and apologize.
[SAKUMI] All that she'd left
were her shoes and a note.
A suicide note.
Why did you hide it, Sakumi?
[SAKUMI] Why wouldn't I?
Come on. Think about it.
If she'd named the fan club as
the reason why she jumped,
it would've ruined our lives.
I was scared, okay?
I never read it.
I couldn't bring myself to.
You didn't destroy it, did you?
[SAKUMI] No. I kept it hidden.
I'll go get it right now.
[NANAKO] "Nanako. By the
time you read this,
I'll already be gone."
[EIKO] But you should know that
there's no reason to mourn me.
I try to seem nice
and stay quiet.
But inside, I'm a
horrible person.
My thoughts are rotten. And on
top of that, I'm a coward.
I couldn't ask out
the boy I liked.
When my friends became bullies,
I couldn't stand up to them.
I was too weak to speak
my feelings, or to act on them.
I was really starting
to hate myself.
And that's when the
growth first appeared.
It got bigger and uglier
with each passing day.
Until it started to
look like a face.
[EIKO] I was too scared and
revolted to tell anyone.
I decided just to
hide it. But then...
[BOY C] What do you mean,
you didn't do it?
[EIKO]
I'm sorry.
[BOY C] That essay's two
thirds of our grade!
[EIKO]
I'm sor--
[EIKO'S GROWTH] Cry me
a river, you lazy jerk!
You gave yourself the easy job
and dumped a team's work on me!
You want an essay?
Write it yourself.
[EIKO] Those dark
thoughts I held inside?
The growth said them for me.
It taught me to speak frankly.
To stop caring what
people might think.
And strangely enough,
that helped me make friends.
The growth told me
that it would go away
once my wish was fulfilled.
I thought there was only one
thing that wish could be.
To tell Yuuichi
that I liked him.
[EIKO]
He said he'd go out with me.
I felt like I could fly.
But the growth said that my
wish wasn't granted yet.
That there was someone
who would steal Yuuichi
if it didn't stop them.
[EIKO] Someone more athletic
than me. Smarter. Funnier.
Better in every way.
"It meant you, little sister."
[BOTH gasp]
[EIKO, NANAKO]
The growth says you'll
steal everything from me.
It says you're in the
way of my happiness.
It says that you can't
be allowed to live.
[EIKO] Nanako. Deep down, that's
how I truly feel about you.
I'm so sorry. I don't think
I can hold it back anymore.
But you're still
my little sister.
Nothing can change the
fact that I love you.
[NANAKO] No. Then the real
reason that she killed herself
was for me. To protect me.
[NANAKO sobs]
It's not right.
I'm the one who
should have died.
[KIRIHA] Huh? Nanako wishes
she were dead now.
Could this be why the amasogi
wanted her to read the letter?
To make her feel this way?
[gasps]
That must be it.
Die, Nanako!
Kazuya!
[KAZUYA grunts]
Shield Weave!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Obi Strike!
[shouts]
[KIRIHA] Don't worry,
that was just a projection.
Now ready another!
On it.
[EIKO'S GROWTH growls]
Crap. Obi shield wea--
[grunts]
Kazuya! How bad is it?
[KAZUYA grunts]
The heck's going on here?
[KIRIHA] Don't you see?
The amasogi on Eiko's chest.
It's what gave rise
to this kamioni.
It may have failed at killing
her sister two years ago,
but it hasn't given up.
And just as it was hoping,
the younger Nago sister
wishes for death now.
That wish has boosted
its power exponentially.
[KIRIHA] Run, Kazuya! This is
not a fight you'll survive.
[KIRIHA]
I said run!
Sorry Kiriha, but I can't
leave Nanako behind.
If malison weren't drawn to me,
then this never
would've happened.
I helped create this mess,
and I'll clean it.
Obi Sledgehammer!
[KIRIHA]
Uh... Kazuya, wait!
[yells]
[KAZUYA gasps, yelps]
[KIRIHA]
Shield Weave, two layers!
Double-Woven shield!
[EIKO'S GROWTH shouts]
[KIRIHA] Seems that girl's not
the only one with a death wish.
Fine, we'll try it.
Thanks, Kiriha.
[KIRIHA] That hair is
tougher than it looks.
But do exactly as I say,
and we can breach it.
[KAZUYA]
Wait. If we destroy it,
she'll face a
malison atonement.
[KIRIHA] If you hesitate,
it will kill you.
Understand that you are her
only chance of survival.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya.
The obi's two greatest strengths
are its versatility and speed.
You need to use them.
Right!
Obi Strike!
[KIRIHA] That won't
be enough. Strike Faster!
Give it everything!
[shouts]
Now switch!
[KAZUYA shouts]
Spiral Weave!
[yells]
[KAZUYA gasps]
Na-Na-Nanako, I'm sor--
I'm sorry.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KIRIHA] Do not misinterpret
what you just learned, Nanako.
[NANAKO gasps]
[KIRIHA] While it's
true that your sister
harbored dark emotions,
and that they gave
birth to that mark,
what matters is that she
was willing to give her life
to subdue that
side of herself.
She defeated it!
Her admiration for you may have
been twisted into jealousy,
but her love is what
won in the end.
Eiko gave everything she had
to ensure your survival.
So live. Lest her sacrifice
be wasted. Understand?
You're right.
[KIRIHA]
And as for you.
Your technique was
surprisingly decent.
I'm impressed.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Ya mean it?
[KIRIHA]
However...!
You defied me when I told
you to run, you insolent fool!
[KIRIHA, KAZUYA shouting]
And for that you
must be punished!
Sorry, but I had to!
[shouting continues]
♪
[KAZUYA] I'm starting
to feel pretty guilty
about the atonements
I've inflicted on others,
when another young
malison cleanser shows up
out of nowhere,
and beats me to a pulp.
Apparently, she wants to duel.
Tsugumomo, Chapter 10:
"Nude in the Futon"
Don't miss it!