[KIRIHA groans]
[KIRIHA sighs]
[KIRIHA yawns]
Kazuya...
Wake. Morning has come.
Some servant. Sleeping in
later than your master.
Cease your insolence.
[KIRIHA chuckles]
[KAZUYA] Cut it out, sis.
I'm still tired.
That weird youkai
kept me up all night.
[KIRIHA] Even in your sleep,
you provoke me.
You've sealed your fate.
You hooded dingus!
--[sound of pummeling]
--[KAZUYA screams]
[NARRATOR] Amasogi:
A tsukumogami that comes
to life after a
relatively short time.
They are both powerful
and without restraint.
[KAZUYA] "The Library
and the Childhood Friend."
[KAZUYA pants]
[KAZUYA] Don't panic.
You can still make it.
As long as she hasn't
called attendance yet...
I made it! Hooray...!
Actually, you're quite late.
[KAZUYA]
...aaah...
[school bell rings]
[CHISATO groans]
What were you thinking?
You are just the worst!
Every time you're tardy,
you insult this entire
school! You hear me?
Business as usual for them.
The class rep seems to be
exceptionally stern with Kazuya.
[CHISATO] Are you even
listening to me? Ugh.
[KAZUYA] Damn it.
This is all Kiriha's fault.
[KAZUYA yells]
How is it already past 8?
I set my alarm clock;
I'm sure of it!
[KIRIHA] Oh. That's
what it's called?
It rang most obnoxiously,
so I silenced it.
[KAZUYA sighs]
You suck!
--Off to school!
--[KIRIHA] Aye!
[KAZUYA]
You can't come with me.
[KIRIHA] A servant
does not simply run off
without his master.
Besides, you've never
left me at home before.
[KAZUYA] That was different; you
were just a cloth back then!
This is bad.
If I let her spout this
"servant" stuff at school...
Bow to me! Dumb servant.
[GIRL STUDENT]
That looks so awkward.
[KAZUYA] Kagami Inc.'s
stock will crash hard.
Okay! I'll take you
to school with me!
Hmph. That's right you will.
[KAZUYA] But might I make
one humble request?
[KIRIHA]
Huh...?
I am an obi once more!
Will that do?
[KAZUYA] Perfectly!
Thanks a million.
Now I'll just put you in
this bag to keep you clean.
[KIRIHA] A commendable
precaution!
[KAZUYA] And this
box here'll stop you
from getting damaged
if you're jostled.
[KIRIHA]
How considerate.
[KAZUYA] Finally,
I'll tie the box up
so it won't break open
if it's dropped.
[KIRIHA]
Very thorough.
[KAZUYA]
Okay. I'm out!
[KIRIHA]
Aye! Let's go!
Kazuyaaa!
[KAZUYA giggles]
Serves her right. Stupid youkai.
Ya wanna share your
joke with the class?
I think Chisato's
finally broken him.
Nah, don't worry
about it. It's nothing.
Kay, well, anyway, back to what
I was saying. Rumor has it that
after school, when almost no
one's around, a ghost appears.
That's simply ridiculous.
Tell that to the many
people who've seen it
with their own eyes.
Some saw a weird slug,
and some a weird hairy thing.
[OSAMU] Uh huh. Sounds more
like an unidentified animal
than a ghost.
[KAZUYA groans]
Pretty sure it was that.
Kazuya. Are you listening, man?
[KAZUYA] Sorry,
I kinda zoned out.
Well, what I'm getting at is
that this is the perfect time
for a test of courage!
Invite a cute little lady
to wander the dark
hallways by your side!
Huddled close,
holding hands, maybe.
If you're lucky, a kiss!
If you're sly, a fondle!
Play your cards perfectly,
and Eden awaits!
Mmm! Adolescence
is sweet! Mmm...
[ALL grunt]
[KAZUYA]
What did I do?
That's what you think
adolescence is?
Perhaps instead of cooking up
these ridiculous schemes,
you could be double-checking the
reports that're due 5th period.
Reports? I totally forgot!
Please, Osamu!
Lemme copy yours!
That'll cost twenty pages
of screentone for my manga.
[CHISATO]
Copy?
[KAZUYA yelps]
You'll copy nothing.
We still have lunchtime!
I'll even assist you, but you're
doing the work yourself.
Am I understood?
[KAZUYA]
Nooo!
[SHIROU] Forgive us, Kazuya.
We'd help you if we could.
[OSAMU]
Sorry.
[KAZUYA groans]
There's no way I'll finish
in time. Lemme see yours.
This is so doable.
Just move your hands
instead of your mouth.
I mean...
That part is clearly wrong.
Prince Shotoku came after
the warring states period.
[KAZUYA]
Mm...
Fine, I'll actually try,
are ya happy now?
I will be when you're done.
[KAZUYA]
Mm...
[CHISATO laughs]
Did I get something else wrong?
[CHISATO]
No. Sorry.
I was thinking about how we'd
do this when we were little.
[KAZUYA] Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
You were a pretty intense tutor.
Thank you for your assistance.
[CHISATO] You are quite
welcome, of course.
I was falling behind back then,
so you were a really big help.
[CHISATO] And you're
doing better now?
Actually...
No, I still suck.
[KAZUYA groans]
[CHISATO] Well, if it's
not an intrusion...
[KAZUYA]
Ah...?
[CHISATO] I wouldn't mind
coming to your house again.
I could help catch you up
on your studies. I mean,
teaching others has always been
something I found enjoyable, so.
You mean it?
Yeah, that'd be gre--
[KIRIHA chuckles]
Um... Now wouldn't
be a great time.
[CHISATO] Oh, no worries.
Sorry for being so meddlesome.
Not at all!
Thanks for the offer.
Oh, that was the last page.
Report's done.
Guess I'll go put the books up.
Hey, way to go.
All right.
I'll see you back at class.
[KAZUYA]
Sure. Thanks again, Chisato!
[CHISATO]
Mm--
Uh...
[CHISATO]
Uh?
Let's see...
[KIRIHA]
Alone at last.
[KAZUYA]
Wha...
[KIRIHA]
Heh. Kazuya.
[KAZUYA screams]
[CHISATO gasps]
Hey, Kazuya. Is everything okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm good.
[CHISATO] What happened
to your face?!
Nothing, I'm fine. Yup.
Everything is just fine.
Weren't you heading
back to class, though?
We've only got a few minutes.
Yeah, I know, but the
door won't open.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[CHISATO grunts]
[KAZUYA]
Come on!
The windows
won't open, either.
[KAZUYA pants]
[KAZUYA] I thought
the door was just jammed.
But if the windows
are stuck too...
That's every exit.
[KAZUYA]
We've been trapped.
Huh? Hmm...
[KIRIHA]
Tsugumomo !
[CHISATO]
This is Tsugumomo .
[KAZUYA yells]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KAZUYA sighs]
[KAZUYA]
All right. I give up.
[KAZUYA sighs]
Not only do they refuse to open,
they're unbreakable now.
[CHISATO]
This is weird.
--[KIRIHA laughs]
--[KAZUYA, CHISATO gasp]
[KIRIHA] This is quite
the quandary, Kazuya.
Seems you've gotten
your comeuppance
for trying to leave me behind.
[CHISATO]
Aah...!
[KAZUYA]
Gone commando...
--[KAZUYA screams]
--[KIRIHA grunts]
[KAZUYA] Wait there, Chisato!
We'll be right back!
[crash]
[CHISATO]
Kay...
[KAZUYA pants]
What's this? Feeling
amorous this morning?
What? No, I'm not. How did
you even follow me here?
Wait. The door thing. Are you
doing this to get back at me?
Heh. I'd hardly bother with
such roundabout measures.
[sound of punches landing]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
My preferred type of abuse
is very much physical.
Ya don't say...
At any rate, should misfortune
befall you near here,
it's safe to assume that
a Tsukumogami caused it.
Wait, a tsukumogami...
So another youkai like you?
[sound of punches landing]
I said it again.
Not at all like me, imbecile.
Heed my words.
Tsukumogami generally
fall into two categories.
Ones like myself arise from
objects after many years
of human use. We are
known as Tsugumomo.
In contrast, the tsukumogami
that attacked you yesterday
was one which took form quickly,
due to intense human emotions.
It's called an Amasogi.
A Tsugumomo has a fully
developed conscience.
We are enlightened creatures.
As you can see.
[KAZUYA groans]
[KIRIHA] But Amasogi
are like mewling infants
with magic powers.
They cause problems
like this quite regularly.
We shall need help
to resolve this.
That friend of yours
should do nicely.
[KAZUYA]
Aah...!
Wait, before you go...!
[KIRIHA]
Huh?
[CHISATO]
Uh...
Hello there!
Thank you for waiting.
[CHISATO] It's nice to meet you.
I'm Chisato Chikaishi.
Right, and I am Kiriha,
the tsukumoga--
[KAZUYA yelps] Just tell her
the story we agreed on, okay?
[KIRIHA]
Fine, have it your way.
[KIRIHA clears throat]
Uh... I am Kazuya's cousin, and
I am here to visit his school.
Uh... Name's Kiriha Obina.
Nice to meet you.
[CHISATO]
Sounds likely.
Anyway. Supernatural
stuff's like a hobby for her.
So, she knows a lot
about weirdness.
She thinks she can find a way
out, but she needs our help.
Oh...
[CHISATO] So, in your view...
This supernatural situation
is being caused by one of these
so-called "Amasogi." Right?
Exactly! Such an
intelligent girl.
Now then. We can move on
to escaping its grasp.
I am unsurprised that smashing
the doors and windows
was all his undeveloped mind
could come up with.
You're lucky I'm here.
Sure we are.
[KIRIHA]
Both of you take one.
What are they?
[KIRIHA] Kimono clasps.
Interwoven with my hair.
If they come into the
proximity of any spirit,
they should react.
[KAZUYA] So this'll show us
where the Amasogi is?
That's correct.
The Amasogi must be acting
on the wish of whoever's
emotions gave rise to it.
If we can find out
what that wish is,
the rest will
likely prove simple.
But who would want to
trap us in the library?
I can't think of anyone
who would benefit.
[KAZUYA]
Huh. I can't either.
There's no use in
idle speculation.
Go. Get started already.
Yeah, yeah.
[CHISATO]
Mm...
[CHISATO gasps]
[CHISATO]
I think I found it!
Ha, ha, ha!
That was fast.
[CHISATO]
Could it be this book?
[CHISATO, KIRIHA gasp]
I found one.
Check it out!
[KIRIHA] Huh. Another book?
Are there two Amasogi?
[KAZUYA] This one's
going off too.
[CHISATO]
And this one!
[KAZUYA]
And another!
--[CHISATO] There's one!
--[KAZUYA] Even this?
[CHISATO]
They keep going off!
[KAZUYA]
Yeah.
[KIRIHA groans]
Uh, Kiriha, they seem to be
reacting to everything.
[KIRIHA]
Hm.
Very well. I have
concocted a simpler plan.
Stand back while I
smash that stupid door.
[KAZUYA]
That was my idea.
[KIRIHA]
Spiral Weave!
[CHISATO shudders]
[KIRIHA yells]
[KAZUYA] I'll explain why
this is happening later, okay?
[KIRIHA]
Ha! Almost through the barrier.
Hm?
[CHISATO, KAZUYA gasp]
[ALL yell]
[CHISATO gasps]
What just happened?
Now I see. It would appear that
this entire study's an Amasogi.
You should step back.
[KAZUYA]
Come on!
Obi Shield Weave!
Hey, look out!
It's above you!
[KIRIHA chuckles]
Sledgehammer Weave!
[KIRIHA grunts]
That all you have?
Stop taunting it.
[KIRIHA]
Uh...
[BOOK MONSTER roars]
Heh. You think I'm impressed?
[KIRIHA]
Run away!
This way!
[KIRIHA pants]
[KIRIHA] Seems I'm
the only target.
[KAZUYA, CHISATO pant]
[CHISATO] Huh. Guess it
gave up chasing us.
[KIRIHA]
Yes. Most disappointing.
I was hoping to have
a bit more fun with it.
[KAZUYA yelps]
[BOOK MONSTER roars]
You just had to open
your big, cocky mouth!
[KIRIHA] Seems it wishes
to have more fun as well.
[BOOK MONSTER roars]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[CHISATO, KAZUYA gasp]
[CHISATO]
Wha...?
[KIRIHA] The books protected
her? That explains it.
[BOOK MONSTER roars]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[KIRIHA]
Kazuya!
[KAZUYA yelps]
[KIRIHA] Think back to your
conversation with that girl,
when you first
came into the study.
[KAZUYA] What?
How would that help?
Just do it!
Okay, uh...
Well, I wasn't really sure
what books we should get.
[KIRIHA]
Aye.
So Chisato pulled down
a few books for me.
[KIRIHA]
And then?
Oh, yeah! I mistook Sudoku
for a Warring States Warlord!
His name is Prince Shotoku!
Doesn't matter! What else?
After that, she asked me
if I want her to come over
and help me study
sometime. I said no!
There it is.
[KIRIHA yells]
--[CHISATO cries out]
--[KAZUYA] Are you okay?
That girl is the host.
She made this thing.
--[CHISATO gasps]
--Chisato?
What makes you think that?
I told you what makes Amasogi.
It's strong human desires.
[CHISATO gasps]
Stop asking dumb questions
and grant her desire!
Chisato's desire?
Oh, yeah. Chisato!
[CHISATO gasps]
Uh huh?
Would you like...
[BOOK MONSTER roars softly]
...to come by my place
and tutor me sometime?
[CHISATO]
Ah...
Sure.
[KAZUYA, CHISATO gasp]
[KAZUYA]
We're back.
Ahh... That's that...
My work is done here.
Thanks a bunch.
You saved us.
And on top of that,
I understand Amasogi better.
[KIRIHA] Mm. Then it
was all worthwhile.
As for you, Chisato...
Yes? What is it?
Sorry I didn't realize sooner.
How you felt, I mean.
But you... do now?
Yeah, I do...
You really love teaching
people, don't you?
[CHISATO]
Huh...?
[KIRIHA] The cringe is
strong with this one.
[KAZUYA] Crap, only two minutes
till fifth period starts!
[CHISATO] Oh, no! My perfect
attendance record! Run!
[KAZUYA]
Hurry, go!
[birds chirp]
[CHISATO]
Thanks for having me.
Hey, Kazuya?
You there?
Kazuya, I'm coming in.
--[KIRIHA snores]
--[KAZUYA groans]
[CHISATO] Caught in
the very act!
--[slap]
--[KAZUYA yelps]
How shameless! How obscene!
I can't even look!
[KAZUYA]
Chisato? Why're you here?
Because you invited
me to come over
and study with you
at 1:00, you jerk!
But my alarm... I set it....
Again?! Really?!
[KIRIHA] What's all
the fuss about?
[CHISATO] I brought these.
Help yourself.
[KIRIHA squeals]
Well done!
[KIRIHA giggles, hums]
[CHISATO]
Kazuya. Kiriha.
I'd like to apologize
for yesterday.
I never imagined that something
like that could happen.
Let alone that I could cause it.
[KIRIHA] The blame
is not yours alone.
[CHISATO]
Huh...?
[KIRIHA] There is a much
larger force at play. Malison.
"Malison"?
I've never heard of that.
What is it?
[KIRIHA] How to describe it...
It's a distortion in reality.
Some think it the
root of all creation.
Some think it a mere vestige.
[KAZUYA] I'm really
not following.
No one's surprised.
It can warp our natural
laws, but it does so
only in response to the
will of sentient beings.
In theory, one could wield
the power of malison
to shape the world
to one's will.
Seriously? You can
make it do anything?
[KIRIHA] At normal densities,
the effects of malison
are rather limited. That's
why events like the one
we had at the library
yesterday are so rare.
Wait, so for that to happen,
there must've been
a high concentration
of malison there.
Precisely. What's more,
there's a system in place
for preventing such
things from happening.
That much malison never
should've accumulated.
So what went wrong?
The blame rests with the god
who oversees this area.
[KAZUYA]
A god?
Aye. Our local god.
That idiot Kukuri did this.
[KAZUYA] Kiriha and I
are taken to a shrine
by a mysterious priestess
named Kokuyou.
There, the masked god
Kukuri awaits us.
Next time, Tsugumomo
Chapter 3: "Kukuri-hime."
Don't miss it!