[HONOKA]
Huh?
Have I passed your test, then?
I suppose you must've,
after surviving that.
Sunao Sumeragi.
I hereby pronounce you
a malison cleanser.
[gasps]
Thank you very much, ma'am.
[SUNAO]
I'll take my leave.
[HONOKA]
Sure I can't change your mind?
About going to Kamioka.
You know you could do just as
much good if you stayed here.
I'm sure.
[HONOKA] Mm. You always
were a stubborn one.
Fair enough, I won't
force you to stay.
Begone. And good luck.
[SUNAO]
Thanks!
[HONOKA] I don't expect to hear
from ya 'til you're in Kamioka
and hard at work.
[FEMALE NARRATOR]
Vendetta.
A personal battle that is waged
to avenge a slain parent
or sibling in the hopes
of restoring their honor.
♪
[KAZUYA]
Nude in the Futon!
[TADATA] I see. So the ghost
was really an amasogi,
which was born from a
lock of Nanako's sister's hair,
but was actually
created by a growth.
Seems like the sister's growth
was actually behind
the whole thing.
Yeah. Luckily for us it all
turned out okay in the end.
[KIRIHA grunts]
[knocking]
[TADATA]
Come in.
[KAZUYA]
Nanako! Hey, perfect timing.
We were just telling Tadata
what happened yesterday.
Has anything happened
to you since then?
[All gasp]
[NANAKO sighs]
[ALL gasp]
A malison atonement?
She didn't destroy
her own amasogi.
But she was fine yesterday.
What's the deal?
Malison atonement can
sometimes be delayed.
[KAZUYA gasps]
I'm sorry. If I hadn't
destroyed the kamioni--
You think?
[KIRIHA grunts]
Yes. Nanako is at fault here.
That's why this
is her atonement.
Kiriha. That's kind of rude.
[KIRIHA]
We're done here.
[sighs]
I still don't think there
was any need for you
to be so blunt back there.
[KIRIHA] Silence! Let's head
home and enjoy some pudding.
Yeah, fine.
[SUNAO]
Hey!
[KAZUYA gasps, grunts]
[SUNAO]
Tsk.
[KAZUYA yelps]
[SUNAO grunts]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[gasps]
Who are you? And why
are you attacking him?
If you have just cause,
let's hear it.
You want my reasons?
Then step up... and beat me!
[KIRIHA, SUNAO grunting]
Down here, you fool!
[grunting continues]
Your hits are soft.
Like your master.
[KIRIHA shouts]
Kiriha!
[KAZUYA grunts]
How pathetic. You call
yourself a malison cleanser?
[coughs]
[KIRIHA grunts]
[KIRIHA] I can't let that
rampaging shrew touch him.
But I haven't been able
to project for weeks.
I've got to try.
Obi Strike!
[KAZUYA, KIRIHA gasp]
[KOTETSU chuckles]
I ordered you to stay
out of this, Kotetsu.
I'm sorry Sunao. I just didn't
think that she could project.
So when she did, I was scared.
Shut your mouth. Tools do not
ever talk back to their masters.
[squeals]
[SUNAO]
Change back already.
[KOTETSU]
Um. Right.
[gasps]
A sword Tsugumomo?
Judging from that exchange,
I doubt you've been
possessed by it.
[SUNAO] I'm not so fragile as
to lose my body to a spirit.
[KIRIHA] Okay. Then why'd
you attack us? Speak now.
What's your name?
I'm Sunao Sumeragi.
And I have come here...
...as a malison cleanser
to test his skill.
Kazuya Kagami!
[KAZUYA]
Yeah?
A malison cleanser should
be able to defend himself.
You are clearly unfit
to replace Kanaka.
Who is Kanaka?
Are you playing dumb now?
I expected far
better from her son.
Kanaka... Her son... You mean--
[KAZUYA grunts]
Hold on. How do you know Kanaka?
Wait. I know you.
Where are you going?
To meet the local god.
I'm going to report our fight.
Feel free to tag along.
The local god?
Wouldn't that be...?
[KUKURI] Kukuri-hime no
Ookami has descended!
Have you now?
--[KUKURI shouts]
--Get real!
What are you doing
to the goddess?
You're not hurt, are you?
[KIRIHA]
Hmph.
[KAZUYA]
Kiriha. Rein it in a bit.
Spiral Weave!
[KIRIHA] You defied me
when I told you to run!
[KAZUYA]
Sorry, but I had to!
[SUNAO]
What's the meaning of this?
Why's a clown like
him using Kanaka's obi?
Are you okay?
[SUNAO]
That can't be.
[KUKURI] But it is.
Kanaka is no longer with us.
Her obi has been
passed down to her son
and successor as
malison cleanser.
[SUNAO]
No... If Kanaka's dead, then...
Lady Kukuri. I have a request.
[SUNAO] On that day, I asked
your permission to challenge
the malison cleanser who
had taken Kanaka's position,
so that I might
test his mettle.
And I said to knock
yourself out.
Filled them in on a few details
about what you and Kiriha
been getting up to, as well.
[KAZUYA] Which would explain
how they knew that Kiriha
couldn't project herself.
[SUNAO] Please. Allow me
to thank you once more.
Aw. It was nothin'!
[KIRIHA] Tell me Kukuri.
Which finger do you like least?
[KUKURI screams]
I must ask you, Lady Kukuri.
Huh?
[SUNAO] Tradition has dictated
since ancient times that a
region's most capable warrior
become its malison cleanser,
correct?
[KUKURI]
Yep! You really know your stuff.
I have just tested Kazuya.
At this time I do not believe
him worthy of that title.
Honestly, I think I am a better
candidate for Kamioka.
Say what?
[SUNAO]
As there are now two claimants
to the post in this region,
there is but one
way to determine
which is truly worthy to serve.
Kazuya Kagami!
I challenge you to a duel!
[BOTH gasp]
[SUNAO]
Tsugumomo!
Tsugumomo.
You may not.
[whimpers]
My brother was killed.
You must let me seek vengeance.
Lend me the aid of a
strong tsukumogami.
I don't care if that
monster hurts me.
I don't even care
if it kills me!
[gasps]
[HONOKA] Know your place,
you stupid girl!
Last I checked, you're no
malison cleanser.
Why should I let you take one
of my spirits to your death?
This was a foe that
Suou couldn't beat!
What makes you think that
you would stand a chance?
Listen... Sunao...
Suou didn't want you to
grow up fighting like he did.
He became a malison cleanser
so you wouldn't have to.
He always hoped you'd lead
a normal, peaceful life.
He died trying to ensure
that you'd get a chance to.
Try and respect that, Sunao.
The best way you could honor
him is by granting his wish.
Understand?
Uh-oh.
[KOTETSU sobs]
[KOTETSU]
I'm sorry, Suou.
If I'd just been stronger,
then you'd still be here.
--[SUNAO] Hey!
--[KOTETSU] Huh?
[KOTETSU groans]
What the heck did ya
do that for, Sunao?
[SUNAO] That's for
blubbering like a baby
when there's work to do.
You and me have a
vendetta to fulfill.
[SUNAO] My brother used to
tell me all about about how
amazing you were. How he could
always depend on his Kotetsu.
But now he's dead. He's dead
because you were weak.
Because his tool was flawed and
it failed him. You failed him.
I oughta throw you away.
I ought to, but I won't.
I'm gonna use you anyway.
You might be a loser,
but at least you know
what's worth dying for.
I don't see it. Are you sure
that it went in this direction?
[KOTETSU] I'm sorry! But yeah.
It should be nearby.
I guess it ran then.
We'll keep on looking.
We're right by the
border of Kamioka.
They have their own
malison cleanser.
She'll have sensed it by now.
What, and she'll kill it first?
I won't allow that!
What do you mean, why not?
[gasps] I sense it!
The same presence as before.
[SUNAO grunts]
[SUNAO] The object of
my vendetta's ahead.
It's time to avenge my brother.
[gasps]
[KANAKA]
Spiral Weave!
[gasps]
[KIRIHA shouts]
Drenched in blood again?
You'd think you'd've learned
how to get a clean kill by now.
Yeah, that's my bad.
Haven't had a challenge in
so long, I got carried away.
My vendetta... It's gone. Dead.
My brother's killer's
been killed.
I was supposed to do it.
But you... you!
[SUNAO shouts]
[KANAKA]
Hey... Hey!
Oh. Good, you're still alive.
Hold on. How'd I...?
You got knocked out.
Kiriha is very sorry.
Tell the child you
abused how sorry you are.
She charged us from the bushes
brandishing a sword Tsugumomo.
She had this coming.
[KANAKA] Whatever. Hey, she's
not crushing you, is she?
No, not really.
That's good.
Now, do you mind if I ask
what this is all about, hun?
[gasps]
[KIRIHA]
You're a damned imbecile.
That monster would've killed you
without batting an eye, kid.
Amateurs, am I right?
[KANAKA whimpers]
You poor dear.
You poor, sweet, little thing!
[SUNAO grunts]
[SUNAO] You... You killed my
brother's killer before I could.
Which means... That you are
now the object of my vendetta!
[KIRIHA]
Eh?
Think about this, kid. Shouldn't
you be grateful to the person
who put an end to your vendetta?
No way! You stole it!
Really? How the hell
does that make sense?
Because. Because I-I have to
take vengeance on someone, okay?
It's the only way Suou
can rest in peace!
You're my vendetta now!
I'll beat you!
[KANAKA chuckles]
Okay, then!
You can have your
vendetta with me.
I'll take you on
when you're ready.
[SUNAO gasps]
So, yeah, 'til then.
[KIRIHA sighs] What possessed
you to fuel her delusions?
I dunno, I felt
bad for her, gee.
[KIRIHA groans]
[KANAKA chuckles]
Right!
[SUNAO] I challenged Kanaka
many times after that,
but I never stood a
chance of beating her.
To hone my technique,
I enrolled in the malison
cleanser school, Tsuzuraden.
I did well there.
But after graduating, I returned
to Kamioka to find Kanaka gone.
And a pathetically
weak boy in her place.
My vendetta was with Kanaka.
But I also admired her greatly.
In fact, she was the greatest
teacher I'll ever have.
And if anyone is fit to carry
on her legacy, then it's me.
[KIRIHA growls] I wouldn't
be so sure if I were you.
Quiet, you insolent tool.
[KIRIHA growls]
Kazuya Kagami.
I've challenged you.
Do you accept?
It would be his pleasure to.
Right, Kazuya?
Get up, Kazuya. Time to train.
[KAZUYA]
No thanks.
Huh? What's the matter?
[KAZUYA]
Lots of things.
You plan to let that girl
get away with all she said?
As if I'd let you!
[KIRIHA growls]
Explain yourself, now.
Okay.
Tadata lost his hair,
and Nanako lost her voice.
Because of me.
Because I attract malison.
If it weren't for that,
they'd be fine.
The world would be better
off if I just disappeared.
So I will.
I'll just stay
in here forever.
[KIRIHA]
Mm?
[KAZUYA]
It's for the best.
What of school?
[KAZUYA]
Done with it.
And food?
[KAZUYA]
My sister'll bring it to me.
Malison cleansing?
[KAZUYA]
Had enough.
Have you?
You've always said before that
you wish to take responsibility
for the malison you attract.
What changed?
[KAZUYA] Sunao says that
she wants to do it instead.
So let her.
[KIRIHA]
And what'll you do?
Live your life huddled up
in a makeshift cocoon?
Yeah, I will. If that's what's
best for everyone else,
then it's fine by me.
[KIRIHA growls]
Clothes off, now!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Kiriha. What are you doing?
I don't understand.
[KIRIHA] I think you do.
This puts your heart at ease.
Does it not?
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KIRIHA] Do you truly believe
that this is a solution?
Are you really doing this so as
not to cause others trouble?
I'd understand if you
were simply afraid.
[KAZUYA]
It's not that.
[KIRIHA] You'll likely have
to witness someone else
suffer a malison atonement.
And you'll eventually face even
more fearsome amasogi.
It's a fate many would run from.
[KAZUYA] You don't get it.
I've put so many people at risk.
Almost everyone I know has
suffered because of me.
Even you must think
I'm a pain to deal with.
[KIRIHA gasps] You fool.
Don't you ever think that!
[KAZUYA screams]
It's my right to give you hell,
but I've never treated you
like a burden,
and I've never said I
didn't want you with me!
Listen. I don't care how many
people get hurt, you are mine!
If you were a blight upon
creation that turned the air to
poison with every breath
you took, then I alone would
stand beside you!
Cause all the trouble
you want. Understand?
If that is the price
of your existence,
this world can
damn well pay it.
I'll see that it does.
And if seeing that pains
your heart, then I'll sooth it.
I'll sooth it. And if the
world's pain truly is yours,
then we will go out and
make it better together.
You will always have my aid.
Kiriha.
[KIRIHA]
Men, spirits, even gods.
None of us can survive alone.
The only reason I can
take this form is because
I have you to wield me.
Kazuya... Please understand.
You needn't be the
exception to that rule.
You're acting like this
world would be better off
if you died.
And you're wrong, because...
...because...
[gasps]
If you weren't here,
then I would be lonely.
I guess I can stick around.
Just for you.
[KIRIHA]
Hmph!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA shouts]
[KIRIHA sneezes]
Too cold.
[KAZUYA shouts]
Why did you grow
all of a sudden?!
Uh? You're suddenly
growing as well.
Why don't you tell me?
C'mon.
[KIRIHA] There were signs,
come to think of it.
I managed to project
myself just yesterday.
It all makes sense.
[KIRIHA] Now, Kazuya. Do you
recall what Sunao told us?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[SUNAO] I can wield my sword
at range with an air attack.
[SUNAO] Empty Blade. And an
earth-channeled strike.
Ground Tracer.
Well. That about covers it.
Why are you showing us
all of your techniques?
Huh! That confident, are you?
[SUNAO] I've seen Kanaka's
attacks many times before.
This is only to be fair.
I'll give you a week.
Try and use that time
to come up with a plan.
She seemed super confident.
Aye. And she's right to be.
She has more skill than you.
And it's a bad matchup for me.
Sword cuts cloth.
They have the advantage.
Maybe. But I won't give up.
Ha! I'm glad to hear it.
Let's make this
interesting then.
Should you win,
I'll reward you.
[KAZUYA yelps]
Heh. So, what would you
like for your prize?
[gasps]
Breakfast is ready, brother!
[KUKURI]
Up 'n at 'em--!
[KUKURI screams]
[KASUMI] I knew it. I knew
you couldn't be trusted!
[KUKURI]
How could you, Kiriha?
What is it with you two?!
I will not allow you
to despoil my Kazuya!
Wait, how far did you two get?
[KIRIHA]
Far! It's done.
[KASUMI]
Stop struggling!
You aren't getting up
till we've talked.
[KUKURI]
Aw.
[KAZUYA]
Thank you, Kiriha.
You're hurting
my back, damn it!
[KUKURI]
Just tell us if he got inside.
[KIRIHA] Oh yeah!
Deep inside... the futon.
[KASUMI]
No!
How could you do this with
her when you have me?
[KAZUYA]
What do I say to that?!
[KUKURI]
So how was he?
♪
[KAZUYA]
My weeks up.
It's time to fight Sunao for the
right to be malison cleanser.
She's crazy strong,
but I have to win.
And protect Kiriha too.
Tsugumomo Chapter 11:
"Duel."
Don't miss it!