[PEOPLE yelling]
[MARIE]
We've gotta hurry!
There isn't much
time left to stop it.
Besides, the faster we go,
the sooner I get to meet AnchoR!
That's your priority?
Ugh!
What, you're just
gonna stop there?
[MARIE] We don't have
time for a longer lecture.
It's too quiet.
[HALTER] We haven't seen
a single soul so far.
You think the military
forced them to leave?
[MARIE] Honestly, that
might be for the best.
They'll be safer that way.
There are people in there,
more than a few.
[HALTER gasps]
What d'you know?
[MARIE]
You're all here!
Oh! I'm glad to see
you're in one piece.
What are you doing?
Why haven't you evacuated?
Hey, what do you think of us?
Running away when there's
still work left to do?
We'd never be so irresponsible.
[gasps]
I'm sorry for doubting you.
Of course you wouldn't.
[rumbling]
Another anomaly, huh?
Do you have any
new leads for us?
[MARIE]
Better than that.
I've got the answer to
our problem right here.
Naoto!
Oh my God, it's so beautiful!
I've never seen anything
like this before!
Oh! Look at all the gears...
He's certainly enthusiastic.
Naoto!
Oh, wow! It's so
gorgeous I could cry!
Seriously, can you imagine
the genius it takes
to design and build something
that's not only
perfectly functional
but also incredibly beautiful?
He is such an idiot!
Excuse me, Master,
but I believe you have
better things to do
than gush over this mechanism.
Yeah, you tell him, RyuZU!
Your juvenile outburst is
unseemly and unacceptable.
You are giving this
mold-covered antique
higher praise than you give me.
That's not the point here!
You looked at my entire
body, even inside me,
and you said I was
the most beautiful,
perfect thing you'd ever seen,
but now I can see those
words were just a lie.
I wasn't lying! You are
beautiful and perfect.
But still, these gears
are pretty amazing, too.
Can't I like you both? Eh?
[RYUZU]
I see.
As long as there
are gears involved,
you don't care who
they're attached to.
Not true! You're the best!
Nobody has gears
like you, RyuZU...
[RYUZU]
I see what you're doing.
You want me to take
my clothes off.
No, I didn't say anything
about you stripping!
Keep your clothes on,
--I beg you!
--I've had enough!
Shut up! Right now!
Don't push me!
Then stop acting like a
love-struck school girl
and get to work!
[RYUZU] I would expect a
Meister to demonstrate...
[KONRAD]
Interesting.
How did that boy come across
an Initial-Y Series Unit?
Ahem.
Now, allow me to
introduce him properly.
This is Naoto Miura.
I'm sure some of you will find
this difficult to believe,
but with his help,
I think we'll be able
to repair the Core Tower.
[ALL]
Hmm...
Those aren't... the most
welcoming looks I've ever seen.
I'm sure you've noticed,
he is an idiot.
[NAOTO]
Hey. Shut up!
That said, he's an idiot
we need right now.
The truth is, this kid is
the only hope we have left.
[ALL gasp]
[KONRAD]
Time's running out.
Three hours and 57
minutes until the purge.
We may have some
reservations about this boy,
but following Meister
Marie's lead is our best bet.
Understood, sir.
You won't be sorry.
Well?
Right. Give me a sec.
I will hold those for you.
Cool, thank you.
[NAOTO]
There. That's one.
Two...
[NAOTO]
Three.
Mind telling us what he's doing?
Be quiet.
[sighs]
Good work, Master.
Would you like these back now?
Yeah, thanks a lot.
What did you find?
[NAOTO]
Eighteen spots.
That isn't very many.
Actually, there are 4,047
irregularities that exist,
but those 18 are
the only ones
connected to the
gravity anomaly.
[ENGINEERS gasp]
That's more doable
than I expected.
Now tell me where they are.
I don't really know
how to read that.
Just give me a rough idea.
I'll figure the rest
out from there.
We're ready to assist you.
Simply tell us what
needs to be done.
It will go faster
if we split up.
You and your team can take the
12 problems up on Level 3.
[ENGINEERS]
Got it!
[MARIE]
Please move quickly.
Skip the inspection and move
straight to repair work.
Halter, get the materials
we need and follow me.
[HALTER]
Roger that.
There is an irregularity here.
That boy can't even
read a blueprint.
So how did he find this?
There we go.
All finished up over here.
Yeah here, too.
This one's done.
Good to go, sir.
This one's taken care of.
Excellent work.
One of the problems is in a spot
a human won't be able to get to.
So, RyuZU?
[RYUZU] The only person I take
orders from is Master Naoto.
Please, RyuZU. Fix it?
Very well, as you wish.
[MARIE] From your current
location, jump up 52.3 meters.
Rotate 47.5 degrees
horizontally,
then proceed upward
another 14.25 meters.
Look for a loose gear with a
diameter of 0.07 micrometers.
[RYUZU]
This must be it.
[MARIE]
That gear has to be fixed
without a break in its rotation.
I hate to admit it, but you're
the only one who can do this.
The gear is repaired.
Am I part of the materials
she told you to bring?
[HALTER] Very delicate material.
I'll handle you with care.
Thanks, I think. Hm?
Marie, the spot you're
looking for is up there.
[MARIE] Fourth from the
right edge, correct?
[NAOTO] Yeah. But you'll
need a scaffold to reach it.
[MARIE]
We don't have time for that.
[NAOTO]
Hey, what are you--?
[HALTER]
Just watch. You'll see.
Amazing.
[chuckles]
Okay, on to the next one.
Impressive, huh?
The princess has skills.
Uh-huh.
[HALTER]
That head of hers may look tiny,
but inside it, she's
got every single defect
and repair method stored away.
All she has to do
is consult that data
and she can determine the best
course of action in an instant.
That is the gift of
Marie Bell Breguet.
She's no ordinary Meister.
You're not the only genius here.
[HALTER] Well done, Princess.
Another job well done.
That was the last one!
[chuckles]
[NAOTO chuckles]
Nicely done, Marie.
[HANNES] The Brown's
constant of Floor 24's
pressure control block appears
to have returned to normal.
The dissonance is gone.
Everything sounds right.
How's it looking, Hannes?
Finishing checks now.
We are all clear.
Are you saying what
I think you are?
[HANNES]
I can't believe this.
The repairs succeeded.
We really did it!
[ENGINEERS gasp]
[ENGINEERS cheering]
[KARASAWA] This is unreal! I
didn't think we stood a chance!
[ENGINEER B] It's not a dream,
right? It really happened?
[ENGINEER F] Damn, boys, we did
it! We actually pulled it off!
[HANNES]
I'm sorry for doubting you.
You really came through!
[NAOTO] Huh? But...
I didn't do anything.
What are you talking about?
We couldn't have
done it without you.
If we don't know what's
broken, we can't fix it.
We'd been working for
days to identify the spots
that needed repairing.
You did what we were unable to.
Oh, really?
You mean I was useful?
Useful?
You just saved the lives
of 20 million people.
[NAOTO]
Uh...
Okay.
That's cool!
--[ENGINEER H] What's that?
--[ENGINEER I] What's going on?
I thought we fixed it!
What's happening?
[HANNES]
It's the purge.
The military's
beginning the purge!
[growls]
You've got to be shitting me!
[OPERATOR A]
Coupling shaft disengaged.
[OPERATOR B]
Shaft number 52939 disengaged.
Get this done as
quickly as possible.
We can't afford to
waste any more time.
All the evidence must be
destroyed in the purge.
Can't you people
move any faster?
[grunts]
[MARIE]
To orchestrate the purge,
they'll use the gravity
control system
to drop the city into
the core of the planet.
What can we do that'll
give us the best chance
of stopping them?
Try to access the
system directly?
We don't have time for that.
Should we at least
inform the public
of the military's actions?
At this point, that would only
add to the chaos and confusion.
[MARIE]
There's gotta be something
we haven't thought of yet.
There must be.
Come on, Marie, think!
It looks like there's
something on your mind.
[NAOTO]
Uh, no. It's nothing.
Are you sure about that, Master?
If we had another hour,
no, just 30 more minutes.
That could buy me enough time to
prevent the city from falling.
The Imaginary Gear!
[NAOTO]
No!
[MARIE]
Uh? Naoto?
[MARIE] In order to prevent
the city from falling,
we need to find a way
to generate anti-gravity.
The only chance we have
is to use the Imaginary Gear
contained within RyuZU.
It will allow us to reverse
the energy output!
Do you really expect
me to sacrifice her?
It will only be temporary.
But you can't guarantee
that she'll be okay!
I can repair her!
You just have to trust me!
[NAOTO] I said no!
It's not gonna happen!
[RYUZU] Master, I swear
I will honor the title
"One Who Follows"
and keep you safe,
no matter how perilous
the situation may be.
However, foolish Master Naoto,
if you aren't willing to make
the sacrifice yourself,
somebody else will
have to do it for you.
Try not to waste too
much time crying.
Will you at least
listen to my plan?
I don't wanna hear any more
about sacrificing RyuZU!
Don't be so dramatic.
I have faith in you, Master.
[ALL gasp]
[inaudible]
[wailing]
[NAOTO]
RyuZu.
Marie, you said you had a plan.
So tell me... what do
you need me to do?
[OPERATOR A]
Purge, final sequence.
Counting down for gravity
energy generator.
Commence countdown at once.
[OPERATOR A]
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Final stage commencing.
Purge confirmed. The
city is falling 50...
...100, 150.
[ringing]
Hey, what's happening?
[OFFICER A]
The gravity, it's been reversed.
Somebody is trying to
push the city back up!
Impossible!
Hurry up!
Reconfigure the system!
[ENGINEERS]
Right!
[NAOTO]
How long?
[MARIE]
Thirty minutes.
Longer than that and the
Imaginary Gear won't last.
RyuZU.
[MARIE]
Don't worry.
Thirty minutes is more
than enough for this.
Did you hear something?
There are multiple sounds
approaching quickly,
and they're familiar.
I've heard them before.
[LIMONS]
Find them and kill them!
We're too close now.
No one can stand in
the way of this purge.
Kill them all!
[MARIE]
We're so close!
[HALTER]
I'm gonna go buy you some time.
I'll be more useful out there
than in here, anyway.
[KONRAD] Mind if an old
man joins in the fun?
You sure about that?
[KONRAD]
I have one or two tricks
that make me useful in a fight.
[HALTER chuckles]
[HALTER]
By all means.
[HALTER] Nice of them to
bunch together like that.
There's no need to aim.
Very true.
Let's take advantage of
their formation, shall we?
Whoa, nice.
A bit of a mess, but I can
repair it later. Now, let's go.
We make a good team, Meister.
[MARIE]
Naoto. Naoto.
Naoto!
Now is not the time
to lose focus!
I know that, but I'm
worried about her.
Let's do this, then
we'll bring her back.
Are you with me?
[NAOTO]
Yeah, I am. Let's do it.
[MARIE]
What next?
[NAOTO]
The fifth cylinder,
you need to rotate it
34 degrees to the right.
[OPERATOR A] Soon we'll lose
all control of the system!
[OPERATOR B]
Gravity at...
No. No! They're ruining my plan!
[screams]
Marie! Where are we?
Just a bit longer.
[NAOTO]
Hurry. She's at her limit!
Marie!
[HANNES] Meister Marie!
We did it. We're in!
RyuZU!
Naoto!
[NAOTO screaming]
[RYUZU] Barely awoken
and now I sleep again.
There's no help for it.
Even after 1,800,926 hours,
nothing has changed.
Humanity's intelligence
has still yet to surpass
that of a flea.
And so, I must sleep again.
It shouldn't matter.
I've slept before.
Nothing's changed.
But this feeling...
It's as if my heart...
is constricting.
[RYUZU]
I see now.
I was wrong.
Something has changed.
[NAOTO gasps]
Master Naoto, your face
is already plain, at best.
These tears do
nothing to improve it.
No more crying.
[RYUZU]
Was it a matter of circumstance,
or was it inevitable
from the very beginning?
There are no elements
of coincidence
in the four trillion,
207 billion, 600 million,
8,643 gears that
comprise my body.
Each one has its purpose.
The same is true for me.
I, too, exist for a reason.
I am propelled, as is
everyone on this planet.
Driven by the Gears of Fate.
In this world comprised
entirely of gears,
I have a feeling that the
most important gears of all
will soon begin to turn.
[ANCHOR] Tick, tock. Tick,
tock. Tick, tock. Tick.
[ANCHOR]
The Core Tower was repaired
and the Kyoto Grid was saved.
It seemed as if the planet
had regained a
measure of tranquility.
But that brief peace
would not last long.
In the deepest layers
of the world,
another Gear of Fate was
beginning to creak and move,
promising change ahead.
Next time: "Trishula."
Beginning imaginary output
through the Chrono Hook.
Perpetual Gear,
materializing now.