[MARIE]
My name is Marie Bell Breguet.
As you can see, I'm a member
of the Meister Guild.
If we have inconvenienced
you somehow,
I offer my sincerest apologies.
Holy sprockets, is that
really a Chrono Compass,
the mark of a
world-class clocksmith?!
The thing that allows
you to inspect and tinker
with all the gears in the world?
Can I please, oh please, see?
[MARIE]
Hmph.
If you would calm down, there
are things we need to discuss.
This automaton, YD-01 RyuZU,
is the property of
the Breguet family.
We have a project that
requires its abilities.
So I ask that you
return it to us at once.
Not a chance.
[MARIE gasps]
Of course, I'll make
sure that you're given
an appropriate reward.
I said no.
Sorry, but RyuZU's mine now.
[grumbles]
Well, Halter, looks like
we'll have to bury this guy
and forget we ever met him.
Something tells me
he won't be missed.
We don't have time for this.
We can't afford to be
picky about our methods.
I think you should
stop talking now.
[MARIE]
Shut up!
I'm not gonna let this
idiot get in my way.
I'm serious, Marie,
shut your mouth.
And look.
Now, then...
What was that you were saying
about burying someone?
[RYUZU]
You are a piece of junk,
and that gun is nothing
but a pathetic little toy.
But, toy or not,
I will not allow you
to point it in my
master's direction.
I will prove this by turning
you both into mincemeat.
[gasps]
[HALTER]
I have no intention to hurt him,
and the princess here
wasn't serious, either.
Maybe this will
finally teach you
to keep that big mouth
of yours closed.
I almost just died,
so be nice to me!
You're wrong about that.
If she wanted us
dead, we'd be dead.
Now calm down.
Like it or not, she's the
one who's in control here.
I retract my statement that
you are a piece of junk.
Obviously, you
grasp the situation.
[HALTER]
I apologize for our behavior.
But I would like to ask
that you hear us out.
[NAOTO] They're going to purge
Kyoto and kill everyone
who lives here without
a second thought?
And this is happening
in seven hours?
You've gotta be kidding!
That's why we need you. Now.
The Initial-Y Series
are masterworks,
the best automata
left behind by Y,
the creator of the
Clockwork Planet.
They are maintenance
machines that were entrusted
to the future
generations of our world.
You awoke now for a reason.
Because you are the guardian of
this planet and it needs you.
So am I wrong?
Well?
I'm very sorry.
You aren't as stupid
as I thought you were.
You're stupider.
In fact, you're so
far off the mark,
I can't tell if you're
even trying to arrive
at the correct answer.
[MARIE] Hey, stop that!
I don't need pity from you!
Fine, if I'm wrong,
why don't you tell
me what you are?
[RYUZU]
"One Who Follows."
I exist to stay by
Master Naoto's side
and do everything he wishes.
I'm his servant. I am
to fulfill his desires.
Yeah, baby!
[RYUZU]
However, fortunately for you,
there is somebody who can help
with your current problem.
Really? Who is it?
[gasps]
Well, you see--
Quick, over here!
[MARIE]
Hey, what's going on?
[NAOTO]
There's a big one coming!
[MARIE]
A gravity anomaly!
Is the military
beginning the purge now?
No, it's way too early.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[HALTER]
The damage looks extensive.
[MARIE]
This is just the beginning.
Once the real purge starts,
it won't be so contained.
[NAOTO]
RyuZU, are you all right?
Of course. I am perfectly fine.
Okay, tell me how you knew
what was about to happen!
[NAOTO] There was a loud
noise from underground.
I figured it had to
be an anomaly.
[MARIE] Wait, those are noise
cancelling headphones.
Nowadays, even the cheapest
pair has a 100% block rate.
How can he even
have a conversation?
There's some dissonance.
It's coming from the Kyoto Core
Tower somewhere on Floor 24.
Hold on!
When I told you
about the problem,
I said nothing about
it being on Floor 24.
How did you know?
You're saying that you
pinpointed some anomaly
seven kilometers beneath us
while wearing
noise-cancelling headphones?
Well, yes, why?
That isn't possible!
There's no way a human could
do something like that!
[RYUZU] That's child's
play for Master Naoto.
He did what no one else could.
He was able to locate
and repair the defect
that kept me in
slumber for 206 years.
Given that, I believe
he can save this city.
Where generations of Breguet's
most talented clocksmiths
failed, you succeeded.
I just have slightly better
hearing than the average person.
Not true.
As I've said before,
you're mankind's most
talented clocksmith.
That's nice of you to say,
but I'm not, seriously.
[MARIE]
Naoto, that was your name?
Yeah, that's me.
[MARIE] We have a full
team working on it,
but we still haven't been able
to locate the
problem on Floor 24.
And you're saying
you can do it alone?
[NAOTO]
No.
I can't pick out all
the details from here.
Then I'll take you where
you can pick them out.
Anything to keep the
purge from going forward.
I don't understand why
you're even doing this.
It sounds like you're
surrounded by enemies
and you have no hope of
solving the problem in time.
So why try?
Why not get out while you can?
I've never been the type
of person to calmly accept
that something is impossible.
I know things don't
always work out,
but we're alive right now
because of the people
who weren't afraid
to keep trying
no matter how hopeless
it all seemed.
If I run away, then I'll never
have faith in myself again.
[MARIE]
So please, Naoto.
Help us. The city needs you!
I don't know.
[RYUZU] Since I am nothing
but a servant to Master Naoto,
I was torn about
whether to mention this,
but my younger sister is in
the basement of the Core Tower.
[gasps]
You... Uh... Huh?
[RYUZU]
That's right.
My younger sister,
Initial-Y Series Unit Four,
"One Who Annihilates,"
also known as AnchoR.
[NAOTO] Um. Could you
tell me a little bit about her?
[RYUZU]
She has pretty black hair,
which she wears in a short
bob, and bright red eyes.
She has a little trouble
expressing her emotions,
and she likes to be spoiled.
[NAOTO]
Well, what are we doing?
It's time to get movin',
everybody! Come on...!
Great, we've set an
automaton-obsessed teenage boy
loose on the streets of Kyoto.
[MARIE] If the military finds
out what we're up to,
they'll stop us
however they can.
We need to make it to the
Core Tower before that.
[NAOTO]
Uh, too late. They already know.
What?
[VOICE A] They're approaching
the underground parking lot.
She's with a civilian
and a bodyguard.
A civilian, huh?
That's interesting.
I expect you to capture
Dr. Breguet alive,
whatever the cost.
The civilian and the
bodyguard are disposable.
I can make out a dozen
military automata.
They're ready and
waiting for us.
[MARIE]
No, wait a second.
We can't just go barging
in there like that.
It would cause a rift
between the Meister Guild
and the military for sure.
If that happens...
Okay.
So what should we do
instead of barging in there?
Play politics?
[MARIE]
What do you even know about it?
Nothing, that's why
I'm asking you.
You guys are here because you
wanna fix the Core Tower.
And I'm here because
I wanna meet AnchoR.
So let's do what
needs to be done.
Just focus on the
things that matter, 'kay?
[gasps]
[MARIE]
Halter.
What's up?
[MARIE] I've just been
out-argued by a complete doofus.
I find that very unsettling.
I can tell your ego's
been dealt a serious blow.
Would you like a little
time to recover?
We can always go on without you.
He has a point.
Right. We'll focus
on what matters.
Saving Kyoto.
Let's get to work.
[HALTER]
Sounds good.
Since you're so eager
to get in there,
you better be ready
to help us out.
Um. I'm not really much
of a fighter, so...
It's not your fighting
prowess I'm interested in.
Don't worry,
it's that super hearing of yours
that I mean to put to use.
Is that the best you can do?
Impressive! You're no
ordinary cyborg, are you?
Nope, I'm an eighth
generation Breguet Unit,
a prototype two generations
ahead of what's current.
So cool!
Hey, do you think I could take
a look inside of you later?
[RYUZU] Master, since you
have yet to release
a torrent of pent-up
lust upon me,
I started to think
you were impotent.
Now, I suspect the problem
is that I am not
actually your type.
No! It's not like that, RyuZU.
Any gear nerd would want
the same thing, I swear!
[screams]
[MARIE] Wake up!
Do you have a death wish?
[NAOTO] I'm sorry about before.
Thanks for not letting me die.
It's in my best interest
to keep you alive.
Now try not to
fall behind, okay?
[MARIE] He's dead
accurate on the location
and type of all the enemies.
No one should be
able to do that.
Whatever this is, it's more
than just good hearing.
[NAOTO]
Hey, Marie, hold on a second.
What now?
There's a big one right there.
Optical camouflage?
Is that the VS-08 Goliath?
These guys definitely
aren't screwin' around.
I don't understand
how this happened.
She's dead?
[VOICE A]
It was us or them.
We had no choice
but to shoot her.
Okay, here's what
we're going to do.
After the dust settles,
we'll release a statement
saying she was lost
during the purge.
[VOICE A]
Are you certain?
The military has as
much to lose as we do
if anybody ever finds out
that someone from Vacheron
was involved in the murder
of Breguet's daughter.
Damn it! This wasn't the plan.
People keep getting in my way.
[HALTER chuckles]
[HALTER]
Was that all right?
[MARIE] Yeah, I got
the recording I needed.
It should be plenty of evidence
to prove the connection
between the military, the
Guild, and the Vacheron pigs.
Was it necessary? Did you
have to fake your own death?
[NAOTO] Wow, RyuZU, that
was seriously awesome!
[RYUZU] You are too easily
impressed, Master Naoto.
You should have
higher expectations
of the people who serve you.
Yes.
Marie Bell Breguet is dead.
There is nothing left
to bind me now.
From here on out... I choose
my own path to follow.
Halter!
I'm on it.
[NAOTO yelps]
[NAOTO] How could you destroy a
perfectly good Chrono Compass?
What's the big deal?
It's just a hunk of metal.
"Let's focus on the things
that matter," right?
Now come on. Let's
go and save Kyoto!
[NAOTO] My God. And it's
going to get so much worse.
[MARIE]
Drive faster.
[HALTER]
Right.
[RYUZU]
Excuse me, Master Naoto.
What's going on back there?
[HALTER yelps]
That was close.
Are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
I'm okay, thanks to you,
but what about the others?
[MARIE screams]
Were you trying
to freaking kill me?
No.
In fact, I managed to save
your insignificant life
while ensuring my
master's safety.
Couldn't you have found
a better way? Jeez!
[HALTER]
Sorry, folks.
I think we need to save
this little chat for later.
They sent out the Core
Tower's defense squad.
It looks like we've reached
the end of the road.
[MARIE growls]
Hold on, RyuZU,
what are you doing?
Eliminating them.
These unsightly piles
of junk made the mistake
of pointing their
weapons at my master.
So now, they are mine to
dispose of, as I see fit.
What do you think you can do?
Those are the latest
military automata,
designed specifically to
protect the Core Tower.
[RYUZU]
It doesn't matter how many
of these scrap heaps there are.
They're no match for me,
even though I am the
weakest among my sisters.
Classification: Initial-Y
Series, Unit One,
"One Who Follows," RyuZU.
Unique ability: Dual Time.
Initiating activation sequence.
[RYUZU]
Commencing shift
from Clock One, real time,
to Clock Two, imaginary time.
Chrono Hook.
Making the jump from normal
mode to imaginary mode.
RyuZU!
[RYUZU]
Don't worry, Master.
It will be all right.
I am simply going to activate
the Imaginary Gear
that you fixed.
To you, only a moment
will seem to pass,
but it will be approximately
three hours for me.
I ask that you please allow me
to leave your side
during this time.
[NAOTO]
No!
Relative activation,
Mute Scream, begin.
[NAOTO]
RyuZU!
I'm coming!
Hey, RyuZU.
Ah, thank God. Her gears
are just out of energy.
[NAOTO] She really did
all this by herself?
No time for gawking.
Let's get outta here.
We've gotta get inside
the Core Tower.
Just give me a second
and I'll wind you back up.
[MARIE]
Imaginary time. Incredible.
Mind explaining the
concept? For us laymen.
Imaginary time,
an idea that exists only
in physics calculations.
At least, that's what I thought.
Imaginary time runs orthogonal
to what we experience
as "regular time."
The time is rotated by
a Lorentz transformation.
It becomes symmetrical
in Minkowski space-time.
[NAOTO] Ah, I see.
No, actually I don't.
[MARIE] Essentially, RyuZU
defeated those automata
by fighting in a timeline
that we can't perceive.
Incredible.
No wonder she was completely
drained after that.
You haven't understood half
of what I've said, have you?
How did you fix her when
you don't know anything?
[NAOTO]
Hm...
Maybe not knowing
actually helped me.
I mean, the fact
that Y even thought
of building a
planet out of gears
suggests he had a
screw loose somewhere.
So doesn't it kinda make sense
that the automata he built
are a little absurd, too?
[MARIE]
Unacceptable!
I can't believe the
esteemed Breguet family
was shown up by this
monumental moron!
[RYUZU] Good morning, Master.
Have I been out long?
[NAOTO]
RyuZU?
Um, I have something to ask.
RyuZU, will you
please marry me?!
[BOTH]
Huh?
That was a very ridiculous
question, even for you.
[NAOTO whines]
[MARIE]
So, have you been planning
that insane proposal long,
or is this a nervous breakdown?
[NAOTO]
I couldn't help it.
I opened my mouth,
and it just came out.
I mean, you saw what she did.
How could I not fall in love
after something like that?
I'm human, you know!
After this latest
embarrassing outburst,
I think it's painfully clear
that you are a few
gears short of a clock.
[NAOTO sobs]
Of course, I should've known.
We can only ever be master and
servant; never anything more.
I was under the
impression that automata
had to obey their masters
in every regard.
[RYUZU]
How insulting.
Please don't presume to
compare me to the love dolls
who happily spread their legs
the moment the master
registration is complete.
I am not a mindless object
designed to be lusted over.
I like Master Naoto
of my own free will.
[gasps]
Your free will? But
you're an automaton.
I wanna ask you something.
[RYUZU]
Go ahead.
When I proposed just now,
you said it was ridiculous.
Is there a reason
I can't marry you?
I'm your servant,
but if we married,
we'd be a couple and
that would put us
on equal footing
with one another.
The idea that a master and his
servant could ever be equal?
Impossible.
[NAOTO]
Then let's do this.
Just nod if the answer's yes
and shake your head
if the answer is no.
Is it true what you said before?
That you like me of
your own free will
and not because you were
previously configured
by somebody to do so?
[NAOTO]
Okay, here's my next question.
Is it more than "like"?
D-D-D-D-Do you love me?
[NAOTO]
You do? A little, or a lot?
Can you nod a few times
to show me how much?
I'm so happy.
Best day ever!
Woo-hoo! She meant...
This is quite an
accomplishment, master.
I've never been subjected
to such shameful treatment.
You are singlehandedly
giving new meaning
to the word "perversion."
Are you happy?
[HALTER chuckles]
[MARIE] Am I the only
one who understands
that we're busy, here?!
[RYUZU] The Kyoto Grid is
sinking deeper and deeper
into the ground.
The two geniuses work hard,
doing everything they can
to repair the Core Tower.
But what will happen
when the military
and the Guild crush their
last hope for saving the city?
Next time: "Imaginary Gear."
Foolish Master Naoto.
If you aren't willing to
make the sacrifice yourself,
somebody else will
have to do it for you.
Try not to waste
too much time crying.