[ANCHOR]
All right.
I'm going now.
[RYUZU]
AnchoR, whatever happens,
promise me you'll come back.
Classification:
Initial-Y Series, Unit Four,
One Who Annihilates,
AnchoR.
Differential ring number 13,
initiate self-destruct sequence.
Beginning imaginary output
through the Limitless
Engine--Perpetual Gear.
Materializing now.
Final maneuver:
Steel Weight!
[GENNAI]
You will know despair.
You will feel how heavy a
crime it was to twist the world.
Y...
[NAOTO] Marie, I'm
finishing up the tourbillon
and hooking it up
to the bypass now.
[MARIE] I can handle
number 15,000 by myself.
Okay, then I'll wrap
up number 19,000.
Hya!
[HOUKO]
Incredible!
It's like no repair
work I've ever seen.
That's because it
isn't repair work.
They're giving birth
to brand new gears!
[NAOTO] I swear,
I'm going to turn up the heat
and roast that thing.
Please, AnchoR, give me time!
[ANCHOR] I am AnchoR,
the one who annihilates.
The one who devastates.
The one who destroys.
So that is exactly
what I'm going to do!
[ANCHOR]
Full firepower.
Here we go!
[grunts]
Break already!
I'm passing you the
bearing for number 20,326!
Okay. Good.
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
I'm so gonna die.
[HALTER] If you can still talk,
things can't be that bad.
We've got less than
three minutes to go!
[NAOTO]
I know. Just keep moving!
[roars]
[NAOTO] That monstrosity has
1,033 clockwork generators.
Right now they are all
working at full capacity
to charge its cannons.
[ANCHOR]
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to break them all.
Come on, body, hold out for me.
Just a little longer.
[roars]
Get up.
Just get back up.
[HALTER]
This doesn't look good.
They're becoming more
and more indiscriminate.
Yeah, they're not
holding back anymore.
They'll blow us up
along with the Pillar.
[VERMOUTH]
Let's get outta here!
--[MARIE gasps]
--[NAOTO] Huh?!
Oh, no!
All that hard work!
[HALTER]
Damn it.
We're only making things
worse for the princess.
[VERMOUTH]
Is there any hope left?
We were already down
to the last shred.
[HALTER]
Yeah, well.
It may just be a shred,
but it's a strong one.
With the two of
them working together,
who knows what's possible?
[HOUKO]
Can they recover?
How much of a setback was this?
It's more than a
setback, I'm afraid.
The damage
they did was critical.
But, regardless...
It doesn't look like those two
have any intention of giving up.
This is no good.
We'll need a new bypass.
Already on it!
[GENNAI]
Too little too late.
I've defeated you.
What do you hope
to gain from this?
[GENNAI] Have you
learned your lesson yet, Y?
You pretended
to repair the world,
but really you
were deforming it.
Do you understand yet
how it feels to be powerless?
To be unable to resist
while the world crumbles?
Can you taste the despair?
This is how humanity has
suffered because of you.
How the hell can
you be so arrogant?
Nobody gave you the right
to speak for all of humanity!
[NAOTO]
Huh?!
How can you be
so arrogant, old man?
You don't have the right
to speak for all of humanity.
You may have given up, but
whatever happens, we never will!
[gasps]
I see now.
Y was actually
two different people.
You can praise humanity all you
want, but I won't accept it.
You have no right
to speak for us.
You are the monster
who broke the world.
So close.
C'mon!
[GENNAI]
What is going on?
The charge has decreased?
But how?
One of Y's dolls must
have come out to play.
[ANCHOR screams]
[ANCHOR grunts]
[ANCHOR]
It hurts!
It hurts. It hurts.
It hurts. So much.
But I can't stop.
[grunts]
It's no use.
I-I can't destroy it.
It's what I was made for,
but I failed.
I failed them.
[ANCHOR screams]
[ANCHOR groans]
[screams]
Time's up, but it didn't fire.
I don't think Naoto's prediction
about the time was wrong.
Something must have
happened to stop it.
This must mean
AnchoR's begun her attack.
Don't say it.
Let's just keep working.
[ANCHOR roars]
[ANCHOR screams]
No, I'm not finished yet.
I still have to
destroy all this.
[ANCHOR]
Father, Mother.
I don't want to let you down.
[ANCHOR grunts]
[GENNAI] It looks like Y's dolls
aren't strong enough
to stand against a railgun.
The charge is delayed,
but the main cannon
will fire soon enough.
Your efforts were in vain.
Nothing's going to stop me now.
Your master lost.
Humans won.
[ANCHOR]
I failed.
I couldn't destroy it.
[ANCHOR]
I am the one who annihilates.
All I know is destruction.
But it wasn't enough.
[ANCHOR]
Father.
Mother.
I couldn't do it.
[NAOTO]
Here.
For you.
Thanks so much.
I love it!
And, um, well,
I want you to have it.
[MARIE] Hey, you know, if you're
not busy, you could help me.
[ANCHOR]
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
What the?
[ANCHOR gasps]
Big sis?
[RYUZU]
It is the duty of a servant
to faithfully follow
her master's orders.
Just as important,
it is an older sister's duty to
take care of her younger sister.
Damn you! Ah!
[GENNAI]
You can kill me now,
but it's not going
to make a difference.
Everything's in place.
The cannon will
fire in a moment.
[laughs]
[GENNAI]
What?
Why isn't it firing?
[RYUZU]
That's easy to explain.
[RYUZU] AnchoR attacked
your giant weapon
and bought my master enough time
to put his extraordinary
abilities to work.
That's all it took.
To be completely honest,
he may have had a tiny amount
of help from someone else.
Hya!
Unbelievable!
They've done the impossible!
The holy tree has
been completely reborn.
[HOUKO] You made it in
time to stop the cannon.
We did.
But we took longer
than the 70 minutes
we told AnchoR we'd need.
It's okay!
RyuZU will bring her back.
I don't doubt that for a second.
Alrighty, ladies,
gentlemen, boys, girls, cyborgs,
and whoever else
we've got, look lively!
No time to rest.
Reinforcements are
coming up from below.
[HALTER]
We need find a way out,
or we're gonna be
in serious trouble.
Well, the way out
is right in front of you.
[multiple gasps]
You are joking
about that, aren't you?
Jumping down from here would
be nothing short of suicide.
I see what you're getting at!
We just need to use the weather
control to create an updraft,
and we should be
good to go, right?
You're getting the hang
of this intuition thing! Hya!
I'm leaving you in
charge of the controls.
Wow.
That boy is crazy.
And I like 'em crazy.
Let's go!
Ahh!
[HALTER] Do you think the
updraft'll be strong enough
to support this new body?
[MARIE] Are you doubting
my abilities, Halter?
[HALTER] Sorry, Princess,
don't know what I was thinking.
[HOUKO]
You're going, too?
Yes. I'll leave
the rest of it to you.
Right, I know what to do.
By the time I'm done,
the world will believe
you're the greatest criminal
masterminds in history.
[HOUKO]
Goodbye. And thank you.
[GENNAI] I guess he won
in the end after all.
[RYUZU] Now you're
just being ridiculous.
To say that
Master Naoto won implies
there was some sort
of contest to begin with.
And between your posturing and
his skills, there could be none.
Surely even your
old eyes can see that.
[GENNAI grunts]
Your existence betrays humanity.
You and your kind
may look like people,
but you are nothing
more than hollow dolls.
Suffering defeat over
and over again in a world
that's cruel and ugly.
Fighting for just
a taste of victory.
That's what it means
to be human.
[laughs]
Just wanna check: We're
not plummeting hundreds
of meters to our
deaths here, are we?
Have a little faith.
The updraft will kick in soon.
3, 2, 1, 0!
Yahoo!
Oh my god, poor AnchoR.
Daddy's here!
She'll be all right.
The damage is extensive, but
thankfully none of it is fatal.
Marie and I can repair her.
I'm sure of it.
Thank god for that.
I'm so sorry.
[gasps]
I tried to,
but I couldn't destroy.
I failed you.
Even though it's
all I'm good for.
I left, Father.
I disobeyed.
And I still failed.
Don't say that.
I don't know what to do.
Please help. Please help me.
I feel so confused.
What should I do?
I need an order.
Please, Father.
[whimpers]
Okay, I'll give you an order.
[MARIE]
Naoto?
[NAOTO]
Hold your head high and say,
"I did my best, and
I deserve praise for that."
[ANCHOR]
Hmm?
I did my best?
Do you really believe that?
Yeah!
Of course I believe it.
There is nobody out there
who works harder than you do.
And if I want to be praised,
then that's okay?
Really?
Absolute--
Uh... Listen to me.
We're here because of you.
Thanks to you,
we made it in time!
[ANCHOR]
Mother.
Thank you.
You did so well.
I'm very proud of you.
[sobs]
[KARASAWA]
Hi, Meister Marie.
I brought what you asked for.
Sorry for the wait.
Better late than never,
though, right?
[MARIE] I'm always
asking so much of you.
But no matter what it is,
you come through for me.
Thanks so much.
[KARASAWA chuckles]
Nah, you know I'm always honored
to help any way I can.
You look so much smaller now,
after that other body.
[HALTER] I guess it'll take
a little getting used to.
[KARASAWA]
You've got a head start,
but your pursuers
are closing in.
The weather's not ideal.
But unfortunately, you can't
afford to rest for long.
Actually, this
weather is perfect
for ditching people
who're after us.
Okay, everybody.
Let's get out of here.
[NEWSCASTER] The multiple grid
sustained significant damage,
but repairs are well underway
and should be
completed before long.
The Akihabara Grid was
by far the most affected.
However, an inexplicable
and dramatic increase
in temperature
demagnetized the grid,
saving it from complete ruin.
[MARIE]
Hmm? AnchoR?
So... what do you think, Mother?
[MARIE laughs]
Ah! Your repairs
are finally finished!
[ANCHOR]
Yes.
Unfortunately, it was more
first aid than a full repair.
Don't worry, AnchoR.
Once I get his brain
to spill your blueprint,
I'll fix you to perfection,
and you'll be in better
shape than ever!
Oh, like hell!
I will be the one
doing her repairs.
No way!
Yeah!
I can't leave
it to you and RyuZU.
You'll just create
another pervert like you.
Excuse me?
Yes, that was wholly
uncalled for, Miss Marie.
That's what I'm saying!
You tell her, RyuZU!
However, I don't like the
idea of Master Naoto cheating
on me with my little sister.
So perhaps having
Miss Marie take care of her
would be preferable.
It hurts me you would even
suggest something like that!
Okay, AnchoR,
which of us do you prefer,
me or the walking landmine?
That should be easy to answer.
You like me more than mega
perv over there, don't you?
Oh, um. Well, actually...
What I really like best
is when the two of you
are working together.
That makes me happy!
[NAOTO, MARIE]
Huh?
[HALTER] Pretty sure that asking
a kid if they like mom or dad
more is a textbook
example of bad parenting.
[NAOTO, MARIE]
Well, nobody asked you!
Hey, could you all stop
shouting for a second?
Sorry to interrupt
your little party,
but I've got some news,
and I don't think it can wait.
Don't worry,
I'm way ahead of you.
From the sound of it, there's
a decent-sized fleet of ships
nearby, and they're
headed right for us.
[MARIE]
Seriously?
If you knew that,
why didn't you say something?
[NAOTO]
Because I have a good idea.
[MARIE]
Which means it's a bad idea.
Let's take over a battleship and
blow up the rest of the fleet.
You are seriously
the biggest idiot ever.
There's something
I've been thinking about.
The Gears of Fate.
Do you believe in them,
or are we all on our own?
Sadly, I do not have
the ability to assess
such a complex
philosophical notion.
However, in this world
made entirely of gears,
everything is as
it is meant to be.
As an automaton of
the Clockwork Planet,
that is what I believe.
[VERMOUTH]
Woooo!
Great idea, Naoto!
All that relaxing was
starting to get boring.
[MARIE] I'll go along with the
plan, but if we're doing this,
we can't afford to
make a single mistake.
We've already got
our work cut out for us
overhauling the planet,
so let's not waste any time.
Don't worry, as long
as we're all together,
there's nothing we can't do.