[MINISTER OF DEFENSE]
Our primary objective
is the rescue of Her Highness
Houko Hoshinomiya.
All units, advance!
[MARIE] Connected the
bypass to block C-21!
Readjusting the rotational
speed of the AOS 5-0-2-2 gear
to increase it by
one fifteenth of a second.
Acknowledged.
Gear readjustment successful.
[MARIE] Please connect the HT
shaft to the deceleration gear.
[ENGINEER A]
On it!
[VERMOUTH]
Look at all you busy bees!
You deserve a reward
for working so hard.
Here's your prize!
[HALTER]
Are you done fooling around?
We've got work to do, kid.
Come on.
[KONRAD]
What's this?
You're heading back out?
[HALTER] The military's
starting to get a little antsy.
Thought we'd go out and
keep them busy for a bit.
Good idea, thanks.
Buy as much time as you can.
[HALTER]
Roger.
[HOUKO]
A moment, Naoto Miura?
Um, what do you need?
I'd like to borrow
you for a little chat.
[HOUKO]
I admit I am curious about
your single-minded determination
to destroy the giant weapon.
Is it retaliation for having
hurt the automata dear to you?
Well, yeah.
They enslaved AnchoR and forced
her to do something awful.
If that wasn't enough,
they also hurt RyuZU.
It's only natural
I'd want them to pay for that.
I mean, who wouldn't?
[HOUKO]
Your motivation makes sense,
but I don't understand why
you would assume the risk
of taking over
the Pillar of Heaven.
Would it not have been quicker
to purge the Akihabra Grid?
[gasps]
I believe that would have given
you the revenge you are seeking,
and it would have been
more efficient and less risky.
I could never do that.
I want to strike back
against whoever's controlling
that weapon,
not innocent people.
I understand.
Thank you for clearing that up.
I see now I was correct
in assuming you were
a dangerous person.
[NAOTO]
What?
How'd you get that
from what I said?
Well, fair-minded people
can be difficult to predict.
[gasps]
Something wrong?
Frankly, I find your
response astonishing.
I never expected to find
another human being
who wasn't completely blind.
Aside from
Master Naoto, that is.
I'm relieved to know
I meet with your approval.
[GENNAI]
Let me ask you something, boy.
Have you never felt like
giving up on this world?
Haven't you ever thought
that maybe it's
not worth fighting for?
When all it does is
crush us, stealing hope?
How can you be
so arrogant, old man?
You don't have the right
to speak for all of humanity.
You may have given up, but
whatever happens, we never will!
[GENNAI]
Someone came along
and stole everything
we humans thought we knew.
In place of Earth,
he created this grotesque
"Clockwork Planet."
If he had been a god or a demon,
I could have accepted it.
There would be no
reason for our species to fight
a superior being we would
have no hope of defeating.
I could resign
myself to that fact
and live with what he had done.
But then I met that boy.
Gentlemen!
[OPERATORS]
Huh?
I thank you for your dedication.
What is this?
Your Excellency,
what's going on?
Please, we've been loya--
[screaming]
[GENNAI] I shall challenge
you one more time.
We shall see who wins, you
monster who pretends to be Y.
[VERMOUTH]
You shitheads!
Take that!
[VERMOUTH]
The damn things keep on coming.
I've got more stamina
than most people,
but I can't go on forever.
[HALTER] This might go better
if there was less talking
and more fighting.
Sorry old man, but I can't
squeeze out another drop.
I'm on empty. Ah!
[HALTER] Princess, you'd better
make something happen. Quickly!
They'll launch
the Tall Wand soon.
Thirty minutes left!
This is the home
stretch, people!
[ENGINEERS]
Roger!
[grunts]
[NAOTO]
Look at her.
If I could work instead of just
standing here, being useless.
[NAOTO gasps]
What is it, Master?
[NAOTO]
No.
This can't be happening.
We were supposed
to have more time!
[MARIE]
What's wrong?
We've almost completed the
bypass to take full control.
[NAOTO]
Marie! Quick!
No time to waste!
Gather all clouds
to the south of here!
[MARIE] Initiate weather
control on the exterior
of Floor Twenty, six o'clock!
It's no use.
We're not gonna make it!
Everybody!
Run!
Shit!
What the hell?
Now the sky's falling, too?
[screaming]
They actually shot it.
Shot what?
[NAOTO]
Can't you tell?
The Yatsukahagi's main cannon.
That was the same type of
pulse that took out Akihabara.
[MARIE]
No way!
We were supposed to
have another fifteen hours.
I thought they were trying
to stage a coup d'etat!
If they destroy
the Pillar of Heaven,
they'll go down with Tokyo
and the rest of us.
[NAOTO]
I don't understand.
We were so sure they were trying
to take over the
country, but now--
[GENNAI] Shifting the clouds
was indeed the appropriate
countermeasure against
a microwave maser cannon.
And you gave that order
without even knowing the
underlying principles behind it.
Right, Naoto Miura?
I know that voice.
It's gotta be him.
[GENNAI]
I haven't introduced myself yet.
My name is Gennai Hirayama.
[MARIE]
You know this guy?
Who is he?
He's the man we met when we
fell into the Deep Underground.
An ill-mannered recluse who
has given up on the world.
[GENNAI] Despite the conclusions
you seem to have drawn,
I was never interested
in a coup d'état.
[MARIE gasps]
What the hell is he after?
[MARIE]
The bypass was disconnected?
With that one shot?
We have to get back to work!
[KONRAD]
Marie.
We've received an
urgent transmission.
Huh?
[KONRAD] They moved the
launch of the Tall Wand forward.
We're out of time.
No way.
[MARIE gasps]
[GENNAI] If you thought
I would let this end easily,
you were mistaken, Y.
Did he say Y?
[GENNAI]
Do what you can to stop me.
You'll see how strong
we common men can be...
...you monster.
[MARIE]
Okay.
We should get back to work.
Let's rearrange those gears.
Yeah, that's what we'll do.
Are you coming?
[NAOTO]
Marie.
I'm sorry, but I don't think
I can help with that.
[NAOTO] What sound am
I supposed to be listening for?
I can't hear gears
that have disappeared.
[MARIE gasps]
[NAOTO]
They diverted all energy
to charging the
weapon's main canon.
That's why it was able
to fire again so quickly.
[MARIE] How long until it's
ready to take its next shot?
[NAOTO]
It fired more than once, so...
...72 minutes.
That doesn't give us much time.
Damn.
[HALTER]
Hey, Princess! Are you safe?
What's going on over there?
[VERMOUTH]
And how long are we supposed
to keep holding down the fort?
These guys are rough.
They're giving us
a real pounding.
[whimpers]
[KONRAD] Meister Marie, do you
remember what happened in Kyoto?
Everybody else had given up,
but you refused to.
Do you know why that was?
Because I found a miracle.
The same one that I've
been relying on ever since.
A miracle called Naoto Miura.
[KONRAD]
Hmm...
Naoto.
Can't you destroy that weapon
using AnchoR and RyuZU?
[NAOTO] You're asking
me to make them fight,
to endanger them again after
everything they've been through?
I can't!
It's okay.
Order me.
Please.
I can't do that.
I won't, ever!
We can't stand by
and do nothing.
Yes, I know.
Just give me time.
There's got to be another way.
I'll figure something out.
I'm sorry, Father.
Really, but... I have to go!
AnchoR!
[NAOTO]
AnchoR! AnchoR!
You have to bring
her back, RyuZU!
Hurry!
I'm sorry, but once she is fully
powered, even I cannot stop her.
Then find her.
Ask her if she will please
just give me 70 minutes.
I'll figure something out.
I just need time!
I will deliver your message.
Miss Marie.
There is something
I would like to tell you.
You should know
that you're right.
[MARIE]
Huh?
[RYUZU]
Like Master Naoto.
And at the same time,
you're wrong.
Right and wrong?
I don't understand.
Think about it.
It may take every cell
of your stunted brain,
but I believe you can manage.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
All right, let's do this!
[MARIE]
Do what?
There isn't anything we can do.
Don't say that!
We can come up with something!
You said it yourself: you can't
even hear the gears anymore.
But you think we'll
"figure something out"?
That's not how things work.
There are no miracles!
Yeah. You're right.
I have no freaking
clue what to do.
But I'm not alone here.
I have you,
and you're different!
Remember?
What happened to the
woman who always says
that she doesn't believe
in the word "impossible"?
As much as it disgusts
me to say it to your face,
you're a genius, Marie!
All this time,
it's been your talent
that's made my random power
into something useful!
You have knowledge
and skill; I don't.
So why are you the one
who's so ready to give up?
Use your damn talent, Marie!
Or if you won't,
then give it to me!
Please!
[MARIE]
Talent?
Did you say talent?
[MARIE] Why are you
looking at me like that?
You're envious.
You envy my talent.
[NAOTO screams]
Stop it you idiot!
You're going to break something!
Did you hear that pop?
[MARIE] Everything that comes
out of your mouth is crap!
You are such a jerk!
[NAOTO groans]
[MARIE]
There. Much better.
I'm done agonizing.
It's over. Finished.
Thanks for playing.
It's ridiculous when
you think about it,
that someone like
me would have to rely
on an idiotic pervert like him.
Damn! I'm so angry, I don't
even know where to start!
I'm pissed at myself
and everybody else.
That little shit should
be kneeling before me.
On your knees!
You've said enough.
Shut up!
[MARIE]
The fact of the matter is:
If I had Naoto's senses
or if he had my skill,
we could easily
construct a new bypass.
We just need
to combine our talents.
It won't work.
How can we rebuild the bypass
when all the parts and
gears have disappeared?
We'll find a way.
Naoto and I can do it.
[RYUZU]
Wait a second.
[gasps]
Don't stop me.
Please don't.
I can do nothing but destroy.
It's who I am.
[RYUZU] There's much more
to you than you realize.
You don't understand why you
were given the name AnchoR.
[ANCHOR]
Why?
Master Naoto believes in you,
but you should believe
in him and Miss Marie.
Father and Mother.
I do believe.
[MARIE]
It took me awhile to understand,
but your senses
were right all along,
which means that what's wrong
is the original clocksmith
technology itself.
You do get what you're
saying here, don't you?
[MARIE]
Yes.
A thousand years of research by
who knows how many clocksmiths.
And all of it for nothing.
We got it wrong.
What?
Unbelievable.
But not you.
You know the answer, Naoto.
What do you mean?
[MARIE]
This isn't about academics.
I don't have to
give you a lesson.
Textbooks and
blueprints won't help.
All you can rely
on is your mind.
Everything you need
to know is already there.
In your head.
Say what now?
Naoto.
You hear the orchestra before
the performance has even begun.
But, then it begins
and you're disappointed
with the way the song sounds.
[MARIE] So, you listen to
each instrument one by one
until you locate the problem.
You tune them and let them play
again until they're in harmony
and the song sounds like
you know it's supposed to.
[MARIE]
What you're seeing is music,
the transition from
one piece to the next.
The flow of the symphony.
You don't have to think about
repairs and construction.
You're a conductor.
Your job is to
guide the orchestra.
[NAOTO]
Huh...?
Uh! Okay, enough of that.
Now it's your turn to teach me.
Well, um, actually, I think
you already understand.
Huh?
[NAOTO] I think you're capable
of more than you know.
I realized it when you
connected Halter's brain.
What are you talking about?
I had the blueprint memorized,
so I was just
working off of that.
Oh, really?
You could do a modification
you'd never done before
in that short a time
without thinking?
[MARIE]
Uh...
[NAOTO] You can see
it as you work, Marie.
The result.
The outcome you're striving for.
[MARIE]
No! That's not...
I see. That's it.
You and I, we're opposites.
Opposites, how?
[MARIE] Naoto constructs
the situation from the answer,
and I arrive at the answer
by looking at the situation.
I want you to tell me
everything you heard
when you listened
to the Pillar of Heaven.
I'm going to decode it
all and memorize it.
And then I'll make it my own.
All right, but I might have
a hard time putting it
into words properly.
Listen carefully to
what I am about to tell you,
and then let it go.
[MARIE]
Huh?
[NAOTO]
You don't have to memorize it,
but don't forget it.
Listen to everything
and nothing.
Think without thinking.
Everything is right and wrong.
Contradictions make sense.
Right is left.
Nothing exists,
and everything exists.
[MARIE]
Huh?
[NAOTO]
You don't know, but you know.
You know, but you don't know.
You don't remember,
but you remember.
Let's go.
[MARIE]
Wait!
[NAOTO]
You don't have to memorize it,
but don't forget it.
[MARIE screams]
[NAOTO]
You don't have to memorize it,
but don't forget it.
Listen to everything
and nothing.
You don't know, but you know.
One last thing.
If something built using
clockworks can't function
when even a single
gear is missing...
[MARIE, NAOTO]
...the question is:
How is the planet still working?
[NAOTO]
Marie. Marie?
All right, you're awake.
You get it?
[MARIE]
Huh? Get what?
[NAOTO]
Okay. Good.
You memorized it.
[gasps]
[MARIE]
Hold on!
I have no clue what you told me.
I think you do.
Remember?
What you said?
That was quick.
What, do you have the blueprint
for every automaton
model memorized?
Yup, know 'em all by heart.
It comes in handy.
Memorizing god-only-knows
how many blueprints?
Something like
that's impossible.
Unless you are you.
[MARIE]
Uh...
[NAOTO]
It's fine.
Let yourself believe.
Are you ready to eat my dust?
Do you know who you're
talking to, newbie?
Let's do this!
[NAOTO]
Here, everything is right.
And everything is wrong.
Contradictions make sense.
Right is left.
Everything exists.
Nothing exists.
[MARIE]
Uh... Mm!
[MARIE laughs]
All right!
In case there wasn't already
enough proof of my brilliance.
Am I seeing what
I think I'm seeing?
New gears are being born!
There, y'see?
Did you really think there
was something I could do
that you couldn't figure out?
[MARIE]
Ha! Of course not!
I am a genius who makes
the impossible possible.
I'm also the woman
who's going to crush you,
so let's keep going.
[NAOTO] Marie! Listen to the
carving sound of the coaxial.
The locking corner is worn down,
and it's not going deep enough.
[MARIE]
Not a problem.
I'll just push in the
H-I-M-0-3-3-1, and... there!
That did it.
Try to focus!
Back at ya.
No more giving up, Marie!
Those two are amazing.
Yes, I've never
seen anything like it.
I wonder how far
they intend to go.
[ANCHOR]
It's time now.
Here. I don't want
this to get lost or dirty.
You take it.
Keep it safe.
I'll look after it
until you return.
[ANCHOR]
My music box.
Just like the one
I gave to Mother.
[ANCHOR]
All right.
I'm going now.
[RYUZU]
AnchoR, whatever happens,
promise me you'll come back.
Classification:
Initial-Y Series, Unit Four,
One Who Annihilates, AnchoR.
Differential ring number 13,
initiate self-destruct sequence.
Beginning imaginary output
through the Limitless
Engine--Perpetual Gear.
Materializing now.
Beginning final maneuver:
Steel Weight!
[ANCHOR] Instead of
following Father's orders,
I attack the giant
weapon on my own.
Desperate to save
both Akihabara and me,
Father and Mother
work frantically
to repair the Pillar of Heaven.
The two geniuses push
themselves to the limit
as enemies close in all around.
When the gears
of fate turn again,
will they bring hope or despair?
Next time, "Steel Weight."
It's no use.
I can't destroy it.
It's what I was made for...
...but I... I failed.