[RYUZU] Everything comes
to an end someday.
Perhaps it shouldn't
have been a surprise
when the world did, too.
[RYUZU]
It was sudden.
One day, the Earth simply
reached the end of its life.
At first, it seemed as if
humanity had no choice
but to die along with the world.
But then a clocksmith appeared.
He called himself "Y."
He said that he could rebuild
the destroyed Earth with gears,
the same way he would
repair a failing clock.
He did. And a thousand
years passed.
[NAOTO]
They'll be here in nine seconds.
We're looking at two
silent helicopters
and one transport helicopter
loaded with 12 combat automata.
3, 2, 1, 0!
[NAOTO]
Heh.
Take this!
[HALTER]
Heh.
[NAOTO] Enemy reinforcements
from the southeast.
Twelve seconds.
Clean these up before
they get here. Got it?
I don't take orders from you,
so let's drop the
bossy tone, okay?
I hate to break it
to you, Princess,
but this was your idea.
I didn't ask for
your opinion, did I?
Now shut up and fight
like a good bodyguard.
Well, crap.
[MARIE] Gotta say,
this doesn't look promising.
I think we're a bit
outnumbered here.
Agreed, so what now?
What do we do now?
We end this. Right, RyuZU?
[RYUZU]
That's right, Master Naoto.
If sending these crude machines
is someone's idea of a joke,
it is not an amusing one.
In fact, I find it
downright insulting.
Don't worry, Master,
I'll deal with these
worthless contraptions.
And there will be nothing
but scrap metal left.
[RYUZU]
Sorry if I'm late.
Were you waiting long?
[laughs]
That was high-class
butt-kicking. Oh, yeah!
And that was a very low-class
assessment of my performance,
indicative of your
inferior intelligence.
[RYUZU]
Y named the world he built
of a seemingly infinite
number of gears.
It was no longer Earth.
He called it the
Clockwork Planet.
[NAOTO humming]
[NAOTO]
I'm back!
I hope you weren't too
lonely without me!
Oh, you were, weren't you?
My lovely ones,
patiently waiting for me
even though I'm a complete
and utter failure.
I know I've never managed
to repair a single clock,
but my love for you is true!
I swear! Someday I will finally
be able to prove it to you!
I'll become the clocksmith
you deserve. Really!
[yelps]
[NAOTO] I'm sorry. You
have the right to choose.
I won't force you
to wait for me.
[sighs]
I confess, I have another love.
The pinnacle of clockwork
achievement: Automata!
I really wanna make
one of my own someday.
Ugh.
Come on, fate, help me out!
Give me something!
Materials, money, maybe
just a scrap of talent?
Huh?
What is that? Rain?
Go! Go, go, go, go, go.
[NAOTO screams]
[NAOTO]
My sweet lovers, all destroyed!
Who did this to
you, lovely ones?
They'll pay! I will
have revenge!
Huh?
[clock tolling]
Beautiful.
[MARIE]
You dropped a YD-01 container?
[SUBORDINATE A]
Yes. I can't apologize enough!
It belongs to the Breguet family
and contains a national
treasure-class automaton.
[SUBORDINATE A]
I promise the person responsible
will be punished accordingly.
[growls]
Halter! Send out our own
recovery team immediately.
We can't trust those incompetent
shitheads to do anything!
[HALTER]
Roger that.
But if I can make a
suggestion, Meister Marie,
you may consider
behaving more like a lady.
Huh?
[HALTER] Since this is a
request from the Kyoto Grid
to the Meister Guild, we should
put our best foot forward.
Don't you think?
You know what they're really
saying, though, don't you?
"This is too much of a hassle
for us to deal with,
so you take care of it."
Still, I suppose we can't
exactly ignore problems
with the Core Tower.
Let's get there quickly.
As you wish, Princess.
It won't be long.
Idiots.
[MARIE]
Well, at least this looks like
it'll be an
interesting job, huh?
[NAOTO] This is everything
I love about clockworks
in human form.
Incredible. I have to
know what she sounds like.
'Kay.
Oh, wow. Amazing.
The sound of the gears
is more perfect
than anything I've ever heard.
No. Hold on.
[NAOTO] It's faint, but there's
an unpleasant sound mixed in.
The gear at the
very center is stuck.
It isn't turning like it should.
That must be why
she isn't booting up.
The power spring
seems to be functional.
[NAOTA yelps]
No way.
At this rate, it won't be long
before this whole
place collapses.
[NAOTO]
Huh?
[yelping]
[NAOTO]
Look at that!
So pretty.
[NAOTO] You've never even
fixed a simple clock.
What the hell do you
think you're doing? Idiot.
[MARIE]
Meister Konrad!
[KONRAD]
Good to see you, Meister Marie.
It's been too long.
We're very glad to have you
as our service chief here.
Thanks for coming on board.
[MARIE, HALTER]
Hm?
[HALTER]
Friends from the military.
[MARIE] Didn't take 'em long to
tell us to stay off their turf.
Afternoon, Dr. Breguet.
We were sent with orders
to provide any assistance
that you might require.
And we require none.
Thanks so much, though.
We're more familiar with
the Kyoto Core Tower than you.
It would be foolish to refuse
our help because of--
We were called in because
you can't handle this.
The last thing we
need is help from you.
Have a good day.
Don't let the door hit
you on the way out.
[NAOTO] I must be
outta my freakin' mind.
If my hand slips and I put
even the slightest scratch
on the main cylinder, that's it.
The mechanism will
be irreparable.
But still, that sound
it's makin' is wrong.
I have to fix it.
Whoa.
[NAOTO] There it is. I just
have to reach that screw.
There. It's over.
Aw, yeah!
So tired.
That really took it all
out of me. I need a nap.
Huh?
[screams]
[NAOTO gasps]
I am a part of the
Initial-Y Series. Unit One.
I am called RyuZU.
Uh. I'm Naoto Miura.
[RYUZU]
Thank you for repairing me.
I am very grateful
for the assistance.
However, I am surprised
it took so long
to repair a simple malfunction.
It suggests
humanity's intelligence
leaves a great deal
to be desired.
I think a monkey could have
resolved the issue more quickly.
Yes, a monkey,
or even a smart dog.
I confess I had hoped the person
who is to become my master
would be superior to an animal.
[chuckles]
[chuckles nervously]
'Scuse me. I'm gonna
pass out now.
[RYUZU]
Huh?
Are you feeling any better?
You look quite pale.
[whimpering]
[NAOTO screaming]
[RYUZU] Master Naoto,
may I ask you a question?
[NAOTO]
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
[RYUZU] Tell me. Do you
have my design plan?
[NAOTO]
Uh. No, I don't.
I see.
Do you know how many gears
my body is comprised of?
Uh, four trillion, 207 billion,
600 million, 8,643, I think.
So you were able to determine
the issue and repair me,
using sound alone.
You could sense
what was going on
while I was making the repairs?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, awkward!
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't mean to go
opening you up,
but that stuck gear was
ruining the sound, ya know?
Master Naoto...
you are a pervert.
Sorry, guess I kind of am.
Okay.
With your permission,
I would like to register
you as my master.
I will serve at your side and
help in any way you require.
Really?
After observing your work,
I have come to the conclusion
that you are the most talented
clocksmith on the planet.
Uh, no, sorry. I think
you've got the wrong idea.
What's wrong?
You aren't pleased at the
thought of becoming my master.
Is it because I am powerful,
skilled, and highly capable?
Does my perfection threaten
whatever scraps of pride
you've clung to in
your sad little life?
Well, no, I wouldn't say that.
I understand. You don't want me.
You don't have any
use for an automaton.
[NAOTO] Okay, calm down
and get a grip, Naoto.
Who is this girl, anyway?
She's both high-spec
and crazy beautiful.
Is she a prototype for a big
corporation? Or the military?
Part of some international plot?
Will they kill me to shut me up?
Will anyone ever
find the pieces?
Careful! You have
to weigh the risks.
[NAOTO]
Please, who am I kidding here?
I can't say no! I'd have
to be an idiot to do that!
And maybe I'm an idiot
anyway, but if you want me,
I'll be the best
damn master I can be!
All right.
Then give me your right hand.
[NAOTO]
Uh...
[gasps]
Initial-Y Series Unit One.
I am "The One Who
Follows." RyuZU.
I swear to remain by
Naoto Miura's side
and help him in
any way he wishes.
I pledge loyalty and
servitude to him alone.
[MARIE]
It's weirdly quiet.
[KONRAD]
Is that a problem?
[MARIE] It seems strange
to me that those officers
haven't come back.
[HALTER] You think
they're up to something?
[KONRAD]
I have somebody who can help us
find the answer
to that question.
Karasawa.
What can I do for you?
We believe the military
may be hiding something.
Think you can look into it?
[KARASAWA] I do have some
experience with shady business.
My last job saw to that.
You don't mind helping, do you?
No one can refuse
you, Meister Marie.
I'll see what I can find out.
[NAOTO]
Whew. You saved me again!
If you hadn't gone
in to get my things,
I'd be broke as
well as homeless.
I'm sorry, though.
It was a dangerous
thing to ask you to do.
You may be frail and weak,
but I am strong and capable.
I fail to see how entering
a building put me in danger,
no matter ho derelict.
Were you intentionally designed
to be so sharp-tongued,
or was that some kind of glitch?
Sharp-tongued?
What do you mean?
[NAOTO]
Uh, forget I said anything.
Now then, we need
a place to stay.
I believe that building
will provide
suitable accommodations for us.
[NAOTO screams]
[NAOTO]
But-- But--!
That's a love hotel!
[RYUZU]
It is also reasonably priced,
close to our current location,
and provides the best
amenities in the area.
We should keep looking.
Master, remember that
no matter how unusual
or indecent your primitive
desires might be,
it is my job as your servant
to see that all of
your needs are met.
What kind of sicko
do you take me for?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Let's just go someplace else.
A manga café'll
work for tonight.
[PUNK A] Hey, babe.
You're really freakin' hot.
Yes, I am aware of that.
[PUNKS laugh]
[PUNK A] I like you!
You wanna go have some fun?
Come on. There's a
hotel right there.
[NAOTO]
Huh?
[PUNK A] Brat. What are
you doing? Piss off.
No! You jerks don't deserve
somebody like her!
Just leave her alone.
[gasps]
What did you say to me, punk?
Got a death wish?
Hit 'im already.
RyuZU, go!
Master Naoto, that's the first
time you've called me RyuZU.
You seem to think
I need defending.
Allow me to correct that
misguided assumption.
That hurt.
[RYUZU] It's possible I
took things a bit too far,
but you shouldn't die of your
injuries and now you know
I don't tolerate fools
who insult my master.
[NAOTO]
Phew! Ha.
Oh, I see, rather than the
big bed at a love hotel.
you prefer the close proximity
necessitated by a narrow bench.
No, that's not it!
This was the only
place that was open.
[NAOTO sighs]
Jeez, I could sleep for a week.
You should totally
get some rest, too.
Thanks for everything.
[RYUZU]
Are you going to ignore it?
Say wha--?
[RYUZU] The perfect opportunity
to sleep on my lap.
[gasps] Wait, I can
do that? Really?
Yes, you did it earlier
today, didn't you?
Was it unsatisfying?
Nope, not even a little! Ha!
Night!
Master Naoto.
Yeah?
You know I'm an automaton,
a manufactured clockwork doll.
Sure. I know that.
Okay, then tell me something:
Why are you treating me
like I'm a human girl?
A strange master.
So young and naïve.
I wonder what he
thinks about me.
[clicking]
[gasps]
Too loud. Need to sleep.
[HALTER] Problem, Princess?
You have a scary dream?
Don't treat me like a child!
Get the team chiefs
together, now!
[HALTER]
Okay.
Uh, quick suggestion?
[MARIE]
Yeah, what?
[HALTER] You might wanna
cover your girly parts first.
[screams]
I hate you!
[MARIE] We just experienced
a gravity irregularity.
[KONRAD] Yes, though I'm
amazed you could tell.
It didn't shake so
much that your body
should've been able to sense it.
The consequences will be
serious if it continues.
It could cause the entire
Kyoto Grid to fall.
[ENGINEERS gasp]
[MARIE] That's right.
There's no time to waste.
We need to find the point
that's causing the problem now.
[door opens]
[KARASAWA] Unfortunately,
it seems the military
has a different idea.
[KONRAD]
What have you found out?
That they have their own plan.
One they'll put into effect
in the next few days.
[MARIE]
Wait, you don't mean...
[KONRAD] A forced purge
of the Kyoto Grid?
[MARIE, ENGINEERS gasp]
Impossible! There's not enough
time to evacuate everybody!
They're aware.
Doesn't seem to make
any difference, though.
Insane.
They truly mean to let Kyoto and
its 20 million residents fall?
[RYUZU]
Even the greatest genius,
possessing the greatest skills,
can only do so much.
No clock, however well-built,
can tick on infinitely.
Everything comes to an end
someday. People. Worlds.
Eventually, they must receive
new life. Restored.
Rebuilt. Just as Y once did.
[MARIE] I'm working with
Konrad and the other Meisters
to repair the Core Tower.
Unfortunately, the military
wants to purge the Kyoto Grid,
so they're not
making it easy on us.
We're running into one
problem after another,
and the purge inches closer
with every minute that passes.
It doesn't help that I can feel
the weight of 20 million lives
resting on my shoulders.
Next time: "Purge."
I am Marie Breguet,
a woman who doesn't believe
in the word "impossible."