May I ask where you're
going, Dr. Breguet?
[MARIE] To inspect the
situation in the lower floors.
Do you really expect me to
report my every move to you?
This is the Core Tower,
under the jurisdiction
of the military,
so I will be accompanying you.
We'd love company.
[MILITARY OFFICER A]
Try to remember your place.
The military has the
final say on anything
that happens in the Tower.
You may have the
title of "Meister,"
but we all know that you people
are just glorified repairmen.
[MARIE]
You've got one thing right.
We of the Meister
Guild are repairmen.
We fix things.
Which is exactly what we're
going to do with this Tower.
And nothing will
stand in our way.
Nothing and no one.
[MARIE]
Now I've got a question for you.
Answer quickly.
When will the purge happen?
Twenty hours from now.
Tomorrow at 02:42.
[BOTH gasp]
Why do it so soon?
Because we can't
afford to lose face.
There's an anomaly we can't fix,
so the purge is our only option.
If the public learns that we
couldn't handle the repairs,
our authority will
be questioned.
You people are monsters!
Twenty million
lives are at stake
and all you care
about is saving face?
Tell us where the anomaly is.
Fine, Floor 24, in the
pressure control block.
Sounds like we know
where our next stop is.
[MILITARY OFFICER A] You really
think you're going to fix it?
The purge is in 20 hours.
That'll never be long enough.
A lot can happen in 20 hours.
Let's do this.
We'll fix it if
we can, and if not,
then I guess I'll
die with this city.
What now?!
Why's it so loud?
Good morning, Master Naoto.
How are you feeling?
You don't appear to
have slept very well.
Was there something displeasing
or inadequate about my lap?
No, not at all!
Y-Y-Your lap was amazing,
pure perfection, I swear!
It's just that lately,
the ground beneath the Core
Tower has been really noisy.
I assume that is due to errors
in the city's mechanisms.
Well, it's 70,620
meters below ground.
[RYUZU] Interesting. That
would put it at Floor 24.
What? You know that?
Of course. Y designed
me and the planet.
I guess you could say
we have a lot in common.
[VOICE A] There's no limit
to what you can achieve
as part of the Meister Guild...
[NAOTO]
Ugh! The Meister Guild! I wish!
[RYUZU] You want to
join the Guild someday?
[NAOTO]
Yeah, of course!
Those guys get paid to spend
their days ogling clockworks
and playing with
the Core Towers.
I can't think of anything
I would rather do.
They're amazing!
I'm afraid I must disagree.
They had 206 years, and they
still couldn't repair me.
These are mankind's most
skilled clocksmiths?
I find that a rather
pathetic joke.
Well... Ha-ha...
Wait, 206 years?
I had no idea you'd
been around that long.
When were you built?
[RYUZU]
About a thousand years ago.
Seriously?
[HALTER] Think you'll be
able to get it going again?
[MARIE]
I need to secure a line first.
We have to inform
everybody about the purge.
Usin' the emergency frequency
for the Meister Guild.
[MARIE] The military is no
longer just a hindrance.
They are the enemy.
Yeah, that's for sure.
[MARIE]
All right.
Got it.
This'll reach the communication
officer outside the tower.
[LIMONS] Kyoto Grid
Communication Officer Limons.
[MARIE]
This is Marie Breguet.
Hi, Dr. Breguet.
It's been a while.
You're calling on the special
frequency, you all right?
Is everything okay?
[MARIE]
No, it isn't.
The military intends to purge
the Kyoto Grid in 20 hours.
[LIMONS]
That is serious.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I need to speak with
Service Chief Konrad
on Floor 3 immediately.
[LIMONS] Certainly. I'll have
you patched through right away.
Good-bye.
[KONRAD] Konrad here.
Are you all right, Meister?
[MARIE] Yes, but the
situation is critical.
We questioned an officer
and learned that the military
means to purge the
Kyoto Grid in 20 hours.
You sure? That's earlier than
we expected them to act.
We know where to go.
Please head to the
24th Floor immediately.
That's where the anomaly is.
I'll meet you as
soon as I'm able to.
[KONRAD]
I understand your urgency,
but we've got another problem.
I can't say for
sure what happened,
but Floor 3 has had its
power system severed
from the power spring
barrel on Floor 15.
I'm sorry, but there's simply
no way we can get to Floor 24
until we repair it.
The military doesn't
want us interfering.
They're actively
sabotaging us now.
Explains why the elevator
shut down on us. Damn.
[KONRAD] I promise we're
doing everything we can,
but the repairs will still
take about four hours.
[MARIE]
Given the situation,
wouldn't it be faster to
go directly to the barrel?
Good thinking. You're right.
[HALTER] I have to ask,
though I'm sure I'll regret it,
we're going down to the power
spring barrel, aren't we?
That's a 30,000-meter
descent, you know.
Well, there's no other option.
C'mon, where's your
sense of adventure?
[COMM. VOICE A] Commencing
purge from the outer edge
of the Kyoto Grid.
[HALTER] Special express
to the depths of hell.
Better hold on tight,
Princess. It's a long fall.
You've got a pretty girl
all wrapped around you,
I would think you'd be happier.
[HALTER]
Heh.
[KONRAD] Meister Marie is
on her way to the barrel.
We're going to assist her
as best we can here.
We've got a lot
to do. Stay sharp.
[ENGINEERS]
Yes, sir!
[NAOTO groans]
[NAOTO]
Everyone's staring,
wondering what a pretty
girl like you is doing
with a loser like me.
So this is the high school
you attend, Master?
Yep, this is it.
I hadn't thought
about it till now,
but what will you do
while I'm at school?
That's simple.
I'll do what's required
to perform my duties
as your servant.
[TEACHER A] Listen up, class, we
have a new student joining us.
Like the teacher said, I am
now a student at this school.
You may call me RyuZU Yourslave.
Is this really happening?
It is not a habit of
mine to spend time
with people of vastly
inferior intellect.
So there's no need to be
friendly to me, at all.
One more thing,
and this is very important,
so listen closely.
I'm a servant. I am
Master Naoto's property.
[chuckles]
[NAOTO screams]
What the heck are you saying?!
[MARIE] It's going to get
more narrow up ahead.
Think you can squeeze through?
I dunno. It'll be
a tight fit for me.
I'm not exactly a small guy.
We can't all be as flat as you.
[MARIE]
What?!
I'm still a growing
girl, damn it.
[HALTER] That sounds
like wishful thinking.
You know that wanting something
doesn't make it true, right?
[MARIE]
Die!
Ow!
We're almost there.
The barrel is through here.
Be sure to stay with me.
I'll be right behind
you. You ready?
As much as I'd like to,
we don't have time to
deal with these guys.
Then we'll take a shortcut.
You up for it, Halter?
Sure, let's go.
[MARIE
All right, we're here.
That's the barrel's connection
to the main shaft.
Ugh. I knew it.
They were waiting for us.
Come on. Let's go.
Right.
How much time do
you need, Princess?
Forty-one seconds please.
[HALTER]
Okay. You got it.
Tch.
[HALTER]
A VS-071-A minotaur.
The latest offering
from Vacheron.
You wanna test your
strength against me?
Well, come on then, let's dance.
Okay.
Another 1-20 to go.
[HALTER]
I'm done with you!
[MARIE] Damn, I only
had three more to go!
Come on, think, Marie!
You've gotta do something!
[KONRAD]
Nice work, you two.
I hope you don't mind if we
give you a hand with these.
We don't mind at all!
Thanks, Meister Konrad.
Just one more left.
We're done here.
[MARIE]
We've got 18 hours left.
Let's hurry and get
back to the others.
[RYUZU] Is everything
all right? You look tired.
Oh, yeah? I look tired, huh?
Well, considering I
just spent all day
with my classmates looking at me
like I'm the scum of the earth,
I guess that's not surprising.
They envy you because you
have something beautiful
they have no hope of possessing.
You have me now, and that
makes you their superior.
You shouldn't allow the stares
of lesser mortals trouble you.
Okay, if you say so.
[RYUZU] I'm surprised at
how little it's changed.
[NAOTO]
Hm?
Wait, you mean you've
been to Kyoto before?
[RYUZU] I was talking
about the planet itself.
In 206 years--no, more.
In the thousand years since I
was built, it's barely changed.
It's stagnated.
Thousand years, huh?
Long life, even for
a clock. Real long.
It must be needing
an overhaul by now.
[KONRAD]
Pressure control unit JD-90021
appears to be working fine,
so that wasn't the problem.
This is impossible.
The control block has
trillions of parts.
That's just way
too many to check.
We can narrow it down some,
but that still leaves something
like 520 million parts
to look over.
No way we'll find
it soon enough.
It'd take a miracle.
[MARIE] Then we'll just
have to make one happen.
There are 20 million
lives at stake right now.
We'll fix this. Whatever it
takes, we'll make that repair.
We still have 9 hours
and 44 minutes.
Let's keep narrowing it down.
Meister Marie, we're
going to keep working,
but shouldn't we give an
evacuation notice to the public?
We can't. That might
spook the military.
They could move up the purge.
They'll do anything
to cover their tracks.
Yeah, he's right. It would
be too much of a risk.
So our hands are tied?
It feels wrong not
to warn people.
[HALTER] We got a message
from Guild headquarters.
We're to withdraw.
You've got to be kidding!
[MARIE] Man, can't we
catch a freaking break?
If only RyuZU were here.
[HALTER] You think having that
thing with us would be helpful?
Assuming we could
get it working.
Which would be a
miracle on its own.
I'm grasping at straws.
Right now, I'd take help
from anywhere I can get it.
[MARIE]
So many people depending on us,
and they don't even know it.
Finding one defect in more
than 500 million parts?
We're looking for a needle
in a stack of needles.
It's going to be impossible.
There's no way.
But you're gonna
do it, aren't you?
You bet I am!
I'm Meister Marie Bell Breguet,
and I'm a woman
who doesn't believe
in the word "impossible."
Good, now here.
You and I both know you'll
be practically useless
without that.
You're such a jerk.
But thank you.
[NAOTO]
Huh? Ha-ha!
Is there something wrong?
Hey, would you mind
trying that outfit on?
[RYUZU]
Um, Master Naoto?
I'm not so sure about this.
I don't think it's an
appropriate outfit
for a servant.
Nope, I think it's
totally appropriate.
You look really good!
Better than good! Amazing!
Thank you, but it doesn't
seem very practical to me.
[NAOTO] It's more fun
this way. Date-like!
I'm confused, though.
I don't understand why
you would want things
to be "date-like" with a clock.
What do you mean?
You're not a clock, RyuZU.
All right, but if I'm not
a clock to you, Master,
then what am I?
Only the best thing ever!
A cute automaton girl.
Wait a second.
You-You think I'm cute?
[NAOTO]
Super cute!
Hey, what if we do something
fun with your hair?
We could make it look a bit
more playful, you know?
--Just hold still.
--Wait. Please stop.
--I think I've got an idea.
[NAOTO yelping]
[RYUZU]
I see now.
This makeover was actually
a calculated plot.
A way to disguise the sexual
harassment you intended.
No! No!
I'm not smart enough
for that, I swear!
[LIMONS]
I'll say it again.
You and your team are to cease
your repair efforts immediately.
[MARIE]
Will you tell us why?
[LIMONS] The military maintains
all the world's Core Towers,
which gives them a great
deal of authority.
We can't disregard their wishes
because we don't
agree with them.
It's a matter of give and take.
Give and take, huh?
We're talking about 20 million
people losing their lives,
and that's how you're
going to justify it?
[LIMONS]
A regretful sacrifice.
You're in bed with the
military, aren't you?
[LIMONS] The world needs both
the military and the guild.
It makes sense for us to work
together, don't you think?
You were the one
I spoke to earlier.
Bet you leaked
that message, too.
[LIMONS]
Going so soon? Where to?
[MARIE] Where do you think?
To resume my work.
Do that, and I will be forced
to revoke your license.
You'll be nothing more
than a regular civilian.
Of course, you won't be allowed
to enter the Core Tower, either.
What's going on here?
Your name. You're
Limons Vacheron.
So, what?
Is this the Vacheron
Company's attempt
to discredit the Breguets?
Quite an imagination you've got.
I have no clue what
you're talking about.
You disgust me!
[gasps]
[HALTER]
Marie!
Let's go.
This guy isn't worth the
effort of pulling the trigger.
Yeah.
No.
[screaming]
his isn't helping. Calm down!
[MARIE]
Let go! Let go! Let go!
Don't you get it?
Don't you see what's going on?
This is happening because of me.
These guys want
to screw me over,
and the 20 million
people in this city
are nothing more than
collateral damage!
No.
The purge was gonna happen
anyway. The military wants it.
The shitheads from Vacheron
are just along for the ride.
How can you know for
sure that's true?
If I hadn't been here, maybe the
purge could've been avoided.
[HALTER] Even so, that doesn't
make this your fault.
Shut up!
Shut up! Just shut up!
[MARIE laughing]
All those people...
just... gone.
Are you calm now?
[MARIE]
What are talking about?
Nobody's calmer than me.
I'm the damn queen of calm.
Whatever you say, Your Majesty.
It's okay. It's
going to be okay.
If these jerks think I'll
give up that easily,
then they're even
stupider than I thought.
I'll teach them not to
mess with Marie Breguet.
We've got a city to save,
Halter, let's get back to work!
[NAOTO]
RyuZU, how should I say this?
Well, to be perfectly
honest with you,
that outfit is just
a little unsettling.
I cannot comprehend the fetish
you have for skimpy outfits
or your wish to style my hair
"playfully," as you refer to it.
However, I do know that there is
a time and place for everything.
You don't have to come
with me, you know.
I realize I'm just being
willful at this point.
Of course I'm coming.
Unless you've got yourself
another bodyguard.
Besides, when have you
ever not been willful?
You shut up.
[HALTER chuckles]
So, uh, is this really
where we're gonna stay?
Master Naoto, you have
the courage of a flea,
so this may be difficult.
But could you please attempt
to display the dignity
and composure that a servant
of my caliber deserves?
--Is that...?
--You all right? What's up?
[RYUZU]
Why are we stopping?
Is something wrong?
No, it can't be.
That's the first unit of the
Initial-Y Series. RyuZU!
[NAOTO] The countdown for
the purge of the Kyoto Grid
draws steadily closer to zero.
As trouble continues to brew,
two geniuses meet.
With their powerful
automata at their sides,
an unlikely and unexpected
quartet is born.
The gears that will
determine the fate
of the Clockwork Planet
are beginning to turn.
Where will they lead us?
Next time: "Conflict."
Come on, ya gotta be kidding me!
How could I not fall in love
after something like that?