[NAOTO]
Huh?
[ANCHOR]
This shop's weird.
What kinds of things
do they sell here?
[NAOTO]
Um, well...
It's a place for grownups.
You'll understand
when you're older.
[MARIE]
It doesn't make sense.
Why would Meister Konrad
want us to meet him
in a place like this?
[KONRAD]
Oh! Meister Marie!
Meister Konrad, you're... Uh...
[KONRAD]
I'm so glad you're safe.
We've been worried.
We didn't know what to think
when we lost contact
with you in Akihabara.
What in the world happened
since our last communication?
[MARIE] I'm sorry, he wants to
know what happened to me?
[NAOTO]
Whoa!
[ANCHOR]
What is it, Father?
Is something wrong?
This isn't something you
should be looking at, AnchoR.
[ANCHOR]
Okay.
Hey. You shouldn't be
looking at any of it, either.
For that matter,
neither should I.
Now, let's keep moving.
[KONRAD]
Isn't this a great place?
The automata I've adjusted
around here are quite popular.
And the customers are very
appreciative of the work I do.
[MARIE]
A "great" place?
Try corrupt, depraved, immoral.
Well, this is where I work.
Uh!
Huh?
[KONRAD] It's not something you
want to be too noisy about,
but there's a thriving
black market for automata here.
It's an open secret.
We even sell to the
authorities now and then.
Good, this is perfect.
It's exactly what we need.
Put RyuZU onto
that hanger over there.
We're going to
cool her down slowly.
'Kay. On it.
[NAOTO]
Hmm...
[MARIE]
And Halter...
I don't know what I'll do if
we can't wake him up again.
He's been magnetized.
But if his brain
is still intact...
[KONRAD] It looks
like we're going to need
a spare body, then.
[MARIE] Within the next
twelve hours, if possible.
As you can imagine,
that won't be easy.
I'll look around, though,
and see what I can find.
That's all I can ask for.
I know you'll do your best.
[ANCHOR]
I hate seeing big sis like this.
Will she be okay?
[NAOTO] RyuZU took
all the proper precautions
to protect herself.
I don't think we have
anything to worry about.
[ANCHOR]
That looks painful.
Does it hurt?
[NAOTO]
Not too bad.
I barely feel it.
Soon I'll be good as new.
They could still get infected.
Stop acting tough
and let me treat you.
Yeah, okay. Good idea.
You all right, Mother?
I want you to stop
calling me that.
Now, let me see your burns.
[NAOTO]
Oh, right. Sure.
[NAOTO] What's the point
in waking him up?
He's not really...
himself anymore.
It might be nicer to let him go.
[VERMOUTH]
What did you say? Well?
How dare you talk about Vermouth
Handsome Face like that?
[VERMOUTH]
Oh...!
What the hell did you do to me?
No need to get shrill.
The only way to revive you
was to connect your
brain to an automaton.
[VERMOUTH] And you had
to pick a pleasure doll?
There must have
been other options.
Does my dignity mean
nothing to you at all?
Honestly, I can't
say that it does.
[VERMOUTH] She connected
a cyborg brain to an automaton
that was of a
completely different make.
That goes way
beyond genius level.
Who is this chick?
The devil?
[NAOTO] I'd play nice
with her if I were you.
Halter's not waking up,
so she's on edge.
Well, more on edge than usual.
[MARIE]
Too much information, Naoto.
I want to hear everything you
know down to the last detail.
The weapon's in play,
but I still haven't figured
out what the endgame is.
You aren't seriously
this clueless, are you?
Huh?
[VERMOUTH] All the pieces
have been laid out for you,
and you still can't put
the puzzle together?
[NAOTO]
Those shitheads are just gonna
sit back and
do nothing. Right?
What?
[VERMOUTH whistles]
You look like such
a sweet little kid,
but you've got a devious mind
behind that baby
face, don't you?
[MARIE]
I still don't understand.
The appearance of the weapon
has pitted the government
against the military,
and that's not a fight either
one is likely to survive.
Things getting
clearer now, little girl?
[PRIME MINISTER]
We made a request
to the International
Territory Administration
for the use of the Tall Wand.
We'll target the Akihabara
Grid and the Yatsukahagi.
[OFFICIAL A]
The Tall Wand?
[KARASAWA]
This guy can't be serious.
We're talking about a weapon
of mass destruction dropped
from equatorial orbit
that's easily capable
of wiping out a city or two,
and he means to deploy
it on his own country?
[PRIME MINISTER]
Now that the public knows
about the electromagnetic
weapon, there will be
no escaping reproach from
the international community.
We must try our
hardest to make amends.
Like that matters to you!
All you care about is
avoiding responsibility
for illegal research and
the creation of the Yatsukahagi.
I won't allow you
to speak to me that way!
Oh, shut up!
This is obviously a situation
that will be best resolved
by the military.
Please! You and your
precious military
couldn't so much as
dent the Yatsukahagi.
[OFFICIAL B] Between the
mess in Kyoto and now this,
you've proved yourselves
completely worthless!
[MINISTER OF DEFENSE]
Take that back, you bastard!
Take it back right now!
[MARIE] You're saying that
the military and the government
are going to destroy
themselves just by being there?
That's why the weapon's
not making a move?
You're starting to get it.
This is no ordinary
terrorist attack.
These fools are
orchestrating a takeover.
A full-blown coup d'état.
[NAOTO]
Actually, for the record.
The weapon's not moving
because it can't right now.
What do you mean?
[VERMOUTH]
Yes, do tell.
Where'd you get that idea?
It's charging, using its
1,333 clockwork generators
to replenish its energy.
That's gonna take some time.
I'd say we've got...
66.5 hours 'til it's done.
Clockwork generators?
But it's electromagnetic.
The Yatsukahagi's a hybrid
electromagnetic
strategic mobile weapon.
Its creators combined
electromagnetic
and clockwork technologies.
The Yatsukahagi.
At least we finally
have a name to call it.
So, what,
you saw the blueprints?
I don't think even that would
explain how much you know.
What's your secret, kid?
They're charging it.
But why?
Somebody's still got
plans for that weapon.
[MARIE gasps]
[MARIE]
What else are they planning?
If they act again, it won't just
be Japan's problem anymore.
Is that it?
Are they trying
to start a world war?
What can we do in
66 and a half hours?
How do we stop
an unstoppable weapon?
[ANCHOR]
Uh...
[NAOTO]
All right!
Come on, AnchoR.
We're going out.
What?
You've got to be kidding me!
[MARIE]
Where are you going?
Into the city.
To do what we can.
[OPERATOR A]
Energy level is at 12 percent.
At the current pace,
we won't meet the target
for remobilization.
[SUPERIOR OFFICER A]
The chance of another attack
by the military is small.
Lower the energy levels
of the weapon systems.
[OPERATOR A]
Roger.
Only 66 hours now.
Less than three days
and our greatest goal
will be realized at last.
Indeed.
[GENNAI]
I know better.
It's not over yet, is it, Y?
What will your next move be?
[NAOTO]
Okay, AnchoR, let's do this!
Are you ready to
have some serious fun?
Ahh...!
[ANCHOR giggles]
Oh!
[NAOTO]
Oh. What?
You see something interesting?
[ANCHOR]
That shop over there.
May I go in?
Do I have permission?
Do you?
Yeah!
You remember what
I told you before, don't you?
You can do anything, 'kay?
[ANCHOR]
Anything? Really?
Really, really!
[giggles]
What a cutie!
I wonder what I did to deserve
such an adorably
perfectly perfect daughter!
I still want to know
what we're doing here.
Is there a point to
this little excursion?
Right now, I'm doing
what needs to be done.
She's been denied
these experiences
for a thousand years!
But that ends today!
I'm gonna make sure she has
fun if it's the last thing I do.
Is it her fun or yours
you're more worried about?
And can we talk
about the outfit?
[NAOTO]
We are wanted, you know.
It only makes sense
to wear disguises.
Hey.
Well, would you look at that.
I'm pretty cute.
Vomit.
[ANCHOR]
'Kay, all done.
There's another shop
I want to see.
Can I, Father?
[NAOTO]
Yeah, of course!
I'm not going to refuse
you anything today, sweetie!
[gasps]
Huh?
Will you come, Mother? Please?
I already told you: I don't want
you calling me that anymore.
[ANCHOR whines]
[MARIE]
With everything that's going on,
why are we out on
a shopping trip?
[ANCHOR]
Oh...!
Hey, Father.
Do I have permission
to want that bear?
Uh, yeah!
[ANCHOR]
Aaah!
[SHOP WORKER A]
Hello there, honey.
Out shopping
with your big sister?
[ANCHOR]
Mm-hmm!
Look at you!
Such a sweet little thing
deserves my undivided attention!
[NAOTO] Ahhh! Oh,
I don't know if it's possible
to die from an
overload of cuteness.
Oh, but if it is,
I'm a dead man walking!
[ANCHOR] You know,
Father, you're cute too.
[NAOTO]
Here, for you.
Thanks so much.
I love it!
[NEWSCASTER A] In the wake
of last night's terror attack,
the entire Akihabara
Grid has been shut down.
There's been no indication when
the lockdown might be lifted.
The public has become
increasingly insistent
that government officials
provide an explanation.
People are still going
about their everyday lives
with no idea how bad
things are about to get.
[NAOTO]
Hey, good job!
[ANCHOR]
Ahh!
Oh!
[MARIE] Those two actually
know the danger we're in,
and they're still out
messing around.
[MARIE]
I feel stuck.
I don't know what to do
until the Yatsukahagi
starts moving again.
There has to be something!
[approaching footsteps]
[MARIE]
Hm?! Huh?!
That was the first time
I played that game.
But after a few tries,
I won something, and um, well,
I want you to have it.
[music box playing]
[ANCHOR]
Do you hear that?
It plays a pretty song.
[MARIE]
Okay. Thank you.
I can't believe
how fun the city is!
I've never done anything like
this before, but I love it.
[MARIE] We don't have
time to be doing this.
We need to be
coming up with a plan.
So finally, on my
fifth try... I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You understand?
You're allowed to
do anything you want.
I am not going to stop you.
[ANCHOR] Mother,
will you give me an order?
You're upset. I can tell.
I don't want you to cry.
[gasps]
[ANCHOR]
Give me an order so I can help.
Please?
[MARIE]
What are you talking about?
You're just a kid.
A cute little doll.
So you won't give me
permission to help you, then?
[MARIE]
Can I do it?
Is it really that simple?
[MARIE]
An order?
Here you go!
Destroy the Yatsukagahi now!
If you're a weapon,
you can do that, right?!
'Kay. You don't have
to cry anymore, Mother.
I'll go and destroy it for you.
No, I... I shouldn't've...
[NAOTO grunts]
[gasps]
[ANCHOR]
Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
[NAOTO]
Sorry, could you please,
keep it down a bit?
Thank you.
[gasps]
You're in pain.
What happened to
your headphones?
[NAOTO]
They broke back in Akihabara.
So I ditched 'em.
You should've
got more first thing!
[NAOTO]
No time for that yet.
Once I find what I'm
looking for, I'll get some.
Hold on!
Tell me what you're looking for?
[NAOTO]
Isn't it obvious?
A chance.
A chance to beat up the people
who hurt RyuZU so badly.
I want to see them punished.
[MARIE]
Huh?
[MARIE] So he wasn't
just screwing around.
He's been thinking
about this all along.
[NAOTO] Multiple grids
are connected, right?
So that means they
all affect each other.
Um... Well, yeah...
They're all connected,
with the State Central Territory
Control Tower and the
Pillar of Heaven at the center.
[NAOTO] I found a way to
get us into Akihabara, but...
I've got some ideas, but
before we start making plans,
I need to know
what you want to do.
[ANCHOR] Well, what I want
is to destroy that thing
to help Mother.
[NAOTO] All right,
what did you say to her?
Well, if she can take it out...
[NAOTO]
No way! Not happening.
How could you ask that?
You think you can just use her,
like she's some tool?
What do mean?
She's the Initial-Y
Series annihilator!
She's a weapon!
Don't you dare call her that!
She's my daughter!
And besides that,
she's charging right now.
You'd be sending
her out to fight
before she was
even at full strength.
Huh?
[NAOTO] You're okay
with making a small child
shoulder your burden
just because it's gotten
a little too heavy for you?
Don't you have any pride, Marie?
[MARIE gasps]
[ANCHOR whines]
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
[NAOTO sighs]
[MARIE]
I didn't mean to say it.
I was so frustrated about not
being able to do anything.
So I just...
[gasps]
I'm sorry,
but I need to head back.
AnchoR, please
take care of Naoto.
A request? Right.
That's more important
than an order.
She can be difficult, but
she's actually pretty amazing.
Like, a total genius.
She's that smart?
For all her intelligence,
she has a tendency to get
hung up worrying about stuff.
Still, she does get things done,
which is more than
I can say for myself.
Huh?
Well, hello there, kids.
I wondered when
you'd get back here.
Almost scary to watch, isn't it?
She's done all this
in only four hours.
Kinda makes you wonder
if she's actually human.
"A genius." I see.
You're right.
Yeah.
It's not fair.
That should be me.
[NAOTO]
I should be fixing her.
Damn it.
Huh?
[MARIE screams]
I'm all out of sugar.
Chocolate.
Choco...
[MARIE]
Thank you.
[ANCHOR giggles]
Ah, that's better!
Oh. Hey!
I didn't know you were back.
Just now.
[MARIE] I take it you found
what you were looking for?
[NAOTO]
Mm-hmm
How about you come over
and give me a hand, then?
I need three resonance
movement connectors.
It shouldn't be too hard.
I'm sorry.
I can't make those.
[MARIE]
That's fine.
Just the circuits, then.
[NAOTO]
Nope.
Can't do that either.
Huh?
But that's the kind of stuff you
learn back in middle school.
How'd you ever manage
to repair RyuZU?
I did it by feel.
Say wha?
[NAOTO] I didn't have
any particular plan in mind,
I just knew that
something sounded wrong.
I figured all I had to do
was fix that sound, so I did.
And that's when she woke up.
No way.
She's a crazy complex automaton.
That's ridiculous.
No one could repair her without
any theoretical knowledge!
Yeah, whatever.
Clearly, I did fix her.
[MARIE] He doesn't know
what he's talking about.
Unless, what if he is right?
What if we experts
have been missing something
fundamental all along?
[NAOTO]
Hey, Marie.
[MARIE]
Huh?!
You did say the Pillar
of Heaven is at the center
of all the grids
in Japan, right?
[MARIE] Naoto, what's going
through that head of yours?
We're going to take over
the Pillar of Heaven.
[gasping]
[laughs]
There's a plan!
Sure, why not?
I could kiss you, kid.
I think it's amazing, Father!
[MARIE]
Really?
'Cause I think it's insane.
Who was it who took
over the Akihabara Grid
in the first place?
That was us.
Who publicly
claimed responsibility
for the entire thing?
Again, us.
So, why don't we continue
to play our parts
and act accordingly?
Coup d'état?
Government conspiracy?
Nothing like that happened.
All of this was the
work of the villains
who seized control of Akihabara
and bragged about it on TV.
Makes sense, right?
[NAOTO] We're gonna throw
these people into the fire.
Akihabara is the fire pit.
And if we do this right,
the Pillar of Heaven
will be the fuel.
Hold on.
It's the center of the nation.
For something on this scale,
we need more people.
If it helps,
I've got an idea where to
get a spare body for Halter.
[VERMOUTH] And for what
it's worth, you can count me in.
I don't mind doing my part.
You get that this
isn't a joke, right?
We're going to be criminals,
and not just petty ones.
What could possibly
be in it for you?
A whole lot of fun.
What better motivation could
a man ask for than that?
[MARIE]
Hmm...
[ANCHOR]
Mother?
Are you frightened?
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
[MARIE]
Uh...
Come on, Marie.
These guys have spent years
putting their plans into action,
and now, we have the
chance to ruin it all for them.
Are you really gonna tell me you
don't like the thought of that?
Huh?
[MARIE]
We're gonna save the world,
and it's gonna be awesome!
[MARIE]
I was so busy being frustrated.
I forgot what's
really important.
Sometimes you just
have to do what's right
even if it means
becoming a criminal.
You're right, Naoto.
This'll be amazing, Let's do it!
[HOUKO]
It is out of our control.
As hard as we've tried,
we cannot come up with
a single countermeasure
to the threat that lies
deep beneath Tokyo.
I can do nothing.
In the face of this danger,
I'm powerless.
[HOUKO]
Marie.
If only you were here.
[VERMOUTH]
Without Halter,
the attempt to occupy the Pillar
of Heaven would likely fail.
After finally locating
a suitable automaton,
Marie begins the daunting
task of connecting it
to her bodyguard's mind.
But will even someone of her
genius be able to pull it off?
Next time, "Progressor."
Knowing old man Halter, the
scent of the battlefield alone
would probably be enough to
bring him back from the dead.
Fair warning, though,
he'll likely be in the
worst mood imaginable.