[ANCHOR]
Absolute maneuver.
Bloody Murder.
[ALL gasp]
Go!
[HALTER grunts]
Quick! Jump out of its reach!
Enough.
You have one last chance
to explain yourself.
For your sake, I hope that you
have a satisfactory explanation
for threatening my master.
I won't hesitate to destroy
you, sister or not.
What's wrong with her?
RyuZU, jump!
[ANCHOR]
I don't want this.
I don't!
[gasps]
Please, do it!
Destroy me! I want you to.
It's wrong.
She's not operating correctly
for some reason.
[HALTER]
What do you think?
Is there any way we
can beat this thing?
We need to move!
I suppose I can try
my Mute Scream.
I would have a
chance of success.
Chance, huh?
Well, that's reassuring.
What are you planning?
Be quiet and hold on.
You will die.
[HALTER]
I was dead a long time ago.
[NAOTO]
Halter! Jump to the left!
Again!
[NAOTO]
RyuZU!
What?
Dimensional warping?!
[ANCHOR growls]
Under her feet!
[ANCHOR grunts]
Halter!
[HALTER grunts]
[MARIE]
All right!
Beneath that floor is
the Deep Underground.
She won't be making it out
of there anytime soon.
[ANCHOR grunting]
[HALTER, RYUZU, NAOTO gasp]
No way! She climbed
up the falling debris?
My ears, damn! I don't like
the sound of that at all.
I think it's a triple resonance.
[MARIE]
This can't be happening!
A weapon that massive should
be mounted on a battle cruiser,
not wielded by a
single combatant.
Do you know what that is?
It's a Resonance Cannon!
Let's get out of its range!
[screaming]
That packs a serious punch.
Hey, Marie, are you okay?
Uh! Halter, get away from there!
[MARIE]
Oh, god! He'll never make it!
Halter!
[NAOTO]
RyuZU, stop that thing!
[grunts]
Let's go.
[gasps]
Naoto, RyuZU!
[gasping]
[whimpers] No way...
[HALTER grunts]
Marie!
Hey, stop! What are you doing?!
[HALTER]
Retreating. [grunts]
[MARIE]
Go back!
Come on, Halter, stop!
Are you listening to me? Stop!
[HALTER]
No.
We have to save them!
Turn around and go back!
There's no point.
[gasps]
[HALTER] The Deep Underground
is similar to outer space.
An unprotected human
can't survive there.
Marie.
Naoto Miura is dead.
[gasps]
[cries]
[HALTER]
We're almost above ground now.
Get some food in your system.
A hot shower might help, too.
[MARIE] There was a floor
that wasn't supposed to exist,
and an enormous weapon that
shouldn't have been built.
[MARIE]
You got them into this.
Who built it?
What do they plan to do with it?
[MARIE]
Naoto Miura is dead.
Are the leaders of Mie
our enemies, too?
[MARIE] You wouldn't know
enough to ask that question
if it weren't for Naoto.
And there's AnchoR.
She was supposed to be in the
basement of Kyoto's Core Tower.
So, what was she doing
guarding that thing?
[MARIE]
It doesn't matter what you do.
There's no bringing him back.
You killed Naoto.
It's your fault.
[gasps]
[crying]
[HALTER]
Listen...
I'm gonna tell you something,
and I want you to hear me out.
[MARIE]
What?
You're still a child, Princess.
Young in a lot of ways.
You've said as much yourself.
[MARIE]
So what's your point?
[HALTER] The thing about being a
child is, you're allowed to cry.
Nobody will judge you for it.
[MARIE cries]
That's not true.
Even if no one else
judges me, I will.
I can't let go like that.
I can't. Don't you see?
My strength is all I have.
Without it, who am I?
[MARIE cries]
So, what are you gonna do?
I think I've got a
pretty good idea,
but I can't pretend I like it.
I don't care whether
you like it or not.
I have no intention
of backing down.
I only have a life
because Naoto gave his.
I'm not going to waste it.
[GOVERNOR'S DAUGHTER]
What?
But I thought we were
going out to eat tonight!
Your father had to work a bit
late to handle an emergency.
Fine, so let him handle it, and
we can just go without him.
You know we can't.
We'll go another time.
But I've been wanting to try
out this restaurant forever!
[GOVERNOR grunting]
[MARIE] Sorry if I ruined your
family's plans for the evening.
But, you see,
I've got questions,
and as the governor
of the Mie Grid,
you're the one to answer them.
[GOVERNOR grunting]
[gasps] You little brat--
[GOVERNOR groans]
[groaning]
[MARIE] Only speak to
answer my questions.
Don't waste my time
with screaming.
Okay! I'll talk.
[MARIE]
There's an enormous weapon
on the deepest floor
of the factory in Mie.
Tell me everything
you know about it.
I... I know of its existence,
but nothing more than that.
I swear to you.
It was agreed that we'd
leave the details to them.
--[thud]
--[GOVERNOR groans]
It's true!
We decided it would
be best for everyone
if we stayed out of
each other's affairs.
Kill the wife and daughter.
[HALTER]
Cool, who dies first?
[MARIE]
Whichever one screams louder.
Uh! No, you can't--
--[GOVERNOR gagging]
--[MARIE] Shh. Heh.
[GOVERNOR]
We have an agreement,
an understanding,
you might call it.
It goes beyond just
hiding that weapon.
If word gets out that
they're here in Mie,
I don't know what might happen.
[MARIE] Who do you mean?
Who're "they"?
People you don't want to cross:
military remnants from
the purged Shiga Grid.
[gasps]
[GOVERNOR] Thirty years ago,
there was a defect in Shiga,
one on a large enough scale that
necessitated the grid's purge.
[MARIE]
Yes, I know.
The fallout would have affected
all of western Japan,
so it was decided to go ahead
and conduct the purge,
rather than wait for the
Guild to perform repairs.
What you probably don't know
is that was actually a ruse.
The defect was the direct result
of electromagnetic research
that was being carried
out in Shiga.
But that's illegal!
Electromagnetism is banned now
because of its negative
effect on gears.
You're right.
It was a clear violation
of the national treaties.
During one of the
illegal experiments
they were conducting,
the electromagnetic waves
broke containment.
The entire city was disabled.
The Japanese government
couldn't let it be known
that they were in charge
of that research.
In order to cover up
their involvement,
they purged Shiga and pretended
as if it had never happened.
Afterwards, the scientists
and members of the military
who had been abandoned by the
government went underground.
They consolidated their power,
working from the shadows
to gain control of Mie
so they could cannibalize
Shiga's remains and
Mie's Clock Tower in order
to finish their pet project.
[MARIE]
So they were silenced
because it was discovered
they were conducting
illegal research on behalf
of the government.
Still, if you knew,
why didn't you go public
with all of this?
If I had done that,
Mie would have been
sunk like Shiga.
[gasps]
[GOVERNOR] The only way you can
negotiate with the government
is if you have
power of your own.
That's why the weapon is there.
It acts as a deterrent.
The national government knows
of the weapon's existence
and because they fear it,
they cannot purge Mie.
Both parties circle each other,
the principle of mutually
assured destruction
preventing either from acting.
[MARIE]
You say it's just a deterrent.
If that's really the case,
why is it ready to activate?
It's not!
[MARIE]
We saw it with our own eyes.
I assure you, it's ready.
[laughing]
Why are you laughing?!
[laughs]
You don't see the
absurdity of this, do you?
The weapon that was built
specifically to be a deterrent
and nothing more is
ready to deploy.
Given the timing,
it should be perfectly obvious
what's going on here.
And yet, the person
whose actions led
to the weapon's activation
is asking me why
it's been activated?
This is happening because
of you, Marie Bell Breguet.
[GOVERNOR]
Thanks to you,
the purge of the Kyoto Grid
was narrowly avoided.
The information you so
carelessly disseminated
cost the government badly,
both in money and in
the trust of the public.
So now they need an enemy,
one that will justify
their existence and
force the people to look to
them for safety and guidance.
With the activation
of that weapon,
Mie will become the enemy.
The government will crush us,
saving the country
from a rogue city
and becoming heroes in
the eyes of the people.
That's what this is all about!
[MARIE whimpers]
So, tell me, did it feel good?
Was it satisfying to reveal
the government's sins?
Are you happy now,
having outsmarted those
who tried to bury you?
You showed them, all right.
Was it worth it?!
I hope so, because your
stupid sense of justice
is going to get even more
people killed now!
Why couldn't you die
like they wanted you to?!
Instead, you had to play
the goddamned hero!
[HALTER] The information we
got from Meister Konrad
makes more sense now.
I researched the Initial-Y
Series unit as you asked.
We found evidence it was
moved from Kyoto to Tokyo.
What's more,
well, it seems Tokyo's military
is amassing nearly all their
forces in one location,
like they're readying
for a fight.
[HALTER]
I think we can guess
what Tokyo's military
is preparing for.
There's gonna be
a war before long.
What am I supposed to do?
You aren't responsible
for this, you know.
It started 30 years ago
with Shiga's purge.
[MARIE]
I know that,
but...
[HALTER]
But what, Princess?
Tokyo's military is going
after that weapon.
You want to stop the fight?
[MARIE] Should I just
sit back and watch?
[HALTER]
Well, hell yeah.
If two of your enemies want to
bash each other's heads in,
I say let 'em.
Makes your job easier.
This isn't a joke!
Just speakin' the
truth, Princess.
All right.
So, what's next?
[MARIE]
I don't know.
I'm lost.
So lost.
[MARIE cries]
This world of ours...
...is it worth fighting for?
Does it deserve to survive?
I've always hated knowing that
even if I'm doing
the right thing,
there are some
fights I can't win.
But somehow, when
I was with Naoto,
things didn't
feel so hopeless.
Then I let him die, and
that hope died with him.
[MARIE grunts]
Useless.
I'm too small and weak
to do anything.
[MARIE cries]
[gasps]
[NAOTO]
Aw, damn, it's raining!
I thought we might get
a chance to dry off
once we were out of the sewer.
[RYUZU] Considering it will wash
away the filth of the sewer,
the rain might be
seen as a good thing.
However, if this weather
is the result
of insufficient maintenance,
the city's administrator
should be fired
for dereliction of duty as
well as soaking my clothes.
I don't enjoy being wet.
[NAOTO]
It's muggy and gross out here.
I thought rain was supposed
to cool things off.
[NAOTO]
Oh crap, it's Marie.
Maybe we should run away
while we have the chance.
Is it possible?
Have you finally
acquired the ability
to learn from your
mistakes, Master?
[gasping]
[whimpers]
[growling]
[NAOTO groans]
[NAOTO]
Jeez! What was that for?
Ow!
You stupid ass!
If you were alive, you could've
let me know sooner!
Coming, Master!
For daring to touch you,
I'll put her down like
the rabid dog she is!
[MARIE, NAOTO shouting]
[HALTER] Could you
all please calm down?
I'm getting a headache.
[MARIE] So, you gonna
tell me what happened?
During the fight, I realized
from the way sounds resonated
that there was ground beneath
the floor we were on.
So, I thought dropping down
there might be okay.
[RYUZU] It was not okay,
it was reckless.
You were lucky the
air was breathable
and the oxygen wasn't
sucked from your lungs.
Still, if you hadn't had such a
capable servant to assist you,
I doubt you would have lived.
[NAOTO] Anyway, there was this
weird old guy living down there.
He turned on an elevator
and sent us back up.
There you have it. End of story.
Hang on a second.
So when you let yourself fall,
you didn't think you
were going to die?
Huh? No, of course not.
If I died, then RyuZU
would lose her master.
Not to mention I wouldn't
be able to help AnchoR.
You didn't sacrifice
yourself to save me?
[NAOTO]
What? Are you kidding?
Where did you get
that idea from?
I was just tryin'
to stop AnchoR,
nothing more
complicated than that.
Oh, wow, you actually thought
I would die for you?
You're gonna die,
all right, you jerk.
[NAOTO] So, AnchoR was in
Tokyo before coming to Mie?
Yeah.
That's what Meister
Konrad told us.
Right. I guess we're
takin' a trip to Tokyo.
Huh?
AnchoR is protecting that giant
weapon, which we now believe
is going to make its way
toward Tokyo, right?
So that's where we go.
You say that like
it's so simple.
But the situation is more
complicated than that.
We need to think this through.
Tokyo's gathered its army, and
Mie's activated their weapon.
In all likelihood,
Mie will strike first.
But even if we were
able to catch up to it,
I don't have the first idea how
we'd go about defeating it.
Should we go to Tokyo
and wait for it, then?
If it reaches Tokyo, the city
will become a battlefield.
Civilian loss
would be significant.
[NAOTO]
Shut up already!
No matter how many what-ifs
you come up with,
I've got no doubts about
what I need to do.
I'm going to Tokyo
to save AnchoR!
So, what's it gonna be?
Are you comin' with me,
or are you gonna sit here
like an idiot thinking about
what could go wrong until it's
too late to do anything?! Huh?!
Are you kidding, here?!
You calling me an idiot?!
That's rich!
Ha!
What else do you call
someone who does nothing
but whine about how impossible
everything seems?
You don't even have
a concrete plan!
Yeah, well, who cares?!
It's better than being a walking
landmine, so damn uptight
you're ready to explode
at the slightest pressure!
Meister Marie!
[grunts]
[MARIE growls]
[NAOTO growls]
[MARIE]
Get this straight:
I am a woman who doesn't believe
in the word "impossible."
[NAOTO]
Heh. Yeah, that's right.
I thought you could use
a little reminder.
Hope it helped.
No thanks needed.
[laughs]
You're an idiot, an
absolutely, absurd idiot.
Hands down, a much better
idiot than I could ever be.
Hey.
I mean, when you think about it,
we're all idiots in our own way.
People are irrational.
We're stubborn and
stupid and selfish,
and there's not a damn
thing we can do about it.
Because we're human,
and humans are imperfect.
Maybe this sad,
half-broken world of ours
doesn't really
deserve to survive.
Even so. I'm still
going to fight for it.
Okay, why's she getting
poetic all of a sudden?
I hear that tends to happen when
a girl's going through puberty.
For the record, you're rude
and I hate you both!
Now, here's the plan.
The two of you are going to be
in charge of saving AnchoR,
and I will focus on
saving the world!
All right, let's go!
Uh, Princess. What are we doing?
[MARIE]
Isn't that obvious?
Whatever we have to do.
Now, come on.
First thing's first,
we're going to go attack Tokyo.
[RYUZU]
Tokyo's military readies for war
as the giant weapon
heads in their direction.
Drastic measures must be taken
in order to prevent
civilian casualties.
Sometimes to defeat evil, good
people must become criminals,
and sisters must
battle each other.
Next time:
"Attack the Multiple Grid."
Master Naoto, I believe in you.
And you, too, AnchoR.
Little sister,
I believe in you, as well.