[SOLDIER B]
Huh?
Enemy fire!
Everyone hold positions!
[RYUZU]
May I have your attention?
[gasps]
I am Initial-Y Series
Unit One, RyuZU,
also known as One Who Follows.
And, I'm Initial-Y Series
Unit Four, AnchoR,
One Who Annihilates.
[RYUZU] And, now that we've
made our introductions,
it's time to say farewell.
[ANCHOR] But we'll try not
to make it hurt too much.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
I'm so sorry!
[RYUZU sighs]
The last 48 hours have
been rather suffocating.
The fresh air makes
for a nice change.
[VERMOUTH]
Ohhh!
You're having fun out there.
[NAOTO]
Okay, got 'em. Your two o'clock.
[VERMOUTH]
Hmm?
[NAOTO]
In formation number five.
[VERMOUTH]
All right.
[MARIE] Hey, you sure
you're going to be able
to pull this off?
[VERMOUTH]
Just trust me.
[MARIE]
In what world would I trust you?
[VERMOUTH]
Well, if you can't manage that,
then at least trust
the body you tuned.
You did an amazing job
with the supplies at hand.
[VERMOUTH]
Now, shall we?
Oh, clumsy me!
[VERMOUTH]
Good-bye, now.
Sorry, no time to chat.
[VERMOUTH laughs]
Like it a bit rough, do you?
Two can play at that game.
Here, let me show you!
[SOLDIER D]
What kind of insult is this?
Being attacked
by a pleasure bot?
I'm gonna destroy that filth!
[gasps]
[SOLDIER D laughs]
Take that!
[VERMOUTH]
There.
Alrighty, then,
let's take a peek inside.
[gasps]
[VERMOUTH] Hey, kid, this is
a pretty sweet ride you've got.
Let's make a deal:
Hand it over, and I'll let
you have this cigarette.
Sound good?
"Sure. No problem!"
Good decision.
Now, you're going
to take a little trip.
Feel free to send me a postcard.
[screams]
It's been a pleasure!
Honestly, complete the mission
without any human casualties?
That's a hell of a lot easier
said than done, Naoto.
[VERMOUTH]
There.
Show me your moves, baby.
Give me everything you've got!
[MARIE] You want me
to hook Halter's brain
up to a heavily armed automaton?
That's a crazy idea!
[NAOTO]
No, it's not.
I really think
he could handle it.
Do you have any clue how
many things can go wrong
when you attempt
something like that?
I wasn't worried about it
with you because I didn't care
about the outcome,
but the point is, it's risky.
Please, tell me how
you really feel.
Besides, there's no
precedent for this kind of--
[VERMOUTH]
There is, though.
[MARIE]
Hmm?
Directly wiring
a weapon to a brain--
no, it's not exactly
common practice,
but it has been done before.
And by none other
than our man Halter.
[MARIE]
No way, I never--
[NAOTO]
Perfect. Then it's settled.
Now, we just need
to see if the enemy
has a suitable body for us.
[VERMOUTH]
What?
You're talking about nabbing
a heavily armed automaton
from the middle
of hostile forces?
Where are you gonna find
someone nuts enough to do that?
Heh. I think I know the
perfect man for the job.
[VERMOUTH chuckles]
[roars]
[VERMOUTH]
There you are, Genbu.
I've been waiting.
[MARIE]
I have a condition.
What was the body
that Halter used?
Do you know?
It was an HS-FK2 Oberon.
They're not deployed
anywhere in this country.
The Oberon, huh?
[MARIE]
I want a CZ-35 Genbu.
They use the same design
philosophy as the Oberon
and should be deployed
at the Pillar of Heaven.
That was quick.
What, do you have the blueprint
for every automaton
model memorized?
Yup, know 'em all by heart.
It comes in handy.
[VERMOUTH]
Uh! Are you shitting me?
[VERMOUTH cackles]
This is freaking awesome!
Come on, a little
love tap like that
is no way to satisfy a girl.
Watch and learn, friend.
When I give you my spear,
you won't forget it!
[VERMOUTH] Man, there's
nothing like a cigarette
after taking care of business.
[MARIE] Is it physically
impossible for you
to open your mouth
without being filthy?
[VERMOUTH laughs]
Such delicate sensibilities.
Anyway, I destroyed the Genbu's
artificial intelligence unit
but left it intact otherwise.
The remaining enemies
have been taken out as well.
Is there anything I missed?
Wow, I was half-convinced we'd
asked you to do the impossible.
Well, I did my job,
now it's your turn.
[MARIE]
Damn straight it is.
This is it.
If I mess up,
I could lose him for good.
[VERMOUTH] Let me tell you
something that might help.
[MARIE]
Hm?
[VERMOUTH] For a career soldier,
fighting is like breathing.
And your right-hand man
is nothing if not a soldier.
Knowing old man Halter, the
scent of the battlefield alone
would probably be enough to
bring him back from the dead.
Fair warning, though,
he'll likely be in the
worst mood imaginable.
[NAOTO]
Marie.
[MARIE]
Hm?
They're gathering more troops.
I think you'll have
about... 30 seconds.
Got it?
Yeah.
I'm ready to do this.
[MARIE] I can't afford
to make a single mistake.
One error and
Halter will be gone.
Hyah!
[MARIE]
Now!
Dismantling all 2,876 parts
of the destroyed processing
unit: 4.2 seconds.
[MARIE] Connecting all
the parts: 7.6 seconds.
Testing the nerves: 6.1 seconds.
Tuning the control unit:
4.9 seconds.
Rebooting the chassis:
3.3 seconds.
4.1 seconds until
consciousness returns.
A total of 30.2 seconds,
which means I can't afford
to make a single error.
[MARIE]
My hands are too slow.
I have to move faster than this!
Are you really
she's human, Naoto?
It's kind of hard to believe
once you've seen her work.
Yeah.
That's what genius looks like.
Mother's the most amazing woman!
Just look at her.
She can do anything!
It may look impressive,
but don't get carried away.
There are limits to what
humans are able to accomplish.
At least there are, for now.
[MARIE]
I can see it all.
Every part of this
machine is visible to me.
And my perception
is only expanding.
[MARIE] There seem to be
no limits to this new sight.
I could use it to
grasp the entire city.
[MARIE]
Huh?
That's an SK-30
self-propelled artillery unit.
Crap, its projectiles fly
at supersonic speed.
[MARIE]
They haven't noticed it yet.
Even Naoto can't hear
something moving that fast.
Come on, I thought I'd
connected everything perfectly!
Wake up!
Wake up, wake up,
wake up, wake up!
You have to wake up, Halter!
[gasps]
[RYUZU]
Huh?
[HALTER]
Those bastards.
That's what happens
to anyone stupid enough
to point a gun at me.
Is it you?
Halter!
Yeah!
[HALTER] Huh?
What's going on here?
You hooked me up
to an automaton?
What trouble have
you gotten yourself into?
[MARIE] It's not me
I'm worried about right now.
Where the hell have you been?
[HALTER]
Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
I was sleeping.
Sleeping?
[HALTER] It's been a long time
since I've slept that deeply.
Once my sensory receptors
were disconnected,
I kind of drifted off I guess.
Uh...
[NAOTO] Well, old man,
how's the new body?
[HALTER]
Just fine.
Like you'd expect with
our princess doing the work.
[NAOTO] If you're up for it,
I've got a job for you.
[HALTER]
So you're giving the orders now.
All right, what's the job?
I need you to destroy the
remaining 378 enemy units.
You've got 38 seconds, and we
don't want any humans killed.
Sound good?
[HALTER]
Oh, come on.
That's too easy.
[VERMOUTH]
Aw, man! Look at him go!
Looks like 38 seconds
was a bit generous.
[HALTER]
Hey, Princess.
[MARIE]
Huh?!
[HALTER] This body's
heavier than I'm used to,
but it's working great.
Well, of course it is!
It was tuned by
yours truly, after all!
[HALTER]
I almost pity these guys.
I mean, I'm always
a little grouchy
when I wake up from a nap,
but after such a long one,
I'm in the worst
mood imaginable.
[REPORTER A] What we're
seeing now is unbelievable.
The security forces that
guard the Pillar of Heaven
were overrun in minutes.
And leading the group of
attackers is the same boy
who orchestrated the
takeover of Akihabara!
Nnnnh!
Hey! How is everybody today?
You haven't forgotten
me already, have you?
I thought I had an awesome
party set up in Akihabara,
but you military boys
made it too easy!
Here's hoping you'll put up
a better fight next time.
Who is this little brat?
What's his connection
to the Shiga group?
Now for the exciting news: after
that last disappointing shindig,
we've decided to go all out and
drop the entire multiple grid
that comprises Tokyo
into the abyss!
Yes!
Is this a joke?
[NAOTO]
Oh, excuse me!
I almost forgot that I have a
very special guest to introduce.
I have a feeling
you'll recognize her.
[OFFICIALS gasp]
It's Her Highness, Hoshinomiya.
[HOUKO]
Please listen carefully.
The Pillar of Heaven is tasked
with the governance of Tokyo
and the control of our
country's Core Towers.
It has been seized
by an unknown group
and is no longer
under our command.
This broadcast should
leave no doubt of that.
I know, this is frightening,
but please try to remain calm.
We hope for an orderly
evacuation of the capital.
Thank you all.
[KARASAWA]
No point staying here.
I need to get my report
to Meister Marie.
[GENNAI]
So...
They've made
the Yatsukahagi a pawn,
manipulating its presence
to suit their needs.
But why claim responsibility
for crimes we committed?
What is their motivation?
Are they setting
themselves up as martyrs?
Divert all energy to the main
cannon's charger at once.
You heard His Excellency,
prioritize main cannon!
[GENNAI]
Can you guess my next move, Y?
Let's see.
[KONRAD] I'm sorry
if I've kept you waiting,
but I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
Karasawa's been keeping an eye
on the Japanese government
for us, and he sent
word of a new development.
They intend to use the Tall Wand
against the Yatsukahagi.
[gasps]
It will be dropped from
orbit today at 1400 exactly.
Roughly 6 hours
and 45 minutes from now.
That's insane!
Ahhh... How did I live
before I knew this joy?
Even the gods themselves
are envious of the treasure
that is my lap.
There is no earthly
luxury that can rival it.
Um, Father,
may I have permission?
Heck, yeah!
Sweetie, come on over here
and give your dad a snuggle.
Yay!
There. Good girl!
This is nice.
You're so warm.
Oh, yeah?!
Who's the happiest man
to ever walk the face of this
or any other planet?
That's right: me!
[MARIE] If we can bring
down the Yatsukahagi,
the government won't have
a reason to use the Tall Wand.
Everyone knows what to do.
Let's get to work.
[ENGINEERS]
Right!
[HOUKO]
I'm sorry.
May I have a word?
I'll be right back.
Can you take over for me?
[KONRAD]
Heh.
[HOUKO] It's been such
a long while, Marie.
I went to your funeral,
of course.
[MARIE] At which they
buried an empty coffin.
I'm surprised to see
you still wear the watch.
[HOUKO]
Why wouldn't I?
After all, a friend
made it for me.
That makes it
a prized possession.
Hold on, you two
know each other?
[MARIE]
Yes, we do.
We met at a university in Europe
where I was spending
a year abroad.
I was slow.
I took the whole year,
but Marie was done in a month.
If I hadn't been
goofing off with you,
I'd have graduated in a week!
Oh? I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize
I was holding you back.
It was fun.
Not like I'm complaining
or anything.
Okay, I've been patient,
but I must know.
Will you tell me what you
want with the Pillar of Heaven?
I suppose.
How much do you know about
the situation in Akihabara
and the weapon
that's appeared there?
[HOUKO] From what I've heard,
Shiga is behind this mess.
It appears they are
attempting a coup d'état.
It seems that,
judging from its attack,
the weapon is most likely
electromagnetic in nature.
[MARIE]
Pretty impressive.
[HOUKO]
So, it's true, then?
Yes.
The electromagnetic pulse it
emitted magnetized Akihabara.
But, if we can find a way
to destroy the weapon
and demagnetize the city,
repairs would be possible.
[MARIE] Our plan is to
light a fire under its butt.
We're gonna turn up the heat,
to two thousand degrees.
[HOUKO]
Wow.
[MARIE] And the only
way we can do that,
is by using the
Pillar of Heaven.
I bet you'll never guess
whose idea this was.
[gasps]
Can't take it! Too much!
I'm gonna die
from all the happy!
No, Father, you can't die!
Don't worry, my dear!
With you here, I'm invincible!
Your papa will stay
by your side forever!
Ah... I'm so glad!
There, there!
I'll never leave you!
[ANCHOR giggles]
As you can see,
he is the biggest idiot
in the entire world.
Even so, he's an idiot who
knows how to get things done.
[HOUKO]
Hmm...
[NAOTO]
All right. I figured it out.
Let's do it, Marie.
Ready?
[HOUKO]
Uh...
[HOUKO] So, he truly analyzed
the Pillar of Heaven's
components using
nothing but his hearing?
[MARIE]
Sounds ridiculous, right?
[HOUKO]
Yes.
But, if you of all people
believe in him, so will I.
I do hate to say this, but his
existence poses a real threat.
He could endanger
the public safety.
Oh, the guy's
a hazard all right.
It might be wise if we
took steps to contain him.
Huh?!
Huh? Oh, god. Ow!
I had not realized
you had a death wish.
In that case, please feel free
to take half a step forward.
I'm more than happy
to offer you an end
that will be quick
and relatively painless.
You'll hardly feel a thing.
I won't let anyone hurt Father.
[sighs]
[HOUKO]
I apologize.
You may lower that now.
I mean him no harm.
[NAOTO]
Hey, RyuZU!
What's up with you
flying away like that?
I hit my head!
[RYUZU]
I am very sorry, Master. Truly.
It certainly wasn't my
intention to harm you, but,
perhaps the fall revitalized
your sluggish brain cells.
Aw... That was pretty harsh...
[ANCHOR]
Pain, pain, go away.
Come again another day!
He's a strange person.
You can say that again.
Well, I'm gonna
get back to work.
Wouldn't things
get completed faster
if he helped you instead
of lying around here?
[MARIE]
Honestly, Naoto's done more
than his fair share already.
Now it's time
for me to do my job.
I don't think I could stand
losing to someone like him.
Okay, everything
should be set here.
What's up AnchoR?
[ANCHOR]
Oh, hi, Mother.
Would you please stop
calling me that, already?
Why are you here?
Where are Naoto and RyuZU?
[ANCHOR] Father said there
was something important
he needed to
discuss with sister.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder what that's about.
Well, back to work.
[MARIE]
Hmm?
[MARIE sighs]
Hey, you know, if you're
not busy, you could help me.
Huh...?
[NAOTO laughs]
Amazing!
Look at the flowers!
There's an entire garden of 'em!
Master Naoto,
I'm very eager to know why
you've brought me
to a place like this.
Do you have a flower kink
I should know about?
[NAOTO] Call me crazy,
but I feel like you've avoided
looking at me
for the past few days.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Perhaps the more pertinent issue
here is the serious
over-inflation of your ego.
Do you expect me to spend
all of my time looking at you--
RyuZU.
Tell me.
I can't look at you.
I don't dare.
The destiny of this
planet is in these hands,
and because of
my severe failings,
they have suffered
irreparable harm.
I don't deserve your
forgiveness, but I am sorry.
You're safe, and that's
all that matters to me.
Why not try thinking of them
as badges of my masculinity?
[RYUZU]
I cannot.
I've proven myself to
be a worthless servant.
Please punish me.
[NAOTO]
All right, then.
Close your eyes.
[NAOTO]
Now, open them.
[RYUZU]
Huh?
Master Naoto?
What's this?
Is this ring my punishment?
Yeah. That's what it is.
I designed and made it myself.
Wearing this ring
is your punishment.
So, um, don't ever take it off.
[RYUZU] I'm afraid to inform
you this sort of gesture
is only appreciated when made
by a certain type of man.
Generally, somebody
who is better looking
and smarter than you are.
[NAOTO]
Eh heh... So ruthless.
Promise me, Master.
Swear you will never do
something like this again.
Of course, I'm sorry I--
This once. And never again.
[NAOTO]
Just this one time, RyuZU.
[RYUZU]
For better or worse.
In sickness and health.
Master Naoto.
[NAOTO] It's only a matter
of time before the Tall Wand
is deployed and the Yatsukahagi
is recharged and ready to fight.
Marie and the others
work relentlessly,
but their efforts
are nothing in the face
of Gennai's deep-rooted
delusions and hostility.
In spite of everything, though,
I refuse to give up hope!
Next time, "Theory of Y."
As much as it disgusts me
to say it to your face,
you're a genius, Marie!
All this time, it's been
your talent that's made
my random power
into something useful!