[CROWD chattering]
[NAOTO]
Heh.
Hello. Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen!
Sorry for interrupting your work
as mindless corporate slaves.
I realize that you're all busy
desperately trying to find
meaning in your
monotonous lives.
However, that's exactly
what I've come here
to help you with today!
It's time for this city
to start a new chapter,
and I've taken the liberty
of setting things
in motion for you.
Aw, yeah!
What's happening?
Something's up with Tokyo
Tower. It's freezing over!
[CROWD screaming]
[NAOTO]
Allow me to explain.
I have seized control
of all the gears
that comprise the
Akihabara Grid.
You do know what
that means, don't you?
All right, let's turn
things up a notch.
Come on, everybody! Yeah!
Yeah!
You ready?! This is gonna
be fun! Let's party!
[NAOTO]
Don't worry, AnchoR.
It won't be long now.
I promise. I will save you.
[MARIE] The giant weapon
is moving underground,
using the deepest floors
to make its way to Tokyo.
Here's the plan:
we get to Tokyo before it does,
take over a district,
and scare the residents away.
Then, the military can fight
the weapon in an empty city.
Not really the easiest
plan to pull off.
Security is gonna be tight.
Well, it's an interesting plan.
I'll give you that much.
But I don't see how we're
gonna find the manpower
to get it done.
[MARIE] Oh, that's not
going to be a problem.
Fortunately, I have
a friend or two
who would be more than
happy to help out.
[ENGINEER 1B]
Meister Marie!
Number 3340 through number 7990
are officially confirmed
as synchronized.
The connection checks
for all of the floors
have been taken care of as well.
Roger, thank you.
[HALTER]
This is Clock Tower Four.
As requested, we've
brought in all the material.
Meister Hannes asked me
to send you his regards.
[MARIE]
Great. Please thank him for me.
When you guys have everything
under control there,
rendezvous with Naoto.
[RYUZU] RyuZU here, checking
in from the Deep Underground.
I have confirmed the sortie
of the Tokyo military.
However, there is one concern.
[MARIE]
What happened?
[RYUZU]
I suspect their officers
may have suffered some
sort of brain damage.
That seems like the only thing
that could explain them
falling for a plan of yours.
[MARIE]
Oh, shut up! [growls]
Stupid, mouthy
piece of junk...
[KONRAD] It looks like we've
made it just in time.
Yes. We couldn't have done it
without you and your
team, Service Chief.
[laughs]
It was my pleasure, but you know
I am no longer a service chief.
Which is my fault.
I'm so sorry about that.
No apologies are necessary,
I assure you.
I couldn't be part of an
entertaining plot like this
if I were still in the Guild.
The Clock Tower controls
the city's basic functions,
its bones and muscles.
By controlling it,
you hope to also gain control
of the Core Tower,
the brain of the city.
I am always amazed by
the surprising things
you young people come up with.
Well, we should be able
to take it from here.
[MARIE] Then please control
the city's functions
according to Naoto's
instructions.
Thank you, everyone.
Your help means so much.
I don't know what I've
done to deserve it.
All right, enough of that.
It's not very complicated,
you earned our loyalty
simply by being who you are.
That's more than enough for us.
[gasps] That means a lot!
Hello and good evening,
ladies and gentlemen!
Sorry for interrupting
your work...
What's the idiot doing?
He looks like he's hosting
some cheesy game show.
[KONRAD]
You know, Meister Marie.
I've noticed something about you
in the time we've
worked together.
I hope you won't be offended
by me saying this,
but you're a terrible actor.
Huh?
Your true self is beautiful.
There's no need to keep it
hidden from the
world all the time.
What?! It isn't nice to tease
people, Meister Konrad.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to go.
[NAOTO]
They'll be here in nine seconds.
We're looking at two
silent helicopters
and one transport helicopter
loaded with 12 combat automata.
3... 2... 1... 0!
Take this!
[HALTER]
Heh.
[RYUZU] Sorry if I'm late.
Were you waiting long?
Not too bad for the debut
of a super villain
bent on world domination.
Well done, Naoto.
From what I'm hearing,
the military's begun
their underground battle
against the weapon.
I think it's safe to say
most of their focus
will be on that for a while.
All right. Then I guess it's
time for us to get going.
As planned,
the princess and I will help
the others get out of here,
and we'll all regroup
at the safe house later.
We'll leave AnchoR
to the two of you.
Try not to die or anything.
[NAOTO laughs]
I wasn't planning on it.
[RYUZU]
May I make a request?
I'd appreciate it if you would
accompany us, Miss Marie.
Why do you want me?
Master Naoto has devised
a plan he thinks
will let me defeat AnchoR
without harming her.
However, there is a chance
things could go wrong.
And if something does,
having you there could
make a difference.
You really think so?
All right. I honestly
don't think
there's anything that I
can do against AnchoR.
But if you want my help,
then you've got it.
I hoped you would say that.
Thank you, Miss Marie.
I'm starting to wonder
if she'll come.
[NAOTO] She will.
She knows that you're here.
She'll come because she
wants you to destroy her.
She's weak and
tired of fighting.
This isn't going to be easy.
I realize that.
But I know you can do it.
You can save her.
Can you hear me, AnchoR?
I hope so.
I know you are trapped, but your
voice reached my master.
I will do what he has asked.
Because I am his servant,
and your older sister.
I'm going to save you.
But not alone.
You will have to fight, too.
Do whatever you can
to protect yourself
from the thing that binds you.
Classification:
Initial-Y Series, Unit One.
One Who Follows... RyuZU.
Classification: Initial-Y
Series, Unit Four.
One Who Annihilates... AnchoR.
[RYUZU]
Initiating Chrono Hook.
Jumping from normal mode
to imaginary mode.
[ANCHOR]
Threat level category five.
Beginning shift to
differential 12.
Beginning imaginary output
through the Limitless Engine.
Now materializing
Perpetual Gear.
Following instructions.
Sighting.
Target: RyuZU...
...marked for destruction.
Come at me with everything
you have. I'm ready.
I'll show you what it means
to be an older sister.
Relative maneuver!
[ANCHOR]
Absolute maneuver!
Engage Mute Scream!
Engage Bloody Murder!
[ANCHOR growls]
[ANCHOR grunting]
[ANCHOR yelling]
With your limitless heat energy,
you tore open the
space-time continuum.
I was not designed for battle.
AnchoR was.
The difference between our
combat power is evident.
And only becoming more so.
However, that difference is not
always the deciding factor
in who wins a battle.
[ANCHOR yells]
[RYUZU grunts]
Severing space itself!
[ANCHOR yelling]
[RYUZU] She followed me
into imaginary time.
One hit from her,
and it'll be over.
Now, time to implement the plan.
[RYUZU]
If I were to fight AnchoR,
my chance of winning
would be nearly zero.
You don't need to win, though.
All you have to do is
destroy that ugly mask.
[RYUZU] Even if I
activate the Mute Scream,
the result would be the same.
[NAOTO] Then as far as I can
see, we only have one option.
You'll just have to
use me as a shield.
Absolutely not.
Are you offering to trade
your life for AnchoR's?
Do you truly think that is
an acceptable sacrifice?
[ANCHOR growling, yells]
A large-scale
dimension distortion!
[ANCHOR yells]
[RYUZU gasps]
[groans]
[grunts]
I have cut my offensive and
evasive potential in half.
But that is not what
matters right now.
[yelling]
My master has put
his faith in me.
Knowing that makes
anything possible.
I must succeed.
Technically, I'll be putting
my life on the line,
but I have no
intention of dying.
I won't sacrifice you, either,
nor do I mean to
give up on AnchoR.
I believe in you.
I know you can do this.
Besides, I'm pretty sure AnchoR
isn't able to kill humans.
When we were fighting
in the factory in Mie,
she didn't target me or Marie
once, despite having the chance.
There's too much at stake
to base a decision on that.
She isn't herself.
She's being controlled
by something else now.
But part of her remains.
[RYUZU]
Faster.
Faster. Hurry.
You have to move faster...
[RYUZU]
Master Naoto. I believe in you.
And you, too, AnchoR.
Little sister.
I believe in you, as well.
[ANCHOR growling]
[yells]
[gasps]
[ANCHOR groaning]
It wasn't easy, but you
fought well. I'm proud.
Now, I'm going to release you.
[RYUZU] Rest for a while.
You've earned it.
I have faith in AnchoR.
This whole time, I think she's
been desperately struggling
against whatever it is that's
holding her captive.
[ANCHOR gasping]
[NAOTO, MARIE grunting]
[NAOTO]
RyuZU! AnchoR!
Everything sounds
fine on the inside.
That's a relief!
Even so, I'll take
a closer look.
You go ahead and
wind RyuZU's gears.
[NAOTO]
Okay, great.
Thank you.
I can't believe it
worked like he planned.
Honestly, I expected you
to change things up
at the last minute
rather than actually use
Naoto as a human shield.
Master Naoto made it clear that
he has complete faith in me.
It was my duty to repay that
trust by keeping to the plan.
[MARIE]
Right. I can understand that.
You surpassed
expectations this time.
Color me impressed.
Miss Marie, you
have my gratitude
for agreeing to come
with us to face AnchoR.
The plan was a good one,
and I trust Master Naoto.
But it never hurts
to have insurance.
[NAOTO]
Hm?
Hold on, what in the
hell does that mean?
The sounds of battle
have died down,
so the military must be
wrapping things up.
[MARIE exhales]
Finally, some good news.
Well, let's get back
to the safe house
and see about repairing AnchoR.
[ANCHOR]
What is this?
It feels so familiar.
[MARIE] First there's
the Imaginary Gear,
and now there's
the Perpetual gear?!
I swear, the universe
is mocking me!
[NAOTO]
Hey! Quit yelling.
I need to fix her!
Give me the driver!
[MARIE]
I want some answers!
What the hell is this crazy gear
that no one's ever heard of?!
[NAOTO, MARIE]
Uh?
The Perpetual Gear is AnchoR's
unique functionality.
[NAOTO]
There! It's a special gear
that lets her do special things!
[MARIE] That's the worst
explanation I've ever heard!
[NAOTO, MARIE shouting]
[ANCHOR sighs]
I remember...
This is just like
when I was born.
It feels safe here.
[NAOTO laughs]
I'm glad you're finally
awake, AnchoR.
So, are you feeling better?
Father.
Mother.
Big sister.
I feel great.
[NAOTO, MARIE gasping]
I'm sorry.
As I had feared,
Miss Marie's skills
were insufficient to repair you.
[MARIE] My repairs were
impeccable, thank you!
But I wanna know what's
up with this whole
"Father, Mother" thing.
It's just plain creepy.
[NAOTO] If anyone was going to
be my wife, it would be RyuZU.
Calling me "Brother" would
probably make more sense.
[ANCHOR] Hm? I don't understand.
You're my daddy.
Oh my gah--! Go right ahead.
You can call me whatever
you want, AnchoR.
Mega-pervert...
Mother!
Hey, that's not fair!
Where's mine?!
Dial back the perv factor!
I remember you.
[RYUZU]
AnchoR.
[ANCHOR]
Huh?
[RYUZU]
Am I correct in assuming
you've not yet
registered a master?
[ANCHOR]
Yes.
[RYUZU] This is Naoto Miura.
He is my master.
Would you like for him to
be your master as well?
That depends on whether or not
he would like to be my master.
Oh, yeah, I'm totally
down for that!
All right, then.
[NAOTO]
Hm?
Requirement for
registering master.
Question. Tell me, who am I?
You will only be registered
as her master
if you are able to answer
that question correctly.
Make sure you take your
time and think carefully.
Who are you? That's easy.
Your name's AnchoR, and you're
a super cute automaton girl.
So, how was that?
Did I pass the test?
What the hell kind of
answer was that?!
Answer accepted.
What? That was a lame answer.
She's an Initial-Y Series unit
equipped with the
Perpetual Gear!
[NAOTO] AnchoR is a
one-of-a-kind automaton,
so beautifully constructed that
she's practically a work of art.
She's sweet, and shy, and
almost ridiculously cute.
She just so happens
to come equipped
with a few flashy weapons.
[ANCHOR]
I am Initial-Y series Unit Four.
"One who annihilates"... AnchoR.
Naoto Miura,
you will be my master.
I await your command.
Master Naoto, after she has
completed master registration,
AnchoR is not permitted
to exercise free will.
As Miss Marie pointed out,
AnchoR is first and
foremost a weapon.
Do weapons require
consciousness?
That's not what I
was trying to imply.
You have a choice to make.
As her master, the decision will
fall to you, and you alone.
Think carefully.
[NAOTO] AnchoR, what
would you like to do?
Can you think about it and
tell me what you want?
Certainly, Master.
I would like to perform
the tasks I was created for
as "One Who Annihilates."
[NAOTO] Mm-mm. I'm not
talking about duties.
Not what you're supposed to do,
but what you want to do.
[ANCHOR]
Yes, Master.
However, that answer
is impossible.
At present, this unit's
free will is locked.
Okay. We'll have to
unlock it, then.
Huh?
Yes, Master. Requesting details.
Is this an order to
act however I wish?
According to my own judgment?
Unlock everything
that is preventing you
from having free will.
Consider that my official order.
You understand?
You are allowed to do
anything you want.
I'm not going to stop you.
Wait, anything... that I want?
[NAOTO]
Of course!
I want permission...
Huh?
[ANCHOR]
I want permission... to cry.
May I?
Go ahead, AnchoR. Cry.
[ANCHOR cries]
I want further permission.
Okay.
May I please... touch you?
Yeah, sure.
[ANCHOR]
And may I... apologize?
You don't have to, but you
can if it's what you want.
[ANCHOR cries]
I'm sorry. So sorry.
Sorry... Sorry.
[NAOTO grunts]
[crying continues] I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
[ANCHOR sobs]
You can be a real
jerk sometimes,
you do know that, right?
If that is how your feeble brain
interprets what has
happened today,
then I'm afraid I'm
unable to help you.
So, I don't have to
destroy things anymore?
Nope. You don't have to do
anything you don't want to.
[giggles]
[RYUZU] Master Naoto, I don't
know where your path will lead,
but wherever it does, I believe
I am meant to follow.
[MARIE] Our plan to protect
the capital and save AnchoR
appears to have been a success.
Until we realize the giant
weapon has not been deactivated.
It emerges from underground,
equipped with the forbidden
power of electromagnetism,
a force that may disrupt the
workings of the Clockwork Planet
and alter the destiny
of the human race.
Next time: "Yatsukahagi."
Everything. Literally everything
has been destroyed.