[water running]
[GINOZA] The body found
at the crime scene was
Enforcer Yamatoya
from Division Two.
It's the work
of a Dominator.
And the one who
pulled the trigger
was Inspector Shisui,
also from Division Two.
After the enforcement, she
took Yamatoya's Dominator...
...and just disappeared.
[AKANE] An Inspector's
gone missing.
[GINOZA] To be honest,
I'm stumped.
This is all we have
to go on for now.
♪
[AKANE] WC.
[MIKA] I typed up my report
about our pursuit and
apprehension of the bombing
suspect the other day.
In it, I made sure to
include my analysis of
where I think we went wrong.
Please see that
it gets to the Chief.
This is way out of line.
Mm?
It's not a report.
It's an attack on an Inspector
who did things differently
than you would've.
[MIKA] Keep reading,
Mr. Ginoza.
I had some choice
words for you, as well.
Don't think I'd leave out
the part about one Enforcer
aiming his Dominator at another!
[GINOZA] You know, Inspector,
going by the book doesn't always
yield the best results.
You should keep that in mind.
I'm not looking for
opinions from Enforcers.
ou may wanna go easy on him,
Inspector Shimotsuki.
If you don't mind me saying,
he used to be an Inspector, too.
[KUNIZUKA] His advice
comes from experience,
and it could be helpful.
Yayoi, I--
It's because he quit
being an Inspector,
[MIKA] that I don't wanna
hear what he has to say.
Yeah, everything in this
report looks good to me.
Huh?
[GINOZA] Are you sure?
I authorized your
use of the Dominator,
so they can't punish
you for it, Mr. Ginoza.
[AKANE] I'm off to
question Kitazawa now.
Who's doing the Holo analysis?
[KUNIZUKA] That would be me.
[AKANE] I'd like Mr.
Hinakawa to take over for you.
Uh. You want him?
You can handle it.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, sure. No problem.
Ms. Shimotsuki, please
work with the others,
and decipher the message
we found at the crime scene.
[AKANE] I'm leaving things
in your hands, okay?
[door opens]
[door closes]
♪
[SAKUYA] Inspector Tsunemori!
[AKANE] Mr. Kitazawa, your
Crime Coefficient didn't rise
until immediately
after the fourth bombing
the other day when
it suddenly spiked.
But... normally it'd
be the other way around.
[AKANE] How did you manage
to keep your Psycho-Pass
so clear the whole time you
were planning these attacks?
Answer me.
[laughs]
Why are you laughing?
My Hue is--
It's crystal clear.
It can't ever, ever get clouded.
I've always been so
clear, clear, clear.
[KITAZAWA] All thanks to him.
He always looks out for me.
He's my guardian angel.
[AKANE] "He"?
Why'd you use a Holo
to fake the hostage?
Was it just to
lure out the MWPSB?
Huh? What Holo?
What're you talking about?
[SAKUYA] I'm talking about the
Hologram you used to make us
think you'd taken a hostage.
[KITAZAWA]
No! That was all him!
He made me clear!
I'll fight to the ends
of the Earth for him!
I would die for him!
[KITAZAWA crying]
[AOYANAGI] We're getting
nowhere with Kitazawa.
We interrogated him, too, and
got the same results as you.
He just kept raving
on and on about
his imaginary accomplice.
This guy's nuts.
[AKANE] Raving.
The cymatic scan didn't detect
anyone else there with him,
so he had to be working
alone. Simple as that.
Where are you with
Inspector Shisui?
Have you found anything yet?
[AOYANAGI] It's the weirdest
thing. Although it fades
in and out, we've been able
to track her GPS signal.
Meanwhile, her Dominator
has stayed online
throughout and somehow, it's
still properly authenticated.
[AKANE] So, in other words,
all of Inspector Shisui's
actions must have been
sanctioned by Sibyl.
[AOYANAGI] Yeah, that's
Chief Kasei's read on it, too.
That everything
Shisui's done up to
this point's been totally legal.
I don't know. Maybe
she's conducting her own
Sibyl-approved investigation.
If we're to have
any faith at all
in our Dominators' judgment,
that's the only possibility.
You think Mr.
Yamatoya's enforcement
was justified, too?
[AOYANAGI] What if he
tried to make a run for it?
That'd be more
than enough cause to
shoot an Enforcer, wouldn't it?
[AKANE] Yeah, but then
why did Inspector Shisui
immediately disappear?
[AOYANAGI] Maybe she had to
do the enforcement in secret?
And all she could do
to try to key us in
was leave a cryptic message.
W-C.
[AOYANAGI] Yep.
Ms. Aoyanagi.
Do you really think
that's what happened?
Well, do you have
any better ideas, Akane?
What if--
[AOYANAGI] Hm?
[AKANE] What if
someone else was there?
Someone besides the MWPSB?
And what if that's
who killed Yamatoya?
And then wrote WC on the wall?
[AOYANAGI] Oh, come on.
You believe what Kitazawa said?
I'm saying that
it is possible.
[sighs]
[AOYANAGI] There's no such thing
as a person the Sibyl System
can't see and track.
We're MWPSB investigators.
[AOYANAGI]
We're not ghost hunters.
[door closes]
[GINOZA] When I see the phrase,
"WC," I think a "water closet,"
a-k-a, a toilet.
[MIKA] Huh? I see that
and think, "World Cup."
"WC" could also
stand for "wild caught."
An animal captured in
nature rather than farm-raised?
That makes no sense.
Says the guy who thinks
it refers to a toilet.
[MIKA] Is that your way
of saying you gotta go?
Just go, you don't
need a bathroom pass.
[GINOZA] No! I'm just
throwing out ideas.
Mm!
♪
Hmph.
[SAKUYA] You're not gonna
get rid of your stress
by standing there... Inspector.
[SAKUYA] Didn't have
a chance to say it.
Thanks for letting me pop in
during the Kitazawa
interrogation.
Officially, my conflict
of interest should've
prevented me from taking part.
Do you mean the
Togane Foundation?
[SAKUYA] Yeah. I don't
know what you've heard,
but OW Pharmaceutical,
the company that
makes LACOUSE, and that
Kitazawa was targeting...
Well, it's run by
the Togane family.
My family.
[AKANE] I'm aware.
But I don't think of you
as someone who lets
his emotions cloud
his judgment during
an investigation.
So I saw more benefit
than risk to letting you
join me in the
room with Kitazawa.
After all, you were
once a therapist,
right, Mr. Togane?
[SAKUYA] You used your knowledge
of my prior work background
to make a quick decision.
You're quite
perceptive about people.
Oh, man. This is good.
[SAKUYA] You left the Holo
verification to Hinakawa,
in order to take
advantage of his own
skilled background,
as a Holo designer.
[exhales]
Ah, that's
too much credit.
[AKANE] I'm just
delegating, that's all.
Tch.
What is it?
[SAKUYA] Your ghost is real.
[gasps]
I'm with you. It makes sense.
[AKANE] Yeah, but there's
no proof. And I'm well aware
how hard it is to get
around town without being
noticed by a cymatic
scan or Drone.
But on the flip side,
Kitazawa doesn't
appear to be delusional.
It's just that it's
hard to imagine someone
like him acting
by himself.
Right. Someone else has
gotta be pulling the strings.
[SAKUYA] Otherwise
it doesn't track.
[HINAKAWA panting]
Inspector! Inspector!
[AKANE] Mr. Hinakawa,
what's wrong?
That Holo, it's incredible!
[SHION] Yeah, the movement, the
details; it's very elaborate.
[HINAKAWA] This design uses
a massive amount of data.
If you just
want to trick people,
you don't need this
many layers of detail.
[AKANE] What's the first step to
creating one this sophisticated?
[HINAKAWA]
Well, you'd need a model.
Ms. Karanomori.
Already on it.
[SHION] No face matches in the
Ministry of Welfare's database.
[HINAKAWA] Right. Using an
existing person is hard,
mainly because she could
always bump into the Holo.
However, use someone
who's not alive...
You mean use
a dead model?
Okay, then. Let me try
a different database.
[SHION] We've got one deceased
individual whose features match.
Looks like she bought the
farm in an airplane crash
fifteen years ago.
Good thinking, Sho.
Wait, that's interesting.
It says that that girl
was eight when she died.
[SHION] Yeah, that Holo
sure didn't look like
an eight-year-old.
Whoever created it
must've taken the
dead girl's image
and run an age progression
program to extrapolate
what she'd look like if
she were still alive today,
fifteen years later.
I don't get it.
No matter how you look at it,
this is all way too elaborate.
[SHION] Whoever did this
could just be the kinda guy
who likes to go all out.
I see that type more
often than you'd think.
[digital beeping]
[AOYANAGI] Inspector
Tsunemori. Where are you?
[AKANE] The Analysis Lab.
Why, something happen?
[AOYANAGI] Kitazawa's
Crime Coefficient.
It's dropped so
low he's no longer
a target for enforcement.
[gasps]
♪
[AKANE] How could this happen?
[GINOZA] Yeah. For a Crime
Coefficient high enough to
necessitate enforcement
to suddenly fall this low.
[SAKUYA] This is
completely unprecedented.
Heh. I owe
everything to him.
I knew that he'd
come to see me in here.
He made me clear again.
Check the visitor log.
I already looked. He's
making the whole thing up
just to mess with us.
[AOYANAGI] According
to the security footage,
the only person who's
been to see him was
a therapist from the
MWPSB's medical agency.
No one else has gone
in or out of there.
[AKANE] I'll need to
speak with that therapist.
It's been quite a while.
Under normal circumstances,
I couldn't bring
myself to face you.
Well, it's not like
any of this is your fault.
Can you tell us
what sort of therapy
you tried with Kitazawa?
And was there anything
out of the ordinary
about your session with him?
[THERAPIST] I simply
provided my usual services.
Nothing more, nothing less.
If you check the
security cameras,
you can see for yourself.
Of course.
I'm sure you're right.
You look like you
haven't been sleeping.
Stressed about work?
[THERAPIST] You know,
sleep's very important.
You should make time
for some relaxation.
Yeah, yeah, I know,
but sadly, that is
easier said than done.
One more thing.
It's outside my area
of medical expertise,
but smoking really is
bad for your health.
[gasps]
[THERAPIST] You should quit.
♪
This is ridiculous.
[KUNIZUKA] Why are we
transferring a monster who's
guilty of some
pretty serious crimes
to a general medical facility?
[GINOZA] Well, our hands
were tied the second
his Psycho-Pass turned clear.
There are rules.
[MIKA] Inspector, why'd you
let Division Two transfer him?
I mean, we're the ones who
captured him in the first place!
Oh. I just wanted to
go home early today.
Seriously?
I'll have the report
finished by tomorrow.
That therapist earlier
scared me a little.
He said if I didn't rest,
my Hue would get clouded.
Well, have a
good night, everyone.
[MIKA] Hey! Wait!
[GINOZA] Once Kitazawa's
checked into that facility,
he'll be out of our jurisdiction
and totally off limits to us.
This transfer's the last
opportunity to question him.
Yeah, no kidding.
That's my point!
[GINOZA] Tsunemori's
probably just trying to take
Aoyanagi's feelings
into account.
Try to understand.
♪
Is this enough to
get the smell to stick?
Secondhand smoke is extremely
hazardous to your health!
Please give it a rest.
I know it's bad.
Hey, I've got an idea!
Why don't we clean your room
for a change? That'll
cheer you up in no time!
[AKANE] All right, all right.
[CANDY] Oh my. It looks
as though the wall
has been scratched somehow.
Would you like me
to contact a repairman?
[AKANE] A scratch?
Here.
[AKANE gasps]
No, it can't be!
[phone ringing]
[MIKA] Inspector Tsunemori!
Kitazawa's escaped!
[police sirens]
[MIKA] It happened
in the Tama Area.
Division Two was
trying to get info out of
the suspect on where
he made the bombs.
He led them to a
small rental office
in the back of the KT Building.
[MIKA] He slashed Inspector
Aoyanagi with a knife
he'd hidden in the
room ahead of time,
then retrieved some
pre-constructed bombs
and fled before we even
had a chance to respond.
He's still on the run.
How are you feeling now?
No way. You can't do that
and maintain a
clear Psycho-Pass.
[MIKA] We've advised
local residents to evacuate
and we've set up traffic
roadblocks on all streets.
Considering the amount
of time that's passed,
and that he's likely on foot,
we think Kitazawa's
still in the area.
[AKANE] There's a narrow
alley behind the Building.
And down that is an
entrance to the sewers.
[MIKA] That's true.
But it's locked tight.
I don't see any way
he'd be able to access it.
[AKANE] Yeah,
but what if someone had
unlocked it beforehand?
[MIKA] Again, I don't
see how that's possible.
There's a scanner
right at the entrance.
Even if Kitazawa
did have an accomplice
to pick the lock
for him, that guy would
have been spotted immediately.
[KITAZAWA] Heh.
I see Kitazawa approaching
the sewer entrance.
And I have bad news, guys.
It's been unlocked.
No way! But how?
[KUNIZUKA]
We need to intercept him.
We're too far away to catch up.
[digital beeping]
Don't worry;
we'll take care of it.
[GINOZA] Tsunemori?
[KUNIZUKA] You already figured
out Kitazawa's escape route?
Escaping in the middle
of a transfer isn't easy.
I can't see him
doing it without help.
Besides, there's
no way he could have
planted that weapon
while still in custody.
[GINOZA] So in other words?
[AKANE] There's no doubt
in my mind that someone on
the outside guided Kitazawa
through his entire escape.
Someone who moves without being
detected by cymatic scans.
[AKANE] And this person
is bringing his war
right to the MWPSB.
[KITAZAWA running breaths]
[KITAZAWA] Keep running.
Keep running.
[panting]
♪
[AKANE] Stop right there!
Don't! I've planted
another explosive!
If you come even one step
closer, I will set it off!
No, wait.
Give up, Kitazawa!
[KITAZAWA] What? You
think this is all just
a bluff or something?
Stop patronizing me!
That's enough!
Ah...!
[tires screech]
[GINOZA] The hell.
[KITAZAWA]
I've got one more bomb.
My friend went to a lot of
trouble helping me escape.
So, I don't have
time to stay and chat!
You said you admired me!
That my goals were
noble! Didn't you?
What I said means nothing,
now that you've
pressed that button.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient
is three hundred fifty-seven.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Inspector. Just say the word.
[KITAZAWA] Kamui, I failed.
And after you went through
the trouble of making me clear.
Kamui?
[AKANE] Who is that?
Hey. Tell me
something, will you?
What color am I?
[gasps]
[AOYANAGI] What color?
Let's call it...
"raw sewage red."
I get it now.
[AKANE] The message.
I know what it means.
[MAN] The Public Safety
Bureau is made of fools.
He could have been
made clear again.
[MAN] He still
could have been saved.
[MAN] Akane Tsunemori.
I thought you, of all
of them, would understand.