[KASEI]
And that's that.
The true nature of
the Sibyl System which
maintains order in our society.
[MIKA nervous exhales]
Thank you, Chief.
That's so incredible!
It's such a wise decision--
having the criminally
asymptomatic judge others.
Because of this
one fantastic idea,
we have a system that
protects every one of us!
The Inspector
unconditionally accepts what
the state determines to be
the right course of action.
She really is the very
model of an ideal citizen,
wouldn't you agree, son?
Yes, and her Hue still
remains crystal clear.
I'd say that makes
her your opposite.
[MIKA clapping]
[PUPPY yelps]
[MISAKO]
This boy is historic.
He's the only successful
example we have of a
criminally asymptomatic person
being created, artificially.
Mama!
You're such a remarkable
boy, you know that?
[panting]
[squelching]
You did a good job, son!
[MISAKO clapping]
Aah.
[SAKUYA] Hmm.
[MIKA clapping]
I'm so moved by
everything I've heard.
Ours really is an
ideal code of law.
Mother, if she's someone
who can help keep you pure,
then there's no reason
for us to color her.
We can use her in a
different kind of way.
Oh? And how's that?
Against Akane Tsunemori.
We can color her black.
Huh?
[AKANE] Mr. Saiga. Suppose
there's a perfect being
that judges people.
Is it possible to
then judge that being?
A perfect being, huh?
Are you referring to a god?
What you just described
is the "omnipotence paradox."
[SAIGA] Here you go.
Can an omnipotent
being use his powers to
create a stone so heavy
even he can't lift it?
That's a paradox.
[SAIGA] Right. If a god with
infinite power creates a rock
that he cannot lift,
he ceases to possess
infinite power the very
moment the rock is created.
And also, if he can't
create the heavy rock,
then he's not
all-powerful to start with.
In either scenario, it only
leads to a contradiction,
as does your initial question.
If the being who casts judgment
is perfect and infallible,
then it still must
judge itself as well.
Then is there any
solution to the paradox?
You can either find
a mistake somewhere
in the assumption,
process, or conclusion.
Or from the other
direction, you prove that
one of those three things
is actually correct.
Find a correct answer,
or find a mistake.
Hmmm.
I'm wondering what got
you thinking about all this.
[SAIGA] I thought we
were just gonna have
a little chat about Sibyl.
[sighs]
[AKANE] "WC." "What color?"
You want to know
the color of Sibyl,
and also the color of yourself.
But what happens
if those two colors
turn out to be the same?
She asks me about
this world's god.
[SAIGA] I should tell her
these topics are dangerous
and to avoid
them at all costs,
and yet, I can't
wait to hear her answer.
[SAIGA] Huh. I'm pathetic.
Dependence.
[SAIGA] So this is
how Kamui's sympathizers
must have felt about their lot.
[footsteps]
Huh?
[MASUZAKI] Who are you?
[KASEI] It's been quite a
long time, Doctor Masuzaki.
I believe our last meeting may
have been at Kirito's surgery.
[MASUZAKI] Mmm.
I don't understand.
You're still alive?
Doctor Togane?
[KASEI chuckles]
[AKANE] How do I solve
the omnipotence paradox?
[AKANE] Maybe the omnipotent
being doesn't have to be
omnipotent every single moment.
[AKANE] After creating
a rock he can't lift,
he then redefines
the parameters--
either lightens the rock
or strengthens himself.
There's still nothing
he can't do by the end.
That seems to
be the workaround
the Sibyl System's been
using. At least until now.
[AKANE] All this time,
by absorbing the
criminally asymptomatic,
the people it couldn't judge,
it's been able to
maintain its perfection.
But now, Kamui's created
a new type of people
who are artificially
asymptomatic,
through his Psycho-Pass
manipulation.
In doing so,
he may have eliminated
that solution to the paradox.
[AKANE] And then, Kamui
takes it a step further,
and poses the question,
"Is Sibyl capable
of judging Sibyl?"
Because if it
can't judge itself,
Sibyl becomes an
exception to its own rules.
So like with society's
other exceptions,
Sibyl's only answer would be
to absorb Sibyl into itself.
And of course,
since that's impossible,
the perfection would be ruined.
Okay, so what if
Sibyl can judge itself?
That would avoid the
self-absorption paradox.
[AKANE] But if it could
judge itself, that would mean
the minds that make up Sibyl
weren't criminally
asymptomatic, after all.
And that would mean Sibyl
failed to judge those people
when it could have
in the first place.
[AKANE] I see just one
solution to this paradox.
[digital beeping]
[gasps]
Masuzaki had to have
been executed by a Dominator.
Well, it looks
like I've lost another
good conversation partner.
Since the murder
weapon was a Dominator,
[SAKUYA] it's safe to assume
this was Kamui's handiwork.
[gasps]
[SHION] Going back to around
twenty-two hundred hours
last night, the security
footage from the MWPSB's
cameras has been overwritten
with video from an earlier date.
So wait, now
they've managed to
get into the
MWPSB's system?
Yeah, and they weren't
all that stealthy about it.
They left some
sort of trace behind.
As you'll see,
it's pretty bizarre.
Doctor Masuzaki knew too much.
[SAKUYA] We have to
eliminate anyone who
knows my mother's secret.
So it really was
you who did this.
What's the matter?
Are you scared of me now?
[SAKUYA] There's no reason for
you to feel frightened here.
After all, I'm still
my mother's child.
That is to say,
the son of Sibyl.
[SAKUYA] My will
is society's will.
My eyes are society's eyes.
You've taken a vow,
Inspector, to respect the law,
which means you have no choice.
You can't defy me,
no matter how much
you may despise
latent criminals.
Fine, then what
do you want from me?
[SAKUYA] There's something
I'd like you to look into.
Find out where
Tsunemori's grandmother is.
Huh?
We'll help the Inspector
get to a place where
she can assume the role
of Kamui's executioner.
Hey. I'm concerned about this.
[KUNIZUKA] A Ministry
of Land, Infrastructure,
Transport and Tourism
official's been holding
a lot of meetings lately.
His name's Koichi Kuwashima.
He's twenty-three.
Already has a reputation as
a promising young
hope within the MLIT.
And after a little
digging, guess what I found.
[KUNIZUKA] He went to
the same elementary school
as the kids from
that plane crash,
except he switched schools
just one week before
they went on their
doomed field trip.
[SAKUYA] So this guy escaped
getting killed in the accident?
That connects him.
It's something.
Yeah, and that's not all.
Kuwashima's a shareholder
in the company that
manages the port where
Kamui's hideout was.
So if he's an official at
the MLIT, and we assume that
he's working with Kamui,
it would help to explain
[AKANE] how Kamui's
been able to get close to
so many different dignitaries.
We've got a lot of questions
to ask this gentleman.
Find me his current location.
Let's go. I want Koichi
Kuwashima in custody right away.
♪
To the beginning of
a great new society!
[KUWASHIMA] Cheers.
Sorry you
had to do that.
Oh, it's fine.
"Master of ceremonies"
does suit me well.
I always enjoy the charade.
[chuckles] We're
really going to do it!
We can finally eliminate
the Sibyl System now.
[MALE OFFICIAL C] Well believe
it! Right now we stand
at a crossroads of history!
Thanks to your
ingenuity, these people can
all deny Sibyl without worry.
That alone is a revolution.
[sighs] Let's just
get this over with.
I can't stand it.
Right.
[clap]
[MALE OFFICIAL C] Uh-huh.
Thank you for
your help, my friends.
You all did a wonderful job
fulfilling your roles tonight.
[MALE OFFICIALS murmur]
[KUWASHIMA] Gentlemen!
To conclude this meeting,
we now present you
with the main dish.
We hope you enjoy.
Huh?
[MALE OFFICIAL A screams]
[MALE OFFICIALS scream]
Ah!
[MALE OFFICIAL D moans worried]
[commotion]
[MALE OFFICIAL B]
You sick bastard!
[WOMAN retches]
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient
over two hundred fifty.
Enforcement action required.
You poor little thing.
Why--Why're you
doing this to us?
I could ask you
the very same thing.
You people ignored the
chaos of the Season of Hell.
You took advantage
of its victims' pain
to gain your current positions.
Furthermore, in order to
keep yourselves in the clear,
you kept playing with
other people's lives.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient:
three hundred thirteen.
Enforcement mode.
Lethal Eliminator.
Stop! Help me, Kamui!
I'm sorry, but your true
color has now been revealed.
No! Stop it!
[MALE OFFICIALS yelling]
Inspector Shisui's Dominator
is online and it's in use.
[SHION] Location:
Central Hall, Chiyoda Ward.
That's the same
place we're going to.
Seal off the whole
area with Drones! Hurry!
[police sirens]
[KUWASHIMA] Thank you, friend.
Now I'm able to
apologize to them.
It's not something you
should feel responsible for.
[KUWASHIMA] I almost became
a latent criminal as a child.
All because of the guilt
I felt in missing the crash.
Social order in our country
is maintained by Sibyl.
Because of that arrogance,
one hundred and eighty-four
children were killed that day.
And I was about to disappear
from society myself.
I won't let your
Hue get clouded.
Now. Let's go
witness the judgment.
I'm not able to
give people the kind of
guidance that you can.
[KUWASHIMA]In the end,
I'm really no different
than these guys. I'm
just one of those saved.
[KUWASHIMA'S cell phone ringing]
[KUWASHIMA] I see.
Do the rest as we planned.
I was skeptical
about that information,
that said, we just
pulled our trump card.
[KAMUI] I thought I said
that wasn't necessary?
[KUWASHIMA] Akane
Tsunemori is the biggest
potential threat to our plans.
We're better off
containing her movements.
[KAMUI] That wouldn't
be enough to stop her.
[KAMUI] She keeps her Crime
Coefficient low no matter
how stressful a
situation she's in,
which is exactly why I want
her to see the judgment.
[KUWASHIMA] Then we can test
the Inspector tonight with this.
[KAMUI] Koichi.
[KUWASHIMA] Go, Kirito.
I'll stay behind
and fulfill my duties.
[SHISUI] Hey, guys! MWPSB!
Koichi. You've always
been a loyal friend to me,
even in those years
before we were reunited.
[KUWASHIMA] My pleasure.
Now go and change the world.
[KUWASHIMA] The time is finally
right. Let Sibyl be judged.
[police and ambulance sirens]
[KUWASHIMA] Well, that was fast.
Gotta hand it to the MWPSB.
Where is Kamui?
[KUWASHIMA]
Oh, you just missed him.
[gasps]
[KUWASHIMA] But coming
here hasn't been
a waste of your time.
In his stead, I offer up
these people for judgment.
♪
[gasps]
[MIKA] Hhhuuugh--
It's awful. I don't believe it!
♪
[GINOZA] How could a person
do something like this?
[KUWASHIMA] This is
a true vision of Hell.
Yes. Enough to make
your blood curdle.
[SAKUYA] So is all
of this Kamui's doing?
[KUWASHIMA] Don't be ridiculous.
It's those dead bureaucrats
in there who couldn't keep
their Psycho-Passes clear
without resorting to
playing these kinds of games.
So, what? You're saying
they deserved this punishment?
[KUWASHIMA] Those people
burning are all illegal aliens.
For whatever reasons,
they fled their own countries.
[KUWASHIMA] Officials used sweet
talk to gather them together,
and then toyed with them.
[MALE OFFICIALS screaming]
[KUWASHIMA] They committed
countless unspeakable acts
just like this, but then,
always, when their
Crime Coefficients shot up,
they'd seek help from Kamui.
And for that, Kamui
unleashed his wrath upon them.
[KUWASHIMA] These people who
were turned into livestock,
they themselves
begged to be burned!
Because they couldn't
just go back to
who they were
before all of this.
Any more than
Kamui, himself, can.
♪
[AKANE] Could you please
come with us, Mr. Kuwashima.
[KUWASHIMA] Of course.
But before I do--
here.
♪
[AKANE] Uh!
[AKANE grunts]
What did you do?
[GINOZA] Tsunemori!
[AKANE] What did you do?
[GINOZA] Hey! Calm down!
What did you do?
[AKANE grunting]
[GINOZA] Kunizuka!
[transfixed exhale]
[KUNIZUKA] Aoi Tsunemori.
What?
[MIKA shaky breathing]
♪
[sighs] I'm Jouji Saiga.
[SAIGA] I'll be your
interrogator for today.
There's a peculiar
rumor about me
that I've never
been able to shake.
They say I can cloud
a person's Psycho-Pass
merely by speaking with him.
I can honestly say this
is the first time ever
that I've wanted to put
that theory to the test
and see if I really can.
[SAIGA] What is it you want?
Your friend Akane Tsunemori's
closing in on Kamui.
[KUWASHIMA] She's become a
nuisance, a problem for us.
So all that I want
is for her to behave.
Are you speaking
for yourself here?
[SAIGA] Because I thought
Kamui wanted Tsunemori
to come after him.
[SAIGA] Where is he now?
[KUWASHIMA] In the
bowels of this city.
♪
[GINOZA] The subway?
Yeah, that's right.
Security cameras picked up
Kamui fifteen minutes ago.
Who are the
people with him?
[SHION] Huh. I'm not seeing
a common thread anywhere.
[digital tones]
[SAIGA] Check and see if any of
them lost a loved one in either
a traffic accident or a
plane crash fifteen years ago.
I'm on it. [gasps]
Ryosuke Hasebe lost
both parents in a collision
caused by a
defective runway light.
Shinichi Ogi's
older brother was killed
in a rear-ender when a
crossing gate malfunctioned.
And Yukiho Oura's father
died in a plane crash, too.
Another one.
[SAIGA] As I thought.
The tie that binds them all...
[SAIGA] is the Season of Hell.
Up to this point,
Kamui has deliberately chosen
to operate like a ghost,
but now he's made
a brazen move out into the open.
Which means...
♪
[AKANE] He's trying to settle
things once and for all.
[door opens]
♪
Are you one of my
granddaughter's colleagues?
[SAKUYA chuckles]
Yes.
♪
[squelch]