♪
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[SHISUI screams]
[MAN] If one wants to purify
her Hue, there are times when
excitement is the best approach.
Far better than trying
to maintain constant calm.
[SHISUI] Wh-Who's there?
[SHISUI whimpers]
No!
[MAN] Oh, I am sorry about
that. But I really needed
to acquire an
Inspector's eye for things.
[SHISUI whimpers]
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
one hundred twenty-nine.
Enforcement action required.
[SHISUI crying]
[SHISUI] No...
[MAN] Your fear will
end soon, Mizue Shisui.
To make up for
removing your eye,
I will make your Hue clear.
[MAN] I understand
the suffering you endure.
The constant anxiety that
every time a crime occurs,
your Hue will worsen.
The gnawing fear
that the Enforcers might
turn on you at any time.
But the real thing
that's holding you back,
Inspector Shisui, is you.
You have the strength
to adapt, to mold yourself
into who society
wants you to be.
But that--that is
exactly why you do suffer.
[SHISUI whimpering]
[SHISUI crying]
[MAN] Now I'm going to release
you. Not only from yourself,
but also from the Sibyl System.
I want you to remember.
Remember the real you.
The one who's been locked
away inside for so long.
[DOMINATOR] Crime
Coefficient, eighty-five.
The Target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement action
no longer required.
The trigger is now locked.
[SHISUI] Who are you?
[MAN] Me?
My name is Kirito Kamui.
And together we can make
this whole world clear.
So clear that it
becomes invisible.
[GINOZA] Oh, man.
This place is a real mess.
[AKANE] I'm sorry, I wasn't
exactly expecting company.
Inspector, there's
still plenty of time to
save your Hue with
the right therapy.
Are you insinuating
that I vandalized
my own home, Inspector?
[GINOZA] The scans for the
area didn't detect anyone
remotely suspicious.
So explain this--
if this is a crime scene,
where is the criminal?
[AKANE] You think I
did this, too, Ginoza?
That I'm losing my mind
and writing strange
messages on walls?
If you really think that,
then point your Dominator
at me and check
my Hue right now.
[GINOZA] That's not--
[MIKA] And what are you doing?
Didn't you just hear
this isn't a crime scene.
It's true that there
are no signs of a break-in.
But equally true is that
there's no reason to think
the Inspector's losing her mind.
[SAKUYA] So we're faced
with what appear to be
two impossible scenarios.
However, one of them
definitely happened,
so I say, all
things being equal...
we must give the benefit of
the doubt to the Inspector.
Thank you, Mr. Togane.
[MIKA] According to the rules...
we should move your family.
Preferably into a safe house,
under constant
Drone protection.
Though, it seems
like busy work to me.
I doubt there's
any actual threat.
I guess my parents
can be relocated to
the nearest MWPSB facility.
That might be too difficult
for my grandmother, though.
Difficult how?
She can't move much.
Not on her own.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Hang a right
at the next exit.
[MIKA] But the
MWPSB's straight ahead?
[AKANE] I need to
make a stop first.
[AKANE] You could've
dropped me off and left.
[MIKA] What business
does an Inspector have
at an isolation facility?
I have a duty to get the answer.
Well now. I didn't
expect to see you today.
[MIKA] Jouji Saiga?
Do you know him?
Yes, I do.
His record at least.
I've seen the file.
[MIKA] Sorry, Inspector.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm going back to the office.
[AKANE] Uh...
Looks like I scared her off.
Couldn't get away
from me fast enough.
I'm sorry.
[SAIGA] The clearer one's
Psycho-Pass, the more he or she
lives in fear of having
it clouded by others.
She was worried her
Crime Coefficient would
shoot up just
from talking to me.
If she's read my file,
it's a logical concern.
Is that something
you really believe?
[SAIGA] If you think about it,
the irrational one here is you.
Why aren't you afraid?
Because after the
last time that we spoke,
Mr. Saiga, my Psycho-Pass
never got clouded.
Hmmm. Well, fair enough.
So then, what
brings you here today?
[AKANE] Please, be honest.
Do I appear sane to you?
Hmm.
[SAIGA] A message
no one could've written
scrawled on a wall
no one had access to?
Except for one person
who did have access.
That's true. If it's
in your own apartment,
then it'd be simple enough
to write whatever you want
without it showing
up in the logs.
I see now.
You wanna use me as some
sort of mirror, is that right?
If that's what you're
looking for, you should ask
somebody healthier
to help you out.
A guy like me's not
really suited for the task.
[AKANE] On the contrary,
I can't think of anyone better.
[SAIGA] Hm.
To begin with,
tell me what it means.
You deciphered
the message, right?
Yes. I figured it out after
hearing Kitazawa's final words.
Hey. Tell me
something, will you?
What color am I?
[AKANE] "WC?"
stands for "What color?"
[SAIGA] What color?
Sure about that?
It's an odd question to
ask in this day and age.
[AKANE] Yeah, I know. If by
"color" they're referring to
a person's Hue,
then there's no reason
to ask anybody that.
Not when you can easily gauge
it yourself with a checker.
[SAIGA] And therein
lies our first puzzle,
for whom is this
question intended?
Is it someone at the
scene of the crime?
Or MWPSB personnel
who'd see it later?
Or maybe--
He's asking himself.
Hmmm...
One common factor
linking both messages
is that they each could've
only have been written
by the Inspector who
was there at the site.
No one else had the access.
[AKANE] According
to Inspector Aoyanagi,
this has to be
the work of a ghost.
A ghost who doesn't
know his own color,
so he has to keep
asking people what it is?
Quite a campfire story.
So what do you
make of all this?
You must have some thoughts.
A missing Inspector.
Messages that
can't possibly exist.
Whatever's happening, I intend
to get to the bottom of it.
I will. The problem is
I'm just not sure
where to begin.
And you think an old geezer
like me can offer advice?
I'm flattered.
[AKANE] You're the
only one who can help.
[SAIGA grunts lowly]
All right, let's start
with the undeniable
facts of the case.
The evidence we can
be certain is real.
[AKANE] The message
written on the walls.
And Kitazawa's
Crime Coefficient
dropping rapidly
all of a sudden.
[SAIGA] Very good.
Next we focus on the things
that are only conjecture
at this point.
Like the existence
of a message-writer
who can evade scans.
Or the man Kitazawa said
lowered his Coefficient.
"Kamui," he called him.
[SAIGA] Yes. Then regardless
of whether or not
this Kamui fellow
actually does exist,
we know for a fact
that both the person who
wrote the message,
and some means of
lowering Kitazawa's Crime
Coefficient must exist.
[SAIGA] Tell me, do you know the
concept of "The Devil's Proof"?
[AKANE]"The Devil's Proof"?
As it stands, we have
no evidence that proves
the devil really exists,
but at the same time,
it's impossible to
prove that he doesn't.
[SAIGA] For now, we're
just spinning our wheels.
[AKANE] In other words,
if we can find even
the slightest proof that
Kamui's real, that gives
us a way to move forward.
Why does it suddenly feel
like I'm being recruited?
[AKANE] Inspector Shisui
from Division Two is acting
on her own, and we
don't know where she is.
Surely you have some
insight into the matter
you'd be willing to contribute.
Are you not the man who
turned himself in out of guilt
for helping Mr. Kogami
when he went rogue?
Here's a chance to make amends.
Do you think I'm the
kind of person who can
be swayed by appeals
to the heart? Really?
You know the value of
doing whatever you can
in the face of
overwhelming odds.
I think you're
that kind of person.
You truly are an
excellent student.
You're a fantastic teacher.
[panting]
[footsteps]
[GINOZA] Wanna drink?
My dad left it behind.
[AOYANAGI] You're joking, right?
Remember I'm an Inspector.
[GINOZA] And a human being.
Are you okay?
"Okay"? How could you
possibly think I'd be okay?
[sighs]
Sorry, I snapped.
It's fine.
Just ten years as an Inspector,
they say, that's all,
then a Ministry of
Welfare job is yours.
Put in your time,
retire fat and happy--
that was the plan.
[AOYANAGI] It all sounded
so simple at the time.
[GINOZA] You're tellin' me.
Huh?
I tried that plan, too.
Now I drink.
[laughs lightly]
Least you can joke now.
Hmhm.
All I can do is think,
"Where did I screw up?"
Was it when I helped
you guys in Division One
allow Kogami to escape?
Or maybe it was
the time I shot him?
[GINOZA] "Him"?
You mean that Enforcer?
[GINOZA] You didn't
do anything wrong.
It's an Inspector's duty
to shoot an Enforcer
who's trying to run.
[sighs]
Our duty and feelings
don't always line up,
wouldn't you agree
with that Ginoza?
[AOYANAGI]
Sometimes I do wonder,
if I put a lid on whatever
was left of my feelings
the moment I squeezed
that Dominator's trigger...
[GINOZA] Lid?
[AOYANAGI] And now,
whether it's joy or sadness,
when my emotions start to rise,
the lid keeps them down,
locked away
somewhere deep inside.
Even in the rare
moments when I desperately
want to feel something,
they won't come.
I'm nothing more
than an empty vessel.
That's where I'm at anyway.
[AOYANAGI] Sometimes, though...
[AOYANAGI]
when I point a Dominator
and squeeze that trigger,
the lid starts to open
ever so slightly.
And just as I
sense that happening,
my rationality stops it.
[AOYANAGI] It's this
trait, above all others,
that makes me an Inspector.
[AOYANAGI] That time,
when I shot Kitazawa,
God, I almost enjoyed it.
That's on the edge, isn't it?
After everything,
all I have left is the job.
[AOYANAGI]
And I'm clinging to it.
Thanks for the drink.
Next one's on me.
[AOYANAGI] We should have
done something like this
together a long time ago.
The old Ginoza wouldn't
have had this drink with you.
[exhales deeply]
[digital beeping]
[AOYANAGI] Go ahead.
[SHISUI] Inspector Aoyanagi.
It's me, Shisui.
[gasps]
An investigation into
the missing Division Two
Inspector, Shisui,
and into strange messages
you believe left by
an unknown suspect.
[KASEI] I see. And you would
like me to approve Division One
taking the lead
role on both cases?
Yes, and on top of those,
we promise to still
handle our usual workload.
[KASEI] You have my approval.
[AKANE] Thank you for your
confidence, Chief Kasei.
[KASEI] Inspector Shimotsuki.
You're dismissed.
[MIKA] U-Uh...
You want me to leave?
[KASEI] I need to speak with
Inspector Tsunemori. Alone.
[MIKA] Understood.
Good evening, ma'am.
Tell me, what do you
really think is happening
with these W-C cases?
My question first.
Is there any way someone
could exist whom
Sibyl can't see?
That would be
completely impossible.
The angle of your
question answers my own
about your thoughts
on these cases.
[AKANE] Do you
doubt my sanity, too?
[KASEI] That would be the
normal judgment of Sibyl,
but you are also presenting
an interesting situation.
Can someone lose her
sanity when her Psycho-Pass
remains crystal clear?
[AKANE] If you want to sit
back and watch, be my guest.
Don't go just yet.
I have a question about
Division One's new personnel.
[KASEI] Specifically, the
new Enforcer. How's he doing?
[AKANE] Enforcer Togane
or Enforcer Hinakawa?
[KASEI] Sakuya Togane.
I'd like you to report on
his performance to me
as often as possible.
Why's that?
[KASEI] Although the results
have since been erased from
the official report,
testing revealed him to have
the highest Crime Coefficient
ever seen in our society.
[gasps]
[KASEI] He's a useful
model case for us.
Exercise caution
in how you treat him.
[AKANE] I know this is
asking a lot of all of you,
but we've already
got one dead Enforcer,
one missing Inspector,
and a Dominator that
we are unable to locate.
This is not a case we
can afford to leave alone.
What's your real goal here?
My gut tells me this is about
pulling the sheet
off of your ghost.
[GINOZA sighs]
Don't let this investigation
become too personal.
I'm going to ask Ms.
Karanomori to provide
assistance, too. I
appreciate your cooperation.
[sirens]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] Elevated
Area Stress Level warning.
A Psycho-Pass above
the regulation value...
[MIKA] I've got this.
Ms. Kunizuka, Hinakawa.
Come with me.
--[KUNIZUKA] Okay.
--[HINAKAWA] Uh, okay.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
The on-duty Inspector...
There's no way
this Kamui is real.
But by all means, go ahead and
keep chasing after your ghost.
Inspector.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] A Psycho-Pass
above the regulation value
has been detected inside...
[AKANE] We should
get started now, also.
I completed a thorough
analysis of the crime scene,
but nothing even remotely
suspicious stuck out to me.
[AKANE]
Suppose Kamui does exist.
He pretended to be
a hostage in order to
lure out the MWPSB.
Then killed an Enforcer
and abducted an Inspector.
But why do that?
What's his goal?
And what does
that message mean?
Why did he set his
sights on me of all people?
[GINOZA] Watch yourself.
You're becoming obsessed.
[SAKUYA] Inspector Tsunemori
is gonna be just fine.
It'd take a lot more than
this to cloud that woman's Hue.
[MAN] Now's the time to
put the lessons we've learned
to good use, and
finally implement some
much-needed new policies!
Policies that will
improve each and every one
of our citizens' lives!
But in order to do so--
[MALE SUPPORTERS laughing]
[MALE SUPPORTER] That was
a wonderful speech, sir.
[MIKA] Representative
Kotoku Masuda.
[MIKA] MWPSB.
[MIKA] There's been
deterioration in your Hue.
You need to undergo
emergency therapy at once.
Please come with us.
What? There must
be some mistake!
[MIKA] Hinakawa, restrain him.
Now that's how an
operation is supposed to go.
So what does the Chief
see in someone like her?
[MALE ENFORCER 1] So, that's
where Inspector Shisui is?
Yeah, she told me so herself,
believe it or not.
I want you guys to
stay out here for now.
We don't want to
cause a scene, okay?
--You got it.
--Sure thing boss.
[MAN] No! That won't work!
Medication can't save anyone!
It changes nothing! Nothing!
But, sir, please.
You all need
to open your eyes.
If you truly want to
be saved don't turn to
the drug companies.
They won't save you.
gasps]
Don't you see? Only
I can save you people.
It's my mission to save you.
Hold it right there!
[DOMINATOR] Crime
Coefficient, twenty-three.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
That can't be right.
[AOYANAGI] Ahhh!
[MALE ENFORCER 1] What the hell?
Look.
Did you find something?
[AKANE] The Drones sent to
defuse the bombs at the location
where the first
message was found.
One of them somehow
turned up far away
from the crime scene.
And it had to be sent
in for maintenance.
Invoice says it was
missing a part. That's funny.
It looks like the impact
absorber that had been
installed in it must've
been removed at some point.
It just mysteriously
disappeared.
I have a hard time
believing that piece just
wandered off all on its own.
Could it be?
[digital beeping]
[MIKA] Inspector.
[AKANE] Ms. Shimotsuki?
What is it?
[MASUDA] Kamui! Get Kamui here!
Kamui can make me
clear again. Believe me!
[MASUDA] Please! I--I beg you!
[MAN] I want to be
a savior of the people.
I want to save everyone.
Just like Kamui does.