♪
[SHION] We're still a long
way from closing this case.
Yet we're already back
to relying on the Drones.
♪
[mechanical beeping]
[drone tires screech]
[WOMAN screams]
[MAN] This is so rad.
Games are way more
fun when they're real.
[MIKA] Freeze, police!
[MAN grunts]
[MIKA] Hinakawa!
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
one hundred thirty-three.
Enforcement action required.
This is justice!
♪
[KUNIZUKA] We got
another Area Stress warning.
In the commercial zone,
eight kilometers from here.
Oh, great! When
will this ever end?
[grunts]
[SAIGA] In a society monitored
by scanners like ours,
it's impossible to disguise
yourself as someone else.
However, if you had a
means to artificially clear
your Psycho Pass, that could
change things considerably.
With extensive
organ transplants,
you might assume
enough of a person's
physical identity
to fool biometrics.
[SAIGA] And as long as your
Psycho Pass remained clear,
the system would likely
dismiss any discrepancy
as falling within
the margin of error.
I'm told when they
searched Kamui's hideout,
they found organs, stockpiled.
I'm afraid your interview
with Mr. Masuda is over now.
[SAIGA sighs]
Just like you, there are
people pretending to be
someone they're not.
Are they Kamui's accomplices?
[SAKUYA] Inspector.
[AKANE] Once again,
I couldn't pull the trigger.
Maybe so. But if it weren't
for your quick thinking,
then we'd all be
dead right now.
And most important of
all, you finally got us
face-to-face
with the ghost.
If you ask me, you're the
only one who can catch him.
Kamui is yours.
Kamui found out that
someone un-authorized
could carry a Dominator
like it was his own.
[AKANE] That was
the first encounter.
[AKANE] Then he tried
to see if a Dominator could
judge Inspectors.
That was encounter two.
And most recently,
he attacked the MWPSB,
[AKANE] and stole
multiple Dominators.
Most likely for his accomplices.
Which means, Kamui's
goal isn't one he can
achieve just by himself.
Who are you planning
to point all those
Dominators at, Kamui?
And on the other side
of the gun, why are they
unable to recognize you,
much less judge you?
Who are you?
[KOGAMI] When something
impossible happens to you,
there are only two
explanations on the table.
[KOGAMI] Either it's your basic
assumptions that are wrong.
Or you've gone completely
off the deep end.
[AKANE] Everything would
make more sense if it was
all just in my head.
But that's not the case here.
Kamui's existence
is an undeniable fact.
That's not what
the Dominator said
when you pointed it at him.
He's different from Makishima.
He is more
unique than just being
an asymptomatic criminal.
That's why he can't
be seen by our society.
[KOGAMI] Has to be the
result of some kind of trick.
A shortcoming in our
surveillance-based world
that Kamui's found a way
to exploit for his cause.
[AKANE] The answer.
It's close.
[KOGAMI and SAKUYA]
Closer than we think.
[SAKUYA] Maybe
right under our noses.
Is something
bothering you, Inspector?
[AKANE] Oh, sorry. I just
spaced-out for a second.
What'd you say?
[SAKUYA] About Kamui.
Since he doesn't show
up on cymatic scans,
I think finding out what
makes his body so unique
is the best way to get
to the bottom of all this.
Yeah. If we can figure
out how to see him,
then maybe we could
learn his true color.
Hmph. What's so
special about Kamui
that lets him
become a ghost?
[SAKUYA] Let's look for
any clues left at the scene.
Tell me what color... you are.
[computer keyboard clicking]
[SHION] Searching Kamui's
hideout not only turned up
the transplant organs,
but also pairs of
bio-contact lenses with
a traced retinal pattern.
The retinal pattern must
belong to Mizue Shisui.
[SHION] Excellent deduction.
Color me impressed.
[SAIGA] The only way
an unauthorized person can
wave around a Dominator,
is to have it
falsely recognize
them as authorized.
Kamui is using her retinal
ID to elicit false positives.
[SHION] So that's why
we detected multiple
Inspector Shisuis
moving around the docks.
[SAIGA] He's taken eight
Dominators so far, right?
Well, that means
from here on out,
we should expect the scanners
to track eight Shisuis.
[SHION] You're pretty
calm about all this.
Is that because you're
already working on
a surefire way
to stop Kamui?
Nope, I got
nothing right now.
As long as Sibyl
recognizes "Shisui"
[SAIGA] and her
actions as valid,
those Dominators
will keep getting used.
Hey. Are you doubting
our friend Sibyl?
[SAIGA] I'm suspicious.
[SHION] That's even worse.
We have an Inspector aiding
a criminal mastermind,
while a bunch of
imposters of said Inspector
are allowed to run free.
I'm just re-stating the facts.
[AKANE] All right, the two
of you should head back now.
[AKANE] I'll stick around
here for a little longer.
See what I can find
in Kamui's hideout.
Tsunemori, you really
should get some rest.
Yeah, that's
not a bad idea.
Hm. Well, it's not like
I'd be getting much sleep
at my apartment
anyway. You know?
Since I'm trying to
preserve a crime scene.
What the hell?! You're
still living there?
Are you out of your mind?
Inspector, please
don't tell me you're
using yourself as bait.
Wow, you really think I could
be that foolishly reckless?
I just haven't had the time to
find a new place, that's all.
[GINOZA] Unbelievable.
[tune from AKANE'S communicator]
[AKANE gasps]
That's where Grandma is.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] There
has been a Drone malfunction
at the convalescent
home where Aoi Tsunemori
is residing while
in protective custody.
[AKANE panting]
[AKANE] Grandma!
[AOI] What's the matter, dear?
You look pale as a ghost.
But Grandma, I thought...
It's been a little while,
hasn't it, dear?
[AKANE] I'm so relieved
to see you're okay.
You had me worried.
Oh, you're overreacting.
There was no need to
abandon your work
over something so minor.
It's fine.
Really, Grandma;
it was no big deal.
Oh, Akane, you haven't
changed a bit, have you dear?
[AOI] You were always the most
selfless child, focusing on
the needs of others
while neglecting your own.
I'm sorry if I caused
any trouble for you.
Don't be silly.
You've never caused me
even a single moment of trouble.
You know the value
of people's lives.
That every life has worth.
[AOI] That's something
you must always hold on to.
Promise me you'll
never forget that...
Akane.
[AKANE] Oh, Grandma.
Thanks so much.
[KASEI] I've already been
briefed on this case, Inspector.
[AKANE] Yes, well, I came
to see you to find out
what Sibyl is thinking.
I'm wondering why you
haven't yet taken any steps to
deactivate Inspector
Shisui's Dominator.
You must be following
her actions closely.
Of course we are.
However, by all measures
Inspector Shisui's
[KASEI] Psycho-Pass is
still registering as clear.
[KASEI] There's no reason
for us to prevent an Inspector
with a clear Psycho-Pass
from enforcing justice.
What you mean is that
you're not willing to do it,
[AKANE] because
you'd be admitting that
the system is flawed.
I highly suggest you watch
yourself, Inspector Tsunemori.
There's no way for us to
bring the bad guy to justice
with our hands tied by protocol.
[KASEI] You mean Kamui?
I've read through your
report quite thoroughly.
In it, you claim the Dominators
didn't even recognize him.
Yes.
[KASEI]
That's simply not possible.
It'd be one thing if he were
criminally asymptomatic,
but a person who
can't be scanned is
an irregularity
that could never occur.
Yes, well, this
irregularity, you say
could never happen,
has happened.
[AKANE] So how are we
supposed to deal with him?
[KASEI] It's simple, really.
In fact, you already tried
to do it once, didn't you?
[AKANE gasps]
[AKANE] You're saying
we should just kill him?
Don't you now agree
it was a mistake for you
to restrain Enforcer
Togane on the dock?
[AKANE] It's strange.
The Sibyl System.
You guys have maintained
[AKANE] this whole construct
by integrating the minds
of abnormal people who
were criminally asymptomatic.
And yet, when it comes to
someone as unique as Kamui,
all you want to
do is eliminate him
without any observation at all.
Seems to me you've already come
to a conclusion about him.
That Kamui is a type
of aberration you won't
be able to incorporate
into your system.
My you are as
fascinating as ever.
Suppose what you say were true,
what do you intend to do now?
I'll solve the mystery
of Kamui's condition.
And once that's done,
we'll arrest our suspect
[AKANE] and bring him to justice
under due process of law.
Any problem with that?
None at all. Continue
performing your duties
as an Inspector.
[AKANE] Then excuse me.
♪
[SAKUYA] They tried
to cover their tracks,
but not hard enough.
Everything's just a
little out of place.
[SAKUYA] They're not done
with me yet, are they?
[SAKUYA] Let's see what kind of
data they were interested in.
Ah, my employment
records. So that's it.
Well, well.
[SAKUYA] I guess you must
really have it in for me...
Inspector Shimotsuki.
It's an old personnel file.
[MIKA] Once,
eighteen years ago,
he was assigned
to be an Enforcer.
He was twenty-three at the time.
All the Inspectors he
worked with had become
latent criminals
and had to be executed.
We weren't informed of
any of this when he came to us.
What's this guy's deal?
[MIKA gasps]
[digital beeping]
[AKANE] We still
waiting on anyone?
No. They told me
Enforcer Sugo won't be
[GINOZA] back on
duty for a while.
Well let's get started
then, shall we?
Our biggest question
right now? How to get back
on Kamui's trail after
losing him at the dock.
After his release,
we checked on
Representative Masuda, thinking
Kamui might approach him.
[KUNIZUKA] But by the
time we caught up to him,
he was already dead.
He chose to die
without hesitation.
That's how much he
admired Kamui and his cause.
Despite discovering he
wasn't the real Masuda,
we couldn't do anything.
We won't let
Kamui slip away.
Let's start by
analyzing every scrap of
evidence left at the scene.
The biggest leads we
found there are the supply
[SAKUYA] of transplant organs,
as well as a huge stock
of stress-care medicine.
This--This is amazing.
[AKANE] Hinakawa,
you find something good?
[HINAKAWA] Well, they're
almost all illicit drugs
that have been
personally compounded.
These cocktails,
they're--they're exceptional.
I mean, this level of
precision's almost impossible.
So he's mixing his own drugs?
This goes way
beyond just mixing.
I'm not talking about crushing
a couple of pills together.
I could manage that much.
No, this is
full-on chemistry.
The guy really
knows his stuff.
You mean Kamui might have
an education in pharmacology.
Is that what you're saying?
Mm--Mmmm.
[HINAKAWA] I did see him
wearing a pharmacist's Holo.
But maybe that
wasn't a disguise.
Wait, pharmacist's Holo?
When was he wearing that?
[HINAKAWA] Hm? Oh, right.
I noticed it during the
barricade. The hostages.
[HINAKAWA]
When I looked closely,
there was no mistaking it.
It was very well crafted.
But it was still a Holo.
It didn't occur to
you to report that?
But I did! I made sure
to send all the data
I had from that day to
Inspector Shimotsuki!
[gasps] Huh?
[HINAKAWA] Here, I have a record
of sending it and everything.
[MIKA gasps]
Why didn't you just
tell it to me in person!
You didn't follow
proper procedure! Hmph.
[AKANE] We can improve
our work flow another time.
Hinakawa!
Send that data to the lab.
[SHION] Hey, is it possible...
that this Holo is
like the others we saw?
[SHION] I knew it.
This one, too, was created
by aging up someone.
Here, I'll cross-reference
this kid with the ones
who died in that plane crash.
Perfect match.
The one we looked at
from fifteen years ago.
It's just like the
female Holo Kamui used
in his first attack on us.
[AKANE] Our initial assumptions
about Holo were incorrect.
We shouldn't have been focused
on just that first woman.
It's all the children.
Everybody who died that day.
Ms. Karanomori, please
bring up the crash files.
[SHION] Will do.
[SHION] Plane went down
fifteen years ago in May.
It was carrying elementary
school kids for a class trip,
and it crashed
into Mount Kumataka.
It says there was a
problem with the airframe.
In total, there were
two hundred and two dead.
That includes pilots,
crew, chaperones--
and one hundred and
eighty-five children. Wait!
It looks like the
crash had one survivor.
[SHION] This student.
[AKANE] Kirito Kamui.
[intense music]
Kamui was the sole survivor.
[SHION] No go. Even with
the MWPSB's authority,
the server won't let us
access Kirito Kamui's records.
Apparently, it takes
medical confidentiality
more seriously than we do.
Check the doctors
who did his surgery.
Let's see, the one
who'd probably know
the most about it is--Yes!
[SHION] The operating
surgeon is still alive.
[AKANE]
I'll go see him right now.
Inspector, please join me.
[MIKA] Very well, Tsunemori.
[AKANE] Thank you, Hinakawa.
Because of you, we finally
learned who Kamui really is.
[HINAKAWA] Oh. No problem.
[AKANE] While I'm gone,
continue creating Holos of
the hundred and
eighty-five children.
Each one aged-up
fifteen years, of course.
What? You want all of them?
Are you having one
person do all that work?
It might help us
identify a third
or even a fourth Holo.
Well, Hinakawa, can you do it?
Uh. I think I can.
If it'll help you, Big Sis.
Ms. Kunizuka, start
digging and find people
out there who may
have the same names
as the plane crash victims.
Yeah. You got it.
[AKANE] Mr. Ginoza and
Mr. Togane, use the organs we
seized at Kamui's hideout
to identify the impersonators.
--[GINOZA] Understood.
--[SAKUYA] We're on it.
[MASUZAKI] I've completed
the preparations.
Once they arrive,
you and your people will
be able to use the Dominators.
That's perfect. Thank you.
Now all I have to do is
locate the one responsible
[KAMUI] for making
society the way it is.
[phone beeping]
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST] Doctor
Masuzaki, the MWPSB are here.
They'd like to speak with you.
[MASUZAKI] Show them in.
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
Yes, sir.
Looks like they're here.
[KAMUI] I truly appreciate
your assistance.
Nonsense. I should
be the one thanking you.
[MASUZAKI] I wish you only the
best in your mission, Kirito.
[knocking]
Doctor Yohei Masuzaki, right?
Would you be
willing to come with us
to answer a few questions?
I fear I'm not the
most gifted of speakers.
I may not be
able to do justice to
the beauty of Kamui's gospel.
[AKANE] Ms. Shimotsuki,
as soon as we get back,
please look into Kamui's
treatment history.
That really
necessary at this point?
[MIKA] We've got a witness now.
All we need to do is
pry the answers out of him.
If Kamui helps
the doctor maintain
a clear Psycho-Pass
like the others,
he might lie during
the interrogation.
We need a way to
corroborate his story.
[huffs]
Ms. Kunizuka.
[MIKA] I could use your
help with something,
if you're not too busy.
Eh... I guess you'll do.
Come on, gimme a hand.
[SHION] He suffered
from severe depression.
So the doctors put him
on meds and he wound up
becoming totally
dependent on the stuff.
[SHION] Poor thing.
[SHION] As a defense
mechanism, he focused on
developing his skills,
which is what helped him
become a Holo designer.
Isn't that adorable?
[KUNIZUKA] If that were
all there was to the story,
then he wouldn't have
had to become an Enforcer.
[HINAKAWA] Weird. The
authorization level for these
surgical records
is set unusually high.
Why is that?
[MIKA] How should I know?
You take it from here.
[HINAKAWA] It's possible it
somehow involves patents for
medical devices or drugs
or something like that.
Hold on, drug patents.
One of the largest
holders of drug patents
in the country is--
if I remember correctly...
[MIKA] The Togane Foundation.
Hey, you know, on second
thought, I'll handle this task.
[MIKA] Just keep working
on those aged-up Holos.
That's what Inspector Tsunemori
told you to do, right?
[HINAKAWA] Yeah. Okay.
Would you please
question him, Mr. Saiga?
[SAIGA] Hm.
I don't think we'll need
much of an interrogation
this go-round. He's itching
to tell us everything.
Isn't that right?
I wouldn't speak to
just anybody, you know.
[MASUZAKI] But fortunately
for us both, you appear to be
a wise and honorable audience,
worthy of hearing this message.
Thanks, I'm flattered.
[MASUZAKI] I will tell
you all about Kamui.
[SHION] Sho just sent me an
email saying he's finished
creating all one
hundred and eighty-five
of the aged-up Holos.
Shall we take a look?
[gasps]
♪
Wait! Him?
[SAKUYA] And that one there.
[SAKUYA] He was
the programmer from
the Military Drone facility.
[GINOZA] I remember
some of these others, too.
I think that's the guy who was
in charge of
vehicle maintenance.
[MASUZAKI] I imagine you
must think this whole time,
it's been just one man, Kamui,
who's been making
fools out of you.
But you would be mistaken.
He was never on his own.
Not for a moment.
[AKANE] It's not just
a third or a fourth Holo.
Kamui's been there,
right beside us
every step of the way.