[MALE ENFORCER]
Inspector Aoyanagi, come in.
Inspector Aoyanagi!
[MAN breathing heavily]
[MAN] The medicine they've
been pumping you full of here
may keep your Hue under control.
But at the same time
it gradually robs from you
the feeling of being alive.
[yells]
[FEMALE whimpers]
I will free you from the
tyranny of this false choice
that you've been presented with.
[MAN] Just as Kamui does.
[MASUDA] If you help me, I
can make it worth your while.
Tell you what.
I'll put in a good word
at the Ministry of Welfare.
All that you have
to do is call Kamui
and let me speak to him--
Inspector Shimotsuki.
Please bring
Representative Masuda
back to the station.
I'll handle
the interrogation.
And why is that?
Because you don't want someone
who doubts the existence
of Kamui to do it?
It's because I want
him questioned based on
the evidence acquired at
the scene and nothing else.
Fine. "Yes, ma'am."
I doubt it's
a coincidence, but--
we need more to
go on or else...
we'll end up like
we did with Kitazawa.
[AKANE] Take a look at this.
It's the space where the
impact absorber was removed.
A person could probably
squeeze into there
without too much trouble,
don't you think?
I guess so. Somehow
that Drone wound up
two kilometers away
from the crime scene.
Drones malfunction,
sometimes on their own.
If someone tampered with it,
there would be some
kind of record of that.
[AKANE] So the fact that there's
not suggests that Kamui has
a way of hacking into a
Drone's logs to alter them.
You're committed to
this theory that he's
actually out there somewhere.
[AKANE] You don't support the
direction this case is taking?
No, ma'am. I'm happy
to play along with you.
[SAKUYA] Hmmhm.
[AKANE] This was deliberate
and premeditated.
And while we're spinning
our wheels looking for
definitive proof, Kamui's
free to plan his next move.
So yeah.
You could say I'm committed.
I have no doubt. Kamui is real.
[SHION] No luck, guys.
I can't access their security
cameras or scanners.
The whole
building's a dead zone.
That's weird. Is this common?
[SHION] No, it usually only
happens after a big disaster,
like a fire or something.
But that doesn't seem
to be the case here.
[MALE ENFORCER 2] Hey.
The Area Stress. It's shot
up to the advisory range.
[MALE ENFORCER 1] Damn it,
what's the Inspector
doing in there?
[MAN] This is
your natural state.
The way you all
came into this world.
Do you feel it?
Feel the joy of being alive?
[MALE HOSTAGE] Ahhh!
Yes, that's good.
Let it all out.
[WOMEN yell]
Oh I understand your
suffering all too well.
Instead of having
your mind healed,
you're on the
verge of being killed
by the very medication
meant to cure you.
[MALE HOSTAGE groans]
Now welcome in the stress.
It's the proof that we're
still alive in this world.
[HOSTAGES shudder]
Feel it all! All of the pain!
Feel your heart beating!
Feel your life pulsing
through your arteries!
[HOSTAGES shudder]
It's such a great gift
to be alive, isn't it?
I think we should
call for backup.
Might as well, right?
We can't do much
without an Inspector.
Yeah, don't I know it.
[MIKA] I'll go ahead and
respond to that Division Two
Enforcer's request
for assistance.
Yes, thank you. Given
everything that's going on
right now, please proceed
with caution, okay?
Yeah, well, I'm
sure it's no big deal.
People got trapped
inside the building
and panicked a little
bit, that's all it is.
Well, it is true that both
fear and confusion do tend
to spread easily within mental
care facilities, but still.
Oh, come on, seriously?
You think even a
routine call like this
is too much for
a junior Inspector?
Huh?
You've gotta be
feeling pretty pleased
right about now,
don't you?
Now that a second person's
name-dropped your Kamui ghost?
Actually,
it's the opposite.
I appreciate
you bringing him in.
I'll take it from here. Be
careful out there, Inspector.
Okay... Miss Big Shot.
A mental care facility, huh?
What's Aoyanagi doing
at a place like that?
I don't know.
But for now, let's
focus on the interrogation.
Before we start, thank you.
Your cooperation
is appreciated.
[AKANE] Who is this man, Kamui?
No idea who
you're talking about.
Well that's interesting.
Because I heard you yell
for us to call him in.
That's not true.
Hm.
[AKANE] You suggested that in
order to maintain a clear Hue,
you relied on a man named Kamui.
How did you first come
into contact with him?
And what means do
you use to communicate?
Oh, sure, now
he's tongue-tied.
[AKANE] It's all so strange.
[worried exhale]
[MALE PHARMACIST] Don't move.
What--What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Miss. He ordered
me to. That man there.
Ah--!
[HOSTAGES gasp]
Everyone here in
this room is alive!
[MAN] All of you!
All of you are alive!
[worried exhales]
All life is so wonderful!
This is just wrong.
[AOYANAGI] No.
Don't move an inch.
But he's--
It's not your
fight. Let me do it.
I'll save everyone.
[AOYANAGI] Because that's
what an Inspector does.
[MIKA] Status report.
[MALE ENFORCER 1] We still
don't know what's going on
inside the facility.
So far, there are no incident
reports from this location.
But the Area Stress
Level--well, it's increasing.
Then simple deduction
says this place
has to be the source.
Why don't we just
force our way in?
No go. First things first.
We gotta find out what's
causing the stress increase.
If we were to
simply release them,
we could make a bad
situation even worse.
All right. Then we have
to find a way to talk
with the people inside.
I recalibrated the Area
Stress check to survey
just the building and
immediate surroundings.
[MALE ENFORCER 2] Look at this.
It's way over the warning line.
I wouldn't be surprised
if everyone in there
scanned as a target
for enforcement.
[AKANE] A new detainee
has mentioned Kamui's name.
On top of that,
a Drone sent to diffuse
the bombs was moved
and is missing a part.
So then, this evidence
could be what you need
for meeting your Devil's Proof.
Is that what you're saying?
This man we're
holding knows something.
I'm certain about that.
Mr. Saiga, I could
use your help with this.
Are you in?
[gasping for air]
[MAN] I want to
become a savior, too!
I want to save... people!
Just like Kamui!
[screams]
[HOSTAGES whimper]
That's enough!
This representative, Masuda.
Sibyl observed that
his Hue was clouding
right as he
started giving a speech?
[SAIGA] Do I have that correct?
Yes. We allowed
him to finish,
then Inspector
Shimotsuki and her team
took him in to custody.
[SAIGA] For someone of
his position, it wouldn't be
atypical if his Hue
worsened consistently
under similar circumstances.
Go back the last few
months and check the days
he gave speeches. Check
his phone records, too.
[AOYANAGI] Savior? You're
a sick, latent criminal,
and you can either give
yourself up to a facility
or receive enforcement here!
[DOMINATOR] Crime
Coefficient, seventy-six.
No enforcement action required.
What the hell?
That's good.
You're on the right track.
But you still have a
ways to go when it comes
to understanding
what I'm saying.
No! Why me?
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
one hundred twelve.
Enforcement action required.
No! He's the victim!
[KUNIZUKA] A Dominator
just went online.
Can you tell the user?
Is it Inspector Aoyanagi?
Looks like a target
for enforcement is inside.
So what should we do?
For now, we do nothing.
We stay put until Inspector
Aoyanagi contacts us.
If we attack and
something goes wrong,
it'll all crash down on me.
The Analysis Lab wrote
back. Let's see here.
They traced the device,
the one Representative Masuda
was contacting before
each of his speeches.
Who did he call?
That we don't know yet.
But right now,
it looks like the device...
[SAKUYA] is at the mental
care facility in Shibuya Ward.
[gasps]
You mean the place...
where Division Two
needed backup?
Then he must be there. Kamui!
[AOYANAGI groans]
[digital beeping]
Inspector Aoyanagi.
Division One is here, standing
outside of the facility.
Can you report on the
current situation inside?
[audio feedback]
[MAN OVER SPEAKER] To those
who rely on force to suppress
citizens merely seeking
to live healthy lives,
heed my words!
Who is that?
[screaming]
From personal experience,
I know what becomes of someone
after they've had all
of their stress stolen
[MAN] from them by a
destructive prescription.
[whimpers]
Yes. It's called
eustress deficiency.
[MAN] External stimuli
could no longer affect me,
and all I felt was numb inside.
It got to the
point I was prepared
to give up on my own life.
I reject the system where
misguided mental health care
drains the joy of
living away from us.
My mission is to rescue
lost souls from this horror,
just as Kamui once rescued me.
He said Kamui!
Not again. Is he some
kind of shared delusion
suffered by all crazy
people or something?
And now this one's
spouting off about
that old eustress
deficiency urban legend.
I don't know that one.
What about Inspector
Aoyanagi? Hear back yet?
No, I still haven't.
Despite the fact that she came
online briefly.
Is there a possibility
that the guy we just heard
could be holding everybody
in there hostage right now?
If so, we should move
in and subdue him.
Maybe. But we haven't
received that order yet.
[GINOZA]
There's that name again.
What the hell
is going on here?
[AKANE] Hinakawa.
Come in, Hinakawa.
Uh, yeah?
I mean, yes, ma'am.
[AKANE] I need you to
check and see if anyone
around there is wearing a Holo.
A Holo? What am I looking for?
It could be the
same woman as before,
or it may be a different one.
But if there is one there,
you'll be the person to spot it.
[AKANE] Please try!
Yeah. I'll see what I can do.
Ah, I get it. You think
because the Holo we saw
was so elaborate, it's
likely that Kamui would have
an unusually strong
obsession with them.
Exactly the sort of
costume a ghost would wear.
If this is all simply
part of Kamui's plan,
then what's the goal?
Why would he go through
all of this trouble?
[sighs]
[HINAKAWA] No. Not him.
That's not him either.
[HINAKAWA] No. No.
[MIKA] Hey!
What're you doing?
I--I got an order
from Inspector Tsunemori.
I'm the officer
in charge here.
Right now you
take orders from me.
Yeah, but--
♪
Division Three will
take it from here.
Just do what we say
and stay out of our way.
Ugh! What the hell?
You can't just show up
and take over like that!
Take it up with Chief Kasei.
This was her call.
Now if you'll excuse us,
we have an enforcement.
I don't get it. Chief Kasei
wanted me off the case?
But why would she?
[KASEI] Yes, that's right.
Disperse the crowd.
And don't let any media
get through to the area.
We can't have them
broadcasting a baseless
conspiracy theory like
eustress deficiency.
Not that anyone
would be foolish enough
to buy into such a crackpot
idea, but best not to
give a platform to
the ranting of a madman.
He's doing the
same thing as last time.
Isolating an Inspector
away from her team.
Kamui's targeting Inspectors?
Or maybe, it's not the
Inspectors he wants.
It's their Dominators.
Under normal circumstances,
it wouldn't be possible,
but what if Inspector Shisui
didn't shoot Enforcer Yamatoya?
It was Kamui.
If an unapproved user
could somehow manage
to fire a Dominator,
that would be disastrous.
Perhaps the first
incident was just
Kamui experimenting with it.
That's enough,
Tsunemori. Don't go there!
You're gonna get your
Psycho-Pass clouded!
We're chasing a ghost.
But even if you
can't see a ghost,
that doesn't mean you can't
still follow its trail.
[DOMOTO] Division three.
We are good to go!
Uh...
[shrieks]
[whimpers]
[MAN] Foolish MWPSB.
[AOYANAGI shaky breathing]
[AOYANAGI] I am an Inspector.
Aaahhh!
[MAN yells]
We got an elevated stress
level warning for the building.
There's no way
they'll be able to
keep their Psycho-Passes
stable now.
An experiment. Kamui's
set up the entire thing
as a way to learn
how to use a Dominator.
But he's already used
one on Enforcer Yamatoya.
[AKANE] If he anticipated
the MWPSB surrounding him,
then his plan
this time isn't to be
the one pulling the trigger.
[GINOZA] You think he's
trying to get someone else
to do his killing for him?
That's a pretty
roundabout strategy.
Who the hell does he want to--
[gasps]
[grunts]
[muffled groans]
[AOYANAGI] To protect these
people and uphold the law,
I will enforce you--!
[HOSTAGES scream]
They shot right
through the wall.
[DIVISION 3 INSPECTOR] That's
the MWPSB's latest weapon:
The Assault Dominator.
When there's a wall
between us and the target,
this creates a hole.
Looks like it worked well.
"It worked well"?
What about the
remaining people in there?
Doing something like that
can stress them out so much
that it triggers
Eliminator mode!
Ms. Kunizuka, please stop.
Hey, I'm only following
the orders I was given.
[DIVISION 3 INSPECTOR] You
sure you got the right guy?
Don't know. Whoever
had the higher number
was who I enforced.
[HOSTAGES whimper and scream]
[MALE HOSTAGE]
He's killing everyone!
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
three hundred twenty-two.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Now what the
hell is this number?
[screaming and crying]
[DOMINATOR] Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
They're all targets!
Enforce them!
[panting]
[KUNIZUKA] My God.
We have to stop them!
[MIKA] I can't. This isn't
Division One's case anymore.
I have no power now.
They won't listen.
[police sirens]
Stop it!
What is going on?
[AKANE] What did you do?
[KAMUI] Seems we've
answered my question.
Inspectors can be
judged by the Dominators,
same as anyone else.
Thank you, friend.
Because of your help,
we've taken a big step
in the right direction.
Follow me. I have our
escape route planned.
[MAN] After all
that's happened today,
I wonder what my color is.
When I first became
familiar with you,
I was a zombie, whose life
had been robbed of all color
because of a sickening
eustress deficiency.
But now, I'm as
different as I am healthy.
I was finally able to
repossess my own existence!
Please let me stay behind.
[sighs]
I have done all I can do.
My work here is now finished.
[MAN] But you...
You can change the world.
I'm glad I met you,
Kamui. Thank you.
[KAMUI] Can you see it?
The color of the blood we shed?
Why don't you tell me
then, what color we are.
[GINOZA shudders]
[GINOZA] It can't be. Aoyanagi.
[SAKUYA] Inspector!
[AKANE] This question.
I think he's directing it
at society itself.
[SAKUYA] Each of us.
For us to question
our colors, and also--
[KAMUI] Sibyl.
What color are you?