[explosions]
♪
[DOMINATOR] Enforcement mode:
Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be
completely annihilated.
Aim carefully and
eliminate the target.
[rumble]
[AKANE] Ms. Karanomori.
Are you certain?
Yep. The people who
are remotely operating
those Drones are--
[beeping from game]
[BOY STUDENT A grunts]
Crap! Where did he go?
Quick, find him!
I got him!
[BOY STUDENT B] On your right!
♪
Wait, civilians are doing this?
Bastard! You're
scrap metal now!
[SUGO] Wait! Don't chase it!
Hasuike!
[BOY STUDENT F] Damn it!
[BOY STUDENT G] Run faster!
[SHION] The Ministry of
National Defense's Drones
getting hijacked
is alarming enough.
But add to that a
horde of random citizens
controlling them? Why,
it's simply unimaginable.
[SHION] They probably
aren't even aware
of what they're doing.
It's using a protection
program designed
for border security
Drone operators.
Protection program?
[SHION] It converts video into
virtual Holo representations
to keep the
operator's Psycho-Pass
from getting clouded.
It's making the
Drone's camera feed
look like a cute video game.
[AKANE] People who kill
without the intent to kill.
What color are those people?
Is that what you were asking...
[AKANE] Kamui?
[SHION] The game's been
posted to multiple sites.
And every time I delete it,
it gets uploaded again.
[music from game]
[SHION]
I'm chasing my tail here.
It's only a matter of
time before all the Drones
at the port have been hijacked.
[AKANE] Is there any way
for you to seize control
and shut them down?
Well, let's see
it's a cloud-based app--
so if I can gain access
to the cloud server.
[SHION] Unfortunately,
they've gone to great lengths
to mask the server's location,
so I'm gonna need some time.
[AKANE] Please work
as fast as you can.
And try to warn the players.
We have to stop it
from spreading further.
These can only fire
three Decomposer shots.
That does put
us in quite a bind.
Yeah. I think we should
all get out of here now.
Was that your intent?
To lure the PSB
into a hunting game?
I think not. There's
more to it than that.
[AKANE] Kamui's been
experimenting with Dominators.
Figuring out how they work.
He must know by now
that we can disable Drones
with Decomposers, and yet...
You think he's playing
a bigger game here?
[gasps]
[AKANE]
Attention, all Enforcers!
Do not go off on your own!
You must remain with
an Inspector at all times!
[AKANE] The Drones
are just decoys!
A human with a Dominator
is the real danger!
[rumble]
[HASUIKE panting]
Heh.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient:
Three hundred twenty-two.
Enforcement mode.
Lethal Eliminator.
Ah! You're kidding me.
[HASUIKE groans]
[yells]
[screaming]
[HASUIKE] Inspector... Shisui?
In the world Kamui's creating,
hunting dogs aren't needed.
[labored breathing]
How are you feeling now?
I feel absolutely fine.
I don't need a scan
to tell me that my
Psycho-Pass is still clear.
[KAMUI] The clarity
you're feeling...
that's the mind
you were born with.
You've finally been
released. Congratulations.
[SHISUI] It's all
thanks to you, Kamui.
[KAMUI] I don't
deserve such gratitude.
Not after that. I did
a terrible thing to you.
It's okay. All my life,
I never liked my eyes.
[DOMINATOR] User authentication,
Inspector Mizue Shisui.
Dominator usage approved.
[KAMUI] For me, your eye
is of critical importance.
[KAMUI] It's perfect.
With its help, this Dominator
will always identify me as you.
I'm glad my eye could
become part of you.
[SHISUI] If I can be
of any more use to you,
please use my body as you wish.
[KAMUI] Thank you. For now, we
should proceed with our plan.
[SAKUYA] So if this isn't
about just killing Enforcers,
what is Kamui's goal?
If we take all his
attacks into account,
[AKANE] only
one goal makes sense.
Okay, I understand.
[SAIGA] I know what
your boss is doing.
[AKANE] He's
collecting Dominators.
♪
He's been tracking
her Psycho-Pass levels
all this time.
[MIKA] Since he came here.
Every day? Creepy!
[digital beeping]
[SHION] Mika! Where the
hell did you run off to?
Why aren't you out in the field
with your senior Inspector?
Huh?
[computer keyboard clicking]
[KUNIZUKA] I don't get it.
Inspector Shisui has
activated two Dominators.
And they're moving
in two directions.
It means somebody's
stolen her identity,
so they can use a
Dominator in her place.
Impossible.
[SHION] So we thought,
but it's the only explanation.
I'll wait for
Shimotsuki to get here,
and then we'll move in.
[AKANE] Negative.
As long as he
has a Dominator,
all Enforcers should stay back!
[groans]
[screaming]
Aikawa!
[groans]
♪
[DISTRICT THREE
INSPECTOR groans]
[GINOZA] Tsunemori!
[AKANE] Ginoza!
[GINOZA] You okay?
[GINOZA] Both of the
Division Three Inspectors
are out of action. What now?
[AKANE] Karanomori. Lock in
on both Shisui's Dominators.
And send the
location to us.
Do you want
to attack them?
[AKANE] You guys
get out of here.
Your safety's the most
important thing right now.
Akane, please
don't do this!
An Inspector can't be
killed by a Dominator.
I have to! I'll capture Kamui.
[MIKA]
She's gone off the deep end.
Standing down the Enforcers
and chasing Kamui by herself.
Thinking she's
so smart and capable
with her perfect
little Psycho-Pass.
I hope it clouds up.
[MIKA] Wait. I shouldn't
say stuff like that.
[KUNIZUKA]
Her plan is crazy!
Those Dominators are guarded
by a whole army of Drones!
[door opens]
[SAIGA] So, the cloud
server that game's on--
Is it possible it's
been right in front of us?
[gasps] That's right!
[SHION] Why didn't I think
of this potential lead before?
If the Drones are
controlled by a server
in the Ministry
of National Defense,
then that would mean--
Bingo!
[gasps]
Now crack the code and
turn off the display Holo.
We don't want any
Psycho-Pass protection.
Hold on, Professor.
You want the players
to see all the killing?
It's the fastest way
to stop this madness.
The Defense Ministry
isn't doing us any favors.
Terminating the
Holo is gonna require
[SHION]
some heavy duty hacking.
[HINAKAWA]
Hey. I think I can do it.
You think, or you know?
I know. I can
help "Big Sis."
Good. Then I'll help him.
♪
[ALL] Huh?
[BOY STUDENT C] Whoa!
♪
[panting]
[SHION] Akane,
go to the end of the path
and turn right at the hangar.
There are fewer
Drones on that side!
[KUNIZUKA] We got
eight playable Holos,
each one comprised
of fifteen layers.
And we have to analyze
all of them quickly!
Yes. I know.
♪
Mmm!
[SUGO panting]
[grunts]
♪
[AKANE] Mr. Sugo!
[SUGO] Get up!
Hey! Why can't
I shoot anymore?
[DOMINATOR] Enforcement mode:
Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be
completely annihilated.
Aim carefully and
elimate the target.
[beeping from game]
[MAN] Oh, come on!
[panting]
[SAKUYA] Inspector!
[AKANE] Mr. Togane!
[GINOZA] An Inspector's
job is to babysit.
[AKANE] Ginoza!
[GINOZA] Let us
do what we're good at.
[SAKUYA] Hold on.
What just happened?
A safety mechanism keeps the
drones from shooting each other.
[SUGO] When two or
more of the same type are
within a certain radius...
their guns are designed
to automatically lock up.
You sure know this place well.
[AKANE] So?
Yes. I might have a plan.
[SUGO] There may be a way
for me to disable the Drones.
What do you mean "may"?
And what happens
if you fail?
Well then,
I'll die, that's all.
Wouldn't be much of a loss.
Enforcer Sugo, tell me
your plan, and I'll handle it.
[gasps]
Tsunemori!
[digital beeping]
[MAN] This is Shinjo,
Division Three.
Everyone here's dead. Please!
Help me!
[AKANE] Calm down.
We're on our way to you now.
[distant footsteps]
Huh?
[SHINJO panicked gasps]
[distant footsteps]
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient.
Three hundred eleven.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
[grunts] Crap! Crap! Crap!
[SHINJO] No--!
Enforcer Shinjo, come in!
Enforcer Shinjo!
[AKANE] Mister Sugo,
I'm ordering you!
Give me the instructions!
But ma'am, I--
Tsunemori, there's no
need for you to do this.
Hurry! Before there're
any more victims here!
All right, fine.
There's a testing area.
It's up ahead.
[AKANE] Let's go.
Hey, wait! Stay
close and be careful!
[Dominator beeping]
[SAKUYA] Hm.
Even at a time like this,
she's crystal clear.
[SAKUYA] Which is precisely
why I want to color her black.
[music and beeping from game]
[SUGO] The Drones are all
following Inspector Tsunemori.
We can use that
to lure them in here.
Well?
[SUGO] Drone firearms.
[SHION] Okay, Akane,
that's good. Keep it up.
What the--?
♪
[AKANE'S running footsteps]
[beeping from game]
♪
[panting]
[DOMINATOR] Enforcement mode.
Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be
completely annihilated.
[grunts]
Now!
♪
[AKANE] Uh!
[GINOZA groans]
[commotion]
[beeping tune]
Over where
Inspector Shisui is,
I'm seeing five
Dominators clustered.
I bet Kamui's there, too.
[GINOZA] I think
we've taken care of
just about all the Drones here.
[SHION] They're
heading for the docks.
Could be planning
to escape by sea.
[GINOZA] Whoa, hold on.
What're you gonna do with that?
I don't think our
Dominators will work on Kamui.
Do this and you'll
ruin your Psycho-Pass.
I'll take my chances.
Of course.
[SAKUYA] Hey, look.
[electronic beeping]
[music from game begins]
[MAN] Hey, free continue!
[FEMALE NURSE] Ah...!
They've taken over
our Drone network, too.
[SHION] We're losing
control of the situation.
♪
Hey! Guys!
It's done!
[KUNIZUKA] We're sending
it your way, Shion!
[SHION] You just
saved our asses, Sho!
[SAIGA] Great! Terminate
the game screen Holos as fast
as you can!
Time to lift the curtain.
What? We can't show the
players what they've done
with those Drones in real life!
Do you have any idea
how many Psycho-Passes
[MIKA] that will cloud?!
Dealing with the fallout
from that is your problem.
[MIKA] What?
If we do nothing, they'll
eventually take control
of all the Drones we
have. Do you want that?
[MAN groaning]
[MIKA] Our job isn't to make
people's Psycho-Passes worse!
Not all problems, my dear,
can be solved going by the book.
[exhales heavily]
[groaning]
[SUGO grunts]
Damn! I'm all out!
[SUGO] I'm sorry,
Enforcer Ginoza.
[GINOZA]
Just shut up and move!
[SHION] Okay!
Here goes nothing!
[SHION] Heh.
[ALL gasp]
♪
[MAN retches]
[BOY STUDENT E] What the
hell happened to our game?
[CIVILIANS ON SCREEN groaning]
[yowling]
[panting]
[AKANE] The Drones
have stopped moving!
[SHION chuckles]
Wait, look!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] An Area
Stress warning has been issued.
[MIKA] I said
this would happen!
There's no way we can handle
a stress warning this big!
[SAIGA] Whining is for
babies, not Inspectors.
Inspector Shimotsuki,
we have to move out.
But we...
Kamui's pulled off a case of
Group Psycho-Pass pollution.
[SAIGA] I think he's
methodically probing the entire
Sibyl System for weak points
and exploiting
every one he finds.
♪
[AKANE] Kamui!
[SHISUI gasps]
[AKANE panting]
[AKANE] The Dominator
doesn't even recognize him.
[AKANE] Like he's a ghost.
[DOMINATOR] Crime
Coefficient: Twenty-eight.
No enforcement action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
[KAMUI]
So that's your color.
It's clear, just as
I expected it to be.
[AKANE] Who are you,
Kamui? What do you want?
[KAMUI] Inspector Tsunemori,
when the judgment comes,
I want you to see
it with your own eyes.
[AKANE]
Judgment?
Hold it!
I know you won't
fire that gun at me.
♪
[AKANE]
No! Stop!
What are you doing?
I'm one of your hounds.
Let me do your dirty work.
[gasps]
♪
[AKANE] No!