[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Train is now arriving.
Please stand away
from the platform edge.
[MALE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER A]
Train A-1971 just accelerated
all of a sudden.
It's out of control.
[MALE CHIEF]
A runaway train?
[MALE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER A]
At this rate, it'll crash into
the one ahead of
it within minutes.
[MALE CHIEF] Clear out all
in-service trains immediately
and evacuate the passengers!
♪
[MALE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER A]
All trains are at the evac area.
[MALE CHIEF] Good,
now switch the tracks back.
[MALE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER B]
It's rejecting the signal.
[MALE CHIEF] What?
A-1971's headed
for the evac area?
[KAMUI] Let's begin.
[rushing water]
[MALE ANNOUNCER] We're
stopping momentarily for a
routine car inspection.
We apologize for
any inconvenience.
Please remain inside the train.
♪
[DOMINATOR] Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be
completely annihilated.
[SHION] The wastewater
facility in the sector where
the trains are
was just destroyed.
They got all of
the trains diverted to
the same spot, then
stranded them out there
using wastewater from
the neighboring area.
[GINOZA] Luckily, the
shelter's keeping them from
being submerged, but--
There isn't a way
to drain the water,
so the passengers
are stuck down there.
Kamui's gang cornered
themselves, too.
[GINOZA]
Why would they do that?
[beep]
Seems we've stripped the MLIT
of too much of their authority.
[KASEI] Now they can't even
drain a little wastewater.
[KASEI] Ah. Because we held
onto proof of the scandal
as a little insurance
policy in case they should
ever try to
take our place again.
That's the reason
Kamui's taken over
five hundred passengers
as his hostages.
Is that his goal?
No. If all he wanted was to
recreate the Season of Hell,
we would've been able
to eliminate him by now.
[gasps]
[police sirens]
This is too big.
Division Three can't
handle this alone.
♪
[SAKUYA] Just where do
you think you're going?
This is urgent. I need
to assess the situation,
and quickly devise a plan.
From the moment one
of your family members
was taken hostage,
you got too close
to continue with
this investigation.
Yeah, well, that's
my call to make.
I'm still the Inspector here.
But this decision came
straight from Chief Kasei.
Enforcer. Please step aside.
[shaky exhale]
[MIKA] It's not my fault.
It's not my fault.
[SAKUYA] That's right. Feel the
pain that comes from knowing
you are the reason someone
precious to you has died.
Akane Tsunemori,
paint yourself black.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
one hundred forty-eight.
Enforcement action required.
[PASSENGERS whimper]
[PASSENGERS scream]
Start with the ones who
might go over three hundred.
Knock them out using Paralyzer.
[FEMALE PASSENGER B crying]
[KUNIZUKA] They're shooting
passengers at random?
How can they do that?
[SHION] It's up to you now.
The Chief's ordered
Akane to sit this one out.
[MIKA] Right. I'm the
only one they've got.
I'm the head of
Division One now.
It's okay. I was just
acting in accordance
with Sibyl's will.
My Psycho-Pass can't
get clouded by this.
But our Dominators
don't work against Kamui.
So, what's our plan?
I'm not sure, but
we can't just sit back
and let him get
away with this.
[GINOZA] What's his
goal? If we knew that
we might stand a chance.
[MIKA] Kamui's main
goal is retaliation
against the Togane Foundation.
Which means this
subway attack must also
have a connection to that.
[AKANE] That's right. Both
the Kitazawa and Barricade
incidents had connections
to the Togane Foundation.
But what would these
attacks be retaliation for?
[MIKA] It's because of this.
The Togane Foundation
are the ones who
pushed for Kamui's surgery.
After the crash,
they used him in a
clinical trial
for their benefit.
[AKANE] Surgery.
A multi-body transplant.
This is Kamui's motive.
This is why I believe
he wants to retaliate
against the Foundation.
[MAN] Look at it fly.
So much data moving.
[KASEI] I see. I thought
this might be their plan.
[KAMUI] The Dominators capture
the details in front of them,
and relay that data
to Sibyl for a ruling.
[KAMUI] If enough Dominators are
heavily used at the same time,
the amount of data moving
around becomes massive,
overloading the normal
processing routes.
When that happens,
a bypass appears on the network
to handle the extra demand.
[KASEI] Ah, so
because security on our
back-up route isn't as good,
they want to trigger
its use with these attacks.
Kamui, I think
we've located the bypass.
That's good,
keep working on it.
[KASEI] You've collected all
those Dominators to help you
find the physical
location of the Sibyl System.
[KASEI]
Isn't that right, Kirito?
[KASEI] Inspector, I thought
I ordered you onto standby?
[AKANE] This isn't a
situation either of us
can afford to sit out.
I see. Then I shall assign
you a more specific task.
[AKANE] Assassinating Kamui.
That's right, Inspector.
[AKANE] I knew it.
How's that?
Considering the crimes
he's committed so far,
as well as how he's connected
to the Season of Hell,
it's obvious that
Kamui's final target
isn't the Togane Foundation.
He wants to
question the color...
[AKANE] of Sibyl itself.
And you're in a hurry
to have Kamui eliminated
because he's closing in
on the System's location.
[KASEI] You sure do like
sticking your nose where it
doesn't belong,
don't you, Inspector?
As you've correctly deduced,
I expect Kamui to
achieve his goal and
reach Sibyl in as little as
an hour, at his current rate.
Of course, I don't ever
intend to let that happen.
Because Division Three
was first on the scene,
I tasked them with
setting bombs in the tunnel
directly above the train
Kamui's taken prisoner.
What are you thinking?
You can't do that!
He's got five hundred innocent
passengers down there!
[KASEI] I would think an
Inspector would realize that
normal people's Crime
Coefficients don't exactly
stay healthy when
they're taken hostage
in a cramped environment
by a murderous cult.
Most are latent
criminals by now.
[AKANE] That's not reason
enough to just kill them all!
This is absurd!
[KASEI] This plan's
not up for discussion.
And it's your duty
to follow my orders.
Oversee the detonation.
Push the button yourself.
I can see through this.
You just want to kill Kamui!
[KASEI] I want to
protect society and Sibyl.
Unless we stop Kamui's
attempts to destroy
all that we've built,
many more will die.
One more thing.
[KASEI] I've just received
some very unfortunate news.
[KASEI] Moments ago,
the body of your grandmother,
Aoi Tsunemori, was found
in the warehouse district.
[gasps]
[KASEI] It looks like the
perpetrator tied her up
and then beat her to death.
It's a rather cruel way to die.
[AKANE sobs]
[KASEI] I'm putting
the trigger in your hands,
so you can end this.
Protect the
society we call home.
I have faith in you,
Inspector Tsunemori.
[SAKUYA] Kill him,
Akane. Kill Kamui.
[SAKUYA] Come to terms
with your lack of control,
and embrace your true self.
Give in to your desire to kill.
Then you're certain
to paint your Hue black.
[AKANE breathing heavily]
[AKANE screams]
[breathing heavily]
[KOGAMI] Well.
Are you gonna kill him?
[police sirens]
[MIKA] Blow it up?
And they don't even want to
watch the Togane Foundation's
buildings in case
they're targeted?
[MIKA] Why are we only
hearing about this now?
This is our first priority.
Your division
will be on stand-by.
I don't get it.
♪
We're running out of
time to save those hostages!
What is going on?
[AKANE] I don't know.
Maybe I should do it.
That's not like you.
Remember what you said?
"The law doesn't protect people.
It's the people
who protect the law."
[KOGAMI] The reason you
tried to stop me was because
you believed that to be true.
[AKANE]
Yes, it was... at the time.
Hmph. Well, who am I
to lecture you on this?
[AKANE] Sibyl has no
way of judging Kamui.
But we have to
stop him somehow.
I have no other choice.
[KOGAMI] You're wrong.
It's not that you
have no other options,
just none are
presenting themselves.
You already have all the
pieces you need to solve this.
You're just
hesitating right now.
[AKANE] There's no room
for failure here, but I--
[KOGAMI] Isn't it worth taking
a chance? Don't let them win.
Ah!
[sighs]
[AKANE] Thank you for that.
What're you--?
[AKANE] Mister Kuwashima.
I have a favor to ask.
Huh?
[digital beeping]
[AKANE] Kirito Kamui?
This is Inspector Akane
Tsunemori from the CID.
I'm with Division One.
How's my friend Koichi doing?
[AKANE] After I had
a little chat with him,
he became very cooperative.
[AKANE] Sibyl's trying to bury
you along with all the hostages.
[KAMUI] We'll find a way
out before that happens.
[AKANE] If you do,
you'll be met by an army
of Inspectors and Enforcers.
There's no way that you'll
ever get past all of them.
Do you honestly believe
I'm scared of you people?
[AKANE] Listen, Kamui,
if you release the hostages,
I'll give you what you want.
I sent you a map of
the subway tunnels.
Go to the spot that I've
marked on it. There, I'll--
[digital humming]
[KASEI] What do you
think you're doing?
[AKANE] It's the
omnipotence paradox.
The reason why Kamui's
been doing all of this
is to judge the Sibyl System.
And I believe you should
welcome that judgment,
since it will allow
you to judge him as well.
[AKANE] You've tried to create
this perfect system of justice
by incorporating criminally
asymptomatic people,
the very people you
weren't able to judge.
However, a new exception
has presented himself.
[AKANE] Kamui exists
as a collective entity,
not as an individual.
In order to judge him,
Sibyl has no choice but to
accept the concept
that defines him.
[KASEI] You don't
understand, Inspector.
To evaluate someone
like him, we'd need to
measure his Psycho-Pass
as a collective entity.
But if we changed
the judgment parameters
to make that possible...
[AKANE] Sibyl,
another collective entity,
would become subject
to judgment, too.
That was his goal all along.
By making himself
a threat to society,
he creates a situation
where you're forced to
acknowledge a
collective Psycho-Pass,
which then presents a paradox.
And the solution to it
enables him to judge you.
[KASEI] All the more reason
why we mustn't allow this man
to get anywhere near Sibyl.
[AKANE] And to stop Kamui,
you would kill him
without judging him?
Thus violating
your own perfection?
[KASEI] You're so focused on
the immediate problem at hand
that you've lost sight
of the bigger picture.
The price our society would
have to pay once it began
to accept the notion of
a collective Psycho-Pass.
A world where the
potential exists to condemn
a group despite each
individual being clear.
[AKANE] I understand the risk.
However, if you confront
head-on this scenario
you've been desperately
trying to prevent,
it might just lead
to you evolving as well.
On the other hand,
if you continue to resist it,
and choose to take the easy
way out by killing Kamui,
then this system has no future.
I'm tired of listening
to your pompous conjecture.
If you insist on going
rogue and acting on your own
I'll rescind your
rights as an Inspector.
And we'll have to seriously
consider removing you
from this society
along with Kamui.
[AKANE] Frankly, Misako Togane,
your individual
opinion doesn't matter!
[AKANE] Sibyl System. The
only reason you guys have been
permitted to exist
in this society at all
is that you dispense
pure, impartial justice.
But now that there's a gap
in that perfect objectivity,
the value of your existence
has to be called into question.
You don't know
what you're saying.
How can you continue to serve
a purpose in this society now?
What steps do
you need to take?
[AKANE] Think it over
long and hard, as a group.
You really want us
to blow it up, Chief?
[KASEI] Yes, do it now.
Roger that!
[HYODO] This is for
Aikawa! You're toast!
What the hell is this?
Where's my boom?
[gasps]
[footsteps]
[SHISUI] Because the MWPSB isn't
equipped with high explosives,
the only ones you
can get your hands on
are those you've seized
during investigations.
And there was only one
incident in the last few months
that involved explosives.
[SHISUI] Kitazawa
constructed his so we could
control their countdowns
and detonations, remotely.
[SHISUI] Isn't that wonderful?
Kamui can see through
anything that's in his way.
That's why he has the
gift of making people clear.
All that's left is to
keep the MWPSB tied up here.
[gasps for air]
It won't be long
before Kamui finishes
making the entire world clear.
[water sloshing]
[SHISUI] The water's draining!
They must have used
a different pumping station!
♪
[PASSENGERS yowling]
[KUNIZUKA] The hostages
have been released?
Roger that. We'll go
and apprehend Kamui's crew.
Okay, Inspector?
This can't be true.
This isn't my fault.
I would never--
Inspector,
what're you doing?
[HINAKAWA] Uh. Huh?
Is something wrong?
Where did Enforcer Togane go?
[gasps]
[footsteps]
[SAKUYA] Inspector.
Sorry for the surprise.
Chief Kasei said
I'd find you down here.
I was hoping I could join you.
[AKANE] Why?
[SAKUYA] By now, you must
be aware of the connection
between Doctor Misako
Togane and Kamui.
[SAKUYA] My mother's responsible
for that monster's birth.
And as her son, it falls
on me to make things right,
even if in the end my
hands are left bloodied.
So then that's it.
You're going to kill him.
[SAKUYA] If Kogami were in my
shoes, he'd do the same thing.
Alright. Let's go.
[AKANE scoffs]
[SAKUYA] Hmph.
Your acting doesn't
fool me, Enforcer Togane.
[AKANE] That multi-body
brain transplant
your mother performed on Kamui.
I know a system based
on the same principle.
[AKANE] Which of course means
she knew about it, then.
But most of society isn't
privy to that knowledge.
Except for the
criminally asymptomatic.
If Misako Togane was
one of those people,
the Sibyl System
must've taken her in.
So when it comes to this
case, it's all but certain
she's pushed for herself
to be in charge of it.
[AKANE] In other words, the
person controlling Chief Kasei
is Misako Togane.
[SAKUYA] Inspector. I don't
have the slightest clue
what you're talking about.
I had a chance to read through
all of your personal info;
the truth about you,
that's been hidden.
[AKANE] It all started with
Inspector Shimotsuki's report.
There were many parts
that contradicted your
established background.
So I re-examined your file.
[SAKUYA] Interesting move.
You drove all the other
Inspectors you've worked with
into becoming latent criminals.
At first, I didn't want
to believe it was true.
[AKANE] At the very
least, I wanted to think
you weren't doing
it intentionally.
[SAKUYA] Just like Mr. Saiga.
Not him. You're nothing alike.
[AKANE] If I think back to
everything you've said and done
since this case began,
it becomes clear to me
what your true motives are.
Now I'm the one you
want to paint black.
Am I wrong?
[KAMUI] Even someone
of your abilities
can't color this Inspector.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
Kirito Kamui.
[SAKUYA] Well,
this makes things easier.
[SAKUYA] Just the fact
that you exist at all
sullies my mother,
Kamui. Which means--
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
seven hundred sixty-nine.
Lethal Eliminator.
[SAKUYA] I can't
let you exist anymore!
[AKANE]
Don't shoot!
[KAMUI]
Be gone, black soul.