[FEMALE COMMERCIAL VOICE]
Do you stay up all night
worrying about your Hue?
Do you live in fear that
stress or a mental disorder
will brand you a latent
criminal and send you
to a rehab facility?
Well, worry no more!
Psycho-Pass Treatments have
evolved to the next level!
Kick your fears in the
rear with the Hue-saving,
psychotropic drug, LACOUSE!
[PROMOTION GIRL A]
Try some LACOUSE!
You won't be
disappointed! Thanks!
[PROMOTION GIRL B]
Free LACOUSE sample!
Get a healthy Psycho-Pass!
[PROMOTION GIRL A] Here!
LACOUSE, sir? It really works!
[PROMOTION GIRL A]
Free samples!
[PROMOTION GIRL B] Try LACOUSE!
Kick your fears in the rear!
[MALE] No thanks.
Bye.
♪
[beep]
[explosion]
[GIRLS scream]
[police sirens]
[ambulance sirens]
[SHION] At precisely six
o'clock, a video claiming
responsibility for tonight's
bombing was uploaded
to all major
video-sharing services.
Just like the three
previous bombings.
It's all lies. The Sibyl
System has deceived us.
[SHION] Right after the blast,
a quick cymatic scan of
the crime scene
turned up an individual
whose Hue had abruptly
changed for the worse.
[MASKED MAN] We are
flesh-and-blood citizens!
[AKANE] Abruptly changed?
Ms. Karanomori.
Please run an ID match for
that person and
the guy in the video.
[SHION] If we estimate the
length of his vocal cords
based on his bone structure,
and lay that over the video.
Bingo!
[SHION] The man's
name is Akira Kitazawa.
He's a building
demolition site supervisor.
Demolitions, huh?
That means high explosives.
We have to stay
on Kitazawa while
the trail's still hot.
Trace his movements
on the area map.
[SHION] You got it.
[AKANE] Drones can handle
the bomb site inspection.
Inspector Shimotsuki,
reprogram our route.
[MIKA] Understood.
[police sirens]
♪
[AKANE] This is where the
demolition company that employs
Kitazawa stores its equipment.
A security camera
recorded him entering
the place twenty minutes ago.
[GINOZA] He also hinted
in that video manifesto
that he's got more bombs.
So things could
get even worse.
Yeah. And with people
already on pins and needles
from one blast, the Area Stress
Level could rise quickly.
[AKANE] All right, then;
here's the plan.
Division Two will
work alongside us.
Ginoza!
[AKANE] Please assist
Inspector Shimotsuki.
[GINOZA] Okay.
♪
Enforcer Togane.
Enforcer Hinakawa.
[AKANE] I'm sorry your
first case has to be
such a difficult one.
Please proceed with caution.
Sir, yes, sir.
[DOMINATOR] Activating Dominator
Portable Psychological Diagnosis
and Suppression System.
[DOMINATOR] User authentication,
Inspector Akane Tsunemori,
Public Safety Bureau, Criminal
Investigation Department.
Dominator usage approved.
You are a valid user.
[MIKA] Inspector Tsunemori.
Why are we just standing
around out here? Let's move in.
The bomber's Psycho-Pass.
Why do you think it didn't
cloud during the
previous bombing attacks?
[MIKA] Kitazawa's a building
demolition site supervisor.
Making bombs isn't
difficult for someone
with his training.
[GINOZA] Yeah, but doing it for
his work is a different thing.
I didn't ask for
your opinion, Enforcer.
[sighs]
Normally, if you're
planning a big terrorist attack,
your Psycho-Pass will worsen.
[AKANE] Preparing a series
of bombs just isn't something
you do if you want
to keep your Hue clear.
[GINOZA]
But the facts don't lie.
Kitazawa's Psycho-Pass
didn't get bad
until after the explosion.
So what you're saying
then, Mr. Ginoza,
is that our man has some
way to keep his Hue clear.
[MIKA] Does any of that
really matter right now?
Is that something
we need to know
in order to get this guy?
[digital beeping]
[AOYANAGI]
Inspector Tsunemori.
I agree with Shimotsuki.
We've gotta charge in now.
[KOMISSA] This is the Criminal
Investigation Department of
the Public Safety
Bureau. We are issuing...
[AOYANAGI] Due to
the earlier bombings,
the Area Stress Level's
skyrocketing to a record high.
We need to take care
of this bomber fast,
before any new latent
criminals are created.
[AKANE] Hold on.
[AOYANAGI]
I'm through wasting time.
Two! Move in now!
[AKANE] Please, just wait!
[MIKA] Inspector.
We should go, too!
[AKANE] No.
Are you serious?
[AKANE] Ms. Aoyanagi.
Listen to me.
In all these bombings, there
hasn't been a single casualty.
That leads me to
believe that this guy
went out of his way to
not harm innocent civilians.
But if that's the case,
what's his goal?
When you look at all
the possible effects of
an explosion, one thing
you can be sure of
is a heightened
Area Stress Level.
Damn, it's cold in here.
[AKANE] Something else you
can count on is that the MWPSB
will pursue the suspect.
Does that mean?
[AKANE] It's quite possible the
bomber's just been baiting us,
trying to lure
us into an ambush.
[gasps]
[MALE ENFORCER] Get out! Now!
[explosion]
Damn it. Looks like
you were right all along.
[SAKUYA] Unfortunately.
[ALL groan]
[groans]
[FEMALE INSPECTOR]
Let's go, Yamatoya!
[YAMATOYA] All right.
[AKANE] Inspector
Shimotsuki! Stay alert!
Don't have
to tell me that!
[tires screech]
[GINOZA] Stop that truck!
It's on auto-drive!
[KUNIZUKA] Watch out!
A diversion.
Are you okay, Inspector?
Yes, thank you.
[SAKUYA] Inspector!
♪
Stop!
Uh! Hold fire!
There's a hostage!
[car accelerates]
[SAKUYA] Hey, Inspector!
Look at this guy's back.
Mr. Togane,
Mr. Hinakawa.
Please chase down the suspect.
I'll hang back here
and take care of this.
[MIKA] What?
She's got it backwards!
The Enforcers should
be used as shields.
[DOMINATOR] The Target's Threat
Judgment has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Destroy Decomposer.
[DOMINATOR] Target will
be completely annihilated.
Please proceed
with maximum caution.
[distant footsteps]
[MIKA] Are you
all right? Inspector?
[AKANE] We're going
after him. Come on!
Geez, I was just
worried about you.
[police sirens]
Enforcers' hands are
effectively tied without
an Inspector by their side.
[FEMALE INSPECTOR]
Surely you know that.
[chuckles]
We've got a
lock on the target.
He's moving along Route Twenty,
making his way towards Shinjuku.
[AKANE] We'll cut off all
possible exits and force him
into the Yoyogi Park area.
Inspector Shimotsuki,
please work with
the Enforcers to
evacuate the vicinity.
[MIKA] Why me?
Is it because you're
worried about my Psycho-Pass?
You think it'll get
clouded if I'm in the fray?
[MIKA] Don't underestimate me.
I'm not a rookie anymore.
I've been an Inspector
for a year-and-a-half.
I can do the job and
keep my Psycho-Pass clear.
She sure is confident.
[WOMAN] Shisui,
Division Two, reporting in.
Situation has changed.
It looks like our
suspect is releasing
the female hostage
that he took.
[AKANE] The timing's weird.
[SHISUI]
I agree. Something's up.
Karanomori?
I'm here.
I knew you'd be calling.
Son of a bitch.
[SHION] I was
not expecting this.
So, you know that hostage
our perp just let go?
[SHION] She's not real.
A Hologram. Has to be it.
He's setting us up.
[SHISUI] A trap?
[AKANE] Yes.
Despite excelling at
academics from an early age,
Kitazawa's path
to becoming one of
society's elites was blocked.
His occupational aptitude
assessments revealed a Hue
that was easily clouded.
[panting]
[AKANE] Between that
background, his video,
and his actions
at the warehouse,
we've got a
pretty clear profile.
[AKANE] He thinks society
deprived him of a better life,
so he's getting back at it...
...by attacking us, the PSB.
[AKANE] And the most
effective method he has for
achieving that goal right now,
is to draw his pursuers
in close by
releasing the hostage.
Because waiting there
with her for us to catch up
will most certainly be...
a bomb.
So, you're saying as
long as we're giving chase,
we're playing
right into his trap.
[AKANE] Shisui, you and your
men find and disable that bomb.
You can leave Kitazawa to us.
[SHISUI] Okay. Will do.
[tires screech]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[WOMAN and CHILD whimper]
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient
is three hundred two.
Enforcement action required.
[AKANE gasps]
[DOMINATOR] Enforcement
mode: Lethal Eliminator.
Trigger safety released.
Aim carefully and
eliminate the target.
Back off!
--[MOTHER] Oh, my God!
--[CHILD] Mommy!
[gasps]
[AKANE] No!
Inspector?
Hinakawa, get down!
[HINAKAWA] Everyone okay?
[gasps]
[AKANE] Wait!
Don't. He can still be saved.
We're aiming
for Two-Nine-Nine.
♪
[GINOZA] I get it.
Two-Nine-Nine, huh?
She's something else.
So, the plan--
Go!
[GINOZA] We'll back
up the Inspector!
[KITAZAWA yells]
[KITAZAWA] What's the
problem? Shoot me already!
Isn't that the
right thing to do?
[AKANE] I won't shoot you.
Because if I do it right now,
the Dominator will kill you.
[KOMISSA]
Your attention, please.
This is the Criminal
Investigation Department...
[GINOZA] Everyone,
get out of here! Now!
Let's move!
Hey! Remain calm and orderly!
Why do I have to do this?
[KOMISSA] ...and exit
in an orderly fashion.
[AOYANAGI] Ginoza!
What are you doing?
We're supposed
to be hunting down
and eliminating the suspect.
Tsunemori is...
[GINOZA] trying something
different tonight.
[GINOZA] Think you can give
her a pass for the time being?
You know, for not
going by the book on this?
You sure changed.
Of course. I've worked
with her a long time.
It's natural.
[KUNIZUKA] Ginoza! A Division
Two Enforcer is moving
to the building next door.
[GINOZA] Got it.
Hey, wait!
Now what?
[MIKA] So, that's what she
meant by "Two-Nine-Nine."
I can't believe her.
An Inspector should not be
making up their own rules.
If you shut out those
you disagree with
or close your eyes and try
to pretend they aren't there,
you'll only end
up regretting it.
[GINOZA] Learn to
accept what's happening
in front of your nose as fact.
That's a little shortcut
to adulthood. Okay, Missy.
[KITAZAWA gasps]
Stay back!
We're all just puppets
being manipulated by Sibyl!
We're slaves to the System!
[KITAZAWA] Don't you
think that's messed up?
[KITAZAWA] No free
will! Our potential,
our futures decided for us!
Only a select few benefiting
at all from this racket!
Well, what does that
make the rest of us, huh?
Worthless garbage
to be tossed aside?
[AKANE] No. That's not
true. You have value!
You serve a purpose and
so do those bombs you made!
Are you crazy?
Why would you say that?
[AKANE] Society doesn't
always do the right thing.
Which is why we ourselves
have to lead virtuous lives.
[KITAZAWA] But I--
[AKANE] Your innate desire
to right systemic wrongs,
not to mention
your technical skills.
Those are things
society needs more of.
Society isn't
some monolithic beast.
It's made up of
individuals like you.
By simply living
a virtuous life,
you move society towards
the path of virtue.
I admire your sense
of justice. It's noble.
[SAKUYA] You're more than
just a cog in the machine.
Even when society
pressures you,
as long as you resist it...
you can remain
human. Just stay strong.
[AKANE] Mr. Togane.
What the hell are
they waiting for?
[DOMINATOR] Target is
a registered Enforcer.
Status, enforce at will.
Hm.
[AOYANAGI] Put the gun down!
Ginoza!
What is... going on?
[KITAZAWA crying]
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient
is two hundred ninety-nine.
The target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement mode:
Non-Lethal Paralyzer.
Trigger safety released.
Aim calmly and
subdue the target.
This is justice.
[KITAZAWA falls on ground]
[AKANE inhales]
[shaky exhale]
[AKANE] It was a team effort!
Thank you all for your help!
You know that an
enforcement target's
Crime Coefficient
almost never decreases.
In fact, I'd say it's
practically unheard of.
[MIKA] And yet your strategy was
to gamble on it happening here.
Sibyl had made a decision.
That creep didn't
deserve to draw breath!
But you--
Bought time.
In the end, Sibyl
reversed that initial,
hasty assessment.
Which is good, because
we still need to find out
how he was able to
make all of those bombs
while keeping his Hue clear.
I made a judgment call with
the future firmly in mind.
[MIKA] Inspector. On this one...
you're flat-out wrong.
♪
It's a... Holo?
[FEMALE HOLOGRAM] So naïve.
Just because something is
fabricated doesn't necessarily
negate its existence.
You failed to recognize that.
[SHISUI gasps]
[MAN] Which is why...
I am here.
[DOMINATOR] Crime
Coefficient is forty-eight.
Target is a
registered Inspector.
Warning: Any rebellious
conduct by an Enforcer
will be recorded and
reported to headquarters.
[YAMATOYA yells]
[SHISUI] You can't.
[AKANE] So, it was a
new beginning for me.
The start of
my own personal battle
to decide who I really am.