[SAKUYA] I can't
let you exist anymore!
[AKANE]
Don't shoot!
[KAMUI]
Be gone, black soul.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
thirty-one.
Enforcement action not required.
The trigger is now locked.
[AKANE and SAKUYA struggling]
[SAKUYA grunting]
[AKANE, SAKUYA grunt]
[SAKUYA] Kamui's the reason
your grandmother's dead!
He's the bad guy!
It's unlikely Kamui had
anything to do with her murder.
[SAKUYA]
Are you blind?
That psycho had her
kidnapped and beaten!
[AKANE] It's true that
he has the means to
track down my family.
But the MWPSB can
do it just as easily.
You'd really suspect
your own colleagues
over a proven murderer?
You're just afraid of
clouding your Psycho-Pass.
So you're repressing all your
negative emotion toward him.
[SAKUYA] You can't eliminate
your desire to kill!
[sighs]
[AKANE] There have been
countless innocent lives
I've failed to protect
even though that's my job.
But still.
That doesn't mean
I should just give up
protecting our society.
[AKANE] Let's go.
No, don't! Akane!
[SAKUYA] I won't
let you disgrace me!
And I certainly won't
let you disgrace my mother!
[WOMAN LACKEY grunts]
Fire!
[GINOZA] Hold it, Shisui!
[yelps]
Kamui, I can still help you!
She's using neuroactive
drugs to keep fighting.
You'll see. It's coming.
Kamui's going to
change... everything!
[KAMUI] What made you
decide to show me the path?
[AKANE] I wanna
judge you the correct way.
[KAMUI] You could've gone
outside the law to stop me.
In my view, that's
not a legitimate option.
[MUKOJIMA]
It's obvious to me now.
Your devotion to justice
is also what keeps you clear.
What now? What do you think
Sibyl's reaction will be?
Will the act of
judging us destroy it?
[MUKOJIMA] In this
"ideal" society that has
sacrificed its humanity,
what is the morally
correct judgment?
It's finally our turn
to judge the Sibyl System!
There's one more
possibility. You.
[AKANE] All of you, I mean.
You have to be
aware of it, right?
What if Sibyl doesn't
give you the answer you want?
Will you still move forward?
I had to know why
we died in that crash.
I looked for the meaning
of life as a dead person,
[KAMUI] and it led me here.
So many have their
hopes riding on me.
Everyone's being abused,
under the pretenses of healing.
It's my duty to save them.
We'll judge Sibyl.
There's no other
way to save people.
People's anger is what
truly makes society clear.
It's a high-stakes poker game,
between us and the system.
You could've taken
a non-violent path.
[AKANE] Instead of becoming
a champion for anyone
with a grudge against society.
[KAMUI] That was never
an option for me.
Even if you and I had gotten
to know each other sooner.
[KASEI] I understand my
little Frankenstein's monster
has been causing
quite the commotion.
Misako Togane.
They haven't reached a
judgment yet, am I right?
Akane Tsunemori.
Your privileges as an MWPSB
Inspector are
henceforth revoked.
[KASEI] You'll be put
down like the dog you are.
If that's Sibyl's
true judgment of me,
[AKANE] I'll walk through
these doors and hear it myself.
[AKANE] Kamui?
It's time to put our lives
on the line and ask you this:
[KAMUI] Sibyl.
Can you see what color we are?
[SAKUYA grunts]
[panting]
[SAKUYA] I never needed anything
else. So long as I had Mother.
[SAKUYA] And yet.
[MISAKO] It's time I
said goodbye, my son.
Huh?
[MISAKO] I'm leaving to
become a member of the entity
that rules over our society.
Don't be sad;
it's a wonderful thing!
[MISAKO] Eventually, you'll
be led to the same place, too.
Goodbye.
[MISAKO] Sakuya?
[MISAKO gasps]
[BOY SAKUYA] You
belong with me, Mother!
[BOY SAKUYA yells]
[yells]
[SAKUYA] And so,
I painted myself black.
[KASEI] Latent criminals,
Enforcers, even Inspectors.
No matter who they are,
you purposely worsen
their Psycho-Pass then
administer punishment.
Why do you do that?
Because that is the very
reason for my existence.
[SAKUYA] My purpose in
life is to darken souls,
even the pure ones,
until they turn pitch black.
By my doing so, Mother,
you can remain beautiful
and shine brightly. That's why.
It's because I love you.
[SAKUYA] Mother.
[SAKUYA groans]
[DOMINATOR] No enforcement
action required.
Trigger will remain locked.
No use.
Listen, Sibyl System. If you
truly are gods of judgment,
then there's only
one choice before you.
[KAMUI] The one challenge
you need to overcome in order
to maintain perfection is
standing right in front of you!
Can you judge us?
Well, can you?
[KAMUI] Can you question
our color and your own?
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
over three hundred.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
You can't.
[KAMUI] So this is your
true color, Misako Togane.
[KASEI groans]
I will not abide--
--a change like this!
[blood sploshing]
Judgment has come at last.
♪
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
over three hundred.
Enforcement mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
Nice to finally
know your color, Sibyl.
[SIBYL] Welcome, Kirito Kamui.
Upon careful deliberation,
we've decided to
acknowledge all of
you together, as a group.
Also, as Akane
Tsunemori recommended,
we will begin to
institute and monitor
a collective Psycho-Pass.
As a result, we will
take action to discard any
and all elements that
increase our Crime Coefficient.
[SIBYL] Through this
revolutionary adjustment,
we have now
obtained a new level
of awareness and perfection.
In this manner, we continue
to evolve and flourish.
[DOMINATOR]
Crime Coefficient, zero.
The Target's Threat Judgment
has been reappraised.
Enforcement action
no longer required.
The trigger is now locked.
[AKANE] This is the
answer. Kirito Kamui...
You are under arrest.
♪
Let's go!
[digital beeping]
[SHISUI breathing heavily]
[GINOZA] Surrender!
It's over now!
[SHISUI groans]
Give it up! Shisui!
[SHISUI]
No. We're not done yet!
I'll be your vessel, Kamui.
This is all for you!
[SHISUI] Those confiscated
bombs that Division Three
planted to try and kill us.
Looks like you're the ones
who'll be buried here by them!
[GINOZA] Don't do it!
Thanks for everything, Kamui.
Sorry, I cut it close.
[sighs] Yeah, you did.
But you made it in time.
Yeah.
Hm.
[HINAKAWA] She's okay.
Still breathing.
Well, we brought back your
junior Inspector, Aoyanagi.
[MIKA] But we're in the
middle of an operation!
[SAKUYA] Just do what I say!
Now, you should have
a lock on my location.
So come and get me!
♪
[SAKUYA] Mother?
[SAKUYA shaky exhales]
[SAKUYA screams]
Things can't stay like this.
Everything that's happened
is his fault. Sakuya.
[MIKA] The Chief just ordered
me onto a different objective.
Follow Inspector Domoto's
lead 'til I get back.
Wait, what? Hey!
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
over four hundred.
Enforcement Mode:
Lethal Eliminator.
What color am I? Can you tell?
[SIBYL] Inspector Tsunemori:
We recommend that
you administer
justice, promptly.
Do not resist.
Hand over the Dominator.
I can feel it.
Even some in that inhuman
monstrosity are happy to have
their colors judged again.
You think so?
We're not done.
You should try
pointing that barrel
at Sibyl yourself.
If it's seen as a
true collective now,
then whoever
holds the Dominator
becomes part of it
and how it thinks.
Through the moral
lens of that person,
[KAMUI] the Dominator may
reveal a different color.
That's your plan?
Sibyl can never go
back to how things were.
[KAMUI] Someday, a truly
worthy judge will appear
before this beast.
And then no matter how
many brains Sibyl removes
from the collective, its
Crime Coefficient will remain
high by the judge's standard.
[AKANE] Was that your
goal from the very start?
[SIBYL] Administer
justice, Inspector.
[KAMUI] It's possible
the judge is already here.
The person standing
in front of me right now.
[AKANE] Stop it.
I'm not like you, Kamui.
I'm not fueled by revenge
or by what other
people want from me.
Why, Kamui? Why did you have
to take the violent path?
[KAMUI and HOLOGRAMS]
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
It was the only way.
Get out of this place!
You desecrators!
[AKANE] Stand down, now!
[SAKUYA] I like that
look in your eyes.
[SAKUYA] You do realize,
Akane, that I'm the one who
bludgeoned your
grandmother to death, right?
[AKANE gasps]
[SAKUYA] For a shriveled up old
lady, she put up a real fight.
She was crying your name.
"Help me, Akane, please!"
♪
[KAMUI] There's
one more possibility.
You're aware of it,
too, aren't you?
It's the spirit of the law
that matters most to you.
If that way of thinking
were introduced into Sibyl
and then used to rebalance
our scales of justice,
then one day, that
spirit of the law
may change that monster into
a real god for our society.
♪
[SAKUYA] This is impossible!
There's no way that you can be
more pure than my mother!
♪
[SAKUYA and KAMUI grunt]
[SAKUYA whimpers]
Why won't...
your soul turn black?
[AKANE] Sakuya Togane.
You're under arrest. Charges:
The planned murder
of Aoi Tsunemori,
[AKANE] and acts of rebellion.
[shaky exhales]
[yelling]
[SIBYL]
Inspector Akane Tsunemori.
We have followed
your suggestion.
And it is with great
relief that we announce
we have solved the
problems and contradictions
inherent to the
previous version of Sibyl.
[SIBYL] However, with our
current processing ability,
we are still unable
to calculate a collective
Psycho-Pass for the
citizenry as a whole.
While we work to
achieve that goal,
we recommend you
continue to contribute
to society and live
a healthy, clear life.
♪
[SAKUYA] Look who's here.
[DOMINATOR] Crime Coefficient,
eight hundred ninety-nine.
Enforcement mode.
Lethal Eliminator.
You call yourself
the son of Sibyl?
You're pitch black.
[SAKUYA] Mother.
You and I, we have...
something in common.
We're both slaves
to Sibyl after all.
I can never forgive myself
for following your orders.
And there's no way I can
remain clear unless I do this.
[SAKUYA chuckles]
So she's your new lackey, huh?
Tying up loose ends?
Try to do your best
and devote your life
to keeping Sibyl... beautiful.
I can't keep someone who
clouds my Psycho-Pass around.
[MIKA] I need you gone!
I won't. I can't take
it any further than this.
[MIKA] I'll keep this a secret.
No, I'll forget everything!
I know nothing!
I trust--I trust
the Sibyl System!
And I--I love this
society we live in!
[DOMOTO] Akane Tsunemori!
I know your privileges as
an Inspector have been rescinded
due to insubordination.
Do not resist.
Now put your hands--.
[GINOZA] Hold on! Look again!
Her rights. They've
been fully restored.
[AKANE] Tell me.
Now what color am I?
♪
[GINOZA] Crystal clear.
[MIKA] I tracked down escaped
Enforcer Sakuya Togane.
He died before I
could render justice.
This concludes my report.
[SAIGA] Well, thanks for
escorting me back to this place.
[AKANE] Your Psycho-Pass is well
on its way to a full recovery.
You don't have to be here.
I know the reason why
it's been improving.
And being dependent
doesn't really suit me, so--
[AKANE]
I'll come back and visit!
[SAIGA] Look forward to it.
A man who clouds
the Psycho-Pass of
everyone he's around?
Now that he's gone away,
feels like I
missed my opportunity.
[KUNIZUKA]
According to Kuwashima,
the person who
leaked the location of
Inspector Tsunemori's
grandmother
was Enforcer Sakuya Togane.
But unfortunately, we'll
probably never find out
how he got it, now
that Sakuya's on a slab.
That's too bad.
Whoever helped him,
I'll never forgive them.
[MIKA] Hm.
[MIKA] Me neither.
[KASEI] As the result of recent
events, we have a number
of vacancies to
fill within the system.
In fact, some of us have
suggested that we bring you in.
If your desire is change
there's no better way to
effect it than from the inside.
You don't really want that,
so are you trying to
provoke me? Is that it?
[KASEI] I suppose
that means you're
turning down the proposal?
For now, yes.
But when the time comes
that you're truly ready to
rid the world of yourselves,
I'll be right there
to help you do it.
[KASEI]
A collective Psycho-Pass.
In the not-so-distant
future, there will be a
society where group
evaluations are the norm.
Even if each
individual is clear,
it's conceivable that
collectively, they won't be.
The fear and doubt this will
cause could lead to chaos.
There may be
witch-hunts the likes
of which we've never seen.
And as a result,
we would begin to see
judgments quickly dissolve
into brutal massacres; anarchy.
And the one who made
it all possible is you.
[AKANE] I'm not as
pessimistic as you are.
I think this will lead to
more righteous law and order,
and greater peace and freedom.
Your trademark foolish optimism.
[AKANE] Maybe I'm being naïve,
but we won't know unless we try.
It's not society that
determines people's futures.
It's people who
determine society's future.
That's it.
That's what I believe.
[footsteps]
[door opens, closes]