[ENDEAVOR growls]
[yells]
What happened to...
to my strength?
[MIRIO]
The sedative worked!
[BEST JEANIST] I do not know
who accomplished this...
...but our hopes
have been repaired.
The fact that
this drug kicked in
at the 11th hour
isn't a coincidence.
We've been chipping away at
this villain little by little,
using whatever meager power
we were able to cobble together.
Sacrificing ourselves to break
his spirit and slow him down.
We held him off as best we could
until the drug had
time to take effect.
If I've learned one thing
through my Quirk,
it's that, though a
single fiber is weak,
it can be braided with others
to form a mighty rope.
[BEST JEANIST coughs]
Had even one thread broken,
we would have failed.
It's only together that we've
woven a tapestry of faith.
[MR. COMPRESS grunting]
[MR. COMPRESS]
What a shameful predicament.
All I can do is grope
my own posterior.
You're no better, Shigaraki.
Remember why you
summoned us here?
We were supposed to gather
together and create a spectacle.
What'd you have to go
and get beaten up for?
Now we're trapped!
There's so much left
in this world to destroy.
[MR. COMPRESS]
It's just as Spinner said.
We haven't done anything yet.
Not Dabi.
Nor Toga.
Nor I.
None of us have
achieved our dreams!
[BEST JEANIST]
Blackout Bind!
[MR. COMPRESS grunts]
This cannot be
where our performance ends!
[MR. COMPRESS]
The other League members
never asked about my past.
We were a group
of twisted players,
only concerned about ourselves.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Even so.
With them...
[CRC MEMBER 126A] Why have you
entered our compound?
[CRC MEMBER 126B]
Do you know who we are?
Do you seek to join us?
[SPINNER]
The Creature Rejection Clan.
AKA the CRC.
You bastards spew
outdated ideas.
Discriminating against
heteromorphs like me.
You're bigots.
[CRC MEMBER 126C]
They brought a pet.
[CRC MEMBER 126AA]
Repulsive.
[CRC MEMBER 126A]
Hold on.
This is the League of Villains!
[MR. COMPRESS] We're currently
a tad short on funds.
So we're in the market
for things to sell.
Are these rare?
[CRC MEMBER 126D]
Don't touch!
[MR. COMPRESS]
I know, I know.
Burglary isn't the most
fashionable crime.
I wish we didn't have
to resort to it.
[CRC MEMBER 126BB]
This is sacred ground!
[CRC MEMBER 126E]
Filthy criminals!
[CRC MEMBER 126A]
You'll pay for your impudence!
[SHIGARAKI] We'll leave
when we have what we want.
You'd be smart to
stay out of our way.
[CRC MEMBER 126B]
Kill them!
[TWICE] Thought these culty
types were supposed to be rich!
[TOGA]
Dumb skull faces got nothin'!
[TWICE]
This crap looks valuable!
Nothing special.
Ah! They broke it.
[MR. COMPRESS]
My prosthetic arm is creaky.
Let's have Giran
get us new gear.
[TWICE]
Great idea!
We have no money
to pay him with.
[SPINNER]
Boss.
This is no way to live.
How long can we keep this up?
As long as it takes.
Until we're finished.
[MR. COMPRESS] If we'd teamed
up with the Hassaikai,
we'd probably be eating
the finest sushi right now.
[SHIGARAKI]
Don't be an idiot.
[MR. COMPRESS laughs]
What a world.
We spread fear
across the country,
and now we're reduced
to a band of paupers.
I feel pity for every lunatic
who looked up to us.
[TWICE]
Nothing here of any interest.
Huh? Uh, speak for yourself.
I'm keepin' this.
[TWICE]
Oh, it's lovely!
For an old lady. Toss it.
Typical.
The whole gang's
just sittin' around.
Am I the only one
who's actually working
to find us some more members?
[TWICE]
All you're doin' is goin' around
burning people to death!
Have you ever brought
back a single person?
[DABI]
Not my fault nobody's worthy.
The streets are full of walking
trash with no ambition.
Maybe you're just a bad
judge of character.
[DABI]
Please. Like you're one to talk.
So. What exactly's our
top priority these days?
I joined the League because
I was inspired by Stain.
What?
I'm from a backwater town
in the countryside.
Everyone there believed
old-fashioned ideas.
And shunned me
because of how I look.
I can't describe
how hollow I felt.
Then, while watching
the news one night,
I witnessed Stain's
final moments.
[SPINNER] He was trying to
change our antiquated society.
By himself.
That was the first time I
realized how suffocating
the culture around me was.
I couldn't sit back
and do nothing.
And now I'm here!
Wow. Cool.
So you're basically
an empty cosplayer.
[SPINNER] That's right!
I'm still completely empty.
Which is why...
...I don't understand
why we're wasting time!
I thought we were supposed
to break the world here.
Answer me, Shigaraki!
What the hell is our goal?
What're we doing?
[MR. COMPRESS]
Until six months ago,
we were so strapped for cash,
we had to worry about
where our next meal
would come from.
We also lacked
a unified vision.
And yet... How do I explain it?
Simply put...
[MR. COMPRESS]
...I loved being in
the League of Villains, Spinner.
What're you talking about?
[MR. COMPRESS]
Our boss is the key.
I'll buy you time
to wake him up.
Use it well.
Every good show
requires teamwork.
This is my duty to my bloodline.
The reason I'm here!
[MR. COMPRESS groans]
[BEST JEANIST gasps]
[MR. COMPRESS] Gouging my own
flesh loosened the bindings.
My arm is free. And so are you!
[TENYA]
The League!
[MIRIO] They've escaped
their restraints!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Don't think you're the only ones
risking your lives for a cause!
Now. Keep your eyes peeled.
This will be the performance
of a lifetime!
[BEST JEANIST] I can't
believe he'd use his Quirk
to carve up his own body.
What fortitude!
Still. That wound looks fatal!
You will not escape!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Clever!
He's imprisoning me
with my clothes.
But I'm perfectly positioned for
a little sleight of hand magic.
Goodbye, costume!
[BEST JEANIST]
He got away.
[CHIKAZOKU]
H-Hey. Over here!
I can't move!
Don't leave me!
[MR. COMPRESS]
I'm a master
when it comes to trickery
and deft escapes.
Those talents are all I need
to save us from abysmal defeat.
[MR. COMPRESS'S DAD]
Atsuhiro.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Oji Harima: the peerless thief.
A criminal from days long past.
When the current system
was starting to take shape,
he stole from false heroes
who cared only about
lining their pockets.
[MR. COMPRESS] As he spread
his loot among the needy,
he preached social reform.
[MR. COMPRESS'S DAD]
My son.
The spirit of justice flows
through our family line.
It's our duty to
expose unfairness.
[TODOROKI]
Flashfire...
...Fist!
Jet Kindling!
No. Jetburn!
[TODOROKI groans]
I'm sorry, Shoto.
We'll dance again later.
Enji Todoroki hasn't
suffered enough to break,
and there's no point in
continuing if he's knocked out.
Too bad, little masterpiece!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Dabi! Quick!
It was a good run, Harima.
Though I didn't cause
the reform I wanted.
I know who will.
Tomura Shigaraki of the PLF
and the League of Villains will
change the world in my stead!
[MR. COMPRESS] I'm Oji Harima's
great-great grandson.
The blood of the bandit king
pumps through my veins.
You barely noticed me, right?
That was part
of my grand deception!
My role was saved
for when it really mattered.
One must always keep
an ace up their sleeve.
I won't let you get away
with anything else!
At last, center stage!
[MR. COMPRESS] It's time for
Mr. Compress's spectacular,
once in a lifetime escape act!
[HERO 126A groans]
[yells]
[BURNIN yells]
[MASTER DRILLER]
I've got this one!
No! Master Driller!
[MASTER DRILLER yells]
Monster. You'll pay!
[FIRST WIELDER]
Wake up. You can't sleep now.
Arise, Ninth Wielder.
[IZUKU]
Was I KOed?
Dabi's blast knocked me back.
Then Endeavor...
Where's Todoroki?
[IZUKU]
Thank goodness.
I'm glad he--
There it is again!
I've felt this a few times
since the fight started.
A sharp, stabbing pain
in my head.
Wait a sec, this sounds like
something from
All Might's notes.
It's the Fourth User's Quirk.
Danger Sense.
[IZUKU] I haven't started
training for this power yet.
It's killing my head.
This isn't good.
I have no control,
like when Blackwhip manifested.
[IZUKU]
Can't black out!
[MR. COMPRESS]
At last, center stage!
Time for Mr. Compress's
spectacular,
once in a lifetime escape act!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Admission is free!
Relax and enjoy the perfor--
[MR. COMPRESS]
Don't banish me to the wings
before the final curtain falls!
[MR. COMPRESS]
On our way here,
I saw a horde of Nomu.
They only move on
Shigaraki's orders,
so he must've called them
sometime after he woke up.
Destroy it all.
Machia.
[MR. COMPRESS] The boss spoke,
but from the look
and sound of it, he wasn't
completely awake.
He must regain consciousness.
Then the League can
escape on the backs
of a bio-engineered chorus!
I bought them time.
After all. I'm not
the lead in this play.
Just a diversion.
The rest is up
to luck and my crew.
I even managed to tuck
Dabi and Longhair away.
Don't let me down, Spinner.
You're the most devoted of us.
I'm just a
supporting character.
You two are the real
stars of the show.
[SPINNER] Now's our chance!
Dammit, wake up, Shigaraki!
[SHIGARAKI] When I put
them on, it's so strange.
Though it still
makes me feel sick
to my stomach, wearing them
washes calmness over me.
Don't you think that's bizarre?
[SPINNER] I'm not sure
this'll work, but...
I saw something stashed
in your melted suit.
Charred and crushed, but whole.
You need to remember
who you are.
[SHIGARAKI]
There's a heaviness in my heart,
like a lump of lead.
Never moving, fueling
the rage that propels me
but never brings relief!
[MIRIO gasps]
[MIRIO yells]
[BEST JEANIST]
What's this?
[TODOROKI grunts]
[IZUKU]
My head again. Don't tell me.
Please, no!
[ALL FOR ONE] I must say, Tomura
has some admirable friends.
[SPINNER]
His voice.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Power is drawn from the heart.
The more he embraces
the pain and hatred born from
his past trauma, the stronger my
will becomes within this body.
[SHIGARAKI]
I don't know why.
But there are so many bad
feelings inside of me.
No matter what I try,
they won't go away.
Then don't hold back.
Long live the king.
Tomura.
They stopped?
[HERO 126D]
This is our chance.
We'll take them out!
[HERO 126D]
A retreat?
[BURNIN]
Same as before.
They're heading for Shigaraki.
[ALL FOR ONE] This is why the
Radio Waves Quirk is so crucial.
It can be used to send
long-distance signals
to the Nomu.
Though it's difficult for Tomura
since he's a mere hatchling.
[TENYA]
What?
[BEST JEANIST]
You're mine!
Fight until the end!
Do not give up!
[SPINNER] Boss. How do you
want to attack them?
[ALL FOR ONE]
We're withdrawing.
Wait, you wanna run?
We can't do that!
Compress is hurt bad!
And Machia's not going anywhere.
Toga's supposed to be
heading this way, too!
We're experts at doing
whatever we want.
But... make sure that
you come back to us.
You're going to
abandon your comrades?
[ALL FOR ONE]
Hold your tongue, Iguchi.
Did you say "Iguchi?"
Hold on. Who are you?
[ALL FOR ONE]
Tomura already lost this fight.
To One For All and Endeavor.
He awoke before
his body modifications
could be completed.
Unfortunately, this meant
his regeneration
abilities were lacking
and no match for
the assembled heroes.
That's why I came
to lend my aid.
The poor boy's body
is in dire need of rest.
[SPINNER] I don't know
what you're going on about.
But you can't run away and
leave your teammates behind!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Yes. I can.
[SPINNER gasps]
[ALL FOR ONE]
It's only fair that Tomura pays
for his failures.
Remember, this is
all for my sake.
[BEST JEANIST] The League
is gathering in the same spot
the Nomu are headed.
Dabi's probably there, too.
Do not let them escape!
Output level 100.
Spiraling flood. Nejire Flood!
[TENYA]
Recipro Turbo!
I'll finish this in a flash,
then get Midoriya and
Bakugo to the hospital!
After all, I became
a hero to save people!
[MIRIO]
You won't escape!
[ALL FOR ONE]
The Permeation Quirk, huh?
[ALL FOR ONE] I have no patience
for attacks I can't predict.
Shigaraki!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Still, they swarm.
[TODOROKI, TENYA groan]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Now. Time to go.
[IZUKU]
Move. Get up.
You can do this!
[SHIGARAKI]
Learn your place, Master.
[IZUKU]
C'mon, Deku!
You can't just lie here!
I'm in charge. This is my will.
The dream I chase is mine.
[IZUKU]
Stand and fight these villains!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Hm? You haven't given up yet?
I'd say this child's tenacity
is comparable to All Might's.
[ALL FOR ONE]
The useless Izuku Midoriya.
Let's meet again when
this body's complete.
You better keep your
mouth shut, All For One!
[ALL FOR ONE]
I'll see you soon.
[IZUKU]
Shigaraki...
You killed so many.
Everybody is in pain.
There's no way
I can forgive you.
Never.
But...
Back there, when you
were being overtaken
by All For One.
I saw it. So clearly.
You looked like
you wanted to be saved!
♪
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
We battled fiercely,
but in the end,
Shigaraki managed to escape.
Many pros gave their lives,
and countless homes
and city blocks were destroyed
as a result of the fighting.
The country has lost
their faith in heroes.
Is there still a future
where everyone can smile?
Next time, "Hellish Hell."
This disaster will leave us all
with deep, painful scars.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!