[ALL MIGHT] If not for the car,
I would have been a goner!
This isn't a car jacking.
They're out for blood.
If that's the case,
their goal must be
trying to separate
me from him.
Assassins!
They're after Young Midoriya.
[VILLAIN 134A]
Wait. Is that All Might?
[VILLAIN 134B]
Don't back down.
This doesn't change our job.
Look at him.
The number-one hero we knew
and feared died a long time ago.
Huh, yeah. Guess you're right.
Step aside.
I swear to protect your son.
Even if it costs me my life.
[ALL MIGHT] That boy has been
carrying a burden far heavier
than mine, and I gave it to him.
All Might. No matter what
happens to you from now on,
I'll be there
to help fight fate!
Yet despite that,
he continues to idolize me.
If the unthinkable ever
happens to that young man,
it'll be over my dead body.
[IZUKU] I'll zigzag
to avoid the line of fire
and keep her from
guessing my path.
Then get close!
My speeds with One For All
have gotten faster,
and as long as she's
not quicker than me,
I can stay one step ahead
and get the jump on her
before she can react!
I'll make her talk.
She'll tell me where All For One
and Shigaraki are hiding!
[IZUKU]
A bullet! No way!
[IZUKU groans]
How'd that happen?
Without a search-type Quirk,
she shouldn't be able
to sneak up behind me.
Does she have help?
No, I don't sense any
other hostility nearby.
[IZUKU]
Damn it! I see now.
I should've figured
that was a possibility.
She's All For One's hired gun.
Of course he gave her
extra Quirks!
[ALL FOR ONE] Air Walk.
This power will dramatically
expand the range and
accuracy of your attacks.
[IZUKU] Right. I know she's
trying to capture me alive.
But since I dodged
her first shots,
she's shortened the
distance between us.
The bullet that hit me
from the back
was fired from my flank
with a crazy curve.
As she gets closer, it's easier
to lock onto my location,
instead of calculating my path.
And as the distance shrinks,
it's harder for the Fourth to
warn about consecutive shots.
In that case--Sixth, full blast!
[LADY NAGANT] Another Quirk?
He has multiples, too.
What secrets are you hiding?
[EN]
Hey, Ninth! Keep it together.
Did you already forget
what I told you before?
It's way too risky to
put out that much smoke!
Listen. Your opponent
is basically a high-speed,
long-range rifle.
You've trapped yourself.
She'll tag you the
second you try to run.
[IZUKU] I'm not going to run.
I just needed to buy some time.
[EN]
Whoa, wait. You're joking!
Are you doing what
I think you are?
[THIRD WIELDER]
Terrible idea.
I can see what you're
attempting to do right now.
But this plan is beyond
your current abilities.
You said so yourself.
First off, you need to be able
to do two things at once
without concentration.
When you master that,
add something else.
You have no experience
using my Quirk.
Parallel processing
takes practice.
[IZUKU]
It's a little late for that.
If I can get some good
intel out of Lady Nagant,
I can make sure All For One
and Shigaraki are defeated.
I'll learn how to use
your power on the fly.
Third. Fa Jin!
[LADY NAGANT]
A decoy! What's he playing at?
Cheeky brat!
Hiding in a puff of smoke
is a waste of time.
I'm still going to capture you.
You might be right,
if that was my plan!
[LADY NAGANT]
He's somehow faster than before!
This kid powered up
while he was down there!
[IZUKU] The rain doesn't
affect my smokescreen.
So it was easy to send out
decoys and track Nagant's
movements based on the
timing of her shots.
I didn't know her
exact position,
so I couldn't attack head-on.
But she never expected me
to burst out of a building.
With the help of Fa Jin,
I caught her off guard.
A sniper's skills are
useless at close range!
Give up the fight and start
talking about who hired you!
You think you've won?
Not a chance!
[groans]
[LADY NAGANT] The safety
commission trained me well.
Why are you helping
a monster like All For One?
He's an evil tyrant hell-bent
on controlling people.
I don't get it.
You used to be a hero!
The just world you've
been sold is a lie.
You've been brainwashed.
You'll never
understand the truth.
[IZUKU] Crap! I had her
there for a second!
The Third was right.
Using multiple Quirks at once is
a whole other difficulty level.
[IZUKU]
From behind?
[LADY NAGANT] I was exhausted.
I'd killed so many.
All to keep our
citizens in the dark.
[LADY NAGANT]
Say some group was plotting
a terrorist attack against pros.
Or a famous hero team worked
with a villainous
organization on the sly.
When someone is capable of
shaking the foundation
of this society,
they can't be tried.
They have to disappear quietly.
That's where the safety
commission comes in.
[gasps]
[LADY NAGANT] Back in the day,
there were vigilante groups
who were seen as heroes.
They earned the trust
of the public,
and the country approved
of their actions.
That's when our
leaders discovered
that this superhuman
society works best
if people have faith in heroes.
I was a cog in the state-run
machine that upheld that trust.
[FISHMAN VILLAIN 134A] Wait!
We haven't done anything yet.
--This was just talk!
--[gunshot]
[LADY NAGANT]
To maintain the status quo,
the government needed a
public face and a secret one.
So I obeyed.
And obeyed.
[BOY 134A]
Lady Nagant!
Oh, wow! Can I shake your hand?
--[BOY 134B] Me, too!
--[GIRL 134A] You're the best!
Sure. But only if
you kids have been good.
[LADY NAGANT] The fragility of
our world made me spiral.
[LADY NAGANT]
It's all a sham.
[COMMISSIONER 134A] We have two
heroes pushing civilians
to commit crimes.
Afterwards, they turn them
in to the police and collect
rewards for capturing them.
It wouldn't do for us
to bring any
official charges against them.
But they must be dealt with.
[LADY NAGANT]
You think that by killing them,
society will be improved?
If we don't show people
the bad side of things,
that's brainwashing by omission.
Nagant. Wouldn't you agree
that the most important thing
for us to do is
maintain the hope
that public-facing heroes
have brought the world?
[LADY NAGANT]
If this is the only way,
then what does the
future hold for us?
[COMMISSIONER 134A]
Your duty is to follow orders.
This is not a job you can quit.
[LADY NAGANT] Chairman.
You were a strong leader.
You murdered the previous
head of the Safety Commission?
But wait. I read about you!
The media reported that
you killed fellow heroes.
[LADY NAGANT] That's what
the commission told them
to hide their shame.
They wouldn't say I rebelled.
That could expose the
reason I turned on them.
Here's the sad truth.
[LADY NAGANT]
The hero world everyone admires
as a force of good is
nothing but an illusion.
And if things go back
to the way they were?
History will repeat itself.
The citizens will see
the infallible public face,
while someone else gets
crushed by the dirty work.
Bright-eyed hopefuls will be
chewed up and spit out.
All For One's future makes
more sense than that.
[IZUKU]
There!
Fifth! Pinpoint Focus!
[LADY NAGANT]
The hell?
He's mapping my movements from
the trajectory of the bullets!
I had no idea.
[LADY NAGANT]
He's fast!
But now, little by little,
I think I'm starting
to understand.
Nothing is truly
black and white.
Our society exists
in a gray area,
swirling with anxiety and anger.
[SHIGARAKI]
You cover up the pain you cause.
This world has grown so rotten.
It's infested with maggots.
That's exactly why
I have to keep
reaching my hand out to help!
You're the product
of their indoctrination!
[LADY NAGANT] Even in midair,
he's managing to avoid
major damage to his joints.
He's focused on predicting
and evading my attacks.
Fine, then.
I'll give him more
to think about!
Is that Chisaki?
[LADY NAGANT]
Now I have you!
[CHISAKI]
I've met your target before.
[LADY NAGANT]
Huh?
[CHISAKI] Kid stopped me
from enacting my plan.
He has a bad case
of hero syndrome.
It's like this was fated.
I knew you might come in handy.
I'll bring you along so you can
confirm it's the same boy.
I've got one condition.
[LADY NAGANT]
I don't care about your grudge.
It's not that. I'm not
looking for revenge.
I've lost everything.
There's only one thing
that's left for me to do.
I just want to talk
to the old man.
Pops. I'm sorry.
I really am.
I've already fulfilled
my part of the agreement.
Hurry up and take me
to the boss, damn it!
Is that Chisaki?
[LADY NAGANT] I'm increasing
the velocity of my bullets,
even if I risk
jamming as a result.
I'll make you face the worst
outcome a hero can imagine.
[LADY NAGANT] It doesn't
matter who the person is.
When you can't save somebody,
your conscience is destroyed.
[LADY NAGANT] Give you
too much to think about,
and it'll slow you down.
That's when you're mine!
[IZUKU]
Quirk. Fa Jin!
By repeating a motion
over and over again,
I can temporarily store kinetic
energy to be released later.
While I was being shot at,
I continuously bent
and stretched my legs
to keep from being hit.
Plus!
One For All at 45 percent!
Centrifugal force!
There's something everyone
my age has seen.
All Might, the Symbol of Peace,
moving faster than
a speeding bullet!
[IZUKU]
Faux 100 percent!
[LADY NAGANT] Impossible.
He caught up to the bullet?
No, he's even faster!
While I'm over here aiming
the muzzle for another shot,
he's already
shifting directions!
[grunts]
[LADY NAGANT]
This kid.
I'll come for
you later, Chisaki.
[THIRD WIELDER] Earlier, he used
One For All at 45 percent,
cycling through Danger Sense,
Smokescreen, Blackwhip,
Fa Jin, and Float
in rapid succession.
But he couldn't process those
powers fast enough and froze up.
After figuring that out,
he narrowed his scope
to One For All, Blackwhip,
and Fa Jin this time.
[LADY NAGANT]
We're not finished.
[THIRD WIELDER] And, even now,
he still has built up strength
from Fa Jin stored in one leg.
[IZUKU]
Faux 100 percent.
Manchester Smash!
Your barrel's broken!
It's over, Lady Nagant!
[LADY NAGANT]
I don't hesitate.
Once I recognize someone
as the enemy,
whatever happens next plays out
like it was inevitable.
[LADY NAGANT]
When did that start?
Let's use that
right arm of yours
and make this country
a better place.
[LADY NAGANT] When did empty
sentiments start making me sick?
You shot towards Chisaki,
but you didn't aim at him.
And if you really believed
in All For One's future,
your first bullet would've hit
my spine and paralyzed me.
[IZUKU] You've seen the
darkness in this world.
So you know what needs
to be brought into the light.
It's not too late for you
to fight on our side.
I know the heart of a hero
still beats inside you.
Nothing is truly
black and white.
Our society exists
in a gray area
swirling with anxiety and anger.
That's exactly why
I have to keep reaching
my hand out to help!
[LADY NAGANT]
Incredible.
Izuku Midoriya.
You are a hero.
[ALL FOR ONE] The heart
is a fickle, unruly beast.
Knowing this fact,
I made a few preparations
in the event of an unfortunate
breach of contract.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Such a pity.
You were used by others
until the very end.
Though perhaps the Quirk you
were blessed with is to blame.
What a pathetic life
you've led, dear Lady Nagant.
Nagant, no!
I won't let you die,
you hear me?
Hawks, you're here?
[ENDEAVOR] Deku! All Might
sent word of an assassin!
I'm sorry we're late.
I'm not good in this weather.
What's going on?
Are there other enemies?
[IZUKU] Chisaki's on the roof
of that building over there!
I've got him.
[HAWKS] Endeavor!
My wings can't handle this!
It's too soon for me to fly!
[IZUKU] I'm all out of strength.
I can't pull him up.
Hold on, Hawks!
I can't be sure, but I don't
think she meant to do that.
She got at least one extra
Quirk from All For One.
He probably added
some kind of trap to it.
[HAWKS]
This boy.
My name is Hawks.
I sort of replaced you.
We're in this mess because of
All For One's manipulation.
If you fought against that kid,
then you should
understand that now, too.
It's not too late for you, okay?
You don't have to
throw everything away!
Please tell me you realize that!
Help us create a future
you can be proud of!
Take control of your own life!
You're Lady Nagant,
and you are a hero!
[LADY NAGANT]
My replacement, huh?
They probably made you
do terrible things, too.
For the "greater good."
So how is it you still have
so much hope in your eyes?
[LADY NAGANT] In all this chaos,
with no control over the future,
how can you people
keep fighting?
Here's what I know.
In two months, at a mansion,
in Haibori Woods--
[LADY NAGANT] I was supposed
to bring the boy there.
[LADY NAGANT]
And it's not just me.
He sent the other hunters
after the target, too.
The same job.
Hey. Replacement.
I fell apart. I just
couldn't take it anymore.
But you? How do you
still keep going?
[HAWKS] Because there was
someone who helped me out.
Also, I'm an optimistic guy.
Oh. Is that so?
[ENDEAVOR]
Deku! Was he the only one?
No. This isn't what
we agreed on.
Why'd you get caught?
You said you were gonna
take me to him!
I need to visit Pops.
He's all I've got left.
I have to see him.
To tell him I'm sorry!
[ERI]
Please. Please don't go.
[IZUKU]
Chisaki.
[CHISAKI]
Not a word, you sick freak!
I was talking to the woman.
You remember Eri, right?
What you did to her?
Eri? Oh, yeah. Yeah, the girl.
If I had her, she could
Rewind the old man.
[IZUKU] You want forgiveness
from somebody?
Apologize to Eri.
And in return, I'll fulfill
Nagant's promise.
You have my word on that front.
How does that sound to you?
Young man! Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm all right.
We've captured Lady Nagant
and Kai Chisaki!
Contact the police.
Nagant needs medical attention.
Midoriya's been roughed up
pretty bad as well.
You, too, by the looks of it.
[IZUKU]
All For One.
Here's the preview.
In order for everyone
to live in peace again,
in order to smile again with
the people I care about,
I need to push
myself even harder.
I have to fully unleash
the power of One For All.
That's what has to happen.
No matter what.
Next time, "Friend."
I'm fine. Really, I am.