[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
where about 80 percent
of people are born
with an uncanny ability
known as a Quirk.
Not everyone uses their
powers for good, though.
Which is why the world
needed a new profession:
the hero.
[IZUKU]
My name is Izuku Midoriya
and I inherited a secret
Quirk called "One For All"
from All Might.
That's how I was enrolled
in the hero course at UA.
After a series of incidents
that put us up against
the worst of the worst,
my incredible classmates and I
got our provisional
hero licenses.
Meanwhile, the League
of Villains,
led by Tomura Shigaraki,
joined forces
with the Metahuman
Liberation Army.
In that instant, their power
increased astronomically.
Shigaraki renamed this group
the Paranormal Liberation Front.
His closest allies are now
lieutenants of different units
within the organization.
The Wing Hero, Hawks,
was sent undercover
by the Public Safety Commission.
Through careful recon,
he uncovered
some of the group's secrets.
Using that information,
the police called on heroes
from around the country
and began a huge operation
to round up this
new legion of villains
and get them off
the streets for good.
[TSUKAUCHI] First, the pros
will be split into two groups.
Team Endeavor will be
in charge of securing
Kyudai Garaki at Jaku Hospital.
Team Edge Shot will storm
the Gunga Mountain Villa
we believe to be the Paranormal
Liberation Front's hideout.
These two events will
happen simultaneously.
In addition, hero course
students will be deployed
as logistical support
for both teams.
They'll assist with civilian
evacuation and rescue
if the encounters
start to escalate.
We expect substantial resistance
from the villains, their
supporters, and the Nomu,
but we cannot wait any longer.
If we don't act now,
they will prevail.
The doctor,
his pets, Shigaraki--
every villain must fall.
Heroes, the idea is to
take out the entire
Paranormal Liberation
Front in one sweep.
[NOMUS growling]
Hah, this'll be fun!
[NOMU 114E shrieks]
[gasps]
[screams]
[MIRKO]
What's up, Doc?
I'm guessing you're
the real one!
[DOCTOR]
Who's a good boy? Is it you?
Yes! My little Johnny.
[gasping, screaming]
[yells]
[DOCTOR]
No!
[yelping]
[screams]
[MANDALAY]
Prioritize critical patients.
Instruct anybody who can safely
walk on their own to head
to the nearest official.
[HERO 115A]
Roger!
[CIVILIANS scream]
Go! Work faster!
[MIRKO]
Hey, team.
I've got some old geezer
crying over a Nomu down here.
[ENDEAVOR]
Is it the real Garaki?
Or is it a copy?
[MIRKO]
Not sure.
But I'll know once I kick 'im.
Your goal is to
capture the doctor.
[MIRKO]
After I rough him up.
Well, I'd like to say we're
on our way to help you,
but we've got a few
issues of our own.
They might take a minute.
[NOMU 114A growling]
Flashfire Fist. Jetburn!
Mirko's on top--
[LOCKLOCK]
Deadbolt!
We're putting the weak ones down
but they won't stop coming.
The last person
has been evacuated.
No need to hold back.
C'mon, we gotta help Mirko!
Right, we will not
fail our mission!
[gasps]
Jetburn!
[NOMUS growl]
[ENDEAVOR]
Such a handy Quirk.
You know, it's not too late
to become one of my sidekicks.
Yeah, that's a "no."
Who else is gonna step in and
train all my useless children.
[NOMUS growling]
They must be part
of the evacuation.
Probably carrying the
most serious patients
to another hospital
somewhere closeby.
[BURNIN] Attention
logistical support units.
Team Endeavor is currently
fighting inside the building.
So they ran into villains.
The city sent a text
message to locals
ordering them to evacuate now.
Start clearing your
assigned areas immediately.
[gasps] Right!
Okay. You guys hear that?
Yeah. Let's go start our sweep.
I can't believe
I'm stuck back here
helping a bunch of
randos run away.
Pit me against a villain!
[TENYA]
Our role is integral, Bakugo.
Stay the course.
[KATSUKI]
Hey, idiots!
The city told you
to run the hell away!
Did you not check your phone,
or are you just stupid?
I can help Iida with the
apartments around the corner.
That leaves the houses
to the rest of you.
We got this, guys!
[TENYA]
Let's go, Midoriya!
[CRUST]
These rooms look as though Nomu
were held inside of them.
Another passage! This is
how they got below us.
Those monsters upstairs
didn't come from the morgue.
[NOMUS growling]
[CRUST]
What's this?
Those are common minions.
Tortured souls!
[PRESENT MIC]
The number six hero, Crust!
His Quirk: Shield!
He can form them
all over his body!
[CRUST] You were victims,
but I must defeat you
to catch the man
who defiled you!
First let's find out
if you're the real deal!
[yelps] Yes, yes, I am.
No need for violence!
Only one way to make sure.
[screams]
[DOCTOR] If Dabi had managed
to retrieve Hood's corpse
from Kyushu, we'd be in
a far better position.
My other little darlings
are still baking
and barely in
the testing stages.
With All For One gone,
it's difficult
to produce more High Ends.
It took Hood ten hours
just to stabilize
after he was activated.
This batch can fight,
but ideally, they'd have half a
day after waking to acclimate!
--[MOCHA yelps]
--[MIRKO grunts]
Mocha!
--[MIRKO growls]
--[MOCHA squeals]
[MIRKO] So this goblin
has the Double Quirk.
[DOCTOR]
It's a miracle!
I can't believe you used your
power without a direct order!
You were protecting me,
weren't you?
You're so sweet, my pet.
I won't let Mocha's courage
and sacrifice be in vain.
Precious High Ends,
it's time. Awaken!
[DOCTOR] Slaughter this hero
and those who follow!
[HIGH END 115A]
He...
That's it.
[HIGH END 115A]
Hero...
It's time.
[HIGH END 115D]
Been so long.
Yes. Yes.
[HIGH END 115D]
Can go wild. Destroy.
[HIGH END 115A]
Kill. All of them.
Make them suffer.
[CRUST]
Mirko!
You're Crust from
the hero charts.
But I forget what
number you are.
[CRUST]
This one talks?
You're right about that, beast.
[HIGH END 115B grunts]
[CRUST grunts]
It's so powerful.
[DOCTOR] I'm sorry you don't
have more time to adjust,
but I'm counting
on you, High Ends!
[MIRKO] Like I'd let you
escape. This is great.
Now that I'm warmed up,
the fun can really begin.
[HIGH END 115B growls]
Too cramped.
Need more space
to tear you apart.
[HERO 115B gasps]
The Nomu is communicating!
Help me!
There are more of
the big ones ahead!
Mirko's in trouble!
Your weak attacks
will not save you
from destruction.
I pity you, abomination,
but we must pass.
[DOCTOR] The Nomu are created
when I bioengineer human corpses
and gift the reanimated
beings with Quirks.
They have no will of their
own and can only act
as they're programmed.
Based on their strength
and the number of
Quirks they command,
I split them into lower,
middle, and upper tiers.
In addition to Quirks,
upper tiers have more than
ten times the muscle
of an average person.
But another group outperforms
these champions.
The High Ends.
In addition to having
far higher specs
than the others
across the board,
they're capable of advanced
independent thinking.
Their personalities reflect
the human they were
before they shuffled off
the mortal coil.
As such, all High Ends
were once villains
who had a strong
desire for carnage.
Preparing raw materials
and surgically transferring
abilities is a chore.
And the Quirks take over
three months to adhere.
Without All For One's power,
it's hard to mass produce
these exquisite creatures.
Currently there are five in the
testing phase, but just barely.
That includes the
one called "Woman."
I'm sorry I left
you behind, children,
but you must protect us!
We lost Warp when Johnny died
and Double went with Mocha.
Which means Shigaraki
and I have lost
our most trusted
means of escape.
Do I wake him?
While my creations do their
best against the heroes?
[DOCTOR] My masterpiece.
Tomura Shigaraki.
[MIRKO]
You're back there, aren't you?
Oh, Villain?
I wonder what's keeping you
from running further.
I can hear you clacking away
in the back a' the tunnel.
[HIGH END 115A]
How can she still move?
[HIGH END 115E]
Must stop the hero.
I will kill her.
I cancelled out the impact
of that landing with my legs!
[grunts]
[PRESENT MIC]
The number-five hero, Mirko!
Her Quirk: Rabbit!
She can do stuff a rabbit
can but so much better!
Suckers! The old man's mine!
[HIGH END 115C growls]
Must kill her.
That's the order that
our master gave to us.
She must die.
[HIGH END 115D]
Hero!
[MIRKO]
Not a chance.
[HIGH END 115C growls]
[MIRKO]
Luna Ring!
Got 'em. But not enough.
Dumb bastards! Outta the way!
[HIGH END 115C growls]
[HIGH END 115E]
Why does she not give up?
[MIRKO yells]
[MIRKO]
Luna Fall!
Creeps like you who only ever
attack from a distance,
are always weakest when it
comes to close combat.
[HIGH END 115E]
You will die.
Sure. When it's
time to die, I will.
That makes me human.
[MIRKO]
Luna Tijeras!
Can't ignore this busted arm
if I wanna keep doing my job.
[HIGH END 115A]
Hero filth.
[HIGH END 115C]
How dare you!
[MIRKO] Looks like crushing
your heads will stop ya.
Makes you easier to deal with
than some random villain
with unknown weaknesses.
I live every day as if I'm
not gonna see another one.
That way I'll have
no regrets when I die. Heh.
But you zombies are out of luck.
Mirko's not going down.
[OPERATOR 114A]
Update!
The Garaki we captured
turned out to be a fake.
[OPERATOR 114AA] Mirko appears
to be chasing the actual doctor.
[OPERATOR 114B] Endeavor
remains on the ground floor
fighting more Nomu.
[OPERATOR 114A] Yes, and the
team has confirmed that multiple
High Ends have joined the fray.
[OPERATOR 114AA]
Team Edge Shot is advancing now.
They're about to proceed with
their raid on the Gunga Villa.
[SERO] It's almost time.
Stand up, Grape Juice.
Why bother?
The rear guard's job
is to catch any bad guys
who slip past the
heroes out front.
It would basically be like
an insult to the pros
if we looked like we expected
them to miss some villains.
Off your butt!
It's beginning now.
Well jeez, thanks for
the warning!
Okay, they're on the move.
Look alive.
An unprecedented number of
heroes have gathered for this.
Nevertheless, you should
all stay on high alert.
Think of it this way.
We had to recruit this many pros
because the enemy
is that dangerous.
Tokoyami's probably fine.
So maybe Kaminari is, too.
[YAOYOROZU]
I'm sure he'll be okay.
You'll see.
[KAMINARI]
I think I might throw up.
This is so scary!
Dang. I miss
the rest a' Class A!
You consented to this job
before the mission began.
Well, yeah. Of course!
How was I supposed to say no
when everybody was
there watching me?
I didn't want them to see what
a coward I can be sometimes.
I'm sorry, but we do
need your power.
Just tell yourself that we
useless adults need your aid.
No! It's so much
worse if I think
the pros can't handle
this without me!
[TOKOYAMI]
Kaminari.
You scared, too?
During the school festival,
I discovered the real you while
we played guitar together.
You are an incredible person.
How does being
a guitar god help?
Not the point.
Open up!
[CHIKAZOKU]
An enemy attack? Perfect.
This is all your
fault, Bubaigawara!
Where'd you go?
Damn it! This is
terrible timing.
The whole organization's
in trouble.
[TWICE] We gotta get ya
in front a' Shigaraki
so he knows you're legit!
[HAWKS]
Seriously. Kind weird
that I haven't gotten
to talk to him.
[TWICE] That's because
he's off getting stronger.
He'll be in the mountains
near Kyoto for four months.
Whoops, that's a secret.
Though I'm sure that
long-haired spy heard me.
Ya big creep!
[CHIKAZOKU]
After that idiocy,
I made sure to watch
Hawks even more closely.
But not a single thing
he did seemed suspicious.
He tricked me!
No, I'm not to blame.
That fool is!
The heroes are coming!
The concrete's moving
like it's alive!
[LIBERATION ARMY 115B]
What's happening?
Our meeting is cancelled!
Regiments assemble!
They're attacking head-on!
Violet and Black to the front.
Brown unit, join them.
Carmine, stay put for now.
[AMPLIVOLT VICE COMMANDER 115A]
They got us good,
didn't they, Mr. Skeptic?
Let's go light 'em up, huh?
[LIBERATION ARMY 115E]
They're here!
[LIBERATION ARMY 115F]
Out front!
[LIBERATION ARMY 115G]
L-Look!
[LIBERATION ARMY 115H]
Is that...?
[EDGE SHOT]
Not one villain gets away!
They'll give their lives
to bring down society.
If we miss a single person,
the world is in danger.
We attack to protect!
[MIDNIGHT] Charge! Try not
to get overwhelmed, kid.
Uh, sure thing, Ms. Midnight.
If protecting the world is hard
for you to gear up for,
here's a trick you can use.
Just imagine you're
really protecting
whatever is most
dear to your heart.
That would be...
I know you can
do this, Chargebolt.
[MIDNIGHT]
If protecting the world is hard
for you to gear up for,
here's a trick you can use.
Just imagine you're
really protecting
whatever is most
dear to your heart.
This happened because
we were waiting for Shigaraki.
But we don't have time
for that anymore.
Now, it begins.
Liberation and revolution!
[LIBERATION ARMY 115I] The vice
commander's doing his thing.
[LIBERATION ARMY 115J]
Don't get caught in the attack!
Your numbers are meaningless
when facing my Quirk.
My Amplivolt reigns supreme,
a power that electrifies any
who stand in the way of my will!
[EDGE SHOT]
A wide-range attack!
[TOKOYAMI]
Kaminari. I know the truth.
[KAMINARI]
O-Ow.
Shall we call it
a day, you think?
Nah, I got more practice in me.
Jiro's way into
this music stuff.
She's super passionate about it.
We gotta make this
a great show for her.
[TOKOYAMI]
You are kind.
You would do anything
for your friends.
Supreme Discharge. Thundernet!
The hell?
The attack is being absorbed?
Aw, yeah.
That's one scary leader
rendered powerless. Ha!
He did it.
Good boy.
All right, pros,
you think you can finish
this up really quick?
I don't want anyone in the
back worrying about us.
Incredible, Charge. Well done!
Thanks! Just glad I could help.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The surprise attack
to capture every last villain
at the Gunga Villa is underway.
Thanks to the efforts
of the heroes,
the Paranormal Liberation Front
is at a severe disadvantage.
Unfortunately, Twice has
the power to give the villains
more than just
a fighting chance,
so Hawks is forced
to move quickly.
Maybe too fast.
Next time: "One's Justice."
You can do it, pros!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!