If Deku returns,
everyone taking shelter
here will be in danger.
[NEZU] I'll figure out a way
to make them understand.
You see, when we were preparing
for the last school festival,
we reinforced the U Barrier.
We didn't end up needing
the extra security. So this is
our chance to test it out.
Don't forget. All Might grew up
in this school, too,
and we survived.
Go ahead, students.
Bring your classmate back.
[TENYA] Principal Nezu. You
mentioned that the UA Barrier
was upgraded.
Will you elaborate?
We're here because we
understand Midoriya's concerns
and why he left us.
If campus defenses are strong,
that might help us
convince him to come back.
We need evidence that his return
won't bring harm to
anyone at the school.
That's why, initially,
we were just planning
to fight with him
in the streets.
I didn't suggest he
come back out of pity.
Practically speaking,
Midoriya is an invaluable asset
in our fight against the League.
We want to keep him safe,
which means we should
protect him in a
state-of-the-art facility.
Luckily, UA was able
to buy the country's
latest security tech
on the cheap.
In fact, our defense
systems are comparable
to what you might
find at Tartarus.
This sounds impressive, sir.
But those systems
were no match against
Shigaraki's forces.
[NEZU] Correct. However, since
UA was infiltrated last year,
I've stayed focused on
the threat Shigaraki poses.
So when it was time to
reinforce the barrier,
I went ahead and added
my own personal improvements
to the plans.
Our school's better
protected than a prison?
[NEZU]
It caused quite a stir.
Let me be blunt.
If an army of villains
were trying to invade UA
at this very moment,
no harm would come to the
evacuees or the students.
Frankly, the attackers
wouldn't stand a chance.
You see, the UA Barrier
is more than a stationary
defensive wall.
This whole campus can move!
[NEZU] The grounds have
been divided into a grid,
every part of which
is independently mobile.
In the event of an emergency,
sections can be lowered
to become an
underground shelter.
These shelters are then able
to move along various paths.
All powered by
the magic of science.
That's some mecha anime tech!
Of course, if the system
were to break down,
our careful planning will
have been for nothing.
Which is why there are also
3,000 layers of reinforced
plates underground.
If we detect anything abnormal,
the interception
system activates.
This unlocks the supports
so the defensive plates
can move as needed.
As such, we can delay any
especially troublesome attacks.
In the meantime, the shelters
would travel along safe routes,
eventually stopping at
another secure stronghold.
Shiketsu, for example, recently
bolstered their defenses.
There'll be no more
imposters for them.
And of course, there are other
similar hero high schools
out there, too.
Shiketsu? But their
campus is so far away!
[KATSUKI] UA in East.
Shiketsu in the West.
[BOTH]
Oh, right, Shiketsu. Those guys.
If I'm not mistaken,
these plans have Shigaraki's
upgraded Quirk in mind. But at
the time of the school festival,
we didn't know that Decay was
going to become supercharged.
You're right,
I had no real evidence.
Just a gut feeling.
That's why I paid for
the extra measures myself!
And what did that set you back,
a few 100,000,000?
If you weren't aware,
the principal supports
Quirk morality education.
His passion is
recognized globally.
His contributions in this
crisis have been vital.
Ignorance. Intolerance.
Some people refuse
to take that extra step
to try and understand others.
Many even group together
and act out of fear.
This prevents progress.
Putting in the work is
the more difficult path.
Anyway, it would be both
logical and beneficial
for Midoriya to come back.
You kids get out there
and give it your all.
[EVACUEE 137E] No way!
Send him somewhere else.
[CITIZEN 136A]
You're out of your minds!
We won't let him in! Leave!
[CITIZEN 136AA]
Shigaraki will come!
[EVACUEE 137A] Wasn't UA
supposed to guarantee our safety
and peace of mind?
[EVACUEE 137AB]
Don't let him in!
[EVACUEE 137B]
Send him away!
If he's got multiple
Quirks, he's a Nomu!
Izuku!
No, it's too dangerous!
[EVACUEE 137C]
You're scaring people.
[EVACUEE 137D] If you wanna
fight, do it somewhere else!
[EVACUEE 137B] What else
are you lying about, huh?
[CITIZEN 136AA] Yeah, start
talking. We want answers!
The principal couldn't
convince them?
At first, there were people
who acted as though
they understood the
situation we're in.
But speculation leads to unease,
and it can be
difficult for reason
to overcome
fear and rumors.
Dial back the volume, will ya?
[BEST JEANIST] I'm not sure
they're going to listen
to teachers. They came
here because of me.
Perhaps I can sway them.
You got it, Jeany.
Best Jeanist! The only
reason we came here
is because we believed
what you said!
[BEST JEANIST] Yes. And I
stand by that sentiment.
As the principal explained,
this is the safest place
for you to be. Your
lives are the priority.
In order to prevent
further violence,
our plan was to use
Izuku Midoriya as bait
to find the villains.
Unfortunately, our search
was fruitless.
We have little to show for it.
While the boy is a target
of the villains,
he is also our most
valuable asset.
To allow him to wear
himself down any more
could prove fatal.
This may not be ideal,
but we're doing the best we can.
We understand some among you
feel anxious about this.
But we hope you'll let him
rest here, in this stronghold.
If we want him to
fight for our futures,
we need him to be
healthy and strong.
Wait. Are you kidding me?
You know how things
got this bad?
You losers failed and turned
Japan into a lawless country.
And now that you've
screwed everything up,
you want us to pay
the price for it.
That's what you're
asking, right?
What the hell is that about?
[EVACUEE 137F]
Yeah, he's right!
[EVACUEES]
Keep him out!
[EVACUEE 137G]
And you call yourselves heroes?
[EVACUEES]
You call yourselves heroes?
[gasping]
My baby.
[EVACUEE 137F]
Give us a break!
[EVACUEE 137G] We just want
to be able to live in peace.
It's no good.
[EVACUEE 137K]
Protect us! What good are you?
[OCHACO]
If we don't do something...
[OCHACO ...this crowd
will turn into a mob.
[gasps]
[inhales]
That's...
That's our girl!
Dek--Izuku Midoriya has
a very important power.
So what? That just makes him
even more dangerous.
He'll get us all killed
because he wants to take a nap!
You're wrong! He left UA
because he didn't want to
cause trouble for anybody!
We're the ones who
made him come back!
What is she doing?
[OCHACO] His ability
is special, a power created
to beat All For One! That's why
the villains are after him!
Why he's been fighting
this whole time.
And he's been doing it alone!
He left to protect
every one of us,
but I want you
to look at him now.
[OCHACO] He wants to change our
situation more than anybody,
and he's put himself
in harm's way to do it.
Do you see what
that's done to him?
Just because someone
has a special power,
that doesn't mean they're
a special person!
[IZUKU] Leave her to me.
You can go now. I've got this.
That hero. He's the one
who rescued me.
There's a fancy system in place
to protect these idiots.
And still, they're scared
out of their minds.
But don't worry, we'll clean up
any messes you can't handle.
[NEZU] Putting in the work
is the more difficult path.
But it's worth it.
Once someone is able
to take that extra step forward,
it will clear a path
for the person who will become
the best hero we've known.
One who surpasses
even All Might.
[OCHACO] I've always liked
to see people happy.
Growing up, my parents
looked so worried, though.
It made me feel worried, too.
The first time I saw
someone doing hero work,
I couldn't help but watch
the faces of those around me.
It was amazing to see
everyone overcome with joy.
[EVACUEE 137J]
Look at him.
[EVACUEE 137EA]
Poor kid.
He must have kept fighting.
That boy went out
of his way to save me,
then ran off to help others.
We looked at him.
Happy now? Let me guess.
You want us to get
beat up like that, too?
You wanna see us broken down
and covered in mud?
The heroes are the ones
who are getting dirty!
They're the people who'll
have to wash away the stain.
Ochaco.
You get it, right? She's up
there fighting. For all of us.
She wants to see everyone smile.
Especially you.
Uraraka.
[OCHACO] I wish I could reassure
everybody here, but I can't.
And I'm sorry about
that, really, I am.
The truth is, we're all scared.
We're just like you!
We care about our friends
and neighbors, too!
[OCHACO] Watching him trying
to save people so desperately
got me thinking.
When a hero is in pain...
When heroes are suffering...
...the ones who will
protect them are...
[OCHACO'S DAD]
Ochaco. You're missing it.
The hero is over there!
[CITIZEN 137A]
Hey! Eel-Boy!
You're the best!
--[CITIZEN 137B] Thank you!
--[CITIZEN 137AA] Thanks!
[CITIZENS chanting] Eel-Boy!
Eel-Boy! Eel-Boy! Eel-Boy!
[OCHACO]
The people who will protect them
are the ones they fight for.
[inhales]
So please. Lend him your
support! Help him fight for us!
[OCHACO]
Search your hearts.
Will you allow him
to rest at your side?
Will you give him time
to prepare for his battle
to protect you?
Izuku Midoriya is carrying
the burden of his power
and trying to keep us safe.
But he still has a lot
to learn. He's just a kid.
Yeah, but--
[OCHACO]
I'm begging you!
Let UA...
[OCHACO ...continue to be
his hero academy!
[sobbing]
[NEZU] A single step is all it
takes to start down a new path.
[gasps] Come back!
[MANDALAY] So? Which pair
of shoes did you pick out?
[KOTA]
Those! It's gotta be them!
The red ones!
[IZUKU]
This is the story
of how I became the
world's greatest hero. Sure.
But not just me. It's the story
of how we all became
the greatest of heroes.
Midoriya.
We can't just sit here!
[TENYA]
It shouldn't be us this time.
You've got this, Uraraka.
Mr. Deku, I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
I was too afraid to say anything
before. I'm sorry. But--
That girl was trying so hard
to get everyone to let you stay,
and I knew I had
to do something!
Because I want
to be like you!
[KOTA]
And that's why I'm here!
So you don't have to cry
anymore! Everything'll be okay!
Wow. Kota.
I take it you're
a UA student?
[IZUKU]
Yes.
A bunch of the shelters
turned me away.
They said they weren't letting
any heteromorphs inside.
UA was the only refuge
that would welcome me.
But you know, I got to see
you again, so I'm happy.
Thanks for what you did
back then, crybaby hero.
Maybe before we start
getting hysterical,
we listen to what the
young hero has to say.
He just wants to rest.
It's not like he's planning
to stay here permanently.
The city's short on resources
and pros, so where else
can he recover safely?
Don't you think
he deserves a break?
That's what you teachers were
trying to explain, right?
Yes.
Can't he go to Shiketsu? They've
got a secure campus, too!
He could.
But this same thing would
probably happen to him there.
To be honest, I've had to
face some hard truths lately.
Before things got bad,
I felt like the pros
were just performers
on a stage.
We watched an extraordinary
man named All Might
show us what a “hero”
really was.
We applauded him,
and wanted to be him.
And somewhere along the way,
we forgot that he was a person.
But the stage has
been destroyed.
The script was thrown out.
There's no more money
or fame for the pros,
and plenty of them
have called it quits.
Given all that, you gotta
wonder why the rest of them
still bother fighting for us!
If we reject those who are
trying to help us even now,
what do we have worth saving?
How can we expect
to get our lives back?
I know this is tough.
But come on!
We can't keep acting like
a bunch of spectators!
[EVACUEE 137H]
There, uh, were lots of rumors
about a young man in rags
who could use multiple Quirks.
Some said he was working
with the villains,
and some said
he was a true hero.
So tell us. If you get
some rest here,
will you win?
Will things go back to
the way they were before?
I'll make sure of it.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] Because I have
my friends beside me.
And together, we'll
make things right.
[ECTOPLASM] Uravity's speech.
I'm guessing you heard it?
[ECTOPLASM]
You should go on inside.
Things are settling down.
For the moment, at least.
[ENDEAVOR] In the end,
our actions made Deku suffer
even more, didn't they?
We've made no headway.
We should've sent him here
from the beginning.
No, I think what we're seeing
right now is big progress.
One For All is a
crystallization of power
that can link people together.
It connects hearts. It bound
All Might to Midoriya.
Then Class A planted
their feet at his side.
And now, Uravity has pulled
the citizens into the mix.
Take a sec to look around.
[HAWKS] If these people can
unite and think about others
instead of themselves, we might
just see a bright future
where everybody has
a smile on their face
and heroes really do have
too much time on their hands!
Hey, Dad.
We're in this together.
[ENDEAVOR]
Yes.
[NEZU]
I couldn't make them see.
But then, your kids got them
to open their eyes, Aizawa.
They sure did. Tell the class
rep he's done a good job.
[NEZU]
How's the leg?
[AIZAWA] I won't be out-jumping
Mirko any time soon.
What about Kurogiri?
[AIZAWA]
I try talking to him every day.
Unfortunately, there's
been no change.
[NEZU] After he responded to you
and Mic calling out to him,
I was hoping we'd
see some improvement.
That's why he was secretly
transported to Central Hospital
for restoration research.
Mirko crushed the Nomu
with his Quirk in the lab.
But if you hadn't been able
to break through to Shirakumo,
at least a little bit,
we wouldn't have
any strongholds today.
[NEZU] It's not much, but we
were able to spin a thread
of hope that helped
us turn the tables.
[AIZAWA] We're continuing
to watch for Toga?
[NEZU] Yes. We figured out
the amount of blood she needs
to ingest and the duration
of her transformations.
That's why evacuees
can only enter campus
after a period of isolation.
[AIZAWA]
UA is our stronghold.
It's time for our next move.
[NEZU]
Yes, it is.
[ECTOPLASM]
Where are you headed?
[ALL MIGHT] Check on those
hero-hating groups.
They still refuse to
take shelter with us.
[ALL MIGHT]
I could try to stop you,
but I know your
mind is made up.
Well, even if you
don't want my help,
I won't let you do
this alone, understand?
[IZUKU] That's why
you don't have to worry.
One more thing!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
After returning to UA, I make
a new vow with my peers--
No, my friends from Class A.
We swear to take back
everything we've lost.
From now on, we'll work together
until everyone is
able to smile again.
Next time,
"No Man Is an Island."
The heroes connect.
And the heroes disperse.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!