[ALL MIGHT] When your disciple
was desperate and hurting,
you couldn't do
anything for him.
Remain at their side.
Your presence is enough
to inspire greatness.
That's the truth.
[ALL MIGHT] The reality is,
you've been holding him back.
Great job, All Might.
[STAIN]
What's this?
Have you come to blaspheme
against a great hero?
I think not, heretic!
The Hero Killer. Hello, Stain.
Unfortunate that our
paths never crossed
when I was still a hero
who could've stopped you.
And then, after your
capture and imprisonment,
I figured we'd never
have a reason
to meet each other
face-to-face.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I see you don't know.
Quite a bit has happened
since you were put away.
I am All Might.
You lie.
Don't disgrace his name
with your falsehoods.
I don't blame you for
thinking that I'm lying.
[coughs] You gonna kill me now?
If not--
It's a trick.
There's no way you're
the real All Might.
You're an imposter!
We're on sacred ground.
Why are you pretending to be
that man here, of all places?
Who are you to claim
the title of "hero?" Speak!
Pretending.
Sure. That's not far off.
[ALL MIGHT] I always felt like
I had to do something
to help others.
I couldn't stand in
the wings and watch.
Not when I saw people's lives
stolen away from them every day.
Even though I was powerless,
I had to take action.
I wanted to improve society.
[ALL MIGHT]
And then I hung up my cape.
And this is the result.
I was supposed
to protect my successor.
But I couldn't even find a way
to protect him from himself.
[ALL MIGHT]
The reason is obvious.
I am a failure,
watching everyone else
become true heroes.
[ALL MIGHT]
Strange.
I'm not feeling murderous
intent from him.
I'm usually a hugger,
but we just met.
Perfect timing. Watch!
[gasps]
[WOMAN 49A]
They put the sign up again?
Jeez. When are they
gonna cut this out?
[STAIN] Every day, without fail,
she cleans this statue
the hero haters love to defile.
She's probably staying
at a nearby shelter.
No doubt they'd rather
she not come out here.
But she's in danger here.
Why do this?
[STAIN] Because she's the
last person All Might saved.
[gasps]
[WOMAN 49A]
Don't lose.
Keep going.
All Might! We need you!
No matter how terrible
the situation,
All Might smiled as he
faced the insurmountable.
That didn't have anything
to do with his power.
It was the only way
the Symbol of Peace knew
to bring security
to the citizens.
People praised the heart
of his conviction.
You say you're All Might,
but you obviously have
no idea who he was!
Look at that woman!
Make no mistake,
this is All Might's legacy.
The smoldering embers
he left behind
won't be easily extinguished.
They are fueled by the select
few who live in his image.
Before long, they will form
a new, unstoppable blaze.
The important thing is making
sure that fire doesn't go out.
As long we're alive, we have
to keep stoking those flames.
Even if we struggle
or face indignities.
Try your best. I will, too.
You can do it. I believe in you.
Don't give up.
[STAIN] If a person
has the soul of a hero,
they exist only to
help other people.
But if a god is reduced
to a mortal shell,
one who can fall in
the rain, what then?
Wait, don't tell me
this whole time you've--
[STAIN]
I don't know who you are.
But if you really have
the soul of a hero, prove it.
[STAIN] Use this information
I took from Tartarus.
And when you've finished,
make sure you track me down
and put an end to Stain,
the vigilante who
killed 40 heroes,
all for the sake of
forging a better society.
[WOMAN 49A]
Look at that.
The rain's clearing up.
I want that water
scorching hot!
Let's heat it up!
[SERO, SATO]
Strip him down!
[KIRISHIMA, KAMINARI]
Hose him off!
And now...
[GROUP]
It's dunkin' time!
Most things in life can be fixed
if you take a nice, long soak.
Morons! He's dirtying
up the bathwater!
Scrape his skin with steel wool
and buckets of bleach first.
I'm pretty sure
you're suggesting torture
instead of cleaning.
Despite the sincere apology,
he's still the same.
Hey, hold on!
No jumping.
Make no mistake, I'm still
gunning to be number one.
Which means you extras
are my rivals.
And you know I'm mostly
talking to you,
right, De--uh, Izuku?
Don't force yourself
if it's hard for you
to say my real name.
[KATSUKI] Watch your mouth!
Nothing's hard for me, damn it!
[SERO] Well, having ambition's
a good thing, isn't it? Mostly?
[MINETA] This is our chance.
Let's gang up and dunk Bakugo!
[KATSUKI]
No way, shorty!
[IZUKU]
Where's Uraraka?
[JIRO]
Sleeping.
Once she stopped worrying,
the adrenaline wore off.
Some of the others are out, too.
[IZUKU]
That's good.
Hey, guys? Thank you.
And I'm sorry for causing
you so much trouble.
[ASHIDO] Keeping One For All
from us that whole time?
Super lame. Ooh!
The bright side is, after
reading your bonkers confession,
nothing's gonna surprise me.
I just wish you would've told
Hawks to return my calls.
Sorry about that.
I imagine it was difficult
to go from being Quirkless
to wielding such a power.
You managed it, though.
[SERO] Even with those
gnarly broken bones,
which would've been a problem
for anyone in your shoes.
What's One For All feel like?
Can you put it
into words for us?
Well, I guess
it's kinda, like, uh--
We all have questions,
but Midoriya's tired.
Let they guy get some rest.
Isn't that one of the main
reasons we brought him back?
That's how it is, now?
You walk into rooms
posing for pictures?
Yo. Do I look cool?
Hard no, bro.
[TODOROKI]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Thanks for the concern,
but I can't sleep.
Why not?
I acted pretty terribly
towards All Might,
and I haven't apologized.
I feel like it's something
I should do in person.
But he's not picking up
his phone, so--
[IZUKU]
What's he doing outside?
I am here to apologize
for not being of any use.
Young Midoriya!
[IZUKU] Huh? No! What are
you talking about?
You helped me a ton out there!
If you're gonna apologize
for being shady,
you better ask us
for forgiveness, too!
You can't just take our
friend away and ghost us!
[ALL MIGHT] The day of the
final battle will soon be here.
I'm sorry that I caused
everyone to worry.
[ALL MIGHT] The truth is,
I lost sight of who I was.
I thought I was
no longer a hero.
All right, Stain.
Even if all I can do is
crawl, I'll still fight,
because I want to witness
the fire raging in their hearts
with my own eyes.
The details aren't
important at the moment,
but there's new intel.
We should have more information
in the coming days.
And we'll need everyone's help.
Even mine.
This weakened body may limit my
usefulness, but I'll do my best.
[IZUKU]
All Might!
The food you brought me
gave me the strength
to keep going! I'm sure
that I lost my way
because I distanced
myself from you.
So from now on,
we fight side by side.
Let's protect the world!
Thank you all.
[ALL MIGHT] I'll show these kids
that I can stand by their side.
[ALL MIGHT]
Anyway, I gotta go.
Dude, you're bouncing already?
[ALL MIGHT] I need to speak
with Endeavor and the others.
There's still a lot to do.
Please tell Hawks he could
at least send me a text message.
[ALL MIGHT]
Right. I'll pass that on.
[ASHIDO]
Ooh, someone's an Angryami.
I'm concerned, not angry.
[SATO] Why don't Endeavor
and the others
just set up shop at UA?
He would need a good reason
to show his face on campus.
Anyone who sees him
will think of Dabi.
He's doesn't want
to be triggering.
We may have sold the
evacuees on Midoriya,
but they're not thrilled.
Many still don't trust heroes,
especially my old man.
[YAOYOROZU] Seems someone
finally calmed down enough
to get some sleep.
[TODOROKI] As Dabi's brother
and Endeavor's son,
I know people are skeptical
about me being here, too.
Can't blame them.
Just because of your family.
That sucks so bad,
and it's not like you did
anything wrong yourself.
But I did.
I got so obsessed with my
bloodline, I forgot who I was.
I'm acting with a clearer
head now, though.
And I'll destroy
any doubts about me.
I'll do my best to regain
everybody's trust.
Now that's chivalry!
You're making me
cry manly tears!
Right. If we've got
a bunch of evacuees
who aren't exactly fans of ours,
then we just fix that. No prob.
Huh? Jiro? You're
getting really close.
What's going on?
It might be kinda weird
to compare these two things,
but stay with me.
During the school festival,
there were plenty of people
who were on the fence about us.
We wanted to find a way
to reassure them, remember?
And make them feel good, too.
So we made a plan
to win their hearts.
[JIRO]
If we could do it back then,
I know that we can do it again.
We just have to give it our all.
Let's show them who we are.
Yeah, you're right.
[JIRO]
We won't just go back to normal.
We'll make it better
than it was before.
If we can do this together,
we'll go beyond!
[HAWKS]
So.
We got some info about
Shigaraki's upgrades
from Garaki's polygraph
and cross-referenced it
with Central's Nomu research.
It was tricky, since we were
comparing a living person
to some lackeys created
out of corpses,
but we did come to a conclusion.
We believed his body would
be completed after two months.
All our intelligence
pointed to that timeline.
There was also
additional testimony
from the assassins Deku caught.
It sounds like All For One's
intention is to get his hands
on One For All before
his protégé's body
has reached full potential.
A month has passed since
the attack on Tartarus,
which, in theory, left us
with another 30 days or so
to plan our next move on
All For One and the League.
Or so we thought.
[HAWKS] We received Tartarus
security records from Stain,
who gave them to All Might along
with an overzealous love letter
to our Symbol of Peace.
Mr. Fanboy had no intention
of giving this information
to anyone but All Might himself.
[ENDEAVOR] I never thought
that the Hero Killer
would end up being
some sort of ally.
[alarms blare]
[INMATE 138A cackles]
Hell yeah!
I'm coming for you, ladies!
I'm gonna find me so many
girls and take whatever I--
[STAIN]
What is this mess?
If Tartarus has fallen,
what of the outside world?
I need information.
[STAIN]
Nothing left.
[STAIN] The others clung to
their weapons as they died,
but this man?
He's cradling that box
as though it were his child.
[PRISON STAFF 138A]
You can't.
Why would you take this
instead of a gun?
[STAIN]
I need to know.
Away! Leave me.
Chizome Akaguro, you were
on Shigaraki's side.
[STAIN]
This must be important.
[PRISON STAFF 138A grunts]
[STAIN]
Data storage.
[PRISON STAFF 138A]
Stop. Murderer.
Give it back! It's not yours.
Those files have to go
to someone just!
[STAIN]
This world is broken.
But you don't have to worry.
I'll pass your conviction
on to a worthy man.
[PRISON STAFF 138A]
Hero Killer Stain.
Are you a man, or a monster?
Someone who wants to
bring about a better world,
but a monster still.
[STAIN] I have no idea what
that man was trying to protect
with his final breaths,
or what value it may hold.
These events have me lost,
which is why I will entrust this
to the only man I believe in.
I told the guard I would
pass on his resolve,
so you must pick up
where he left off
for the sake of the world.
Because all of this
began with you.
[SANSA] We're done with
our regular patrol.
That's great to hear.
Well, I'm glad you
patched things up
with Midoriya, at least.
Same.
I'll take any good
news I can get,
seeing as how we're being
saved by a murderer.
Without him, we'd have nothing.
Tartarus has a security system
that's completely cut off
from the outside world.
It's a defensive measure.
We shouldn't have been
able to get our hands
on this data at all,
especially since it contains
the reason for
the system failure.
Shigaraki used Radio Waves
liberally in that last battle,
and it caused havoc both
inside and outside the prison.
You mean All For One
and his consciousness
inside Shigaraki were in sync?
Is that what allowed him
to coordinate his attack?
It's more complicated
than that, Sansa.
Yes, he shared his thoughts
through the consciousness
that resides inside
of his Quirk.
I've experienced
a similar phenomenon
as a wielder of One For All.
But the thing is, that sort
of Quirk communication
doesn't go both ways.
Which means what?
[ALL MIGHT] My vestige inside
One For All knows everything
that the me living in
this world sees or thinks.
But in all my years dealing
with this synchronization,
I've never experienced it
working the other way around.
Except in one recent moment.
In the hospital,
when I touched Midoriya,
or close enough, anyway,
my vestige's thoughts just
seemed to flow into me.
But even if All For One
has a higher rate
of synchronization
than the users
of One For All communicate with,
could a body at 500 meters
below sea level
really have the power
to reach out to Shigaraki
on the ground?
Using nothing but thoughts
and the sheer force of will?
Isn't there something
like that with twins?
Some kinda connection
between brains?
Yeah, well, I can't
speak to that.
In this case, though, I know
they talked using Radio Waves.
The data suggests that if
someone has that Quirk,
they can send messages
and receive them.
Our analysis shows
that the radio waveforms
recorded at Tartarus were,
in fact, a conversation.
I didn't realize we had
those results back.
Any idea what they were saying?
That Shigaraki would
be complete in 38 days.
[gasps] But reports from Central
said it'd be two months.
I don't get it.
[ALL MIGHT]
He knew we'd investigate.
So he arranged for the research
to lead us to a
specific conclusion.
We believe these private
communications between his body
and consciousness reveal
the actual schedule.
[ALL MIGHT] Which means
Shigaraki, All For One's vessel,
will be complete
in about three days.
Wait. No way. That soon?
Yes. Which means that we're
quickly running out of options.
We need time and
allies to figure out
how we can go up
against the League.
Soon.
[AMBASSADOR 138A]
A plea from All Might himself?
[AMBASSADOR 138B] He's asking
for them to be deployed
tomorrow, but that's impossible!
A mountain of
paperwork is required
to dispatch heroes overseas.
[AMBASSADOR 138C] And a
country's power is determined
by the strength of its heroes.
Deploying them abroad
upsets the equilibrium
and invites all manner
of attack on a nation.
[AMBASSADOR 138D] Whenever a
wealth of heroes are dispatched,
crime syndicates
jump into overdrive.
We're overwhelmed as it is.
Every country's facing
domestic threats.
The villains are
conspiring across borders.
[AMBASSADOR 138E]
According to Interpol,
All For One has
allies and supporters
scattered across the globe.
[EGYPTIAN AMBASSADOR 138A]
That may be.
But Hawks, Endeavor,
and of course All Might
sent in this request.
There's no way we can ignore it.
Our Salaam wants to
move out immediately.
He's convinced he'll be the one
to take down All For One.
[SINGAPOREAN AMBASSADOR 138A]
Big Red Dot in my country
is also chomping at the bit.
He keeps asking why bureaucracy
should keep him from
saving a friend.
[AMERICAN AMBASSADOR 138A]
Yeah, so, our hero left already.
[AMBASSADORS gasp]
[AMERICAN AMBASSADOR 138A]
Apparently she couldn't stand
to wait around. She dropped
everything and flew off.
[WEDGE] Don't blame us if you
get in trouble, Star!
[STAR AND STRIPE]
It wasn't a question
of whether or not I would help,
so why not start sooner,
rather than later?
And besides, we're talking
about a direct request
from All Might himself.
If my master's got
himself in trouble,
why would I even think twice
before rushing to his side?
Which means now,
it's your turn.
[IZUKU yelps]
Oh, good morning! Hey!
U-Uraraka. Am I--
Dang, Midoriya, did you know
you talk in your sleep?
You're nestled safe and
sound back at UA...
Put those things away.
They look gross.
[IZUKU]
Right! I'm sorry!
There's no need to worry
yourself any more.
Right. From now on,
we'll be standing at your side.
[KIRISHIMA] Yeah.
We're gonna fight as a class.
[IZUKU]
The final battle draws near.
But oddly enough,
I'm not afraid.
I know that I'm not alone.
My friends are with me.
Together, we'll
set things right.
People will smile again.
They'll be happy.
[IZUKU]
The world will get better.
[IZUKU] We'll put an end
to despair, and go beyond!