[HIMURA] It's truly on honor
to be approached by the man
many believe will be the next
number-one hero in Japan!
I never expected such an offer.
Fortune has truly
smiled upon us.
[HIMURA] As you surely know,
the Himura family
has enjoyed a long
and celebrated history.
Which makes my daughter
the perfect match
for a man of your status.
A top-tier pro needs
a fitting bride.
[ENDEAVOR]
She was a woman made of ice.
On the surface our union seemed
like any arranged marriage,
but I had an ulterior motive.
My goal was simple.
To produce the
strongest child possible.
One who wielded
our combined powers.
This was a Quirk marriage.
My flames were strong.
Add the ice abilities of
the Himura family to the mix,
and surely my offspring would
grow to surpass All Might.
While Rei's family
was once prestigious,
they were now struggling.
They craved the
status associated
with the number-two
hero and my money.
Which is probably why her father
quickly agreed
to my proposition.
She had the option to refuse me.
Rei knew exactly what
this marriage was.
And yet, she accepted my
intentions and became my wife
for the sake of her family.
Do you like the flowers?
Yes. They're quite beautiful.
[ENDEAVOR]
There was a strength to her,
but still, she seemed
like she might melt
at the slightest touch.
[ENDEAVOR]
Rei. Hello.
Are you okay?
In what world would I be?
That's why I've come here.
You aren't the
only one suffering.
Because you're not the only one
who overlooked our child.
[DABI]
These are some wicked burns.
I can't feel a thing, though.
Knowing how tough my father is,
I doubt he'll die from whatever
injuries he racked up.
Even if he wanted to,
the number-one hero can't die
unceremoniously
on the battlefield.
I bet he'll do a
press conference soon.
Can't wait to see
his pathetic face.
After so long.
I get to watch 'em break.
Enji.
Mom.
Fuyumi.
Natsuo.
Shoto.
When you're crying in hell,
be sure'n wave.
[DABI]
Huh? No fair!
I don't have school today.
We should be doing
Quirk training together!
C'mon, Dad, you said
you would! 'Member?
I've told you already.
This time off
is for your own good.
[ENDEAVOR]
I have to go.
[DOCTOR 130A]
It's unusual.
Your son inherited a strong
version of your flame Quirk,
that's true, but unfortunately,
his body appears to have
taken after his mother.
In other words, he's physically
built to tolerate freezing
temperatures far
better than heat.
And, uh, in terms
of designer babies...
Look, the whole
concept is taboo.
I suggest you stop pursuing it.
Regardless, Toya shouldn't
be using his Quirk.
Try to keep him from doing so.
I'd hate to see
the boy burn himself
and end up in the
emergency room.
[ENDEAVOR] Toya. I thought
you would exceed All Might
with flames more
powerful than mine--
you should've been the best.
How did this happen?
[TV NARRATOR 130A] He saved
62 municipalities today!
As long as we have this
shining star protecting us...
[DABI]
Hey, Fuyumi.
Why do you think Dad won't let
me do Quirk training anymore?
Uh...
So I got some dumb
burns, big deal.
I'm more than tough
enough to take that.
I know my body
better than anyone,
and I say I'm totally fine.
I agree with Dad,
I don't like it
when you come home
looking hurt. Really.
I was stupid to think
you'd get it.
No girl would understand this!
But I'm worried
about you, brother!
[DABI] I've made my decision.
I'm gonna be better than him.
The top hero!
You're the one who lit
this fire under me, Dad!
[ENDEAVOR grunts]
[REI]
No. That's too much.
It's downright cruel!
Tell him anything else.
He already knows what you
want from your children.
Just let him have hope!
[ENDEAVOR]
No matter what I say to him,
he shows up at the house
with new injuries every day.
The boy is stubborn,
just like his father.
This is the only way
to make him give up.
He has to know.
He can't beat All Might.
[ENDEAVOR grunts]
[TODOROKI crying]
[gasps]
[DABI] You're wrong, Dad.
I can be the next number one.
Watch me.
My flames are stronger
every time I come out here.
I've been practicing
this entire time.
I know I can do it.
I'll surpass All Might.
Wait and see.
Just keep your
eyes on me, okay?
[ENDEAVOR] Dammit, when will you
get this through your head?
Have you learned nothing
from getting burned
over and over again?
Listen, Toya! Find a new
dream to pursue.
Go play with Fuyumi and Natsuo!
Make friends at school
and do stuff with them!
There are plenty of things
to do with your life
besides being a hero.
Leave this unattainable
goal behind you.
But the kids at school say
they're gonna be pros one day.
[gasps]
They don't get what it's
like for me. But you do.
You showed me being the best
is what matters.
Toya, no, you have to cool off.
[DABI] You pushed me
to want this, Dad!
It's too late now.
I can't unlearn
what you taught me.
Keep watching. You'll see.
[ENDEAVOR gasps]
[DABI]
Look at me, Endeavor!
[ENDEAVOR]
From now on, Shoto isn't allowed
anywhere near
the other children.
I have work.
I can't watch him all the time.
But that's why we have the help.
You don't let Toya
out of your sight.
[REI] He just wants you
to pay attention to him.
I only know the world of heroes.
There's nothing there for him.
[REI] So that's it?
You're running away.
[FUYUMI]
Hey, Toya! Come play!
Yours!
[DABI]
Got it.
--[laughs]
--[FUYUMI] Are you hurt?
[ENDEAVOR]
Ignore them, Shoto.
They live in a different world
than the one I'm
training you for.
Can't I just play with
them a few minutes?
They look like they're
having fun together.
[ENDEAVOR] There's no time.
You've work to do.
[DABI]
Y'know what?
I think I had the
wrong idea back then.
Shoto isn't the one
I should blame.
Dad's the person who
messed up everything.
We're failures to him, so he
pretends we don't even exist.
That's just how it works, not
like he's all that different.
Lots of heroes have kids
that they don't want.
[NATSUO] You've already told me
this, like, 1,000,000 times.
Ugh, why don't you go
bother Fuyumi instead?
No, hold on, are you
ignoring me, too, Natsu?
Please don't do that!
I'm telling you this stuff
'cause you have to understand.
You agree, right?
Besides, the women in
our family are all useless.
[REI]
Wait!
Are you planning to go
to the mountain again?
Why don't you hang out
with your classmates in--?
No. I don't need friends!
I'm different from them!
Toya, tell me, do you really
want to become a hero?
'Cause from what I see,
it looks like you're suffering
simply because you want
to please your father.
Son, there are many
different paths in life.
You have countless
opportunities.
Don't spend your life chasing
someone else's dream.
I want you to find something
you're actually passionate
about in this world.
Shut up, Mom.
You don't know anything.
[gasps]
[DABI] This from one of your
self-help books or something?
I know Grandma and
Grandpa were poor.
That's why they sold you, right?
You had no choice in what
your life would be like.
[REI]
Son.
[DABI]
But you did decide to have me.
So you're to blame
for this, too.
[REI]
Toya.
[DABI]
My fire wouldn't go out.
I was smaller than
most kids my age,
but when I hit puberty,
things changed.
And my flames suddenly
transformed from red to blue.
[DABI] I see. They're like
extensions of my body.
When I get excited, my firepower
goes through the roof!
Oh, man, I'm incredible.
Dad is gonna be so surprised
when he sees this!
Ugh. Dammit. No crying!
Why do I always tear up
when things go my way.
[DABI]
Dad!
Your next day off, you gotta
come to Sekoto Peak!
[ENDEAVOR]
New burns!
He's hiding them beneath
his clothing now.
Toya you're still training?
And I've gotten super awesome!
Make sure you come watch!
I bet I can get to Shoto's
level pretty soon.
Or All Might's
level. No, better!
And I guess then
you'd have to accept
that I'm not actually
a failure like you thought.
After all these years you'll be
happy to have me as your son!
--[slap]
--[TODOROKI screaming]
[ENDEAVOR]
I asked you to do one thing.
Just stop him from training!
I won't let you
be mean to Mommy!
Stop it! You're being a bully!
[ENDEAVOR]
Get out of here, Shoto!
This has nothing to do with you.
Shut up, Mom.
You don't know anything!
[REI] My options were limited
when I was younger.
But I chose to marry you
of my own free will.
I thought, if I kept
a smile on my face,
things might work out.
I tried my best.
He wouldn't listen.
He's your problem now.
You deal with this.
Be of use for once.
[REI] What do you see when
you glare at me like that?
Please don't look at me
with those horrible eyes.
[REI]
Those eyes!
I was taken to a facility.
Which is where I heard
about Toya's death.
That loss shattered whatever
was left of my mind.
[DABI]
Suck it up. Do not cry.
[REI] You didn't go to
Sekoto Peak like he asked.
[ENDEAVOR]
I was afraid if I did,
it would feed a fire that
was already out of control.
No. The real reason is
I had no idea what to say.
Or how to be Toya's father.
[DABI]
Dad.
I guess we both failed
in that sense.
[DABI screams]
It's too hot! Please
go out! It hurts!
Now that was some
impressive heat.
Well. What did you
expect, old man?
All you ever taught me
was how to burn everything.
[ENDEAVOR] If onlyI'd just given
everything up that day.
But after I killed Toya,
I couldn't go back.
The only thing I knew how
to focus on was molding Shoto
into the hero I could
never be myself.
The more domineering you were,
the harder it was
to look at you.
And whenever I looked
at my children,
it was your eyes I saw
staring back at me.
Even though I knew
we were falling apart.
I was too scared to get
to the bottom of our pain.
So I tried to
keep up appearances.
Ignoring the truth.
You're the one who
put us on this path,
and I know you're to blame.
But if I'd been able to
knock some sense into Toya
before he ran off
to the mountain,
he wouldn't have
turned into Dabi,
and things might've been
different between me and Shoto.
[REI] The responsibility is
not yours to bear alone.
Your heart may be broken,
but we're going to help you
put it back together.
Because you have no choice
but to fight Dabi one day.
Rei, are...
Are you sure? How can I...
Shoto must've suffered
so much more than we did.
But he still started
calling me "Mom" again.
Even though he has
every right to hate me.
He's made friends at UA High.
And he's protected each of us,
likely more than we know.
He is the true hero
in this family.
[coughs] Before coming in here,
I had a long talk with Mom.
I thought you wouldn't
be able to fight
after how things went down.
That I would have
to face Dabi myself.
That's not the case, though.
So whenever you're done crying,
you and I will work
to stop Toya together.
[ENDEAVOR]
Sho... Shoto.
Shoto!
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Pardon us.
We were kind of listening
in to your convo.
And since we're in the loop,
mind if we join your
weird family reunion?
[TODOROKI]
Best Jeanist and Hawks!
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A] I was
discharged from the hospital
yesterday, and already
gathered a bunch of info
about what's going on--
[REI] I am deeply ashamed and
apologize for my son's actions.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Huh? That's definitely not
the reason we're here.
Seriously. Please stop, ma'am.
[BEST JEANIST] I admit we
wanted answers about Dabi,
but eavesdropping is sketchy
like blackmarket denim.
[TODOROKI]
What does that even mean?
[BEST JEANIST] Knowing the
source of his resentment
could make things easier.
The more we know
about how he survived
and why he adopted this
Dabi persona the better.
We can speak to
the child inside him.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A] I've
watched a lot of videos of you
over the years, Endeavor, but I
never guessed the tenacity
you had in your younger years
would make your home so hellish.
Gotta admit, it's shocking.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
This didn't come up
when you were talking
about Toya, but...
Are you to blame for the burn
on Shoto's face as well?
[TODOROKI]
So close.
No that was me.
Mom, you--
[REI] But he still started
calling me "Mom" again.
Even though he has
every right to hate me.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
I see.
[HAWKS] I never got
to confront my parents.
Instead, I abandoned them.
But you've stood your ground.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Shoto. You're a heck of a kid.
Endeavor, the world
is going to pieces.
I know.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Shigaraki, Dabi, Himiko Toga,
Spinner, Skeptic, and 132
Liberation Front
members escaped.
As well as seven
Near High End Nomu.
At this point, we have no leads.
No idea where they're hiding.
In addition to Tartarus, six
other prisons were broken into.
At least 10,000 prisoners
have been released
into the wild.
Causing mayhem and panic.
There's also no agency
calling the shots for us.
Not that there are a ton
of heroes left to organize.
Pros are resigning
left and right.
Many civilians have lost faith
in our ability to
protect the streets,
so they're taking up arms and
fighting villains themselves.
Which inevitably leads
to collateral damage.
Currently, the government
is requesting aid
in the form of rescue
teams and heroes
from other countries, but
with the safety commission
in shambles, bureaucracy
is getting in the way.
Everything's gone to crap
in just two days.
And I second what
your wife said.
You have no choice
but to keep fighting.
Of course, we've got your back.
Responsibility for this can't
be put on your shoulders alone.
And it's not your
family's fault either.
You would help me?
[HAWKS] Even if Dabi was right
about the Todoroki family,
things are different now.
I want to do what's right
and support people
who are trying their
best to do the same.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Yep!
We propose a little a team-up
between the top three heroes!
[BEST JEANIST] I've already bet
my life on Hawks once.
This will be another
tricky runway to walk,
but we will prevail.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A] Look at
who's standing in front of you.
Don't we make the burden
feel a little lighter?
Isn't it time to move forward?
Yes. Yeah.
We'll help you,
just till we stop Toya.
[ENDEAVOR]
Right.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Now, to get down to business.
First, we explain things
to the public.
After Dabi's dramatic speech,
that's unavoidable.
I've given some thought to how
we might go about responding,
but there's still
a little confusion.
What do you know
about "One For All"?
Oh, yeah. A reporter
mentioned that, too.
[REPORTER 130A] While he
was fighting Shigaraki,
Endeavor mentioned something
called "One For All."
Do you know who or what
he was referencing?
[REPORTER 130B]
Does it have anything to do with
that terrifying supervillain
known as All For One?
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Whatever it is,
we need to figure out how
it factors into the puzzle.
[IZUKU]
Sorry for using a private line.
It's highly possible that
I'm the one Shigaraki's after.
Deku.
Deku, you bastard,
you're dead!
I've been awake for how long...
[MINETA] Stop yelling,
this is a hospital!
[SATO]
...we're trying to grieve?
[TENYA] Uh, thank you
for the assistance, Tsu!
What is wrong with that boy?
When I saw the extent
of his injuries,
I figured he'd be
out for a while.
And yet, he's somehow
louder than ever.
[JIRO]
Hey, guys.
Sounds like Tokoyami
and Kaminari
are cleared to go home now.
Are they really?
That's wonderful news!
Are there, uh,
any updates on
Midoriya's recovery yet?
[OCHACO]
They said his body's fine.
But I'm still worried.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Heyo.
[BEST JEANIST] Great Explosion
Murder God Dynamight,
are you all right?
[KATSUKI]
What's it look like?
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
We'd like a few words
with Izuku Midoriya.
[TENYA] Well... All Might said
to leave the two of them alone.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
He did, huh?
[HAWKS] Endeavor said that
Shigaraki was after Midoriya,
and All Might is clearly
involved somehow.
What in the world
is One For All?
[ALL MIGHT] Young Midoriya.
I can feel it.
The vestige of me that
lives within One For All.
Inside you.
Right now, you must be talking
with the previous wielders.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
While I sleep in the real world,
my consciousness is awake
inside of One For All.
Past generations of wielders
share their secrets.
And eventually, I'm faced
with a question.
"Can you kill Tomura Shigaraki?"
How do I answer that?
Next time,
"Izuku Midoriya and
Tomura Shigaraki."
My origin is about to be tested.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!