[ALL MIGHT]
I can feel it.
The vestige of me that
lives within One For All.
Inside you.
[ALL MIGHT]
Right now, you must be talking
with the previous wielders.
[IZUKU] What's going on?
What happened to everybody else?
My friends. My teachers.
Please. Let them be okay.
[BANJO]
We need to have ourselves a talk
before you wake up.
My apologies.
The timing's not ideal.
Fate has brought us here.
Oh, please.
It's just bad luck
this is happening now.
[EN] Banjo, you spoke
to him before, yes?
When he first used Blackwhip.
[IZUKU] These are the people
who had One For All before me.
They're in my dreams again.
[FIRST WIELDER] At first,
we could only talk to you
when we found cracks
in your consciousness.
But we're not limited
to those moments anymore.
The reason is related
to my power,
which you now hold.
About four months ago,
it suddenly began to
grow at a rapid pace.
As a result of
this acceleration,
the previous wielders,
the figures you see
in front of you now,
were able to take shape
and communicate with each other
inside of One For All.
When my brother
forcibly pulled us
into the battle earlier,
we gained even more freedom.
It's now far easier for us
to appear before you.
Don't you worry,
we'll still give you plenty a'
privacy if you know what I mean.
[IZUKU muffled grunting]
Oh, right. I forgot you don't
have a mouth in here.
[IZUKU]
Right. Back then...
[IZUKU yells]
[IZUKU] I wasn't able to do
much more than make noise.
Now it feels like my mouth's
starting to take shape.
[IZUKU muffled]
Dang! I can almost
understand what you're saying.
[SHINOMORI]
Allow me to explain.
My name's Hikage Shinomori.
and I was One For All's
fourth wielder.
During the recent battle,
you unintentionally tapped
into my Quirk and
used it on the field.
[IZUKU muffled]
Yeah!
[IZUKU]
According to All Might,
the fourth wielder's Quirk was
the ability to sense danger.
It was kind of
a shock to be honest.
[IZUKU muffled]
Strange that I didn't
sense you'd be
using Danger Sense
since it is my Quirk.
[IZUKU]
Makes a lot of "sense." Heh.
Number four's a weird one.
He got tired of everyday life,
so he started living in
seclusion like a hermit.
Mine was a terrible era.
The rest of society
was strange, not me.
Were you informed of how I died
and how old I was at the time?
[IZUKU muffled]
[IZUKU] All Might didn't mention
specifics in his notes.
Actually. I'm pretty
sure he crossed out
the important details.
We discovered
I died of old age.
[IZUKU]
But, he was so young!
I was as surprised as you.
Neither Banjo nor I had any way
of knowing how we died.
We only found out because
Yagi looked into the matter.
What this fact
leads us to believe
is that One For All
can't be wielded safely
by an ordinary human being.
[SHINOMORI] I'm second only
to Yagi in terms of users
who lived with the
Quirk the longest.
For 18 years I spent
my days training
and building up the
power as best I could.
Avoiding All For One.
I always knew I didn't
stand a chance
of defeating him myself.
So I figured the best
thing I could do
was improve the Quirk
for its next user.
But as time passed,
cracks began appearing
on my body.
I thought perhaps
I wasn't training enough
or that I'd contracted
some unknown disease.
That wasn't the case.
As Yagi researched,
he was able to track down
my medical records
and autopsy report.
That's when the truth
came to light.
The "natural causes"
that killed me
were due to the multiple
Quirks inside my body.
They drastically
shortened my lifespan.
[IZUKU muffled]
That's correct.
Which is exactly the reason
we needed to talk to you.
Yagi is fully aware
of what a burden it is
to carry One For All.
A burden that you'll
have to deal with.
We don't have a
proper sample size.
Most of us didn't
have the power long.
We died in battle,
not of "old age."
So we asked,
what was the intrinsic
difference between
Yagi and Shinomori?
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU]
All Might was Quirkless!
Yes. Yagi may still be alive,
but as he gathered information,
we took what he learned
through the piece of him
that exists inside
of One For All.
And then, after I
heard what my brother
had to say, I was certain.
According to what he said,
a person's consciousnesses is
etched into their Quirk factor.
So why is Yagi's vestige
here even though
he didn't have an
ability of his own?
We always thought
a piece of the user
ended up inside of One For All
because of the power
they were born with.
More precisely,
that the consciousness
of every wielder after me lived
on because their Quirk factors
were added to my One For All.
Yagi being the exception.
[FIRST WIELDER] With no Quirk
of his own, he's the only user
who gained a vestige through
One For All itself.
Think of one's ability
to hold a Quirk as a glass.
If it's not empty when
they inherit One For All,
it overflows, eating
away at your lifespan.
Yagi was able to use
One For All over the course
of 40 years because his
vessel was empty at first.
My cultivated power
fit perfectly,
and it became his true Quirk.
By some twist of fate,
this ability that's passed
from person to person, could
only reach its true potential
when wielded by someone
born powerless.
[IZUKU muffled]
There is a caveat.
You could pass it on
to another Quirkless person,
but they're like an
endangered species,
few and far between these days.
It's not something we could've
known in the beginning.
We learned this over
generations of observation.
[FIRST WIELDER] It must have
been fate once again that
the two of you somehow became
back-to-back recipients.
If we'd been able to talk with
the other users sooner,
perhaps fewer people
might've suffered
over the years.
Ya get what this means, kid?
You might be the last person
who wields One For All.
[IZUKU muffled]
And now the real question.
Izuku.
Tell us.
Can you kill Tomura Shigaraki?
[NANA]
Tell us.
Can you kill Tomura Shigaraki?
[IZUKU gasps]
[NANA]
That's not a request.
I'm gauging your resolve.
When you saw that boy's face,
you thought he looked as though
he was asking
for help, didn't you?
We feel your emotions,
so we know what was ringing
through your head in that
moment of desperation.
[BANJO] The problem is,
the rest of us had a completely
different take on the situation.
We know All For One
was inside his head.
Which was causing
Shigaraki pain, yeah.
But in that moment, it didn't
seem like he wanted to be saved.
Even as he suffered
in front of us,
those terrible eyes held
nothing but hatred.
Because that's the person
All For One raised him to be.
My brother was incarcerated
during the fight.
I think his plan was probably
to possess Shigaraki
both physically and mentally.
So that he could
take One For All.
Me and En, my junior here.
We both ended up
facing All For One,
but we managed to keep him from
stealing the power from us.
Cause in order to make
One For All surrender,
you gotta come at it with
a passion that surpasses
the Quirk's incredible power.
No person can produce such
an overwhelming will alone.
Our best guess is
All For One's trying
to use Shigaraki's
hatred as a booster.
[BANJO] At the heart of
the Quirk inside of you
is a grit that refuses
to yield to that monster,
despite his strength.
[FIRST WIELDER]
We believe that One For All
is meant to destroy
All For One completely.
It looked like Yagi
had accomplished this.
But my brother is tenacious and
he's trying to make a comeback.
[NANA]
Izuku. I know it's not fair
to tell you this
after explaining
you can't abandon your power.
But Tomura Shigaraki
is my grandson.
I left my family
to fight All For One.
Abandoned my child.
And this is the result.
We're in a terrible situation.
It's disgraceful that I failed
to achieve my goal,
and now have to rely
on a 16-year-old.
However, if that monster
manages to fully awaken,
no one will be able to stop him.
You can't make him see reason
or offer him forgiveness.
Some people are simply
beyond redemption.
And I believe Tomura
is one of them.
So if you think he looked
like he wanted to be saved...
Ask yourself.
In the end, will you have the
resolve necessary to kill him?
[IZUKU muffled]
[IZUKU] When Shigaraki's
consciousness penetrated
One For All, we were so close.
I know how hard he
focuses on his dream.
Yet in the depths
of that hatred.
I could sense
a lost child crying.
I've fought a lot of people
since I received this power.
I had to, because they
wouldn't back down.
It was my only option.
The thing is,
I never found out why they
ended up becoming villains.
What caused all their anger.
If I had known, maybe things
would've been different.
Maybe I still would've
had to fight. Maybe not.
Shigaraki killed so
many innocent people.
He hurt those I care about.
But still.
One For All isn't a power
meant to do harm.
It's a power meant to save.
That's something I learned
from All Might.
[IZUKU]
It's not just me.
This thing you've cultivated
through blood, sweat, and tears
has encouraged countless people
to become better versions
of themselves over
the generations.
Even if it started as a way
to destroy your brother.
It's evolved into something else
thanks to what you've done.
One For All has taken on
another purpose in this world.
I don't know what I should
do next, that's true,
and I get that the
only way to stop him
might be to kill him, but...
I want to save that little kid.
[gasps]
And that's why
we'll follow your lead.
I'm so happy that my power
was passed on to you two.
[IZUKU]
M-My body!
[NANA] This was a test,
for which I apologize.
Gran Torino is alive.
When you wake up,
tell him I said hello.
[NANA]
Sorahiko.
We made a mistake
those many years ago.
Yet somehow,
we were still blessed
with the most amazing students.
You two better start
helping out.
You can't just ignore us.
We need your cooperation
to unleash
One For All's full potential.
[ALL MIGHT] I don't know
what you're saying,
but I can feel the conversation.
The predecessors are
sharing their stories.
The truth about One For All.
My master's regrets.
The exact details may be hazy.
But the information
is flowing through me.
You were once Quirkless.
And now look at you.
[knocking]
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A] It's
nice to meet you, All Might.
You're Hawks right?
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
Let's skip the intros
so I can get straight
to the important stuff.
Is Midoriya going to recover?
Yes. He'll pull through this.
He should be conscious soon.
But he's not the only
reason you're here.
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A] This is
about Midoriya and One For All.
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[SMARTPHONE VOICE 129A]
A hero from the raid
heard something about
it on the radio.
Then mentioned it to reporters.
More and more people
are asking questions.
And Endeavor told us that,
as the battle progressed,
Shigaraki was targeting
Midoriya, a mere UA Student.
I'm trying to get
the full picture.
Because from now on, we're
not just fighting villains.
We're also battling
public sentiment.
[ALL MIGHT]
You must keep this secret
to ensure your
own wellbeing, true.
But also for the safety
of the world.
[ALL MIGHT] Things have
changed so much, so quickly.
And these two aren't
the types to back down.
We should talk
somewhere private.
I'll tell you everything.
[OCHACO] It's been three
days since the incident.
With every passing hour,
there's more panic.
But despite reports,
I don't think everyone
wants blame the pros.
They want to believe
heroes have integrity.
To feel their protectors
did nothing wrong.
People want to feel safe.
They need somebody
to put their faith in.
Dabi is indeed my oldest
son, Toya Todoroki.
I can't deny what
he spoke is the truth.
I stand before you to
apologize for my misdeeds.
[OCHACO] Endeavor talked
to the press at length
about his family's ugly past.
And asked the world
to forgive him.
[MAN 131A]
Oh, man.
That's the end
of his pro career.
What a terrible father.
Dude, he shoulda denied it.
I was rooting for the guy.
[REPORTER 131A] You're saying
that he didn't lie, but he did.
He's right,
Best Jeanist is alive,
which refutes Dabi's claims
that Hawks murdered him.
Yeah. Get your
stories straight.
Best Jeanist was made
to look like he was dead
and that's how I
infiltrated their ranks.
But the rest of the awful
things Dabi mentioned
are correct for the most part.
My father's identity.
How I killed a desperate villain
who was running away.
That's all true.
I apologize for hiding
the truth about my origin.
I know now that
it was a mistake.
Regarding Jin Bubaigawara.
The League member
known as Twice.
I thought I had no other choice
but to keep him
out of the fight.
If he had activated his Quirk,
the damage would've been
unimaginably worse
than it already was.
I did want to bring him
in for his crimes.
But in the end, his concern
for his fellow League members
forced the issue.
I had to act.
I feel awful for
how things went down.
I just hope you'll believe me.
I've got a question.
In the chaos caused
by Gigantomachia,
my own mother was
seriously injured.
Do you really think apologizing
and saying you feel
bad fixes anything?
Do you have any idea
how many people
lost their homes?
Their livelihoods this week?
I don't think you understand
how much you screwed up.
It was the villains
who did this, sure,
but the only reason they
were able to wreak havoc
on such a scale is because
of your mistakes.
If we stood up here
crying and carrying on,
would that make
your mother better?
Huh? No of course it wouldn't!
But you could do
something besides talk!
Take care of the villains
on the streets!
Be a...
...a hero.
You make a good point.
As number one, that's how
I will atone for my sins.
[BEST JEANIST]
But right now,
there are fewer heroes
in the field.
We're no longer equipped
to protect so many citizens.
With that in mind,
we have patterned
a temporary solution.
After consulting
with government officials,
we'd like to announce that,
starting today, UA High
and other schools
with hero courses
will be designated
as emergency shelters.
There should be plenty
of space in these facilities
for anyone who is scared
or seeking protection.
Families of enrolled students
are already moving
into these buildings.
[REPORTER 131C]
You want us to leave our homes
with no idea when
we can go back?
We're looking toward the future.
Direct your blame and anger
at me, but let us help you.
Plenty of pros are still
risking their lives for you.
Again, I'll say, watch me.
[OCHACO] Our champions
are at a crossroads.
If a hero is someone people
know they can call on
when they need help, then the
heroes disappeared that day.
Even so.
There are those still
willing to fight.
[DABI]
Haven't had enough pain yet?
[OCHACO] When Endeavor was
asked about "One For All,"
he said he knew
nothing about it.
That way no one could be
mad at Deku or All Might.
[MINETA]
Guys, this is super bad!
Look! I had a letter
from Midoriya on my door!
Yeah, we know. Us, too.
[KIRISHIMA]
What is this?
[SHOJI]
All For One?
The villains are after him?
Doesn't make any sense!
Poor Midoriya.
[IZUKU]
Uraraka, thank you.
So much.
It's time for you and the rest
of our class to know everything.
So I'm writing letters
to try and explain.
My Quirk is a power passed
on to me from All Might.
It's a gift that Shigaraki and
All For One want to steal,
so they're coming after me.
The last thing I want to do
is put others in danger,
and it's dangerous
to be near me.
So I'm leaving UA.
Being in the hero course and
meeting everyone in Class A
has made me happier than
I could have ever imagined.
Thank you.
And goodbye.
You idiot.
[OCHACO] If heroes are those
who don't hesitate
to take the hardest path,
then who will be willing
to follow them when
they're suffering?
[OCHACO] In April,
Deku left our hero academy.
[IZUKU]
Looks like a huge villain.
Here's the preview!
It was tough, but I left UA High
and my friends from
Class A behind.
Sorry, everyone.
But I can't stay.
As the final successor of
One For All, it's up to me
to stop Shigaraki
and All For One.
And I don't want anyone
else getting hurt.
Next time, "Full Power!"
The final act in the
story of how I become
the greatest hero
is about to begin.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!