[IZUKU]
This is a superhuman society,
where about 80 percent
of people are born
with an uncanny ability
known as a Quirk.
Not everyone uses their
powers for good, though.
Which is why the world
needed a new profession:
the hero.
[IZUKU] My name is Izuku
Midoriya and I inherited
a secret Quirk called
"One For All" from All Might.
That's how I was enrolled
in the hero course at UA.
After a series of incidents
that put us up against
the worst of the worst,
my incredible classmates and I
got our provisional
hero licenses.
We had our hands full
at the end of our
first year at UA.
Which is why we didn't realize
the evil quietly growing
in the shadows until
it was too strong to ignore.
[YOTSUBASHI] Welcome,
and thank you for coming.
Liberation warriors!
I am Re-Destro. It is
a pleasure to see you.
From this moment,
the Liberation Army
recognizes Tomura Shigaraki
as grand commander.
Now, the name please,
Tomura Shigaraki!
[SHIGARAKI] "The Paranormal
Liberation Front"!
We got rid of the term
"villain" and expanded on
the whole meta angle
to be a little more inclusive.
The nine people on stage
are my lieutenants.
Teams will be assigned
to them based on our needs.
Anyway, the name's
the same as this hand,
a decoration.
We'll do what we want.
[LIBERATION ARMY cheers]
[HAWKS]
I'm too late!
This superhuman society may be
overflowing with heroes,
but Shigaraki has
gathered so much power
that it might be
impossible to stop him.
Come on, Hawks.
If you're too slow,
it'll be the end of Japan.
[DOCTOR] Your Quirk blossomed
in the Deika City fight.
Now, you can obliterate
not only something you touch,
but also whatever
is connected to it.
You have become the
embodiment of destruction.
I won't underestimate
heroes anymore.
I'll use all the power I can get
to destroy All Might
and his legacy.
Our next fight's his last.
[IZUKU]
A decisive battle is upon us.
An all-out war
between the villains
of the Paranormal Liberation
Front and the heroes
sworn to protect this world,
is about to begin.
[HAWKS]
It's been a week since I passed
the safety commission my hint.
The word "Hospital."
[TWICE]
Hey! Hawks!
Hey there, Twice. 'Sup?
[TWICE]
I need some help, pronto!
Crap. You've got
Carmine guys with you?
Uh, could we...
Excuse me for a moment.
Start talking.
[TWICE] I gotta come up with
something to use as a credo.
Why do you need my help?
[TWICE] Spinner and Compress
are in meetings
with Re-Destro all day.
Talk, talk, talk.
Giran and Dabi
couldn't care less.
And Toga's too cute to ask.
Please, Sensei.
Help a confused man out.
Sanctum just said,
"There are still troops
who don't trust us.
Even if you're
just a figurehead,
they should hear some credo
or mission statement from you,
and it better be inspiring."
And the only thing
I could think was,
"Uh, I gotta take a dump!"
And that's when I
ran out here to find you.
[laughs] You actually said
that to ol' Sanctum?
That dude is one of the founding
members of the Liberation Army.
[HAWKS]
The Paranormal Liberation Front
has been split into regiments.
These groups specialize in
different areas and are led
by members of the
League of Villains
and high-ranking brass
from the old MLA.
The three strongest
members of each regiment
serve as aides
to the lieutenants.
All but one of the aides
previously headed bases
across the country.
Their duties
kept them elsewhere,
so they didn't participate in
the revival party in Deika City.
Still, their abilities surpass
those of the average hero.
Lemme think a second.
[HAWKS]
If they move first, we'll lose.
I've been under strict
surveillance since I came here.
The only way I've been
able to get a clear idea
of the organization's
structure is because of
the intelligence skills
the safety commission
drilled into me
when I was a kid.
One thing is obvious.
There's hostility and resentment
toward the current system.
[HAWKS]
I think I got somethin'.
"The freedom of an
individual reigns supreme
and the existing status quo
must be destroyed."
A little wordy, but I
think it would work.
[TWICE]
Perfect!
[HAWKS]
Oh, yeah.
And "We must be completely
devoted to Re-Destro."
[TWICE]
Huh?
I mean, it's because of
his bloodline that we were able
to band together
in the first place.
[TWICE]
Uh, maybe we could add that.
I'll think about it.
We should totally
talk that guy up!
Good call! Thanks for your help!
[HAWKS]
Anytime, friend!
The future looks dire.
What they're really
trying to accomplish
by breaking the status quo,
is the annihilation of
every hero in existence.
[HAWKS] They'll attack major
cities across the country.
Citizens will be left
without leaders.
Chaos will ensue.
Then, Re-Destro and the
Hearts and Mind Party
will swoop in.
They'll hand out weapons
and encourage self-defense.
It'll be like when
Quirks first appeared
and laws became meaningless.
Shigaraki will ascend
a throne of rubble
and rule a world of anarchy.
Which really means, the second
coming of All For One.
The end of Japan as we know it.
[TWICE]
Hey. You know, you're the best.
Especially to me.
Glad I got such a nice pal.
Right back atcha.
[HAWKS] All of this came
into focus thanks to you,
Jin Bubaigawara.
When I heard you'd
overcome your trauma,
I feared what you might do.
You went from being
a petty criminal
to a one-man army.
The person we needed
to keep the closest eye on.
But I also knew that
you were friendly guy.
[TWICE] You sure know a ton
about the Liberation Army
for being a pro hero.
Why is that?
Because I believe in
what they preach.
The world I once dreamed of
turned out to be a birdcage
that kept me prisoner.
I wanna fly free.
But I can't do that
as things are now.
[TWICE]
Ah, jeez, man!
We gotta get ya
in front a' Shigaraki
so he knows you're legit!
[HAWKS]
Seriously.
Kinda weird I haven't
gotten to talk to him.
[TWICE] That's because
he's off getting stronger.
He'll be in the mountains
near Kyoto for four months.
Whoops, that's a secret.
Though I'm sure that
long-haired spy heard me.
Ya big creep!
Anyway, I don't think
it matters if you know
since you're working
so hard for us.
We're a lot alike.
The best people are those
who help their friends.
Don't you agree?
Yeah, I thought so.
[TWICE] Let's fly
where we want together!
[HAWKS] I was right.
Friendly and far too trusting.
[DOCTOR humming]
You sure seem happy, Doctor.
Good morning!
[DOCTOR laughs]
And to you!
[IZUKU]
Kyudai Garaki.
Quirkless.
The founder of
Jaku General Hospital
and its current
chairman of the board.
He championed the idea
of Quirk-based community
medical care and started
doing philanthropic work
soon after opening the hospital.
That meant building
orphanages and nursing homes
throughout the country,
as well as partnering with
private hospitals and clinics.
On the surface,
the doctor comes across
as a kind man.
He's respected and even admired.
[LOCKLOCK]
So this is the monster.
A true villain.
All For One's
most trusted agent.
Right. And he's
the mad scientist
who bioengineered
those Nomu abominations.
How are you so certain
he's the one to blame?
I sent someone in
undercover after receiving
intel from the
safety commission.
He found a restricted area
within the hospital.
None of the staff
knew its purpose.
[TSUKAUCHI] This off-limits
area has one entrance:
through the morgue.
Garaki is the only person
who ever comes and goes.
If you need more evidence...
This picture's from
our man inside.
Is that a tiny Nomu?
It would be easy
to arrest the doctor
since he's a public figure.
But if we act rashly, the
Paranormal Liberation Front
will enact countermeasures.
The last thing
we want is a repeat
of the widespread devastation
in Hosu or Camino.
Those events traumatized
the public and we lost
too many good people
on our side.
Sure, we were able
to apprehend All For One.
But it was at the cost
of our number one.
All Might was forced to retire.
Therefore, we'll
face this situation
with every available
resource at our disposal.
First,
the pros will be split
into two groups.
Team Endeavor will be
in charge of securing
Kyudai Garaki at Jaku Hospital.
Team Edge Shot will storm
the Gunga Mountain Villa
we believe to be the Paranormal
Liberation Front's hideout.
These two events
will happen simultaneously.
In addition, hero course
students will be deployed
as logistical support
for both teams.
They'll assist with civilian
evacuation and rescue
if the encounters
start to escalate.
We expect substantial resistance
from the villains,
their supporters, and the Nomu,
but we cannot wait any longer.
If we don't act now,
they will prevail.
The doctor, his pets,
Shigaraki--
every villain must fall.
Heroes, the idea is to take out
the entire Paranormal
Liberation Front in one sweep.
[EDGE SHOT] Our intel states
that the lieutenants
have gathered for
a routine meeting.
Every one of them should
be inside this mansion.
Our enemy has someone
with a warping power,
but apparently that creature
is at the hospital.
As long as he's kept
out of the equation,
these foes will have
nowhere to run.
[KOMORI] Um. Is it a good idea
for us to be this close?
[HONENUKI]
What's wrong?
Doesn't the League of Villains
have it out for UA students?
[MIDNIGHT] They've become
too big of a problem.
[HONENUKI]
Ms. Midnight.
[MIDNIGHT] Now that they've
amassed so much raw power,
Shigaraki will move
to dominate society.
That means the entire world is
in danger, not just the school.
[MIDNIGHT]
Don't you worry.
We just want you
to help us a little
at the very beginning
of the raid.
After that, you'll
go to the rear.
Whatever you need.
[KAMINARI]
Hold up!
Why would they put me on the
front lines of this smackdown?
Aw, I should be
back with the others!
I never knew I could miss
my stupid classmates so much!
Doesn't feel right
being kept outta the action.
'Specially with
those two drafted.
[YAOYOROZU]
Honenuki and Komori from Class B
were also taken to the front.
Kaminari's Electrification.
Tokoyami's Dark Shadow.
Honenuki's Softening.
And Komori's Mushroom.
These are all Quirks
that can be used to subdue
large groups of enemies
quickly and from afar.
We have no idea what
this army is capable of.
As such, the pros are relying on
our brave classmates to take out
as many of our opponents
as possible from
the mission outset.
Sounds smart I guess,
but what if they end up
getting their butts kicked?
[HAGAKURE]
We gotta have faith!
Yeah, they're all great
heroes. Even Kaminari.
[EDGE SHOT] Every auxiliary
base has been surrounded.
No one will escape.
[FATGUM]
This is nuts.
I can't believe we have info
on the exact date and time
of their meeting.
[ENDEAVOR]
It was him, wasn't it?
He led us to these locations.
So where is he now?
[TSUKAUCHI]
That's classified.
[ENDEAVOR]
Hmph. Of course it is.
I've been preparing.
Just as you told me to.
[ENDEAVOR]
We're ready, Hawks.
[MAN 114A] I don't think I've
seen a single pro out today.
There's usually a couple
on patrol at least.
Look! There's one!
[SLIDIN' GO] Hey. Why am I
the only hero around?
Somethin's not right.
[DEATH ARMS] Guess we forgot
to tell you the big news.
You backstabbing
Liberation scumbag.
[TENYA] The infiltration
should begin shortly.
Ah, man!
Why the hell am I way
back here playing support?
I wanna be on the
front line, damn it!
Remember, Bakugo, we only
have provisional licenses.
You shut your face.
[TENYA]
Please, we need to remain calm!
This is a gigantic operation.
Coordination is going to be key.
The best thing we can do to help
is complete our assigned
duties successfully.
Right. The heroes
are moving in now.
That's our cue.
Start evacuating residents
block by block.
Top speed!
[HEROES]
Right!
[IZUKU]
It's really happening.
[NURSE 114B gasps]
What is this?
Heroes! Quick, follow me!
[ENDEAVOR]
Mirko. The morgue.
[MIRKO]
On it!
[MANDALAY] Everyone,
please leave the building!
This area may soon
become a battlefield.
[DOCTOR humming]
[DOCTOR]
Things are progressing nicely.
Tomura Shigaraki
will be complete
in a little over a month.
Ooh, I can hardly wait.
[ENDEAVOR]
Stop right there.
You're the creator of the Nomu.
And All For One's
right-hand man. Aren't you?
[gasping]
[ENDEAVOR]
You're the Devil's pawn.
And you will face justice.
[NATSUO]
Wait. Dad called?
[FUYUMI] Yeah. He said
there's a big work thing,
so we may not hear
from him for a bit.
Wow. I never imagined he'd think
to keep us in
the loop like that.
I hope this job doesn't
turn out like Kyushu did.
[ENDEAVOR]
Stop right there.
You're the creator of the Nomu.
And All For One's
right-hand man. Aren't you?
You're the Devil's pawn.
Impossible. How?
[ENDEAVOR]
And you will face justice.
[DOCTOR gasps]
[ENDEAVOR]
As expected.
His profile in the
official registry is wrong.
The instant you used Erasure
on this madman, he aged.
He has a Quirk.
That could answer
a big question.
How All For One has been
alive such a long time.
Super Regeneration
is also something
the more powerful Nomu have.
Not a common Quirk
by any measure.
Did you reproduce
an existing power,
or create it artificially?
Whatever the case,
All For One benefits from
the ability now, doesn't he?
[PRESENT MIC]
Impressive. Regeneration.
A Quirk that can heal.
Used correctly,
it becomes a cheat code
that lets you escape death.
So, why?!
Why are you using it
for evil, Doctor?
You could be saving countless
lives with that power!
But you've hurt so many.
Tell me what the hell
you did to my friend!
[NURSE 114AA]
Let him go.
Are you trying to hurt him?
[NURSE 114C] Why are you
heroes attacking the doctor?
Step away from the man.
[TSUKAUCHI] You have
to leave. It's dangerous.
[NURSE 114AA]
Explain this.
[NURSE 114C]
What's going on?
[TSUKAUCHI] Sorry. We'll
have to fill you in later.
While you decay before us,
our comrades are evacuating
everybody in the hospital.
We're more than prepared
to fight the Nomu here.
Although, it would be beneficial
to all parties if blood
was not spilled in these halls.
You've programmed those
creatures so they don't act
unless they receive instructions
from a specified individual.
Without commands,
they're nothing but corpses.
We figured that much out
by analyzing the
Nomu we've captured.
[SHIRAKUMO] I been thinkin',
when we graduate,
we should start a hero agency!
[AIZAWA]
Those you've toyed with,
and those who cared for them.
Do you know what they all say?
It's our turn to take
something away from you.
[OPERATOR 114A] Team Endeavor
has entered Jaku Hospital.
Garaki is in custody thanks
to Eraser Head's Quirk.
[OPERATOR 114AA]
Ninety-seven percent of patients
have been evacuated.
[OPERATOR 114B] Team Edge Shot
is closing in on the main base.
So far, there's no evidence
of enemy defenses.
[OPERATOR 114A] Update!
Mirko's found the secret area
in the morgue at Jaku Hospital.
Mercy. I'm begging you
to forgive me.
[gasps] Hey, ya there, Endeavor?
No, please.
[MIRKO]
We got company.
[gasps]
[DOCTOR laughs]
It seems Erasure doesn't destroy
a body created using
Double. Fascinating.
Were you really not
clever enough to guess
that I would employ
such an ability?
What fools you heroes are.
[ENDEAVOR]
Twice's Quirk? He was a copy.
[NOMU 114A growls]
You will burn!
[DOCTOR laughs] I suppose
they couldn't have known
that I've been so consumed
with my masterpiece,
Tomura Shigaraki,
that I left everything else in
the capable hands of my double.
Still. That ruse only
bought me a little time.
And I can't just walk away
from this hospital.
Do they have any idea
how much equipment and time
is needed to copy or
cultivate one simple Quirk?
Of course not.
I've spent incalculable hours
stockpiling these abilities.
I will not leave them behind.
My world is in this facility.
My entire life's work.
[DOCTOR] The blood and sweat
and fruitful days
I shared with All For One.
Every memory!
[NOMU growling, snarling]
Oh, this'll be fun!
[DOCTOR]
Playtime's over, Lil Johnny.
You must warp me and
Shigaraki out immediately!
[gasps]
[screams]
[MIRKO]
What's up, Doc?
I'm guessing you're
the real one.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The massive raid
has finally begun.
While Endeavor's team
is up top fighting the Nomu,
Mirko, the number-five hero,
runs into her own problems
as she chases Doctor Garaki
through the hospital's
underground facilities.
And she has no idea
what awaits her.
Next time, "Mirko,
the Number Five Hero."
Do your best, pros.
We're here to support you!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!