[screaming]
There you are!
[MIRKO]
I'm not done!
[yells]
[MIRKO]
Luna Arc!
[gasping]
Wait!
[screams]
[DOCTOR yelps]
[OPERATOR 114AA] Checking with
Team Endeavor to confirm
the status of Jaku
Hospital evacuations.
[OPERATOR 114BB] Some of
the heroes stationed there
are still combatting lower-level
Nomu on the ground floor.
[OPERATOR 114A]
Mirko's encountered multiple
talking-type Nomu underground.
Where Garaki's hiding.
[OPERATOR 114BB]
Endeavor, Crust, and a few other
team members are
rushing to support her.
The hospital evacuations
are completed.
The building is cleared.
The pros who've been
aiding in the process
will now join the fight.
[OPERATOR 114BB]
We have the upper hand.
The enemies who appeared
at the surface level
are falling rapidly.
So our only concerns
are the ones underground.
The talking Nomu are formidable.
There's a reason they're
referred to as "High Ends."
If they're anything like
the one who appeared in Kyushu,
then their Quirks
and physical ability
will surpass those
of a typical Nomu.
They're likely equipped
with fast-acting
self-regeneration as well.
The top two heroes
were in Kyushu,
and they were barely able
to defeat the monster
that attacked there.
You better call 'em off if
you know what's good for ya.
Ya hear me?
X-Less! Deal with Shigaraki!
Right!
[DOCTOR]
It's over.
[PRESENT MIC]
Can't you run yourself?
[DOCTOR] So many years.
So much planning.
And now, our dream is dead.
[X-LESS]
What was that machine?
Looks like those tubes
took the brunt of the attack.
I'll finish the job.
It's cold.
Try my Shoot Shield!
And this is with
its Quirks erased.
[HERO 115B]
What a tough bastard.
[AIZAWA] I can't blink
or look away from these Nomu.
But if Endeavor lures
the other one over here,
I can add it to the group.
[WOMAN]
I'll feel even more amazing
when you're bleeding
out, Number One!
[ENDEAVOR grunts]
[ENDEAVOR]
I can't leave Mirko alone!
What's the deal?
You need me to kick her?
No. Stay back.
Hell Spider!
[WOMAN]
More. C'mon. More!
You're mine!
[GRAN TORINO]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Just glad you're here.
You've done well.
How 'bout a hand?
Thanks for the backup!
[AIZAWA] We'll handle them.
Go help Endeavor further inside.
[RYUKYU]
On it.
Locklock. Backdraft.
You're with me!
[gasps] Another one.
[BACKDRAFT yells]
[WOMAN grunts]
[LOCKLOCK]
Deadbolt!
[WOMAN grunts]
It's able to heal
itself immediately.
[ENDEAVOR] Thanks for your help,
but, this one's mine.
Flashfire Fist. Jetburn!
[AIZAWA]
Is it over?
[PRESENT MIC]
Eraser! Got the doctor!
There's no way.
[yelps]
[SHIGARAKI]
Seriously. I'm freezing.
[FATGUM panting]
Is that...? Oh, no.
[FATGUM]
No, Tsukuyomi! Get back here!
What the heck are you doing?
It's not safe.
Hawks was in that blast!
He's in deep trouble.
[FATGUM]
You sure?
[TOKOYAMI]
I'll help him!
It's too dangerous to go alone!
[FATGUM]
I knew he was strong, but jeez.
Nobody's ever escaped
from my fat before,
much less without a struggle!
Right, that's far enough.
Hurry back to the rear guard.
Tell your classmates
we're doin' fine.
Hey! You forgot to pay
for your Fataxi ride!
See ya, Hawks.
At the end of the day,
your death means nothing!
[TOKOYAMI]
Hawks!
[DARK SHADOW]
Got him!
It's bad, Fumikage.
[TOKOYAMI]
How bad?
[DARK SHADOW]
His back is a nightmare!
His wings. They're gone!
[HAWKS] Weaknesses? Hm.
Well, that's a tough one.
My Achilles heel is
fire I guess.
Oh?
[HAWKS]
Of course.
My wings are tough
but flammable.
[DABI] You're a UA rookie.
You must be joking.
They dragged students out
to fill their ranks?
Well, take a good look.
Your pal here killed Twice.
Stabbed him in the back with
one of those big feathers.
Twice was just trying
to save his friends.
Well? What are you here to do?
Come to rescue him?
You still think
that's the right thing?
These pros you admire
play dirtier than me.
Better learn that now
before you waste your life
worshipping them.
[HAWKS]
Tokoyami.
[TOKOYAMI]
Villain.
I'm only concerned
about my mentor.
You're brainwashed.
[TOKOYAMI]
No room. I can't dodge much!
Sorry, Fumikage!
[TOKOYAMI]
The light of the flames
is forcing Dark
Shadow to retreat.
I need to get away quickly and
get Hawks medical attention.
He's still running his mouth.
[DABI] Think about it,
ya barbecued birds.
Who do you think really
needs rescuing.
Because it's not you.
[TOKOYAMI]
Your orders?
[HAWKS] He couldn't
finish me off before.
'Cause he was too busy talking.
He's doing the
same thing again.
But why?
His powers may have
some drawbacks.
So he's throwing us off
guard to stall for time.
The flames he just shot were a
lot weaker than the last ones.
Which means...
He can't fire in rapid
succession anymore.
We go. Now.
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark Shadow!
[DARK SHADOW]
Brace yourself!
No! Too weak.
Hawks! Hey. Are you okay?
[TOKOYAMI]
He's still breathing.
The impact must have
knocked him out.
My apologies.
[HERO 118A] Lady, block that
passage to the underground!
Roger!
This is good. There's
far less light here.
Try Dark Fallen Angel!
I thought it might
go down this way,
so I saved power by making
my last two shots weaker!
Say goodbye!
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark Shadow!
[FATGUM]
What is that?
Oh!
Booty incoming!
[MT. LADY]
Ouch.
[GETEN] You won't get in
Re-Destro's way any longer!
You'll suffer before you die.
You government dogs!
[LIBERATION ARMY 118A]
Geten, sir!
We've broken up their line!
Don't fight them on your own.
It's what they're counting on!
Coordinate and push
through together.
Ow. That ice bastard
didn't hold anything
back this time.
Oh, well. Maybe
I'll start early.
Your pal here killed Twice.
Stabbed him in the back with
one of those big feathers.
Twice was just trying
to save his friends.
These pros you admire
play dirtier than me.
Better learn that now
before you waste your life
worshipping them.
I know that you're
a good person, Hawks.
I believe in you! We all do.
Whatever you did was justified!
So don't you die!
Give me a battle update now!
And hurry up with my spare legs.
[LIBERATION ARMY 118B]
Re-Destro.
What is it?
[LIBERATION ARMY 118B]
He stood.
My master's scent. He has...
...awakened.
[BURNIN]
We're fighting to protect you,
but this whole neighborhood
could become a battlefield.
Please tell us if you know
anyone who has limited mobility.
Or if you haven't been able
to connect with somebody
who might not know
what's going on yet.
Everyone into the police vans.
Move your asses!
Thanks for your help, young man.
Here, have a chocolate bun.
Are you crazy?
I'm working here!
She's being nice.
You should take it.
If you're so
desperate for dessert,
you can eat it yourself!
Can't even be nice
to an old lady, huh?
I've got a printed manuscript
my publisher's waiting on!
Please don't let my
only copy get destroyed.
[TENYA]
We'll be certain to protect
your important
literary contribution!
Aw! So cute!
[KODA]
Thank you, friend.
Anima here. The fifth ward
has been cleared.
[HADO]
Hey, hey!
It looks like we'll be done
after this last group heads out.
[TENYA] We should check nursing
homes and apartment buildings
one more time.
It's the best way to be sure no
citizen has been left behind.
Remain calm. There's
no need to panic.
You can wait in the
shelter outside the city
until we know
it's safe to return.
[IZUKU] If anyone is feeling
sick, please don't hesitate to--
[FIRST WIELDER]
He's... coming.
[IZUKU]
That voice in my head.
Is that?
Midoriya. What's wrong?
Stop slacking off!
You're making us look weak!
[FIRST WIELDER]
Stop him.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
I knew it.
This voice is the first
wielder of One For All.
[IZUKU] It's been a long time
since I heard from him.
[FIRST WIELDER]
It will begin soon.
I don't have much time.
Deku, what's up?
[FIRST WIELDER] Freed from
the shackles of humanity,
his power grows.
[FIRST WIELDER]
A transcendent one approaches.
Stop him.
[GRAN TORINO]
This is Shigaraki's Decay.
But it's spreading
farther than before,
destroying things
he hasn't touched yet.
We'd been warned that
they were trying to improve
his Quirk somehow.
Is this the result?
Get out of here!
Don't touch the cracks!
You'll die!
The hospital.
[HEROES groan]
[panting]
[RYUKYU]
Climb on!
[RIBBY groans]
[HEROES yelling]
[gasps]
[DOCTOR]
We were defeated.
[DOCTOR] You insufferable heroes
put so much time and effort
into planning this
assault on our dream.
But look. A miracle
has occurred.
Something "Plus Ultra"
as you would say.
Tomura Shigaraki is awake.
All of your preparations
turned to dust
the moment he opened his eyes
and flexed his raw power.
We did it. Victory is ours!
Hey, not cool.
[TENYA gasps]
What?
This doesn't look good.
Quick! The civilians!
Make 'em move faster!
Endeavor! Sir. Are you there?
Everyone run!
Wait, Deku!
[IZUKU] One For All,
Full Cowling, 45 percent.
[IZUKU]
St. Louis Smash.
Air Force!
No effect.
This isn't some
normal shock wave!
The whole town
is falling apart.
[SHIGARAKI] As soon as all five
of my fingers touch your neck.
Your throat'll be the first
thing to disintegrate.
You'll be nothing
more than dust.
Shigaraki!
[TODOROKI]
Heaven-Piercing Ice Wall!
--It can't be.
--[BURNIN] Get back, everyone!
Hospital team, come in?
Someone respond dammit!
Endeavor!
[CITIZENS yelp]
[BURNIN]
Ryukyu? Mirko!
Crust!
Whoever's there,
please talk to me!
Crap. Why aren't they answering?
[BURNIN]
Hello? Can you hear me?
Endeavor! Ryukyu!
Someone! Anyone!
Tell us what's going on!
[POLICE OFFICIAL 118B] Why are
the feeds disappearing?
[OPERATOR 114AA] I don't know.
No one's responding to us.
[OPERATOR 114A] The source of
the disruption appears to be
coming from Jaku Hospital.
[OPERATOR 114BB]
Given what we saw,
we're projecting a large
number of casualties.
I want any information
you can get.
[OPERATOR 114AA]
Yes, sir!
This is unacceptable.
What in the world is going on?
[SHIGARAKI]
Damn.
Most of these look
too damaged to use.
[SHIGARAKI] A strange thing
happened to Compress
after he was shot with this.
He couldn't use his
Quirk for a while.
So I'd like to know
what this is,
and what you're planning
to do with it.
Tell me.
[CHISAKI] I'll break the
natural order of things.
And after all the pain of
getting the Doc to make more.
Overhaul wouldn't be happy
to see this outcome.
What's that?
[ALL FOR ONE]
Listen.
Hear me.
[SHIGARAKI]
My head. This pain.
[SHIGARAKI] I'll be fine, small
price for the upgrade to Decay.
Now then.
It seems like the situation's
gotten out of hand.
They were supposed
to wait for me to wake.
To me, Machia.
Bring the others with you.
[SHIGARAKI]
From this moment on,
I'll destroy everything.
[roars]
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
Tomura Shigaraki is out
of suspended animation
and obliterating
everything in sight.
And that's not our only problem.
Gigantomachia is on the move.
Endeavor takes
Shigaraki on alone,
knowing he must be defeated.
With the heroes scattered
and at a disadvantage,
is there any hope for success?
Next time: "Encounter, Part 2."
I know who Shigaraki is after.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!