[MIDNIGHT] If this monster
stampedes through Jaku City,
it will be an
unthinkable disaster!
[MR. COMPRESS]
A gift!
[MIDNIGHT]
The League's on his back?
Damn it!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Don't underestimate the heroes!
[MIDNIGHT]
Creaty, can you hear me?
[YAOYOROZU]
Ms. Midnight?
[MIDNIGHT] You know
what's coming, don't you?
Yes.
No one in our ranks can stop
that thing with force.
We need you.
[YAOYOROZU] But that--
What are you saying, ma'am?
[MIDNIGHT]
It's up to you. Be strong!
What's going on?
Ms. Midnight,
are you still there?
[YAOYOROZU]
Oh, Ms. Midnight, what do I do?
[ASHIDO gasps]
We can't just stand here!
Everybody, be prepare to move!
It's been a year since
we enrolled at UA High.
And in that brief
period of time,
our teachers taught us
that a real hero
never turns their back
or runs from an enemy.
[YAOYOROZU]
Together. As one.
We'll take down this villain.
[YAOYOROZU]
We'll stand our ground
and end the villain's
rampage here.
From Tentacole's observations,
we know he stands
about 25 meters tall.
What's more, the blue
flames that shot
from his back earlier
looked like the ones
used by the man who
attacked Mr. Aizawa
at our summer training camp.
That means, it's likely
the League is with him.
They may be on his back.
According to Ms. Midnight,
the only way
we'll be able to subdue this
giant is to put him to sleep.
Normally, this tranquilizer
would be injected,
but given his size,
I estimate we'd need to pump
at least 30 liters in him.
Considering how quickly
he seems able to move,
an injection is impossible,
so I'm proposing we
administer the drug orally.
These jars contain
undiluted doses
that should be enough
knock him out.
So we get one in his mouth
and that'll do it?
The big guy goes down
for a long sleep.
[YAOYOROZU] Mm-hm.
We'll set up a trap for him.
And when he goes down,
we move in.
[HONENUKI] Okay, if the reports
of his size are accurate,
this should be enough
mud to snare him.
Poor Ms. Midnight.
She's still alive, right?
There's no way she'd let
those losers kill her!
[ASHIDO]
I'm sure she's fine.
She'll be teaching us
cool stuff before ya know it.
[growling, panting]
[YAOYOROZU] I could conserve
some energy just in case.
No, this isn't
the time to hold back.
This is it, everybody, be ready!
He's right in front of me!
This moron won't stop!
Kamui! Wake up!
You gotta let him go now!
We should do something
about this mammoth woman.
[MR. COMPRESS] I'm afraid we're
not up to such a performance.
[roars]
Yikes!
[TOKAGE]
He's on course!
Almost there!
[KAMUI WOODS grunts]
[MT. LADY grunts]
We've got him!
Pull! Give it all ya got!
I hope you can forgive us
for outnumbering you.
[SERO]
You kiddin' me?
We're the ones
at a disadvantage!
If he stands up, I doubt
we'll get him back down!
[SATO]
C'mon, ugly. Say, "Ah!"
[MR. COMPRESS] It's a whole
troupe of UA students!
[SHOJI]
Five more villains.
They won't get away.
[MR. COMPRESS]
My word!
[JIRO groans]
[TOGA]
Huh?
[SPINNER]
[YANAGI]
Let's do this, Kaminari!
Try to be gentle with me.
[KAMINARI]
With these pointers,
I can shoot with
everything I've got.
[gasps]
[MR. COMPRESS]
Close call. The kid is powerful.
I used every shot I had left,
but he's no longer a threat.
[YANAGI]
Oh, my gosh.
Kaminari is out, guys!
Harder! Open his mouth!
That's it! Attack!
[TOKAGE]
Just one.
[MINETA]
Go to sleep!
[SERO] We can't let this
monster get to the city!
[HEROES yelp]
[ASHIDO]
Hold on!
[DABI] Gigantomachia.
Gotta love your Quirk
that converts morale
into physical energy.
And the one that keeps
you from feeling pain.
And there's more, of course.
According to the good doctor,
they chose powers that let
you stay on the battlefield
as long as possible.
Which makes you a perfectly
engineered bodyguard.
You do know your
arm is smoking, right?
It's fine.
[SERO]
Dang that's hot.
The fire is blocking us.
No shadows.
My poor spores are burning up!
[KENDO] Oh, no! He's
crawling outta the trap!
[MINETA]
Crap! What're we supposed to do?
Now!
I placed bombs beneath the mud.
That's our plan B.
If we bury him deeper,
maybe we'll take him!
Hah! Machia here is the king
of burrowing underground.
He's like a big mole!
[MR. COMPRESS] If he goes
under, it's curtains for us!
Huh?
[MR. COMPRESS]
He was probably ordered
to bring us along with him.
In truth, we're likely
holding him back.
He could be in a bit of trouble.
That's just great.
Hey! Is this really time
for chitchat? Look!
League members!
[HERO 121B] The rest of your
friends have been captured!
[HERO 121C]
Accept your fate and give up!
[MT. LADY screams]
[MT. LADY]
The kids, they were trying
to get something in his mouth.
Don't fight!
That's it. Open wide!
[MT. LADY] Did they come up
with a way to stop him?
They're damn smart.
[MT. LADY] You got this.
I believe in you, baby heroes!
[SERO]
Is everyone okay?
[TETSUTETSU] The flames're
spreading too fast.
[KIRISHIMA]
That was some insane firepower.
[YANAGI] Kaminari. I'm sorry
I didn't move you.
Are you okay?
Less talk. So soft.
[SERO]
We were blown way back,
so we're out of
immediate danger.
But some of our classmates are
still trapped inside with him.
[ASHIDO]
Max viscosity. Acidman!
With this gooey armor, the heat
won't be a problem for me!
I got this!
[MINETA] Poor Ms. Midnight.
She's still alive, right?
[ASHIDO] You gotta
do everything you can do!
Even if you feel frozen with
fear, you fight through it!
Take a nap!
[GIGANTOMACHIA]
Must get to Master.
That's it. Open wide!
[GIGANTOMACHIA]
These annoying flies
are costing me too much time.
A mistake in judgment.
Yes, I will not let them
swarm me again.
Everything is for my master.
[ASHIDO]
That voice.
[ASHIDO gasps]
[ASHIDO]
You guys! That was so scary!
[STUDENT 72AA]
Thank you! You saved us!
[STUDENT 72BB]
If you hadn't stopped him,
he would've squashed
us for sure!
Kirishima!
Regroup with the others!
Mudman's gonna put out
the fire by sinking it.
I can't. He needs help!
Yeah, the dumb punk.
He won't burn like me,
but I bet it was still hot.
Ugh! I can't believe
he rushed in faster!
[GIGANTOMACHIA]
The insects are handled.
Comrades. Hold on tightly.
[KIRISHIMA]
Think again. I am Red Riot!
I won't let more
blood be spilled!
This ends here!
[KIRISHIMA]
That was my jar, but...
[gasps]
[KIRISHIMA]
Ashido.
I'll channel your chivalrous
spirit and use your dose!
[GIGANTOMACHIA groans]
[SHOJI]
Red Riot got it in his mouth!
He pulled it off!
That's our boy!
The more he moves around,
the faster the
trank is gonna work.
'Kay, Majestic?
Nice job, Momo!
I knew you had this.
You're an impressive
young woman!
Now, heroes!
We can't rely on the work study
students to do all the work!
The insignificant
pests keep coming.
I won't waste
any more time on them.
[MAJESTIC]
Hold on!
No way.
Seriously?
That is crazy.
How many powers does he have?
[KATSUKI]
You're kidding.
The bastard is still alive?
It's over, Tomura Shigaraki.
No matter how powerful
you get, we will not allow
you to continue with this
pointless destruction.
You people. You heroes.
In order to save strangers
you don't know,
you hurt those who love you.
That's what my father said.
Pointless? I have a mission.
Always have.
Stay sharp. Watch him.
We need to find some
shelter somewhere!
Right, Manual. You just
keep him hydrated.
[SHIGARAKI]
Self-described heroes.
You pretend to embody
all that's good.
Ah, he's on his feet again.
[AIZAWA]
Quickly. The finishing blow.
[SHIGARAKI]
Your kind is always the same,
every generation.
You pretend you don't see
those you can't protect
and cover up the pain you cause.
Always thinking of
yourselves as righteous.
[WOMAN 112A] I'm sure
a hero or a police officer
will be here soon.
This world has grown so rotten,
it's infested with maggots.
[SHIGARAKI]
It happened little by little,
but your mistakes added up.
The coddled trash got
used to being protected.
While you took
advantage of these
so-called victims
for your own profit.
Everything that I've ever known,
everything in this world
you built rejected me.
But not now. I'm the one
who's rejecting you.
That is why I destroy.
That is why I keep
gaining power.
Heh. Simple, isn't it?
And yet you just
don't understand.
The fact that you
don't get it is why
we have heroes and villains.
[ENDEAVOR growls]
Thanks for the break,
I needed a little breather!
You're knocking at
death's door, aren't you?
That's good.
[ENDEAVOR]
How is he still moving?
[GRAN TORINO] Endeavor's
firepower has grown weaker.
Must've used too many big moves.
And he's wearing down, as well.
[GRAN TORINO] Surpassing
his limits to fight...
[GRAN TORINO]
...without Quirks.
[GRAN TORINO groans]
[ENDEAVOR growls]
Gran Torino!
[GRAN TORINO]
What a terrible face, Shimura!
[NANA] I doctored the records
so he's not linked to me.
If that man finds out
Kotaro exists,
he'll use my kid against us.
So, I no longer have a son.
[NANA] I'm not a mother
anymore, Sorahiko.
I never was.
[SHIGARAKI]
You heroes.
In order to save strangers
you don't know,
you hurt those who love you.
That's what my father said.
[GRAN TORINO] Shimura.
Did we make the right choice?
[IZUKU screams]
Deku, no!
[SHIGARAKI]
I'm over this.
[IZUKU]
Go.
[KATSUKI]
Faster!
[RYUKYU grunts]
Ryukyu!
[RYUKYU groans]
[SHIGARAKI]
It's getting hard to move.
Shigaraki! You're
the one person...
...I can't forgive.
And I'll grant no
forgiveness to anybody.
[groans]
[IZUKU]
Turn this anger into power.
Keep him bound, Blackwhip!
[IZUKU]
Shigaraki's faster than me!
I need to make sure
he doesn't escape!
Yes, that's it. Hold. Hold!
[ENDEAVOR] Muster your strength
for one more attack!
That should bring
an end to this.
[SHIGARAKI]
Muster your strength.
[SHIGARAKI] These fools still
don't know I have this.
A Quirk deleter.
[IZUKU]
But how?
That's the thing that
stole Togata's Quirk. No!
I can't let him fire it!
One For All 100 percent!
Wyoming Smash!
[SHIGARAKI]
This is it.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Act as your heart desires.
Don't be held back by them.
What's inside of you is more
important than anything else.
[SHIGARAKI]
Right now.
I feel as though I can overcome
anything standing in my way.
I just have to keep
running toward my dream
and remember where I came from.
Eraser!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
Gran Torino and Mr. Aizawa
have been horribly injured.
Despite our setbacks,
we haven't lost hope yet.
We can't afford to.
Come on, Izuku Midoriya!
You have to use the new power
you got from One For All!
Next time:
"Katsuki Bakugo: Rising."
The feelings lurking deep inside
of Kacchan are about to explode!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!