A Quirk deleter!
[AIZAWA gasps]
[AIZAWA]
Thanks for the warning, Ryukyu.
Now I won't hesitate.
[AIZAWA]
I'll be rational.
And do what I must.
[SHIGARAKI]
Clean cut.
You're such a badass, Eraser.
But for a second there,
you were distracted.
[yells]
[ENDEAVOR grunts]
[IZUKU grunts]
[SHIGARAKI]
This game is coming to an end!
Is he okay?
[SHIGARAKI] The kid who was
following them earlier.
Please, sir. Stay alive.
[SHIGARAKI]
What's your plan to stop me now?
Fight all you want.
You're just delaying
the inevitable.
[TENYA] Midoriya and Bakugo
aren't responding.
And now I can't reach Todoroki!
He said he'd bring the
House Arrest Boys back!
Ugh! What in the world
is going on out there?
That's not good.
I wonder if someone's
Quirk is causing
a communications blackout
on the battlefield.
You guys.
I think we should go
after them, just in case.
[CITIZEN 122A]
Whoa, are you seeing the news?
This country's
falling apart. Jeez.
[TENYA]
May I listen?
Yeah, sure. One sec.
[TV NEWSCASTER 31A]
If you're in one of these areas,
you must evacuate immediately.
I repeat, a giant villain
is currently moving north
from Mt. Gunga in Wakayama.
His destination appears
to be Jaku City in Kyoto.
The predicted path
of his rampage
will take him through Mino City,
Kakun City, Nebaro City,
Hando City, Mosu City, Horisu
City, Kuraudo City, Karida City,
Karamari City, Suinara City...
[TENYA]
That's so many civilians.
[OCHACO] Almost every hero
in Japan is on this mission.
There's nobody left to stop him.
[PASSENGERS yelp]
Shoji. Can you see the pros?
[SHOJI]
No. We're too far away.
It's likely some
of them are injured.
Or worse.
Tokoyami. You better be okay.
[CROWD yelling]
[TOKOYAMI]
What was that?
[YAOYOROZU]
I can't believe it.
We had little time.
But we prepared meticulously,
and Kirishima managed
to administer a dose.
[YAOYOROZU] And yet, the real
reason we're here right now...
[YAOYOROZU]
The reason we're even alive...
[YAOYOROZU] ...is because
they didn't consider us
to be actual threats.
Just insects.
Majestic! You're here!
[MAJESTIC] You did the
right thing today, kids.
Your decisions were sound.
No matter what happens now,
you should be proud
of that fact!
[YAOYOROZU gasps]
[KOMORI] Hey. Why hasn't
the giant fallen asleep?
Does this mean it didn't work?
Are we sure that Majestic
was right about us?
Should we have
tried something else?
And what about the heroes
and their big raid?
Was this mission something
they should've done?
This is... This is,
like, really bad.
Do you think we were
doomed to fail
from the very beginning?
[GIGANTOMACHIA]
I'm coming to you, Master!
Ah! A delightful development!
You had us at the hospital.
It was quite the
impressive showing.
Please, allow me to commend
your splendid display of force.
But your fate has been sealed.
Shigaraki is awake.
And the tables have forever
turned against you!
[DOCTOR cackles]
[DOCTOR]
Gigantomachia is a calamity
that lives and dies
only for his master!
In fact, my Nomu soldiers
were modeled after him!
A king needs pawns, of course.
A powerful army.
Now that Machia's on the move,
this world will see
true horror at last.
The end is near!
Shigaraki will destroy
this hero-saturated society!
[ENDEAVOR]
Shoto!
It took me a while because
I stopped to help Ryukyu.
You cool off. The ice
should help you rally.
[growls]
[MANUAL] Elevate his leg!
I'll make a torniquet.
If I can just untangle this.
Dangit, where's the end?
Deku.
[LOCKLOCK]
Run!
Not a chance.
That's better. Now die.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Look at him.
[SHIGARAKI]
Wh-What's happening?
I don't understand.
Earlier, I couldn't use my
Quirks, so of course my body
suffered as I pushed past
my physical limits.
But now?
Super Recovery should be
working full force again.
So how the hell
do I have injuries?
Hold on. What is today's date?
[SHIGARAKI] Has it been
four full months yet?
His body isn't healing?
[IZUKU] Gran Torino said All For
One's roster of stolen Quirks
was transplanted into Shigaraki.
[IZUKU]
He's like me.
He's the vessel for
a huge amount of power.
But his body's not strong
enough to handle it.
[SHIGARAKI]
Whatever.
So I'm not
regenerating instantly.
I'll just rely on Decay.
Huh?
[IZUKU]
One For All.
The Seventh User's Quirk. Float!
[LOCKLOCK]
We're flying?
I know this power.
It's Shimura's.
[IZUKU]
If Shigaraki touches the ground,
he could cause another
wave of mass destruction.
I'll put a stop to you
up here, in the air.
Using every ability
I've got in my arsenal!
I won't let you
escape from here!
[IZUKU] My control's
not the best. But...
I can get them outta the way.
[IZUKU]
Please take care of the injured.
Shoto. You help out with triage.
I'm on it.
This is pathetic.
The number-one hero should
be fighting him, not this kid!
You moron!
You should be getting far away
from that guy while you can!
We can't bank
on Erasure anymore.
Who else is still
able to face off
against him in the air?
Go!
[SHIGARAKI]
You like it up here so much?
Then after I steal One For All,
I'll send your ass
all the way up to heaven,
and the rest of your little
friends will be right behind.
You won't lay a finger
on my friends!
You've hurt them enough!
[SERO] You want us to
help with your training?
That's...
Awesome!
=What should we do?
I know you're busy,
so thank you for assisting.
I need your advice
on how to control
this new power
that I manifested.
Y'mean Blackwhip? You're
gettin' the hang of it.
Also, what's with the hair?
About that.
Kacchan's been amazing
and agreed to let me
chase after him
as a form of training, which I
have not done very well at.
I thought you might have
some guidance for me
given your abilities.
My ultimate goal is to be able
to capture super-fast targets.
But why did he explode you?
Jeez, Bakugo. Can't you
be nice for a change?
[KATSUKI]
Deku's the one who wanted it
to be like a real battle!
Well, you can
count on me to help!
Although, I'm pretty
new at using my wires.
Isn't Mr. Aizawa the master
of capture techniques?
Well, Young Uraraka,
I'd like you to teach him
how to control his body
when he brakes in midair.
But he doesn't stop,
he's always jumping around.
Yeah, he's a hopper for sure.
[ALL MIGHT]
As his power increases,
he's gonna be able to
stay in the air longer.
[OCHACO]
Ooh!
[ALL MIGHT] He needs to be able
to move around more freely
when his feet aren't
on the ground.
And as for your
homeroom teacher,
I'm afraid he's
busy at the moment.
I've been studying the moves
you and Mr. Aizawa use.
I'm pretty sure
I have them memorized.
But what would really help
is if you can tell me
how they make your body feel.
[OCHACO] Try to imagine that
you're swimming through the air.
Use your arms
and legs to balance.
Know what I mean?
Like swimming.
Yeah, that makes sense.
And then I can use
Air Force for propulsion!
[OCHACO]
Look at you! Nice moves!
Why don't you add in
some Blackwhip training
while you're up there?
[IZUKU]
Right!
[KATSUKI]
Well, he's getting it.
[ALL MIGHT]
Float is a power that allows him
to stop in midair.
It's basically
like Zero Gravity.
If he can train for my
master's Quirk in advance,
maybe it won't
activate randomly.
He can unlock it
when it's necessary.
No surprises.
[KATSUKI]
Hey.
What's up?
[KATSUKI]
I don't think you'll be able
to hide the truth much longer.
[KATSUKI]
This is totally different
from when he just
had super strength.
People will ask questions.
Which is why we
won't let them see
any new Quirks from now on.
The trick will be making sure
he doesn't go out of control.
Like with Blackwhip.
That night we spoke,
you seemed to understand
the situation.
Before we share
this with others,
we have to think
about it carefully.
What are the ramifications?
Would we be putting
others at risk?
The villains of this world
aren't the only ones
who seek power.
[KATSUKI]
Deku has complete faith in you.
But I still have some questions.
Why didn't you tell him
more about the fourth user?
We know how numbers
five-through-seven died,
but you avoided him. Why?
Before, when I asked you
the same question,
something kept you from
being honest with us.
So talk.
Did you realize something
you wanted to hide?
Is One For All a--
I can't. I'm not certain yet.
And I won't tell him something
I don't know for sure.
Frankly,
I'm concerned about
Young Midoria.
Just like you are.
The thing is, he doesn't
think about himself.
He never has.
Even now, with everything he can
do, that still hasn't changed.
It always freaked me out.
That's why I pushed him away.
But as a kid, I didn't
recognize my own weakness.
So I bullied him.
Which is the reason
you're always so quick
to help him train,
so you can make up for
your actions in the past.
Like a penance.
I don't think he feels
you have anything
to atone for, though.
Before, when I said
you were like Endeavor,
I meant that
you've both changed.
He only has hindsight.
My weakened state
was his catalyst.
I'm sure you'll
have another chance
to talk things over
with Young Midoriya.
Though I'm not a great role
model in that department.
[IZUKU]
Smash!
I'm punching at 100 percent
and he's still smiling.
Although his body's not
healing as fast as it was!
He's taking damage!
[IZUKU]
My left arm's a mess after
the two full-power
shots I got in.
But One For All has been
cultivated over generations
specifically to
defeat All For One!
Which means I'm the one
who has to stop Shigaraki.
Right here. Right now!
[IZUKU] Using every ounce
of strength in my body!
No matter what happens to me!
[DOCTOR 46A] If you sustain
this type of injury,
even just two or
three more times,
I don't think you'll be able
to move your arms anymore.
[IZUKU]
Three hits, one after the other!
Detroit Smash!
[SHIGARAKI groans]
[IZUKU]
Wyoming Smash!
[SHIGARAKI] I'm getting hurt
faster than I can heal.
He'll beat me if I
don't focus on defense.
St. Louis Smash!
[SHIGARAKI] If the heroes
hadn't pushed me
past my limit earlier...
No. Even if my body
wasn't incomplete.
This boy... This power...
You are holding me back
from my dream.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Texas Smash!
[SHIGARAKI]
What do I have?
Which Quirk can stop him?
Come on.
[MANUAL]
He's seriously just a student?
[KATSUKI] Yeah, but if the idiot
keeps this up, he's dead.
[MANUAL]
Huh?
He's using his legs and
Air Force to maneuver around.
Controlling multiple Quirks
at the same time.
Every skill he's ever
learned is in play here.
He's hellbent on
keeping Shigaraki
from touching the ground again.
But his power attacks
didn't stop the bastard.
So now it's an issue of who
can hold out the longest.
Deku's body is busted,
he won't be able to outlast
someone who can regenerate.
Soon, his Quirk is gonna
be stolen from him,
and he'll be nothing but dust.
Todoroki. You done
with the first aid?
Yes. What do you nee--
[KATSUKI]
Shut up and grab ahold a' me!
Endeavor, save your strength
and let me get the
three of us into the air!
You. Keep your old man cool.
We're gonna need him
to pull this off.
You want me to use
maximum firepower.
To end this fight
with a single blast.
I can do that.
They're just children.
[TODOROKI] You take care
of things down here.
[LOCKLOCK] No, I can't
think of 'em that way.
After all,
I recognized Deku as a hero
a long time ago.
You got it. Leave 'em to me!
Strike when Blackwhip
is fully stretched out.
Once I'm in range,
you two beat it, quickly.
The blast is deadly.
[TODOROKI]
Hang in there, Midoriya.
[ALL MIGHT]
I'm not certain yet.
And I won't tell him something
I don't know for sure.
[KATSUKI]
This passed-on ability
originally came
from All For One.
He's got control over
multiple Quirks, too.
I see it now.
You're basically
the same as him.
Even if Deku's Quirk is
some kinda cursed power.
[KATSUKI]
It's still our only hope!
[IZUKU]
You can call me Deku.
But I'm not the same helpless,
defenseless kid anymore!
You hear me? I've changed.
[IZUKU] From now on,
Deku is the name of a hero!
[groans]
[KATSUKI]
Now!
--What?
--[ENDEAVOR] Back, Deku!
You!
Plus Ultra. Prominence Burn!
[SHIGARAKI screaming]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Tomura. Lend me your body.
[BOTH]
Endeavor!
Why won't you die?
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
Little Brother.
[KATSUKI]
In that moment...
...I didn't plan or think.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
[KATSUKI]
My body just moved on its own.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
After Kacchan is impaled,
I lose myself to anger
and go after the king
of villains even harder.
But, things change
in an instant.
And I find myself standing off
against Tomura Shigaraki
and All For One in the world of
One For All and its past users.
Next time: "The Ones Within Us."
Who could have foreseen this?
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!