[BEST JEANIST]
Faster!
I want to be there
within five minutes.
[PILOT 124A]
I'm trying, but it's not like
I'm Hawks or Mirko!
I'm pushing this thing
to the brink already.
You shouldn't even be standing!
We're happy you're
back in the field,
but you're still recovering.
[BEST JEANIST]
Don't change the subject.
What matters is
that countless lives
are being unraveled as we speak.
[PILOT 124A] Please take
care of yourself, too.
[IZUKU]
It wasn't stolen.
But...
Shigaraki. Please, stay down.
Bakugo! Midoriya! Endeavor!
[IZUKU]
Is Kacchan...?
[TODOROKI]
He's still alive!
Stay calm. I'll patch you up.
[thud]
[ALL FOR ONE]
No, Tomura. You must leave.
Don't do this.
Shut up.
I don't take orders from you.
Dammit!
Found 'em!
[TENYA] A gigantic villain
is headed this way!
We've already informed the
heroes fighting Nomu nearby.
You're here, too, Iida?
[TODOROKI] Get Midoriya
and the others to safety!
[TENYA] This is... No wonder
you guys never returned!
I need to stay here.
I can't leave!
Shigaraki wants my Quirk.
He'll follow me if I run off.
You go, Iida.
Take Kacchan and Endeavor.
He's not healing near
as fast as he was.
He must be weakening!
Hado, help me.
Let's put pressure on him!
Got it!
[SHIGARAKI] More maggots keep
wriggling to the surface.
[OCHACO]
Okay, fine.
What I wanna do is save as
many people as I possibly can!
And you're in
my way, Himiko Toga!
So I'm gonna have
to stop you right now!
Sorry. But I'm way stronger
than I was last time.
[OCHACO]
I need to touch her
without letting her
steal my blood.
And I can't take too long!
What do I do?
[TOGA] Ochaco. When I think
about someone I love,
it makes me want to
become that person.
To live inside of their skin.
I wanna drain their blood so
badly, it makes my chest hurt.
That's just who I am.
I can't help it.
But not everyone is like that.
It's so hard to be me.
[TOGA] The other day,
there was this meanie reporter
who called me a poor,
lost child and tried to kill me
because she said my
cravings weren't "normal."
That's why I used
your blood and your Quirk
to drop her and her friends
from way, way up high.
[gasps]
It turns out, if I love
a person, I can become them
and use their power!
You have no idea
how happy that makes me.
Stop it!
[OCHACO]
You're happy?
I would never feel good
about hurting another person.
What are you even
trying to get at?
What's this?
You must've dropped it, friend.
That's mine!
[TOGA]
Something precious?
Give it back!
[TOGA]
Jin was precious to me, too.
Like a brother.
Y'know, we're the
same, you and me.
Because I'm pretty
sure you've got
a massive crush on Izuku, too.
Huh?
[TOGA] I put it together
a long time ago.
Hold on. Does this
thingie belong to him?
Aw, see, we really are twinsies!
[OCHACO] I can't spend
any more time on her!
If I attack head on,
she'll dodge, so...
Zero Satellites!
[gasps]
[TOGA]
Earlier, when she fell.
[OCHACO]
Focus.
I have to shut out
every other feeling.
Heh. Great.
Neither of us has
to hold back anymore!
When I was little, everyone
said I had to change.
But that didn't help at all.
Ignoring your urges
makes them worse!
Enough!
If you threaten people
and do what you want,
then you have to answer
for your actions!
There's my answer.
--[gasps]
--[TOGA] Thanks for the chat.
Goodbye.
[OCHACO]
Froppy!
Why is Himiko Toga here?
[TOGA]
Tsu.
I've told you.
You can't call me that.
[thudding]
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
[BOTH gasp]
It's a sneak attack!
Back to back.
We'll cover each other!
Don't worry.
She ran away.
[TOGA] Ochaco. The girl
I share a crush with.
I thought maybe we could bond
over romantic stuff, but...
Those were tears.
[TOGA] I'm coming back home.
I'm not confused anymore.
Master!
[TODOROKI, HADO gasp]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Ah! Perfect timing, Machia.
Between the blows
from One For All
and Endeavor's Flashfire blast,
Tomura's body could fail
at any moment, I'm afraid.
Which is why Rivet Stab is
extending from his spinal cord.
It's auto-tracking should reduce
the burden on his mind and body.
What a precarious situation
we find ourselves in.
We must give Machia
the order to retreat.
[TODOROKI]
We can't fight that behemoth
and Shigaraki at the same time!
Best to take the injured one
off the board first.
[ALL FOR ONE]
What fearsome Quirks they have.
Surge, Half-Cold Half-Hot.
This body is crumbling
and they aren't letting up!
One hundred percent.
Spiraling flood. Nejire Flood!
Flashfire Fist. Jet Kindling!
[SHIGARAKI screams]
Incoming!
[TENYA]
Oh, no. Nejire! Shoto!
[KATSUKI] Put me down,
ya four-eyed robot.
[TENYA]
You're awake?
[KATSUKI]
Put me down!
[TENYA] I can't!
Your organs were punctured.
[KATSUKI]
I need a complete victory.
Master. I'm here.
What is your next order?
I will do as you command!
Shigaraki! What happened?
You look terrible.
Shoto. You good?
Yeah.
[ENDEAVOR]
Sorry, Hawks.
It's my fault this guy
started moving.
I must defeat him.
No matter what horrors he
turns out to be capable of.
But one of my lungs collapsed.
I'm not sure I can
damage him much
when every breath
I take is hell.
So instead, just
watch what I do.
[ENDEAVOR] I can't give up.
I promised them.
As this country's top hero,
I have to keep fighting.
[DABI]
Hey, there you are!
From all the way up here,
everyone looks like
tiny little ants.
Ah. Shoto's with you.
Perfect.
[ENDEAVOR]
He brought the League?
Dabi!
[DABI]
Hey now, don't be rude.
You're acting like
we've never met.
Call me Toya.
After all, it's the name
you and Mom gave me.
Our live coverage continues.
The giant vill--
[NEWSCASTER 124B]
We're having s...
...echnical issues.
New reports suggest that
the radio interference
in Jaku City has
been getting worse.
Our correspondent can't
say exactly what--
[DABI] Sorry to interrupt.
My name is Toya Todoroki.
The number-one hero
is my father.
[DABI] Yeah, I know, my face
is pretty disgusting now.
But it's still surprising my own
family didn't recognize me.
It's honestly kinda crappy.
Or maybe it's just
depressing, you know?
Huh?
I thought you three were close.
So I figure you would have
told them all about Toya.
It's not exactly an easy
subject to broach.
[IZUKU]
Wait, he's...?
[DABI] Yes, the so-called
villain sitting in front of you
is Endeavor's oldest son.
At the time of this recording,
I've killed more than
30 innocent people.
Are you confused?
Lemme just explain how
I turned out like this.
I'll start at the beginning.
Endeavor has always
obsessively yearned for power.
Much to his despair,
he could never surpass
All Might on his own.
So he forced my mother
to marry him
in an attempt to create an
heir with the perfect Quirk.
I was bred for my
father's selfish dream.
But it didn't matter.
I was a failure.
It wasn't long before
he gave up on me,
and I was cast aside
and forgotten.
[DABI]
I didn't forget our family.
I've been watching you from
the shadows this entire time.
You know, out of
everyone in the world,
you should be beyond
reproach, number one.
And so a pre-recorded
video of my life story
is currently streaming on
every device in the country.
What an unexpected twist.
[DABI]
Oh, man. I didn't expect this.
I'm starting to have fun!
I wondered how I
could make you suffer.
How I could ruin your life.
Ever since I burned up,
it's all I've thought about.
As a kid, I didn't
know why I existed.
I'd cling to Natsu,
bawling my eyes out.
But you didn't know
that, did you?
At first, when I realized
your little puppet Shoto
was complete,
I figured I'd kill him.
But then, you unexpectedly
became the number-one hero!
Who'd woulda guessed, huh?
I was suddenly so invested
in your happiness.
Can you believe, in Kyushu,
I was actually afraid
you were going to die?
I led Starservant and
Ending to your doorstep.
Did they make you
feel like a big shot?
Must've been a heavy burden
to achieve your
dream after so long.
[DABI] But you were soothed by
public admiration, weren't you?
Is that why you finally decided
to try to bond
with your children?
Just keep looking
towards the future
and you could be a better man?
What? Nothing to say?
Well, allow me.
The past never dies.
You will reap
everything you've sown.
Enji Todoroki.
Let's fall together.
Come and dance with me
in hell, won't you?
Well? Speak up, Dad!
[ENDEAVOR gasps]
[ENDEAVOR]
I remember a cold and windy day.
The air was dry.
Toya and I often trained
on Sekoto Peak.
And that's where he
was consumed by fire.
The flames raged at over
2,000 degrees Celsius.
We were told that his bones
must have turned to ash,
scattered far and wide
in the updraft.
No body was found.
We only recovered a small
fragment of his jawbone.
What's happened to your hair?
[DABI]
Huh?
It's turning white.
Nuh-uh! I'm not old!
[ENDEAVOR]
Did you dye it?
No, I'd never do that!
Forget about my hair!
It's time for you to teach me
an ultimate move!
[ENDEAVOR] I could see
that Toya's firepower
held greater potential than
my own, but he wasn't born
with my wife's Frost Quirk.
This posed a problem
since he couldn't keep
himself from overheating.
Despite that. I wanted
to raise him to be a hero.
At the same time,
I continued to hope for a child
who could harness
both fire and ice.
My wife wanted Toya
to have siblings as well.
That's how our family grew.
Fuyumi only had
Rei's Frost power.
Another Todoroki
who wasn't my ideal.
Though at the time,
I was fine with that.
Toya continued to show more
raw talent than I ever had.
So I placed my hopes and
ambitions on his shoulders.
[DABI]
Agh, Too hot!
[ENDEAVOR] I was certain
that you could find the success
I always wanted.
[ENDEAVOR] My frustration
and jealousy, my disgrace.
I thought you could
smash through
every one of my failures.
And be the best of the best.
My son is dead.
These are disgusting lies.
Oh, I'm very much alive.
You're just a broken man who
refuses to accept the truth.
How could you not
recognize your child?
Is it because fire
Quirks are so common,
there's nothing special
about someone who has one?
[MR. COMPRESS]
Wow, Dabi, I had no idea.
Yeah, I wonder what
he's playing at here.
He hid this from us,
too? What for?
C'mon, boss. You gotta wake up!
We're here! Machia needs orders!
Pull it together!
[MR. COMPRESS] Our little troupe
has dramatic lineages.
[DABI] If you doubt me,
I'll happily give you some blood
or a chunk of skin.
You can do a DNA test.
Obviously, I've already done one
and I released the
results to the public.
This here is an
official paternity test.
I used the blood Endeavor
left in Kyushu as my sample.
He's a 99.99% match
as my father.
You might think I fabricated
this, but all I can do
is say what I know to be true.
Endeavor continued to
make my mother have kids.
Their fourth child is
someone you probably know.
With Shoto, he finally
found his hybrid.
Not that that stopped my father
from abusing the child.
I saw it over and over again.
Endeavor is not a man who
cares about other people
or their well-being.
He's self-righteous
and weak-willed.
Consumed by ego.
Do you really believe someone
like that has the right
--to call himself a hero?
--[TAMEDA] It's not true.
Who would believe
a stunt like this?
These lies won't make us
lose faith in number one!
Does this bad guy think
we're stupid or something?
[DABI] Those working with
Endeavor are just as bad.
Take the number two pro, Hawks.
[gasps]
[DABI] He didn't hesitate
to drive his blade
through the back of
a despondent opponent.
Hawks murdered my friend
right in front of me.
It was hastily edited, but the
end result was quite powerful.
You should be impressed!
Stellar work.
Those cameras of yours
got some great shots,
so I'm glad the rest of
the world got to see 'em.
Endeavor! Allow me
to give you a gift.
I did some digging on
that bastard spy of yours.
[ENDEAVOR]
Hawks!
[DABI]
In order to get us to trust him,
Hawks murdered one of his peers.
He killed the number-three hero.
Best Jeanist is dead.
Since violence is essential
to a pro's life,
Hawks is comfortable
with blood on his hands.
It's something he was
exposed to early on.
His father committed serial
robberies and murders.
That's why Hawks kept his past
and his real name hidden.
Kinda funny that his old man
was put away by mine.
I don't know if that's
fate, or if Endeavor
naturally attracts damaged
people to his side.
But I do know
he must be stopped.
He can't cover up
his appalling behavior
by calling it "justice."
He really claims to be a hero?
He's tricking the whole world!
The thing I want you
to realize today
is that that these heroes
only protect themselves.
You're being used.
These disgusting people
treat you as tools
for their own self-affirmation!
Aw, "Look Boy." People
are gonna believe him.
He's telling the story first.
So there's no evidence
against it yet.
Even if everyone knows
that guy's a villain,
it doesn't matter.
I... Sorry. I've gotta bail.
I don't want it to be true, man.
But look at how much damage
the heroes've done lately.
I just don't know.
The people watching this
are gonna freak out.
He's already won!
Thank you for living long
enough to see this day.
Endeavor!
[panting]
[ENDEAVOR]
I looked for you everywhere.
Dammit. He's fast.
You ready, Dad?
[ENDEAVOR]
I believed you were alive!
Protect Midoriya and Bakugo!
Hado and I will hold him off!
Snap out of it! Protect them!
Please! We'll deal
with this later!
Flashfire Fist.
[gasps]
Ha! Prominence...
[DABI]
What the.
[BEST JEANIST]
Sorry I'm late!
As of this moment,
Best Jeanist is back.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
Dabi's shocking revelations
throw the heroes into confusion.
But Best Jeanist arrives
at the last second
to turn the tide of battle.
His appearance has a profound
impact on my classmate.
It's not over yet.
Our hopes and futures
are knotted together.
Next time, "Threads of Hope."
Kacchan's hero name
is finally revealed.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!