[IZUKU] It's time for you
and the rest of our class
to know everything.
So I'm writing letters
to try and explain.
My Quirk is a power passed
on to me from All Might.
It's a gift that Shigaraki and
All For One want to steal.
So they're coming after me.
The last thing I want to do
is put others in danger,
and it's dangerous to be
near me, so I'm leaving UA.
Being in the hero course
and meeting everyone in Class A
has made me happier than
I could've ever imagined.
Thank you.
And goodbye.
You idiot.
[OCHACO]
In April,
Deku left our hero academy.
[OCHACO]
The fight between heroes
and the Paranormal Liberation
Front was a disaster.
Japan is still reeling.
As if that weren't bad
enough, after the battle,
tons of criminals were set free
from prisons around the country.
Heroes were once the
most admired people
in our society, but now...
We've become lawless.
[IZUKU]
Looks like a huge villain.
[RADIO VOICE 132A]
Urgent request from
the Daina Police department.
A monstrous jailbreaker showed
up in the south ward yesterday.
Please search for any civilians
remaining in the area.
This shouldn't take long.
Most residents got
outta here early.
[PRESENT MIC] Ketsubutsu Academy
hero course third year,
Yo Shindo.
Hero name: Grand.
Might be hard to
convince the holdouts
that it's still a good
idea to evacuate.
[PRESENT MIC] Ketsubutsu Academy
hero course third year,
Tatami Nakagame.
Hero name: Turtle Neck.
Yeah, probably gonna be
a bunch of stubborn people
who think they're better off
protecting themselves.
Which is why...
I'll channel Ms. Joke.
If we keep it light,
they'll see things our way.
[NAKAGAME]
You're delusional.
[SHINDO]
Whatever, let's go!
Word is there's a buncha people
in the Taguchi Building.
[NAKAGAME]
Yo! Not so fast!
[CITIZEN 132A]
First police, then heroes.
Now they're sending children
here for us, huh?
Get lost. Run along home.
[SHINDO]
It's dangerous to stay here.
Your stockpiles of
food and supplies
are gonna run out before
long, and then what?
We've got plenty of resources
at Ketsubutsu Academy, though.
Come with us,
and we'll hook you up
with everything you might need.
[CITIZEN 132A] Heh. You expect
us to believe you'll keep us
all safe when
villains attack there?
You're painting a target
on that school.
Didn't need your help when
I kicked thieving punks
outta my store n'
I don't need it now.
The pros've shown
they're useless.
We're taking matters in our own
hands to protect this town.
We can't trust you
with our lives.
[SHINDO] Look, I'm sure you're
capable of holding off
some petty criminals who're
after money or whatever.
But, guys. The jailbreakers
and Nomu are different.
We got reports just yesterday
that a gang was causing chaos
around here. Not thieves.
Their only purpose
was to spread violence.
Monsters like that
could take down a pro.
You don't wanna face them.
They're barely even human.
I said...
We don't put faith
in heroes anymore,
and you're not stupid enough
to think you can force us
to leave our homes, right? Kid?
All I'm saying is that we've
had a lot more training.
Let us make your lives easier.
We fell for that before
and look how great the
country's doing today.
[CITIZEN 132B] Do you know what
the heroes around here did
when things started looking bad?
They ran off with their tails
between their legs.
[CITIZEN 132C]
It's happening everywhere.
The east and west wards
have been abandoned.
We gave pros nothing but support
and this is how they repay us?
I'm tired of talking.
Go back to where you came from.
And tell your bosses
we're not goin' anywhere.
Well, that didn't go as planned.
Total bomb. You suck at this.
They just need a
little persuasion.
If I used Vibrate,
I could demolish that
building in seconds.
Agh! We should
just drag 'em out.
It's for their own good.
Tone it down.
[phone rings]
[SHINDO] Oh. At least
phones are still working.
It's Makabe.
[MAKABE]
Get outta there! He's coming!
Itejiro saw him
with his own eyes.
He's heading your way, fast.
Run! We won't make it
in time to help you!
Incoming.
Whoa, he's big!
[MUSCULAR]
Let's go. I'm ready to play.
It's just you two wimps?
Damn, I'm gonna need more.
Don't you have some
powerful friends?
Tatami, call Ms. Joke and
tell her we need backup now!
Then evac civilians.
What will you do?
Crush this guy.
Being free feels so good.
[CITIZEN 132A]
That scumbag wont' tear up
our town up anymore!
No way! This guy's
out for blood.
He's a wanted murderer!
You don't stand a chance! Run!
Move. We don't take
orders from you.
I'm trying to keep
you from dying!
[rumbling]
Not good.
Are you kidding?
I was hoping you'd
make this worthwhile.
Don't they always say that,
if you see one hero,
there are ten more nearby?
Ah! Whaddaya know. I found 'em.
[SHINDO grunts]
S'not gonna work!
I've got 12,000 layers of
muscle fiber acting as armor.
A little massage isn't gonna
break through to my actual body.
Is that so?
[SHINDO] If I let loose
at maximum power,
I won't be able to move
for a while. But...
[SHINDO] Sometimes a man's gotta
do what a man's gotta do.
The most important
thing a hero can have
when the world is going
to hell around them
is fortitude to keep fighting!
I'm gonna shake your brain
right outta your head.
[MUSCULAR] In that case,
I guess it's not a bad idea.
[NAKAGAME]
Watch out, Yo!
C'mon, let's save the boy!
[MUSCULAR] You feel that?
It's a blood frenzy!
[IZUKU]
Muscular.
No wonder the Fourth user's
Danger Sense kept going off.
I recognize that voice.
It's you. Midoriya. Right?
I'd never forget you!
In fact I've missed ya!
I keep running into
these benchwarmers
who don't quench my
thirst for blood.
But you will!
[MUSCULAR laughs]
Yes. This is what I need.
Don't run off. We'll
have a real battle.
And so we're clear, revenge
has nothing to do with this.
I just want to experience
that rush again.
You got me addicted to it
when we threw down last time.
I can't get enough
of that feeling.
[IZUKU] Why not jump
straight to the roof?
[yells]
Let's not hold anything back.
Show me your blood!
[CITIZEN 132A]
What's going on?
This smoke! I can't see!
[IZUKU]
There you are. Perfect.
Please take care of him.
Is he okay? Yo,
you're such an idiot.
[IZUKU]
Sorry I didn't get here sooner.
You should take him
to a doctor quick.
And abandon the building;
it's not safe.
I'll make sure nothing
else is damaged.
Got it.
[NAKAGAME] Hard to make him
out through the smoke.
But, there's something
familiar about his voice.
Who is he?
[IZUKU]
Was that overboard?
[EN] Yeah. Too much
of my Smokescreen.
You exceeded the
controllable limit.
[IZUKU]
Okay.
[EN] Careful not to let someone
use your own attack against you.
That's how you lose.
[IZUKU]
Right.
[EN]
Because of One For All's growth,
things've really
gotten out of control.
After eight generations,
it's a lot to harness.
And of course,
since you're the latest
on the chain of wielders,
that means it's going to be
hardest on you,
the ninth person to use it.
I'd recommend you
pull back a bit.
Don't forget that
most of our Quirks
aren't ultimate
moves on their own.
You're putting too much focus
on these individual powers
instead of the whole.
Think of Quirks as tools.
You can use them to build
a path that leads to victory.
[IZUKU]
Muscular.
The man who can withstand
a Smash at 100 percent.
I haven't forgotten you, either.
[IZUKU]
Seventh. Float!
Sixth. Smokescreen.
I'll use it to confuse him.
Think, Izuku.
Remember how your first
battle with him went.
Where the hell are you going?
[IZUKU] Fourth. Predict his
moves with Danger Sense.
Fifth. Blackwhip!
[MUSCULAR]
Enough playing games.
[IZUKU] Tell me where Shigaraki
and All For One are hiding.
I know they broke you out.
Who cares? They told me
I should go wild
and do whatever I want,
which is how live anyway.
This talking is so boring.
Like your dumb tricks.
Let's cut to the good stuff.
I live for the adrenaline.
I want a full-power brawl
like we had that night.
No holding back!
[IZUKU] Why do you chase
after such extremes?
Cause I don't wanna have any
regrets when I finally die.
[IZUKU] Oh, yeah?
And what would you regret?
Not enjoying every thrill
life has to offer to the max.
[IZUKU] You don't think there
was another path for you,
Goto Imasuji?
Nope! Not a chance.
What? You trying
empathize with me?
Waste someone else's
time with that BS.
My heart beats with a thirst
for blood and battle!
Nothing else in this
whole wide world matters.
[IZUKU] I never found out why
they ended up becoming villains.
What caused all their anger.
If I had known, maybe things
would've been different.
Shigaraki killed
so many innocent people.
He hurt those I care about.
I wish there was a way
of reasoning with you.
But it sounds like
this is inevitable.
Give me your full
power, Midoriya!
[IZUKU]
If we have to fight,
at least I'll learn
something about him.
When did you turn
into a boring guy
who just stands around?
[IZUKU] There are spaces
between your muscles.
Whenever they've
reached their limits,
they peel back and disappear.
[IZUKU]
You want a head-on fight,
but you tried to
trap me at first.
Is it because you know
something's wrong
with your power?
You didn't realize how strong
Shindo's Vibrate truly is.
You think you're so clever?
[IZUKU]
One For All, Full Cowling.
Forty-five percent impact.
[IZUKU]
Detroit Smash!
This is my full power at work.
[TOTEKI]
Where are Shindo and Nakagame?
[PRESENT MIC] Ketsubutsu Academy
hero course third year,
Itejiro Toteki.
Hero name: Boomerang Man.
Ketsubutsu Academy
hero course third year,
Shikkui Makabe.
Hero name: Mr. Smith.
Hey. Up there!
Huh? That's the villain!
I didn't even get a chance
to say "thank you."
[CITIZEN 132A] Here. Use this.
It'll make carrying him easier.
[CITIZEN 132B]
Get the car!
[CITIZEN 132C]
And, up!
You're helping us?
It's not like we want anyone
to get hurt or anything.
I figure the least we can
do now is hear you out.
[SHINDO] That guy.
He was at the licensing exam.
But today, he fought like
a different person.
Was it really the same kid?
[ARMORED POLICE OFFICER 132A]
Freeze! What do you want?
[IZUKU]
You have any spare iron maidens?
[ARMORED POLICE OFFICER 132A]
Maidens? Wait, that's...
One of the escapees!
[IZUKU]
Please restrain him.
[ARMORED POLICE OFFICER 132A]
Ah! Hold on!
[IZUKU] Danger sense has calmed
down for the time being.
[IZUKU]
All Might. I'm heading back.
Are you injured?
[IZUKU]
No. I'm good.
Your arms and legs?
[IZUKU] Fine thanks
to the Mid-Gauntlets.
As far as compression
support items go,
they're super high quality.
Thanks again.
Glad you thought to order
them from the US
before travel and shipping
restrictions were imposed.
They're prototypes, but they
should boost your endurance.
Best of all, the support
affects your entire body.
They won't withstand your power
if you're at 100
percent, though.
Try not to go overboard
before your rematch, okay?
[IZUKU]
No matter what happens to me!
I won't.
[ALL MIGHT]
I am here in your phone!
[IZUKU] Whoa. The Silver Age
version of his ringtone.
It's me, hey.
[HAWKS]
All Might. Good to hear you.
Just wanted to check in.
How is Midoriya?
[ALL MIGHT]
Fine. He's here with me now.
[IZUKU]
Gotta go. Sorry.
[ALL MIGHT]
Or at least, he was.
Heh. Let me guess.
He ran off again.
He doesn't want any people
around if he gets attacked.
Pretty brave, actually.
He's chosen to
isolate and prepare,
not the worst idea in the world.
But if the people who stormed
Tartarus come at him
in full force,
it's over for all of us.
Like Midoriya said,
our best chance
is to track them down instead.
I know it's a hard
position for you,
but I'm glad you're there
to support him.
[DOCTOR 132A]
Let's see.
From what I understand, you
survived some serious injuries
in the past and were told
that further trauma
could cost you the
use of your arms.
Previously your injuries
were caused
by small explosions
inside your body.
Fortunately, this time, that
power surfaced and escaped.
Your scans suggest that
you used your Quirk
to reinforce your physique
from the inside out,
which is why your limbs
weren't completely
shattered like before.
In short, the injuries
are similar,
but your frame was more
prepared for them this time.
Nevertheless, your body
won't keep bouncing back.
You still need to be careful.
[IZUKU'S MOM] Will you explain
what's going on? Please?
[ALL MIGHT] Hope you're
sure about this, kid.
So, this power of his.
He can control it because
he was born Quirkless.
And now there are some bad
people who're after my son.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
What's going to happen to him?
We're still figuring out
the logistics,
but he should be
safe at the school.
[IZUKU]
I'm not going back to UA.
What do you mean?
Oh, kid.
[ALL MIGHT]
I thought he might say that.
No matter where I go,
Shigaraki will know my location.
He must be licking his wounds,
or else he'd be here
storming the hospital.
I don't want anyone
else to get hurt.
Especially not because of me.
And If the League is able
to reach their full power,
things will be even worse
than they are now.
That cannot happen.
I have to stop Shigaraki
and All For One.
You're here because you
couldn't beat those villains!
Don't throw your life away!
[IZUKU]
I'll get stronger.
[IZUKU'S MOM] I have loved
watching you grow into a hero.
But hearing this. It's too much.
When I was a kid,
you once smiled
and thanked me for saving you.
[IZUKU]
That made me so happy.
Oh, help me!
I am here!
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Wow! Thank you, All Might.
Hey, wait. Izuku?
It was my boy the whole time?
[IZUKU]
That's why... I have to go now.
Don't you worry.
I'll always come home to you.
[ALL MIGHT]
From now on.
Will you allow me to devote
myself to Young Izuku?
I beg you.
I swear to protect your son.
Even if it costs me my life.
[ALL MIGHT]
I could try to stop you.
But I know your mind is made up.
Well, even if you
don't want my help.
I won't let you do this
alone, understand?
[BEST JEANIST]
He's leaving UA?
No. I get it.
This works in our favor.
He's the only one with a
chance of pinning down
Shigaraki's whereabouts.
In fact, I already planned to
design our operation around him.
Right. We'll follow at an
appropriate distance.
Gotta be all cool even
on the phone, huh?
[GRAN TORINO] You don't say.
That's Shimura for you.
Even in the afterlife,
she's crying over our choices.
[GRAN TORINO]
I should've killed him
on the battlefield when
I had the chance.
I apologize.
Don't be too stubborn.
Sometimes you have to kill a
person in order to save them.
Be sure to remember that.
Whatever you decide to do,
you make damn sure
you settle the score with
the League of Villains.
[IZUKU]
Hawks. Best Jeanist.
Endeavor and All Might.
We're teaming up to end this.
[IZUKU] Together we'll keep
anyone else from getting hurt.
[IZUKU]
We have to stop All For One.
I have to.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
As I try to figure out where
Shigaraki could be hiding,
I take on every escaped prisoner
who crosses my path.
But a new obstacle awaits me,
a deadly assassin in
All For One's employ.
Her name is Lady Nagant.
Next time, "Hired Gun."
This sniper has
a complicated past
and now she's got me
in her crosshairs.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!