[OPERATOR 119A]
Endeavor, come in.
Respond! Hello?
Endeavor! Are you there?
We still haven't heard
from any of the heroes
who were fighting
in Jaku Hospital!
[POLICE OFFICIAL 118B] Do we
know the extent of the damage?
[OPERATOR 114A] The effects
of the blast extended
in every direction
from the hospital.
and the resulting dust cloud
is blocking our visuals.
[SHIGARAKI]
To me, Machia.
Bring the others with you.
[SHIGARAKI]
From this moment on,
I'll destroy everything.
[FATGUM panting]
Hawks was in that blast!
He's in deep trouble.
[FATGUM]
You sure?
[TOKOYAMI]
I'll help him!
[FATGUM]
Tokoyami.
[LIBERATION ARMY groans]
Whoa, what is that?
[gasps]
[FATGUM]
Oh! Booty incoming!
[MT. LADY]
Ouch.
[FATGUM]
That came outta nowhere.
[TOKOYAMI]
Fatgum!
[FATGUM]
Tsukuyomi!
[FATGUM] There's a medic
team with the rear guard!
Head there!
[TOKOYAMI]
Roger!
[YOROI MUSHA grunts]
[LIBERATION ARMY groans]
Are you okay, Cementos?
Yeah. I've got this. Stand back.
[GETEN] You state-sponsored
pawns love to provoke us.
But I won't let you get
in Re-Destro's way!
[GETEN]
What is this?
That's fine. I'll attack
from above instead.
[gasps]
[MT. LADY]
So it was you.
Do you have any idea
how much that hurt?
Mt. Lady. For you!
[MT. LADY]
Thanks! I like my ice crushed!
Take that! And that!
She's opening a path!
Arrest as many as you can!
Oh, hey.
I thought you were dealing
with Toga and Compress.
[gasps]
[COMPRESS] My, my, my.
This is a catastrophe.
[DABI]
Hey.
[COMPRESS]
Dabi!
What, are you hiding out here?
[COMPRESS] Where have you
been? You're a lieutenant!
Yeah, and so are you.
This whole "commanding troops"
thing isn't working for me.
Where is everybody else?
[COMPRESS sighs] Twice helped us
but I believe he's dead.
Toga insisted on fighting
despite my objections.
I've never seen her lose
composure like this before.
[HERO 119F groans]
[TOGA]
Being alive is hard.
[TOGA] I just wanna
make the world easier.
[TOGA] It should be
full of things I love.
Nothing else.
[LIBERATION ARMY 119A grunts]
[TOGA]
And you're in the way, heroes.
[COMPRESS]
Machia's moving
You know what that means.
The boss is awake.
[SHIGARAKI]
Until Machia gets here, I can--
[ALL FOR ONE]
One For All.
[SHIGARAKI]
What was that voice?
Halt, Shigaraki!
[SHIGARAKI] Heh. The number-one
hero right after I wake up?
[ENDEAVOR]
Hell's Curtain!
A vast wave of hellfire!
There's no escape!
[ENDEAVOR] Can't let him
take a single step forward.
He's too dangerous.
I have to take him
out of commission.
Jetbur--
[ENDEAVOR] Only someone
with heat resistance
could overcome Hell's Curtain.
No. He's just
regenerating instantly.
[ENDEAVOR]
The same way they did.
This is Endeavor,
does anybody copy?
I'm here!
[ENDEAVOR]
I'm fighting Shigaraki
where the hospital stood.
If there's anyone who can move
without touching the ground,
form a perimeter.
Hands to yourself.
[SHIGARAKI] It's almost as
though I've had my master's
stockpiled Quirks since
the day I was born.
I feel like I'm omnipotent.
[DOCTOR]
For four long months,
you'll suffer
indescribable pain.
If you can endure it,
the world will rest
in the palm of your hand.
So why do I feel unsatisfied?
[ALL FOR ONE]
One For All.
[DOCTOR] He wanted to acquire
that Quirk so desperately.
But in the end, it was the
one power that eluded him.
[SHIGARAKI] Something deep
inside is urging me to act.
[ENDEAVOR] As I feared,
he has multiple Quirks.
Like the High Ends!
[SHIGARAKI]
I must have it.
Where is One For All?
[ENDEAVOR]
One For All?
Wait, what's a One For All?
Endeavor are you there!
[RAGDOLL]
So frustrating.
If I still had Search,
I could be out helping
the heroes right now.
[PRESENT MIC]
Search!
The Quirk All For One
stole from Ragdoll.
It shows the location
and weaknesses
of someone you've seen!
[SHIGARAKI]
One For All.
I've gotta get over there
and help him out!
You kids should
fall back and evacuate.
Burnin, wait!
[BURNIN] Listen to the police
and keep your distance!
[SHIGARAKI]
One For All.
Ah, there you are.
Shigaraki is heading
straight toward the evacuees.
The battle zone is expanding.
Clear the area
surrounding the city!
[BOY 119A] Wait for me!
You're too fast!
Hurry up!
Every single second
counts right now!
[HERO 119AA]
Funkman. Wake up.
You can't be dead!
[HERO 119I]
Mourn him later!
[HERO 119J] If that destruction
wave comes again we're dead!
Keep the line moving!
[BOY 119A]
Where's my mom?
[KATSUKI]
You can't tell them your secret.
The heroes would try
to split their forces
to protect you
and the civilians.
Yeah, I know!
[KATSUKI] The only thing
they know right now
is that he's after
"One For All."
It's not a lot to go on.
It's a hero's job
to protect the people.
So you only have one choice.
I need to make sure that
the evacuees can be protected.
Yeah, which means you gotta
get outta here quick.
Hey! Where are you two going?
Uh. I left something!
I'll be right back!
[IZUKU]
There's debris everywhere
and good amount of
distance between us.
He probably can't see me.
Unless, he has some other
way of tracking me down.
[IZUKU]
Come on. This way!
[SHIGARAKI]
There.
[IZUKU] Deku here. Sorry for
using a private line.
It's highly possible that
I'm the one Shigaraki's after.
What are you talking about?
I might be able to lure him
to an unpopulated area!
Please keep this channel open!
[KATSUKI]
I'll crush the scumbag!
[IZUKU]
Follow me. I'm the one you want!
[ENDEAVOR] Why would Shigaraki
be coming after you?
Explain yourself now!
[IZUKU]
It'll have to wait.
I'm too far away
to have eyes on him,
especially given all
the dust in the air.
If it looks like he's
changing directions,
can you give me a heads up?
I don't like being in the dark.
[SHIGARAKI]
I can access the data
this Quirk's previous
user accumulated.
And they saw One For All right
before their power was stolen.
Lucky me.
He's down!
[ENDEAVOR] New course!
He's moving to the southwest!
Yeah. Pretty much
what I expected!
I can buy you more time.
You evacuate the civilians!
[ENDEAVOR]
What?!
[SHIGARAKI]
Their communicators are a pain.
I'm sure I can get rid of them.
Okay, heads up!
Shigaraki is now
heading southwest!
He has super
regeneration somehow!
Nobody underestimate him.
[ENDEAVOR]
Targeting Midoriya? Why?
I don't understand,
but he did take the bait.
I have to catch up.
I won't leave him on his own.
Right! He said
he's following us.
I heard!
You're the one
who's not listening!
That creep has leveled-up
into a final boss!
You better make damn sure
you don't get caught.
Um, Kacchan, why are
you following me?
Y'wanna die?
[IZUKU]
What?
[KATSUKI] There's no time
to explain the situation
so I'm the only one who
gets what's happening!
I had to come!
Wow! Thank you!
[KATSUKI] You idiot.
I am not doing it for you.
Don't think you're the main
character on the battlefield.
I just owe that piece a' crap
villain a beat down.
[SHIGARAKI] Will you join
the League of Villains?
Oh! You must've been scared.
But you stayed strong.
[KATSUKI]
It's my fault All Might
had to hang up his
costume and retire.
You can act as bait.
And once he gets close, I'll
have revenge for what happened!
I will defeat him.
And I'll prove that I'm a hero.
Just don't let your guard down
or get in my way, got it?
[IZUKU]
Yeah, I got it.
[KATSUKI] Deku can
consistently use Full Cowling
at 30 percent without
hurting himself.
In order to keep his body
from getting wrecked,
he only brings it up to 45
percent at the moment of impact.
His time at Endeavor's agency.
All Might's special training.
Every time Deku improves,
I have to grit my teeth
and try to match him.
That's not a problem at
this 30-percent speed.
But as he gets stronger...
Well, I can do the
exact same thing
and keep getting better myself.
I'll go higher than
even you, chosen one.
I won't lose to a damn nerd.
And there's no way I'm gonna
give up when I'm still behind.
[SHIGARAKI]
Let's see. This should work.
[gasps]
[SHIGARAKI] The Air Blast from
earlier, plus Radio Waves.
Sorry, Number One.
I don't have time
to play with you.
[ENDEAVOR groans]
Why is my comm on the fritz?
[OPERATOR 114AA]
Emergency!
Our audio's down. We've lost
contact with Team Endeavor.
What's happening over there?
[OPERATOR 114AA] I don't know.
Some new interference!
[KATSUKI]
Hey. Deku!
You feel that?
[IZUKU]
Yeah. I feel it.
I've felt it before.
[gasps]
[SHIGARAKI]
This echo in my brain.
I know what it wants.
[IZUKU]
It's the same omen of death
I had that summer
night in Camino.
Izuku Midoriya.
Give me One For All.
Gran Torino!
After I heard "One For All"
over the radio,
I was afraid he would
track you down.
Were you two planning to
fight him by yourselves?
Nonsense.
Shigaraki's Decay destroys
everything it touches!
The smallest piece of debris
could kill you on contact.
He's not someone you can
handle on your own.
Well, we can try.
[GRAN TORINO] Don't forget,
the pro heroes aren't dead yet!
[GRAN TORINO] Those of us
left will handle him.
[AIZAWA] Gran Torino just
grabbed two people.
Looked like Midoriya and Bakugo?
Why are they here?
Was he chasing after them?
[AIZAWA]
Crust, our number-six hero.
Your sacrifice saved me.
[AIZAWA]
While I draw breath...
My Quirk...
My life...
...has one purpose.
To take you down.
I will not let you lay
a finger on my students!
Wow.
You're still pretty cool,
aren't you, Eraser Head?
Kill everyone you see
on the surface.
Now, Kido!
[KIDO] Figured you might
need an adjustment.
[PRESENT MIC]
Endeavor's sidekick, Kido!
Quirk: Traject.
He can change a
moving object's path!
[KIDO]
Go!
Guess we should've found
a hiding spot first.
[MANUAL]
But we couldn't risk him
touching the ground
again, right?
[AIZAWA]
Thank you, Manual.
No problem. If I go overboard,
the water's gonna force you
to blink, I'm afraid.
We'll work together.
[ENDEAVOR] Tomura Shigaraki.
This is the end for you.
[SHIGARAKI]
Uh-oh.
[ENDEAVOR roars]
That hurt!
[AIZAWA]
I haven't released Erasure yet.
[ENDEAVOR]
He should be powerless!
Was that his physical strength?
And the jump from before.
He can fly through the air with
a simple swing of his arms.
I've seen abilities like this.
[DOCTOR] Even though
he's got tremendous power,
he's still not as strong as All
Might in his prime, I'm afraid.
I focused on altering his brain
instead of
overpowering his body.
What kinda monstrosity
did you create?
[AIZAWA]
He has a bioengineered physique.
It's almost like
he's the perfect Nomu.
[MANUAL]
Strength is great,
but the number one and number
ten heroes can take him.
You're an atrocity!
[ENDEAVOR] His movements are
getting even faster.
That was a nice warmup.
[GRAN TORINO]
You should be safe here.
His power. Erasure took
it just now, right?
[GRAN TORINO] Yes.
He's weakened, if only slightly.
What, did you get tired?
Why are we still
so close to him?
I trust Gran Torino.
[GRAN TORINO] So, Bakugo
knows your secret, right?
Toshinori told me.
We can't go much further.
Shigaraki's moving faster than
anyone could have expected.
Few will be able to follow him.
And now that our comms
have gone down,
if he chases you too far out,
no one will be able to catch up.
You stopped him temporarily.
Got him away from the civilians
and put him within
Eraser's field of vision.
Those are quite
the accomplishments.
I'll go back and keep
your teacher on the move.
Wait, are you saying we're
just supposed to hide?
[GRAN TORINO]
All For One's Quirks
were transplanted
into Shigaraki.
That's what Present Mic
said, anyway.
So that means that he can...
"All For One."
It allowed its user to
take Quirks from others.
Then the user could
keep the Quirks for himself
or give them to someone else.
I can't imagine a worse scenario
than him stealing One For All.
Who could defeat him then?
Right now,
he's just one person.
If we can't stop him,
then what's the point
of there being so many
heroes in this world?
Are those--?
[NOMU DOG 119A growls]
[NOMU 119A screeches]
[IZUKU]
No!
[KATSUKI]
Where did they come from?
The whole lab should've crumbled
to dust in that Decay wave!
So how are there Nomu here?
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
Shigaraki is
approaching full power
and his goal is to steal
One For All from me.
Meanwhile, in order
to stop Gigantomachia,
pros and students
alike are thrown
into a deadly defensive battle.
The fighting continues
with no end in sight.
Next time: "Disaster Walker."
Do Class A and
Class B have enough
combined strength to succeed?
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!