[IZUKU]
Our futures are intertwined.
[TSUKAUCHI]
We expect substantial resistance
from the villains, their
supporters, and the Nomu,
but we cannot wait any longer.
If we don't act now,
they will prevail.
[yelping]
[ENDEAVOR]
You're the Devil's pawn.
And you will face justice.
[KAMINARI]
Aw, yeah.
That's one scary leader
rendered powerless.
[EDGE SHOT]
Ninpo: Thousand Sheet Pierce!
The last thing I wanna
do right now is fight.
Just come quietly.
[MIRKO]
Luna Arc!
[YAOYOROZU]
Together. As one.
We'll take down this villain.
[KIRISHIMA] I won't let
more blood be spilled!
This ends here!
[RYUKYU grunts]
A Quirk deleter!
[IZUKU] Using every ounce
of strength in my body!
No matter what happens to me!
Now!
Plus Ultra. Prominence Burn!
[IZUKU]
Our hopes and dreams.
Our deepest desires.
[IZUKU]
Every piece of us is connected.
[DABI] But I do know
he must be stopped.
He can't cover up
his appalling behavior
by calling it "justice."
He really claims to be a hero?
He's tricking the whole world!
[BEST JEANIST] Exploiting family
issues on a global stage.
This reveal was
carefully designed.
You've been biding your time
in the shadows, Dabi.
Waiting for the public's
faith in heroes to waver.
[BEST JEANIST] But despite
this widespread damage,
you haven't won!
Flashfire Fist.
[gasps]
Hah! Prominence...
[DABI]
What the--?
[BEST JEANIST]
Sorry I'm late!
[BEST JEANIST] As of this
moment, Best Jeanist is back.
[PRESENT MIC]
Best Jeanist.
His Quirk: Fiber Master.
He can manipulate
any fiber at will.
[GIGANTOMACHIA grunts]
[BEST JEANIST]
Together we will spin...
...the threads of hope!
[BEST JEANIST]
Apologies.
It was my intention
to arrive far earlier.
Best Jeanist.
Where'd he come from?
--[coughs]
--[TENYA] Bakugo!
And they said he was missing.
Shows what they know.
There's no way.
You're s'posed to be dead!
The corpse I saw was real!
So how the hell are you alive?
[BEST JEANIST] Greed has caused
your plans to fall apart,
like cheap denim.
Okay, fine, you're not dead.
That doesn't make
my past any less real.
Right? You saw it yourself.
Shoto!
[MR. COMPRESS gasps]
This can't be happening.
He was able to trap Machia?
Too tight. My bones're
gonna snap!
[MR. COMPRESS grunts]
What an unexpected
and most unwelcome cameo.
[SPINNER] I guess this
means Machia's stamina
isn't infinite after all.
[SPINNER] Once he got to
Shigaraki and stopped running,
it looked like he
was out of breath.
He did what he was told,
then basically shut down.
You follow commands perfectly.
That's what you do.
So that's what the problem is.
You need instructions
to go all out.
Shigaraki, enough sleeping.
You're still alive
in there, right?
You better start talking.
Tell Machia what to do!
You haven't lived
your dream yet.
There's so much left
in this world to destroy.
Sorry, you made me do this!
Wake up!
Output level 100.
Spiraling flood. Nejire Flood!
[screams]
[gasps] Hado! Hold on!
[DABI cackles]
Uh-oh, Endeavor!
You let sombody
get burned again.
Another kid with a bright
future ruined thanks to you!
[DABI cackles]
Damn it, stop!
[IZUKU]
Come on.
Stand up, Izuku.
It's just physical pain.
Todoroki's the one suffering
the most right now,
and he's still fighting.
[BEST JEANIST coughs]
[BEST JEANIST]
This is no time to hold back.
If the number one hero is
defeated here, in disgrace...
...this whole country
will unravel!
[SHIGARAKI]
It itches.
[whispering] Destroy.
Destroy...
[SHIGARAKI'S MOTHER]
No, dear. Stop scratching.
One day, we'll figure out
what you're allergic to.
I know, it's hard.
[SHIGARAKI]
It's worst when I'm at home.
I must destroy.
Have to stop this itching.
Shigaraki?
[whispering] Destroy it all.
Machia.
[roars]
[BEST JEANIST]
He got stronger?
[roaring]
[HERO 125A]
That's half down.
[HERO 125B] Yeah, but we lost
more than half of our forces.
[gasps] Incoming!
Headed toward Shigaraki.
[BURNIN]
What's going on?
Are they on the
hunt for new prey?
In the last 30 minutes,
the Nomu started
working together in
a coordinated effort.
I don't like this.
Do they have some kind of plan?
Burnin!
[BURNIN gasps]
[roars]
[BEST JEANIST coughs] How is
he growing more powerful?
How many Quirks does he have?
[yells]
You pushed those villains
to attack our family?
One of them almost killed Natsu.
Why, Toya?
You used to cry to him.
What happened to you?
What if he'd been murdered?
I was kinda hoping
that'd be the outcome.
Think about how much
Endeavor would've suffered.
You've gone completely insane.
You got that right.
Long-lost brother can't
feel a thing anymore.
Don't do this! Toya!
But I've waited
so long to kill you.
[SPINNER]
That's it, Machia.
You heard the boss's order.
Now start with the rampaging!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Spinner! Look!
[MR. COMPRESS] Plot twist!
Fortune shines on us.
[IZUKU]
Watch out, Best Jeanist!
I have to get up.
[IZUKU]
Can't let him get free.
[IZUKU] They seem evenly
matched right now,
but if Jeanist
loses concentration,
that giant and the League
will be on the loose.
Gotta do something!
If I use Float and Blackwhip,
it won't matter
that my limbs are
totally wrecked.
[IZUKU]
Nobody has been saved yet.
I won't be the useless Izuku
who was too weak
to rescue anyone!
I'll protect Best Jeanist!
Power!
Let's hear it again! Power!
Lemillion?
Right when we needed you.
But how did you know?
[MIRIO] The pros at the villa
gave us a heads up,
so I rushed over
using Permeation.
The Nighteye Agency was scouting
a villain hideout nearby.
Dang, he's a big one, huh?
[MIRIO] It's been half a year
since I was in the field.
Woof. Gettin' kinda sappy here.
[MIRIO] Bubble Girl reached out
to me with the intel personally.
She says tomorrow there's
gonna be an operation
that'll wipe out villains
on a national scale.
And I want to do whatever I can.
These past two months,
Eri has done extensive
training with her power.
Using small amounts of energy
on lizards and bugs.
I've been by her side
the whole time.
I've seen the results.
Sorry, Eri.
I know I'm sorta,
kinda using you, but...
Will you try Rewind on me?
So I can help them?
[ERI]
Don't apologize.
This is why I've been
practicing so hard.
[MIRIO]
Thank you, Eri.
You're too good to me.
Whoa not cool.
I wanted to end this fight fast,
but it's gonna take
way more than one punch.
Heya, somebody! Help!
[KATSUKI]
My explosions earlier...
[KATSUKI] ...were unlike
any I've unleashed before.
These were intense.
Strong, fast, distinct blasts.
[KATSUKI]
I've never felt such a rush.
[KATSUKI] This what happens
when you face death?
Whatever. I'll save everyone.
[yells]
[TENYA] I can't take my eyes
off you for a second!
Ground yourself!
You shouldn't be fighting!
Output at 100 percent.
Yo, Nejire!
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm peachy now that you're here.
Weird, huh?
[BEST JEANIST]
Your hero name is a wish.
How you want to be or how
you think you should be.
You haven't started looking
beyond yourself yet.
When you become a second year
and get your provisional
license, come back here.
I'll ask you for your
chosen name again.
[BEST JEANIST] Were you able
to look beyond yourself, Bakugo?
I chose a hero name.
I wanted you to hear it
in person first.
From now on call me...
...Great Explosion Murder God
Dynamight, got it?
[BEST JEANIST]
Child!
[TENYA]
So long!
[HADO]
Big yikes.
[MR. COMPRESS]
How crude!
[SPINNER]
Lame
[laughs] That's an
awesome hero name!
It's super funny.
You take that back, ya moron!
"Without joy and laughter
to balance the sorrow,
this world can't hope
for a bright future."
That's my motto.
Be careful not to wear it out!
Now then.
It looks like the big bad
is on the ropes.
[MIRIO] If we handle the rest a'
these creeps, we'll be golden.
Think your friends are
having fun over there!
[DABI]
But you look distraught.
I'm worried you're
not enjoying yourself.
Yeah, well, you either.
Your body's burning up.
I'm glad you were raised
to be a nice boy.
Don't worry 'bout me.
I'm not sure I've
ever felt better.
Look at that face.
You may be his
little masterpiece,
but you're about to be killed
by his greatest failure.
[laughs] See how broken he is?
It's too good! [laughs]
Shoto!
Can you imagine the
expression Dad'll have
when he watches my flames
melt the flesh off
your blackened bones?
[IZUKU] Lemillion and the
others have their hands full
covering Jeanist.
But I'm with you, Todoroki.
I have no strength in my limbs,
but I can still help.
[IZUKU]
Blackwhip. Froppy Style!
[DABI]
Back off.
This fight is none
of your business!
Yes it is!
Todoroki is my friend.
And Endeavor is my mentor.
He made me stronger.
[IZUKU]
The past never dies, sure.
That's why...
...I'm watching Endeavor closely
as he fights to be better.
But you are not Endeavor!
[ENDEAVOR]
Midoriya!
[IZUKU]
You're obsessed with his fire,
but this is your Quirk, not his!
[laughs] Everyone can see
we're nothing alike.
But c'mon, don't you feel
the least bit bad for me?
I'm a crime
committed by someone
claiming to seek justice.
Evil is flourishing because
hero society is collapsing.
I know you idiots need
to be spoon-fed a story,
so I'm showing you
exactly who's to blame.
[IZUKU]
I felt this earlier, too!
[DABI] The future we're
heading for is built on chaos.
The lies you heroes spew
won't matter anymore!
Uh, guys?
[BEST JEANIST]
He's breaking free!
[IZUKU gasps]
[roars]
Endeavor, no!
Please, Dad!
What happened to my strength?
[SPINNER]
Machia!
We got a report from
the heroes in the field.
They said their plan had failed.
[MIRIO]
But the sedative worked!
[BEST JEANIST] I do not know
who accomplished this,
but our hopes
have been repaired.
The fact that this
drug kicked in
at the 11th hour
isn't a coincidence.
We've been chipping
away at this villain
little by little, using
whatever meager power
we were able to cobble together.
Sacrificing ourselves to break
his spirit and slow him down.
We held him off as best we could
until the drug had
time to take effect.
If I've learned one thing
through my Quirk,
it's that, though
a single fiber is weak,
it can be braided with others
to form a mighty rope.
[BEST JEANIST]
Had even one thread broken,
we would have failed.
It's only together that we've
woven a tapestry of faith.
[DABI] Just when things
were getting good!
It's obvious your
body is overheating.
Look around.
In a battle of wills,
we have the upper hand.
As I'd expect from his creation.
Brother, you're making me proud.
Power!
The heroes have been
fighting a difficult battle.
These Nomu don't
have fancy attacks,
but their speed and
toughness are crazy.
[MIRIO] Each one of these
is as strong as the High End
from Kyushu that almost
killed Hawks and Endeavor.
You do not wanna tango with them
'less you've been well trained!
[TENYA] Get back, Great
Explosion Murder God Dynamight!
You're wounded! You're in
no condition to fight.
Ugh.
[KATSUKI]
Dammit. I hate that he's right!
[HADO]
I can draw fire off of Jeanist
as long as I manage
to keep dodging!
[TENYA] I'll stick it out
until that giant quiets down.
Even if a complete victory
against him seems impossible.
[BEST JEANIST] The resources
used to stop this mammoth,
can now be employed
against the League.
[MR. COMPRESS]
This binding is so tight
that I can't touch the cables.
Which means I can't
activate Compress
to get us out of this mess.
What a shameful predicament.
All I can do is grope
my own posterior.
You're no better, Shigaraki.
Remember why you
summoned us here?
We were supposed to gather
together and create a spectacle.
What'd you have to go
and get beaten up for?
Now we're trapped!
There's so much left
in this world to destroy.
[MR. COMPRESS]
It's just as Spinner said.
We haven't done anything yet.
Not Dabi.
Nor Toga.
Nor I.
None of us have
achieved our dreams!
This cannot be where
our performance ends!
[BEST JEANIST]
Blackout Bind!
[MR. COMPRESS]
The spotlight is mine now.
It's time for these
philistines to witness
the greatest show on earth!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
A fight to the death
between brothers.
A hopeless Endeavor.
Spinner's wish.
The determination
of Mr. Compress.
And Me and Shigaraki.
No. One For All and All For One.
We each race towards our goals
as this war reaches
its dizzying conclusion.
Next time, "Final Performance."
Who'll be left
standing in the end?
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!