[IZUKU] The Counter-Quirk
Maximum Security Special Prison,
also known as "Tartarus."
[IZUKU] It's a facility
built on the open sea
about five kilometers off
the coast of the mainland.
To the public it's just
another out-of-sight place
to lock up villains.
But in reality, it's a dumping
ground where the government
can monitor those they deem a
serious threat to public safety.
Those imprisoned here
have terrifying Quirks.
[IZUKU] Inmates are split among
six cellblocks that reflect
how severe a criminal's
offenses were
and the danger their
abilities pose.
The more dangerous the person,
the deeper underwater
they're held.
It's said that no one sent
here will ever leave alive.
This is the dark side of
our super-powered society.
[ALL FOR ONE]
I feel it.
Events didn't play out exactly
to plan, but we have momentum.
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE] Those
poor fools like to think that
tomorrow will bring them hope.
But I'm not giving the
world time to recover.
It's my turn now.
My turn forever.
Listen well, my tireless Nomu.
It's time to give you
an important task.
Free my real body.
[GYGES] So, Brother,
you hear that Endeavor
let Tomura Shigaraki escape?
[BRIAREOS] Yeah. Word is
him and 132 members
of the Paranormal Liberation
Front are on the run now
along with seven
of those Nomu things.
[GYGES] Raid teams got
their butts handed to 'em.
[BRIAREOS]
A hundred and forty-five pros
are in the hospital,
including Endeavor.
Word has it Midnight
and Majestic are dead.
Some other big names, too.
[GYGES]
Damn it.
If only we could've
been there to help.
[BRIAREOS]
Don't get worked up.
Guarding this place is an
important, honorable duty.
Best thing we can do
is keep a strong front here.
[GYGES]
Yeah, yeah, I know.
[BRIAREOS]
What set those off?
[GYGES]
Control room, come in!
Look there!
[GYGES]
Are those Nomu?
[BRIAREOS]
Shoot them!
[GYGES]
What the...?
What's going on?
Briareos! Gyges?
Control room here!
Give us a status report.
Come in? Hello?
Can you hear me?
[GYGES]
This is Gyges.
We've got Nomu out here.
Not sure how many, but I think
they killed my brother.
This is a code red.
No time. Authorize
counter protocols!
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
Such feeble resistance.
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
Sounds like they expect
that giant city crusher
tomorrow morning.
[PRISON STAFF 128C]
Gigantomachia.
He's 'ol scarface's
flunky, right?
[PRISON STAFF 128B] Yeah.
They're having to copter him in.
[PRISON STAFF 128C] Should have
killed him in the field.
[PRISON STAFF 128B] How would
you propose they do that?
Hit him with a missile?
We don't just blow people up.
I mean, they guy's still human.
How do you call him that
with a straight face?
He's a beast. Just a
walking monstrosity.
Same as the other
deranged animals
we've got caged up in here.
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
Stop talking like that.
You know everything you're
saying is being recorded.
The Hearts and Mind Party
is defunct now,
but there'll be others.
We already get enough flak
about human rights
violations as it is.
Last thing we need's a
conversation like this to leak.
Watch yourself.
I'm just speaking the truth.
They may look like
you and me on the surface.
Mostly. But we only
call them human
because Quirks warped
our perceptions so badly.
In truth...
...they're fundamentally
different from us normal people.
[SYSTEM VOICE 128A] Intruder
alert. Code Red. I repeat.
This is a Code Red
security alert.
Floors and exits
have been sealed off.
All staff should
be on high alert.
[PRISON STAFF 128D] We've
got multiple Nomu incoming.
They've already managed to
break through the Bronze Gate.
Nomu? They're attacking here,
now of all times? Don't tell me.
They came straight
from the big battle!
Is this payback?
[PRISON STAFF 128D] Severing our
connection to the mainland.
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
The bridge is going under
starting with section A01!
You're struggling in vain.
[PRISON STAFF 128C]
Attention Cottus Troops,
you have permission
to fire at will.
Capture targets dead or alive.
I repeat, permission
granted to use
any and all modes
of suppression.
[SHIGARAKI]
I told you before, Master.
This is my body, not yours.
[ALL FOR ONE] Ah, you're awake.
But you should keep resting.
Your Super Regeneration
isn't ready,
and I need your body
in tip top shape.
[SHIGARAKI]
So what am I doing out here?
You're sending me
into battle again.
[ALL FOR ONE]
No, just a simple task.
[SHIGARAKI]
Give me back control.
[ALL FOR ONE] You're the one
who wanted my power, Tomura.
You abhor this cruel world
that didn't reach out
a hand to help you.
And I've given you the ability
to manifest your hatred.
What's important now is the
passion that fuels your ire.
Our success is the
result of your will.
I will not be your pawn.
My dear boy, you have
the wrong idea.
You're a treasure in my eyes,
someone I seek to lift up.
You are the next me.
[PRISON STAFF gasp]
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
Tower Two is down!
It's Shigaraki, he's here.
[PRISON STAFF] The decay is
spreading like it did in Jaku!
[PRISON STAFF 128C]
Start evacuating the staff!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Hm... I've found my location
thanks to the
Search Quirk I stole.
In the deepest corner,
500 meters below sea level.
Even if you used Decay on the
building while sparing my body,
the water pressure
would kill me.
And I have doubts
that you're currently
up to the task anyway.
What I need now
is more villains.
It's a terrible fortress
they've built.
Machia would barely
help in this situation.
We'd be hard-pressed
to overcome their forces.
I'd say the same thing
if your body were complete.
Tartarus is all but impenetrable
from the outside.
Of course, there is
always a way.
[PRISON STAFF 128D]
Power is fluctuating.
[PRISON STAFF 128B] The whole
surveillance system is down!
I think we suffered
an EMP attack!
We've still got
emergency security!
Get the sensers back on
before the prisoners
realize what's happening.
Rebooting in three, two...
The attack came from
the inside this time!
[PRISON STAFF 128C]
Surveillance can't be restored!
Crap! Security's offline.
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
That means...
[PRISON STAFF 128C]
An inmate used their Quirk
inside the facility!
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
No, it couldn't be!
How could they know
our systems were down?
This shouldn't be possible.
[ALL FOR ONE] There's not a
single bit of stimulation here.
The world likens this
place to something
out of a Greek myth,
calling it Tartarus.
That's the name of
the underworld prison
where kings and
Titans were punished.
Escaping would be
a struggle, even for me.
[ALL MIGHT] You're trapped here.
You'll never go free.
[ALL FOR ONE]
That's right.
It's just as you said,
All Might.
You put me away forever.
There's no way I can escape.
Unless there's
perfect synchronicity
between the me who's locked away
and the one inside
Tomura's head.
[PRISON STAFF 128B] Backup
security measures are failing.
[PRISON STAFF 128C] The locks
on the cell doors won't hold.
They'll overrun us.
Where are the guards now?
[PRISON STAFF 128B]
Suppression troops
have reached the lowest level!
[WARDEN 128A] Regain control
no matter what it takes.
[SUPPRESSION TROOPS]
Roger!
[WARDEN 128A]
According to regulations,
if an inmate takes one step
outside their cell,
they can be shot down!
Get your weapons ready.
I want you backing up the--
Fire! Shoot him!
[PRISON STAFF groans]
[gasps]
[MUSCULAR] You'll have to try
harder than that to kill me.
Now start talkin'.
Where is the exit
outta this hellhole? Huh?
[INMATE 128A]
Holy crap!
[INMATE 128B] I don't
know how, but we're free!
[PRISON STAFF 128G]
Don't move!
[PRISON STAFF 128G] Everyone,
get back to your cells!
We will not hold our fire
for anyone who resists.
Damn it!
I'd rather be dead
than go back in there.
Why? We were free.
[MOONFISH]
Flesh.
[INMATE 128F laughs] We can use
our powers as much as we want!
[INMATE 128G]
Yeah, thank the guards
for how nice they've been.
[LADY NAGANT] The security
system isn't kicking in
even though people are
using their Quirks.
And this was already a madhouse.
[thudding]
Where is Pops?
[INMATE 128H]
What do we do now?
[INMATE 128I] We can't leave
if there's no bridge!
[MUSCULAR]
No stopping.
Not till I stand on
free ground again!
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
Friends, if you want to leave,
all you need do is follow me.
Well, I'll be damned.
[ALL FOR ONE] Yes. I want
you to stand by my side.
In the era of chaos
on the horizon,
a more perfect demon
lord will be born.
[ALL FOR ONE] You will bear
witness to the story
of how I become the greatest
demon lord this world has known.
[IZUKU] Six hours after
the attack on Tartarus...
[IZUKU] ...All For One hijacked
an emergency aircraft
using a staff member's
biometric ID.
With that, he was free.
[IZUKU] The Near High Ends and
former inmates followed him.
On his orders, they went on to
attack seven different prisons
and released a large number
of criminals from six of them.
[ALL FOR ONE] At last,
my preparations are complete.
What a thrilling 24 hours.
I released as many
prisoners as possible
to confuse those
who would hunt me.
The streets will
scream with violence.
I do have one last request
of you, however.
Protect this body
while it recovers.
Shigaraki and I had
a lot in common.
Games and stuff.
[SPINNER] I want to reform this
society ruled by fake heroes.
That's why I joined the League.
Because Stain's
ideology inspired me.
We had great ideas
if not follow through,
all wanting to crush this world.
But the League
became disorganized.
An aimless band
of petty thieves.
Myself included.
But when his spark returned,
he lit a fire under
even the emptiest of us.
So, then, why shouldn't
I destroy it?
Why must I suffer it?
I wanted to see what
Shigaraki could pull off.
The future he could craft.
So who the hell are you?
You're not the person
I chose to follow.
My loyalty is to him,
Tomura Shigaraki.
[ALL FOR ONE, SHIGARAKI]
Don't fret, Iguchi.
There is no need for hostility.
Please trust that I respect
Tomura's feelings
above everything else.
I long for his body to heal
so he can be complete.
Once he's whole, our every
dream will be realized.
[ALL FOR ONE] I'll take
One For All and reign forever.
No man will stand against me.
I will be its absolute ruler,
the demon lord.
[KATSUKI gasps]
[KATSUKI]
Deku.
[yells] He's awake!
Shut up and start explaining!
Oh, good, he's mad.
That must mean he's
feeling like himself!
I'm about to be real mad!
Where the hell am I?
[SATO] Dude, you're
at Central Hospital.
From what we hear,
they have the latest,
most advanced
medical treatments.
I'm so glad our
class jerk is alive!
[HAGAKURE] Oh, I'll go
tell the nurse he's up.
Good idea.
Deku and Todoroki?
Mr. Aizawa, Endeavor,
and all the others.
What happened to everybody?
I'll tell you, 'kay?
But you gotta try to stay calm.
[NANA] I doctored the records
so he's not linked to me.
If that man finds out
Kotaro exists,
he'll use my kid against us.
So I no longer have a son.
I'm not a mother
anymore, Sorahiko.
I never was.
[GRAN TORINO]
Shimura.
[DOCTOR 128A] If you and
Gran Torino had gotten here
much later, the prognosis
would have been bleaker
than what we're
currently looking at.
You have Locklock
and the first responders
to thank for
prioritizing your lives.
Try not to worry about
anything that's happened.
Focus on your own recovery.
[AIZAWA] We let Shigaraki
get away, and as a result,
villains have broken out
of half a dozen prisons.
[PRESENT MIC] Those escapees are
committing crimes left and right
and we don't have the
resources to stop 'em.
The public's really laying
into us about it.
We did what we were
supposed to do.
We gave everything we had.
Fought with our
lives on the line.
And this is still
how things turned out.
We let Kayama
and the others die.
Let's not do this now.
Tell me how the students
are holding up.
[KAMINARI] There's, like,
a mob of people out there.
Call me crazy,
but I'm pretty sure
they're not here to thank us.
This crime wave
is getting even worse
and the news is
reporting on it 24/7.
It feels like the whole
country's on edge.
Dire times.
[MOB shouting]
Just try to ignore 'em.
I'm sure things will work out.
We know you, Todoroki.
So we know what
a good person you are.
You'll brave this.
[REPORTER 128A]
Did you know about your brother?
[REPORTER 128AA] What's
Endeavor's current condition?
Is he going to pull through?
[REPORTER 128A] Does he have
any idea the disastrous state
Japan is in thanks to him?
Come on, talk!
Everyone wants to know more
about the Todoroki family.
[REPORTER 128AA] When will your
father have a press conference?
Our viewers are scared!
We want answers!
[STARSERVANT]
Him! He's the source!
The fire he gives off
blinds you!
He will be the demise
of our world!
[DABI]
Hey now, don't be rude.
You're acting like
we've never met.
Call me Toya.
After all, it's the name
you and mom gave me.
Enji Todoroki!
Let's fall together.
Come and dance with me
in hell, won't you?
[TODOROKI]
His heat was so intense.
Stronger than my
old man's. Too strong.
Flames of hatred.
That's what they were.
[TODOROKI] He's been
watching this whole time.
Waiting to see Endeavor fall.
Ruining his body and the
lives of anyone in his path,
just to make our father suffer.
[TODOROKI]
Toya is me.
[TODOROKI] The reason
I picked a fight with you
was to show my old man
what I was capable of doing.
Without having to rely
on his damned fire Quirk.
I'm going to show him
that I reject his power
and I can take first place
without using it.
[TODOROKI] I was burning
with hate until that day.
Same as him.
Our father can't stop Toya.
I have to be the one
to handle my brother.
Shoto.
Hello!
Whoa. You're Todoroki's
brother and sister!
I'm afraid his throat
suffered minor burns,
so he isn't speaking.
[FUYUMI]
Yes, of course.
The doctored explained
his condition to us earlier.
[NATSUO]
You don't have to talk, Shoto.
Just listen.
[SATO]
I told you not to get up!
You could die!
[MINETA]
Just stop!
You're the worst patient.
We're not supposed
to let ya leave your room.
Shut up!
Make me fight you and I'll be
even more likely to drop dead.
Why do you have to be so
stubborn about everything, dude?
There's nothing you can do
to help right now.
Didn't you hear
a word Sero said?
[SERO]
I'll tell you, 'kay?
But you gotta stay calm.
Todoroki's burned bad and
Mr. Aizawa has some
serious injuries,
but they'll both pull through.
Everyone else has regained
consciousness except...
[SERO] The doctors said
Midoriya hasn't shown
any signs of waking up.
[KATSUKI] That bastard.
If he dies, I'll kill him.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
Prisons across Japan
have been cracked open
and the villains once contained
are now running wild.
As the country
falls into a panic,
citizens stop relying on heroes
and fight the
criminals themselves.
Most of the anger is aimed
at one man, Endeavor.
Next time, "The Hellish
Todoroki Family, Part 2."
This is when we ask ourselves
what it means to be a hero.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!