[GRAN TORINO] You don't say.
That's Shimura for you.
Even in the afterlife,
she's crying over our choices.
[GRAN TORINO] I should've
killed him on the battlefield
when I had the chance.
I apologize.
Don't be too stubborn.
Sometimes you have to kill
a person in order to save them.
Be sure to remember that.
Whatever you decide to do,
you make damn sure
you settle the score with
the League of Villains.
[IZUKU] Hawks, Best Jeanist,
Endeavor, and All Might.
We're teaming up to end this.
[IZUKU] Together we'll keep
anyone else from getting hurt.
[IZUKU]
We have to stop All For One.
I have to.
[BEAST GIRL 133A]
Gotta get out of here.
Before they...!
[VIGILANTE 133B]
There she is. The monster!
Please! Don't hurt me!
I'm just heading to the shelter.
I wasn't doing anything!
[BEAST GIRL 133A]
I'm begging you. Let me go.
[VIGILANTE 133A] You want us
to let our guards down
so you can attack.
[VIGILANTE 133B]
We're not stupid.
We see you for what you are.
And we're not going to let
this town suffer another day!
No, stop!
[IZUKU]
Listen. Please calm down.
I totally understand
that a night like this
makes you extra nervous about an
attack. But look at this woman.
She's showing no signs
of hostility.
[IZUKU]
Leave her to me.
You can go now.
I've got this. Please.
[VIGILANTE 133A] Well...
Someone who looks like that
shouldn't be out this late.
[VIGILANTE 133B]
What were we supposed to think?
[IZUKU]
You're safe now.
[IZUKU] Why are you walking
around in this weather?
[BEAST GIRL 133A]
I didn't evacuate.
At first, it seemed like the
area wasn't affected much.
I guess...
I thought everything would blow
over if I holed up at home.
Then people around me
started getting hurt
and I got scared.
That's when I decided to leave.
To find a shelter.
I don't know.
The night just went
wrong so fast.
[IZUKU] Y'know, I bet everyone
else is scared, too.
[BEAST GIRL 133A] Do you think
things will go back to normal?
[IZUKU]
I'll make sure of it.
[BEAST GIRL 133A gasps]
[IZUKU]
I'm sorry. I have to go now.
[ALL MIGHT]
Are you okay?
[IZUKU]
Yes, All Might.
Wait. All Might?
[IZUKU] Will you take her
to the nearest shelter?
I've been in one place
for too long.
[ALL MIGHT]
Wait! Here, take this with you.
Pork cutlets to keep
your energy levels up.
[IZUKU]
Thanks. I appreciate it.
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya.
[BANJO]
Widespread devastation.
It kinda feels like we've
traveled back in time.
In my day, we did our best
to stay out of sight
'cause hiding from villains
kept us alive.
It was like that when Quirks
first appeared, too.
[IZUKU]
Shigaraki and All For One.
Dabi. The Nomu.
The League of Villains.
We still don't have any idea
where they disappeared to.
The police have
their hands full
with the jailbreakers.
So they don't have the
resources to investigate
the bigger threats.
Criminals are running
amok out there.
[IZUKU]
Now that All For One's Quirk
has been transplanted
into Shigaraki,
he's even more terrifying.
So powerful, I couldn't stop him
with the help of
Endeavor and Mr. Aizawa.
I need to master every
facet of One For All.
Otherwise I'll fail.
[FIRST WIELDER] You two
better start helping out.
You can't keep staring at
the wall and ignoring us.
We need your cooperation
to unleash One For All's
full potential.
We're counting on you,
my heroes.
Banjo was the first.
He released his Quirk.
And after, Shinomori
followed suit.
Shimura was next.
And En. All of them agreed.
But we need everyone's support
to bring its true
strength to light.
Hey, kid! Try getting'
more accustomed
to the other Quirks
in the meantime!
Especially Shinomori's and En's!
Ya do that and things
should go much smoother
when you wake up.
[EN]
That's a good idea.
[IZUKU muffled]
[THIRD WIELDER] We lived
during the cruelest era.
All For One's physical
strength was at its peak.
He'd managed to amass
incredible power.
Most people he controlled
were unaware
that they were
being manipulated.
But our leader knew the truth.
Together we stood
against All For One.
Fighting to stop his ascent.
You were there, too. You saw it.
Yes.
[SECOND WIELDER]
In order to get to your brother,
we had to sacrifice many people.
The only thing that mattered
to us was winning.
Either he died or humanity did.
Now we're supposed
to leave everything
up to this boy who wants
to save our enemy?
It's absurd.
Is that really how you feel?
That's interesting.
[FIRST WIELDER]
See. I'm a little confused.
[FIRST WIELDER] Back then,
you reached your hand out to me.
[FIRST WIELDER]
If you hadn't chosen to save
a potential enemy, none of
this ever would've happened.
[FIRST WIELDER]
We have no choice
but to leave the future
to the ninth.
You must realize this.
It's why you appeared
here to begin with.
Be honest, you really think
he can bring an end to this?
I do. It's why
One For All exists.
It was born out of my defiance.
But, the power only
became what it is
because you were
willing to reach out.
The stage is set
for the grand finale.
In order to defeat
All For One...
...we must take our
knowledge and power...
...and gather it in this place.
[EN]
The true power of One For All...
...must be harnessed!
Hang on, boy,
we're accelerating now!
Right!
[JAILBREAKER 133A yells]
Idiot! We gotta get outta here!
[JAILBREAKER 133B]
You ain't gonna beat Endeavor!
[ENDEAVOR]
A nail gun support item?
Too overpowered to be used
for actual construction.
Damn Detnerat.
This was meant to be a weapon.
[JAILBREAKER 133B] Hawks?
Crap, and Best Jeanist, too?
[BEST JEANIST]
Fiber Fire!
[JAILBREAKER 133A yells]
Ignited Arrow!
[JAILBREAKER 133A]
You have no right.
Number one.
Your crimes are worse
than mine are.
You caused this mess.
[ENDEAVOR]
I'm aware of that.
Which is why I'm here now.
[BEST JEANIST] As usual,
there's nothing connecting
these escapees to
our actual target.
You'd think we would've
been able to get some intel
by this point in the search.
We'll double down our efforts.
[CITIZEN 133A]
Disgraces! Get out of here!
[CITIZEN 133B] We don't want
your so-called help.
If you'd caught Shigaraki
and the others
and when you were supposed to,
these criminals would still
be locked in their prisons.
Take a good look at this town.
You turned it into hell!
[HAWKS]
Endeavor? Let's go.
[CITIZEN 133C] I've been
following reports on the news.
They say Shigaraki was after
someone other than you!
Which means you're still
hiding things from us.
We can't trust you!
You cowards!
[CITIZEN 133C] The families
of the people Dabi murdered
were on TV! Did you see them?
[CITIZEN 133AA]
You created a monster!
[CITIZEN 133A]
Stay away from us!
[CITIZEN 133B]
Seeing your face makes me sick.
[CITIZEN 133AA]
Fake hero!
[CITIZEN 133D] Don't you
ever show up here again.
[HAWKS]
Is that so? I see.
Yeah. Understood.
Maybe someone from the
Paranormal Liberation
Front will crack.
Thanks, Edge Shot.
[BEST JEANIST]
No progress, I take it.
If we keep driving in this
direction, we'll catch up
with Midoriya before long.
Would it be better
if no one figured out
we're working together?
People might start throwing
things at him, too.
Right. Let's put some
distance between us.
[ENDEAVOR] Deku has enough
of a burden to carry as it is.
Even if he's the one who
chose this solitary path,
we're still using him as bait
to draw out the League.
The least we can do is not
make things worse for him.
[HAWKS] Our enemies are doing
too well at laying low.
Meanwhile, the supervillains
who were locked up
in Tartarus are acting up.
And they're almost
certainly taking orders
from you-know-who now.
The League's being smart.
They'll hide behind the chaos
and confusion and use it
as a cover to steal One For All
when the time's right.
[BEST JEANIST]
Meanwhile, the country's heroes
continue to unravel.
If I were All For One,
I'd go on the offensive.
[ENDEAVOR] Right now,
his priority is taking over
Shigaraki's body,
like Deku said.
After losing to All Might,
he couldn't survive
without a labyrinth of
tubes and machinery.
So he's strengthening
his protégé's body
in order to make
that his new home.
[HAWKS] According to Garaki's
post-raid interrogation,
Shigaraki was brought
back online
before his upgrades could
be fully completed.
I don't know how All For One
plans to move into
his new digs, but it's
clear the boy's body
needs to be perfected
before he does.
[ENDEAVOR]
And once that's accomplished,
he'll focus on his next goal.
Taking One For All
by any means necessary.
There's still something
bothering me about that.
[BEST JEANIST]
What?
[HAWKS] Based on what
Midoriya and All Might said,
you have to have a strong body
to steal One For All.
Got it. Cool.
That's where Shigaraki's
younger, enhanced physique
comes into play.
My question is,
why is Shigaraki's hatred
such an important
component in this?
[BEST JEANIST] The force
of that feeling is vital.
With eight people's
minds fighting back
inside One For All, you'd need a
powerful will to overcome them.
But All For One has been
chasing One For All,
his younger brother,
for generations at this point.
Sounds pretty intense to me.
You'd think he'd be carrying
around more than enough
hatred for the
successors already.
Not to mention,
All Might's the reason he ended
up weak and imprisoned, right?
[BEST JEANIST] It would appear
his spite simply isn't enough.
[HAWKS] Or maybe
he just doesn't have any.
I'm going off my
gut here, but...
Despite everything,
doesn't it seem like
the guy's always laughing?
Perhaps his heart is just empty.
[BEST JEANIST]
Whatever the case,
no villain we've found
has information.
And the League is dormant.
They're trying to avoid a fight,
so let's use that
to our advantage.
We should start
expanding our search,
even though that will mean
fewer heroes on the streets,
maintaining order.
[HAWKS]
I don't know, man.
Things get much worse out there,
and the public is going to
turn against us even more.
It'll be harder for us
to rally support.
[BEST JEANIST]
Cut away too much fabric,
and the design falls apart.
[ALL MIGHT]
He's still on the move.
Have you gotten any
rest at all, young man?
I recommend a
solid night's sleep
on a sublime mattress.
Nighteye. I'm trying.
[beeping]
What was that?
Not good.
[ALL MIGHT]
His GPS signal disappeared!
Damn it!
[ALL MIGHT]
Crap.
[LADY NAGANT]
Little boy dressed in green.
You're coming with me.
[IZUKU] Wait. Then this isn't
just some random villain.
I'm her target!
Right. This is it!
A jailbreaker with ties to him!
[LADY NAGANT]
Don't move a muscle
and I'll let you
keep your limbs.
[IZUKU] This sniper was
hired by All For One!
[LADY NAGANT]
Little boy dressed in green.
Don't move a muscle.
And I'll let you
keep your limbs.
[IZUKU] This sniper was
hired by All For One!
[HAWKS]
From what I'm told,
you should be able to hold your
own given the power you have.
But I'm still concerned.
All For One and
Shigaraki can't steal
this cultivated ability
from you yet.
And in the last fight,
we confiscated every scrap
of Garaki's tech we could find.
Without that, they don't have
a way to store a Quirk Factor
to be transplanted later.
So, the best choice
for the League
would be to take you in alive.
Thankfully most of the escapees
wouldn't stand a
chance against you.
But... there's one woman
we should be worried about.
[IZUKU]
Is that her?
[HAWKS]
We were basically colleagues,
though she was my senior.
Of course, I'm trying to
track her down her, as well.
But, Deku.
If the two of you
ever cross paths,
run like hell.
Fast as you can.
[IZUKU]
Bullets made out of indigo
and pink strands
twisted together.
I said, "don't move."
[IZUKU]
There's no mistake! It's her!
A former public safety
commission hero.
Lady Nagant!
She destroyed my
secure communicator!
That'll signal All Might, Hawks,
and the others that something
is wrong, but I have
no way of warning them
that she's the one
behind this attack.
If they rush in, they'll be
in her line of fire.
What do I do?
Try to escape like
Hawks said to?
Why bother running
when you're already mine?
[IZUKU]
High-angle fire?
Analyze the trajectory.
[LADY NAGANT]
Now I get it.
Huh. That's why he wants you.
[IZUKU grunts]
[SNIPE]
Oh, her? She's insane.
If she weren't around, I'd be
the best long-range shooter
in Japan, no contest.
My Quirk, Homing,
lets me hit any target
I can see within 600 meters.
Can't choose where the shot hits
and it don't pack much punch,
but not too shabby, right?
Her, though.
She can hit the same
mark with skill alone,
and from a perch
three kilometers away!
She's taking away
all my business!
I'm gonna be sent
out to pasture!
The secret's in her bullets.
She has the ability to
make them into any shape
her heart desires.
See, her two-toned hair
gets mashed together
like epoxy putty, which then
hardens into her ammunition.
I'm talkin' curving bullets,
hollow-point bullets.
Sky's the limit.
Her Quirk is Rifle,
and she's the walking
personification of
a sniper rifle.
Everybody who shoots targets
is jealous of her right arm.
[IZUKU] Precision even
Mr. Snipe is jealous of.
And a good firing rate.
Without Danger Sense,
she woulda had me.
But thanks to the first shot
and the one just now,
I can tell where she is!
About one kilometer ahead!
Her range is triple that.
No point trying to evade
her bullets and outrun her.
Gotta get close!
That's the first time
someone's dodged
more than one bullet.
Where's Pops?
I need to hurry to him.
Right now.
[LADY NAGANT] Yeah, yeah.
After I'm finished with this.
It's time to hide.
The target'll see you.
I'm coming, Boss.
Just hang out
in here for a minute.
Ugh, great.
Maybe I should've
ditched him before.
[LADY NAGANT]
Come on. Walk faster!
Do you want to be
locked up again?
[CHISAKI]
Must find him.
What is wrong with this guy?
[ALL FOR ONE]
Ah, an erstwhile hero.
The lovely Lady Nagant.
It's an honor to meet you.
[LADY NAGANT]
All For One.
You know, not long ago,
you were my main target.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Yet here we are.
I have a favor to ask you.
You're not like the
rest of this rabble.
In the coming days,
a certain student from UA
will set out on his own.
My request is simple:
I would like you to
bring the boy to me.
[ALL FOR ONE]
A number of annoying guardians
will be watching
over him from afar.
It would be wise to get him
alone before you make your move.
[ALL FOR ONE] Perhaps you
could wait for a rainy night.
I find that atmosphere
to be quite--
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Did I say I agreed
to be your pawn?
You told the others to go wild.
So why am I the only one
whose freedom comes at a price?
Because you once killed
a hero. Heh. An ally.
You also desire the destruction
of this failed society.
But that will never come
to pass so long as the boy
is allowed to play
at being a hero.
Great. Another one
of those. Damn.
[CHISAKI]
Pops.
[ALL FOR ONE] The young head
of the Shie Hassaikai.
A friend of yours?
[LADY NAGANT]
No. Something's broken in him.
But I thought
he might be useful.
[ALL FOR ONE]
He is also a victim.
Driven to ruin by these
corrupt false heroes.
Let us seal their coffins shut.
Come. You're hired for the job.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Consider this power an advance.
[LADY NAGANT]
Air Walk. Nice.
I have a mission to complete.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
As my fierce fight
with Lady Nagant begins,
she channels the despair
and anger in her heart
into deadly bullets that
explode through the night sky.
I'll need all my wits
if I want to defeat her,
which means trusting in the
Quirks of the previous wielders.
Next time, "The Lovely
Lady Nagant."
The superhuman society
we admired
was more fragile
than anyone imagined.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!