Strike when Blackwhip
is fully stretched out.
Once I'm in range,
you two beat it, quickly.
The blast is deadly.
[KATSUKI] Even if Deku's Quirk
is some kinda cursed power.
[KATSUKI]
It's still our only hope!
Now!
--What?
--[ENDEAVOR] Back, Deku!
You!
Plus Ultra.
Prominence Burn!
[screaming]
[BOTH]
Endeavor!
Why won't you die?
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
Little Brother.
No.
[KATSUKI] Stop trying
to win this by yourself.
[SHIGARAKI]
Let me go.
[IZUKU]
Kacchan!
[SHIGARAKI]
It's my body.
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
You've fought and fought today,
spilling so much
blood for no reason.
No reason?
[5TH WIELDER]
Listen well.
If you use One For All in anger,
the power will react
to that feeling.
What's important is keeping
tabs on your heart.
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
This last boy who interfered
now suffers, because he mistook
foolishness for bravery.
[IZUKU]
You take that back.
Midoriya!
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
You're finally mine.
[gasps]
[SHIGARAKI, ALL FOR ONE]
Come to me.
One For All--
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU]
I know this place.
I'm inside One For All.
What's going on?
Where's Kacchan?
[IZUKU]
Shigaraki?
No. Not just him.
[SHIGARAKI]
Learn your place, Master.
[ALL FOR ONE]
There's no need to be petulant.
If I hadn't lent you my power,
you would be nothing
but ash right now.
Dead from Endeavor's blast
or the resulting fall.
[SHIGARAKI] Didn't I tell you
to shut up, earlier?
I'm in charge. This is my will.
The dream I chase is mine.
[NANA]
It's no use.
You can't move
in this world yet.
Fear not.
Let us take care
of this for you.
Currently, the villain
is continuing north
through Sairo City with
no sign of slowing down.
This is catastrophic.
The city's being demolished.
[GIGANTOMACHIA]
I smell two Masters?
[HERO 123A] Heroes!
Leave the remaining residents
to the rescue team and police!
We need to focus on saving
people from that giant!
Evacuations are almost done here
but countless others
are in danger!
With the comms down,
we can't update those
who went after Shigaraki.
We must act.
Push yourselves to the limit!
Work quickly and keep harm
from coming to anyone else.
You three flyers
help spread the word!
Tell Endeavor and the
others the situation!
[NEJIRE]
Roger that!
[TENYA]
I'll lend you support!
No, kid, you'll be caught up
in Shigaraki's Decay--
Dang, he's fast.
Hey, hey, wait, Ingenium.
Why are you coming with us?
[TENYA] I deserve to be punished
for disobeying orders,
but I have three classmates
who may be in danger!
Two of them are
treasured friends
who set me on the right path!
Then let's hurry.
[TENYA]
Right!
[OCHACO] We were supposed to
make things better, but have we?
[OCHACO] Since that day,
it's like darkness
has fallen over this world,
with no sun in sight.
[OCHACO]
Come on, guys.
I didn't think I'd
see you after I died.
Hello, All For One.
[IZUKU]
Whoa, it's her.
The seventh wielder!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Look at that, Tomura.
What an extraordinary sight.
It's the talking corpse
of your grandmother,
the pitifully incompetent
Nana Shimura.
Do you know how she's here?
It's transference!
[IZUKU]
Transference?
[ALL FOR ONE] It's said,
when a person receives
an organ transplant,
their personality can change.
Some call this superstition,
but evidence suggests
some traits are passed on
through our cells.
Even I find myself having
the most peculiar dreams
every once in a while.
In them, the original owners of
Quirks I've stolen rage at me.
Afterward, I awake dejected,
closest I ever come to
feeling a sense of guilt.
Fortunately, once I
part with a Quirk,
the person I took it from
never haunts my dreams again.
I find that odd.
I'm not the type
to let anything go.
It wasn't until I met the Doctor
that I discovered the reason.
Just as memories and personality
can reside inside
transplanted viscera,
Quirk factors contain a piece
of the person who wields them,
even after they've
passed on to new users.
My ability to tamper with Quirks
makes me acutely aware
of these phantom souls.
Though I admit, I'm not certain
if this is a blessing or curse.
You coward.
I won't let you keep
disgracing Shimura's memory.
Nana Shimura.
[HANA]
I found a secret.
This lady is our grandma.
She's a hero!
[NANA]
Don't forget.
[SHIGARAKI]
What do you want?
Of course I'm not the only one
who has the ability
to meddle with powers here.
While I was capable
of manipulating Quirks,
someone close to me--
my younger brother--
had the power to gift
his to someone else.
When his Quirk mixed
with my stockpiling one,
it created something
truly unique.
A purgatory of dead wielders
clinging onto a sad
sort of afterlife.
Ah, I'm sorry.
You two have so much
to catch up on.
So you're Kotaro's son.
[SHIGARAKI] And you're
someone I don't even know.
But rest assured, Grandmother.
I hate you like
I hate everyone else.
[IZUKU gasps]
This world.
It's falling apart!
[ALL FOR ONE] Good, Tomura!
Your hatred is breaking through!
Normally, One For All can only
be transferred by its owner,
but your anger opens a path
to take it by force. [laughs]
Oh, that's right.
You've decided to
hate me as well.
A fine development!
You are becoming the new
Symbol of Fear, aren't you?
I'm afraid your hatred
isn't strong enough, though.
My brother is quite
stubborn, like me.
Is he the next you?
We wouldn't be
in this predicament
if you'd surrendered, you know.
You won't be taking
this Quirk, Brother.
Because we've all chosen
to remain inside of this boy.
[SHIGARAKI]
They forced me back.
One For All screwed things up
for my master, and now for me.
What in the hell is this?
It is abject power, Tomura!
If we simply join forces
and combine our might,
we'll have the
strength to steal it.
Don't forget,
these are both people
I already put in the ground.
[ALL FOR ONE] You say you've
chosen, Little Brother?
Stop acting tough.
You must know the truth.
I've been observing this
conflict through Tomura.
Even though this boy
has a remarkable Quirk,
he can't protect his loved ones.
No. They end up hurting
themselves to protect him!
And he's allowing his body
to succumb to his anger,
like his master did.
As a result, he can't
even move right now!
He's powerless. Just watch
him cower in fear.
It was a mistake to let this
child have your ability.
He is a useless creature.
You're wrong about that.
But since you only use people,
you wouldn't understand.
You can't see what drives
this boy to keep going.
He rages for others.
He works as hard as he can
for the sake of those
who can't fight for themselves.
[FIRST WIELDER] This boy is
so focused on saving others
that he's unimaginable to you.
And we will stay by his side.
[IZUKU yells]
[IZUKU]
It wasn't stolen.
But...
[ALL FOR ONE] Since the Quirk
transplant wasn't complete,
you couldn't find enough
power to take One For All.
Do stay awake, Tomura.
Your new body must be completed.
Withdraw for now
and regain strength.
[IZUKU]
Shigaraki.
Please. Stay down.
[POLICE OFFICIAL 118B]
Direct local police
to assist the firefighters.
Everyone else help victims
of the rampaging villain.
[OPERATOR 114AA] It appears the
real Garaki has been arrested!
[POLICE OFFICIAL 118B]
That can wait until later!
I want real-time information
on the giant's location
and predicted path!
Keep field members updated.
[OPERATOR 114A]
He cut a path through Sairo City
and is now in Nabato City.
We've clocked him running
at 100 kilometers per hour.
He's moving that quickly?
[OPERATOR 114A]
Our best estimate?
If he's headed to the remains
of the Jaku Hospital,
he'll be onsite in
less than ten minutes!
[CHIKAZOKU] I've got a visual
of Tomura Shigaraki.
He's currently
fighting Endeavor.
[DABI]
Excellent. Get ready.
Get ready for what?
You're gonna help me
tear down this society
built on false heroes.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Penny for your thoughts.
[TOGA]
Huh?
[MR. COMPRESS]
I saw your face earlier.
You like those UA kids.
But they're heroes, too,
so are you okay with our plan?
[TOGA] Where do these
pros draw the line?
[TOGA] If their purpose
is to save people,
did they not think Jin
was a person?
[TOGA] The heroes didn't
hesitate to murder him.
So will they kill me
if they get the chance?
I'd like to ask them.
Izuku, of course.
And Ochaco. I think...
...once I know how
they feel, I'll be okay.
[HERO 123B] He's barreling
through Nabato City
at 100 kilometers per hour.
[HERO 123C]
That speed can't be right.
[HERO 123D]
Even if he was standing still,
he's too big and
too tough to fight.
[HERO 123B] His giant claws are
tearing through the buildings,
strewing debris everywhere.
The scale of destruction
is horrifying.
We have to evacuate areas
anywhere near his path!
[HERO 123A] If we keep
advancing at our current rate
and the villain continues
to move in a straight line,
we'll engage him in
approximately eight minutes!
The damage wrought
is already unprecedented!
We are the ones
to blame for this.
The citizens in danger here were
just going about their day!
Protect them, even if
it costs you your life.
Don't make innocent
people suffer any more
on account of our failures!
The heroes are getting closer.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Is that a satellite feed?
How ingenius.
If you're that impressed
by simple tech,
you should be embarrassed.
It's not as many as we have at
the villa, but there are plenty.
We've only gotten
as far as we have
due to fortuitous hindsight.
For now, we must continue
acting with caution.
[MR. COMPRESS gasps]
Stop, Longhair!
Zoom in there!
Are you always so impolite
when you ask for a favor?
[MR. COMPRESS] Speak of the
devils and they appear.
Toga!
Quick! Mister! You got
any a' my equipment?
[MR. COMPRESS]
Dearest ingenue,
you're making
this old man blush!
Give it! Now! [screams]
[MR. COMPRESS]
Yes, sure, fine, one moment.
[TOGA]
Later.
[MR. COMPRESS]
You can't just jump off!
It's dangerous!
[TOGA] It feels gross to be
confused and pent up like this.
It'll be way better
if I get some answers.
[MR. COMPRESS] You don't
have to do it right now.
Dabi, stop grinning
and agree with me.
[DABI]
I don't care.
Hey, stop eavesdropping and
focus on what's important.
Or you'll burn.
You bastards are impossible.
[SPINNER]
Toga! I know we're basically
just a bunch of misfits who
happened to find each other,
but you're not the only one
who's upset. I liked Twice.
[gasps]
[SPINNER]
The League was the only place
he felt like he belonged,
and the boss probably wants us
to stick together
now that he's gone.
We're experts at doing
whatever the hell we want.
But...
...make sure that you
come back to us.
Bye.
[MR. COMPRESS] You sure about
letting her run off like that?
You think she'd listen
if we tried to stop her?
I love Mr. Stainy,
and I love Izuku,
and I love Ochaco, too!
It's so amazing that I can be
all these wonderful people!
[HERO 123E] Please run
in the opposite direction
of the villain's path!
We need to keep you out
of the way of falling rubble!
[HERO 123F] There are still
people stuck indoors!
Split up and rescue them!
Don't let there be
any more victims!
Let's do our best.
[crash]
[HERO 123G]
I can see the beast now!
[HERO 123H]
So fast!
[HERO 123F]
Keep searching!
[OCHACO]
He already made his way here?
[TSUYU]
Uravity! Two civilians!
[OCHACO]
Coming.
Froppy!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
Thank you so much, you saved us!
Hope I wasn't too rough!
[TSUYU]
Are you injured?
[MAN 123A]
No. I'm fine.
[WOMAN 123A]
Thanks, girls.
[WOMAN 123B]
Please, I need a hero!
My poor husband's bedridden!
I can't get him outta
here by myself!
He's heavy, and I've
got a bad back.
Our place is right
around the corner.
Follow me!
You make sure they're safe
and I'll help her, kay?
Just be careful! I don't
want you getting hurt!
[OCHACO]
I'm good!
I have to help everyone I can!
[OCHACO]
It's just...
I can't help but think that
I could have done more.
I...
[WOMAN 123B]
I'm coming, Takeo!
[OCHACO]
That's one fast old lady!
There's no time to spare!
He must be so scared.
Our love is fueling my legs!
He'll be fine! I'll
protect him, I promise!
Oh, you're so nice!
No.
Himiko?
It's been forever, Ochaco.
[OCHACO]
Get back here!
[TOGA]
How sad.
I wanted to talk to you
and Tsu together.
How is my precious
little froggy friend? Hm?
And of course, I wanna
see Izuku real bad.
He's so cool when he gets
all bloody and beat up.
I love him like that, don't you?
[OCHACO] Sounds like she's
coming from every direction.
[TOGA] Don't worry, I love my
super-cute floaty friend, too.
In fact, I think
I want to be like you.
So be honest, Ochaco.
--[gasps]
--[TOGA laughs]
Hero. What do you
want to do to me?
Do you wanna kill me
like Jin was killed?
Will you murder me, too?
Start talking.
Exactly what are
your intentions?
[OCHACO] You pulled this whole
stunt just to ask me that?
Well it's important.
[OCHACO]
You think so?
Why don't you tell that to the
old lady whose blood you took.
You kill her to ask
a stupid question?
[TOGA]
Did you say "stupid"?
[OCHACO]
Okay, fine.
What I wanna do is save as
many people as I possibly can!
And you're in
my way, Himiko Toga!
So I'm gonna have
to stop you right now!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview.
The battle is creeping
closer to its final stages,
but more surprises await.
As Gigantomachia finally joins
Shigaraki on the battlefield,
Dabi reveals a shocking truth
to us and the world.
Next time: "Dabi's Dance."
It's a cruel,
brutal performance.
Choreographed to
showcase the depths
of his bitterness
and undying hatred.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!