When the rosary seal
over her breast is removed...
Moka's innocent self vanishes...
and her inner vampire awakens!
Now that's my big sis!
The real deal, and not
that lame, wimpy version of her!
'Scuse me...
Miss Kokoa?
I apologize for
interrupting like this.
But with all due respect,
maybe this whole analyzing
film archives thing
isn't the best strategy
on how to get the real Moka--
Who asked you?!
Why didn't I see it before!
Ko-buddy, our new plan
is to steal that rosary!
Gotcha, whee!
Ohhh...! I'm gonna
get her back!
You won't if you stay here
drooling, so let's go, whee!
Listen up, Sis!
I'm gonna rip that
rosary from your chest
and toss that stupid
thing in the trash!
Hah!
Uh...
A ski trip...!
This should be fun!
I'll say!
Um, Tsukune?
Huh?
Well, once we get
to the resort, you and I
are gonna ski together,
aren't we?
Of course...
Oh, Moka...
Oh, Tsukune...
Oh, Moka!
Oh, Tsukune!
What the hell is this?!
Whoa!
It's so pretty!
--This place is awesome!
--Wow!
So this is the ski lodge
where we're gonna be staying?
Yeah, it sure looks like it.
Hello, everyone...
We welcome you!
What, by freezing us?!
I've missed the feel of my
hometown's traditional welcome.
"Hometown"?
Oh...
You mean this place
is where you're-...?
From?
Yes.
So welcome to
Snow Woman Village.
Hello again, Tsukune.
It's good to see
the rest of you as well.
There you are...
Hi...
Mrs. Shirayuki is the reason
that we came here...!
She was able to get us
an incredible deal...!
So all of you...
Say thanks!
Don't mention it...
I just want everyone here
to have an enjoyable time...
That'll be thanks
enough for me.
And that you nab
Tsukune while you're here.
I'm way ahead of you, Mother.
We're on our home turf here,
so we've got to take advantage
of the situation.
Almost...
there...
Just a little further!
Mistress!
Over here, whee!
It looks like I might have
stumbled upon a shortcut, whee!
Great, Ko-buddy...! Nice job!
Hey!
Now listen up...
You're all free to ski wherever
you want on the course...
but no going off-course
under any circumstances, okay?
So, Rubi...
I guess you're working as
a ski instructor today?
Yup!
And it's a very
long story, right?
Um...
What is it?
My line...
I only get a few each
episode and you just-...
Uh...! Oh, Rubi, I'm so sorry!
Hey, why don't we just do it
over and take it from the top?
Okay then...! It's a long story,
but right now I'm filling in
where needed for
the school director.
These mountains sure are
pretty, aren't they?
Yeah.
Big, too...
One time on a junior high
ski trip, we'd yell at them
to hear our echoes.
Ya-ho...! Ya-ho...! Ya-ho!
Ya-hoo...! Ya-hoo...! Ya-hoo!
Wow, that's a really
long echo, isn't it?
Ya-hoo-hoo!
Tsukune, help me...!
I can't slow down at all!
I'm so sorry...! I'm
a total klutz on these skis...!
Please teach me...! I want
you to be my ski instructor,
Tsukune, 'kay...?!
Pretty please?!
Help, I can't stop!
Um...
Hey there, Tsukune...
Instead of Kurumu, will you
teach me how to ski instead?
I suck at it.
Really...? So you're
a genius at school,
but when it comes to skiing,
you're a total doofus, huh?
Well, you're one to talk!
You not only suck at school,
but on the slopes, too!
Quiet, you...!
Besides, I have an excuse;
my breasts are so big
that they get in the way.
Why don'tcha just take those
gi-normous sweater snowballs
of yours and ski on 'em?!
Hah!
You should do that yourself!
You'd slide a whole lot better
since there's nothing there!
See?
Whoa, you're right!
Um, I mean...
How dare you insult me
like that?!
So then...
Tsukune...
Who you gonna ski
down the slopes with?
With me, dummy!
No...! He's not...!
Tsukune's doing it with me!
Wrong.
Tsukune's going down with me.
She just took Tsukune!
Hey, you can't
steal him from us!
That's right,
you psycho stalker...!
And there's no way we're gonna
let you get away with this!
Well, if you think you
can catch me, then go ahead
and give it a try, girls!
Um...! Mizore...! Stop...!
This really hurts!
Yeah...
It really hurts
inside for me, too,
whenever I think
of you, Tsukune.
No, wait, that's not
what I meant!
Those are the ski runs...!
We finally made it, Ko!
Get your ass back here!
Bring Tsukune back now!
Everything went
as planned, Mother.
Great, and I've got all
the preparations in place.
As you can see.
Operation Sunrise
Snowcone can begin.
Wait a minute, Mizore...
It can't begin at all without
Tsukune, so where is he?
Oh...
He's inside here.
Tsukune!
I'm so glad I found you...!
Are you okay?
Sure am...
But it was
a really close one, though.
I finally found you!
Huh?
Yo!
Say goodbye to that
rosary on your chest,
Big Sister,
because I'm takin' it!
I take this... and
I get my sister back!
Ow-ow-ow...! Kokoa, please
...! That hurts...! Let it go!
What the...?! Why isn't
this thing coming off?!
Kokoa, stop pulling on that...
Can't you see how much
it's hurting Moka?
Spill it, you!
Just how do you get this
stupid thing off all the time?
Uh, what do you mean "how?"
It just sorta comes off.
Stop lying to me, wiseguy...!
a pathetic wimp like
you can pull it off
but a vampire can't...?! You
really think I'm stupid enough
to fall for something
like that?!
No, but like I was saying-...
don't you dare give
me any more crap...!
You better tell me right
now, mister, or else...!
Don't mess with me...!
Hey, do you even know
who you're dealing
with here...?
I'm the real Moka Akashiya's
younger sister...!
The name's Kokoa Shuzen,
idiot...! get on your knees...!
kneel before Kokoa...!
kneel before Kokoa...
It's an avalanche!
Tsukune...! Where are
you...! Can you hear me...?
I've just gotta find you, and
if you're freezing right now,
don't worry; I'll warm you up
tonight in ways that only
a snow woman can!
Kokoa...?! Tsukune?!
Oh, no...! Not down there!
Let them be alright!
Kokoa...! Tsukune!
Relaxing in a hot spring
in the falling snow...
Isn't it the most
romantic thing?
You sound...
just like a little kid!
And you sound
just like an old lady.
I love celebrating the end
of a long day with a cold beer!
I wouldn't know because I'm
under the legal drinking age,
so I'm gonna
celebrate with juice.
That stalker skank may
have gotten the jump on us
back there and made
off with Tsukune...
But you and me are gonna kick
the ice cubes out of her!
So who's this stalker
skank you just mentioned?
Tell me, how's the
water feeling tonight?
Well, to be honest with
you, Mrs. Shirayuki,
it was perfect until
a few seconds ago.
Yeah, now it's really cold.
Oh...
Hey...!
what're you looking at?!
Stop, you're embarrassing me!
Mother...! There's
a big problem!
Oh, Mizore...
You came at the perfect time.
You win head and shoulders
over these girls when
it comes to delicate,
porcelain-like skin.
We don't have time
for that nonsense right now!
Quick, we need
everybody's help!
But why, Moka?
Because of Tsukune and Kokoa!
They got caught in an
avalanche and fell to
the bottom of a ravine!
Then let's go and get
'em out of there!
But not naked, okay?!
Take...
that!
Well, that's enough for today.
Wait, come back...!
I can still keep fighting!
Let's do this, Sis!
Don't leave!
You shouldn't fight again
until that bruise is healed.
See you later...
'Kay, Kokoa?
But Sis...
I promise I'm gonna get way,
way stronger than this!
So just wait until I do, okay?
Just wait Sis...
Um, Kokoa?
You're awake...! I was
starting to get worried!
Where the hell are we?!
In a cave...
At the bottom of a ravine.
Oh, dammit, this is just
great...! It would happen
right when I almost got
her back! where is she?!
You can't go out there!
When I finally
came to in here...
It was already
snowing like crazy.
Well, who cares?!
It's only snow!
Kokoa!
I've gotta get that rosary so
I can get my sister back...!
I've just gotta!
This storm's too strong; we've
gotta get back to the cave!
What was that?!
Crap...
It sounded...
Like a monster...
C'mon, Kokoa...
We need to get back.
Hey, why's your hand on me?!
To protect you!
Uh...! Oh... well Okay.
Now nobody do anything
without at least
one other person there,
and don't go near
any dangerous spots
on your own, okay?
Right!
Search and Rescue Team...
Let's do it!
Go!
You guys just
stay here and wait.
And don't you worry;
once we find Tsukune,
we'll be sure to give him the
special hands-on attention
that only we can provide.
Uh-oh...
I better hurry up
and find him first then!
Hey, don't touch me...!
Go find someplace else to sit!
Oh, I'm sorry...
It's just kind of tight
in here, you know?
Geez!
Um, excuse me, Kokoa...
Yeah, what?
I've been wondering...
Why do you hate me?
Huh?
Honestly...
I was hoping that you and
I would have become friends
by now but that
hasn't happened.
What, are you crazy
or something...?
Become friends with you?
I don't think so!
But why not?
You mean you
really don't know why?
Huh?
Because Moka always
gives you everything!
Everything?
What do you mean?
You, a human,
can take her rosary off,
but I can't even
make it budge.
I also heard that my
sister gave you some
of her vampire blood once.
Is that story really true?
Yeah...
But she had a good reason...
It's because...
I would have died...
see?
But why?
Hm?
I said "why?!"...
Why is it always you,
but never me?!
Kokoa?
Somehow you get to
take off her rosary...!
And she winds up
giving you her blood!
It's always you and never me!
Uh...
So why is it...?
How come I'm not good enough
for her but you are?
Kokoa, it'll be okay...
Don't you dare touch me!
You think if
you're nice to me...
I'll be just like
the others...
That I'll fawn all over you like
the rest of your dumb harem!
Well, I'm sorry to tell you...
That it's never...
ever gonna happen!
There's no way in hell I'd
ever fall for a jerk like you!
Kokoa...
That's not what I'm after.
Someday soon...
I'm gonna be
together with her again...
And...
go home...
we'll go back to the house...
where we used to live...
Kokoa?!
So...
cold.
I've gotta get you warmed up.
Hold on, Kokoa.
Oh, no...! Miss Kokoa...
where are you...?!
Can you hear me, whee?!
Uh-oh...! That sounds scary...!
I hope it's not headed
in Miss Kokoa's
direction, whee!
Oh, crap, whee!
It's getting closer!
An Abominable Snowman?!
Grargh rargh...
Rargh rargh rargh.
Get away!
I won't let you hurt her,
you big furry freak!
Are you alright, Tsukune?!
Mizore!
I'll take care of him;
get out of there!
But-...!
Trust me, just go...!
I couldn't live with myself
if I let something happen
to you in my hometown!
And besides...
You've got someone in there
who needs help, don't you?!
Yeah...
I guess you're right.
Thanks!
Don't you lay
a finger on my Tsukune!
Holy crap...
He strong!
I hope we lost him!
Tsukune!
Moka, it's you!
Oh, Tsukune!
Oh, Moka!
Moka!
Tsukune!
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Tsukune.
Grargh...! Grargh rargh
rargh rargh rargh!
You need to learn
your place!
This episode's
showdown took-...
Ah, who cares!
Miss Kokoa, whee!
Tsukune's alive!
Sorry it took
so long to get here!
Is everybody okay?!
We will be...
As soon as we
get Kokoa warmed up.
Moka's rosary...!
It's ... mine!
Kokoa, wait!
I'm taking it...
so I can...
keep...
big sis.
Hold on, 'kay...?
We'll get you to the lodge.
Look, I'm sorry
to tell you this, Kokoa...
But this rosary of mine...
I can't just leave it off
and be without the seal.
But why...
Why not?
See you later...
'Kay, Kokoa?
Moka, no...
Um, Moka, are you alright?
Somebody grab her!
I'm sure you did
your best, Mizore.
Uh, Mother...
Yeah, I did.
Even so, I guess it
wasn't enough against
such a formidable
opponent as this one...
Was it?
Guess not...
But eventually, I am gonna
beat her one of these days.
Forget that stuff...!
What was that snow beast?!
Yeah, with dangerous
things like that around...
How could you
let us go skiing?!
Dangerous...? I can assure you
there are no dangerous beasts
in this valley.
Huh?!
Grargh rargh!
Rargh rargh rargh
rargh rargh rargh!
Tsukune, you stay back!
We'll take care
of this monster!
We'll make a rug
out of his hide!
Wait, now that I get a better
look at him, he looks familiar.
Hey, that yeti is my father.
Huh?!
What...?! You mean that thing...
is your daddy?!
Well, if that information
disturbs you so much, Tsukune...
How about this?
Thanks...
but that's okay Mrs. Shirayuki!
So that yeti...
and her mom...
They did it?!
Yeah, I guess they did!
Uh-huh!
Grargh...! Rargh...!
Rargh rargh...! Mrargh!
Oh, is that so...? He says
that he found some lost skiers,
but when he tried to help,
one of them called him
a big furry freak and ran.
What...?! Crap...
Oh...
I'm sorry, sir...!
I'm just not fluent in Yeti!
Grargh rargh, mrargh
rargh rargh rargh rargh.
Don't worry, Tsukune...
My father says that he
won't hold that against you...
And besides, in the middle
of that blizzard...
his very own daughter
didn't even recognize him
at first glance.
Oh, Mizore...
You're such a goofball,
dear...! You might have
grown up, but you're still
our silly little girl!
Mother, you're
embarrassing me!
Thank you so much
for having us!
And we're sorry, Mr. Shirayeti,
I mean, Shirayuki!
Bye, everyone!
Come back again
sometime, okay?
But next time it'll be
for an engagement party!
Brye-brye!
Darling, don't you think
it's about time you took
that ridiculous suit off?
So, That Tsukune Aono boy...
Tell me...
Don't you think he'd make
a terrific son-in-law
for both you and I, sweetie?
You know, I still can't
get over the fact that
Kokoa ran off this morning...
With that fever...
I'm really hoping
that she's okay.
Somehow I get the
feeling she's just fine.
Huh?
I wonder if Kokoa and
I will ever be good friends
like normal sisters should be?
I hope so...
I hope that Kokoa
and I can become closer...!
Kokoa?!
No way, come on, forget that
bitey little brat, Tsukune...!
Pick me...! 'Kay?!
Nuh-uh...! I'm the love
of his life, so back off!
There's only one person on this
bus that he's in love with...
And that person is me...! Plus
he's already been to meet
my parents and everything!
I'm the love of his life...!
Not the three of you...!
I love, love, Tsukune
so much...! You'll see!
I've had about as much
love as I can take!
Kurumu, come look!
Some totally hot pretty boy
just transferred to our school
Yeah, who cares!
We've already got
a pretty boy: Tsukune!
But this guy's weird!
We still need to make him
feel welcome, though...
Next time: "Pretty Boy and
a Vampire" and another!