The academy I was
approaching was
an enigma shrouded
in secrecy...
But even so,
I refused to be afraid...
Scaredy-cat...! Get Up...!
Where's all that
bravado you just had?!
Oh, you're going to
visit Tsukune's school?
That's right!
Well, in that case,
I'll make some of
Tsukune's favorite rice balls.
You don't mind bringing
them to him, do you, Kyoko?
This isn't a social visit!
Uh...
Tsukune's friends from
school had weird powers;
he might be in danger!
Kyoko, we've already
had this conversation.
You must have just dreamed that
those girls had strange powers.
I'm sure of what I saw, Auntie!
And that's why I'm
got to get to the bottom
of things here at
this weird school!
Move it!
Get outta my way now!
Huh?!
Yee-owch!
Hey, what the
hell were you doin'
just standin' there
like an idiot?!
We don't have
time for this, whee!
Yeah...
You're right!
We just got our hands
on a secret weapon
that's gonna bring
my big sister back!
Wait, was that a bat talking
to that girl just now...?!
And speaking of which,
I'm pretty sure that I've
seen her somewhere before...
Those bells!
I'd better get going!
♪ opening song ♪
So this is Yokai Academy...?
I thought it would be modern,
but it looks more
like a gothic building
out of the Middle Ages!
What the--?
Tsukune!
Hey, wait!
Tsuki!
--Anyway, like I was saying...
--Tsuki!
Hey, there, cous-...!
Tsukune!
Take a look at this!
I'm wearing it because I
heard this maid outfit is all
the rage with girls
in the human world...!
And I'd be happy to serve
you any way at any time...
My incredibly sexy master!
No, I'm the only one who's
gonna be serving Tsuku--...!
No, I am.
It's those same girls again...!
I thought there was
something strange about
them when we first met,
and this confirms it...!
Why are all of
them fawning over
Tsukune like that
in the hallway...?!
What kind of school
would allow that?!
Oh, my God, Yokai Academy
must be some kind
of training school for
workers in the sex trade!
It has to be, because that's the
only explanation why all those
cute girls would be
throwing themselves
at Tsukune like that!
Fight...!
Alright, come on,
you guys, calm down.
--There's no reason to fight.
--We're all friends here...
I'm tired of you and your
gi-normous jugs
getting in my way!
This situation is
just way too weird...
Maybe I should forget this
place and these rice balls
and just leave.
You wouldn't happen to be
my new master would you?
Don't call me master
I'm not one of those
tramps over there...
But...
If I was dressed in
one of those maid outfits,
I'd be way cuter than any
of those hookers in training!
Um, Master?
What?!
A mirror...? How did Auntie's
rice balls turn into a mirror?!
What's this?
Some of the yummiest
Rice balls I've ever had, whee!
That's not the damn point!
So nice to meet you...!
My name is Lilith,
and I'm the spirit
of this mirror...
And I'm guessing that you
must be my new master, right?
This is too freaky;
it's like something
out of a scary
movie or a TV show!
That's it!
That must be what's
going on here!
I'm getting punk'd on some
crazy hidden-camera
show, aren't I?!
Huh?
But how'd they
pull this effect off?
It looks way too
real to be a prop.
I wonder if it's
some kind of CGI?
Um...
Oh, I see, Master,
you're just a regular human,
so you probably haven't seen
too many monsters before.
"Monsters?!"
That's pretty funny.
Well, I guess this is obviously
a comedy show, isn't it?
I'm being serious;
can't you tell that I'm real...?
Great, my new master's
a total moron!
Say hi to Dracula and
Frankenstein for me...
But I've gotta admit, this
is a pretty funny idea...
Watch, I'll prove
this isn't a joke!
Look, I just got my hands
on another hot video of Moka!
Alright!
Way to go!
Um, excuse me, guys?!
Huh?
You know, I've got a
thing for small chicks...
I don't, but I could
learn to have one...
Uh... Thanks,
but do you guys think you could
do me a teensy favor and
look into this mirror?
Huh?
What the hell just happened?!
It changed us into
our monster forms!
And on campus!
We're gonna get suspended!
See, look at those guys.
They were making
themselves appear human,
but they're actually monsters.
But this mirror of mine here
shows a monster's true nature,
and once they
look inside of it,
their transformation
magic undoes itself.
Those are best
special effects ever!
So the kids only dress
up like monsters here...!
But even so,
that only makes this school
even more suspicious to me...!
There's still something really
weird about this place!
My cousin Tsuki goes to
this school, so I don't care
what it takes,
I've gotta get to the
bottom of what
this joint's about!
Okay then...
So that's what you
wish for, eh, Master...?
Well, your wish is my command.
Huh?
This stuff weighs a ton!
Why did you have to buy
so many freaking ingredients
anyway, Kurumu?
Because I'm gonna bake
Tsukune a huge cake
that's gonna be yummy-wummy
for his tummy-tummy!
Geez...
Huh?!
Huh...?!
Why's everybody screaming?
Who or what is that?!
Dunno, I've never
seen her before!
Sorry to interrupt, but
I need you to show the world
what hideous monsters
the both of you really are!
Kurumu and Yukari are late;
I wonder where they're at?
Oh, they told me that they were
both gonna go shopping first.
'Kay...
I guess that just
leaves Mizore then.
I feel like we're
forgetting someone else,
but I don't know
who that might be...
Careful, Moka!
Here, let me get that for you!
It's okay; I've got it.
Hold on, Moka!
Oh no, you poor thing;
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
You're actually
really light, Moka.
Tsukune, I--...!
Thank you very much.
Tsukune?
Yes, Moka?
You smell good...
Uh...
Moka, no, wait!
Tsukune...!
Sorry to interrupt!
What the?!
Rubi?!
What's with that outfit?!
It's a long story, but the
Director assigned me
to serve on academy
patrol detail today!
But that's not as
important as the favor
I need to ask of the
Newspaper Club!
Huh?
You see, a very rare and
important item has been
stolen from the Director's
treasure store and I--
Panties!
Ooh, yeah!
Woo, Moka's wearin'
white ones today!
Gin, please stop doing that!
Hey, Ginei...
You didn't happen
to look into a
strange gold mirror
just now, did you?
If I say yes, will you show
me your panties, too?!
I warned you,...!
No more of this...!
Enough!
Oh, no, what'd I just do?!
Please, don't be dead,!
Does this mean--...?!
Uh, Rubi?!
Just as I feared,
it looks like we're too late.
What the heck's going on here?!
Eat my Twirling Umbrella Attack!
Wait a minute; why's everybody
in their monster forms?!
Did they all decide
to break the rules?!
No, they looked
in Lilith's mirror.
It's a legendary mirror that
emits a very special light...
When monsters view that light,
everything about them
is completely laid bare.
Their true form
and their true nature.
Unfortunately, someone's
made off with that mirror!
Any idea who it was?
According to eyewitnesses, the
thief had orange hair tied into
pigtails on the sides,
knee-high socks,
and had a really ugly bat
companion with her, too...
That's all that we have.
Doesn't that sound
just like someone
that you and I know, Moka?
At any rate, we've gotta get
that mirror back immediately!
If we can't contain this flood
of monster energy that's
been unleashed, then the
great barrier that surrounds
Yokai Academy could be
very well be annihilated!
Uhh...
It even got Miss Nekonome!
I'm gonna go look
for the others!
Please be careful!
Right...
I understand.
Thank you...
There's been a
strange development.
Lilith's Mirror has
just been spotted,
but it's in the hands
of a human girl.
Apparently, she wandered
onto campus somehow.
Oh wait, did you just
say a human girl?!
I know it's nuts but
everything's way
too realistic to
be special effects...!
They don't even make
costumes as big as
some of the things I've
seen wandering around...!
And not to mention
the fact that everyone
she shows that mirror
to transforms...
...and that means
that every student
at this school must be a...
muh--...!
Oh, come on, what's the problem?
Isn't this exactly what
you wished for, Master...?
Don't you remember...?
Getting to the bottom of
what this school's about?
Actually, you've
done enough, Lilith.
Maybe we should stop now.
No, Master.
Huh?
There's plenty more
to get to the bottom of...
If you live long
enough to see it!
What's this?
It smells like the scent
of a delicious human girl.
Huh?
What the?
That must be the mirror
that Rubi mentioned!
Hey, Tsukune...
Oh, Kurumu...! I'm so
glad to see you're oka--...
Kurumu?
Tsukune...
I don't know why, but I
feel so hot all of a sudden...
You don't mind if
I take this off, do you?
Tsukune, I can't
tell you how much
I love the feeling
of being with you!
Is that so...?! Well, I can't
tell you how much I love
the feeling of your big,
bouncy, bodacious boobs!
Back off, you slut!
If you want to squeeze some
boobs, try mine instead!
Forget Kurumu and
her massive milk jugs!
My tiny, developing
ones are like...
Yukari, we're veering
dangerously close
to kiddie porn
territory...! Uh?!
Well, if it's boobs you
want, I've got some nice,
icy peaks of my own...
They're like two snow-white
mounds of heaven with
little pink cherries on top...
I love cherries!
I want cherries!
Yummy little cherries!
Gimme your cherries now!
Get away from my guy!
Oh, man, this is really bad!
The magic from that
mirror must be making
all of them act
berserk like this!
Tsukune, are you alright?!
Uh... Oh thank God! Someone
who's not been affected.
What would you like
me to do to or for you?
Huh?!
I want you to
command me, Tsukune.
Please, I'll do anything
that you ask of me...
That mirror's turned all of you
into a bunch of sex fiends!
Please, give me a command now.
Uh...
Um...
A command...?
Okay, why don't you tell
me what happened to Moka!
As you command.
The two of us ran off
together trying to chase
down Lilith's Mirror, but at
some point, we got separated.
If Moka were to look
into that mirror,
which side of her would be
revealed to be her true nature?
Don't you have another
command for me yet?
Uh...
Tsukune!
There's nothing quite like the
taste of a delicious human...
Now...
...it's...
...time...
...to...
...feast.
No...! Somebody help!
You get away from her!
Is that you, Kyoko?!
Moka?!
I thought it was!
I'm so glad you're alright!
No, stay away...!
I know what you are!
You're a monster like everybody
else at this place, aren't you?!
Uh...
If you are, then
I don't want you coming
anywhere near me, Moka...!
There's no way I could ever
trust you after
what you've done!
You made us think
you were a human,
but I know what you are now!
Do you think I'm gonna
let my cousin stay at a
place like this and with
monsters like you?!
No way!
I'm taking Tsuki home with me!
No, Kyoko, please don't!
Well, of all the people to
run into Moka Akashiya,
the uppity student who came
between me and Tsukune.
Is that Lilith's Mirror?
You caught me off guard
last year, but this time I've
brought along some
teacher's pets that are
not only obedient,
but hungry, too!
Kyoko?!
If I can get you to it, can you
grab that mirror over there?!
Huh?!
What?!
Are you insane, Moka...?!
Even if there was some way we
could get past those things...
I still wouldn't trust
you at all because
you're one of those
monsters, too!
You're right!
I am a monster that's
posing as a human, Kyoko...
So I really can't blame you
for not believing a word I say.
But listen...
You and I both have
something in common.
Huh?!
I believe in Tsukune
just like you do.
Yes, it's true that
I'm a monster...
But as far as Tsukune goes,
I trust him with all my heart!
And right now, Kyoko, I need you
to trust me so we can stop this
madness and save
Tsukune before it's too late!
Come with me, Kyoko!
You've gotta trust me on this!
Save the human girl for me!
Ahhh!
I can't believe I'm doing this!
Got it!
No, stop it!
Let me go!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Now, Kyoko!
The mirror!
Right here!
Master?!
Alright, now it's my turn!
Do your thing, mirror!
I've just about had
it with you two!
Pi r squared, boys!
Moka, hurry up!
So she used the mirror to
bring me out without having
to take off the rosary;
I've gotta admit
that my other self
is pretty clever.
You, however, are pretty stupid.
Just what gives you to
right to go around
exposing people's true natures?
This does!
You...
it can't be...
Well, well...
I guess this is the
first chance we've ever
had to meet face-to-face
now, isn't it?
Apparently, you have
two true natures,
and they were both
brought out by my mirror!
This is too weird!
I...
...feel weak all of a sudden...
Just stay down and
wait this one out...
I'll take care of the
pipsqueak here.
No, wait!
You're not the only ones who can
transform into something else!
You used the mirror on yourself
to unlock your own powers,
but what are you?
A powerful and sacred
Shinto spirit
who's the soul of a
treasured antique item!
Not only that, but you'll
find me impossible to beat!
How could such a
weak attack stop me?!
It's because the two of you
always shared a single body,
and when you split it up, your
strength halved as well, moron!
No, come back!
We need to recombine
our bodies!
Stay out of this!
But...!
Listen up Moka, you said you
trusted Tsukune, didn't you?
You can trust Tsukune all that
you want, but you're not
strong enough to protect him
on your own now, are you?
Let's cut the crap
and get on with it!
Given your state,
even a little pipsqueak
like me can defeat
a vampire, huh?!
My body feels so heavy...
We're not gonna let that happen!
We're here, Moka...!
Wait, what the hell?!
Both Mokas together?!
Tsukune!
Glad you could make it!
Yeah, so am I, 'Cuz!
What the?!
Kyoko?!
What are you doing here?!
Impossible!
How did you manage to break
free from the mirror's power?!
Sorry to disappoint
you, Tinkerbell,
but my boyfriend freed us...!
His name's Tsukune Aono!
What?!
Whoa, Tsuki saved you guys?!
How'd you do it?
Oh, Tsukune!
You can always count on me!
I'll take such good
of you Tsukune...
Come on, you've
gotta pick one of us
to be a replacement for Moka.
Huh?
--Please pick me!
I can't.
--Huh?!
--Why?!
Because, honestly, none of you
could ever replace Moka.
Please, I'd be much
better than Moka
because I love you
more than she does!
And I feel the same
way about all of you.
Uh?!
Just like Moka,
no one in the world
could ever replace any of you.
It was nothing...
Really, it was no big deal...
You bastard!
I guess the light
wasn't strong enough!
Well, in that case, I'll just
have to use a stronger one!
That's not gonna work this time!
This way we don't hafta
look into the mirror at all!
Clever huh? I thought it up
and call it the
Yahoo-hoo-hoo blindfold!
That name really sucks, Kurumu.
Yeah, well so do you...! You
guys ready to do this thing?!
Ready!
Yeah, let's do it!
Bring it!
I shoulda asked this before...
...how do we take her
down if we can't see her?
--Huh?!
Crap...!
That's a good question!
Oh...
...we never discussed
anything past the blindfolds.
What a bunch of idiots...!
You won't even see the
killing blow coming!
Left thirty degrees!
Distance ten meters!
Right...! Thanks!
I think that it's
well past time...
...for you to learn your place!
Yeah!
Why was learning
my place so painful...
Alright, we did it!
We defeated the bad
guy instead of Moka.
I didn't need
their help, Tsukune.
Moka?!
Are you okay?!
Are you hurt?!
I'm fine thanks to you.
Huh?
Uh...
Thanks so much
for trusting me...
That was a brave
thing for you to do.
Uh...
Oh, come on, you
don't have to thank me.
I really didn't
do anything at all.
Hey, Big Sister!
Now that the real you is back,
I'm never gonna let you go!
Great, another little
pest to deal with!
If we wrap it back up in
this cloth, Lilith's Mirror
should be rendered
completely ineffective.
Then let's hurry and get back
into the same body again.
What?!
Big Sis!
Hold on!
I don't understand what
you said back there...
Tell me!
You'll have to figure
that out on your own.
Uh...!
Go on, do it!
Okay, right!
No, please wait!
Huh?
What happened...?!
Pi r squared!
Meow?
The real Moka's
gone now, isn't she?
Why'd you have
to screw up my plan?!
"Your plan?" I guess that
makes you the thief
who stole Lilith's
Mirror, doesn't it?
Me and my big mouth!
You're going straight to
the secret underground
detention hall, where you can
think about what you've done.
Man, what a day.
Um, hey, Tsuki?
Uh!
Look, Kyoko, I can
explain all the
crazy stuff you saw
here, I swear!
Just tell me this...
Do you like going to
this school, Tsuki?
Uh...
You heard me...
Do you like going
to this school?
Yeah...
Of course, I do.
I've got so many wonderful
friends here that
I wouldn't want to go to
school anywhere else!
Okay then.
Huh?!
If you're happy here,
then this place's
secret is safe with me...
And if you trust them, then I
guess I trust your friends, too.
Um, sorry, but just to
set the record straight,
they're the friends
and I'm the girlfriend...
Isn't that correct, Tsukune?
No, it's not, and it never
will be, you big, smelly sow...!
Sorry, Lilith's Mirror
must still be affecting me!
Well my hand's
affected by spank-itis!
That was actually an
insult to all sows.
What did you just say?!
Whoa, guys, come on, calm down,
please! Kurumu, stop spanking!
I wonder if it really is
like the other me said...?
That I'm not strong enough on
my own to keep Tsukune safe.
You can trust Tsukune all that
you want, but you're not
strong enough to protect him
on your own now, are you?
The fact that she'd even
say something like that...
That must mean...
...that the other me
feels the same way!
She must love Tsukune, too.
Hey, what are you, a gigolo?!
--Tsukune... what's going on?!
Don't let that
be what I think it is!
No, it's happening even
faster than we feared!
Look up there!
Huh?!
No, the great barrier!
♪ closing song ♪
Oh, no, the great
barrier's breaking up!
Leave it to me, meow!
Who are you?!
Stand back!
Kitty jump...!
Shoot, I didn't mean to
trip and fall down, meow.
Uh, right...
Next time: "Holy Seal and
a Vampire" and another!