Hey there, Tsukune.
Oh, Moka.
Oh... Tsuku... ne...
Oh, Moka...
Um, Tsukune?
Yes, Moka?
Do you wanna
suck my blood again?
No...
not today...
I want something
else instead...
Huh?
Um...
are you sure about this, Moka?
As long as it's...
with you.
Trying to steal a kiss
from me takes some nerve...
I think it's time that you...
...learned your place!
Oh, crap!
Look at the time!
If I don't get a move-on,
I'm gonna miss the bus!
Hey, Mom, I've
gotta go right now!
Wait, what about breakfast?
I'll eat when I get there!
Just make sure you come home
for summer this year!
Also, I hope that you packed
plenty of clean underwear...!
Bye, sweetie!
Hey, Tsuki!
How long has it been, cousin?!
Sorry, Kyoko!
I've gotta go!
Geez...! Thanks so much
for the warm welcome, cuz!
My name's Tsukune Aono,
and I'm seventeen years old...
As of today,
I'm a high school junior...
Our spring break just ended,
and I'm about to begin another
year at Yokai Academy.
Hey, kid?
Huh?
It's been a year now.
You gotten used to it yet?
Yep... I guess so.
Yokai Academy is a school
of monsters, by monsters,
and for monsters.
If you can blend in there,
you're no ordinary guy.
Still, watch your back.
Why?
'Cause just when you think
you've got it all figured out,
that's usually when
things go to hell.
You have to pass through
this secret barrier to reach
my school, Yokai Academy.
There was this
mix-up, you see...
That's how I ended up enrolling
in this scary-ass school
in the first place.
I decided to stay, though...
And despite its scariness,
there's no other school
I'd rather attend
than this one.
I've got friends here,
and this is the only place
we can be together.
Speaking of friends,
isn't this the exact spot
where I first met Moka?
That's a bike...!
Alright, maybe it's Moka!
Ow...
Here, let me give you a hand...
I'm so sorry!
Whoa, she's so cute!
Hey...!
Stop groping me, you creep!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to!
I was just-...!
Perv...!
You felt me up!
By accident...
Wait...
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but you smell really good!
You were gonna grope me again!
No...! I swear
I wasn't going to!
Hmph...!
Drop dead...!
Pervert!
It's only been a couple
of weeks, but it feels like
I've been gone for ages!
Wonder what everyone's up to?
Oh!
They're so incredible!
They're so billowy and bouncy!
I guess it's true about
bigger breasts being better!
Dunno, Yukari's tiny ones
are pretty cute, too!
Hey what the hell are
you doing your all ...girls!
Hey...! Nothing can
keep me from you Tsukune.
Yes, Ya-hoo-hoo...!
Tsukune!
Hey, you didn't
forget about me, did you?!
Oh, I've missed you so bad!
You're gonna tell me you're glad
to see me again, too, right?!
I would if I could breathe...
Chill out.
It'll be a cold day in hell
before I let you sink
your claws into my Tsukune,
you big-boobed bimbo.
Oh, yeah, you frozen freak...?
He's my Tsukune,
and I'm gonna shred you
into ice cubes if
you come near him!
Bring it on then, Kurumu.
There's only one woman
for Tsukune and that's me,
his little popsicle!
First day of school
and there's already a fight
between the succubus
and the snow woman!
Stop it!
Please, this is no way
to kick off a new school year!
Moka!
Tsukune!
What?
Hmm.
I really missed you...
Moka.
I missed you, too...
Tsukune.
Moka?!
It's been so long since I...
Wait a minute...
Don't tell me.
I can't help what I am...
And what that is is a vampire!
Guess I'm lucky
the other girl didn't do this!
What do you mean "other girl"?
Hey, that's the
legendary Moka Akashiya!
She's so cool!
We're crazy about you, Moka!
So, I guess all of you
are freshmen, huh?
Yeah!
We're thrilled to be here!
We couldn't wait to attend
Yokai Academy, and finally meet
the awesome and sexy
older students we've heard
so much about!
Like Yukari Sendo, who's young
and tiny but totally smart!
And Kurumu Kurono, the bombshell
with the ballistic bazongas!
And also the literally cool
ice queen, Mizore Shirayuki!
But there's one girl
who's even prettier, classier,
and smarter than
that bevy of beauties!
You, the legendary
Moka Akashiya!
Wait! Quit it!
What are you doing?!
No, stop, please
don't touch me there!
What the hell's
with those freshmen...?!
One minute they're pawing
all over me and then
they're going gaga over Moka!
Um, hey, are you alright?
Tsukune?
Hello?
Ya-hoo-hoo!
I'm in the same
class with Tsukune;
it'll be just like
last year again!
Well, not exactly, because
this year I get to be in
the same homeroom
as all of you!
It's so great that
we're all together at last!
'Morning, students!
I hope you had
an enjoyable break!
Wha?!
Miss Nekonome's our homeroom
teacher this year, too?!
That's right, I sure am!
Welcome back to
Yokai Academy, everyone!
Well, let me hear it, class...
Are we gonna have the best
school year ever or what?!
Well hello again, folks!
That concludes all the
explanatory set-up for
any idiot who hasn't watched
the first season whee -...!
Stop, I can't breathe!
If you kill me, who's gonna...
Now that that's out of the way,
I've got another job for you.
What are you doing here?
Wow, this place is a madhouse.
Maybe things'll calm down
after the entrance ceremony
for all the new students.
Yeah.
What are these?!
I got some, too!
Maybe they're fan letters
from those new girls you met.
Yeah, I bet you're right.
Huh, it looks like
I got some, too.
What's it say?
"Greetings! Dear Miss
Mizore... You and I have
a great deal in common. In other
words, I'm a stalker, too.
How 'bout we both spy on each
other from afar sometime...?
Stalk ya later."
I bet you've got
some too, Moka.
I doubt it, but I'll
check. Agh...!
Woh, Moka?
These are all
from Moka's fans?!
Alright, way to go, Moka!
I don't know how I'm supposed
to read all these letters...
That sure is one
weird-looking envelope.
Well, I'm sure the person who
wrote it wanted it to stand out
a bit; you know, so that
Moka would notice it
out of all of the others?
it... says...
"To my dearest and most
beloved Moka Akashiya...
Not a single day goes
by where you are not
in my thoughts or the
center of my attention."
Wow, it sounds like
she's a really big fan!
Yeah, especially if she's
thinking about you that much!
"And now, at long last... I'm
finally getting the opportunity
to meet you in person...
I'm bursting with excitement
at the thought of it."
Aw, she writes the sweetest
things, doesn't she?
Of course; she's a
pure-hearted girl, unlike you.
What was that?!
"And at the upcoming entrance
ceremony for new students..."
"I'm going to rush to
your side... and that's when
I'm going to end your life."
Hey, she said she's
gonna end your life...
Isn't that cute?
What?!
It's gonna be okay, Moka.
I'm sure that letter
was just a prank.
But still...
I'm scared...
I really am.
Well, Kurumu and I are
gonna go try to recruit
some new members
for the Newspaper Club.
In that case, I'll go, too.
No, it's okay
don't worry about it
After getting that creepy
letter, I'm sure you're not
feeling up to doing
anything right now.
Hey, where's our
club president?
Shouldn't Gin be involved
with the recruiting?
He's probably somewhere
taking dirty pictures
of unsuspecting girls...!
Gross!
So this is the
school dorm, huh?
It looks like
a nice and roomy place!
I'm sure that we're all
gonna have tons of fun here!
Slim pickin's so far...
I'm not seein many
sexy babes to shoot yet.
Whoa, look at those
knee socks...!
Those are gonna make for
some nice glossy pics...!
That's no ordinary
chick, no way.
Hey, you...!
Want an eyeful?!
I'll give you one!
No, wait!
I really should be helping
the girls with the recruiting.
No, like Yukari said, you
don't need to worry about
that right now...
But if it makes you feel
any better, I'll stop by
later and help them out.
Hey there...!
Tsukune!
Moka!
Rubi?!
Hey, what are you doing here?
It's a long story...
But right now, I'm working for
The Director and helping out
wherever there's a need.
Um...
Isn't that the same thing
you said to Moka last time?
Yes...
But it is a long story.
Whoa, check it out, Moka.
Those look really
good, don't they?
Wow, they sure do!
What's one doing here?!
"Dearest Moka... At long
last I've arrived here
at Yokai Academy... I'm
looking forward to tomorrow's
entrance ceremony...
Because that's the day that
I'm going to end your
life once and for all...
Heh heh heh."
Hey, Rubi...!
Did you happen
to see who dropped
this bat-shaped letter here?!
See...
There was so much
that happened...
So much so that I can't
do it any justice.
Join the Baseball Club!
Hey, guys, come and join us
in the Swimming Club...!
Our president's
a total hottie...!
She smells like fish, though!
Ya like ghosts...?!
Come take pictures of 'em
in the Photo Club!
Hi, we're the Newspaper Club!
Please take a free copy... here
Oh, cool, I'll take one then.
Whoa...
This looks really professional.
Ya know, this might be
a club worth joining.
Hey, did you hear that?
I think we're a hit!
Ya-hoo-hoo...!
At this rate, we'll probably
recruit a whole bunch
of new members!
What's with this stupid paper?
Huh?
Who wrote it,
kindergarteners...?
Talk about lame.
I'll show you lame, you
freshman brat; get back here!
Um, excuse me...
Your paper...
--Could I have a copy?
--Me, too!
Yes, please, help yourselves,
there's plenty of copies
to go around.
Hey! Where'd that freshman go?!
I should be helping.
No...
You need to take it easy...
'Kay, Moka?
Tsukune...! Your back!
Huh?
How long has this been here?!
"Dearest Moka...
It's almost time...
I'm already on campus
and I'm waiting nearby."
"The entrance ceremony...
That day, my beloved Moka...
...will be your last one alive."
Nooo!
Moka!
I feel bad for her...
Poor Moka...
She was scared
out of her mind.
Moka...
Tsukune!
Oh, Moka...
Tsukune...
Oh, Tsukune...
I really enjoy spying
on you every night
before I hit the sack.
Hmm?
I wonder which room it is?
Hey, you over there.
Just who the hell are you?
Look, I don't know who it is
that you're spying on...
but you really shouldn't be
sneaking around out here
like that.
Yeah, well what are you doing?!
Me? Well, I...
You see... I was trying
to look at this cute guy
that I have a thing for.
Hah...!
Guess that makes you a
stalker then, doesn't it...?
You sicko!
Whoever you are,
you just got on my bad side!
See yah!
Whoa, I can't believe
she dodged my attack...!
Good morning, Moka.
Oh, thanks a lot, but
I really don't know what's
so good about it, Tsukune...
Uh...! you alright...?!
Is something wrong?!
Holy crap!
When did you get all those?!
They arrived last night...
Excuse me, Moka?
Um, yes?
This just came for you.
I think it's a
letter or something.
Huh?
Moka, you home?
Yes, coming!
Here, this is yours.
It was just delivered for you.
Huh?!
Moka?
Not again!
This letter just arrived
for you via special delivery.
It was like that all night...
A new one showed up
every ten minutes.
I hardly got any sleep...
This is nuts!
Oh, Tsukune...!
What am I gonna do?!
I promise everything's
gonna be okay, Moka.
Don't worry;
no matter what happens,
I will find a way
to protect you!
The entrance ceremony's
about to take place...
This is when the letter-writer
said they'd strike!
We've all gotta
protect Moka, guys!
You can count me in!
Well...
Things would get pretty boring
if my main rival got bumped off.
So I'll be happy to lend a hand.
Heh...
you'll "lend a hand"...
I'll bet you would.
You can cram it,
you cold-blooded creep!
Oh...
I almost forgot
to mention it...
But speaking of creeps, I saw
this weird stalker last night,
you guys.
What'd they look like?
Well, she was a girl...
And she had this
crazy bright-orange hair...
Did you say orange hair?!
That'll teach you
pervs to ogle me!
Losers!
Losers?!
Us?!
Do you think you're so
cute we're gonna let you
get away with saying that?
You're the ones trying to
get away with something,
but unlike me,
you're ugly as sin.
--Ugly as sin?!
--What...?!
No girl talks to us
that way, skank!
Now I'm really pissed off...!
Do you know what Yokai Academy
Rule Number One is...?!
It says "Except in
special circumstances,
as long as you're on campus,
you must always remain
in your human form!"
You insulting us is
a special circumstance!
What's the hell's
going on in here...?!
Miss Nekonome,
what just happened?!
I don't know what set it off,
but one of the new girls
has picked a fight with two new
-- and I might add, big -- boys!
Run all you want, baby!
You're not
gettin' away from us!
If you goons think you can
catch me, go ahead and try!
Wait, that voice!
Yeah, it's that snotty
freshman girl from yesterday!
Think you can get away with
dissin' A-Class monsters
like us, huh?
Wow, you guys really are
losers if you're bragging
about being A-Class!
What?!
It's that girl with
the orange hair!
She's the stalker
I saw last night.
You're gonna get it, you tease!
Once we get ahold of you, you're
gonna regret mouthing off!
Please, you're way too slow...!
I've seen paint dry faster
than you two sacks of crap!
Yep, that's her, alright...!
I know those knee socks!
She's the girl in this picture!
As the only teacher
who's currently here,
I've got to put an end
to this and quickly!
Damn!
Where is she?!
Rwarr!
Ahem.
Testing, one, two, three.
Testing, one, two, three...
Um, all freshmen...
Would you please take
your seats and also refrain
--from destroying the gymnasium?
--Shove it, Teach!
Moka, it's too
dangerous in here...
I need to get you
to someplace safe.
That girl being chased...
The loud one with
the bright orange hair...
Uh, what?
What's she doing here?
Moka...
Come on, we've gotta
get out of here.
When the rosary seal
over her breast is removed...
Moka's innocent self vanishes...
and her inner vampire awakens!
Oh, you again!
It's been a long time...
Tsukune.
Yeah...
Putting that aside...
This fight is ridiculous.
Hey, what the hell is this...?!
You feel all that
incredible power?!
It's comin' from
that woman there!
Whoa, who the heck's that?!
She's got blood-red eyes!
And tons of monster energy!
Guys, wait a minute...
Do you think she's a legendary
"S" Class Supermonster?!
A Vampire?!
She's an "S" Class?!
Yeah, man, I think she is!
Oh, wow!
She's super-scary...
but so cool!
Out of all the older students
here, she's my new favorite!
I wanna be her!
Me, too, 'cause she's
the real deal...!
We're your biggest fans,
o' vampire goddess!
Listen up!
All of you here are
in high school now...
So start acting like it, okay?
And knock it off!
Yeah!
Well, am I making myself clear?
Yes, ma'am!
Are you okay, Moka...?
What happened?
She pushed herself too hard
and was beat to begin with.
Well, I guess the entrance
ceremony can finally go off
as planned now.
But who is that girl?
Yeah...!
That's what I wanna know...!
It seems like we've
all run into her before.
Well uh...
I know her...
Wait, you do?
Who is she?
Her worst nightmare.
It's been a really long
time, hasn't it, Moka?
What'd you think of all
those letters I sent...?
Did you manage
to read 'em all?
I busted my bat butt to
deliver all of 'em, whee...!
Now how 'bout
a little praise, whee?
We're not gonna
let you hurt Moka!
Everyone...
Run away.
What; why?
'Cause that girl...
She's my-...
Well...
I said I was gonna take your
life and now it's time...
Big Sister.
What...?!
Big Sister?!
That girl's...
her sister?!
Please help me, Tsukune...!
Why suck my blood now?!
And worse, it's
"to be continued!"
Tsukune, I got
another scary letter!
Let me see it, Moka...!
Wait, it says they're gonna
cut off your electricity
'cause you haven't
paid the bill!
Oh?
That's all...?
Next time...
"Little Sister and
a Vampire,"...and another!