Hello there, my name
is Rubi Tojo...
It's a long story, but
the people at Yokai Academy
have let me stay here.
You wanna hear
the long story, huh?
Well...
It's such a very long story...
So much stuff has happened,
I couldn't possibly
tell everything.
Hey, Rubi...
Morning!
Tsukune...?
Morning to you.
Oh, Tsukune...
Will it ever happen for us?
Will you ever gaze
deeply in my eyes?
Morning, Tsukune!
Oh, hey there, Moka...!
Good morning to you!
Tsukune...!
Good Morning!
Whoa...!
Wh-wh-wh-what are
you doing, Kurumu?!
Hey, Tsukune!
Good morning, Yukari.
Tsu... ku... ne.
I feel dizzy.
Oh, Mizore!
What's the matter?
That's enough, you guys!
Hey...
Good morning, Rubi.
Good morning.
Hello there.
Hi, Rubi...
A very good morning to you.
Oh, uh, hey, Yukari!
Good morning to you!
Now, listen up, everybody...
I've been thinking
about this for a while...
And today I'm gonna
give it to you straight...
You...!
Your skirts are
all way too short!
You think so?
I mean, this is how all
the girls are wearing them...
Right?
No, Don't pull them up!
You're all such pretty
young high school girls...
Why do you dress like tramps...?
Oh, right...
You're doing it
because you're trying
to seduce my Tsukune, huh?
That's rude...!
We're not trying to seduce him!
Rubi, you...
You love the way I dress...!
Come on...!
Our skirts aren't
that short, are they?
They're too long...
Right?
It's just like I said...!
Knock it off, you two...!
You're such a disgrace!
A 'disgrace?'...
Hey, hold on, aren't you
trying to do the same thing?
Yeah... Right.
Elegant, elegant, elegant...
Hey, guys...
Not to be a bitch,
but long skirts are lame, right?
Yea they are!
That's it!
Well...
I believe
I've heard enough...!
As of this moment,
I'm the dress code monitor,
and I'm going to check your
outfits every single day...!
Your skirts now have to be
ten centimeters below the knees!
No way!
This is nuts!
So, as we see here...
The majority of the time,
haikus contain what's called
a 'season' line.
Or a phrase that holds
a sense of the natural seas-
Stand up!
Bow!
Hi there, my name's
Shizuya Nekonome...
You may have heard of me,
I teach here at Yokai Academy.
Hey, guys, did you
hear the news?
Wait, what news?
It's about Rubi...
Apparently, tomorrow, she's
gonna start checking the length
of everybody's skirt
at the front gate.
I mean, can you believe that?
No way...!
That's nuts!
It's so stupid!
It's something about how short
skirts are for hussies and...
Short Skirts? But...
You know what?
I've always thought this...
But Rubi is seriously
too uptight, I mean,
it's like she's old
fashioned or something.
I'm screwed...
I don't even own
a skirt longer than this.
Well, tell me what
you think about this one...?
Meow.
Maybe it's
a little too risqué.
Oh...
I just don't know.
Ne...
Ko...
No...
Me...
What's...
this?
Meow.
What in the world do you
think you're doing, huh...?
A teacher is supposed
to set an example...
Not dress like some trollop.
Oh, uh, nothing, it's just
that I was uh, well, I uh...
This simply will not cut it...
What will your students think
when they see their own teacher
dressed up like
a two-bit hooker?
Come on, that hurts!
Oww, please don't pull on them!
That'll be one thousand, seven
hundred and fifty three yen!
I'm so ashamed, meow.
Yokaiiiiii!
Fight ho!
It's been a while since
we've seen him, hasn't it?
Seen who?
What do you mean, who are
you talking about, huh?
Gin!
Hey, my name's Ginei Morioka...
I'm president of the Yokai
Academy Newspaper Club.
I used to run around
campus day and night...
Chasin' down any
scoop I could find.
I refused to be silenced by
that damned Security Committee.
Whoa, there.
Keep those...
Yep.
There were times
I felt like givin' up...
But then...
These guys gave me
my pride back.
Tsukune!
But how come this guy
gets all the chicks?
What's he got
that I don't...?
What makes him
so damn special?!
Hey, guys!
Good morning everyone!
Tsukune!
Good morning.
Umm, Ginei?
Sorry to tell ya, but you've
got some major bed head today.
What a complete tool!
If we take the three sides of a
right triangle and call them...
Hello, my name
is Ririko Kagome...
I'm on the faculty here
at Yokai Academy,
where I teach mathematics...
Tsukune...
That little tramp!
All right then, people,
that's all for now...
And everybody better
do their homework...
Or...
You...
Know...
What.
Moka!
Aww, look who's here.
Tsukune...
I'm sorry...
I couldn't.
You see, I didn't wanna get
kicked around like last time,
so I took a few precautions.
This can't be!
Well...
I do hope you're fully prepared
for our study session.
That's far enough!
I don't care that you teach...
Forcing kids
to study is just evil!
Who are you?!
Well, I think it's time for...
My...!
Deadly catnip fist!
You must save her,
Mister Aono!
Wait!
How do you know my name?
Who cares?
Hurry!
Yeah, right, okay!
Uh, could you
be gentler, please?
'Cause this really doesn't
feel good at all, Tsukune!
Yeah, of course, I'm really
sorry about that, Moka!
Whee!
Uh...! Um, no!
Please stop looking
at them, meow!
"Meow?"
No...
It isn't me...
Really, I'm not Miss Nekonome,
I swear I'm not!
You, Mister Student, get that
girl home safe and sound...!
And you, Miss Snake Lady,
stop picking on students...
With that, it looks like
my work here is done...
Farewell, meow!
Tsukune...!
Let me suck...!
Hey, there lover...
I brought some candy...
Chop!
Tsukune, look...!
I made some
delicious lunch for us!
You're just so doggone cute!
Kurumu, stop!
Watch where
you're touching, okay?
Sweet buns from
Ikaho are yummy!
Gold leaf sponge cakes
from Aizu rock...!
I just love Maezawa beef...!
Tsugaru apples are juicy!
Miss Kokoa, we're already
way past Tokyo, whee!
Wait, they left this morning?
As you can see, last time
we were seriously late
getting to Tsukune's-
You keep making
snide comments like that,
and I'm gonna hafta punish you!
But you just did, whee!
Yokaaaaiiiii...!
Fight...!
Ho!
Fight-ho!
Whoa...
Whoa...!
Whee!
Ow, ow, ow, oww!
What's your problem,
you jerks...?!
Can't even stop
to say I'm sorry...?!
Ko-buddy, hammer time...!
What the...?
What's the deal, Ko-buddy...?
Where are you?
Ko...
If you don't come out right now,
then you'll be in deep shit!
Uh...
Miss Kokoa...?
I'm right here...
That voice is coming
from down below.
Whew!
Now it's all
bright again, whee!
But, Miss Kokoa,
where are you now?
Whee!
Shut up.
Eh...?
Miss Kokoa...?
What the hell
is going on, whee?!
Just stop talking...
It's itching me!
But, Miss Kokoa?!
God, that itches!
You taste really fruity today.
He tastes like milk.
Tastes kinda sour.
Spicy!
It's way too sweet!
I can't hold out much longer.
Go!
Yeah...
Good morning, Tsukune.
Hey!
Good morning, Moka!
So umm...
Would it be all right if I...
Uh...
Oh, never mind,
I'm not thirsty.
Well, I'd better go...
If I were you,
Tsukune, I'd go too...
You don't wanna be late!
But, Moka, you...
Yuck...!
Tsukune totally
stinks like b.o.
today!
If you smell like b.o.
then none of the girls
will like you...
So be sure to
check those arm pits...
This is me saying
pretty please.
Hello there,
my name is Rubi Tojo...
I'm the dress code monitor
here at Yokai Academy.
Stop right there, you three.
Your skirts are
entirely too short.
Oh...
Come on!
It's super hot out here,
we'll sweat to death!
Besides, we'll
look real geeky!
Nobody messes with this witch!
Take this!
I'm Tonko Oniyama.
I'm Shijimi Chono.
And I'm Sumae Mizuno.
We're just glad we
got to say our names
before the last episode.
That's enough...
This girl's gettin' in
the way of my "scoops."
You said it was important,
what exactly do you want?
Rubi, look...
You've gotta lay off
this dress code thing.
Dress code thing...?
Ah...!
All those lost photo
opportunities spell trouble
for your collection, eh?
I guess I nailed that one.
N-no...
That's not it...!
It just doesn't make
any damn sense!
I'm thinkin' of you here, Rubi.
Thank you, I appreciate
your concern...
But, Ginei...
Do you think you could look the
other way a little bit longer?
If you do that for me,
I might feel inclined to do
a little private
photo session for you.
It'll be just the two of us.
I see where you're
comin' from...
I'll stay outta
your way for a bit.
Thanks a lot, Gin.
I think maybe I'll
buy me a new camera.
He fell for that one,
hook, line and sinker!
Now, all that's left is...
Well, isn't that the truth?!
I require full cooperation
from the teachers, too!
Hey, Rubi, morning!
And a very good morning
to you, Tsukune!
Oh brother!
I hate how this thing
gets caught up in my legs...!
It's too long!
You wanna borrow my cape?
Oh, I have one, too,
if you need it!
This thing is so heavy.
Hey, guys, what's up?!
Hi there, Tsukune!
Good morning!
Good morning, Tsukune...!
You, too, Rubi!
Hi...
Good morning.
Good morning, you guys...!
Tsukune and Rubi!
Good morning, Tsukune.
Yes!
This is more like it...
Just some high school kids
saying good morning...
Boys and girls saying hello...
Yes...
This is it!
It's the brilliant
flower of youth!
And then it happened.
'Sup?
That's about enough of that...!
Right here
in front of Tsukune!
Meow!
Wow, that was a strong breeze.
Yeah...
That breeze sure was
naugh... ty, right.
You there!
Teachers!
Why are you wearing
school girl uniforms?!
Well!
This was the only
long skirt I had, meow!
Yeah, same here.
I won't allow it!
I won't allow it...!
As dress code monitor,
I can't allow those outfits!
Whoa...!
Rubi.
Wow!
Look at those!
Now, that's something.
Well, whaddaya know.
A shocker.
Did you guys see?
I can't believe someone
with that underwear...
Goes around lecturing
people about morals!
So scandalous.
This hurts your credibility.
Yep, sure does.
But...
You...
All of you...
All you guys ever do
is flirt with Tsukune
and hang all over him!
When is it my turn, huh?!
I see...
So it's about that.
Even though you're
not a classmate, Rubi,
that doesn't mean
you're not our friend...
You should feel free to talk
to us about anything.
Oh, thank you, Tsukune...
This does mean you want
the two of us to get hitched...
Right?
Well, my answer is yes!
No, I uh...
Um, that's not what I...
Hey!
What are you trying
to pull, huh?!
Rubi, no!
Crazy bitch...
At least that's
the end of that.
Still, I feel like
we're forgetting something.
Oh, just leave that one to me.
Ginei, what are you...?
Tsukune, wait...!
Woohoo!
She is smokin' hot!
Moron...!
You think you can
call me for this...?!
You stupid asshole!
Like I said, this dress code
makes no sense.
Big Sis!
It's you!
That was the showdown...
It took thi-...
Hey...! Everything went
black again, whee!
Today was the same,
I didn't see anything unusual.
You're doing an
incredible job...
thank you.
I see it as my duty
to watch over this.
We need the great barrier...
It is the key to the whole
existence of Yokai Academy.
If something were to happen
that would result in a breach
of the great barrier,
then the human world...
It would be inundated with
a flood of monster energy...
Without a barrier between
the human world and
the monster world, our entire
existence would be plunged
into endless chaos.
And then things would be
just like before...
Monsters and humans
at each other's throats...!
An endless cycle of violence,
death and destruction.
Managing the barrier is of
the utmost importance...
And you've done excellent work.
Your praise does me great honor.
Even though we've done it to
hide your true purpose here,
I still feel bad about
making you take odd jobs
around campus. I'm sure it's
a source of constant difficulty.
Not at all...
You've kept me safe, sir...
And now, thanks to you,
I even have a new talisman,
Mister Director.
I owe you nothing but
my sincerest gratitude.
I continue to rely
on you, Rubi.
Thank you...
I'll do whatever you ask of me.
Mizore, here...
Next time, Tsukune and I
are getting married...
Got it?
No one better miss it.
Mizore, what are
you talking about?!
Watch it and find out.
Yeah, what I mean is...
Next time...
"Skiing and a Vampire,"
Tsukune and I will...
She meant to say
"and another ..."