[banging sound]
[JUNICHIROU]
I... I... I'm really sorry!
Eh...?
[JUNICHIROU]
I know it was for a test,
but I was still
really rude to you.
I'm sort of an assistant
here at the agency.
My name's Junichirou Tanizaki.
Can you ever forgive me?
It's fine.
Don't worry about it!
[ATSUSHI] He seems like
a nice enough person.
And this here is--
His little sister, Naomi!
You... You two are
brother and sister?
For some reason I thought you
had a different relationship.
Oh? You think I'm lying?
There's absolutely no doubt that
we're related to each other.
None at all.
The two of us are more
similar than you'd think.
Right, big brother?
[giggles]
[ATSUSHI]
Uh, hang on...
You'll leave this subject alone
if you know what's good for you.
Uh... 'kay.
Listen closely, kid.
Now that you have
joined our ranks,
you should try
to act accordingly.
Unlike some people
here I could mention!
I work to uphold the
Agency's good name.
[ATSUSHI]
Hmm?
We are committed to that goal.
Well, at least some of us are.
Right... Dazai?
[OSAMU]
Would you strangle me
with these beautiful,
delicate fingers, young miss?
[DOPPO] Were you listening
to a single word I just said?!
My hands might
not be as nice as hers,
but if you're looking for
someone to break your neck,
I think that honor
should go to me!!
Wouldn't you say?!
I was wondering:
What were the two of you doing
before you joined the Agency?
[OSAMU, DOPPO]
Mm?!
Eh... No big deal,
was just curious is all.
[OSAMU]
Take a guess.
Huh?
It's a game.
We've played it
a lot here, actually.
The newcomer tries to guess his
colleagues' former occupations.
Think of it as part of training
to be a private investigator.
[ATSUSHI]
Hmmm...
I wanna say Junichirou
and Naomi were students?
Whoa, you got it. Nice one!
How did you figure that one out?
I was told you work
at the Agency part-time,
and you're wearing a uniform,
so there was a good chance
you were still in school.
Plus, Junichirou and I
seem to be similar in age.
Just made sense!
Not half bad, Atsushi.
What about Mr. Kunikida?
Nobody cares about what
I used to be, all right?!
[ATSUSHI]
Hmmm...
An official?
Did he hold a government job?
Almost! He was a public
school teacher,
and he taught
mathematics to be exact.
Hmm...
For the last time,
you have to use the law
of exponents in this one!
I can totally picture
that, actually...
It was another life.
I don't even wanna
think about it.
What about me then?
[ATSUSHI]
What did you do?
Yep.
My job.
[ATSUSHI]
Hmmmm...
Mr. Dazai... Mr Dazai...
I have no idea.
Not a single clue.
Don't even bother.
His former profession
is a mystery to all of us.
Nobody here has guessed it.
The person who finally figures
it out collects an award,
isn't that right?
[ATSUSHI]
A reward?!!!
Yeah, that's true.
And because no one's guessed
right, it's just skyrocketed.
[ATSUSHI]
The reward...
...has skyrocketed?!
S-So, just out of curiosity,
how much is this
reward right now?
Seven hundred thousand yen.
[ATSUSHI]
Seven... hundred... grand?!
[ATSUSHI] So if I guess
correctly, then it's mine?
This isn't just some
kind of prank?
A suicide advocate
keeps his promises.
I gotta say,
he looks really fired up.
There's no way
he'll ever guess it.
That reward... will be mine!
Stockbroker?
No.
[ATSUSHI]
Writer?
Uh-uh!
[ATSUSHI]
Office worker?
Incorrect.
[ATSUSHI]
Researcher!
Wrong.
[ATSUSHI]
Lawyer?
Noooope.
[ATSUSHI]
Journalist?
Carpenter!
Try again!
[ATSUSHI]
Fortuneteller!
[OSAMU]
Nah.
[ATSUSHI]
Pilot!
[OSAMU]
Wrong again.
Is he even close?
No idea...
[ATSUSHI]
Shinto priest!
[OSAMU]
Blasphemous!
[ATSUSHI]
Model!
[OSAMU]
No! Buuuut...
[giggles]
That's very flattering...
I bet you were just wandering
around doing nothing at all.
[OSAMU]
Not true.
I would never lie about
something like this.
[ATSUSHI]
Hm?
[OSAMU]
You've given up, right?
Eh?
Then... you can be the
one to pay the bill tonight!
[ATSUSHI]
Awww...
It's our Agency's
favorite restaurant,
so you can always
start a tab with them
if you don't have
enough money on you.
Hi, this is Junichirou.
Yeah, okay.
Got it.
Is it a job?
[JUNICHIROU]
Yeah.
The client's already waiting
for us back at the agency.
Well, let's get to work then.
Let's save the guessing
game for another time.
I assume that's
all right with you.
[JUNICHIROU]
Now then...
You mentioned wanting
to request an investigation,
but what manner of investigation
are we speaking of here?
[OSAMU]
So beautiful...
You remind me
of a lotus blossom.
All at once
elegant and ephemeral.
Would you care to
join me in a double sui--?
[ICHIYOU]
Huh?
[sighs]
[DOPPO] Allow me to
apologize for the distraction.
Please continue on.
I'll take care of this.
[DOPPO]
The hell is wrong with you?
Please let me expand
a little on my request.
Oh! Of course!
[ATSUSHI] Wow, she's acting as
if this is all perfectly normal!
You see, there's recently been
a group of seedy
looking individuals
loitering in the back alley
of my company building.
[JUNICHIROU]
Could you give us more details?
They wear clothes that
are very old and tattered.
We've heard some of them
speak in a foreign language,
but none of us can identify it.
[DOPPO]
If I had to guess,
I'd say they sound
a lot like smugglers.
Unavoidable in a port town like
this, and with their numbers,
the police can't
do much to stop them.
Right. If we had empirical
evidence of their activities,
we could shut
them down for good.
That's why...
You want us to get that
evidence for you, right?
Hey, kid...
--Huh?
--[DOPPO] You're on point.
What?!
Relax, it'll just be
a simple stakeout job.
Smugglers are rarely violent,
so you just need to keep watch
in case they try
to make a break for it.
It's really the perfect
first job for a rookie.
Yeah, but...
Junichirou, I want
you to accompany him.
If my big brother's going,
then there's no way
I'm staying behind!
[DOPPO]
Hey... kid...
[ATSUSHI]
Hmm?
You think I was about to leave
you high and dry like that?
I have some important
advice for you before you go.
Look here.
Memorize this picture,
and take note:
Be careful of this man.
If you see him, run.
Who is he?
[OSAMU]
A mafioso.
Huh?
Honestly, we only call him that
because we don't know
anything else about him.
He's part of a vicious
criminal organization
working from the port.
Appropriately, they're
called the "Port Mafia."
They're the most savage group
this city's
underbelly has to offer.
The man in the photo
is especially dangerous.
Not even this
Agency can get to him.
[ATSUSHI]
What makes him so dangerous?
He's gifted,
just like all of us are.
Unfortunately,
his ability is designed
specifically for bloodshed.
The military police don't
stand a chance against him.
I wouldn't want
to fight him, either.
[ATSUSHI]
What's his name?
[DOPPO]
Akutagawa.
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[AKUTAGAWA]
I found this bag on the ground.
I think someone lost it.
[COP A] Ah, thank you
very much for bringing it in.
If you could just fill out
this Lost and Found form...
[COP B] Wait a minute...
I've seen you before.
[AKUTAGAWA] Impressive.
You've found me out already.
Wait...
Isn't he the wanted fugitive?!
Don't move!
The military police of this city
are such a distinguished force.
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
Hello, I'm looking for a--
[gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA]
It's done. Next...
[OSAMU]
♪ Oh, oh, yeeeeahhhhh. ♪
♪ You can't do
a double suicide ♪
♪ Just by yourse-- ♪
Hey, Dazai.
How come you're not working?
I'm waiting for my muse.
♪ Don't forget... ♪
--♪ Grab a friend... ♪
--Hey!
♪ Double suicide, double
su-su-icide, let's go! ♪
♪ Double sui... ♪
It's not something
to laugh about.
All this talk about the mafia
and how dangerous they are...
I'm not sure I'm cut out
for this kind of work.
You'll be fine!
If I've been able to manage,
there's nothing for
you to worry about.
Yeah, but you have a special
ability as well, don't you?
Yours is probably way more
useful than what I have...
I wouldn't set your
expectations too high.
Mine's not really
suited for combat.
I don't care what you say,
I really love it!
Exactly how I love... you.
Cut it out, Naomi.
This isn't the place.
[NAOMI]
Mm?
Heeey, are you giving me lip?
Well, at least put some tongue
into it if you're gonna do that.
Oh, come on!
We have arrived.
Huh?!
[ICHIYOU]
It's this way.
[ATSUSHI] There's something
really creepy about this place.
[JUNICHIROU]
Hmmmmm...
That's strange.
Is this really the right spot?
Miss...
[ICHIYOU]
Miss Higuchi.
Smugglers tend to be a very
cautious bunch of individuals.
They'll always have
an escape route planned.
And yet... this place
leads to a dead end.
If anyone came from that
direction, they'd be trapped.
[ICHIYOU]
That's correct.
I must apologize
for deceiving you
and leading you all into a trap.
[ICHIYOU] My actual target...
is all of you!
Akutagawa, it's me...
Akutagawa?!
I have them cornered as planned.
[AKUTAGAWA] Excellent.
I'll be there in five minutes.
Oh, no, she's...
...with the Port Mafia!
Huh?
Hey...
Brother...
Are you... o... kay?
Naomi?
Naomi!
[ATSUSHI shudders]
[JUNICHIROU]
Oh, God, w-what should I do?
Oh, right!
Tourniquet!
Atsushi, do you have
a tourniquet on you?!
No, first, I have
to clean the wound...
Atsushi, grab her legs!
My research has already revealed
that you are a non-combatant.
I'll do you the favor
of allowing you
to follow your sister
into the afterlife.
[JUNICHIROU]
You...
You worthless thug!
[ICHIYOU grunts]
You're gonna pay
for hurting Naomi!
Special ability...
Light Snow!
Doesn't look like snow to me?
[JUNICHIROU]
Atsushi... stay far behind me.
Huh?
This woman's days
on Earth... are over!
What?
[JUNICHIROU] My Light Snow
ability transposes
the entire space
into a digital realm.
Ugh. Dammit!
[JUNICHIROU] I've superimposed
the imagery upon myself,
so it's impossible for
you to recognize where I am!
Even so, my bullets
can still hit you!
[JUNICHIROU]
That's where you're wrong.
[grunts]
Now you get to... die!
[JUNICHIROU grunts]
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
The stench of death...
It does not discriminate
between those who inflict it,
and those who seek it.
Do you not agree?
[DOPPO]
Be careful of this man.
If you see him, run.
[AKUTAGAWA] It's a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
My name is Akutagawa.
Like this woman here, I'm one
the Port Mafia's black dogs.
[coughs]
[ICHIYOU]
Mr. Akutagawa!
I can handle this by myself!
[yelps]
[AKUTAGAWA] My orders were
to take the weretiger alive.
And yet here you are,
gunning everyone down!
You useless mongrel!
Back off!
I'm sorry.
"Take the weretiger alive"...
I'm the one you're after?
But of course.
The objective of this mission
has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
Your friends got
caught in the crossfire.
Just an unfortunate consequence.
[gasps]
All of this is because of me?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Indeed...
That is your karma, weretiger.
Your life is bound to cause only
misfortune to those around you.
[grunts]
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
[ORPHANAGE WOMAN 1] The world
would be a better place
if you'd just die
in a ditch somewhere!
[ORPHANAGE MAN 3]
You're not welcome here,
and you'll never find a
place where you do belong!
That's my... karma?
Special ability...
Rashoumon!
[gasps]
Huh?
[AKUTAGAWA] Naturally,
I missed on purpose that time.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
But my Rashoumon has
been growing very hungry.
I intend to take you in alive,
but if you decide to resist,
then I'll have no choice
but to have it consume
your leg next time.
But why... why is
this happening to me?
[ATSUSHI]
Is this my fault too?
Do I make everyone around me
suffer, just by being alive?
[JUNICHIROU]
A... Atsushi.
Run... Run away...
You've got to.
[ATSUSHI]
They're both still alive.
Now that you have
joined our ranks,
you should try
and act accordingly...
Work to uphold the
Agency's good name.
[roars]
A fool's errand... How tiresome.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
[AKUTAGAWA] I'll commend
you on a noble effort,
but in the end,
it was a futile attempt.
I told you...
My Rashoumon's
hunger knows no bounds.
It devours anything around it.
It consumed the
very space your bullets
were attempting to cross
to in order to reach me.
No matter what kind of
weapon you might try to use,
none can reach me
in this present state.
[ATSUSHI]
How is anyone supposed
to stand a chance
against him then?!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Unfortunately for you,
I keep my promises.
[ATSUSHI screams]
[sobs]
[ORPHANAGE MAN 3] Quit your
sobbing, you useless brat!
Children who don't have parents
don't have the
luxury to sulk around.
A pathetic,
forsaken child like you
doesn't even have
the right to cry!
[ATSUSHI]
That's right...
I've been abandoned
countless times
over the course of my life.
I was never allowed to cry,
no one ever accepted me,
and I never had a place
I could call home.
And yet, even then...
[crashing sound]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Facinating...
His right leg just regenerated.
[roars]
This is how it should be.
Mr. Akutagawa!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Stand down, Higuchi!
What?
[ICHIYOU]
Akutagawa! Why you...!
It's having no effect!
[grunts]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Rashoumon...
Agito!
[coughs]
So much for taking you alive...
[ICHIYOU gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA]
What's this?
It appears I just ripped
apart an illusion.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Rashoumon!
Murakumo!
[AKUTAGAWA growls]
[OSAMU]
All right, that's enough!
Huh...?
You're from the Agency...
Why are you here?
I just couldn't
keep a lovely lady
like you off my mind,
so I decided to keep in touch.
It can't be...
[ICHIYOU]
That means...
You had already seen
through my plans
even before any
of this happened.
[OSAMU]
Come on Atsushi, rise and shine.
I don't wanna carry three
people back at the same time.
You really think
we'll just let you go?
[AKUTAGAWA chuckles]
Let's leave them be.
We'll return another time.
But Mr. Akutagawa... why?
Ah, well...
we will retreat this time.
However, you can be sure
the Port Mafia will be back
to claim that boy someday.
Why's that?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Isn't it obvious?
That weretiger fetches quite
a sum on the black market.
The bounty stands
at seven billion yen.
Well, I'm just tickled pink
at their utter generosity.
We'll pay a visit to your
Agency at a later date.
So you can be
sure the Port Mafia
will collect what's owed them.
Oh, really.
Is that a formal
declaration of war?
Go ahead and try it...
if you really have the guts.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hmm...
You think that
you can threaten us?
You are a small-scale operation
with only a dozen or so lackeys,
whereas we hold the keys
to this city's operations
at every level.
An agency like yours couldn't
even hope to touch us.
If we so wished it,
we could wipe you all
off the face of the Earth!
Yes, I'm quite aware of that.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Indeed...
I would expect you would,
considering your
previous history.
After all, you were a Port Mafia
member, weren't you, Dazai?
[DOPPO]
Hey, kid...
I heard the news that
there's a bounty on your head
to the tune of seven billion
on the black market.
[ATSUSHI]
This is really bad...
For all I know,
the Port Mafia could come
and raid the Agency
looking for me...
...but what should
I do about it?!
[DOPPO] You're the
one who caused all this,
so you should be the
one to figure that out.
[ATSUSHI]
What can I do?
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 4:
"The Tragedy of the Fatalist."