[ATSUSHI]
We made it back alive.
Still...
I wonder if the Agency
can look past
the people Kyouka's murdered.
[ATSUSHI] What'll I do
if she and the Agency
are hostile towards each other?
Good morning, everyone...
Now could you turn
around for me?
[oohs and ahhs]
[NAOMI]
So cuuuute!
What is going on here?
It's pretty amazing, right?
She looks so incredible
in just about anything!
That's... not what I meant...
Mr. Kunikida...
Don't blame this on me.
You wanted to save her.
Is this really all right?
Yeah, I'm not sure myself...
[ATSUSHI] Even if everyone
else is fine with it,
Rampo's a real stickler
for the rules.
Oh... don't worry about him.
I'm back!
Look what I brought!
[JUNICHIROU] Rampo's
actually into it the most.
[RAMPO] This is the snack that
changes color when you mix it.
Go ahead, try it!
[KYOUKA gasps]
[RAMPO]
First, open the bag, okay,
then put the two pouches of
powder in the container...
They're like children.
Young ones.
[RAMPO]
...mix really well.
You wanna put all
your heart into it.
Then, mix, mix, mix,
mix, mix, mix, mix...
And finally...
look what you get!
[KYOUKA sighs]
Lemme try a little bite.
[several gasps]
Children is right...
Guess that's par for
the course for Rampo.
So, do you happen
to know who asked her
to come visit the Agency?
[YUKICHI]
It was me.
[ATSUSHI]
President!
[YUKICHI]
What's our current status?
The Port Mafia
erased her identity,
so the police haven't
found her yet, sir.
I'm sure they'll label
her a fugitive soon enough.
Please let me stay here.
I'll do anything.
[DOPPO]
I don't recommend it.
Not because of your background,
or not having a job for you.
It's for your own sake.
It's a difficult life.
[ATSUSHI] Besides, if you stay
here, the Mafia will find you.
Shouldn't you run as
far away as you can?
Akutagawa...
He told me that the only thing I
was good for was killing people.
But he's wrong. I have
to prove that to myself.
[ATSUSHI]
President.
I'd like to vouch for her.
Please consider.
Please... consider.
Please... con... sider.
[YUKICHI]
Very well.
[ALL]
What?!
[YUKICHI]
I'll take her in.
[patient monitor beeps]
[OUGAI] Sprain fracture
of the lower jaw.
Avulsion of the frontal bone
and thoracic vertebrae,
damage to the jugular ligament,
rupture of the brachial
and femoral muscles,
and first-degree burns
over the entire body.
To top it off,
he's in a coma.
That's the price he paid
for failing his mission.
[ICHIYOU]
I apologize.
[OUGAI] He may never regain
consciousness again.
No way...
[OUGAI]
Don't feel too bad.
Yes, you did fail in attacking
the Agency and capturing
the weretiger, and you allowed
the transport ship to sink.
But you all did your best
in the end, did you not?
Effort is what's important.
Results come second.
Don't you agree?
Oh, yes... the remnants
of the group
Akutagawa annihilated,
Karma Transit...
Apparently they're regrouping.
I assume they want revenge.
[ICHIYOU gasps]
[OUGAI] Listen to me...
The Mafia is a business
which employs violence
as its currency.
It's allowed to desire
and kill as it chooses.
Retaliation must be weighed
in terms of expenditure
and liability.
But sir, how can you say that?
Akutagawa has accomplished
so much for the Port Mafia.
[OUGAI]
Indeed, he is competent.
His level of violence is high,
even by our standards.
But what about yourself?
[ICHIYOU gasps]
[OUGAI]
Tell me, Higuchi...
Have you ever felt that you
were truly suited for this job?
I look terrible.
[ICHIYOU gasps]
[RYUUROU] That's a sufficient
demonstration, Gin.
[ICHIYOU coughs]
[ICHIYOU]
The Black Lizard...
You gotta excuse Gin.
The boss has him doing
a whole lot of infiltrating
and assassinating.
He'll slice anybody's throat
now, even one of our own.
If he'd been serious,
you'd be dead.
Does the boss intend
to take me out?
[RYUUROU]
Not today.
Tomorrow may be another story.
[ICHIYOU]
Are you here just to gloat?
[RYUUROU] If I were you, I'd
re-evaluate my current situation
before an assassin
arrives at my doorstep.
You, along with Akutagawa,
are a strike force
under the boss's
direct supervision.
As such, you are
our superior.
But do not mistake our
position for obedience.
It is Akutagawa's power
that commands our respect.
[RYUUROU] Tell me...
During the time
Akutagawa will be
indisposed, do you possess
something that could
compel us to obey you?
[AKUTAGAWA]
I don't need help from you!
Akutagawa, please wait!
This is suicide, even for you!
You're walking right into
a building full of
security guards!
We don't even have instructions
on how to back you--
[AKUTAGAWA] Silence!
Just what would you know?
There it is...
A beacon visible from
anywhere in the city.
A powerful beacon for the one
who left without a word.
The one who left without
acknowledging my abilities.
Sir! Please allow me to
do my part in helping you!
I don't need help from you!
[ICHIYOU gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA]
I need no one's help!
[ICHIYOU]
I'm home...
[OUGAI] Have you ever
felt that you were
truly suited for this job?
[ICHIYOU]
No... of course I haven't...
[[patient monitor beeps,
alarm sounds]
[patient monitor beeps loudly]
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
[ICHIYOU]
This is Higuchi.
What did you say?!
[RYUUROU]
Think this over.
The boss won't be happy.
[MICHIZOU]
Are you crazy?
You're gonna get
yourself killed!
Akutagawa was taken by a
bunch of foreign mercenaries
hired by what was left
of Karma Transit!
There's a crapload of them,
and each and every one
of those guys is
armed to the teeth!
The boss'll issue orders
for a retrieval operation.
Just wait until then!
There will be no order!
This attack on
Akutagawa was personal.
If we retaliate
as an organization,
we risk triggering more
conflicts on a larger scale.
The brass doesn't care
about private disputes.
They'll turn a blind eye
to all of this.
Akutagawa's already
been cut off.
Even so, what can you hope
to accomplish by yourself?
Maybe I can't do anything.
Still... I have to try!
I can't just wait!
[ICHIYOU]
I knew where I stood.
I knew I wasn't
suited for this job.
I knew I didn't have the
respect of my subordinates.
[RYUUROU] If I were you, I'd
re-evaluate my current situation
before an assassin
arrives at my doorstep.
[ICHIYOU] It's not easy
to leave the Port Mafia,
but not impossible.
I've thought about it often.
But each time, I could
never go through with it.
[ARMED GUARD]
Huh?
[screams]
[ARMED GUARD A grunts]
[ARMED GUARD B groans]
[ARMED GUARD C yells]
[ICHIYOU pants]
[ICHIYOU]
Damn it...
I can't rescue
Akutagawa in this state.
[ICHIYOU yells]
[ICHIYOU grunts]
[gun cocks]
I could never walk away...
because the truth is...
[gunshot]
[ICHIYOU gasps]
Let's take 'em all out, guys!
You all came... but why?
[RYUUROU]
You're our superior officer.
It's our job to see you
protected from danger
at all costs.
Okay, looks like
we're done here.
[ICHIYOU grunts]
[ICHIYOU pants]
Akutagawa...
[ICHIYOU]
Please... wake up!
[AKUTAGAWA breathes weakly]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Is that you, Higuchi?
Take this, you're bleeding.
[AKUTAGAWA]
I'm sorry...
[ICHIYOU] It's not easy
to leave the Port Mafia...
but not impossible.
But I never went through
with it, because...
It's my job.
[DOPPO] I'm leaving you
to look after the girl.
What? Is that okay?
You were the one responsible
for saving her, after all.
[ATSUSHI]
Right...
[POLICE OFFICER]
Excuse me.
We're from the city police.
[KENJI]
Oh, welcome!
Back again? Didn't one of
your officers get arrested
last time, Minoura?
Hm, I'd rather not
dwell on that matter.
We have another case.
[KENJI] Aw. They didn't
even stay for tea
when they were done
with business.
I guess the city policemen
are too busy for that.
[DOPPO] What are police like
where you're from, Kenji?
We all know each other
in my village.
It's common to see our
policemen doing things
like fixing the pump to the
local well, rescuing cats,
or standing in line to taste
the first crop of watermelons.
[DOPPO]
Are you serious?
And what happens
to your lawbreakers?
They get hogtied
and tossed off a cliff.
Uhh, Mr. Miyazawa...
Just call me Kenji.
[ATSUSHI]
Mm?
I was living in a small
village called Ihatov,
where there's no electricity,
until about two months ago.
After the President
recruited me, I came here.
I'm having fun learning
all sorts of new things!
Learning new things...
Like what?
Well, I don't really understand
the concept of money.
Is that really possible?
Mr. Kunikida, what
should we do about
that request from the police?
[DOPPO]
Mm?
"A car in motion exploded for
unknown reasons"... Huh...
They're completely
stumped by it.
[DOPPO]
You wanna give it a go?
[ATSUSHI]
Mm?
Shadow another agent.
Try to get the hang of things.
I know you can do this.
Thanks.
[CROWD MEMBER A]
What's going on?
[CROWD MEMBER B]
Do you see that?
[KENJI] A car was driving along
and somehow ended up there...
[ATSUSHI]
This is way over my head...
The unidentified driver
died on impact.
Unidentified? Can't we
use fingerprints or teeth
to figure out who they were?
Sure. If we had any.
[ATSUSHI]
What?!
You're saying that the body...
is completely sludge now?
Now then, I know Rampo could
solve this case right away...
but we're just gonna have
to gather information
the old-fashioned way...
[GRAN]
Kenji, dear!
[KENJI]
Hello, lil' miss Maeda!
Thank you for the boar
meat the other day.
It was scrumptious!
[KENJI]
It was nothing, really!
My folks sent me
a lot from home.
"Little" miss?
She'd be one of the younger
ladies in my village.
[GUY]
Hey, kid!
[BOTH]
Mm?
[GUY] You know the vegetable
garden I told you about?
It isn't draining very well.
It must be the soil in the rows.
I'll check it out later.
[GUY]
Great. Thanks a lot!
You're really popular.
[MAN]
Hey, Kenny...
[ATSUSHI]
Hm?
You on a job?
We are, as a matter of fact!
We're investigating the
explosion that just happened.
Can you tell us
anything about it?
Oh... with the car, right?
You could say...
there's rumors...
[MAN gasps]
[MAN shudders]
[ATSUSHI yelps]
I'm really not supposed
to talk about it,
but from what I overheard,
right before it happened,
those backstreet folks
from the factory district
bought a load of fertilizer.
[KENJI]
Fertilizer...
So do you think they realized
the beauty of farming?
[MAN] No, they were talking
about manufacturing something...
Then it was probably
nitrogen fertilizer.
[ATSUSHI]
What's that?
An ingredient for explosives.
[ATSUSHI]
What?!
[KENJI]
Thank you as always.
You've been very helpful.
[MAN]
Anything for you, Kenny...
[ATSUSHI]
We already have a lead...
Kenji's amazing.
[KENJI]
I'll be counting on you.
Speaking of the
factory district,
there's a hangout spot for the
Gojo Youth Association there.
[ATSUSHI]
Who's that?
To put it in city terms...
they're a gang.
[ATSUSHI]
A... A gang?!
I wonder if they maybe
they could be the ones
who built the bomb.
How about we go there and ask
them about it face to face?
--[ATSUSHI] Wait a minute!
--[KENJI] Mm?
Even if they were responsible,
why would they admit it?
Especially to us?!
If we go and ask them nicely,
I'm sure they'll tell us.
That's how life is!
What? That's how life is?
Are you serious?
You are serious.
I guess you're right, Kenji!
[DOPPO]
Hey, Junichirou...
Weren't you with Atsushi today?
Oh, actually, Kenji was
the one who went with him.
[DOPPO]
What?! He's with Kenji?!
Yeah, they went to
the crime scene.
Kenji has solved a lot of
difficult cases in the past,
so I can't imagine that
there'll be any problems with--
[DOPPO]
It's a huge problem!
Kenji's methods are way too
bizarre for him to be copying!
Given how naïve Atsushi is,
he very well may
take Kenji's approach as
being the gold standard!
[DOPPO]
This isn't good...
Huh?!
Did any of you build the
bomb that made that big car
fly into that building?
You're a funny guy!
You cops or somethin'?
Actually, we're with the
Armed Detective Agency.
Oh, that's a real nice
chain you got there!
Do you always keep
one of them handy
in case you ever have
to haul cows around?
Why you!
Explain yourself, kid!
Oh, I just wanted
to ask if any of you
were responsible
for what happened.
[GANG MEMBERS]
Huh?
[GANG MEMBERS laugh]
Can't say we know
anything about it.
Right?
[GANG MEMBERS laugh]
If that's the case, I'm sorry
to have bothered you.
[ATSUSHI yelps]
Thank you for taking the
time to talk to me about it.
[GANG MEMBERS]
Huh?
[ATSUSHI]
K-Kenji, wait up!
They were lying
about everything!
They probably used
the bomb to kill someone
in a rival gang or something!
There's no way they
weren't involved!
But they said they didn't
know anything about it.
[ATSUSHI]
Well, yeah, but...
Whether it's cow or man...
in a village or city...
if you are honest,
others will reply in kind.
It works. That principle
has never failed me yet.
Is... Is that true?
Yes.
[ATSUSHI]
Hmm...
I guess I can see that.
Why don't we head back for now?
Good idea.
[stomach rumbling]
Can we stop by at a beef bowl
place? I'm really starving.
Hang on... you eat beef
even though you keep cows?
Of course! I love absolutely
everything about them,
including how they taste!
[GANG MEMBER B]
I gotta say, I'm surprised
you private eyes figured
out we used a bomb
to kill a rival gang member.
We barely had a chance
to chat back there.
You wanna tell us what kind of
evidence you got against us?
[GANG MEMBER C] Don't think
that we'll just let you
run to the cops.
This is wonderful! I just knew
that you would all come clean
and tell us the entire
story eventually.
[GANG MEMBERS]
Huh?
I knew that my honesty
would be repaid in kind.
In all of the cases
that I've worked on,
everyone ends up
confessing to me like this!
Oh, I get it now--
[clang]
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[GANG MEMBER C]
One down, one to go...
[ATSUSHI]
Crap!
We're surrounded...
What am I supposed to do?!
[GANG MEMBERS yell]
[ATSUSHI shudders]
That kinda stung a bit...
[GANG MEMBERS]
Huh?
[KENJI]
Ahh, up we go...
[KENJI groans]
Oh, don't worry about me.
This happens sometimes.
Out in the countryside,
cows can get in a temper
and refuse to listen to you.
In times like that...
[KENJI]
"Be not defeated by the rain.
Be not hindered by the wind.
Be not halted by iron pipe,
knife, or metal bat.
Be strong of body.
Be without desire.
Be unfettered by anger.
Always carry a quiet smile."
That is the sort of
person I strive to be.
This will not work...
I can't go around doing
things like this, Kuniki--
Calm down, you fool!
I commend you for
realizing that yourself.
Kenji possesses
superhuman strength,
but he isn't totally invincible.
He can only use that
strength when he's hungry.
[ATSUSHI] What?! Then what
happens when he's full?
Ahh... I can't eat
another bite...
[KENJI chuckles]
[DOPPO]
He sleeps.
[OSAMU gulps]
[OSAMU]
Ahhh.
I'll tell them I got away
from the Port Mafia tomorrow.
[ATSUSHI] The Guild,
a North American organization
of the gifted, has declared war
on the Armed Detective Agency.
What are they really after?
Kenji, Naomi... They've captured
our friends one after the other.
And now, I've become trapped
in a different dimension
created by one of the Guild.
Next time on
Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 12: "Borne Back
Ceaselessly into the Past."
I was wondering...
You said you were a doctor.
[OUGAI]
Oh, yes. Indeed.