[DOPPO]
What is "the Ideal"?
The question seems
to beget more questions:
Is it merely a concept?
A lofty notion?
Or the goal of all life itself?
If you were to ask me, however,
the answer is quite simple.
The words rest on
the front of my notebook,
encasing its meaning.
[DOPPO]
"The Ideal"...
Everything about
me is written here.
My day-to-day schedule,
my long term goals...
My future is forever
bound to this notebook.
[DOPPO] I've arrived a
whole ten seconds early.
My name is Doppo Kunikida.
I'm an idealist at heart,
and a pragmatist in
pursuit of those ideals.
It's time.
Good morning, everyone.
Please help us, Mr Kunikida!
What is it this time?
I-I-It's Mr. Dazai...
Look at him!
[OSAMU]
Aaahhhhh!!
Kunikida...
It's an emergency!
Just take a look at this!
Look at what?
It's right here, silly!
The only thing I see
is your stupid face.
It's here!
I've finally arrived!
I can see the pearly
gates and everything!
I have no idea what's going on.
[ATSUSHI]
Mr. Kunikida!
[DOPPO]
Hm?
I... found this.
I knew the Complete Guide to
Suicide was a masterpiece!
Who would've guessed I just
needed to eat those mushrooms
growing nearby to have
such an entertaining exit!
[laughs]
So those mushrooms
were poisonous?
[ATSUSHI] Well, yeah, he thought
they were, but in actuality th--
Yes! I've finally caught you,
rainbow pillbug!
Time for lunch!
[ATSUSHI]
Mr. Kunikida!
I'm doing my routine paperwork.
Wait until I'm done.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?!
[OSAMU]
Oh, Kunikiiiidaaaa...
You should come
to the afterlife, too.
It's amazing here!
So many rainbow pillbugs...
All the drinks you can handle...
Mountains and mountains
of food to eat...
All the sleeping beauties
you could ever--
[roars]
Stop this nonsense!
[ATSUSHI]
How can two people
this completely
incompatible work together?
[door opens]
Mr. Kunikida?
The president has your
case file ready and waiting.
[DOPPO]
Dazai, quit dilly-dallying.
Keep up the pace.
[OSAMU]
Okayyyy.
[DOPPO] We only have
two minutes and 15 seconds
until our appointment!
[OSAMU]
That's a cause for worry.
Is it really okay
for me to come along?
[DOPPO] It's part of
your rookie training.
We need to solve a case
involving a series of
disappearances in Yokohama.
[ATSUSHI]
I heard about this.
Tourists arrive in the city and
are never heard from again.
A lot of people have
gone missing, right?
[DOPPO]
We received an anonymous tip.
It stated that the victims
have all been abducted
and gave the location
where they are being held.
The good, ol' "anonymous tip."
How very convenient
and terribly suspicious.
Even so, we can't ignore it.
So we're gonna check
out whatever this place is?
[DOPPO]
No.
[DOPPO] We're investigating
the tip's source.
[DOPPO] How's the work
coming along, informant?
[TAGUCHI]
Not bad, four-eyes.
Better than
your notebook, I'll bet.
[DOPPO] That's a lot of
attitude coming from someone
who'd be considered
a glorified cyber criminal.
If your activities
came to light,
your father would
be disappointed.
Don't you bring him
into this, Kunikida.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
[TAGUCHI]
More importantly, you're late.
How unusual.
So what...
were you out on a... date?
[DOPPO]
Course not!
Courting will only be
done with a specified woman,
followed by marriage within six
years time, as is dictated here.
Huh?!
So you're saying
you already have someone
that you plan to marry?
I will in another four years.
[ATSUSHI]
Uh...!
So, who's the new kid?
[ATSUSHI]
I'm Atsushi Nakajima.
The name's Taguchi Rokuzou.
I'm a spy.
For the right price,
I can dig up dirt on anything.
[DOPPO] So did you figure out
who's behind the anonymous tip?
The Azure Messenger...
What?
[TAGUCHI] I swiped some of
the data left on the server,
which included these
pictures of the victims.
The mole can't be that
bad of a guy, can he?
I mean he did let you know where
they were being kept and all.
[OSAMU]
It's possible.
It'd just be a shame if we
went there and after all that,
they turned out to
be the kidnappers.
"The Azure Messenger"...
Stay on their trail, Taguchi.
Sure, if I have the time.
I'm very busy
looking after my fish.
Right... Thank you very much.
I called a cab.
We'll head to the abandoned
hospital the tipster mentioned.
[OSAMU]
Tell me, Kunikida:
Why are you looking
after that Rokuzou boy?
[DOPPO]
What do you mean?
[OSAMU] It's not like you
to give a hacker a job.
Not only that, you could've just
talked to him over the phone.
But you took the time
to meet him face to face.
His father's deceased, isn't he?
Are you trying to
fill that role for him?
[DOPPO]
We came here
so that Atsushi could
formally meet our informant.
That's all there is to it.
Nothing more.
[OSAMU]
Then I won't press the matter.
[DOPPO] This driver is
another one of our informants.
He used to be an actor.
[DRIVER]
My career never took off,
so I had to find paying work.
It was fortunate for us you did.
You know these streets.
No on else's knowledge of
Yokohama even comes close.
It's also helpful that
you happened to see two
of the 11 victims just before
they were reported missing.
It's true,
as fate would have it,
I had driven both of them
from the port to their hotel.
Are we sure these
people were abducted?
There haven't been
any ransom requests.
[DOPPO] You're certain these
were the two who you drove?
Yes, there's no mistaking them.
Even their clothes are the same.
[OSAMU]
I see!
That's gotta be it!
Check this out.
Both of these guys
are wearing glasses!
It's gotta be a serial
glasses abduction case!
This is totally
your time to shine!
Not all of the people who
were abducted wear glasses,
so it's not a pattern.
Awww, too bad...
I guess maybe it'll never
be your time to shine.
All right,
now you've gone too far.
There's more to me than
just my glasses, all right?!
[tires squeal]
[DOPPO]
What happened?
We've arrived, sir.
The abandoned hospital,
just as you requested.
[OSAMU]
What a cheery atmosphere.
Think it's haunted?
[DOPPO]
Yeah, right.
[ATSUSHI] It's really
creepy in here, isn't it?
[OSAMU] I think it's
refreshing, actually.
Really gets my blood pumping.
[DOPPO] You'd better not have
eaten another weird mushroom.
[OSAMU] You seem a
little jumpy, Kunikida.
[ATSUSHI] Is he afraid
of ghosts or something?
[DOPPO]
I-I'm not afraid of ghosts!
[OSAMU]
Don't fall behind then.
[DOPPO] Haven't you
ever seen a horror movie?
The person who goes first
is always the first to die!
[ATSUSHI]
Look at these footprints...
They're still fresh.
[SASAKI]
Somebody help me!
[ATSUSHI]
You hear that?
[DOPPO]
Down there!
Huh?
What is this?!
[gasps]
[two gunshots]
[SASAKI coughs]
[SASAKI]
Thank you so much...
You saved my life.
My name is Sasaki Nobuko.
I'm a lecturer at one of
the Universities in Tokyo.
So that would make her victim
number 12, wouldn't it?
Did you happen to see who
it was who abducted you?
I didn't. I blacked out
back at the train station.
When I came to,
I was drowning in that tank,
just as you all came in.
Dazai, what's your
take on the situation?
I'd say she's sexy as hell.
[DOPPO]
Not helpful!
[SASAKI] Hey, I think
there might be other people
who were trapped
in this building as well.
[gasps]
Before I blacked out in the
tank, I was sure I heard voices.
Is that so?
[ATSUSHI]
Mr. Kunikida!
I found them!
[PRISONERS]
Help us! Please!
[DOPPO]
Just hang on!
[PRISONERS]
Please!
[gasps]
Get back Atsushi, It's gas!
We've gotta get out of here!
[DOPPO]
Hey! Do you hear me? Look at me!
[OSAMU]
We've gotta go!
Let go damn it!
These people...
We can't just allow
them to die like this!
You hear me?
Let me go!
[ATSUSHI] "Victims of Yokohama's
recent serial abductions
were located, but all died
when a private detective
agency conducted a raid."
They all... died.
[DOPPO] This must've been
the enemy's objective.
You think that they
set all of this up...
...in order to frame the Agency?
Despite what Dazai said, maybe
it wasn't my time to shine.
Mr. Kunikida...
Where's Ms. Sasaki?
[ATSUSHI]
She should be in the infirmary.
[OSAMU]
Oh, really? That's great!
I'm glad to hear it!
[SASAKI giggles]
Hi! Thank you so much for
saving me the other day.
If you hadn't all
come when you did,
I'm sure I wouldn't be
sitting here right now.
Well...
[SASAKI]
Not to mention,
you were very kind in
putting me up last night.
Huh?
Where did you stay exactly?
My place!
What?!
That's correct.
I am... deeply
indebted to him for that.
What can I say?
A-Are you sure that's not
breaking professional conduct?
[OSAMU] Unfortunately,
Miss Sasaki didn't see
who her kidnapper was.
She apparently faints often
due to a medical condition.
That's exactly what
happened on the day
when she was abducted as well.
How she was transported
afterward, I'm not sure.
You've taken quite
a liking to her, haven't you.
I take quite a
liking to all women.
She does seem like the type
who'd commit suicide with me
if I asked.
That's so nice.
[grunts]
What about you then, Kunikida?
Is she your type?
She's an eye-witness
in a murder case.
Nothing more.
Well... it figures
that you'd say that.
Atsushi, you wanna know, right?
What his ideal woman is?
Uh?! When did you
swipe that, you bastard?!
[ATSUSHI]
He wrote it all down?
Oh, yes! Kunikida's notebook
has a comprehensive list
of obligations, plans,
and ideals recorded in it.
Right here, for example...
Whoa!
You're... You're kidding,
that's a lot of--!
[DOPPO]
You have a problem with it?
Not at all...
I can understand your vision of
an ideal woman, but maybe, um...
You shouldn't share that
with any actual women.
[grunts]
That's not important right now!
We should talk
about the abductions!
Have you picked up on anything?
[OSAMU]
Indeed.
I have deduced
that without a doubt
you look very manly
in this newspaper photo.
[DOPPO]
You wanna see how manly I look
when I punch your lights out?
[sighs]
What's regrettable, however...
You should've
picked sexier glasses.
Here you are in the paper, and
those do not photograph well.
They're so plain.
Hey...
Only someone possessing
my unbridled charm
could pull off wearing them.
What do you think, Atsushi?
[ATSUSHI]
Not bad, actually...
Yeah, well they only
scream "con man" to me.
Hmm?
Wait a minute...
[ATSUSHI, OSAMU]
Hmm?
Something the matter?
[DOPPO]
Both of you, let's go.
I know who's behind this.
[DOPPO]
Sorry for the short notice.
[DRIVER] So you mentioned
that you'd figured out
who's behind the
serial murder case.
I imagine that you're on
your way to arrest the killer?
That's right.
Then we should probably hurry.
So what's our destination, sir?
Right here.
Huh?
The abductions happened here.
You're the kidnapper.
You subdued
passengers with sleeping gas,
and abducted them after
they fell unconscious.
You wore a gas mask
to escape the effects.
Why would he go
through all that trouble?
[OSAMU]
I can think of one reason.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
Merchandise.
[ATSUSHI]
What do you mean?
He'd sell the bodies
for their parts.
There's quite a large
black market for organs
if you know where to look.
The cut may not be ideal
because of the various
economic factors involved,
but if you're flying solo,
the pay's not bad.
[ATSUSHI]
That's horrible.
Hang on... that's impossible.
If I'd kidnapped
people in this taxi,
I would've been found out
when the police traced
their last known whereabouts.
Actually, the police didn't look
give this taxi a second look.
Why would they?
All the victims had vanished,
and subsequently each one became
untraceable the following day.
After the targets got in
your taxi and were sedated,
you proceeded to strip them of
their clothes and belongings.
That's why most of the
victims at the hospital
were only in their underwear.
You would then don their clothes
in order to disguise
yourself as them,
and followed up by
checking into hotels
where they had
previously made reservations.
You made sure
you would show up on security
cameras for that reason.
The victims being the same size
as you was no accident either.
You chose people who wore hats
and glasses because they
were easier to impersonate.
If the security feed
showed someone
looking close
enough to the victim,
the police were
inclined to believe it.
By the time the
last known sighting
of the "victim" was recorded,
the real victim had
already been abducted.
[OSAMU] Ms. Sasaki's abduction
was even easier, wasn't it?
After she collapsed
at the train station,
a good Samaritan passing by
paid for her cab ride
to the hospital.
It's faster than
calling an ambulance
at the train station, isn't it?
[DRIVER] That's all
circumstantial evidence.
[OSAMU]
Hmm?
I suppose.
Guess we got nothing.
What's your move now, Kunikida?
Come on, are you
being serious right now?
How about we all make a deal?
What do you mean?
If you agree to my conditions,
I'll turn myself in.
I need the assurance of
the Armed Detective Agency!
You have to keep me safe
till the prosecution concludes
their questioning and arranges
witness protection for me.
[DOPPO]
What's this about?
It wasn't my idea
to do this job.
I was approached by
a new organ smuggling ring
who told me this
was a great opportunity
and I'd never get caught.
Those liars!
So there's a group
behind all this?
Do you know where they are?
Sadly, no. I was always
instructed to meet them
in the Harbor Central Building.
That must be it.
[OSAMU] One question:
Why do you need our protection?
[DRIVER]
Well...
It appears that one of the
people I abducted was actually
with the Port Mafia.
How unfortunate...
They didn't take
long in finding us...
--[DRIVER] Help me!
--[DOPPO] Hey
[DRIVER]
I don't wanna die!
Wait!
[ATSUSHI]
Mr. Kunikida!
I'm not getting any signal.
They must be jamming it.
If we lose the driver, the truth
may never come to light.
Dazai, pursue the driver.
Kid, go to the police
and get backup.
I will draw their fire here.
Roger!
[DOPPO]
Let's go!
Special ability!
Doppo Poet!
Flash Bang!
[DOPPO]
Now!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Metal can be fragile...
...just like the human psyche.
And perhaps like the Armed
Detective Agency as well?
So it's you!
Akutagawa of the Port Mafia!
The very same.
Are you feeling al lright?
You can't even shoot
a straight bullet.
I don't have killing
anyone in my schedule.
I expected as much from you.
Doppo Poet!
[DOPPO]
Stun gun!
Now play dead, you dog.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Hmm?
[screams]
[DOPPO]
Hm?!
[AKUTAGAWA chuckles]
It appears the Agency isn't
merely a group of clowns.
You are worthy of
being Dazai's partner.
[approaching police sirens]
Huh...?
Seems we have company...
Ah, well...
Our paths will cross
again in the future.
We'll continue this then.
[DOPPO]
Don't come back.
[OSAMU] I turned the
driver over to the police.
[ATSUSHI] So... this is the same
building the organ traffickers
used for their hideout?
[DOPPO]
They've already left.
[ATSUSHI] The walls are
completely scorched.
[OSAMU] This is where the Azure
King blew himself up, isn't it?
[DOPPO]
Correct.
[ATSUSHI]
What?
Are you talking about the
infamous Azure Flag terrorist?
That Azure King?
Yes.
A fanatic who destroyed
many national and
corporate facilities.
When I first heard the
handle "Azure Messenger,"
I wondered if perhaps they
had some sort of connection
to the Azure King.
I remember seeing all the news
coverage about that explosion.
So this is where it happened...
It was out desperation after
the police had cornered him,
isn't that right?
[DOPPO]
Exactly.
I had determined
this to be his hideout
and reported the location
to the local authorities.
I'd heard it was a big
operation; what happened next?
The public safety
bureau, army, police,
everybody was working in tandem,
which created mass confusion.
Upon receiving the report,
only five detectives arrived at
the scene in a timely manner.
[DOPPO]
To exacerbate matters,
the Azure King received word
of the authority's actions,
and proceeded to
hole up inside the building
with an explosive device.
After a set of
conflicting orders,
a decision was made
to raid the building.
However, without
special training or abilities,
they didn't stand a chance.
[DOPPO] Cornered, the Azure King
blew himself up and died,
along with the five detectives.
[OSAMU]
I remember that well.
Of the five detectives
that were deployed that day,
one of them was Rokuzou's
father, wasn't he?
[DOPPO] He was a good
man with strong morals.
If I hadn't tipped
off the authorities,
none of this would've happened.
I may as well have
pushed the button myself.
That's not true!
It's the terrorist's fault for
choosing to blow himself up.
[OSAMU]
You're absolutely right.
Even so, Kunikida can't help
but take Rokuzou under his wing
as a surrogate father.
He feels it's the
least he can do.
[beep]
[DOPPO]
Hmm?
[ATSUSHI]
What is it?
[DOPPO]
Another job for the Agency.
The client is...
...the Azure Messenger.
How interesting.
They're starting to
reveal their true colors.
So... what's the job?
[DOPPO]
It's to go disarm a bomb.
[ATSUSHI]
A bomb?!
[DOPPO] If we fail to disarm it,
by sunset tomorrow...
...hundreds will die.
[ATSUSHI] So what exactly
are we looking at here?
With these schematics,
the explosive would
be quite advanced.
It's not going to be an easy
task to find and dismantle it.
[ATSUSHI]
No way...
[DOPPO]
Don't worry.
Nobody is going to be hurt.
Huh?
I promise...
I won't let that happen again!
[ATSUSHI]
What should we do?
If we don't find and disarm
the bomb by sundown,
there'll be hundreds
of casualties.
[YUKICHI] If such an unfortunate
event were to happen,
we would no longer
have any right
to call ourselves
a detective agency.
[ATSUSHI]
President Fukuzawa...
[YUKICHI]
The future of the Agency
depends on the
outcome of this mission.
Begin the investigation!
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, boy!
Where did Mr. Dazai run
off to at a time like this?
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 7: "Love for
the Disease Called Ideals."