[DOPPO] Speed: 20 knots,
heading out to open sea.
Don't you die on me, kid!
[CHUUYA grunts]
You call that a punch?!
That wasn't even a massage.
Your martial arts skills
are below average
for the Port Mafia.
It doesn't even
matter that I can't
use my ability against you.
Now get up. The party's
only just getting started!
Heh... You always were the best
with hand to hand combat.
Whoopsie daisy...
Thought my arm would
get destroyed there...
[CHUUYA] He blocked my strike
at the last second?
He must've predicted it.
[OSAMU] We've known each
other for a long time.
I'm very familiar with your
moves, pacing, and behavior.
That's what made me a
great partner... right?
[OSAMU]
He's fast!
Then I bet you saw this
coming too, didn't ya?!
Watch closely now!
This is how you punch!
[OSAMU grunts, coughs]
Did you really think you could
predict all of my moves?
Before I kill you... why did
you let yourself get caught?
What the hell were
you waiting here for?
Ah. Not talking, huh?
All right... I'll just enjoy
torturing you a bit more.
The main reason...
was for Atsushi.
Atsushi?
[OSAMU] The weretiger
you're all obsessed with.
I wanted to know who
was responsible for putting
the seven billion
price tag on his head.
[CHUUYA] You put your own life
on the line just for that?
Heh. I'd like to say that's
a real feel-good story there,
but look where you ended up.
Seems even a genius like you,
the youngest executive in
Mafia history, can screw up.
I guess Lady Luck isn't
on your side today.
It just so happens I
caught you on the very day
I returned from putting out
fires in the West. Heh.
Lady Luck must be on my side.
[OSAMU]
Heh.
What's so funny?
[OSAMU]
You should probably know this.
Tomorrow... the five
execs are meeting.
Impossible. They only meet
to make decisions about
the future of the organization.
Critical decisions.
And that only happens
every few years.
If that was happening tomorrow,
I would know about it.
This particular meeting
is in regards to a letter
I sent them the other day.
Allow me to make a prediction.
You are not going
to kill me after all.
Not only that, you're going
to give me information before
leaving this room, about who's
paying the weretiger's bounty.
Plus, once you exit,
you'll prance and talk
like a little rich girl.
Huh?!
My predictions always come true.
But you already know that.
You think you can
wiggle out of this?
Your letter...
What did it say?
Would you like me
to recite it for you?
"Should Dazai fall...
all of your secrets
will finally be revealed
and brought to light."
You've gotta be bluffing!
[OSAMU]
So, yes, you've caught me,
a former executive
turned traitor.
But you have a problem.
If you kill me, a list of
all the organization's
transgressions will be released.
The public prosecutor?
He'll feel obliged to execute
all the Port Mafia leaders.
That's more than enough of a
threat to trigger a meeting.
[CHUUYA] You really think
you can push around
the Port Mafia with
a bunch of words?
The only execution...
will be yours!
[OSAMU]
Possibly.
But in the end, that'll be
the Council's decision.
If you kill me without
their permission, your action
will be considered unsanctioned
and therefore a betrayal.
You'll be discharged.
Or executed.
Even if I decided to go ahead
and kill you anyway, I have
a feeling that you'd actually
enjoy that, wouldn't you?
I think it's time
you made up your mind.
[CHUUYA groans]
Well then.
What do you say?
I'm waiting, Chuuya...
Really? Not doing it?
I was so hoping I'd be the
reason you were thrown out...
I'm a little disappointed.
Don't tell me...
The main reason...
was for Atsushi.
[CHUUYA] Dazai! Was your
second reason for coming here
to force me between
a rock and a hard place?!
[OSAMU chuckles]
By the way, just why
are you here?
To pay you back!
So this whole time,
you had set me up
so you'd have the last laugh.
[OSAMU] With a reunion
this long in the making,
I had to do something special.
Someday... I swear
that I'll see you killed!
By the way... you realize
you're the one
who broke my chains
and freed me, right?
If I were to run away
right now, I'm certain
you'd be suspected
of aiding my escape.
[CHUUYA]
Why, you!
If you do as I say,
I could make it look
like someone from the Agency
came and rescued me instead.
Why should I believe
a thing you say?!
I never lie in these
kinds of negotiations.
I think you know that.
Bastard...
What do you want, anyway?
[OSAMU]
I mentioned it earlier.
[CHUUYA] If it's
about the weretiger,
Akutagawa's leading that
operation. He should have
records in the comm storage
room on the second floor.
How interesting! I had a pretty
good hunch that was the case.
What?!
Oh, you're such an ass.
Just finish what you came for
and get outta here.
[OSAMU]
I duly appreciate it!
Just one last thing...
My dream is to commit suicide
with a beautiful woman,
so dying by your hands never
really interested me. I'm sorry.
[CHUUYA]
Okay...?
I'll let you know
when I find
a beautiful woman
willing to kill herself.
[OSAMU]
Chuuya!
You are...
such a wonderful human being!
[CHUUYA] Go to hell.
I was being sarcastic.
Listen to me carefully...
This isn't the end!
Next time, you won't
be so lucky!
[OSAMU]
No, you're doing it wrong!
Aren't you forgetting something?
[CHUUYA grunts]
[OSAMU]
Come on!
You know you're forgetting
something, Chuuya...
[CHUUYA growls]
Next time, you won't
be so lucky!
[CHUUYA] ...y-you won't...
be so lucky...
Jeez, you could at least laugh!
[ATSUSHI groans]
[ATSUSHI]
Hey...
Did you... come here
to rescue me?
[ATSUSHI yells]
[ATSUSHI grunts, groans]
[AKUTAGAWA]
I had struck to kill.
However, it seems your healing
powers are partially in effect.
[ATSUSHI]
Where am I? At sea?
[AKUTAGAWA] This ship is usually
used for smuggling weapons,
but today it's been
reserved just for you.
You should savor this voyage
before we hand you over.
It'll likely be your last.
[ATSUSHI] I can't win
in a fight against him.
I need to find an
opening and run.
[AKUTAGAWA]
The weak must die.
There's no room for them
to exist in this world.
[ATSUSHI]
I don't understand.
Why does this guy
hate me so much?
[gun cocks]
[AKUTAGAWA] Ha, ha, ha. It seems
being in the outside world
has changed you...
What a shame.
Let go of him, now.
[KYOUKA chokes, gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA] Have you ever
been in the pit of despair?
It's a quagmire.
Desolate. Full of anguish.
At times, someone may peer
down on you from high above,
but they'll never notice you.
Every moment, your body
aches from self-loathing.
That is what's waiting
for you out there, Kyouka.
Demon Snow is
slaughter made flesh.
Do you really think you can
lead a normal life out there?
Weretiger...
teach her how it feels.
Never helping anyone.
Never being trusted.
Living your life in fear,
trembling like a worm.
[AKUTAGAWA] You have
two choices, Kyouka:
Continue killing for the Port
Mafia, or perish by my hand.
Because a human without purpose
has no right to breathe.
You actually may be
right about that...
But that's okay...
Those crépes...
They were delicious...
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[DOPPO]
Where are you, kid?
Are you here?!
Mr. Kunikida?
[AKUTAGAWA]
So, they've found us already...
Atsushi!
Run while you still can!
This ship isn't going
to its destination.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
Just where is it going, then?
The pit of despair.
[ATSUSHI grunts]
--[ATSUSHI] Kyouka!
--[KYOUKA] Run!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Weretiger!
[AKUTAGAWA] You set
explosives in the armory?
You're trying to die,
aren't you?
Is that man really worth
sacrificing your life for?
Is he?!
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[DOPPO]
Kid!
Listen! I can't get any closer,
so you're gonna have to jump!
[ATSUSHI]
I'm going to live...
I'm safe now.
[DOPPO]
That ship'll sink at any minute!
You need to hurry!
[DOPPO]
You fool!
Don't cause more trouble
than you already have!
No one is getting paid
a cent for this rescue!
[ATSUSHI]
What about her?
You have to let the girl go!
We can't save everyone,
no matter how hard we try.
I know that far
better than most.
That's just the
world we live in!
[ATSUSHI]
There's nothing we can do?
[DOPPO] That's right.
We're not heroes.
I've wished so many
times that we were.
But that's not reality!
Atsushi!
[ATSUSHI]
Kyouka...
[DOPPO gasps]
[ATSUSHI] She said the crepes
she had with me were delicious.
She was told humans
who don't serve a purpose
have no right to live...
But I don't think that's true.
Because neither Dazai nor
the Agency ever gave up on me!
I'm going to save her!
[DOPPO]
Hey!
Atsushi!
Run, as fast as you can!
[AKUTAGAWA] Kyouka... is this
truly the path you've chosen?
In appreciation
for your service...
...I'll lay you to rest.
Forever.
I'm here... Akutagawa!
[AKUTAGAWA] Curious...
I had a feeling
things would eventually
end like this between us,
[ATSUSHI] You're not
gonna get that bounty.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Don't worry. My intentions
to hand you over
alive have expired.
I can't forgive you for this!
The sentiment is mutual.
Rashoumon!
[ATSUSHI yells]
[ATSUSHI]
This is the same ability
that stopped those bullets.
My attacks won't get through
as long as it's active!
Pathetic.
[ATSUSHI yells]
Is that the best you can do?
I don't like torture.
However, you have nothing to
blame but your own weakness.
You deluded yourself into
thinking you were worthy
just because you were accepted
by those fools at the Agency.
That in itself was merely
a matter of happenstance.
You're quite the blabbermouth
today, aren't you?
I don't recall introducing
myself as a mute.
[ATSUSHI]
You're right about one thing...
I am weak.
But there's one thing I can do.
[AKUTAGAWA]
And what's that?
I can beat you!
He transformed back to escape!
[ATSUSHI yells]
[ATSUSHI] I thought so. He needs
time to activate his barrier.
I'll just use my speed
to compensate, then!
[ATSUSHI]
What?!
[AKUTAGAWA] I have no time
for childish fist fights.
You'll forgive me if I observe
your efforts from a distance.
[ATSUSHI] I have to close
the distance between us
if I wanna win.
Oh, no!
[AKUTAGAWA] Not long now
before this ship will sink.
[AKUTAGAWA] Using the explosion
to propel himself?!
[ATSUSHI yells]
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[OSAMU]
Your ability's slow to activate.
Your opponent's not gonna
be polite and wait for you.
On your feet.
Answer back with your ability.
[AKUTAGAWA grunts, pants]
[AKUTAGAWA yells]
[AKUTAGAWA retches]
That won't be enough to
survive in the Port Mafia.
Or would you rather go back to
being a stray dog in the slums?
[AKUTAGAWA grunts, pants]
Excellent. Let's go again...
[ATSUSHI grunts]
Before this ship sinks, I have
to get her safely to Kunikida.
[ATSUSHI retches]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Why...
Why are you the one?!
[AKUTAGAWA] You've only just
learned how to use your ability,
and it shows. Your technique
and strategy are sloppy at best.
So why...
Why did it have to be you?!
There it is.
That overwhelming
feeling of hatred...
Where does it come from?
[OSAMU] You think you can
pull that off? Really?
My new apprentice is superior
to you in every way imaginable.
Unacceptable...
I won't allow him to say
such things. Not ever again!
Rashoumon!
Higanzakura!
[ATSUSHI retches]
[ATSUSHI groans]
[AKUTAGAWA]
I've finally defeated him.
[ATSUSHI]
Wait.
Tell me...
[AKUTAGAWA]
There's no way he should be able
to move after that!
[ATSUSHI] There's no question
that you're powerful...
So then why did you have
to use Kyouka like that?
[AKUTAGAWA]
I didn't use her.
The sole purpose of her ability,
Demon Snow, is to kill.
Only by upholding
this responsibility
does Kyouka's existence
have any purpose.
I merely did my part in
giving her life meaning.
[ATSUSHI]
About that...
Whether someone is
worthy of being alive...
...isn't your decision!
[ATSUSHI] Why did you tell
her those horrible things?
She didn't need
to hear any of that.
People need to hear
that they're worthwhile
and that somebody
cares they're alive!
That's human decency!
What don't you get about that?!
[AKUTAGAWA]
He ripped it off!
And he's regenerating!
[ATSUSHI yells]
[AKUTAGAWA] I have to make sure
that I keep him at a distance.
Rashoumon!
Sawarabi!
[ATSUSHI groans]
Akutagawa!
[AKUTAGAWA chuckles]
Rashoumon!
Goku Mon Agito!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Just die already.
[AKUTAGAWA gasps]
[AKUTAGAWA]
He used his tail...?!
Devoured Space!
[ATSUSHI yells]
My new apprentice is superior
to you in every way imaginable.
[ATSUSHI yells]
[KYOUKA grunts]
[KYOUKA gasps]
[DOPPO]
Hmph. You big idiot...
Well done, kid.
[OSAMU]
Let's see here...
Who in the world wants to spend
seven billion on a tiger?
I should know
right about... now.
[OSAMU gasps]
Is it really them?
[bell peals]
[FITZGERALD]
They're late.
The bounty approach
seems to have failed.
Those Mafia types
sure are a mediocre lot.
It's a small setback, though.
The Promised Land will
soon belong to The Guild.
[DOPPO] We have a challenging
assignment that even
the local police passed on.
I'm counting on you, Atsushi.
[ATSUSHI]
Right! I'll do my best!
[DOPPO] What's that? Kenji was
assigned to help him out?
[ATSUSHI]
That's amazing, Kenji!
You've already
found a lead for us!
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 11: "First, an
Unsuitable Profession for Her.
Second, an Ecstatic
Detective Agency."
[DOPPO] This has to be
the best and worst team ever.