[KYOUKA]
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people
in six months.
[KYOUKA]
My name is Kyouka Izumi.
I've killed 35 people.
I don't wanna kill
anybody else ever again!
Not ever!
[DOPPO] Still attracting
trouble, are you?
Huh?
That girl is a lost cause.
It seems that her roots
as a heartless assassin
run much deeper than you know.
She's taken out
entire organizations,
using her appearance
to trick her targets
into lowering their guard.
She accomplished
too much, too quickly.
It was only a matter of
time before she was caught.
[ATSUSHI] Yeah, but whoever
was taking advantage
of her ability
is the one to blame!
[DOPPO] These gifts don't
necessarily bring happiness
to their wielders.
You should know
that better than most.
She's awake now.
Do you think we
can question her?
[AKIKO] Yeah, that
shouldn't be a problem.
[ATSUSHI]
Are you okay?
Oh, uh... you're in the
infirmary at the Agency.
How're ya feeling?
You remember
who I am, don't you?
Tell me.
Who's behind all this?
The Port Mafia is like a snake.
Unless you cut off its head,
it'll just keep coming.
Answer me, girl.
Who is your superior?
Hey, Mr. Kunikida...
[KYOUKA]
Tachibanadou's boiled tofu.
Huh? Tofu?
It's good.
Is that it?
You want us to get you some?
I'll talk if you do.
No problem!
It's a deal. Let's go!
Hey! Are you crazy?!
Huh?
[KYOUKA]
Mmm. Mmm...
More please.
Kunikida!
I'm not helping you pay.
Aww...
Now then, is there anything
that I can bring you, sir?
Just water...
[DOPPO]
Well?
I was left without a home
after my parents passed away
Then the Port Mafia took me in.
They wanted my special
ability, Demon Snow.
It only follows orders that
are heard through a phone.
[DOPPO] This is the
one they used, correct?
[DOPPO]
The battery's been taken out.
Their goal from the start was
to turn you into an assassin.
They were clearly very good
at using your ability
to their advantage.
Hang on, I don't understand...
Why didn't you toss the phone?
[KYOUKA]
They would've killed me.
Besides...
Even if I got away from them,
I had nowhere else to go.
Who was manipulating
Demon Snow through the phone?
A man called Akutagawa.
[DOPPO]
I see.
[DOPPO] I'll go report
this to the Agency.
And you...
Turn her over to
the military police.
[ATSUSHI]
But if I do that won't she be...
[DOPPO]
Yes, with a kill count of 35,
she'll be put to death.
Even if she went back,
she'd be killed as a traitor.
But still...!
What then?
Will you try to save her?
Uh...
[DOPPO]
A fugitive from justice,
and a traitor to
the Port Mafia...
...that's the kind of
person you'd be protecting.
Is that really what you want?
Well, I mean...
[DOPPO]
Listen...
I'm not saying you shouldn't
sympathize with her situation.
But her misfortune may
be more than you can handle.
You only have room
for one on your boat.
If you're overwhelmed,
you will be pulled under,
and you'll both sink.
But...
If that's all true...
Why...?
Why did Dazai even
bother to help me?!
[OSAMU]
♪ Doo-doo, doo-doo... ♪
♪ You can't do...
a double suicide... ♪
♪ all on your own. ♪
♪ Boom boom.
It takes two... ♪
♪ who don't wanna die... ♪
♪ all alone. ♪
Hello...
when did you get here?
[AKUTAGAWA] I believe that you
know what manner of fate awaits
those who are chained here.
[OSAMU] Yes, it really
brings back memories.
I remember when
you were just a rookie.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Your sins are grave.
After abandoning your mission
and vanishing into thin air,
you now reappear as an
enemy to the Port Mafia.
It's quite hard to believe,
coming from a former exec.
You mean coming from someone
who was your superior...
...right?
[AKUTAGAWA grunts]
Heh heh...
Even you aren't
completely invincible.
As long as I don't use my
ability, you're vulnerable.
I could hurt you...
I could kill you anytime.
[OSAMU]
That so?
Just look at you now.
You were so difficult to train
when you first started out.
You were such a slow learner,
and you could
never follow directions.
Then there's that
useless ability of yours...
[AKUTAGAWA] Your bravado
will only last a few more days.
In that time,
we will obliterate the Agency
and capture the weretiger.
Once you learn of
your co-workers' demise,
you'll be nothing but
clenched teeth and fists
Then your execution will follow.
[OSAMU]
You think you can pull that off?
Really?
My new apprentice is superior
to you in every way imaginable.
[KYOUKA sighs]
I ate too much.
[ATSUSHI]
Yeah... just a bit...
Good thing I had enough money.
[DOPPO] You only have
room for one on your boat.
If you're overwhelmed,
you will be pulled under,
and you'll both sink.
Just take her to
the police station.
Don't let her know
what you're doing.
[ATSUSHI] If I turn her in,
then they'll...
[ATSUSHI]
Let's go...
[KYOUKA]
Where?
[ATSUSHI]
Uh?
Well... where are we going?
Uh...
Was there some place
you wanted to take me?
Oh... I suppose...
I thought... maybe...
Uhh... well...
I figured we could go
wherever you wanted to go!
There must be a lot
of places around here
a girl your age would
want to check out.
Somewhere liiiiiike...
Oh! A couple spot!
Like a date!
I mean, I do have
the rest of the day off,
and I doubt you've gotten
to go out and just have fun.
Like a date?
[ATSUSHI]
Mm-hmm!
A date with you?
[ATSUSHI]
Mm-hmm!
Hmm?
Oh! No! Uh!
I-I didn't mean it like that!
[KYOUKA]
Let's go.
[ATSUSHI]
Oh...
Okay.
[ATSUSHI]
Whoa!
That's a giant baseball arena!
[KYOUKA]
It's Yokohama Stadium.
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, really?
[KYOUKA]
I've seen it on a map.
[KYOUKA] This is
Yokohama's memorial hall.
[ATSUSHI]
Ohh...
[KYOUKA]
The Museum of Cultural History.
[ATSUSHI]
Wow.
[KYOUKA]
Yokohama Customs Headquarters.
[ATSUSHI]
Ahhh...
You're amazing!
[KYOUKA]
I just have the map
and building structures
memorized is all.
[ATSUSHI]
Oh! I know this one!
The Red Brick Warehouse, right?
[GIRL 1]
This place has the best crepes!
[GIRL 2]
Oo! Let me have a bite!
Mmm! That's delicious!
[GIRL 1]
Right?! Seriously!
That place is pretty popular.
I think I heard from Naomi
that they make really
good crepes there.
It wasn't on the map...
[ATSUSHI]
Mm?
[KYOUKA]
I wanna try it...
[ATSUSHI]
Really?!
But... you ate so much
boiled tofu earlier...
Crepes sound good.
Ohhh...
I finally got the
plushie that I wanted...
[ATSUSHI sighs]
[KYOUKA] There's just one
more place I need to go to.
All right.
[ATSUSHI]
She's really being proactive.
[KYOUKA]
We're here.
Huh?
[KYOUKA] Today's been
more than enough fun.
It really should've
ended with the boiled tofu.
[ATSUSHI] But, if you turn
yourself in, you'll...
[KYOUKA]
...be sentenced to death.
Thirty-five people have
died because of me.
It's a sin that I'm still alive.
Besides, even if I returned to
the Port Mafia, I'd be executed.
[AKUTAGAWA]
Executed?
[coughs]
[AKUTAGAWA]
We wouldn't execute you...
Not after fulfilling
your mission.
[COP 1]
Hey! What's going on?
[AKUTAGAWA] "I finally got
the plushie that I wanted"...
A transmitter is implanted
inside your body.
Your whereabouts and every
action you make are known to us.
Huh?!
[AKUTAGAWA]
Let's go home.
[ATSUSHI]
Where am I?
[JUNICHIROU]
Atsushi has been abducted!
Abducted?
Well, that's terrible timing.
I guess.
[DOPPO] That ministry escort
job already has the Agency
in an uproar.
We don't have enough hands
on deck to go looking for him.
Do we have any information
on what happened?
Oh... we do.
Based on eyewitness reports, he
was attacked in broad daylight
and shoved into a truck.
Destination unknown.
[DOPPO]
That's not good.
There are numerous
dedicated smuggling routes.
Moving a single person in
secret would be child's play.
[JUNICHIROU] We have to
do something to help him...
[RAMPO]
Do we really?
Why's that?
Huh?
He was captured because of the
bounty on him as a weretiger.
Sounds like a
personal matter to me.
We're not exactly
his foster family,
and it's not like he joined the
Agency to gain our protection.
Maybe not, but Atsushi
is one of our own now.
Actually, Rampo
is right about this.
We shouldn't be the
ones to take action.
[JUNICHIROU]
But Mr. Kunikida...
I guess we should
inform the police then?
[DOPPO] They've designated
Atsushi as a major threat.
If they knew he worked here,
we would certainly take a hit.
[NAOMI]
'Scuse me...
You guys clearly don't
seem to be capable of coming
to an agreement by yourselves.
So instead of going on with the
"ifs," "ands," or "buts"...
...I just went and
asked him for help.
President!
[DOPPO]
Please forgive me.
As soon as our work is done,
I'll gather whatever
information--
Our plans have changed.
Listen up, all of you!
Our newest member
has been abducted.
The current project
will be suspended
until he has been returned
to us safe and sound.
Suspended?
What shall we do about
the escort job, sir?
I will contact the client.
Not to worry...
They owe me enough favors
that we can afford to
hold off on it for now.
[RAMPO]
Sir... are you sure about this?
[YUKICHI]
What's your concern?
Well, just consider
the reasoning behind it...
[YUKICHI]
One of our own is in danger.
He needs help.
Are you telling me
that there can be
any better reasoning than that?
[RAMPO]
Hmm...
Kunikida.
[DOPPO]
Sir.
[YUKICHI]
You have three hours.
[DOPPO]
Understood!
[yawns]
[OSAMU] If my predictions
are correct, I believe...
...it's about time.
Huh?
[CHUUYA]
Plotting as usual, are we?
I know that voice!
[CHUUYA] Well, this sure
is a wonderful sight...
Rivals a billion
dollar masterpiece.
Right... Dazai?
So creepy...
Just... frightening...
[CHUUYA]
I like your reaction.
[CHUUYA] It makes me
want to strangle you...
[OSAMU]
Still the same old Chuuya.
[CHUUYA]
Huh?!
What's that mean?!
I've always had a
question I wanted to ask.
Where exactly do you
get all your tacky hats?
Say what you want, old snake!
I bet you're still
obsessing over committing
suicide, aren't ya...?
[OSAMU]
Yup.
[CHUUYA]
Oh.
It's no fun if you don't
even try to deny it.
In any case, now you're
just a pathetic prisoner.
Makes you cry, doesn't it?
Actually...
I find this all a
bit too convenient...
You might be able
to fool Akutagawa,
but you can't fool me.
I am your former
partner, after all.
So out with it...
What's your play here?
Clearly it was to
be caught and killed.
So far I've half-succeeded.
[CHUUYA] That kind of reckless
planning just isn't like you.
If it was, I would've
killed you a long time ago.
You're overthinking this.
By the way,
just why are you here?
To pay you back!
[OSAMU]
Hmm?
[CHUUYA] You used to
give me a really hard time.
You toyed with me.
But now...
I can give you my "gratitude"
for all of that with interest.
I have no idea what
you're plotting...
...but I wanna
fight you... Dazai.
I want to crush you
and whatever scheme
you've dreamed up.
[OSAMU]
Chuuya...
Huh?
So you could've
escaped any time...
You really thought
you could stop me?
You must be joking.
I'm rather liking
this turn of events!
[RAMPO sighs]
[DOPPO] Scan all security
footage in the city
from the past six hours!
Oh, right...
Kenji, do you have that file?
Right here.
[RAMPO]
That's unfortunate.
There're no comic
strips in this paper.
Hey, Kenji!
What is it?
[RAMPO]
Can you find out if there're any
tricky homicide cases nearby?
Well, okay...
...but the president
won't be happy with you.
Nevermind.
We found it!
[DOPPO] This photo
was taken by a tourist
who witnessed the abduction.
[YUKICHI] That type
of truck is everywhere.
True.
Not to mention
the plates were fake.
However, there's only
a few places nearby
that make those changes.
After Kenji went to all the
repair shops we could think of,
they were happy to oblige us.
I found out the truck
belongs to Karma Transit.
They're mules with a
background in smuggling.
So they would have information
on his whereabouts... yes?
Correct.
They're the only ones
outside of the Port Mafia
who might have information
about the abduction.
Tanizaki is on
standby at the site.
He can move in at any time.
[JUNICHIROU]
Understood.
I'll begin the infiltration.
[DOPPO]
How's it look?
It's so quiet you could
almost hear a pin drop.
There's not a
single sign of life.
Hang on!
[JUNICHIROU]
We're too late!
They beat us to it!
Hey!
What's wrong?
[JUNICHIROU]
They shut them up.
All of them are dead.
It's Akutagawa.
Now that our only lead
was snuffed out, what next?
[YUKICHI]
Rampo...
[RAMPO]
Hmm?
[YUKICHI]
It's your turn.
Do I really have to?
Please, we need you this time!
Look, Rampo...
I'll give you something if
you can bring him back safely.
Like what, a bonus?
A promotion?
I'm not interested.
I think I'll pass.
If you go, I'll give you ...
[YUKICHI]
...praise.
Well... why didn't you
say so in the first place?!
Let's do it!
Ability...
Ultra-Deduction!
[RAMPO]
Hmm, I see...
Atsushi's location is...
...right here!
The boat's traveling
at 20 knots
making it's way
toward the open sea.
Atsushi's alive...
...for now, at least.
[gasps]
[DOPPO]
That means...
[YUKICHI]
Exactly right.
They're shipping him overseas.
That's bad.
The moment he's out of the
country, we can't do anything.
[YUKICHI]
Kunikida...
Huh?
Use this.
[YUKICHI] It's the Agency's
high-speed boat.
Bring him back, no matter what.
[DOPPO]
Understood.
I promise, I will
retrieve Atsushi Nakajima!
[DOPPO]
Don't you die on me, kid...
[AKUTAGAWA]
Do you know what it's like
to live in the pit of despair?
It's an infinite darkness
where no light can reach you.
Teach her how
it feels, weretiger.
To help no one,
to be trusted by no one,
living in fear,
trembling like a worm.
[ATSUSHI]
This ends now, Akutagawa!
I can't forgive you for this!
[AKUTAGAWA]
The feeling is mutual!
[ATSUSHI]
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 10:
"Rashoumon and the Tiger."