[ATSUSHI] I haven't smelled
tatami mats... in a long time.
Hmm... Huh?
Where am I?
What happened last night?
Uhn... Was it... a dream?
Do you remember anything
from when you were transformed?
[ATSUSHI]
What are you talking about?
Oh! Look at that, your right
hand didn't change back.
My right hand?
[gasps]
[pants]
[sighs]
[ATSUSHI] Sleeping under
a roof feels... so good.
[cellphone ringing]
W-What? What? What?!
Huh? Uhh... Okay,
I'll get it. I'm coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
I'm doing it!
Right this second!
Which button am I supposed
to push? This one?
Uh, no, no, no. Uh, this one?
Nope! C'mon! Yes! H-Hello?!
And good morning to you!
[ATSUSHI]
Oh... Hi, Dazai.
It's another beautiful day!
What do you think of
your new accommodations?
They're great, thanks.
I mean, compared
to sleeping outside,
this place is like heaven to me.
I'm happy to hear that.
The change of clothes
at your pillow is a gift
from everyone at the agency.
Oh, wow!
Thank you so much for
everything you've done for me.
By the way, Atsushi,
I apologize for asking, but...
...I need help with a teensy
weensy emergency.
[ATSUSHI]
Emergency?
[OSAMU]
Yes, and it's quite urgent.
I'll give you the
specific location,
and I need you to meet
me there immediately.
This is a crisis, and you're
the only one who can help!
Understand?
O-Okay, I understand.
[OSAMU]
Listen carefully.
Are you ready, Atsushi?
Yes!
[OSAMU]
First, when you leave the room,
make sure you close
and lock the door.
Then look behind you!
Behind me...? Uh?!
[ATSUSHI]
Uh... What are you doing?
[OSAMU]
What do you think?
[ATSUSHI] I think I'm
hallucinating this whole thing?
[OSAMU]
Wrong! Guess again!
An attack from a
dangerous suspect?
Or did you get caught in a trap?
[OSAMU]
I got in myself.
Huh?!
[OSAMU]
Well, you see...
I read about this fascinating
way to commit suicide
by getting stuck in an oil drum,
so I decided to give it a shot.
Securing the feet is key...
But now that I've managed to do
that, I'm really just suffering.
I've wedged myself
in pretty deep,
and I can't get out on my own.
I might die.
I see...
So this is a way
to commit suicide.
You chose to do it, and
you think that it's working.
I don't see what the problem is.
I like the idea of suicide,
but I'm not all interested
in pain and suffering.
Who wants that?!
All right...
[sighs]
There.
My name is Atsushi Nakajima.
[ATSUSHI] Just last night,
I turned into a wild tiger
and went on a
destructive rampage.
This man, Osamu Dazai,
brought me back to normal.
[groans]
[ATSUSHI] Dazai has a special
power, and he's not alone.
He works with a team
of people endowed
with supernatural gifts in
the Armed Detective Agency.
[OSAMU]
Atsushi Nakajima!
[ATSUSHI gasps]
From this day forward,
you're going be one of us.
You're the new member of
the Armed Detective Agency.
[OSAMU sighs]
That was painful.
I owe you a favor, Atsushi.
Without your ingenious help,
I would've eventually
snapped in two at the waist.
Such agony.
Why didn't you call
your coworkers?
Couldn't they've helped
you get out of the barrel?
Oh, I called them, all right.
I told them I was
at death's door.
They didn't understand
my predicament.
They were all like,
"Well, congratulations!
You're finally doing it!"
[ATSUSHI]
Supportive friends.
Heh heh heh...
[OSAMU]
Jeez.
Anyone gifted
with supernatural powers
isn't totally right in the head.
[ATSUSHI]
"Gifted"... Hmm...
Dazai.
[OSAMU]
Hm?
[ATSUSHI] Everyone at the
Armed Detective Agency...
I mean, the private
investigators...
They're all gifted
with powers, right?
[OSAMU] Right, we're an
armed force taking on enemies
the police don't stand
a chance against.
[ATSUSHI] Then I don't stand
a chance at joining the agency.
[OSAMU]
What are you talking about?
You're plenty gifted.
[ATSUSHI] It's true that
I have the supernatural ability
to turn into a tiger.
But what good is it
if I have absolutely no
control over my power?
I'm not even aware of it
once I start to transform.
And I can't will myself
to change into a wild tiger.
So I don't understand
how I'd be of any use,
even if I could join.
I really appreciate
the offer, though.
I am sorry.
[OSAMU]
Very well.
What's your plan, then?
I've decided I'll look
for a low-skilled,
low-wage job I can handle.
I'm just a little afraid it
won't be very easy to find.
[OSAMU] I think I may know
of the perfect job for you.
Huh?
I might even be able
to help you get it.
Seriously?
[ATSUSHI]
Thank you so much!
We'll meet with the supervisor.
He'll give you all the
details about the work,
your co-workers,
and the organization.
I've got a good
feeling about this.
He'll love you.
What's the job title?
[OSAMU]
No point spoiling the fun.
But just so you know,
there may be a test of sorts.
Eh?! A test?
Atsushi, can you read and write?
I can!
They taught me at
the orphanage school.
Great. Then you'll be perfect.
Whew!
[OSAMU] Yes, you'll be
just fine at this place.
I guarantee it.
Thank you so much.
[OSAMU laughs]
You'd better thank me...
Just leave it to me,
and everything will be fine!
Don't you worry!
After all, I am Dazai...
The most trusted member of
the Armed Detective Agency,
and a true hero to
adoring fans everywhere.
I've been looking
everywhere for you, Dazai!
You bandage-squandering machine!
Ohh!!
Oh, you Kunikida.
Why couldn't you come up
with a better nickname?
Because you're delusional!
You think you're "the most
trusted member" of the agency?
You get more complaints
than anyone else!
People curse you
out on a regular basis!
Really?
What? No way.
Since when did I
ever get a complaint?!
[DOPPO] Here was a call
we received in August:
"A so-called employee
of yours has been caught
in our offshore fishing net.
Can you come retrieve him?"
Here is a call from September:
"Some weirdo's got
himself buried on my farm.
Could he be one of yours?"
[OSAMU]
Th-Th-Th-Th...
[DOPPO] "That skinny rat
needs to pay his tab, okay?!
All six months worth!"
I'm flabbergasted...
Who knew you were so
skilled at doing impressions
of other people?!
[growls]
You worthless cad!
Stop ridiculing me.
I'm gonna shake you silly!
I'm starting to have
second thoughts
about accepting his help.
Maybe I should look
for a job on my own.
[DOPPO]
Oh, right!
Huh?
I just lost a whole
minute with this idiot.
He's got a knack
for wasting my time.
We've gotta get to the agency!
We do?
We have an emergency!
A man has taken a hostage and
threatened to blow up our office
Huh...?
A mad bomber?
[ATSUSHI]
Uh...
[DOPPO]
What? What's your question?
The agency's
on the fourth floor.
[ATSUSHI] Eh, no, I wasn't
thinking about that.
It was more, well--
[OSAMU] Let's take
the stairs to be safe.
[ATSUSHI]
E-Excuse me, but I--
--[DOPPO] Quiet!
--[ATSUSHI] Oh, sorry.
[OSAMU]
Atsushi, it's show time.
[ATSUSHI]
It is?
[JUNICHIROU]
I can't...
I can't take it anymore...
It's all your fault...
The awful Armed Detective
Agency's fault!
Now, where's the president?
Bring me the president!
If you don't.
I'll blow everyone in
this place to kingdom come.
[NAOMI screams]
[OSAMU] Sounds like this
guy has a personal grudge.
That's inconvenient.
[DOPPO]
Agreed.
[ATSUSHI]
Why'd you bring me here again?
Based on what he's saying,
the bomber seems
furious at the agency.
Honestly, I don't think
I can help you.
May I go now?
[OSAMU]
Because of the work we do,
we attract a lot of ill will.
[ATSUSHI]
Did you hear what I said?
[OSAMU] That is a military
grade, high-level explosive.
If the bomber acts on
his threat and detonates it,
It'll kill us and
destroy the whole floor.
Oh no.
We may be able to reduce
the force of the blast
if we can find
something to cover
the bomb before it detonates.
[boom]
But given the circumstances...
Since he took her hostage,
he's not only mad, he's cruel.
Do you know who she is?
[OSAMU]
Her name is Naomi.
She's a part-time
office assistant.
[ATSUSHI]
She's not an agent?
Then she's just an innocent
victim in this terrible mess!
So what do we do?
He wants to see the president.
Bring him here.
Are you insane?
He'll try to kill the president!
We can't let the boss walk
into a bad situation like this!
Plus, he's off
on a business trip.
Right, I forgot.
Then there's only one option...
[ATSUSHI] Are they going
to use their powers?
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
[laughs]
Nah-nah-n'nah-nah.
[DOPPO]
Hey.
Easy does it, kid.
Stay away! I only want
to see the president!
Don't you try anything funny,
or I'll blow this place to bits!
Okay.
[JUNICHIROU]
I know who you are.
You're Kunikida!
You want me to lower my guard
so you can use that annoying
ability of yours to stop me!
Well that sure ain't happening.
Lay down on that desk
on your hands and knees
and keep both feet
above your head!
[DOPPO]
Huh?
You'll do exactly as I say,
or I'm taking everyone
here down with me!
Fine.
This is bad.
Because of his personal
grudge against the Agency,
he's done his research on all
the members names and faces.
If I go out there
and try to talk to him,
it'll only make him more angry.
Oh my...
Whatever shall we do now?
[ATSUSHI] Uh-oh. I just
got a really bad feeling...
A-tsu-shi can...
[ATSUSHI]
Absolutely not.
I haven't even
said anything, yet.
I already know
what you're gonna ask.
[OSAMU]
Listen to me, Atsushi...
You're the only option.
You're not a formal member,
and the bomber doesn't
know you at all.
You're right.
But if I go, I won't be
able to do anything.
[OSAMU]
You'll be fine.
We just need you to
distract him for a little while.
Try talking to him.
We'll take care
of everything else.
Let me think here...
Ah! How about you put on
an act? Make it depressing--
like you think you're a
real worthless human being.
I know you can do it. Right?
Here are some props.
[OSAMU]
Trust me.
Scuffles on this
scale are child's play
compared to what we
normally deal with...
You can handle this, Atsushi.
[ATSUSHI]
D-D-D-Don't do it!
Huh?!!
[ATSUSHI] Wh-Wh-Wh-What are
you hoping to get out of this?
I... I bet this would make
your parents really sad!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm sorry!
I don't know who you are.
You're not with the agency.
[ATSUSHI] Uh!
I-I-I'm a newspaper boy.
I was just paaing by
as I was on my route.
Why the hell would you
get involved in this situation?
Because what you're
doing isn't right.
No matter how you feel
you shouldn't
threaten to kill people.
Think about the wonderful
things worth living for.
Yeah, like what?
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
[JUNICHIROU]
What's something to live for?!
Y-Y-Yummy tea on rice!
Tea on rice is a reason to live!
[JUNICHIROU]
Hmm?
Oh, and sleeping somewhere
with a roof over your head!
Waking up under a roof is great.
And when you open your eyes,
every day is a new day...
But...
If you push that button,
neither of us will ever
see another new day...
...and that's because
we'll be dead.
I understand the concept.
Wait!! Seeee...
I really don't think
you've thought about this
from all the angles.
I mean, if you die,
you're really dead!
I'm sure you wish you
were dead sometimes,
but there are many people
who keep on living,
even though their lives
are completely awful.
Oh, people like me!
I don't have any family,
and no friends either!
I even got chased out
of an orphanage.
I have nowhere to go,
and no hope for the future...
What's worse,
I turn into a wild tiger.
Yeah, you heard me right!
In fact, it might be true that
I lack redeeming qualities,
and everyone agrees I'm
a useless member of society.
But I'm still alive and
I haven't gone psycho!
[OSAMU]
Doing great, Atsushi.
It's almost like
this performance
isn't just an act for you.
Now why don't you put
down that bomb detonator...
...and we can look
for jobs together, okay?
No, thanks.
I'm not exactly looking
for work these days...
Now, Kunikida!
[DOPPO]
Already on it!
Ability...
Doppo Poet...
Wire Gun!
Crap!
Get him, Kunikida!
[DOPPO]
Like I already said, I'm on it!
[OSAMU]
Okay, everyone.
One man down. Well done.
[sighs]
[OFFICER WORKERS laugh and clap]
"One man down"?
Are you're kidding me?!
[OSAMU]
Huh?
Fine, so it was just one guy,
but I had to do all
the hard physical work.
Unlike you.
You're all talk and no action.
Oh, now you're being ridiculous.
That was my only option.
After all, you lost
at rock-paper-scissors.
You bastard...
Come on.
All's well that
ends well, teammate.
I'm just glad you're
still in one piece.
But speaking of your health,
I've been meaning to tell you...
I heard that
if you're too neurotic,
your aging becomes accelerated.
[gasps]
Really, is that true?
Yes, write this down.
"A tip for better longevity:
If you're too neurotic...
...your aging
becomes accelerated..."
I'm messing with you.
[DOPPO]
Ugh!! You little weasel!
I'm gonna teach you
to stop ridiculing me!
[grunts]
Hyaaah!
Got it...
The hell?!
[JUNICHIROU]
Now you'll pay!
I swear, anyone
with supernatural powers
is not totally right
in the head...
Thirty seconds
left till detonation!
[DOPPO]
Hey, kid!
[JUNICHIROU]
No way!
Kunikida!
What do I do?
We may be able to reduce
the force of the blast
if we can find something
to cover it before it detonates.
Something to cover the bomb...
Something...
There's nothing here!
[whimpers]
Atsushi! What?
[ATSUSHI] Well, I guess
I'm crazy to do this.
You fool!
No, don't!
Huh...?
[DOPPO]
Jeez...
Huh?
You know I figured
the kid was stupid,
just not that stupid.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
He even has the talent to
become a suicidal maniac.
Wouldn't you agree
with me, Tanizaki?
Sorry. Are you okay?
Huh?
Aw, my sweet big brother!
Ah!
Please tell me you're all right!
[ATSUSHI]
What?
Ah... You were so
wonderful as the villain!
I believed every second of it.
I had the time of
my life being tied up!
And I loved how intense
and dangerous it felt.
Please promise me we'll
continue where we left off,
once we get home.
[ATSUSHI]
Hmm...
So she was in on
the entire thing, too?
You mad?
If you're upset,
you should blame Dazai.
Or yourself.
After all, you chose an idiot
like him to help you find work!
Wait, does that
mean this is the job?
It sure is.
I told you there
was a test involved.
As in, an entrance exam?
Exactly right.
The exam has been completed
without any
complications, President.
[YUKICHI]
I see.
President?
[YUKICHI] Dazai came to
my office saying his work
had brought him in contact
with a capable young man.
But I needed more than his word,
so I had him test your mettle.
[gasps]
[OSAMU]
You did well.
I brought up the idea
that the Agency hire you,
but since you've been
designated a major threat
throughout the ward,
there was disagreement as to
whether we should take you in.
Then Dazai asked me a question.
[OSAMU]
President.
What if the most gifted
person in the world came
into your office, wanting to
work here, would you hire them?
[YUKICHI]
Power alone doesn't make one fit
to be a member of the agency.
[OSAMU]
Mmm...
That's exactly why
I'm recommending him.
With that in mind, are you
ready to make your decision?
Ah...
[YUKICHI]
I'll let Dazai decide.
[OSAMU]
You can trust me, sir.
Hold on, Dazai.
This is all happening too fast!
Does this mean the job you told
me about this morning was...
You apparently passed the test.
Welcome to the Armed Detective
Agency, Atsushi Nakajima.
Not again!
Great, I'm glad
I was able to help.
Congratulations,
you passed your big exam.
[ATSUSHI]
Uh, no, no, no!
This job is way
too violent for me,
and you people are
completely reckless!
Yet, you're the one who
threw yourself on a bomb
to protect the rest of us.
That takes a special
kind of person.
You know he's right.
I can't believe how
brave you were!
You'll do fine working here.
Will I...?
Have you reached
a decision, sir?
Do you think the young man
preformed competently enough
to join the agency?
[KIRAKO] Oh, a tea leaf's
standing straight up...
I think that's a very
good omen, President.
[YUKICHI]
Too hot!
[OSAMU]
Now, obviously,...
...we can't force you to join.
But if you don't, there
are a lot of considerations
that cause me to
worry for your future.
You'll have to vacate
your present Agency-owned
living accommodations.
You don't really have
any specialized skills,
nor do you have friends
or any personal
contacts in the city...
That will make finding
a job very difficult.
And let's not forget,
you are a wanted tiger
with a bounty on your head.
Should anyone discover
of that personal detail,
you'd get fired...
Or worst, you'd be captured,
tied up and maybe shot dead.
[ATSUSHI]
Sh-Shot dead?
But if you were with the Agency,
it would be a
much happier story...
So I'm stuck here?
Welcome aboard!
We're excited to
work with you, Atsushi.
Right, sweet brother?
Remember to follow
the rules, rookie.
Well, I'm glad it's settled...
Oh, brother.
[ICHIYOU]
The weretiger has been located.
[ATSUSHI]
So Dazai, tell me,
what did you do before
you entered the Agency?
[OSAMU]
Take a guess.
If you get it right, I'll give
you a prize of 700,000 yen.
[ATSUSHI]
700,000?!
[OSAMU] Meanwhile, we have
a guest at the Agency office.
It looks like there's
been another incident.
[ATSUSHI]
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 3: "Yokohama
Gangster Paradise."
[OSAMU]
Think about it.
I could have been a manga artist
or even an anime producer!