[ATSUSHI]
"Take the weretiger alive"...
I'm the one you're after?
[AKUTAGAWA]
But of course.
The objective of this
mission has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
Your friends got caught
in the crossfire.
Just an unfortunate consequence.
[gasps]
All of this is because of me?
[AKUTAGAWA]
Indeed...
That is your karma, weretiger.
Your life is bound to cause only
misfortune to those around you.
[gasps]
That's my... karma?
Special ability... Rashoumon!
[ATSUSHI gasps]
What happened...? Where am I?
[DOPPO]
So you've finally come to...
[ATSUSHI]
Kunikida...
Damn it, kid.
I can't believe you pulled that
stunt and at such a busy time.
[ATSUSHI]
I...
[grunts]
[ATSUSHI]
I was... attacked by the Mafia.
[smack]
[ATSUSHI]
I remember!
Mr. Kunikida, are
Junichirou and Naomi...?!
Just calm down.
They're both okay.
Are you sure... Really sure?
[DOPPO]
Yes.
Dr. Yosano is treating
Tanizaki next door as we speak.
[AKIKO]
My, what a big, bad injury
you've managed to rack up
there for me, Junichirou.
It's impressive.
You must really like
my treatment a lot...
[JUNICHIROU grunts]
[slurps]
So I'll give you the extra
special treatment this time.
[laughs]
[JUNICHIROU screams]
[grunts and groans]
[moans]
[ATSUSHI]
That's... medical... treatment?
I heard a rumor...
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
There's a bounty for your
head on the black market.
It may be as high as
seven billion yen by now.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh...?
[DOPPO]
Seven billion yen.
You've moved up in the world.
No wonder the Port Mafia
wants to get their hands on you.
Seven billion yen?
But of course.
The objective of this
mission has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
It's all beginning
to make sense.
W-W-What should I do?
The Mafia might attack
the Agency at any time.
Why me, why me why me???
Stop panicking.
Huh...
[DOPPO] It's true that the Port
Mafia are extremely violent,
but you must keep your cool.
Otherwise you
could wind up dead...
...not that I care.
Um... Uh...
I think your notebook's...
upside down.
I am not losing
my cool over the Mafia!
I'd beat them back, even if
they attacked this very second!
I'd punch and whack
and chip and chop!
[ATSUSHI]
Kunikida's pretty wound up...
He's not making any sense!
[ATSUSHI]
It must mean
the Agency's situation
is pretty bad,
and it's all because of me.
[DOPPO]
They'll come for sure.
[gasps]
[DOPPO] You are the
one who brought this on.
The worst-case scenario
may come to pass...
Think carefully about
what you will do.
[ATSUSHI]
What in the world can I do?
What?
[DOPPO]
By the way, kid...
Huh?
There's something
I've been looking for.
You haven't seen my
glasses around, have you?
[approaching footsteps]
It's time, sir.
[RYUUROU]
Stand back.
[surprised gasps]
[RYUUROU]
Sorry to intrude.
I hate to bother you at work.
[WORKER 1]
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
We're here to work as well.
But we wont be very long.
It has recently
come to our attention
that a group of insurgents has
started selling Port Mafia cargo
on the black market,
and that this is their base.
You won't mind if I have a look
through the cargo for evidence.
[WORKER 2 grunts]
Huh?
Seems I found it already.
[screams]
[WORKERS murmur]
That's impossible!
It's a steel pipe.
Huh?
[RYUUROU] You've never
seen a gift in action before?
[screams]
[WORKERS mutter]
[RYUUROU]
Kill them.
Kill them all.
[RYUUROU] A smoke always tastes
best after a job well done.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
An explosion.
What's going on?
[CROWD 1]
I hear it was a massacre.
[CROWD 2]
Damn...
[CROWD 1] The police
investigating the incident
say the Port Mafia's
military squad did it...
The Black Lizard group,
the most violent of them all.
[CROWD 2]
The Black Lizard?
[CROWD 1]
Yeah.
They're as good as
special ops forces.
And completely merciless.
[ATSUSHI]
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard...
If they actually decide
to attack the Agency...
[ATSUSHI]
Mm...
"The worst-case scenario."
[telephone rings]
Yes?
Who is this?
[ATSUSHI]
It's me.
Weretiger!
He must have seen the business
card I left at the Agency.
Your colleagues may
have saved you the other day,
but that won't be
the case next time.
So what do you want?
[ATSUSHI]
I'm going to quit the Agency.
I'm quitting and
going on the run alone.
Good luck finding me!
I get it.
You want us to call off the
war on the Agency. Right?
Call the Black Lizard now!
[DOPPO] Oh, so you
finally decide to show up.
Thanks to you, we've
got a big mess here.
We're probably looking
at the worst-case scenario.
Help me carry these, will ya?
Hey!
There's no need to worry.
[DOPPO]
Hmmm?
Because the worst-case scenario
isn't gonna to happen now.
The Agency is perfectly safe.
Huh?
Hey, kid, you can't just leave!
How am I supposed
to carry all this?!
[ORPHANAGE MAN 1]
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
[ORPHANAGE MAN 2] No orphanage
wants someone like you!
[ORPHANGE WOMAN 1] The world
would be a better place
if you'd just die
in a ditch somewhere!
[approaching footsteps]
[RYUUROU]
You're late.
Late by two minutes.
Heh!
You really shouldn't be so
uptight all the time, Gramps.
This place is so depressing.
Is Gin here yet?
Or is he late, too?
[RYUUROU]
He's here...
Look behind you.
[sighs]
Why am I even surprised
you're creeping around?
You get on my nerves.
Lookin' for a fight?
[RYUUROU]
Stop being foolish.
Or would either of you prefer to
be reported "Killed in Action"?
[gasps]
Fine, whatever.
Let's just get on
with it already.
[cellphone ringing]
[click]
[RYUUROU]
We're all here.
[ICHIYOU]
Glad to hear it.
We're ready...
What target requires
three of us to bring it down?
[ICHIYOU]
The target...
...is the Armed
Detective Agency's office.
[RYUUROU] Why aren't
we pursuing the weretiger?
The previous attempt failed
because the Agency interfered.
We won't let that happen again.
We'll annihilate the Agency
first so they can't protect him.
And if there are no survivors?
[ICHIYOU]
That's fine by me.
Hmph.
Understood.
[click]
[ICHIYOU] That detective agency
won't make a fool of Akutagawa.
I won't let them!
[AKUTAGAWA coughs]
[AKUTAGAWA]
Fear death.
Fear slaughter.
Those who desire
the death of others
have an equal desire to die.
[coughs]
Men who are worthless
have no right to draw breath.
[AKUTAGAWA]
You have surprised me.
Your resolve is admirable.
[AKUTAGAWA] And now I will
give you a reason to live.
[OSAMU] I have finally
found a reason to live!
Did I say "to live"?
No, I have found
the reason I am still alive!
That's right.
I've lived to this day,
so I could commit double-suicide
together with you.
Ah, belladonna, at last.
Do what you want... alone.
Double-suicide can't
be done alone.
[WAITRESS]
By the way, Mr. Dazai?
How's your life
insurance coverage?
Is it up to date?
I'll tell you anything!
But why ask about that?
[WAITRESS]
Oh, let me tell you why...
You have racked up quite a tab.
It must be paid back.
A good insurance policy
would do just that.
I have the perfect plan. Heh!
Ah! Your vitality
is so blinding.
I can't think straight!
[WAITRESS giggles]
If the best you can do
is change the subject,
I'll just have to
demand compensation
from your Agency.
[OSAMU] Ah, your decisiveness
is even more blinding
than your vitality!
So there's not even a lookout?
Talk about careless.
Ah...!
[AKIKO]
Uh...!
Aah!
[RAMPO gulps]
[DOPPO]
Can I help you?
[RYUUROU]
Apologies, detectives.
We must have forgotten
to make an appointment.
And we even forgot to knock.
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard!
Please, forgive the bad manners.
Our work here will be done soon.
Get out, you good-for-nothing!
[ORPHANAGE MAN 2] No orphanage
wants someone like you!
[ORPHANGE WOMAN 1] The world
would be a better place
if you'd just die in a
ditch somewhere!
[ATSUSHI]
All of them were right about me.
There isn't a place
in the world for me.
I'll never belong anywhere.
[distant rapid gunfire]
Gunshots?
But why is that coming from...
[shocked gasps]
Why is the Agency
being attacked?!
[ATSUSHI]
Uh, sorry!
[pants]
[ATSUSHI]
Why is this happening?
I'm the reason
everyone's in danger...
...again!!
Stop it!!
What the...?
[gasps]
[groans]
Ahh!
There! Yeah!
[AKIKO]
Hyah!
[RAMPO gulps]
[DOPPO]
Hmm?
So you finally came back, kid.
Ehhhhhhhhh...
[DOPPO sighs]
This is exactly
why I hate raids.
They really throw off our
budgetary projections.
[DOPPO] Repairing
all this structural damage
and replacing ruined inventory
is gonna cost us a damn fortune.
[AKIKO] Using machine guns for
a raid was really over the top.
Now somebody needs to go
around the neighborhood
with apologies and
reconciliatory gifts.
Isn't it your turn, Kunikida?
So... the worst-case scenario
has indeed come to pass.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh???
This is the
"worst-case scenario"?
Gifts and apologies?
And that's the terrifying
Port Mafia hit squad?
What the...
[KENJI]
Mr. Kunikida,
what do you want me
to do with all of them?
[DOPPO]
Just throw them out the window.
[KENJI]
Roger!
[hums]
One...
Two...
Three!
[DOPPO]
I wish they would stop
raiding the office
over and over again.
[ATSUSHI]
Over and over again?
[KENJI laughs]
Woo!
[ATSUSHI] The Armed Detective
Agency is so much more violent
than the Port Mafia.
[KENJI]
Yay!
[laughs]
[DOPPO] Hurry up and
help with the clean-up, kid!
[ATSUSHI]
Uh...
[KENJI]
Have a nice trip!
I can't believe you
simply wandered off
in the middle of
all the commotion!
You're a member
of the Agency now.
You should always be thinking
of what you can do to help out.
So stop staring at me
with those vacant eyes,
and start lending a hand!
[ATSUSHI]
Uh...
[DOPPO] Think carefully
about what you will do.
[ATSUSHI]
O... kay.
[laughs]
[growls]
Really?
If you've got
the time to laugh...
Eh... Huh?
Are you... crying?
Huh?! I'm... I'm...
I'm not crying!
Looks like you are.
[grunts]
I think it's pretty
obvious that I'm not!
[DOPPO]
Oh, the youth of today.
Even when given a job, you go
off and play without permission.
Then you cry if anyone
gives you a word of criticism.
So typical of your generation!
[ATSUSHI]
That's not it.
That's not what this is about.
[DOPPO]
But you are crying!
[ATSUSHI]
Okay, I am...
But not about what you think!
[RAMPO] The only reason
they can call themselves
a detective agency
and function as one
is due to my ability,
Ultra-Deduction.
Oh, a murder case has
arrived on our doorstep.
Okay, Atsushi!
Come with me while
I work on the case.
[ATSUSHI]
Uh...
I'm not sure
I'm up to the task...
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 5: "Murder on D Street."
Is this going to be an
actual detective story?
[RAMPO]
All's well that's well for me!