[ATSUSHI]
The Black Lizard...
The Armed Detective
Agency was attacked
by the Port Mafia's military
squad, the Black Lizard.
But the entire squad
was crushed thanks
to the battle skills of
Kunikida, Yosano, and Kenji.
That's how powerful the
Armed Detective Agency is.
Huh?
[RAMPO]
Hey, Harunochi.
A challenge for you:
Do you think you can you take
the marble out of this bottle?
I think I can do that.
Marble, really?
[glass breaking]
[KIRAKO]
Is this what you wanted?
[RAMPO] Mm-hmm. Marbles
are lovely, aren't they?
Now that you mention
it, yes, they are.
Um, isn't Rampo going
to help clean up the office?
[DOPPO]
Hmmm?
Hey, Kunikida.
[skrieks]
[RAMPO]
I can't stay.
I've got to head off to a job.
Oh, have you been called to
assist with a new murder case?
[RAMPO]
Yep.
The police are always
so desperate for my help.
They can't capture a
single criminal without me.
The fact is...
...my Ultra-Deduction is the
best ability in this agency.
I'm sure it's the best power
in the whole country.
It's no surprise that
everyone depends on it.
We're all indebted
to you, Rampo.
[RAMPO] Good, well, you know,
as long as you're aware.
You're funny.
It's odd that you call
yourselves a detective agency,
because the rest of you
have the deductive powers
of a pack of monkeys.
The only way you can investigate
anything is thanks to my ability
What you do is truly amazing.
With your
Ultra-Deduction skills,
you can see right to the
heart of a case in an instant.
[DOPPO] You're a role
model for the Agency--
no, for all gifted people.
[RAMPO]
Yeah, you're right.
[DOPPO]
Hey, kid.
Y-Yes?
Never mind the clean-up here.
You're done.
You need to go with Rampo.
You two will travel by train.
I-I'm gonna be a
detective's assistant?
It's a great responsibility...
[RAMPO]
Don't be silly.
I'm not a two-bit detective.
I don't need an "assistant."
[ATSUSHI]
Then why am I going with you?
Simple.
I never bothered to
learn how to take the train.
[RAMPO]
Hmmm...
[ATSUSHI]
Honestly, I was surprised
at how naive Rampo was.
He didn't know anything:
how to buy a ticket,
how to get
through the turnstile,
or how to figure out
which platform to go to...
I guess he really
can't do anything
without using his
supernatural ability.
You know you're late, Agents.
Now hold on, who are you?
Where's Yasui?
[MINOURA]
I'm Minoura.
I took over from Yasui.
This case has been
reassigned to our division,
so we no longer need
you or your agency.
[RAMPO]
That's ridiculous.
Every difficult case
should be overseen
by a master detective like me.
[MINOURA] We won't need
private investigators on this
because the victim was
a cop who worked for me.
[ATSUSHI]
Eh...
The victim's a lady.
Yes, sir.
Her body was found floating
in the river this morning.
[MINOURA] She was shot
three times in the chest.
We don't know where
or when she was killed.
We haven't found
the bullets either.
[RAMPO]
Any suspects?
Not yet. As far as
anyone at the office knew,
she wasn't in a relationship.
So we doubt it
was a jealous lover.
[RAMPO]
Very interesting.
So does that mean
you don't have any leads?
That's all the more reason why
we can't let some amateur
private eye handle this.
[POLICE OFFICER 1]
Hey!
Looks like the nets
caught something!
They put out nets?
Yeah, the net's
strung across the water.
Standard practice to
dredge evidence from the river.
Look over there! It's a man!
You sure?!
Do you think
that's a second victim?
[ATSUSHI]
Eh...
Hello, Atsushi.
This is quite the
strange coincidence.
Don't tell me you tried
to drown again, Osamu...
Don't be silly.
Committing suicide alone?
That's so passé these days.
I have made a decision that if
I am going to end everything,
I'll do it with a
beautiful woman!
Ah, double suicide!
What a sweet ring it has.
By comparison, it feels so empty
to think about bidding farewell
to this world all
by my lonesome.
That's my new plan.
I'm on the lookout
for a passionate
and suicidal woman
to die with me!
But how'd you get
caught in the net?
Hmph! I was just drifting along,
enjoying the glorious river!
[ATSUSHI]
I see.
But enough about me.
What brings you out
here today, friend?
[ATSUSHI]
I'm on a job.
A job?
What kind of job?
W-W-W-W-What tragedy...
What a terrible situation--
a lovely young woman in
her prime has lost her life...
She could have committed
double suicide with me!
My sorrow's crushing my heart,
and there's nothing
I can do to ease my pain.
[sobs]
Who the hell is
your weird friend?
He's a colleague at the Agency,
and yes, he always
acts this way.
[OSAMU] Oh, how I hope
you rest in peace, milady.
And now, an extraordinary
detective will avenge
your death for you and me both.
Isn't that right, Rampo?
[RAMPO]
It's tough to say.
I haven't officially
gotten the job yet.
[OSAMU]
What? Why?
Ask Mr. Detective.
We don't need
private eyes on this.
Everyone on my team is better
than any private dick out there.
Including you bums.
Oh? Tell me, Officer,
what's your name?
[SUGIMOTO]
What?
I am Sergeant Sugimoto, sir.
The victim, Ms. Yamagiwa was my
superior officer on the force.
All right, Sugimoto.
Here's your chance--solve
this case in sixty seconds.
Ready, set go.
What?!
I can solve this thing
in under a minute.
If you're as good
as he says you are,
you should be
able to do that too.
[MINOURA]
Hmm?
[RAMPO]
Okay, it's show time.
Let's see what you've got.
Ahh! Um, okay, well...
Gyah! Sixty seconds is
impossible, don't you think?!
Tick tock! Fifty seconds left.
What?!
[ATSUSHI] I hope that's
not what I look like
when I'm under
too much pressure.
Hold on. I know
Yamagiwa was pursuing
a political corruption case
and also running an
investigation on the Port Mafia.
The murderer's M.O.
is similar to the Mafia's
when they want retribution.
Maybe the Mafia did it
because they knew
she was getting too close.
No.
Uh...?
[OSAMU] The Port Mafia's
retaliatory methods
are quite specific.
They have a signature
that's as unique to
them as a fingerprint.
First, the traitor is
forced on the ground
and made to bite the curb.
Then they stomp on
his head to shatter his jaw.
Finally, they flip him over
and shoot him in the chest...
[OSAMU]
...three times.
I guess if we're being precise,
then technically yes,
but still...
So this M.O. is
similar to the Mafia's,
but not exactly the same.
That means...
The killer was
attempting a cover up?
Shooting two extra rounds to
make it look like a Mafia hit.
How cruel.
Beep!
Nice try, Sergeant.
Too bad, you've got a ways to go
before your case
solving skills match mine.
But don't feel bad,
you've been useful!
You've helped us prove that
Minoura's best detectives
are inferior to me.
[MINOURA]
Cut the crap!
I'm tired of all your jabber.
You can't crack hard cases
just with deduction.
You've been reading
too many crime novels.
Cases are solved
through investigation:
interviewing
persons of interest,
and closely analyzing
the crime scene.
Uh-huh? You've got
a pretty thick skull.
Great detectives don't
do "investigations."
My ability, Ultra-Deduction, can
instantly identify the killer.
I can also figure out when and
how the murder was committed.
But wait there's more,
I can see in my mind's eye
how to make the killer confess
and where the evidence
lies to prove our case.
My power truly is a rare gift.
Given my line of work,
I know all about you
gifted types and your powers.
But if you have
such a special ability,
then why do my colleagues
and I still have a job?
My thoughts exactly.
Now we're starting to understand
each other, detective.
[growls]
You little bastard!
[OSAMU]
Now, now, Detective.
Please pardon my colleague's
tactless behavior.
What can I say?
My personal motto is...
"All's well that's well for me!
Catchy right?
[ATSUSHI] My personal
motto would probably be
"What's better
than being alive?"
Well, well, well...
You can't stop bragging
about your ability,
so let's have a look at it.
[RAMPO]
Really?
So I guess I'm on the case?
You should've just asked me
nicely when I first got here.
Heh, too bad you've got a lot
more confidence than experience.
You realize there's
no hard evidence...?
Would you like me to
count to sixty for you?
Heeeh...
I won't need that long.
Watch closely now, Atsushi.
This is the ability
that keeps the Agency going.
Once he puts on those glasses...
Rampo's Ultra-Deduction
is active.
[ATSUSHI]
I can't believe Rampo's ability
to solve a case like this.
How does a power
like that even work?
Ability: Ultra-Deduction!
Yes, I see.
Heh! "I see," my ass.
You're trying to tell us
you know who the killer is?
[RAMPO]
Of course!
Okay?
The killer is...
The killer's you.
[RAMPO]
That's right.
You're the killer...
I know that you did it,
Sergeant Sugimoto.
Huh?
[ATSUSHI]
He did it?
[laughs]
Sergeant Sugimoto
works for me on the force.
Sergeant Sugimoto is
the one who killed her.
Ugh! Ridiculous!
What stupid killer would want to
come to the scene of the crime?
That's precisely why he's here.
He wants to stay close
to the investigation.
And in case I didn't
mention it...
I know where we can
find evidence to prove it.
Let me see your gun.
Y-You've got to be kidding me!
I can't just hand over
my firearm to a civilian!
They would take my badge away!
How convenient for you, Rampo.
Your source of evidence is the
one thing you can't look at.
[RAMPO]
But look at it this way.
If we examine that gun
and come up empty,
then you prove your right, and
I'm an idiot with a big mouth.
Hmph. I've had
enough of listening
to your annoying voice!
Sugimoto, show him your gun.
But, sir!
[MINOURA] This so-called
detective has barked up
this tree as far as he can go.
If we prove him wrong,
he'll shut up and go home.
Go on, you can
show him your gun.
Hey, what's the matter,
Sugimoto?
Even here in a city
filled with criminals,
it isn't easy to acquire
government issued ammunition...
Or for that matter a
government issued weapon.
Why aren't you saying
anything, Sugimoto?!
[RAMPO]
He's quiet.
But I think his mind is racing.
Specifically,
he's thinking about
the three bullets he's used and
how he'll explain their absence.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Sugimoto!
You can't be the killer!
Show us your gun,
and get this over with!
[sighs]
That's right, detective.
Not good.
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Are you crazy?!
Atsushi! Go!
--[ATSUSHI] What?!
--[MINOURA] Don't do it!
[gunshot]
[grunts]
Let me go!
I'm not responsible.
[RAMPO]
Running away won't help.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh?
I've already determined
the murder took place
early yesterday morning
at the abandoned shipyard,
just a few hundred
meters upstream from here.
[SUGIMOTO]
Ah. How'd you know that?
I'm sure we'll find
more evidence there.
Including your
footprints and hers.
And the bloodstains
you tried but failed to erase.
How could you know that?
No one could've
figured it all out.
Okay, save your confession...
...till we're back
at the station.
It might be your
last time there.
[SUGIMOTO] It was never
my plan to shoot her.
Y'see, she...
She was following leads in a
small time corruption case.
But as she dug into it, she
realized that she'd uncovered
a larger crime
involving a politician.
But the politician
knew he was vulnerable
and already had a
mole inside the force
to get rid of any evidence.
The mole you are talking
about, that was you, right?
I had always wanted
to become a police officer.
He found me when
I was depressed...
I was at a low point
after my third time failing
the entrance exam.
He asked me what I was
willing to do to join the force.
He used his influence
to help me become a cop,
but there was a price.
I had to report to him
and follow his orders.
So he ordered
you to kill Yamagiwa,
and you obeyed like a lap dog!
That's not true!
I was trying to
warn her about him.
He was on to her.
He'd kill her if...
...if she didn't give
up her investigation.
But she just
wouldn't listen to me.
This is no joke.
He's taking this very seriously.
[YAMIGAWA] Then I'll just have
to take him very seriously, too.
I've already made contact
with a prosecutor I know.
I just need to hand
over the evidence.
What're you doing?
I'm just trying to protect you.
Give me the evidence, or he'll
hire someone to kill you.
I wanna help you stay alive!
Please do it.
No, you're gonna
hand over the gun.
Give it to me.
We both know you're
not willing to shoot me.
[SUGIMOTO]
You're right.
I can't.
Give it to me or I'll shoot!
[gasps]
Sugimoto!
Stop! Don't!
[gunshot]
Ah!
[screams]
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[RAMPO] But we both know
the story doesn't end there,
does it?!
There's still the matter of
what you did with the body.
You were in a bind.
You panicked and
made a rash choice...
You called the
crooked politician for help.
He told you to
destroy the evidence
by making it look
like a Mafia hit,
so you fired two more
shots into her chest.
[RAMPO]
You set her adrift in the river
to delay the body's discovery.
[MINOURA] Where's the evidence
Yamagiwa had gathered?
That politician is
responsible for her death!
Tell me, right now!
[RAMPO]
Hey, Sugimoto...
[MINOURA]
Hm?
Want me to guess what
her final words were?
I have an idea.
"I'm sorry." Correct?
I'm sorry...
So sorry.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
How...
[SUGIMOTO sobs]
How does your power
let you see all that?
The evidence she
had on the politician,
it's in my desk drawer.
[MINOURA]
Thank you, I suppose.
[RAMPO]
Hmm?
[MINOURA] Also, I'm sorry I
doubted your special powers.
We'll come to you the next
time we get a tough case.
If you need my
Ultra-Deduction abilities,
all you have to
do is ask, Detective.
I may even give you a discount.
Appreciate the offer.
[ATSUSHI] What Rampo
did back there was amazing.
I had no idea he'd
figure everything out.
His Ultra-Deduction
ability is truly incredible.
Yes, but I might've
figured out half of it, too.
Half of what?
The case we were
just working on...
I pretty much know
how Rampo figured it out.
Well, maybe,
but he said his ability
lets him solve
the case instantly...
Oh, right, I forgot.
You don't know about him yet...
See, the truth is...
...Rampo isn't gifted
with special powers.
Huh?!
Rampo is a rare breed.
Despite appearances,
he's an un-gifted member
of the crime fighting team at
the Armed Detective Agency.
He himself seems to believe he's
using an ability, but he's not.
And even though he's childish,
he's 26 years old.
Eh?!
The reason why everyone
at the Agency respects Rampo
is because they know his Ultra-
Deduction isn't an ability.
I had heard about it,
but today I was the first time
I got to witness him in action,
and here's a little secret...
I put it to a test.
While he was "using" his
Ultra-Deduction ability today,
I was secretly pinching
his hair behind him.
As you well know,
my unique power
is to neutralize anyone's
ability if I touch them...
I'm "anti-gifted."
No gifted person
can use their ability
while I'm in physical
contact with them.
This has always been true,
no matter how strong
their powers are.
In other words,
Rampo's Ultra-Deduction
is not a supernatural ability.
He's a regular person?
Hold on, then how did he...
[OSAMU]
Pure deduction.
There's nothing
"Ultra" about it.
But how? I mean...
He figured out who the killer
was in such a short time!
How can deduction alone
solve a hard case like that?
Well, I don't have that power,
and I figured it out.
Do you remember what
Sergeant Sugimoto said?
Shooting two extra rounds to
make it look like a Mafia hit.
[OSAMU] Any innocent
person who saw a body
with three gunshot wounds
would assume they were
fired at the same time.
Oh...
[OSAMU]
What Sugimoto said implied
he knew the victim had
died from the first shot.
How could he have known that
before the autopsy
was performed?
'Cause he was the shooter.
But Rampo also knew when
the murder had been committed.
He said it was
yesterday morning.
That's because
he observed the body
was still in good condition.
We could easily ID the victim.
So, at most, it'd only been
floating in the river for a day.
Also she looked as if
she had dressed in a rush.
She wasn't dressed for work.
She had no makeup on.
So the murder clearly
occurred in the early morning.
I see.
But how did he know about
the crime scene's location
and that she was
threatened like that?
I've got to admit, I don't know.
A trained mind like
Rampo's probably caught
a lot more details than I could
hope to quickly observe.
It's really amazing.
Especially how he
was able to figure out
what her final words were.
[OSAMU]
Oh, well...
...that I knew.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
According to the police, she was
not in a romantic relationship.
But her wristwatch
told a different story.
It was an expensive
European model.
Not something a young woman
on a detective's salary
would ordinarily
buy for herself.
[OSAMU] Sugimoto's
watch was the men's version
of the same luxury brand.
So then, they were...
dating each other?
When he called her,
she went to see him right away
without a trace of makeup.
She trusted him.
They even wore
matching watches...
It tells me they were in love.
[OSAMU] With such
strong feelings for her,
he couldn't kick her head
in to finish the cover up.
He knew it wouldn't
look like the Mafia's work,
but it was just too
much for him to bear.
The ability to see all of that
would be par for the course
if it were an actual
supernatural power.
Nothing really worth
getting credit for.
But if it's due to his natural,
personal powers of deduction,
well, that's a different story.
Not only that,
Rampo has solved dozens of
cases using his un-gifted mind.
In every case, he was
able to instantly determine
the truth of the matter
with the slimmest of leads!
He's never been wrong!
Our city is safer thanks to his
work and the power of his mind.
He truly is a great man,
don't you think?
[RAMPO]
Somebody's not doing their job!
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
You're supposed
to help me find my way back
to the Agency, y'know!
[ATSUSHI]
I think I kind of get it now...
[OSAMU]
Huh?
Why everyone at the
Agency trusts Rampo
and tells him how great he is.
[OSAMU]
Heh.
[RAMPO]
Hm... Heh heh.
All's well that's well for me!
[DOPPO]
What is "the Ideal"?
There are any number
of answers to that question.
It is words.
It is thought.
From a moving plan
scheduled five years from now
to tonight's dinner menu,
this notebook has everything
in life written out
in exacting detail.
It represents the
entirety of my ideals!
[ATSUSHI]
But just to be safe,
you really shouldn't
show anyone the page
where you've written
about your ideal woman.
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 6:
"The Azure Messenger."
[DOPPO] What's so bad about
looking for an ideal woman?!