[ATSUSHI]
Do I smell... miso soup?
[sniffs]
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[KYOUKA]
Good morning.
Huh?
[ATSUSHI] Why are
the two of us roommates?!
We just don't have
any more space.
Seriously?
[OSAMU]
She was happy to do it.
Ordered to.
[ATSUSHI sighs]
[OSAMU]
You understand, Atsushi.
No, I don't.
Well, the poor girl
has no family.
She's all alone in the world.
The Port Mafia might
send assassins for her.
That's true.
You must protect her.
I understand.
I'll do my best!
[OSAMU chuckles]
[DOPPO] Instead of messing
with Atsushi, why don't you
write up your report about
being captured, Dazai?
[OSAMU]
Heh, heh, heh. Atsushi...
Yes?
[OSAMU] I want you to
write a report for me.
Huh?!
It's going to be
all about the person
who placed the bounty
on your head.
[ATSUSHI]
You know who that is?
[OSAMU] Going off the
Port Mafia's records,
it looks like it
was the leader of
an American organization of
the gifted called The Guild.
I thought that they were
just an urban legend.
It's said their members
hold key positions in finance,
politics, and the military,
allowing them to utilize
their vast influence
for nefarious purposes.
What would a group like
that want with Atsushi?
--[helicopter whirs]
--[ATSUSHI] Huh?
[OSAMU gasps]
[door opens]
You've all gotta come see this!
--[tires screech]
--[horns honk]
Guess our report'll
have to wait.
Heh.
How nice to finally meet you,
President Fukuna...
Uhh... Fuzuka?
Fukuzawa.
That's it!
Oh, we parked our chopper
on a nearby highway.
Was that all right?
What is it you wish to discuss?
You've journeyed across
the world to come here.
Speak your mind.
My, this is a rare specimen.
I don't recognize
this style of porcelain.
What is the brand of this set?
Royal Blanc?
Or perhaps El Zelga?
It's from the ceramics
store next door.
[sips]
My apologies.
Please call me
Francis, old sport.
I insist.
I'm the leader of The Guild.
We're headquartered
in North America.
I personally own three
conglomerates, five hotels,
an airline, a university--
Mister Fitzgerald...
[FITZGERALD]
Hm?
[YUKICHI] I've received
reports that you issued
a bounty to encourage the
Port Mafia to attack us...
Are they true?
Yes, that was a big
mistake on my part.
To think such a
famed criminal group
would be so incompetent.
To make amends, I bring
you a business proposal.
You've got a nice
little company here
and it's in an attractive
neighborhood.
As such...
...I'd like to buy it from you.
Don't misunderstand.
I could buy every
piece of property
that you can see from here.
It's not the building
I'm interested in.
I want one thing...
And that is?
What do you think?
I want your Gifted
Business Permit.
[FITZGERALD] You see, for a
group of gifted individuals
to open a business, they need
permission from a special branch
of the Ministry
of Internal Affairs.
Those fools are about the only
ones you can't buy with money.
We are a secret society that
officially doesn't even exist.
There's something in
this city that we want.
We'd rather not rile the
Ministry while we look for it.
The permit will allow us to--
I refuse.
Come now, is this not enough?
Very well then...
I'll add this.
It's a limited edition model,
made to order
with pink diamonds.
[YUKICHI] I'm afraid there's no
amount of money you could offer
that would entice me
to give up our permit.
[FITZGERALD]
Hm?
It is a symbol of hope.
Not just for our members, but
also for that of Master Natsume,
without whom this agency
would not exist.
Our permit is not for sale
to the highest bidder.
It is not a plaything
for the idle rich.
So you believe there are
things money can't buy.
That's the boring
mantra of the poor.
If your employees "vanished,"
I make a bet your little Agency
would cease to function.
Any by then it would be
too late to change your mind.
I'll take that
into consideration.
We're done here.
For now...
Escort our guests out, Kenji.
--[door opens]
--[KENJI] Understood!
This way, please.
[FITZGERALD]
I'll leave a message for you
in tomorrow's paper.
Consider it carefully,
old sport...
I always get what I'm after.
--[elevator dings]
--[doors open]
That's a really cute hat.
You think so?
Thank you very much, Miss!
[elevator dings]
[LUCY]
Well? Whaddya think?
[JAMES] It's great, but
you'd look better in burlap.
Why you!
Hmph!
[FITZGERALD]
First, there was one...
[DOPPO] Hey! Did you
hear what happened?!
Yeah, it's on the news.
[TV REPORTER]
As we reported earlier...
A seven-story building has
completely vanished overnight.
According to one
of our sources,
the building was used
to house a front company
for the notorious Port Mafia.
While details...
So this is the message...
No one's seen Kenji
since yesterday.
I'm really starting to
worry about him now.
So they'll get rid of anyone,
whether it's us
or the Port Mafia.
Huh...
Junichirou, I don't want
you out there on your own.
Work with Atsushi to find Kenji.
Dazai, you'll be with me.
We'll consult the President.
We don't know what kind
of powers they have.
If you encounter them,
retreat immediately.
Right.
[JUNICHIROU] Naomi, you should
head back to the Agency.
It's too dangerous.
If they can make whole
buildings disappear,
it doesn't matter where I am.
--[OUGAI] Elise? Where are you?
--[NAOMI] Right, Atsushi?
[ATSUSHI]
I... guess.
[JUNICHIROU]
Hey, man!
You know my sister isn't
gifted like you or me!
--She's gotta go!
--[OUGAI] Please, answer me!
Just a minute!
I seem to recall
someone promising
to do anything I asked.
Yeah, but that was
yesterday when you were--
--[JUNICHIROU yelps]
--[OUGAI] This isn't funny!
[JUNICHIROU]
Let's not talk about it.
[NAOMI chuckles]
[JUNICHIROU] I still think
that you should go back.
[NAOMI]
Oh, really?
Would it help if I
reminded you of how we...
--[ATSUSHI] Hm?
--[JUNICHIROU] Mm?
[JUNICHIROU]
Naomi?
No, It can't be...
[JUNICHIROU]
Naomi! Where are you?!
Where did she go?!
Is this how they attack?
But I... I didn't sense
that anything was off.
Naomi!
[ATSUSHI]
Wait! It's too dangerous!
Where could you be, Elise?
Oh, I'm in big trouble now...
Give her back to me!
[JUNICHIROU]
Found you!
[JUNICHIROU pants]
[JUNICHIROU yells]
[LUCY]
Let's play a game!
[JUNICHIROU, ATSUSHI gasp]
[OUGAI gasps]
[LUCY] I'd like to welcome
all of you to Anne's Chamber!
My goodness!
There's so many of you here,
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm not very good
at public speaking.
But still, I have to explain
what's going on to everyone!
You're all probably
really confused
about how you even got here.
If it were me, I'm sure
my heart would be--
Where is Naomi?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Allow me to explain that first.
Your agents are
over in that room.
[JUNICHIROU]
Kenji... Naomi!
Damn! Naomi!
It won't open without a key.
Unlike that door...
[ATSUSHI]
They're all frozen.
Has time stopped?
[LUCY]
My name... is Lucy.
I created this world
with my ability.
But don't worry, you can
leave whenever you want
through that white door.
But unfortunately your
companions will be trapped here.
What is it that you want?
[LUCY]
That's easy.
I just want you to play
in this room with my friend.
Say "hello," Anne.
--[ATSUSHI shudders]
--[JUNICHIROU growls]
[LUCY]
Anne loves to play.
She's a bit needy,
but she's just so cute!
[CROWD screams]
I forgot to mention
about the door!
If you leave, then you'll forget
everything that's happened here!
Do you understand?
Oh, man... There's only
three of you left?
It's not safe here.
You need to run.
But the girl I'm looking
for might be here.
She's beautiful, just
like a little angel.
Have you seen her
anywhere, perhaps?
[ATSUSHI]
Sorry, I'm afraid I haven't.
[OUGAI]
I see...
Her name is Elise.
Ever since we've been separated,
I have no idea what
to do with myself.
She might be just
behind that door.
If she is, I'd never
forgive myself for running.
So I'm going to stand my ground.
I understand.
[LUCY]
The rules are simple.
Play a round of tag
with my dear Anne.
If she tags you,
then you lose the game.
But if you open the door using
that key before she catches you,
you win, and I'll
return the hostages.
Well then?
Who wants to give it a try?
Can two people play
at the same time?
[LUCY]
But of course!
It's much more fun if
we all play together.
[ATSUSHI] We'll win if we use
Junichirou's Light Snow ability
to project illusions.
Are the two of you ready?
Yeah.
Ready...
[LUCY]
Go!
[ATSUSHI]
She's fast!
[LUCY giggles]
Caught you.
One down!
Junichirou!
Aaahhh!
[LUCY]
We've made another friend!
Aren't you happy, Anne?
Huh? What's that?
You still want more?
All right, then...
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[LUCY]
Incredible! I wanna see more.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[LUCY] You have such a
strong and useful ability...
You must have been highly valued
from the moment you were born.
I know that you're an orphan.
I grew up in an orphanage, too.
I still remember the cold.
After using freezing
rags to clean
for hours and hours on end,
my fingers would ache for days.
Everyone shunned me
'cause of my ability.
They all thought that
I was some kind of freak.
I heard that when
you were taken,
the Agency was
desperate to find you.
How wonderful.
It must've been because
of your great ability.
That's not--
[LUCY] That's the reason
why The Guild took me in.
[ATSUSHI sighs]
[LUCY] But there's no room
for error in The Guild.
If I fail in this mission,
I'll be tossed aside
like a used napkin.
Then I'll be all alone again.
Tell me...
Why are you special?
How come I'm not special?
It's not fair!
You should know how I feel
more than anybody else!
You deserve to
stay here forever!
[ATSUSHI grunts]
[ATSUSHI] I need to unlock
that door with this key.
[ATSUSHI]
I win!
Kid! Be careful!
Huh?!
Aah!
[LUCY] You shouldn't throw
away your chance at escape.
Weren't we supposed to
win if I used that key?!
[LUCY] That's right.
If you could open the door.
I don't know how to
use this key, either.
It's a complete mystery to me.
[ATSUSHI] So there was no way
to win in the first place.
[LUCY]
The real game starts now.
You're obviously
really good at tag...
...but I wonder just how
much longer you'll last?
[ATSUSHI]
There's nothing I can do.
I'm gonna be caught.
There's no way for me to
fight back. It's hopeless!
[ATSUSHI] My only hope is
that Dazai will show up!
[LUCY] You're gonna
leave your friends behind?!
[ATSUSHI] Even in this
impossible situation,
he'd think of something.
I can't do anything!
[OUGAI]
Don't do it, kid.
Face your enemy.
[ATSUSHI yelps]
I wouldn't advise
escaping in this situation.
Uh, assuming...
...you're willing
to trust the words
of a simple neighborhood
physician, of course.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
If we're to believe
that girl's words,
you'll forget everything once
you leave through that door.
You won't remember
the enemy's guile,
or your friends
being in danger,
leaving you
completely vulnerable.
Let me teach you something.
Using game theory,
the optimal strategy is to
launch a total counteroffensive,
catching your opponent
by surprise.
Then you crush your enemy.
I don't think I can do it.
[OUGAI]
An arrogant opponent is likely
to make the biggest mistakes.
And if I heard correctly,
those friends of yours
behind that door...
Didn't they work hard to find
you when you were kidnapped?
[ATSUSHI gasps]
[ATSUSHI]
That's right.
They all saved me.
[LUCY]
Enough chit-chat!
Are you ready to keep
playing our game?
I think it's time for
me to make my move.
Yes. I think that's
your best option.
[LUCY] It wouldn't
be fun any other way.
But sadly...
It's too late for you!
[ATSUSHI grunts]
There's two?!
Well, it's only fair,
since there are two of you!
[ATSUSHI]
Oh, shit!
[ATSUSHI screams]
All done here!
Looks like you're
all alone, mister.
So, what are you gonna do?
It's all thanks to you that
the weretiger didn't run away
in the first place.
I guess I could let you go
as a sign of my appreciation.
Then again, I really
wanna see your expression
when Anne catches you.
Why don't you try it?
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
Wait... What's happening?
My legs are shaking
so much, I can't move.
This feeling of pure evil...
Even Anne is being
affected by it!
[OUGAI]
It's hopeless.
I'm afraid...
you've already lost.
Look at the door.
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY] What?!
But I know I shut that door...
So how?
[ATSUSHI]
You've made one mistake.
This fight was two against
one from the beginning!
[LUCY gasps]
[ATSUSHI] The moment
this door opened,
Junichirou used his ability
to create a false door.
[LUCY]
Impossible...
You were able to resist
the force pulling you in
with just your arms
and legs alone?
[ATSUSHI]
You give me too much credit.
I'm not powerful
and I'm not popular.
My life has been filled
with all sorts of misfortune.
That's why I understand
your feelings of resentment
all too well.
I don't want you to lose the
only place you can call home!
I don't want you to fail!
But I'm weak and inexperienced,
and just can't think
of any other way!
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
A ribbon?!
It looks like it
finally came into use.
--[ATSUSHI grunts]
--[LUCY yelps]
Undo your ability
and let everyone go!
If you don't, I'll throw
you into this room.
[LUCY gasps]
[ATSUSHI] Without a key,
this door won't open.
That means if you're
imprisoned here,
no one will ever be
able to free you
and you'll be
trapped in this room
even if you release
your ability.
Am I wrong?
You can't...
Our powers aren't for
controlling people.
I understand that
better than most.
Are you willing to be
trapped here forever?
Because not even death will
save you in this place!
But... I can't afford
to fail my mission!
[ATSUSHI]
I'm going to let go.
You'll only have
that split second
before the door
closes to decide.
Please no! Don't do it!
[LUCY screams]
--[horns honk]
--[ATSUSHI grunts]
[CROWD murmurs]
[ATSUSHI sighs]
[ATSUSHI gasps]
Lucy! Listen.
If I can help you in any way--
[LUCY grunts]
Wait!
[ATSUSHI sighs]
--[ATSUSHI yells]
--Oh, Elise! There you are!
Are you okay?!
Wh-Where've you been?
I was so worried!
You just up and vanished...
I thought that if I
suddenly disappeared,
it would make Rintaro worry.
I really just wanted
to see him cry.
[OUGAI]
That's so cruel, Elise!
You're lucky you're so cute!
[ATSUSHI]
Uh!
Hey, Kyouka.
Did you come to get me?
I was worried.
Thank you.
[OUGAI] I believe we'll
be taking our leave now.
[ATSUSHI] I wanted to thank you
for your advice earlier.
You said you were
a doctor, right?
Ex-doctor.
I'm just a simple old man
in charge of a small group now.
Remember...
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
An optimal solution
exists in any situation,
regardless of the difficulty.
You must not forget that,
especially in times
of confusion.
Right.
Farewell.
There's always an
optimal solution... yeah.
--[KYOUKA shudders]
--[ATSUSHI] Huh?
Hey, what's up?
What is it?
Kyouka? What's wrong?
[OUGAI]
I had a good time today.
Though I must admit, I really
wanted to use my ability
to decimate my enemies
like I used to.
You're too old for that!
Hey now!
That may be true, but...
[OUGAI laughs]
[OUGAI]
So this is a Guild assassin?
Yes.
[OUGAI] Apparently the
Agency isn't the only one
in a skirmish with The Guild.
It seems I should
take my own advice.
We need an "optimal solution."
The Agency and The Guild...
Those who dare to oppose
us and incur our wrath...
...will die.
[OSAMU] Sakunosuke Oda,
Ango Sakaguchi, and me...
The three of us would often
drink at that watering hole.
That's how we always spent
our nights back then.
And that's when it happened.
[OSAMU]
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 13: "The Dark Age."
In the end, everything in
this world exists solely
to help us kill time
until we finally die.