[DOPPO] A mysterious
criminal group is threatening
to detonate a bomb
somewhere in the city.
Not only that,
they've launched a smear
campaign against our agency.
Sounds like we're caught
between a rock and a hard place.
Do you have any
helpful information
on where the bomb might be?
Not much.
Right now all we have to go on
is the message left
by the perpetrator.
Here it is...
"Greetings, I hope that
the Armed Detective Agency
and its members
are faring well.
Forgive my impudence,
but I have placed a bomb
capable of causing
mass destruction
in a certain location
here in Yokohama.
Since you claim to be
an agency aimed
at securing public safety,
I request you locate and disarm
the bomb as soon as you can.
You only have until sundown.
I wish you the best of luck.
I have full faith
in your abilities.
Respectfully,
the Azure Messenger."
[YUKICHI]
A strange signature.
Who is the Azure Messenger?
[DOPPO]
We don't know, yet.
This bomb could ruin us.
It's rigged specifically
to make our team look bad.
He's setting us up so that
if we fail his challenge,
everyone will hold
us responsible
for the damages instead of them.
Our failure to stop the attack
would spread like wild fire.
The bomb could be anywhere.
The office staff has been
scouring the city for it.
But there are too
many possibilities.
[KENJI]
Hey...
I bet Rampo could help.
Have we had any luck
getting in touch with him?
It seems he's still busy
with the case in Kyushu.
I've asked him to contact
us as soon as possible,
but we need leads right now.
Did you get any information
from that taxi driver?
Unfortunately, no.
He denies any
knowledge of the bomb.
I believe him.
I don't think he's the type
to try to blow up Yokohama.
Okay then, listen up!
This is a cowardly act.
Someone's endangering lives just
to bring down the
Armed Detective Agency.
We have two objectives:
uncover the Azure Messenger,
whoever this person is,
and disarm the bomb they've set.
The bomb takes priority
because of its deadly potential.
If we can't find the bomb, it
will destroy innocent lives...
...as well as the hard-earned
reputation of our agency.
[DOPPO]
Hmm...
Everything is at stake
for us on this case.
It's a full test of our skills
as a detective agency.
[phone ringing]
[TAGUCHI] Do you have any idea
what time it is, four-eyes?
[DOPPO] You're the only one
who's still sleeping at 11:30.
Can you find the one
who sent us that message?
The Azure Messenger?
Maybe I can, but
before we switch gears,
isn't there something else
you want to ask me about?
[DOPPO]
So you already know everything.
Come on. I only know
what I actually know.
[DOPPO] I want you to trace
the bomb-building equipment.
I'll send you
the shipping manifest.
A bomb? Wow, things are
really looking up for you guys.
[DOPPO] Cut the bad jokes and
small talk, and get cracking.
Hey!
[DOPPO]
Innocent lives are at stake!
I know you like to spend
all your time hacking
and breaking laws, but you
should make yourself useful
to society sometimes.
[TAGUCHI] Why don't you
get off your high horse.
Remember, you're not my dad.
[phone click]
[DOPPO]
No, I can't replace your father.
[SASAKI] Are you sure
you have time for this?
The Agency seems so busy dealing
with the new bomb threat.
Especially Kunikida.
He seems so anxious.
You've got that right.
Kunikida is an insane workhorse.
Get this...
He spends two hours reviewing
his notes before going to bed.
I couldn't stand doing
that for two minutes.
Maybe he's got some solider ants
working for him in his brain--
[OSAMU] Oh, I didn't know
you were here, Kunikida.
How could you ditch a
meeting during an emergency?
I guess you thought it was more
important to go on a fancy date.
Are you jealous of
my "fancy" date?
Uh, no, I'm not!
[ATSUSHI]
Yes, he is.
Ever since we rescued Sasaki,
I've been hosting
her at my place...
She still needs help
to ensure her safety
and healthy mental state.
That's our job, too.
I'm just doing the noble
thing for our new friend.
You are too irresponsible and
lazy for such an important task.
Don't be ridiculous.
Besides, an attractive
woman like her
probably has a nice
boyfriend for support.
Nice try, but
I know she's single.
She broke up with her boyfriend.
That's right, Kunikida...
Now's your chance!
Listen, Dazai!
I'm here for one reason:
To fill you in on
what's going on
because you skipped the
emergency meeting this morning.
Yeah, well, I already
know what's happening.
The Azure Messenger planted this
bomb with a specific goal...
...to crush our Agency.
[SASAKI]
Um...
Should I be hearing all this?
It sounds like you're discussing
highly sensitive information.
She's right!
[OSAMU] Unfortunately,
the attempt on your life
makes you part of this case.
[ATSUSHI]
Really?
You can help!
Remind me, what class do
you teach at the university?
[SASAKI]
Social psychology.
Ah, that's great.
We're having trouble
cracking this case.
I'd love to hear
your expert analysis.
[SASAKI]
Hmmm...
About the Azure Messenger,
it may have something
to do with the Azure King.
Remember the Azure
Flag Terrorist incident?
It could be connected
to the situation
you're dealing with now.
I was thinking the same thing.
I know it's a stretch, but it
could be the Azure King himself.
We think he blew himself up
after being cornered
by the police.
But it's possible
he faked his death,
and he still wants revenge.
[AZURE KING]
This world is incomplete.
One may grieve or pray,
but people still die and
evil goes unpunished, allowed
to flourish freely everywhere.
Did you know he was a
former government official?
He set off a bomb in a public
facility and issued a manifesto.
He was targeting killers
whose cases had to be
dropped on technicalities.
And legislators who
enriched themselves
through corruption
on a global scale...
He hated criminals
who evaded justice.
[AZURE KING] I desire the
ideal world for humanity.
It will be built not by
the divine hand of God
but by the work of
our own bloodied hands...
[DOPPO]
Hmm...
[ATSUSHI] But if the
Azure King is actually alive,
why would he attack the Agency
when we're on
the side of the law?
I couldn't tell you.
[OSAMU] Did you know
the guy responsible
for backing the Azure King
into a corner was Kunikida?
He located his hideout.
Maybe... Kunikida is the
target of angry vengeance.
No, the Azure King is long gone.
Military police confirmed his
death with forensic testing.
There's no doubt.
[OSAMU] Just in case,
you should stay on your guard
until we figure out who
the Azure Messenger is.
And we'll keep hiding
Sasaki at my place.
[DOPPO]
All right, that's enough, Dazai!
What did I say?
You really think
we're dumb enough
to just let you keep a
beautiful lady in your room
and use her personal
safety as an excuse?
[OSAMU]
Would you calm down?
Nothing like what you're
imagining is happening.
When I first let her stay,
I slept in a different room
and didn't try anything.
You can ask her,
I was a true gentleman.
But I knew you'd
have torrid fantasies
about what you
thought we were doing,
and that's funny to me
so I didn't correct you.
Can someone please explain to me
how these two guys are partners?
[screams]
I'm no expert but Kunikida seems
to have a crush on you, Sasaki.
Can I ask you--what's
your ideal type of man?
"Ideal type of man"?
Looking for an ideal
type of person is foolish.
But I like a man who has
strong moral principles.
Someone... who pours
his heart and soul
into the things
he knows are true.
No matter what
stands in his way.
Hey, what a coincidence.
That's totally Kunikida.
My work is done.
The two of you
can take it from here.
Shush, Dazai!
Don't assume
you know anything!
Oh, don't be silly, partner.
You're an open book.
[DOPPO]
Geh!!
That's true.
I'll admit, he's a
pretty intense guy,
but he is definitely
a person who lives
and breathes for his ideals.
Hey, would you like to see
what he imagines his ideal
woman should be like?
It's a fun read.
[SASAKI]
Oh...
Hey! Not again, you bastard!
When did you get that? Arghh...
Give it back!
Wow, Kunikida.
Yes?
Too much information.
[DOPPO sighs]
Poor Kunikida is crushed.
[phone beeping]
[ATSUSHI]
Hmm? Uh...
Rampo's ready to help us.
Time to go.
Clock's ticking.
Do we know where the bomb is?
[RAMPO sighs] You know,
I was looking forward
to sightseeing in Kyushu
after I solved my case.
You all disappoint me. Haha.
You can't conduct a single
investigation without me.
We only have until sundown.
Please tell us the location.
[ATSUSHI]
A department store?
A school?
A train station?
Any one of these could produce
casualties in the hundreds.
We need to know
where that bomb is!
[RAMPO]
The fishing tackle store.
Huh?
[RAMPO] The bomb is in a
fishing tackle store in Negishi.
Sure that makes sense.
[ATSUSHI, DOPPO, SASAKI]
Hmm?
Thanks. You're amazing, Rampo.
Why does he think the bomb
is at a fishing tackle store?
Where's a map?
Behind the driver's seat.
Look on page 97.
[ATSUSHI]
Ninety-seven...
Okay, looking... looking...
Got it.
[OSAMU] The terrorist's target
is the petrochemical complex.
[DOPPO]
Of course!
I don't know why
I didn't think of that.
Yokohama is known for being
one of Japan's major port towns.
Next to the shipping docks
on the waterfront
there are many large facilities
that store oil and gas.
If an explosion were
to occur close enough
to ignite the storage tanks,
the entire port would
be engulfed in flames.
However, infiltrating a fuel
storage facility would be hard.
They're all protected by
extremely tight security.
But there could
be one other way...
A terrorist could put a bomb
in a car and leave the vehicle
near one of the
storage tanks when it's full.
Considering the effective range
of a bomb that
can be put into a car,
that fishing tackle
store's parking lot
is the perfect place
to leave the explosive.
[OSAMU]
Hmph.
Bingo.
The military's bomb squad
has found the device,
but there's still a problem.
It's connected to a
motion-sensing timer.
They don't think they'll be able
to disarm it before sundown.
They've started evacuating
nearby residents,
but they're not sure
there's enough time.
Oh, no...
[OSAMU]
There's still hope.
They said we can
deactivate the bomb
if we can transmit
a remote stop signal to it.
But how do we do that?
[gasps]
W-What's going on?!
I got a call.
Oh.
Yes, hello?
[TAGUCHI] Hey, Four-Eyes,
is now a good time?
Yes, Rokuzou?
What've you got?
[ATSUSHI] I think we're
causing a bit of a traffic jam.
[cellphone ringing]
Hello?
[RAMPO]
Hello...
Hey, Rampo!
Yes?
Right...
[YUKICHI]
Dazai?
President?
Yes...
Uh... The military's...?
[DOPPO] I see.
Set a thief to catch a thief.
[ATSUSHI]
All right.
[OSAMU]
That's quite a development...
--[ATSUSHI] Okay.
--[DOPPO] I understand.
--[OSAMU] Sure.
--[ATSUSHI] Mhmm.
[DOPPO]
No, that's helpful.
[ATSUSHI]
I'll tell the others.
[OSAMU]
I understand, President.
I got a call from Rokuzou...
Someone recently ordered
a bomb transmitter,
plus other equipment, delivered
to a former defense facility.
Rampo reached
a similar conclusion.
That settles it...
And I just got a call
from the president.
He was informed by the
military the taxi driver's dead.
He's dead?
How can that be?
I thought they were holding him
in their isolation ward
for extra protection.
They were,
but he died after suddenly
collapsing in his cell.
The forensic team hasn't
determined the cause of death,
but the guards noticed
numbers "00" on his palm.
There were numbers on his hand?
How strange.
What in the world is going on?
We've got company!
Doppo Poet:
Flash Bang!
[SHOOTERS scream]
Well, at least know
we're at the right place!
You two head upstairs!
Find the transmitter, and send
the stop signal to the car bomb!
[gasps]
What the...
[BLONDE]
I wonder what number you'll get.
[DOPPO]
Huh?!
[BLONDE]
How are you feeling?
You're looking great... for now.
Something tells me you
have a really good number.
Huh...?
[DOPPO]
Oh, no...
[BLONDE] You sniffed this out
place quicker than I thought.
The Armed Detective
Agency's impressive.
Or you were
impressive up until now.
[ATSUSHI]
Not much time left!
[OSAMU pants]
[ATSUSHI]
Can you figure it out?
[OSAMU]
Fortunately, yes!
But I still can't
send the signal.
Huh?
[OSAMU] You have to
insert a release key here
to access the controls.
And I have no idea
where to get it.
What are we going to do?!
[GIANT]
What are you doing here?
[OSAMU]
Ohhh!
Looks like someone's been
hitting the weight room.
[DOPPO grunts]
[DOPPO] So this guy's ability
includes remote attacks!
You should check your palm.
What's your number now?
What do you mean?
My power can't be evaded,
but I bet you're gonna try.
[DOPPO screams]
[BLONDE]
See? I can send people
who have numbers
in any direction I want.
Even if they're on the
other side of the earth.
But the really bad news is:
once their number becomes
zero, they'll die in agony.
t's a terrible fate,
and nobody can avoid it.
Nobody... Nobody...
Nobody!
[DOPPO grunts] Are you
the leader of this group?
[BLONDE] The Armed
Detective Agency posed
a greater threat to us
than the Port Mafia.
But now your team is finished.
You see this key...?
It's the release key
to deactivate the bomb.
Without it, there's no
way to prevent catastrophe.
Do you want it?
That's a dumb question.
Of course you do.
Here.
Oops.
[laughs]
Now, there's no hope.
It's finished.
Your entire mission
accomplished nothing.
It's not over, you idiot!
Nice leg work!
[OSAMU] You really
do have very strong arms.
You missed your true
calling as a luggage porter.
[DOPPO screams]
[roars]
--[OSAMU grunts]
--[DOPPO] Huh?
Hey, Kunikida!
[DOPPO]
I'm already on it.
Don't try the same trick twice!
[DOPPO]
Dazai!
[OSAMU]
Here!
So you want me to
give you a number as well?
What the--?!
Why hasn't a number
marked your hand?!
Sorry to say, your ability
won't have any effect on me.
Oh and also,
you should tell your partner
to take my career advice.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh?
[ATSUSHI] That guy was huge,
but Kunikida had no fear.
Dazai's okay...
Their partnership
works so well...
The bomb!
We need the key! Right now!
That idiot broke it.
[ATSUSHI]
What?!
Then what are we going to do?
We need to-- We don't
have time. We gotta--
Calm down, kid.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
Doppo Poet:
Release key.
[DOPPO] My ability allows
me to recreate anything
once I've seen it,
as long as I understand
its form and function.
[DOPPO]
There's a catch...
The object must be small--no
bigger than this notebook here.
So your notebook
is really a tool.
And that's the reason
you have it with you
all the time, isn't it?
[SASAKI]
Who were these people?
Are these the graves
of innocent victims?
[DOPPO]
Yes.
[DOPPO] When I first caused
casualties during a job,
I cried so much
I couldn't get up.
I needed time off from work.
But now, I don't shed
a single tear for them.
Instead, I come to their graves.
I see my visits as
a kind of trade,
so I can move on.
I often wonder about that.
Do our tears do
any good for the dead?
Our tears are useless.
At least, that's how I see it.
We have to be honest.
For the dead, time stops the
moment that their lives end.
I'm afraid I wasn't honest
when I told Dazai how
my relationship ended.
My significant other and I
parted ways because he died.
I see.
What you said is true.
When someone dies, time no
longer has meaning for them.
No matter what
I do for him now,
I cannot make him happy
or make him smile.
I didn't mean to bring this up.
Anyway I really must go.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Uh...
[cellphone ringing]
What is it?
[OSAMU]
Kunikida?
I need you for something.
[DOPPO] Why did you
want to come back here?
[OSAMU]
Check this out.
It's a survey and
analysis of Yokohama
we found on a computer
in their hideout.
Surprisingly,
it concludes that in order
to take control of the city,
they must first eradicate
the Armed Detective Agency.
Why us?
It's the Port Mafia
controls the underworld.
I think they were given
false information... on purpose.
They were manipulated.
So there's another mastermind?
[OSAMU] Yes, and I've sent
an email to the person
I believe is behind all this.
[gasps]
[OSAMU] I told them I have
proof that they're responsible.
They should be arriving
here any moment now.
[approaching footsteps]
[gasps]
No, it can't be you...!
You're the one, Rokuzou?!
What the heck are
you talking about?
So this showdown
hasn't started yet?
[OSAMU] Sneaky.
You took a peek at my email
by hacking into
my account, didn't you?
[DOPPO]
Are you the one responsible?
[TAGUCHI]
No, I just wanted to take a look
at the person who actually is.
[DOPPO]
But it's really not you?!
Tell me the truth!
Look out!
[OSAMU] So... you're
the Azure Messenger...
[DOPPO]
Unbelievable.
[OSAMU] I doubt this
is the first time you used
your deep knowledge of
psychology to execute a crime.
[SASAKI] The Azure King was
a man who lived for his ideals.
He wanted to destroy
the criminal word.
His intentions were pure,
and he was willing to
get blood on his hands.
I just wanted
to fulfill his vision,
make his ideals come true.
[OSAMU] You were deeply
in love with the Azure King...
I'll grant you,
he was an idealist
determined to punish criminals
who managed
to get around the law.
But he used
illegal means to do it.
Put down your gun!
You've caused
enough harm already.
[SASAKI]
Don't you understand?
Huh?
It's strange.
You stopped him but yet
you remind me of him...
You developed a very
sophisticated plan for revenge.
Without committing
a single crime,
you set up the Agency to take
the fall, and you destroyed both
the kidnapper and the criminal
organization behind him.
But you have no
convictions of your own.
You're just being swept along
by someone else's ideals.
[SASAKI sighs]
I'm just tired now.
I want to be
released from all this.
[SASAKI]
Will you shoot me?
Please Dazai?
I suppose you can't
because I lowered my gun.
If you shot me now,
it would be a crime.
An excessive use of force.
And Kunikida would be a witness.
True.
But I'm not going to shoot you.
However...
[three gunshots]
[gasps]
I'm here because the
Azure King killed my dad.
Good riddance to his follower.
But why?
Why did it have
to end this way?!
What went wrong?!
Someone was wrong!
[OSAMU]
No one was wrong.
This was the only
possible outcome.
Shut up!
You're lying to yourself!
You could've saved her!
Are you really telling me
that this is justice?!
To me, justice is a weapon.
It causes people harm
but can't protect them.
If it's the justice
used by the Azure King,
a sense of justice
without law...
...that justice killed Sasaki.
The same justice you believe in.
[DOPPO grunts]
[OSAMU]
Kunikida...
As long as you pursue
these ideals of yours,
the angry flames that burned
in the Azure King
will take root in you...
They'll destroy
everything around you.
[DOPPO]
You're wrong!
I will push right
past those flames.
Don't underestimate my ideals!
[AKIKO] Atsushi, are
you sure you're not hurt?
[ATSUSHI]
No, I'm feeling really good.
But thank you anyway.
[AKIKO]
Oh, that's so boring.
[ATSUSHI] Um, about your
"treatment," Dr. Yosano.
How does it work, exactly?
[AKIKO]
Why don't you ask Tanizaki?
He's received my treatment
a couple of times already.
[ATSUSHI] I have asked him,
but he just shakes with fear.
He won't say anything about it.
Next time on Bungo Stray Dogs ,
episode 8 : "Teaching
Them to Kill; Then to Die."
[AKIKO]
Ability: Thou Shalt Not Die.