- [groans]
I don't know this ceiling.
[grunts]
The wound in my stomach--
it's gone.
All things considered,
it must have been Emilia
and that healing power she has.
[door creaks]
Well, at any rate,
looks like I was able
to get out
of using Return by Death
this time around.
Even so, isn't it normal
to wake up
and see a girl
by your bed asking,
"Are you awake?" after she spent
all night caring for you
while you were asleep
and healing?
Kinda lame for a story
about being summoned
into another world.
- Uh--a looping hallway, huh?
I'd bet I can't get out
until I find the right room.
The typical pattern dictates
the first door
is likely the goal.
[door creaks]
- What a profoundly irritating
and aggravating man you are,
I suppose.
- The first NPC found!
You're gonna ruin
your cute little face
with that cold attitude
of yours.
Come on, smile.
Smile for me.
- The only smile appropriate
to give you
is a derisive sneer.
- Are you upset because
I guessed the right door
in the first try?
I've always been pretty lucky
when it comes
to stuff like that.
I can understand
why game masters
would want me to see all
the cut scenes, but sorry.
So, what is this place, anyway?
- Betty's multipurpose room,
which serves as a library
and bedroom, I suppose.
- Man, talk about
your token response.
So are you one
of those manual girls?
- Betty has had just about
enough of you.
I think it's time to teach you
a lesson, I suppose.
- Hang on.
What are you gonna do to me?
- Stay right there
and don't you dare move.
- [gasps]
- Anything you'd like to say?
- How about,
"Don't hurt me?"
[gasps]
[electric sparking]
[screaming]
[grunts]
What did you do to me,
you drill-haired loli?
- Oh, nothing much.
I only collected the mana
from your body, I suppose.
By doing so, I've confirmed
that you are not an enemy.
- You little freak.
You're not human, are you?
I mean, outside
of your sparkling personality.
- Took you long enough
to notice, I suppose.
- I take it back.
Your personality isn't human,
either.
- Do not measure a proud
noble being such as myself
by your standards, human.
[Konomi Suzuki's "Redo"]
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
- [groans]
[distant birds chirping]
I know this ceiling.
- Oh, he's awakened, sister.
- Indeed.
He's awakened, Rem.
- Hard to believe
a total night owl like me
can wake up so early.
I'm getting all emotional.
I should probably go to sleep
a second time.
No, wait a sec.
I woke up earlier,
so that would make this
the third.
- My, what a deadbeat thing
to say.
Did you hear that, sister?
- Truly the words
of a loser.
I heard him, Rem.
- Hey, who are these two voices
that keep
criticizing me in stereo?
N--no way.
Short-skirted maid costumes
exist in this world, too?
In my mind,
maids were always
the very personification
of elegance.
This is gonna be awesome!
- What terrible thoughts
this one his having.
You're being repeatedly violated
in the mind of our guest,
sister.
- Truly terrible indeed.
You're experiencing
the ultimate shame over
and over in the mind
of our guest, Rem.
- Don't underestimate
the capacity of my mind.
You're both fair prey
in my fantasies, little maids.
[knocking]
[grunts]
- Seems like you
can't even wake up
without causing a commotion,
huh, Subaru?
- [gasps]
[sighs]
[grunts]
Whoever picked that outfit
definitely gets it!
- I'm not even going
to pretend to know
what you're talking about,
but the fact that I know
it's something stupid
is disappointing.
- Listen to this, Miss Emilia.
Without provocation,
my dear sister was just violated
by that man.
- Please listen to this,
Miss Emilia.
Rem was just held prisoner
in shame by that man.
- That's enough, you two.
Don't tease him so much.
- Yes, of course, Miss Emilia.
My sister's very sorry.
Rem's sorry as well.
- Tell me.
Are you feeling all right today?
Does anything feel off to you?
- Huh?
Nah, just a bit groggy
from oversleeping.
So you were the one
who saved me,
isn't that right, Mili?
- Huh?
Mili?
Why would you call me that?
- Uh, it's just a nickname.
No big deal.
Seriously, though,
thank you.
You saved me.
- Not at all.
Honestly, I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
You barely even know me,
but you still risked your life
in order to protect mine.
It's only natural
I'd heal your wounds
after something like that.
- [grunts]
Well, then once again,
I guess it's time to go out
and start a brand new day.
[birds chirping]
This place is really huge.
This isn't a yard.
It's more like a field.
- Those movements
are quite unusual.
What are you doing?
- My homeland's ancient practice
of warm-up exercises
and calisthenics.
Come on. You should try
and do them with me, Mili.
Routine number two.
Bounce briskly on both feet
to loosen up your body!
- Huh?
You're kidding.
That's weird.
- Just do whatever I'm doing.
I'll drill the essence
of radio calisthenics
into you, okay?
- [grunts]
[quirky music]
- Now, raise both your arms
and shout, "Victory!"
- V--victory!
- Victory!
Victory!
[grunts]
Hi there, Subaru.
Great morning, isn't it?
- Well, to be completely honest,
it's been nothing but total
chaos from the minute I woke up.
There were looping hallways
and a mean little girl
on a rampage,
and after that,
shedding the sweat of passion
with Mili.
- There's no need to make
it sound so scandalous.
Good morning, Puck.
Really sorry I put you through
so much yesterday.
- Morning, Lia.
I came really close
to losing you back there,
didn't I?
I'll never be able
to thank Subaru enough.
I think I should do something
for him.
- Yeah?
Okay, let me pet your fur
whenever I feel like it.
- Huh?
Is that seriously all you want?
- For a first-rate fur master
such as myself,
being able to love on the object
of your petting affections
any time you want is worth just
as much as the troves
of a multi-millionaire's riches.
Oh, man, these ears.
I'm so in love with how soft
and cuddly you are.
- I know you feel that way
since I can kind of read
your mind,
but I'm amazed you
can actually say it.
[laughs]
It's okay, Lia.
- [grunts]
- 'Cause I can't find any trace
of hostility or malice
in him at all.
- It's so cute how
you call her Lia, too.
- It's not half as cute
as when you called her Mili.
- You really are
a strange one, Subaru.
- Huh?
- [giggles]
- [groans]
- Well, look at this.
What brings you two here?
- [grunts]
both: Miss Emilia,
our lord Master Roswaal
has finally returned home.
Please, come inside.
[doors creaking]
- I was watching you
from upstairs,
and you know what?
It would appear that you
are quite the imbecile,
I suppose.
- And just where do you get off
saying that, you loli?
- What does that word mean?
I've never even heard it before
and it irritates me.
I think you just made it up.
- Betty!
Haven't seen you in four days.
Hope you've been doing well
and staying ladylike.
- Hello, Bubby!
I've been waiting so eagerly
for you to come home!
Will you stay with me today,
do you suppose?
- Yeah, sure.
No problem.
Today's the day we can finally
relax together.
- Aww, this'll be great!
- [giggles]
- Feeling bewildered,
aren't you?
Beatrice is so taken with Puck,
she can't get enough.
- I can't believe you just
said bewildered unironically.
- My, my!
How unusual to see you here,
Beatrice.
I'm so happy you're dining
with me.
I do ever so love your company
and treasure our times together.
- That boy is more than enough
addle-brained fool
for me, I suppose.
Betty was only waiting around
for Bubby.
- Wow, so you guys hired
a clown to entertain you
before each meal?
I'll never understand
how you rich folks think.
- Um, Subaru,
that man is actually--
- Oh, no, it's quite all right,
Miss Emilia.
I'll handle the introductions.
- What's going on?
- I am in fact the lord
of this manor.
Roswaal L. Mathers.
So very pleased
to make your acquaintance.
Subaru Natsuki, right?
[birds chirping]
[harp music]
- Mmm?
This is way better
than normal food.
- Mm-hmm.
Despite her appearance,
Rem's cooking
is quite impressive.
- So this was cooked by the one
with the blue hair?
I think I got that right.
You made this?
- Yes, that's correct.
I'm responsible for all
of the cooking
in this household.
My sister doesn't happen
to be very good at cooking.
- Ah, so it's the old twins
who are good
at different things trope, huh?
So, your sister good
at cleaning, then, I take it?
- Yes, that's correct.
My sister excels
at housework chores,
especially cleaning and laundry.
- So while you're good
at cooking,
you're probably bad at cleaning
and laundry, right, Rem-rin?
- On the contrary,
I'm generally good
at all household tasks.
I'm also better at cleaning
and laundry than my sister.
- Seriously?
Does your sister
even have a purpose?
- You are truly
a unique young man.
You come to the mansion
of Margrave Mathers
in the kingdom of Lugunica
and you say you
don't understand a thing.
- So what do you mean by that?
Is something bad happening
in this country?
- Well, it is not in
an agreeable state,
which only makes sense.
After all,
Lugunica doesn't have a king.
Now, don't look so alarmed.
There's no need to be concerned.
Everyone in this country
is already quite aware
of that circumstance being
their reality.
- Wow, really?
I expected a,
"Now that you know my secret,
I can't let you leave
here alive" thing.
- Roughly around the same time
the king went into hiding,
an epidemic began to spread
throughout the castle.
The king and his children
are the last of his line.
At this moment,
the nation is being managed
by a council of wise men
and that council is currently
in the process
of selecting a new king.
- Okay, think I'm starting
to get the picture now.
On top of the king's absence,
the royal selection
is causing confusion
in the kingdom.
Suddenly I appear
from another country--
wait, I'm totally suspect here!
- And on top of that,
you made contact
with Miss Emilia,
thus initiating
a direct connection
to my household.
Ah, the dilemma.
- Mm?
Hey, hold on a second.
Why would the lord
of the mansion
call her Miss Emilia?
- I'm not sure how things are
where you're from,
but here we address those
with higher status respectfully.
- [grunts]
But, uh,
that would mean Mili here is,
uh--
- Officially, my current title
is candidate for the 42nd ruler
of the Kingdom of Lugunica,
with the backing of the honor
of Lord Margrave Roswaal.
- What?
- Sorry to surprise you
like that.
I wasn't trying to keep it
a secret or anything.
[exciting music]
- Hey, it's that insignia.
- This qualifies one
to be a candidate for king.
It's a ceremonial touch stone
that's used to determine
if one is worthy to sit
at the throne
and lead this country
as a monarch.
- Wait a second.
Are you saying you lost
an insignia
that qualifies you
to rule the kingdom?
- Now, don't put it like that!
I didn't lose it!
It was stolen from me
by a thief!
- That's the same thing!
And what happens if you manage
to lose that thing, anyway?
Will a government office
issue another one?
- Oh, what a dreadful scenario.
[both grunting]
If you'd lost it then there
would be no doubt.
The belief would be that one
who can't even protect
a tiny insignia has no business
being entrusted
with the nation's rule,
and that would be the end.
- Well, knowing those facts,
I'd say I did a damn good job,
and it totally raises
my expectations
for a nice reward.
- Yeah, you're right about that.
You're a true savior to me
and I'm very thankful.
So ask me for anything.
- Yes, you heard the lady.
Any reward you desire.
Just name it.
- [laughs]
Well, in that case,
I have but one request.
- [giggles]
♪ ♪
I'm starting
to like this mansion.
Hire me to work here.
- [sneezes]
- No, that's not quite right.
Wasn't there anything else
that fit, Subaru?
- Oddly, some of the girls'
stuff fit me, but--
- Our deepest apologies
on the wardrobe, sir--
I mean, Subaru.
- I must say,
you look utterly ridiculous,
sir--I mean, Barusu.
- Oh, good job, Ram.
You just turned my name
into a blinding curse.
- Rem, notice anything about
Barusu's ludicrous appearance?
- Well, the shoulders
fit him funny,
his legs are short,
and his eyes are scary.
- Two of those are things
I can't do anything about, okay?
- We can't allow you
to work here
in such shoddy-looking attire.
People would begin to question
Lord Roswaal's dignity.
Let us alter the jacket
at the very least.
Rem, if you wouldn't mind.
- [chuckles]
If you'll excuse me,
I have to study
for the royal selection.
Good luck with your work,
Subaru.
- Yep, leave it to me, Mili.
[grunts]
- I'll take your measurements
for the fitting,
so stand still
with your back straight.
- [grunts]
[gasps]
- Please don't make
strange noises
during this process.
It's unpleasant for me.
- Unpleasant for you?
And that was beyond my control!
This is awkward for a guy,
you know?
- This is the V.I.P. room.
This is the bathing room.
This is the kitchen.
And this is the lavatory.
- In a mansion like this,
I bet the restroom
is freaking huge.
- My sweet Bubby.
Oh, oh, I love your fur.
- [laughing]
- [groans]
- Don't worry.
I won't tell a soul about this.
The feel of that fur
would make anyo--
[screams]
Ow, come on, now!
Let me finish, you little--
[grunts]
[gasps]
- You just witnessed
Miss Beatrice's door crossing.
- Oh, really?
So it's a spell that can connect
any door in the mansion
to her own room.
Is that it?
- And once Miss Beatrice
has eliminated her presence,
there's no way to find her
without trying every door.
- She's in here!
- [screams]
- Impressive, Subaru.
- All right, how did you pick
the right door again?
- Like I told you before,
remember?
I'm a flag crusher
who makes game masters cry.
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Tell me, how do you fit in
around here, anyway?
You Roswaal's little sister?
- I would never want to be
his sister, I suppose.
- Betty's a librarian
who oversees
the Roswaal Mansion's
forbidden library.
- Master Roswaal is the greatest
magic user in the kingdom.
He has many books
that mustn't be seen by others,
and Miss Beatrice
has been contracted
to protect them
from prying eyes.
- Understand now?
Then go away!
- This concludes our tour
of the mansion.
So do you have any questions?
- I know there's no use
saying this after it's over,
but don't you think it would
have made a whole lot more sense
for Mili to take me around
for the tour event?
- If you have no questions,
then let's get to the ins
and outs of your job.
Basically, you'll be helping
with my work, Barusu.
- This must be the moment when
my hidden skills as a butler
finally reveal themselves.
- My work today consists
of caring for the front yard
and garden,
helping to prepare lunch,
polishing the silver,
airing out the futons,
doing the laundry,
cleaning the bathrooms,
and the mansion's monthly
soot cleaning.
[distant church bells ringing]
- [groans]
Oh, finally.
[knocking]
[grunts]
- This is Rem.
Do you have a moment, Subaru?
- Sure, yeah, I'm good.
I won't do anything weird
so come on in.
- Your permission makes
you sound less credible.
Pardon me.
- You already finished
the alterations?
- When it's
Lord Roswaal's clothing,
I must be careful and precise,
but since this is yours--
- Wait, you cut corners
'cause it's me?
[quirky music]
I hate to admit it,
but it's perfect.
How do I look?
Good, huh?
- With this outfit over
the bizarre attire
that you were
originally wearing,
no one in any strange garment
could rival you.
- Not a compliment at all.
- And what shall
we do with those?
- This one's easy.
Got a needle and thread?
- Yes, I brought them.
Would you like me to repair them
for you now?
- Nah, that'll be okay.
I can do it.
Don't underestimate
my sewing skills.
[humming]
- I'm honestly surprised.
I must give you full marks
for your sewing.
I'd like to add, however,
that much like you,
it doesn't appear
useful whatsoever.
[stabbing]
- Ow!
[screaming]
- You may get full marks
for sewing but you're still
useless with a knife, Barusu.
- As always, you make such
a lovely image
when peeling vegetables, sister.
- Your bias is so blatant,
it's almost comforting.
I'd like a comment on my work,
too, if you could muster one up.
- How about, "I pity the farmer
who grew those vegetables?"
- Stop being so cruel!
You're breaking my heart.
- You don't know how
to handle a knife, Barusu.
You should hold it still
and simply turn the vegetable.
My best dish is steamed tatoes,
if I do say so myself.
- How can you say that with such
a triumphant look on your face?
[gasps]
Damn it, just watch.
My favorite blade Shooting Star
will show you a thing
or two about slicing!
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- How has Subaru been
since he started working?
Five days have passed
since his arrival.
Shouldn't we be seeing something
by now?
- Cooking, laundry, cleaning--
He's useless at all of them.
- How very harsh of you.
And what are the chances
he's a spy?
- I can't deny
that such potential exists,
but I think the possibility
is slim at best,
'cause for better or for worse--
for worse in this case
in particular--
he's too conspicuous.
- And if he's too conspicuous,
then...
Well, despite the odds
of that possibility,
he certainly is carefree,
isn't he?
Personally as I see it,
it would be wise
to interfere with things.
- They're both only children.
Even if we let them be,
nothing will happen.
- Huh.
- It's not that exciting
to watch, is it?
- You may think that,
but nothing's ever boring
when I'm hanging around you,
Mili.
- That's good to hear,
even if you're only
flattering me.
[chuckles]
- Besides, the two
of us haven't had
a chance to just talk
for the past few days, have we?
- That's true.
Bet it must have been difficult
for you to learn
the work expected of you here.
- Ain't that the truth?
It's killing me!
I wish I could be
tenderly comforted
in your arms,
your chest,
and your lap in rotation.
- If you can go around making
tasteless jokes like that,
you're probably fine.
- [groans]
[thuds]
Wow, the moon sure is pretty.
- And it's up in the heavens
far beyond our reach.
- Well, what do you know?
I got a really touching response
without even trying.
- [chuckles]
On another matter,
don't you think you're
a bit lacking in ambition?
Like that one time with Puck,
and in the capital when
you asked me for my name.
- You just don't get me at all,
do you, Emilia?
I want what I want
at that exact moment,
and I want it from the bottom
of my heart.
It's self-gratification
in its purest form.
- Huh?
- Right then,
I wanted to know your name
more than anything.
I had no expectations
for tomorrow
and I was simply trying
to make it through the day,
and on top of that,
I was in a new land,
nervous, and so uncertain
about my future.
Looking back on it,
there were probably other things
I should have wanted.
[dramatic music]
But I can't lie to myself
about things like that.
Same as the request
I made to Ros.
I'm flat broke right now.
I could choose to cheat him
out of a fortune and live it up,
but I can just as easily obtain
an ongoing source
of livelihood, right?
- In that case,
why didn't you simply choose
to become a permanent guest
rather than an employee?
- I never thought of that!
- [gasps]
- [grunting]
Oh, man!
What an idiot!
Talk about a pathetic effort,
huh?
- DO you want me to use
my healing magic?
- Nah, I'm fine like this.
- Really?
Why?
- [groans]
It's kind of hard
for me to explain,
but the way I see it,
this is proof of all
the effort I've been putting in.
I don't exactly dislike
exerting myself, you know?
Learning to do something
I couldn't do before?
To be honest,
it's not so bad.
- Yes, I see.
I would never have thought
of it that way.
[sighs]
You're such an idiot, Subaru.
- Well, that wasn't the reaction
I was expecting.
Wasn't I charming?
- You could never be.
Well, maybe just a little.
- EMA.
- Huh?
- Oh, it's short
for Emilia Major Angel.
- I was being so sincere
and now you're joking
around again?
Anyway, I know
you're working hard,
but how did your hands get
like that just by doing
some household chores?
- This hand I cut
with a kitchen knife,
and the one on the other hand
is from when I went to town
in the evening to shop
and a little animal
some kids were playing with
bit me.
- It wasn't the result
of your labor efforts?
- Those kids were ruthless,
hitting and kicking me,
and wiping their
runny noses on me.
Gotta say,
kinda sucked.
- You do seem like the type
of person who'd be good
with small children, Subaru.
- Hey, wait.
I've got an idea.
Wanna come with me tomorrow
to get revenge
on those little--I mean,
to watch the kids
and that small animal
play together?
- It's not as if I don't want
to go out there with you.
- Fine, then.
Let's go.
- But if--if I come along,
it might end up causing
a lot of trouble for you.
- Okay, understood.
Let's go.
- Are you even listening to me?
- I am, I swear.
I hang on every word
you say, Mili.
- Fine, then,
but only when I'm able
to take a break
from all of my studying
and your work is done
for the day, okay?
- [gasps]
Yeah, all right!
This is gonna be great!
[both laughing]
[humming]
Hey, loli girl.
I see you're still up.
- So now you can just casually
break through my door crossing
like it's natural,
I suppose.
- Well, I just wanted
to say hello
before going to bed.
Can I try that, too?
- Only Bubby has permission
to touch me, I suppose.
- Why should you get to have all
of the fun?
I'm in a good mood
so I can let it go.
- Enough!
Get out of here!
- [groans]
- And that had nothing to do
with Betty, I suppose.
- For our date tomorrow,
I'll have to come up with
a clever excuse
to ditch the kids
in the village.
Oh, but first I gotta find out
where all the good views
and the flower fields
and other stuff are.
Crap, I can't sleep while
I'm thinking about this!
Oh, I know.
One Puck to pet.
Two Pucks to pet.
101 Pucks to pet.
[crickets chirping]
A new dawn has come across
the land.
A dawn of hope!
Subaru Natsuki is going
to make great strides today!
What are you two doing in here?
This is so embarrassing!
You should have said something!
- Sister, Sister, I do believe
that our guest appears
appears to be a bit confused.
What do you think?
- Rem, Rem, yes,
I agree.
It looks as though our guest
has gone crazy.
- Hey, why are you calling me
a guest?
[laughs]
You two and your silly
little jokes.
[tense music]
[shuddering]
The wounds,
they're gone.
[tense music]
- Wh--why?
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[grunts]
[whimpers]
Why have I gone back?
- Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
You don't seem
to be feeling very well.
Are you going to be all right?
- Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
You appear to have
a stomach ache.
You didn't soil yourself,
did you?
- [shuddering]
I take it you don't remember me?
So it's like none
of it ever happened?
[both grunting]
both: What do you mean, sir?
- [weeping]
♪ ♪
- Sir, you shouldn't try
to move so suddenly.
- [grunts]
What happened, damn it?
Everything reset again,
including my promise
to Emilia!
[crying]
[whimpering]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- You come in here
without even knocking?
What an extremely
rude one you are.
- Sorry.
Just let me stay here for a bit,
please.
- This makes the second time
you've walked in
and found me like this,
so how are you breaking
through my door crossing?
- [gasps]
B--Beatrice!
- Addressing me with no title,
I suppose?
- Sorry, listen.
You said this makes
the second time
that I've broken through
your door crossing, right?
- Yes, remember?
I teased you about it
three or four hours ago
for being so insensitive.
- If this is the second time
I've woken up here
in the mansion,
then we've met each other
and you remember me, don't you?
- Well, to be honest,
if I could,
I'd rather erase you
from my memory, I suppose.
- So it seems the conditions
are different from last time.
The save point's changed
from near the guy with the appas
to the two girls
in maid uniforms.
How'd I pass away?
Everything was normal
before I fell asleep.
Even after that,
I didn't get into any situations
where I felt like I would die.
- I wondered what you
were muttering about,
and all I hear is this drivel
about living and dying.
How boring and senseless
to discuss such things
by human standards.
In the end you'll only come up
with lies and abusive speech.
- [chuckles]
Thanks.
You were a big help.
- I didn't do anything.
- Somehow witnessing that
never-changing attitude of yours
seems to have calmed
me down a bit.
- Only an ultimate pervert
would be put at ease
by verbal abuse,
I suppose.
[door opening]
[grunts]
You're leaving,
I suppose?
- Uh-huh, 'cause there's
something that
I wanna make sure of.
I'll wait until afterward
to get depressed.
[doors creaking]
[birds chirping]
Yeah, I knew it.
- Subaru!
- You're absolutely shining.
- [grunts]
I was worried about you!
Ram and Rem were
running around everywhere
in a frenzy saying
that you disappeared
right after you woke up.
- Sorry about that.
Kinda got held up
by Beatrice for a bit.
- Again?
I heard that she played
a trick on you
before you woke up, too.
[grunts]
Why are you staring?
Oh, goodness.
Is there something on my face?
- Yeah, of course there is.
Your adorable eyes, ears,
nose, and mouth.
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
I mean,
I'm glad you're okay.
- [grunts]
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you.
After all,
you did protect me.
But anyway,
enough about that.
How are you feeling?
- Oh, I'm feeling great.
Let's see.
I'm a little low on blood,
all my mana was stolen from me,
the shock of waking up
so suddenly sapped my strength,
and I feel like my mind's been
beaten to death
with a bat,
but other than that,
I'm fantastic!
- I see.
That's great.
[gasps]
Hang on.
Wouldn't that mean
you're hurt all over?
- [yawing]
Hi there, Subaru.
Great morning, isn't it?
I really can't thank you enough
for what you did yesterday,
but I'll find a way to somehow.
- I know!
How about you let me
pet your fur
whenever I feel like it?
- Really?
That's all you want?
- [gasps]
[both moaning]
Okay, let's go.
Our time is limited
and our world is grand.
The story of me and Mili
has only just begun.
There's lots to do!
- That's true.
Wait, what did you just say?
Where did the "Mili" come from?
- I don't know whose idea
of a prank this is,
but I'm gonna make you sorry
for all of it.
Don't underestimate
how vindictive I'll be
after the smile that charmed me
that evening.
I'm going to keep my promise
to Mili no matter what.
I'll get past that night.
- Any reward you desire.
Just name it.
- Well, in that case,
I have but one request.
I'm starting
to like this mansion.
Hire me to work here!
- [sneezes]
- It's how these
looping plots work.
All you gotta do is follow
the same path
and you'll end up
in the same place.
- That's too large for you,
Barusu.
- [grunts]
- It seems that nothing here
will fit you
except women's clothes.
Rem, would you please alter
that one for him?
- Yes, of course, sister.
- All right,
take my measurements,
'cause a man like me
can withstand all kinds
of awkwardness.
- We'll measure you
a bit later.
- Eh, huh?
- Now follow me, Barusu.
- Are you gonna show me around
this place or--
- Not right now.
That will also wait.
You're going to be helping me
with my work first.
- Hey, hang on a second!
Retrace the same path
I took yesterday.
Simple.
That's what I meant to do,
but...
This is totally different
from what happened last time.
It's like when you make
a cheat sheet
for a major exam
but when you see the answers,
you realize
it's the wrong subject.
Total waste of effort.
[doors opening]
Hmm?
- Hi, there!
Mind if I join you?
- Yes, I do.
- This facility is part
of my mansion
which makes it my property.
Therefore I'll do with it
as I please.
- Why bother asking permission?
Take a bath if you want to.
- My, what harsh words
from the hired help.
You don't seem to understand.
As we've both made
abundantly clear,
this bath is my property,
but as you are part of my staff,
does it not stand to reason
that you're my property as well?
- Chomp.
- No hesitation at all.
This is turning out different
from what I'd expected, too.
- I don't know
what's bothering you,
but you'll come to discover
that life is full of things
that don't go your way.
Incidentally, what do you think
of my support staff?
Getting along famously, I hope.
- I haven't spoken that much
to Rem at this point,
but I get along
just fine with Ram.
In fact, I think she might
be getting
a little too friendly.
I can't believe she can work
as a maid that way.
- Well, Rem handles the things
Ram is unable to do.
As sisters,
they must help each other.
If you think about it
in that sense,
I believe the two of them
are getting by quite well.
It seems like Ram's the inferior
version of her sister
and all Rem does
is cover for her,
yet they insist Ram is superior
'cause she happens
to be the older one.
It's scary how much nerve
the two of them have.
- While we're on the subject
of nerves,
yours appears
quite impressive as well,
if I do say so.
- Damn, I'm dizzy
from that bath.
Stupid Roswaal.
[screams]
- Would you mind covering up
that sorry thing?
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- I was just waiting to help
Lord Roswaal
put on fresh clothes.
While I'm sure you
were looking forward to it,
I'm sorry to say that
I finished my bath,
so I won't be changing.
- As if!
I wasn't thinking
about that at all!
On top of that,
you spoil him too much.
Let him dress himself!
- Enough.
I will not condone disrespect
toward Lord Roswaal.
Next time I will use
a more forceful approach.
- Easy.
Don't stir the hornet's nest.
- By the way, Barusu,
do you have plans after this?
- No, not really.
I'm just going to sleep.
- Then please wait
in your room for me.
I'll come by later.
- Huh?
Easy.
She didn't mean anything by it.
Clear your mind.
Mili's the only one for you.
Calm down.
Calm down!
One smiling Mili.
Two smiling Milis.
Three smiling Milis.
Am I in Heaven?
- You're far too noisy, Barusu.
It's nighttime.
You need to be quiet now.
- [whimpers]
- Barusu, come over here.
- Wait, my heart's already
set on someone
and her name is Mili!
- What are you talking about?
I'm telling you that you need
to sit over here
so I can teach you how
to read and write.
- That's what you wanted?
So where's this coming from?
- I could tell by watching you
that you're
completely illiterate.
If you can't read or write,
then I can't send you shopping.
It also means you can't
take down orders.
We'll start with
some children's fairy tales.
Beginning tonight,
I'll help you study
every evening.
- Thanks, but why are you being
so nice to me?
- Well, why do you think?
So I can--no, wait.
It makes things easier for me.
- You're correcting yourself?
You're never out of character.
- It's rather obvious.
The more you're able to do
and handle on your own,
the less I have
to do around here,
and when I have less to do,
that means Rem's workload
is lighter also.
So it's a total win-win.
- Look, I get it,
but that leaves me
with piles of work, though!
- We'll start
with the basic i-glyphs.
After that, we'll move on
to ro-glyphs
and ha-glyphs.
- There are three
different types?
Just hearing that
is depressing.
- You don't have time to waste
on silly doodles.
We have an early start tomorrow
so we're short on time.
I'm sleepy, too.
- You know, can't say I dislike
how you manage to slip in
your own feelings about this
at the end of that thought.
- In my own humble opinion,
I believe honesty
is my most charming feature.
Now then,
let's get started.
- So monotonous,
I feel a Gestaltzerfall
phenomenon coming on.
But still, even if you did
teach me to read and write
just to make your life easier,
it made me happy.
Honestly, I was beginning
to get the feeling
you just didn't like me
that much,
and I'll probably cause
even more problems for you
down the line,
but I'll try to become useful
as soon as I...
- [breathing heavily]
- [grunts]
- Oh, wow.
It actually turned out perfect.
Guess my sewing skills
aren't gonna be needed
this time around, huh?
- Your sewing skills?
If you excel at it,
I assume you enjoy it, then?
- Yeah, kinda.
By the way,
it looks like Ros and Mili
have quite a few outfits
to choose from,
but I don't really see any
for you or Ram.
Want me to sew some for you?
I'll take your measurements.
- That's not necessary.
The uniforms my sister
and I wear daily
are all that we need.
- Seriously?
How can you have nothing
but those uniforms?
You own no other clothes?
- It makes things much easier
when there are guests here
in the mansion or when we're
with Lord Roswaal on business.
Doing so eliminates the need
to explain our place
in the hierarchy which makes it
very logical.
- Well, I'm not talking
about being logical here.
What I'm trying to say is that
a couple of cute girls like you
and your sister ought
to dress up and look nice
both for yourselves
and other people, you know?
- As far as that goes,
my sister's one thing,
but no one would be happy
to see me dress up.
- You're wrong there.
I sure would.
- Well, even if that's true,
what good would come
of making you happy?
- I might take a little
more pride in my work here,
which could boost
my productivity.
- I've no idea what would
make you say such a thing.
That mindset makes no sense.
- I'd also look forward
to seeing the differences
in the clothing
you'd each choose.
Who'd be classy,
who'd be risque.
- That's irrelevant.
Does my looking the same
as my sister
inconvenience you somehow?
- If you ask me, you love
your sister way too much.
[slicing]
[shouts]
- You've no idea how to properly
handle a knife, Barusu.
- I know what I'm doing.
You hold the knife still
and turn the food item, right?
[pot bubbling]
[grunts]
It's kind of embarrassing
when you stare
at me so intently.
[quirky music]
Huh?
- Your unsightly appearance
stands out
and makes you an eyesore.
Especially your hair.
It's incredibly unrefined.
- It really looks that bad?
I thought I did
a pretty good job
of cutting it by myself.
- By the way,
Rem takes care
of everyone's hair
in this mansion.
She styles mine and dresses me
every morning as well.
Nice of her,
don't you think?
- You should try to contribute
a little more around here.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Rem.
If you like,
feel free to tidy up
Barusu's hair a little.
- Pardon me?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Having a girl mess with my hair
will get me all worked up!
- The reason you keep looking
at Barusu
is because his hair bothers you,
doesn't it?
- That's correct.
I think just combing it
and evening out the ends
would make him more presentable.
- Indeed.
Think you should take her up
on that offer.
With talented hands like hers,
you'll feel like
you're in paradise.
- Look, I know
what you're saying,
but why'd you have
to make it sound so dirty?
- Uh, if you don't want to,
you should just tell her,
if you ask me.
Not that I wanna be picked on,
but--
- I don't think that at all.
The truth of the matter is that
it did bother me a little.
Very, very much a little.
Extremely a little.
- Okay, I get it.
It bothered you.
Point taken.
- What's the matter, Betty?
- Oh, it's nothing at all,
Bubby.
Anyway, I have delicious
sweets today, I suppose.
Care to eat them with me?
- [chomps]
Yummy!
[doors creaking]
- Mm?
What's up?
You here to help me?
- No, I'm here
about what I said
earlier at lunchtime.
- Lunchtime?
Oh, about my hair?
You'll really style it for me?
- Not that.
I felt that I said some things
to you that were uncalled for.
I'm very sorry,
and while the two of us may
be colleagues,
as Miss Emilia's savior,
your rank far surpasses mine.
- Guess I never thought
about it.
Is this how you really feel?
Sorry to put you through that.
- No, I should apologize
for saying something
so pointless.
Please forget about it.
- I guess it's never that easy,
is it?
It's part of what makes
being human so hard sometimes.
Fine, I'll give you
a condition, then.
If you agree to it,
whatever it may be,
I'll forget everything
you just said.
- Agree to a condition?
Very well.
I'll hear whatever it is
you have to say.
- [chuckles]
If you use your talented hands
to comb my hair a little
and even out the ends,
then I'll let it slide!
It actually hurts even more
when you choose
to respond with silence.
- It's just like
Miss Emilia said.
You have no motivation
or ambition whatsoever.
- Oh, come on, now.
I'd think a quality like that
would make you fall for me
all over again,
not disgust you.
- My sister said your eyes
take on an obscene look
when she's alone with you.
She still feels them
when your back is turned.
Honestly, I thought
you would suggest that.
- She's killing my reputation.
- All right,
I accept your condition.
I will do as you wish
to have your forgiveness.
- [grunts]
[laughs]
Great, but I prefer you do it
after I keep my promise
to Mili, okay?
- What promise?
- Well, it's one that
I haven't exactly made just yet.
[birds chirping]
It might be a good idea
to scope out
our date destination
before I make that promise.
[peaceful music]
I've researched the places
with the best views.
That just leaves dealing
with this.
- Can't believe you're back.
- His face looks weird again.
- I need to make sure all these
little guys don't find us
wherever we end up.
- What do you mean, find you?
- Hey, did you pee your pants?
- Chill out, you brats!
I played with you earlier!
- Let's play more!
- Yeah, come on!
Change your pants.
- Now, listen up, guys.
Next time I plan on coming here,
it'll be on a date,
so try to take a hint, okay?
[grunts]
But whatever the case,
I'll be sure to allow this
little critter
to play with Miss Emilia.
Hey there, buddy.
[dog whining]
[chomps]
Ow!
Again?
- Subaru.
This is where
you wandered off to.
Are you all right?
- Oh, I'm fine,
I'm fine.
Are you all done shopping,
Rem-Rem?
- Yes, it went quite smoothly.
[all laughing]
- Aww, man.
You're leaving already?
- Yeah, don't leave here yet.
- Wait, you have a place to go?
- It appears that you are rather
popular with all of them.
Weren't you?
- Yeah, I suppose so.
For some reason kids
have always liked me.
- Children observe a hierarchy
much in the same way animals do,
and in that way,
they can tell if it's okay
to belittle someone.
- Those little backwoods brats.
They don't have any respect
for their elders at all.
- In part,
that's because of you.
Did you show them anything
about you worth respecting?
- Yeah, that is
a sound argument.
Still, it doesn't seem right
for them to belittle me
right from the start.
Ram seems like the type who'd
handle that scenario
like a real champ.
- My sister is wonderful,
isn't she?
- Honestly, I think
a personality like hers
would give rise to conflict
more often than not.
- My sister's
self-assured nature
is what makes her so charming.
I can't be that way.
It's just not me.
- [gasps]
- By the way,
how are your reading
and writing studies going?
Have you made any progress?
- Well, uh, I'm plugging along,
though I must admit,
Ram is actually
a pretty good teacher.
I just wish she wouldn't fall
asleep on my bed in mid-lesson.
It kind of kills my motivation.
- On the contrary,
my sister's only acting that way
to stimulate your motivation.
- Why do you have such
absolute faith in your sister?
'Cause that's not normal,
you know.
You're demonically inspired,
for real.
- Demonically inspired?
- Demon version
of divine inspiration.
Sounds kinda cool, right?
- I see.
Do you like demons?
- Hmm.
Well, it just seems to me
that gods don't generally
do much of anything.
Demons, on the other hand,
can't help but laugh along
when you start talking
about future plans,
especially for next year
and things like that.
They'll laugh their heads off.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- [giggles]
- You've really got
a million-volt smile!
- I'm going to tell Miss Emilia.
- I wasn't trying to hit on you.
- Both Ram and Rem said
they wouldn't be coming
to see you tonight
for whatever reason,
so I agreed to stop by
and try to help you along
with your studies instead.
I'm afraid I can't do much,
though.
- [whimpers]
I'm, uh, just writing
the basic i-glyphs
to memorize them.
- Wow.
You're really putting a lot
more effort into this
than I expected you would.
- Th--this fairy tail collection
is aimed at kids,
so it's mostly i-glyphs,
or so they said.
My goal for now is t--to be able
to read this.
[whimpering]
[heart pounding]
Anyway, um--
- Oh?
- [grunts]
- Th--the moon sure is pretty.
- Huh?
- No, I mean, um, listen!
I have a favor to ask you.
Will you hear me out?
I'll work hard
starting tomorrow,
and I'll study, too.
Go on a date with me.
- What do you do
on a date?
- [chuckles]
When a guy and a girl go out
alone together,
it's called a date!
See?
And only the goddess of love
is aware of what will happen
during their
special time together.
- Going by that description,
you went on a date
with Rem today, right?
- [screams]
I didn't expect that response!
That didn't count!
Please don't count that!
- I understand you want us
to go out together,
but where do you plan
on taking me?
- There's this really cute
little dog in the village
near here I'd like
to show you.
There's a flower field nearby,
too.
I wanna see you frolicking
around in a field of flowers,
and after that, I wanna capture
the image for eternity
with my metia.
- You want to go
to the village?
- It's the cutest dog ever.
Say you'll go.
- It does sound nice,
but it might
cause trouble for you
if we went there together,
and for the villagers.
- The kids are so pure
and innocent,
they're just like angels.
Say you'll go!
- You're not leaving me
much choice.
If that's what you want,
then yes.
I will go with you.
- The flower field is colorful
and wonderf--wait, really?
- If doing so will motivate you
to work hard from tomorrow on,
then I'd be happy to join you.
- [squeals]
All right!
- [chuckles]
I bet the weather will be
absolutely lovely tomorrow.
- Yeah, and it'll be a day
I'll never forget.
- Come now,
there you go again with--
- [grunts]
- You were--you were just--
never mind.
See you tomorrow.
- You know,
it makes a guy really anxious
when you don't finish
your sentences like that.
- Okay, butler Subaru.
Remember to work hard 'cause
only those who do and persevere
get rewarded
so this will be a reward.
- ♪ Oh please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch ♪
[MYTH&ROID's "STYX HELIX"]
♪ No don't give up on life
This endless dead end ♪
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I wish I was there ♪
♪ Oh please don't let me die ♪
♪ Waiting for your touch ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Restart ♪
♪ No don't give up on life ♪
♪ This endless dead end ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ For now I'll see you off ♪
♪ And we'll die waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ And we'll start
waiting for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[crickets chirping]
[distant wolf howling]
- All right, fate.
The two of us are going
to settle this,
and I'm not heading
to sleep tonight
no matter what.
I'm staying awake to greet
the morning of my promise.
[heart pounding]
Geez, take it easy.
It's like I'm a grade schooler
too excited to sleep
before a field trip.
Reminds me of when I overslept
on the day we went
to the museum.
[heartbeat pounding]
I wasn't able to retrace
the same loop exactly,
but I did get along pretty well
with Ram and Rem this go around.
In fact, I think I did better
than last time.
[heartbeat pounding]
If there's anything I feel
like I missed this time around
that's different from the last,
it's that I didn't try
and say good-night to Beatrice.
[gasps]
Every single time I saw her,
all we did was insult
each other,
but maybe I should have at--
at least thanked her.
You know,
to be nice.
- [grunting]
[heartbeat pounding]
[groaning]
[gasping]
What the--
[gasps]
It's so cold.
[shuddering]
No.
Could this be what--
[gags]
[vomits]
Someone.
[grunting]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[vomits]
Please, someone help me!
[gasping]
[grunting]
[distant clanking]
[clanking getting louder]
[blow lands]
[grunts]
[shouting]
[gasping]
♪ ♪
What was that?
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[gasps]+
[screaming]
[distant clanking]