[chorus vocalizing]
RICARDO: Hey, boy.
SUBARU: No, this can't be.
- What's wrong?
- [chorus vocalizes]
- SUBARU: Huh?
[gasps]
- [grunts]
- [wails]
- You spaced out,
so I had to get your attention
somehow, neow, didn't I?
- Wait. Felix?
- Of course.
Who else do I look like?
Did you inhale too much
of the White Whale's fog?
- Uh, no. I'm fine.
Actually that told me
what I wanted to know.
So this means...
my save point has been
updated to this moment?
- [chanting]
- ♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Grew up in the loneliness ♪
[wind blowing]
- There are a few new things
I've come to realize
about the Witch's Cult
that are definitely
worth mentioning.
LEADERS: Huh?
- Does anyone know
of something like...
a power you can use
to overwrite
someone's consciousness,
allowing you
to psychologically control them?
- In other words, you believe
that the Sin Archbishops
may have such an ability?
How unsettling.
- No kidding.
Somehow he's able
to possess others.
It's how he stays alive,
and it would also explain
how he manages to keep
popping up everywhere.
- Yes. I once saw an
account
of something quite similar
in an old book.
It's a type of magic
that's been lost
over the centuries,
though it only works
under certain conditions.
- What do you mean?
- Few can use the method.
It is said that certain select
members of the Witch's Cult
acquired the capability.
- In that case,
I guess you mean the fingers?
JULIUS: Most likely, they are
the user's spare bodies.
It's quite
a tasteless arrangement,
but beneficial
to a Sin Archbishop.
- [gasps]
So if those confidants,
the fingers,
were to be wiped out...
- Under that circumstance,
his soul would have
no vessel to take refuge in,
and that would be
the end of him, without a doubt.
- [gasps]
- We should eliminate
each of the fingers
in the forest first
and then face Sloth directly.
That is my conclusion.
[Iron Fangs murmuring]
JULIUS: Hmm?
- You guys,
there's one more thing
I need to say
about all this new info.
Sorry, but I don't think
it's just the fingers.
Think he may have the capability
of possessing me, too.
So, uh, what do you
think I should do?
- Huh?
- Filthy woman.
- Would you also
apologize for being born?
- You silver-haired half-elf.
- A margrave maid has endorsed
a half-devil?
- ...apologize for being born?
- I had such high hopes
for you.
- I thought maybe you...
- ...only you wouldn't give me
the special treatment that
surrounded me my entire life.
- Sorry. I can't do that.
- ...silver- haired half-elf.
- There's absolutely
no way I can look at you
the same way
I look at other people.
It's impossible.
- I've told you I'm not
connected to the Witch at all.
[overlapping chatter]
[music playing]
- What's wrong?
Your forehead
looks all wrinkled.
- [chuckles]
Nothing. Good morning.
You're starting
pretty early today.
- Good morning, Lia.
I figured I'd try going to sleep
and waking up earlier.
Ah, sorry. That was a lie.
The truth of the matter
is I've been kinda worried
about you lately.
You've had a rough go of it,
especially yesterday.
- It was nothing
I didn't know already.
- Even if you're sure
you'll fall down,
you still get hurt and bleed
when it happens, don't you?
- Tell me, Puck,
what do you think I should do?
I mean, what can I do
to be better to everybody?
And have them be better to me?
- [sighs]
Honestly, I think
you should do whatever you want.
I'll be on your side,
no matter what.
Don't forget that, okay?
- [chuckles]
- Regardless of what you do,
you can't abandon everybody
in that village, right?
Ram went to go try again.
She headed out there
early this morning.
Maybe we should wait
to hear from her.
- [grunts]
- I think I'm gonna
check in on Betty.
- Oh, okay. Sure.
Tell her hello for me.
- [door closes]
- [gasps]
Ram!
- Miss Emilia,
there's a visitor
who's come here to see you.
- I know you.
You're from Miss Crusch's
household, aren't you?
- My name is Wilhelm Trias.
I've come to speak with you
on behalf of my master.
- Is that so?
I received a blank letter
from her yesterday.
- Just as I feared, it's true.
- [gasps]
- I beg your pardon.
While it shames me to say so,
the letter contradicted
the message
my master intended to send.
- Oh. It was a mistake, then?
- Yes. Miss Emilia,
and you, Miss Ram,
we would like to evacuate
those
remaining here in the mansion
as well as the nearby villagers.
That is Miss Crusch's will.
- Huh? Really?
There's a ring of criminals
near the forest?
RAM: Yes. The punitive force
this messenger
brought along with him
is already preparing
to fight the enemy as we speak.
- How kind.
But why would Miss Crusch
go out of her way
and do so much
to help this domain?
- My master received
a proposal from the margrave
to form an alliance with respect
to the royal selection.
The condition is a large share
of the mining rights
in Elior Forest.
Do you understand this, ma'am?
- Uh, so that's
what this is about.
- However, it will
certainly be difficult
to evacuate all the villagers
to the capital.
Our plan calls for roughly
half of them to go there.
- And as for the other half,
I will lead each one to safety
in the Sanctuary.
Lord Roswaal is heading there
now to make arrangements.
- Ah. Oh, I see.
So discussion on the matter
is already over.
I'm relieved.
But isn't this circumstance
a bit odd?
It seems too well timed.
[door slams open]
- Pardon me, sir!
The group hiding in the forest
has been observed
moving strangely.
- [gasps]
- We haven't a moment to waste
for the evacuation.
Once they make their move,
the whole region
will be a sea of blood!
What do you want us
to do, Captain?
No, Sword Demon Captain Wilhelm.
- What is your decision?
- [sighs]
I understand,
and I gratefully
accept your kindness.
Has this been explained
to the villagers?
RAM: Yes. They've been informed
in a timely fashion,
Miss Emilia.
- I see.
- Betty says she'll stay here.
- Puck!
- Betty can't go
with you, I suppose.
I'll simply wait here
for you to return.
There's no need
to worry about me.
- So that's that.
Of course, in Betty's case,
the forbidden library
is a safer place to be anyway.
And besides, she can't
leave
the grounds of the mansion
due to her contract.
You know that, right, Lia?
- She's using that
as a reason? Great.
- So since my cute little sister
will be staying here
and can look after things,
I don't think we should
do anything to the mansion.
Betty is kind and sweet,
of course,
but she'll show no mercy
to intruders.
- Understood, great spirit.
We shall heed your words.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- Either way, you should do
whatever you wanna do.
Never forget what I told you.
I'm on your side,
and yours alone.
- We will evacuate.
The villagers need protection.
I don't want to put them
in any danger.
- [chuckles]
- We're all packed up, Lady.
Ready when you are.
- Wait. What?
Sorry, but I think there
may have been a mistake.
- Not at all. Given the number
of people and carriages,
to expedite the process,
we ask you to share a ride
with these children.
It's a necessary measure.
- Can't we put them
in a different carriage?
Think that would be better,
for the children, that is.
- You think no one would want
to ride with you? Is that it?
Tell me, have you asked the kids
how they feel about that?
Perhaps you just assumed
they hate you
and wouldn't want
to be around you
without any actual discussion
on the matter.
- No, that's not what I--
I don't need
to ask them to know.
I'm certain it would be best
for all of us.
- Six children
in one dragon-drawn carriage.
If we stumble here, how
will
your wish ever come true?
- Do I know you?
- What do you think, Petra?
Do you have anything
against taking a ride
in the same carriage
as this lady here?
- [sighs]
- No, of course not.
- [gasps]
- I know her.
You're the lady with
the potato stamps, aren't you?
The same one who always
came along with Subaru
to watch when we'd do
our exercises.
- Well, I, uh...
- You didn't say much,
but I know it was you.
We couldn't see your face,
but we saw you having
a good time talking with him.
[giggles]
- [gasps]
- Please come and ride with us.
- It'll be fun.
- Yeah, I wanna
ride with you, too.
- Come on. Let's go, already.
- [children laughing]
- Let's go!
- Come with us.
- It's gonna be
pulled by a dragon!
- [children laughing]
- That's so cool!
[Petra laughs]
- Ram, take care of things
at the Sanctuary.
Be sure to protect
the villagers.
- Of course, Miss Emilia.
You take care as well.
- And, whoever you are,
I'd like to thank you
for helping me to--
Huh? Where did he go?
- [sighs]
[wind blowing]
- SUBARU: Now I get it.
- Huh?
- We couldn't figure out
how you guys stayed in touch.
Those metia sure are handy,
aren't they?
- [blow strikes]
- Huh? [gasps]
- There's a heavy price to pay
for the crime of interrupting
my touching and long-awaited
reunion with Emilia.
- [gasps] You're...
[swords slash]
- Too slow.
- [groans]
- Guess by now you've realized
we've had you pegged
as a spy for some time.
How we found out
is a little trade secret.
So knowing you were the contact
for the Witch's Cult,
we laid out this trap
just for you.
Two hours.
You gave your buddies
a schedule
that was two hours
behind the real time frame.
We can use that time to get
Emilia and the others out,
raid this forest,
and crush the fingers
that know our location,
then make
the proper preparations
to wipe out your Sin Archbishop
once and for all.
The feeling of your enemy
always being one step
ahead,
you're about to learn
just how terrifying it is
to be in that position.
[music playing]
- Please be careful.
May the blessings
of the spirits be with you.
- [gasps]
- May you prevail.
- So this is what enabled you
to deceive Miss Emilia
and chase her
out of harm's way, huh?
- [groans] Come on!
Don't put it like that!
Even if it's accurate,
it makes me sound bad.
- That robe has been
woven
with quite a peculiar
spell.
- [sighs] It's a handmade item
by Roswaal.
Apparently there's
a spell laced into it
that prevents recognition.
Originally it was Emilia's,
but I--
[gasps]
Look, I didn't steal it, okay?!
- Sure.
What a day, huh?
Things are looking up for you.
The mistake
with the blank letter,
correcting that worked out well.
RAM: The letter was a mistake.
It was all my fault.
- And all of those
doubtful villagers,
you worked hard
to convince them, Subaru.
- [gasps]
- Please!
Emilia's--
she's a girl who could be
friends with every one of you,
and I want you
to give her the chance
to make you see that!
[villagers murmuring]
- I'm sure you all have
a lot you'd like to say,
but please let us
protect you long enough
to allow that chance
to happen!
- [sighs]
Jeez.
You really are hopeless,
Subaru.
Get up, already.
- [gasps]
- If you insist
on protecting us so much,
what choice do we have
in the matter?
You've never let us down.
- Getting old
is the most awful thing.
My tear glands are weaker
than they once were.
- Thanks, everyone.
Thank you all.
- We're the ones who should
be thanking you, young man.
We won't forget this.
- Ah, you actually
moved me back there.
- Don't bring it up again!
It's embarrassing!
- [laughs] That just leaves...
Welcome back!
How did it go?
- We all pulled off
the surprise attack
without a hitch.
That leaked intel
was as good as gold.
Your map helped out, too.
- Good to hear.
So the mark on the map
really was their base after all.
Lucky us.
- I don't know if you'd call
'em fastidious or high-strung,
but it worked against 'em.
And we got
what we were after, too.
This strike should shut down
the communications network.
- Hooray! We killed all of 'em!
- Please don't say that.
It makes us sound awful.
Oh, guess what!
We took a prisoner, too.
- A prisoner?
[boing, boing]
- [groans]
SUBARU: [laughs] Nice!
But he's not
in the Witch's Cult.
I was wondering
why you hadn't shown up yet.
You got caught, huh? [laughs]
- I don't know who you are,
and I don't care,
'cause either way, I'd like
to thank you for saving me.
Uh, what am I saying?!
I'm no mood
to claim that and mean it!
- [laughing]
- Damn it!
[wind blowing]
JULIUS: Everything is
ready and accounted for.
Subaru, we can leave anytime.
- [grunts]
Let's do this, everyone.
We'll begin as planned.
Now...
this time, we'll finish it!
Let's show Sloth and fate
what some motivated people
can do!
- [chorus vocalizing]
- I've been waiting to see you
face to face for a long time,
believer in love.
I am a Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult,
representing Sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti, yes!
- It's a pleasure to meet you,
great Sin Archbishop.
If you could find it within you
to add my body and soul
to the ranks of your
fingers
carrying out the Ordeal,
there would be no greater honor.
- [whimpering]
- Please allow me into the fold.
- Oh, my!
How wondrous,
how vivacious your faith is.
[grunts] To think there was
such a devout believer.
Please forgive my sloth
for failing to find him!
- [pounding]
- Forgive me. Forgive me.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
Forgive me! Forgive me!
- Please stop, Archbishop!
Don't!
- [winces]
But, but, but...
I have no way to atone
for the sloth and
foolishness I have shown
but by self-inflicted
punishment.
- Look, that's not true,
and you know it.
The Witch wouldn't want
to see her beloved believer
in such agony and pain.
She would be
much happier to see you
carry out the Ordeal
to completion!
- [gasps]
Now what was I thinking?
You are absolutely right.
Yes, of course. The Ordeal!
What she needs from me
right now is the Ordeal.
[yelps]
Your inspiring words
have opened my eyes.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Uh...
- With this Ordeal,
we must test her
and find out if this half-devil
is good enough,
if she is a worthy vessel
to put the Witch into.
- What are you talking about?
Worthy vessel?
- If she is worthy,
the Witch will possess her.
If she is not,
the Witch will reject her.
If she proves a worthy vessel,
then the Witch will be reborn
into this world
on the coming fated day.
- Hang on a minute.
You're saying
Emilia is secondary,
with no value to you at all?
You monster.
- The words inscribed
on the pages of the Gospel
tell of her love!
All of it guides me
down this glorious path!
Time to show me your Gospel.
Eh? What's that?
- Just what it looks like,
a metia, Sin Archbishop.
- Huh?
I see him. I see him.
Ugh! His face looks
just as scary as I heard.
- My face? Who are you?
No! I mean what are you?!
- Now then, Tora! Tora! Tora!
[snap echoes]
- [roaring]
[groans]
- [roars]
- Looks like our surprise attack
is a success!
- What?!
[grumbles] Surprise attack?
Then what do you
think of this?!
- [warbling]
- How?!
How can your eyes
see my Authority?!
- No idea.
Maybe you should ask the Witch
who left her scent all over me
for the answer to that
question.
Oh, that's right.
Unlike me, you haven't
received the special pass
letting you meet with the
Witch
anytime you want, have you?
- [gasps] What do you mean?
How dare you speak
as though you are intimate
with the Witch, imposter?!
- I'm not lying.
We're so close,
she's grabbed my heart...
literally.
- [stammers] Inconceivable!
[gags]
That simply cannot be!
- Come on! Let's go, Patrasche!
- [warbles]
[Authority moaning]
[warbles]
- Don't you dare think
you can ever escape from me.
- Here he comes. Here he comes.
He's getting closer!
Hurry! Don't slow down!
- [Authority warbles]
- Impossible!
Vanish in the vengeful face
of my devoted diligence!
[rumbling]
- [gasps]
Sorry to rely on you
all the time.
You're the greatest, Patrasche!
- But, but, but, but, but...
this is the end, the end!
- [gasps]
[both yell]
- [winces]
Careful, you two.
You almost caught me up
in that blast.
Thanks, though.
I thought I was a goner.
- You're welcome, Subaru!
We're happy to help!
- Is that man
floating up in the sky
the Sin Archbishop?
MIMI: Whoa!
What the heck is that?
There's a balled-up man flying.
That's crazy!
- I never seen anything
look so creepy, seriously!
- So he just looks
like he's sitting down,
floating to you guys?
It doesn't matter.
Either way, leave him to me.
Watch the rear like we planned!
- You got it, Subaru!
Let's do this, Sis.
- Aye, aye! Hey, bro,
you're gonna look pretty awesome
if you beat him now!
- Yeah! I got this!
Bring it on, Archbishop!
- What did you say?
He's coming for me?!
Who do you think you are?
That cannot be! It's impossible!
None of this is in the guide
to my divine destiny
in the Gospel
What are you?!
Just what are you?!
- You ask the same things
over and over.
If you're having
nightmares,
then welcome to the club.
- Then, then, then, then,
then, then, then...
you are truly Pride
in the flesh.
- Wrong!
My name's Subaru Natsuki!
And I am the knight of Emilia,
the silver-haired half-elf.
- [shrieking]
- I don't know anything
about this Pride stuff.
The only title I want
is Emilia's knight.
I don't need any others.
[Authority moaning]
- What a strange-looking place.
- Yes, it is.
It's a place
where my time once ended.
But this go-around,
it'll be the one
where your time ends instead,
the last place you'll ever see.
- If your goal
was to lead me out here,
what do you have
prepared for me?
What futile plan
is up your sleeve?
- It's a good one,
your natural enemy,
one you and I
happen to have in common.
- [gasps]
- Your natural enemy, huh?
Now, that's a fine thing
to call me.
[spirits warbling]
- I'm one of the Lugunica
Imperial Knights,
Julius Euclius.
For my kingdom,
I must now slay you.
- So you're a spirit arts user,
are you?
Well, h-how truly--
h-how truly--
Is this also part of your plot?
I have never known such
humiliation in my entire life.
- Oh, really?
Well, you should
make the most of it.
'Cause that's the bill for
all the trouble you've caused.
- [grunts]
- Let's do it, Julius.
- You sure about this?
- I won't back down.
I won't bend. I can't fail,
and I don't want
to lose anybody else.
- I am the man who brutally beat
and humiliated you.
Looking back on it,
I still believe my behavior
was backed
by meaning and reason,
but that is no more
than self-justification,
which has
nothing to do with you.
Are you able to trust me?
Will you put your faith in me?
- Listen. I still hate
your freakin' guts.
- Yes, I'm well aware of that.
- You broke my arms and legs.
That's a pretty traumatic thing,
you know?
Haven't you ever heard
the word "restraint"?
- Just so you're aware,
I did hold back
quite a bit that day.
- Seriously? That wasn't
everything you had?
Man, you really are
the biggest jerk I've ever met.
I truly hate you,
"Greatest of Knights,"
and I always will.
Even so...
I'll put my trust in you.
The shame I feel
that began that day,
attests to my knowledge that you
are an incredible knight.
- I see.
Then with all my soul,
I will live up to that trust!
[chorus vocalizing]
- Is this ridiculous farce
over yet?!
What do you expect
to accomplish
by adding a single
spirit arts user to your ranks?
I will defeat you all,
tear apart those who remain,
resume the Ordeal,
and you can't stop me!
My diligence knows not
of slothful resignation,
nor of demise!
[shrieking]
Sloth! Sloth!
Sloth! Sloth! Sloth!
- Now, Al Clarista!
- [chuckling]
[gasps]
No way.
You should
not be able to see it.
It should be invisible to you.
My Unseen Hand
can't be--can't be seen!
You can't see it!
Yet two people did
other than me.
- I'm the only one
who can see it, Betelgeuse.
- Huh?!
- Julius can only see
what I'm seeing.
Right now,
we're both sharing my vision,
although it's a much creepier
feeling than I thought it'd
be.
- I can use Nect to consciously
share some of your senses,
as well as to maintain them
for a while.
I must admit, when you
first proposed this plan to me,
I questioned your sanity.
- Well, it worked,
though, didn't it?
Gotta have guts sometimes
and be willing to try anything.
- [chuckles]
- Curse you!
Curse you! Curse you!
Curse you!
Curse you! Bah!
- [gasps]
Sharing a collective body
with you
is a pretty disgusting
experience.
Let's get this over with,
already!
- Yes, shall we?
- [chuckles]
- Using your eyes,
I shall slay him...
for my friend, Subaru Natsuki!
[overlapping chatter]
WILHELM: There's something
that's causing me
a bit of concern.
I would like to take
a small number of our forces
to eliminate it.
- [sighs]
What about me?
Could I not be of any help?
- No, Miss Emilia.
Please head to safety
in the carriage,
and hold on to these children's
hands tightly, all right?
- [sighs]
- The two of you
are truly master and servant.
I can see the same thing
in your eyes
that I see in his.
- Uh...
Thank you, Wilhelm.
You've done--[gasps]
[sighs]
- [Julius yelling]
- [chorus vocalizing]
- No! Impossible!
This cannot be!
You cannot use such means,
such evil tricks
to make light of me
and my undying devotion!
[wails]
- [winces]
[groans]
- [groans]
This is some crappy game
where, as soon
as you're caught, it's over.
We must be out of our minds to
entrust our lives to those
odds,
completely insane.
- My body's slowly
getting used to this.
Shall we speed up?
- Sounds good.
Don't worry about me!
Awesome.
- Impossible!
Impossible! Impossible!
Impossible!
How can it be?
Why is this happening?!
I thought I was loved, loved!
I am loved, loved by her,
by the Witch! By the Witch!
By the Witch! By the Witch!
By the Witch!
- It's time I put an end to you
once and for all! [grunts]
- [yelling]
Al Clauseria!
- [gasping]
I won't let you do that.
Ul Dona!
- Burn, fighting spirit!
Howl, magic ball!
I get serious,
I can pitch like a pro!
- What is this?
[sword stabs]
[gagging]
- Your mistake cost you.
You considered your enemy
weak and powerless.
My blade, all six elements,
will slice your very soul apart,
scattered to the end
of the rainbow.
- No, I refuse to let it end.
This faithful servant
has been nothing
but diligent in his duties.
The love of the Witch,
it bathes my entire body!
- [gasps] Julius, we need
to undo Nect right now!
- As you wish, then.
- [laughs] My brain...
it trembles!
SUBARU: Yeah, just tremble
while you wait inside me.
I'll let you meet her
just this one time, okay?
BETELGEUSE:
What's that? Meet whom?
Now what are you
talking about, boy?
SUBARU: The Witch
you've been waiting to see
face to face your entire life!
[inhales]
I can use Return by Death to...
- Hmm?
[gasps]
[squeals]
Ah, yes.
I've waited so long,
waited for your love,
merciful love,
affectionate love,
[gasps]
[gasping]
- No.
You're not the one.
- [squeals]
- [chorus vocalizes]
- [gasps]
I made it back. [groans]
- This cannot--
No, it--it cannot be.
- I was prepared to keep
doing that over and over again
until you finally left me,
but you gave up
after just one go at it?
How big of a coward
are you, freak?
- Take your last breath.
I'm ending you.
- [gurgles]
[groans]
But why?
Why? Tell me.
Tell me why.
After everything
I've done for you,
I can't believe you'd abandon
your faithful servant like
this!
Help me, Witch! Help me!
Give your servant
the love he deserves.
[Subaru sighs]
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti...
you were Sloth.
No doubt about it.
- Subaru, let's hurry back
to the village.
- Hmm?
- Felix contacted me.
It seems they have a problem.
[music playing]
- The magic stones of fire that
were in the merchants' inventory
are nowhere to be found.
OTTO: We unloaded
all of our cargo
so we could take the villagers
on board more easily.
Once we did, we noticed
that the stones were missing.
- And what does that mean?
- Most likely,
it means somebody
left them on board when they
loaded the villagers.
- They were last seen
in Ketty's carriage,
and there are
enough magic stones
packed away in there to easily
blow away a small village.
- [no audible dialogue]
And here's the worst of it.
Ketty's carriage is the one
taking Miss Emilia
and the children to the capital.
[no audible dialogue]
- Miss Emilia.
- [gasps]
- It's time to get moving now.
- [sighs]
- What's wrong?
- Are you all right?
- I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Now come on.
We need to get going.
- Damn it! Just when I think
we've got it all under control,
everything backfires!
- We verified that no spell
was used to set a trap,
but if something were physically
rigged in the carriage,
there's be no way of knowing
without seeing it.
- Hey, Felix,
would a ground dragon
be fast enough
to catch up with them?
- If they're already
out of the Mathers domain
and on the Lifaus Highway,
then I think
it'd be pretty difficult.
- That still wasn't enough?
Even after everything we did,
I still can't...
- Excuse me.
May I say something?
I'm actually in a bit of
a desperate position right now.
If you'd be willing
to accept a trade
and help me out, I promise
to catch up to the carriage--
If there's anything I can do
to make that happen, I'll do
it!
- I like a man who can make
quick decisions, Mr. Natsuki.
Thanks so much.
- I'll send Ia along with you.
That should help.
I wish I could
accompany you myself, but I...
- You can't, Julius.
With all those injuries,
what other help
could you possibly offer?
And your mana's
not even restored yet.
- You just get some rest, okay?
Once this things finally over,
we can all celebrate.
And I'll even make sure
to invite you, so don't die.
- Don't you die, either.
Best of luck to you!
- Careful out there.
OTTO: Instead of
taking this path,
it's faster if we go off-road
and cut through
the glade on the left.
It's the shortest way!
- Man, your soul of language
divine protection's amazing.
- Thanks. I actually had a
hard
time learning to control it.
I can hear the voices
of all creatures, big and small,
from ground dragons
to the tiniest of bugs.
- Then if we choose our path
based on all the
information
that they're giving you,
this shortcut will work,
and catching up to Emilia
and the kids should be
easy.
- What are you talking about?
None of this
will be easy at all.
- [screaming]
We're gonna die!
We're seriously
gonna die at this rate!
It's the end of the line!
- What's this rush
washing over me?!
I just feel so alive!
Honestly, even I had no
idea
I was capable of doing--
- [gasps]
- Hey, what's wrong?
- What are you sensing?
- Something isn't right.
The trees are getting so loud.
The birds and bugs
started making a lot of noise
and then vanished.
There's something terrible
coming this way.
- [gasps]
[music playing]
Move it. Faster, Otto.
Don't stop, no matter what!
- What are you doing?!
- I should have known
that wasn't the end of you.
Just how persistent
are you, damn it?!
- My body! My flesh body!
I must have it!
My head is trembling!
[pants] Give it to me!
[explosions]
- [gasps]
- [children wail]
- It's all right, everyone.
Just hang on tight.
I'm sure there's nothing
to be afraid of, okay?
Huh?
PUCK: It would seem that old man
just ran into
someone behind us.
They're fighting.
EMILIA: Do you know
how many there are?
- Not exactly,
but there's a lot.
Have no fear.
The old man's power is no joke.
- [yelling]
- PUCK: Looks like you and I
won't be needed this time.
Taking my physical form
without reason drains
mana,
and I don't want to end up
being a plaything for the kids.
- If your cuteness could help
everyone forget their fears,
it might be worth it
to take that chance, Puck.
- You sure say
some scary things, my daughter.
[children wail]
- Now don't worry.
Whatever happens,
I'll protect you.
With me around,
there's nothing to fear.
- W-We're okay! Seriously!
- You don't have to worry
about us. We'll be all right.
[children groan]
- We made a promise,
so this is nothing!
- What are you talking about?
- That no matter what happens,
we wouldn't let go of you!
- 'Cause if we're
not here beside you,
you'll do something crazy.
- And he'll be worried
if someone
isn't watching you
this whole trip!
- Who made such a fuss about me?
Why are they so concerned?
- Don't! We can't tell her!
- Subaru!
- He asked us for a favor, okay?
He said you get lonely,
so he was worried about you.
- Yeah! He said--Wait.
I don't think we were
supposed to tell her about that.
- Oh, no.
- [gasps]
- [trees creaking]
- Mr. Natsuki, what is it?
Is there something behind us?
- Just some big, black animal
with a bunch of legs
and a bad attitude.
It has a wild voice
and a scary face,
so you're better off
not looking.
- Everything you're saying
just makes me
want to take a look even more!
- Keep your curiosity in check,
and keep driving!
If it takes a bite out of me,
you're gonna be next!
- [wails]
- Hmph.
How many times do I
have to play the last level?
What about you
is slothful now?
Looks like you're working
pretty hard to me.
- Give me the Witch!
Give me Satella!
Give her to me!
- Give me love, love...
- Listen!
She doesn't love you
or me, you idiot!
What kind of rom-com
has someone trying to squash
their love's heart!
- Satella! Satella!
Satella! Satella!
- I'm the one
who stands before you.
As your opponent,
I won't let you get past me,
and I absolutely won't let you
get to the kid in front of me,
you insane, evil bastard!
- Oh, that's so touching.
You care about me that much,
Mr. Natsuki?
- Will you be quiet, already?!
I'm trying to make myself
look good back here!
[Authority moaning]
- [yells]
- Look, Mr. Natsuki!
We're leaving the forest!
[music playing]
- Love. Love me. Love me.
Love alone is everything.
Love alone!
- If you think I'm gonna
take you where Emilia is,
you've got another think coming!
[Subaru grunts]
- [growls]
[Authority moaning]
- One last card to play.
Thanks for your strength
and help, Julius.
How 'bout a little rental Goa?!
[groans]
Damn it! That hurts!
Man. [gasps]
- Give it to me!
Hand it over! Relinquish it!
- I told you,
if you try to get into my body,
you're only gonna get hurt!
The Witch doesn't
want to see you!
- The Witch! Satella! Satella!
I haven't forgotten
a single moment
of the things you did for me!
I'll treasure them forever!
Even if you've forgotten,
your humble servant
will always remember!
With all of my diligence,
- I'll part with my slothful...
- Bad call, man.
Sucks for you.
Who knows?
If you'd stayed a monster,
you might have beaten me!
- [gasps]
Satella.
[wind howling]
- [yells]
- [gags]
I will not--I won't let it end.
This hasn't ended.
[coughs] It hasn't.
[groans]
- No, you're wrong.
It's finally over.
As of now, you're finished!
- [gasps]
[growls]
Subaru Natsuki!
[wails]
- [sighs]
And this time,
stay asleep forever, Betelgeuse.
Don't ever come back.
- Hey, up ahead!
- [gasps]
Wilhelm!
- Subaru, son.
- Where's Emilia?!
- She's that way!
Go straight
toward the great tree!
This is the perfect chance
to repay my debt!
I pity anyone
who stands in the path
of a man
who's on his way to see a woman!
[chorus vocalizing]
- [gasps] R-Right there.
I see it, the carriage
with the refugees.
[no audible dialogue]
SUBARU: Back then,
I made a promise.
I swore, no matter what...
I would risk everything
to try and save you.
PUCK: So are you
thinking about Subaru?
EMILIA: Yeah.
But it's crazy.
I still can't believe it.
- I can. If he's
really leading the army,
a lot of things
would make sense,
like why Ram didn't argue
and why the villagers
agreed to evacuate
without putting up
any resistance.
- But still...
why?
After all the pain and
suffering he went through...
after I made him look so sad...
why would he...
- [carriage rattles]
- [gasps]
[children moan]
- Lia, something's
coming up behind us.
- [roars]
[all gasp]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- [stones pulse]
- There. Found them.
- I thought a reunion like this
seemed a little sudden for you.
So that's why you're here, huh?
[singer vocalizing]
- [grunts]
- Wait a minute!
You shouldn't...
Why, Subaru?
- 'Cause I love you, Emilia.
- [gasps] Eh?
[music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
- Damn it!
Get there in time!
[stones pulse]
[singing continues]
- An easy price to pay.
Thanks for saving me, Subaru.
- ♪ I stay alive ♪
[singing in Japanese]
- [gasps]
[singing continues]
SUBARU: Where am I?
I can't see a thing.
I can't hear a thing.
Is that Witch lady coming
to grab my heart again?
Who knows?
I don't feel too bad, though.
EMILIA: Subaru! Subaru!
- Oh, hey.
I can hear after all.
[song ends]
[rumbling]
- [gasping]
[roar echoes]
[gasps]
[footsteps pattering]
[panting]
- [groans]
- [sighs]
[gasps]
[cries]
Subaru!
[wind blowing]
[music playing]
- [groans]
- Subaru, you're finally awake.
Thank goodness. I'm so glad.
- I-I'm laying down.
And Mili's kneeling.
Hold on.
I need to get my bearings here.
Considering my perspective,
our distance from each other,
and the heavenly sensation
that's under my head,
could it be...
- You don't have to go
through all that, silly.
Your head's on my lap.
It's not too uncomfortable,
is it?
- There's no finer,
more divine pillow
I could possibly imagine.
- [chuckles]
- Hey, um...
would it be okay
if you told me
how things turned out?
- Well...
to be perfectly honest,
I'm the one who wants to ask
what's going on.
- Is Patrasche all right?
I want to become the wind
with that critter again.
- She was pretty badly burned,
but she's strong.
I think she'll be fine.
Felix is looking after her.
- Oh. Felix joined us, too?
Wow. [chuckles]
So have I been out
for a long time?
- Mm...
about an hour or two.
- Then I guess
everybody's together now.
- Julius, too. [chuckles]
Even him.
I was really surprised.
I never expected to see
you two getting along,
much less working together.
- It was
for the very best of reasons,
ones bluer than the mountains,
taller than the seas,
dear Mili.
[Mimi groans]
[veteran sighs]
- Finally.
I finally made it
all the way back.
Feels like I was having
a really long dream,
a terrible one.
Maybe not that bad.
- Then it was a good dream?
- More like a good reality.
- Hmm?
- Back then, you asked me
why I was doing all the things
I was doing,
why I desperately
tried to save you,
and why I always seemed
to put in so much effort.
You asked me why.
- [sighs]
- Your answer confused me.
You said that it
was because I saved you,
but I-I haven't done
anything like that at all.
I've never been able to.
It seems like you're the one
who's always saving me.
I could never
do anything for you.
And every time, you'd get hurt
and say that it was for my
sake.
- No, I was
pretty messed up back then.
[sighs]
I was only thinking
about myself.
I said it was all for you,
but I really just liked the idea
of doing it all for you.
I had it in my head that if
I just kept telling you that,
you'd accept it.
- Subaru
- I'm sorry.
I used you for my own
stupid self-satisfaction.
All the things you said
back then were true,
every word of it.
I was just so wrong.
But there's one thing
I wasn't wrong about.
I want to save you.
I want to help you.
I honestly mean that.
It's not a lie.
- [sighs]
I know that.
Tell me, why do you
always rescue me?
- I do it because I love you.
I want to stand beside you
and be your strength.
- [cries]
Listen. I'm a half-elf.
- Yes, I know that.
- I'm a silver-haired half-elf,
and people,
so many people hate me
for no other reason than
because I look like the Witch.
They despise me.
They absolutely detest me!
- I saw. I know.
Those guys are completely blind.
- I don't have much experience
with people,
so I don't have friends.
I'm naive and not worldly,
so I say strange things
sometimes.
And the reason I want to be
the ruler of this kingdom
is really, really selfish.
- No matter what anyone else
says about you,
no matter what you
happen to think of yourself,
I love you with all my heart.
I mean it! I'm crazy about you!
I want to be with you
all the time.
I want to hold your hand
You could sit there
and come up with a list
of ten things
you hate about yourself,
but I'd just reply
with 2,000 things
that I love about you.
That's the kind
of special treatment
I want to give you.
That's the depth
of the love in my heart.
- You know,
that's the first time
I've received special
treatment
that actually made me happy.
[cries]
[gasps]
I don't get it.
Why 2,000?
- Because a hundredfold
just isn't enough,
doesn't come close
to how I feel about you.
I'm happy...
just so very happy.
I never even dared to dream
that a day like this
would happen,
when someone
would tell me they loved me.
What should I do?
What do I say?
You've told me so many
of your thoughts and feelings.
I'm thankful,
but also a little overwhelmed.
I don't know what I'm supposed
to do at a time like this.
You don't have
to stress over it.
I'm not demanding
an answer right away.
The way I see it is this.
I'll get your answer one day,
and I'm confident
of what that answer will be.
- Really? I mean...
is it okay for someone like me
to be given such pure happiness
all the time?
To know such joy
in my heart that it--
it actually feels
beyond indulgent?
- Sure it is.
Go on and be indulgent.
As far as I'm concerned,
you can never have
too much happiness.
If there's so much,
it overflows,
you can share it, you know?
- [gasps]
- Don't worry.
Take your time, Emilia.
Take as much as you need.
Then, little by little,
you'll fall in love, too.
I'll always be there
at your side.
That way,
I'll be sure to catch you
when you fall
head over heels for me.
- [music playing]
- ♪ I wish I was there ♪
♪ Oh, please don't
let me die... ♪
- [crying]
- [singing in Japanese]
- Thank you, Subaru...
for everything.
Thank you for saving me!
♪ My time is spinning around ♪
♪ Your deep black eyes ♪
♪ I forgot what time it is ♪
♪ And our memories are gone? ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I wish you were here ♪
♪ Oh, never close your eyes ♪
♪ Searching for a true fate ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ "Restart" ♪
♪ So let us try again
from the very first time ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ For now, I'll see you off ♪
♪ And we'll die
waiting for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ And we'll start
waiting for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Oh, please don't let me die ♪
[wind blowing]
[rumbling]
[carriages rattling]
[Emilia chuckles]
[Subaru gasps]
Hey, Petra...
aren't you a little close?
- Yeah, maybe, but she
had you all to herself earlier,
and I don't think that's fair.
It's my turn.
- Listen, I think you've
got this all wrong, Petra.
Subaru and I were just--
Uh, we had important things
to talk about.
- [groans]
No matter what it takes,
I'm not gonna lose to you.
Understand me?
- [gasps]
- Take it easy, Mili.
She's only a kid.
Just forget about it.
When they say outrageous things,
you've gotta smile
and laugh it off, you know?
- I can't do that!
- [gasps]
- Even if they're
only words from a child,
I refuse to take
such a lackadaisical attitude.
- Who uses words
like "lackadaisical" anymore?
- [growls]
You can't stop teasing me,
can you?
- I'm not a kid,
so don't talk to me like one!
- [both groan]
- Okay, okay, you two.
Take it easy.
Look, I'm sorry, Petra,
and I need to thank you.
You made a promise
not to leave Mili alone,
and you stuck to your word
through thick and thin,
so I really appreciate it.
Once things calm down,
there are actually
a lot of people I need to thank.
I'm grateful
to Crusch and her gang.
Anastasia and her people
helped a lot, too.
I hate to admit it,
but the same goes
for Julius and his crew.
And, you know,
I'm even indebted to Otto.
- Sorry. Were you trying
to say something to me?
- Nah, nothing in particular.
I'm just super grateful
to you, too, buddy!
- [gasps] My goodness.
What brought that on?
You're making me blush.
- Also...
[chuckles]
- What's wrong, Subaru?
- [gasps]
Oh! [laughs] Just, uh--
So listen, Mili.
[sighs]
There's something
extremely important
that I need to tell you.
- Okay. What is it?
- This is gonna be
pretty hard for me to say,
but please hear me out.
And of course
it goes without saying
that I am completely prepared
to be knocked out by Ram
when I tell her!
But I wanted you
to hear it first.
- [grunts]
- This is--
This is actually about Rem.
She--She said that, uh...
- And you'll still
keep me by your side,
no matter where you go
from now on?
- S-So you see
what I'm getting at, right?
I mean, well, Rem said
some really nice things
to me, and, uh...
- Easy, Subaru. Just calm down.
Now, I'm not exactly sure
what you're trying to say to me,
but I can tell it means a lot
and you're trying your hardest
to say it, okay?
Just take it slow,
like a good boy.
- "Like a good boy," huh?
Not exactly encouraging.
But all right. Here goes.
[grunts]
Time for me to man up,
come right out, and say it!
You see...
the thing is,
Rem said that she loves me,
and she meant it in the same way
I told you that I love you!
All right, there! I said it!
[steeds' footsteps rumbling]
[gasping]
[carriages rattling]
- Subaru.
- Yes?
- I'm confused.
Who is Rem?
- [gasps]
[shudders]