- We didn't go through all
of this just to stop now!
Is there no other way
to save him?
- That's all, I suppose.
You can do as you like
with him now.
- I swear.
I'll save you.
- [groans]
Another unfamiliar ceiling.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[groans]
So they managed to save
my life but just barely,
and these are the scars.
[exhales]
Emilia.
I suppose now I owe her yet
another debt for rescuing me.
- I don't know about that.
- [grunts]
- 'Cause this time you
produced results equal
to the effort you invested.
So I seriously doubt Lia
will think of it
as some kind of debt.
- Hey, Puck.
- Hey, good morning, Subaru.
- You say that these are results
equal to my effort
but I don't really remember
much of anything
after I got nommed on
by those dogs in the forest.
- "Nommed on?"
That's a cute way to put it.
But it was actually more like,
munch, garble, scarf, chew,
chop, snap, crack, roar!
Well, at least
for the most part.
- With all those viscous
sound effects,
I should definitely
be dead right now.
I think I'm five or six
arms short for all that.
- Yeah, you were lucky
you didn't go alone,
that's for sure.
The blue-haired maid took
the rest of the damage.
- [groans]
- And she was in awful shape.
Though she heals fast thanks
to her demon transformation.
By the time she carried you back
to the village,
she had no visible injuries
at all.
- [groans]
Come on.
Don't scare me like that.
Anyway, so Rem went back
to the village, then?
Hey, wait!
The kids!
Do you know
if the curse was removed?
- No need to worry.
Betty and I took care of it
so everything's fine.
Way to go.
Your judgment was right
on the mark.
Applause, applause.
Clap, clap.
- [exhales]
Has Emilia been here all night?
- Yeah.
She totally drained
her resources.
She used everything right down
to her od to heal you.
You should let her sleep.
[Konomi Suzuki's "Redo"]
♪ ♪
- [singing in Japanese]
[birds chirping]
- Barusu, you're awake.
- Ram.
Listen, um, I mean,
about Rem, uh--
[stomach growls]
[groans]
- How pitifully shameful
you are,
pestering other people
for food so soon
after being that badly injured.
- [grunts]
- Maybe those dog bites
rubbed off on you.
- How the heck do dog bites
rub off on someone?
- Eat this.
- Hmm?
- [shouting]
- Delicious, isn't it?
- I thought I was gonna die!
But yes, it was good!
- It's freshly made.
Rather, it's freshly steamed,
I mean.
- Why do you look so proud
of yourself?
- Easy, easy.
You're welcome
to have another one,
so just be quiet and eat it.
And, well, as for last night,
you have my sincerest gratitude,
Barusu.
Very nice work.
- Nice work?
Always with
the condescending tone.
Was it something deserving
of your thanks?
Huh?
- When a domain's people
suffer loss,
its lord is held liable.
I hate to think what would have
happened if that pack of ulgarm
had further endangered
those children.
You were right
to do what you did.
- What's an ulgarm?
Is that what you guys call
those black mabeasts?
- Indeed,
but it's all right now.
I reconnected the broken barrier
so the village
is no longer in danger.
I kept an eye on it overnight
to ensure there
were no problems.
-Now no ulgarm should be able
to cross over
and enter the village.
So you can relax.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- Ah.
[grunts]
Beako.
Hey, I heard you played
a big part
in removing the curse
from those kids.
Thanks so much for that.
- No big deal.
The only reason Betty helped
at all was because
Bubby asked,
I suppose.
I have something more important
to discuss.
- Huh?
[birds chirping]
What's so important that you had
to drag me all the way out here
to talk about it, anyway?
- In just a little less
than half a day,
you'll almost certainly die,
I suppose.
- [grunting]
- You don't look anywhere near
as disturbed as I was expecting.
I thought you'd scream
and cry, I suppose.
- The curse still isn't lifted,
then, is it?
- When the pack of mabeasts
attacked you in the forest,
they planted even more of them
deep inside you.
- Gotcha.
Can I ask why this one
can't be removed?
One, or more than one?
- There's a simple enough
explanation, I suppose.
So many curses have been
stacked up inside you,
the removal would be
too complex.
- What do you mean?
- When there's only one curse
to contend with,
removing it is as simple
as untying a knot.
But after the bites
from that mabeast attack,
the curses on you are
a complex web of many threads
far too tangled to undo.
- I get the idea that it's high
on the difficulty scale,
but why only half a day?
- Because after that,
mabeasts activate their spells
to replenish mana.
- [gasps]
- The curse that they used
on you effectively
drains a target's mana,
I suppose.
Basically, they've turned you
into a heaping pile
of mabeast food.
- So they attack people
because they're hungry?
Wild animals for you.
So simple-minded.
I guess we should count
ourselves lucky
that those mangy mutts never
got hungry before now.
- It's so odd.
- Huh?
- You aren't scared,
I suppose?
I'm telling you exactly how
much time you have left
to live,
you know.
- Well, sure,
of course I'm scared.
But I seriously doubt you came
all the way out here just
to tell me I'm gonna die.
Honestly, I don't think even you
could be that mean.
- And what makes you
the expert on me
all of a sudden,
I suppose?
- Well, if nothing else,
I feel like I've known you
four times longer
than I actually have.
- You make no sense at all.
But it's a fact that the chance
for you to be saved
is much lower now.
- Give it to me straight.
Exactly how low are my odds
for surviving here?
- What you're dealing with is
being eaten because of a spell.
If the one that's doing
the eating were to die,
logic dictates the meal would
be canceled, I suppose.
- So that's it, huh?
I just have to take down
every last one
of the things that cursed me.
[grunts]
But every last one of them
is way too many.
- Correct.
That's the reason why Bubby
hasn't told that silly girl
about the curse.
- If Emilia knew,
she'd definitely try to do more
than she's capable of.
Which makes me really happy
but also feel really scared
at the same time.
Difficulty level here
is seriously demonic.
This is impossible.
I might as well give up.
- We didn't go through all
of this just to stop now.
Is there no other way
to save him?
- His head must be hurting,
I suppose.
Guess that's not
terribly surprising.
That's all, I suppose.
You can do as you like
with him now.
- I swear I'll save you.
- It can't be.
Where is Rem?
Beako.
Beatrice, tell me.
Where is Rem?
If you were in her position,
what would you do, I suppose?
- I'm not going to ignore
what you just said.
- [grunts]
Ram.
- Miss Beatrice.
Rem didn't go into
the forest alone, did she?
- [panting]
I have to.
I have to do this all on my own.
I have to save him.
No one else needs
to get hurt.
- But why?
Why in the world would Rem go
to such dangerous lengths
for me?
- [grunts]
- Hey!
Hold on!
- Let go of me, Barusu!
I'm not calm enough
to be kind right now.
You need to release me at once!
- If you want to save Rem,
and if you consider me
an ally at all,
stop for a second, okay?
Do you know where she is?
- No, but if I use
my clairvoyance, I will.
- Your what?
- It's a special power that
allows me to see what all
the bugs and animals on my
wavelength are seeing as well.
- So all those eyes act like
your security cameras?
Well, if we can use it
to get to Rem,
then fine.
Now let me ask you.
Are you the kind
of maid that fights?
- What does a question
like that even mean?
- It means I plan on going into
the forest with you.
- You're following me?
- That's right,
'cause when it comes
to fighting,
I'll totally get in your way.
- [gasps]
If you expect me to be able
to fight like Rem does
in her demon form,
I can't.
- Wait a second.
You're twins, right?
If Rem is a demon,
wouldn't that make you
a demon, too?
- [gasps]
In a way,
I suppose that's true,
but unlike Rem,
I'm hornless.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
I can only use a rather extreme
bit of wind magic.
[grunts]
[whooshing]
- Going to retrieve
the younger sister
from the dangers of the forest
would mean giving up
on your own life.
You do understand that fact,
I suppose.
- [chuckles]
Well, that's not quite right.
Let me correct you.
It's dumb to just start giving
up 'cause you're used to dying.
You get one life so you
should make the best of it.
That's something I realized
after you guys went through
so much to save mine.
So if you don't mind,
I'm gonna struggle pathetically.
Let's go out there
and make a comeback!
I've recovered from the terrible
state I was in earlier.
I guess you could say
I'm a greedy guy
because I wanna see
the continuation of this story
and with me in it.
Now I think it's time
to get moving
to our last big showdown!
You hear me, fate?
Bring it on!
[rain pattering]
- [grunts]
- I must say you gave
a pretty heroic speech
back there.
But when I see you lagging
behind so close
to becoming nothing but baggage,
it's difficult to hide
my disappointment.
- Give me a break.
I'm still recovering,
so my energy's spent
and I'm low on blood.
Oh, I didn't get the chance
to hear Mili say,
"I'll see you soon,"
in her sweet little voice.
- Until you say,
"I'm home,"
last night's "see you soon"
is still in effect.
- Oh, really?
Is that how it works?
- Besides, didn't you get
something from someone
other than Miss Emilia?
- [grunts]
Sure did.
Something pretty beautiful,
in fact.
- I want you
to take this.
It's the sharpest sword
in the village.
- Thanks, I appreciate it.
- We're counting on you.
- Subaru!
- [grunts]
[all laughing]
all: Subaru!
- Hey, guys.
So you're all awake, huh?
- Where are you headed?
- Back into the forest?
- Don't do it.
It's dangerous, Subaru.
- I'll be fine.
Don't worry about a thing.
I'm not gonna go anywhere.
- So what's the sword for?
- You mean this?
- Let's call it a thank you gift
from all of us.
- I wanna thank you, too!
- Hey, easy!
[all laughing]
[grunts]
Candy,
a pretty stone.
I wonder what else
is in here.
Ah, it's a big freakin' bug!
Damn brats sneaking that gross
thing in while I was distracted.
I'll give them
a talking-to later.
- It's only proof
of their admiration,
though I wonder what they see
in a man like you.
- In the pure eyes of a child,
my true manly nature shines like
a bright star in the night sky.
And as I recall,
I'm not the only one
they like, either.
You could tell, right?
- Yes, I could.
[all laughing]
- Hey, why did you put dirt
in there?
- [grunting]
- Ram-Ram!
We wanna thank Rem-Ram properly,
too,
so bring her over later, okay?
Promise, Ram-Ram!
- [gasps]
[grunts]
Barusu, I'm gong to use
my clairvoyance.
Give me a moment, all right?
Barusu, something nearby
is watching us both right now.
- What?
- Up there.
- Up where?
[shouts]
[grunts]
- Get ready.
More are coming.
[both grunting]
[snarling]
- [screaming]
Hey, wait up!
Don't just walk off!
[grunts]
- Anyway,
why does it seem
like every individual
loses their head
when they see you?
To be perfectly honest,
I don't understand it at all.
Is it because you seem
like such a weakling?
- After all that hesitation,
that's your conclusion?
Rude.
- Is it because you seem
like a wimp, then?
- You may have reworded things
a bit,
but that doesn't change the root
of what you're saying,
Ram-Ram.
Hey, would it be okay
if I asked what that
hornless thing you
mentioned before means?
- It's nothing.
As the term implies,
it's another name for a foolish
demon without a horn.
Long ago, after getting into
a little trouble,
I lost the only one I had.
Since that point in time,
I've relied on Rem
for everything.
- I suppose I shouldn't have
asked about it then, huh?
- Why's that?
- Well, I'm not gonna pretend
like I know anything about
your people
or how important horns are
to the race you call demons,
but I assume it's a pretty
serious problem.
So I just figured after asking
about it that it might
have been a little insensitive
of me.
- Back then was one matter.
But now things have calmed down.
There are things I've gained
and lives I've saved
by losing my horn.
I'm sure Rem doesn't feel
the same way I do about it,
though.
- Huh?
- Originally, members
of the demon race had two horns
but when twins are born,
the pairs split with each child
having only one.
- [snarls]
- So twins are detested,
and it's customary to dispose
of them immediately after birth.
But Rem and I were allowed
to live.
A demon's horns awaken
its demon instincts
and allow it to devour mana,
significantly heightening
its ferocity
and combat ability,
but if one is reckless,
the recoil will leave
them battered.
- [shouting]
[dogs barking]
- I don't wanna see Rem
like that.
- Are you feeling worried
because you care for her?
- Well, yes, of course.
It's true that she's
much stronger than I am
but that doesn't mean I'm not
concerned for her safety.
- [grunts]
- No matter what we're told
to do,
she always does it far better.
But in the end,
I'm still her older sister.
And I'm not ever wavering
from that position.
- [grunts]
Is that so?
Okay, I think I understand.
And I've got an idea now.
So don't worry.
We'll bring Rem back safe.
- [grunts[
- If my idea's right,
they're sure to come.
They'll be drawn here
by my attempt to tell her
about Return by Death.
Listen, Ram,
the thing is,
I can Return by--
[birds squawking]
- What's that?
- [gasping]
I made a wager that seems
to have paid off,
but it brought a bit
of pain with it, too.
- What did you do, Barusu?
The wind is erratic
and I smell beasts approaching.
A large number of them.
And on top of that,
we haven't found Rem yet.
- Well, don't worry about that.
I feel like our paths will cross
with hers pretty soon.
- What makes you so sure?
- Because I've been covered
in the Witch's scent.
- [gasps]
- Rem's goal is to hunt down
all the mabeasts, right?
They'll all be drawn
to the sudden increase
in the Witch's scent
and make their way straight
for me.
Then Rem will have no choice
but to follow those hell hounds
toward us.
It's a plan I call Operation:
Subaru Natsuki is the Bait.
[dogs snarling]
Okay, I'm gonna have to rely
on you to do most
of the fighting so feel free
to go for it.
- When this is over,
take an objective look
at what you just said
until you wish you were dead!
- [gasps]
- [grunting]
- This is what I get
for believing you
when you said you could fight!
- Well, I was fighting,
wasn't I?
The problem was my strength
didn't hold out as long
as I thought it would.
- Damn it!
Crap!
[shouts]
[screaming]
Damn it all!
Oh, that was close!
We were almost dead meat.
- If we fall from this height,
we'll both be in trouble.
Barusu, can you climb up?
- I'd like to make it up
by sheer will power,
but the mabeasts waiting
up there are kind of a problem.
Ah, the sharpest sword!
- El Fula!
- [shouts]
[grunting]
Man, that was close.
Seriously, Ram had timing
like Buddha.
Hold on.
Hey, Ram.
Hey!
You can't be serious.
Damn it all!
[dogs snarling]
[gasping]
[snarling continues]
Holy shit, the timing
of all this couldn't possibly
be any worse.
[groans]
[grunts]
Rem!
- [chuckles]
- Thank goodness you're alive!
We're finally saved/
[shouts]
[tense music]
You're kidding me!
She can turn into a demon,
but she can't control it?
- [snarls]
- Hey, Rem!
My name is Subaru Natsuki,
a useless trainee
in various odd jobs
though I always try my best!
The Roswaal Mansion's most
promising servant!
I've caused trouble
for you and Ram
but we've been friends at times
and we've fought at times.
[grunts]
Trying to beat me to death while
I'm still talking to you
is bad manners!
- [grunts]
- [whimpers]
[snarling]
[blows landing]
- [grunts]
Now's my chance.
[snarls]
- [gasps]
[screaming]
[grunts]
- Damn, it's no use.
I can't ignore her!
Take the plunge, Subaru.
Men are about guts, remember?
Time to prove it!
So...
[inhales]
Quit making that face
and try to smile, Rem!
I can Return by--
- [shouting]
- [grunts]
- [panting]
- Her horn.
- You're awake?
- I thought this would be
the perfect time
for me to wake up.
- You've got good intuition,
Ram.
What about her horn?
- That's responsible
for making Rem a demon.
One good solid hit should bring
her back to normal.
- [grunting]
- You sure?
- I am.
I think.
I hope.
- That's kinda vague.
- [grunts]
- A hit to that one little spot?
Doesn't that seem impossible?
- Muster up all your courage
and do something.
- Believe it or not,
I actually do have an idea
for something that we could try
to pull off,
but I'm afraid
you're gonna get mad.
- Well, if you think that it'll
bring my sister back
to her senses,
then I won't.
- Really?
- Yes, absolutely.
- Do you swear to Ros?
- That's the most reckless name
you could have chosen.
But yes,
I swear to Lord Roswaal.
- [laughs]
All right, then!
Heave, ho!
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
I freaked out!
I didn't have the guts
to take that last step!
[shouts]
If I let this chance go by,
there won't be any others!
Smile for me, Rem!
Today I'm more demonically
inspired than a real demon!
[distant wolves howling]
- To us of the demon clan,
twins are taboo.
- Please, wait, chief.
I beg of you!
- Enough!
To protect our pride as a race,
and to ensure
its continued purity,
we must dispose of them.
Such is the demon clan's custom.
It is our law.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [crying]
[booming]
♪ ♪
[all gasping]
[booming]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
One of the children is--
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[all gasping]
She is a true prodigy.
- Such power with only one horn.
Imagine what she could do
if she'd been born with two.
- That was very good, Ram.
- Rem, you'll have to follow
your sister's example
and work hard.
- Oh, don't you worry.
One day soon Rem will show us
that she has incredible power.
- I've no doubt.
She's Ram's sister so I'm sure
it'll come with time.
- 'Course it will.
- [whimpers]
[gasps]
- Don't worry.
- [gasps]
Sissy, I--
- Just be yourself, Rem.
There's no reason for you
to worry about
what other people see.
♪ ♪
- I can never match my sister
in demon power.
Then...
Hey, Mom?
- Ah?
Yes, Rem, dear?
What is it?
- I've decided that I'm
gonna make dinner tomorrow.
- So what are you thinking
about making?
- Maybe a stir fry
with barbaro rabbit meat
and nuts from the trees
in the forest
and some steamed tatoes.
- That sounds good.
I'll help you.
- Mm-mmm.
I'll be okay by myself.
Just watch.
[exhales sharply]
Now I just need
a barbaro rabbit.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[distant thunder claps]
[rain pattering]
[breathing heavily]
[booming]
[screams]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[screams]
[gasps]
Sissy!
- [panting]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
- I was worried so I'm really
glad you're both all right.
- She said both.
- Listen, don't go into
the forest alone again,
okay, Ram?
- You don't wanna worry
your sister now, do you?
- No.
You're right.
I won't.
- Wait, let's not forget
about this.
The steamed tatoes Rem went
through so much trouble to make
turned out really good.
Just taste them.
And they have just the right
amount of salt, too.
- Yeah, you're right.
They are good.
- [laughs]
I had no idea Rem
could make something
so delicious.
[grunting]
[whimpers]
- Okay, that's enough, Rem.
- [gasps]
- In the end I'm really just
glad both of you are all right.
- Yes, we're so glad
you're safe.
- [whimpers]
- No, it would have been much
better if it had only been Ram.
- That's right.
You said it.
- Good point.
If only that useless
Rem had died.
- Leaving Ram as our
only surviving daughter.
That would have been best.
- [crying]
[rain pattering]
[crying]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[groans]
- You were having a scary dream,
weren't you?
You were moaning.
- Sissy.
- It's okay now 'cause
I'm right here with you.
You'll never have to worry
about anything with me around,
all right?
- Right.
Thank you, Sissy.
I love you.
My sister really is amazing.
I can't match her in anything.
In that case, I don't have
to do anything anymore.
I can just be myself
and walk behind her.
[groans]
[grunts]
Sissy?
[distant booming]
[gasping]
[groans]
[fire roaring]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[crying]
[blows landing]
[gasps]
[slicing]
Careful, Sissy!
- [grunts]
Oh, Rem.
I'm so glad you're safe.
- [whimpers]
[blow lands]
- [gasps]
[exhales]
It finally broke off.
Because of me...
My sister's horn was broken.
And she lost her power.
From now on,
I have to learn to do all
the things that Sissy--
that Sister could do.
This is what Sister
would have done.
Sister was even more amazing.
Sister could do even more.
I'm only imitating
what Sister could do.
If I can't even do that
satisfactorily,
then I'm worthless.
- You're doing an excellent job.
- I heard those words back home
so many times.
- Easy.
Don't overdo it.
- Even if I overdo everything,
it will never be enough.
- I don't understand.
Why do you try so hard?
- Why else?
Because nothing I do
will ever measure up.
Why should I go on living?
All of this is my atonement
for what I felt
on that fiery night.-
What else can I do
to make amends?
I'll risk my life to walk
the very same path
that Sister would have walked.
The path I took from her.
Because I'm inferior to her
in every way.
I'm nothing more than
a mediocre replacement.
And that's all I'll ever be.
[cracks]
- [grunting]
- Barusu, head to the right
of that broken tree ahead.
You're too slow.
- Don't ask any more of me.
You got that?
I'm running just as fast
as I can here.
- W--what's going on?
Where are we?
- Rem, you're finally awake!
- Oh, thank goodness.
You really are a handful.
You know that?
[snarls]
[grunts]
Fula!
[dog whines]
[both panting]
- Why?
- Why what?
- Why didn't you just mind
your own business
and leave me alone?
You and Sister showing up
makes it all pointless.
I have to do it by myself,
understand?
Nobody else needs
to get hurt anymore.
- It's too late for that now.
Ram and I are already torn
to shreds,
maybe even more than you are.
My right shoulder's dislocated.
- It's--it's my fault.
So I have to take
responsibility.
If I don't, I can't do anything
for Sister.
For you, either.
- [grunts]
- I'm terrible,
and I haven't changed at all.
I committed the same sin today
that I did when
I was a little girl.
Because I hesitated to extend
my hand to you...
The Witch's scent?
You nearly died.
- Let me get this straight.
Are you trying to tell me that
you decided to do this alone
to make amends for that?
Rem...
- Yes, what?
- Super slap!
For starters,
are you dumb?
No, you are dumb!
- Barusu,
the cut that's on your forehead
has reopened
and is bleeding again.
- Yeah, I know.
I feel it.
I'm dumb, too, okay?
Thanks for the reminder,
but your sister is even dumber!
Listen to me for a second.
Where I come from there's an old
saying that goes,
"Three heads are better
than one."
Or, wait.
Is it two heads?
Whatever, that doesn't matter
right now.
The point is, three heads
thinking together
are way harder to break
than one arrow by itself.
So don't think
about stuff alone.
Just learn to trust and rely
on those around you.
- Subaru, I--
[gasps]
[[rustling]
- Damn it.
Ram, which way should we run
to get outside the barrier?
- We'd have to run left
at full speed.
What's your plan?
- Hmm.
I could shove Rem toward you,
take a dramatic turn,
and briefly stare at you two,
then run tragically
to the right.
- So you wanna draw
the ulgarm's attention
while I take Rem
and run to safety.
- Could you not reduce
my heroic moment to such
a simple plan?
- No, there's no way
you can survive on your own.
I'm begging of you.
Please don't.
You mustn't!
- Don't go worrying about me.
I have a brilliant idea
for rounding up
all the mabeasts
you don't know about.
- Subaru.
Why would you do all this?
- Well, the thing is...
You were my partner on the very
first date I ever went on.
I could never be so heartless
that I'd abandon you.
- [gasping]
- Right, I guess
I'd better go ahead
and get this thing going, then.
Take care of Rem, okay?
I'm counting on you!
- I'll be praying
for our safe reunion, Barasu.
- [grunts]
- He's risking his life
to buy us some time.
So let's make the most of it.
- [breathing heavily]
[snarling]
[panting]
[Konomi Suzuki's "Redo"]
I'd love to finish you off
right about now,
you little mutt.
[snarling]
♪ ♪
- [singing in Japanese]
- [grunts]
Yeah.
I've got an ace up my sleeve,
too.
It's you and me, pal.
Hope you're ready.
[grunts]
- Sister, Subaru's surrounded!
He's not going to--
- Don't look back, Rem,
or Barusu's determination
will be for nothing.
- [gasps]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
Sissy, please!
- [gasps]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
Subaru!
- [chuckles]
[snarls]
Shamac!
♪ ♪
[shouting]
I could do without the bugs,
but I appreciate
the bacca fruit.
Thank you for that.
[spits]
You little brat.
[snarls]
Crap!
[groaning]
Think it's about time
for you to die!
[roaring]
What's the matter, mutt?
Bring it on,
big boss Garm!
[snarls]
- Ulgoa!
Oh, my!
You look an absolute fright,
don't you, Subaru?
- [groans]
Better late than never, I guess.
Right, Ros?
- [chuckles]
- [shudders]
Gotta say, though,
I'm surprised you knew
where to find me.
- Miss Emilia drove it into me
quite thoroughly
in the village.
- [gasps]
- "Even if it's rash
or reckless,
"he'll use magic
if he's cornered,
so don't lose sight of him
from above," she said.
And there you go.
- Lord Roswaal!
[both grunting]
- [breathing heavily]
I'm certain we caused a lot
of trouble for you.
My apologies.
- Quite the contrary.
Truthfully, you both
accomplished fine work
in my absence.
I'm grateful.
And I will certainly
show that gratitude
for what you've done for me.
You have my word.
- Subaru!
- [grunts]
Rem, that hurts!
Stop it!
I kinda hurt all over right now.
- You're alive!
You stayed alive!
Subaru, I'm so happy
you're safe!
- This again, huh?
Suppose I should be used to it.
[groans]
[birds chirping]
- Hey, are you awake?
[soft guitar music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
Was I the one who did this?
I grabbed you and never let go?
- Uh, well, not exactly.
It, uh--
it was me,
to be honest.
I was watching you and it looked
like you were in pain
while you slept so I...
- You held my hand?
- I don't know what to do
at times like these.
It's always so confusing
and overwhelming.
So I did what would have
made me the happiest
if I were in your place.
- I'd like to hear the rest
of that.
I mean, I'd like to find out
how everything ended.
Like, were my curses removed?
- They were.
Lord Roswaal was meticulous
and took care of all
the mabeasts in the forest.
So there's no chance the curses
placed on you
will ever activate.
- Oh.
- I'm so sorry, Subaru.
- Hey, come on.
Lift your head up, Rem.
There's nothing wrong with me.
You know, you always look
so calm and collected.
But you're not either
of those things at all, are you?
- I'm aware of my shortcomings.
At the heart of it all,
I'm a powerless and incompetent
demon clan drop-out.
So no matter what I do,
I can never match my sister.
I'm only her replacement.
One far inferior to her,
at that.
Good for nothing.
I don't get it.
Why was I the only one
between us that kept her horn?
Why couldn't it have been her?
Why couldn't Sister be the one
to keep hers?
Why was she born
with only one horn?
I've caused her nothing
but trouble
since the day of our birth.
It's my fault.
Why did we have to come into
this world as twins?
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
Goodness, I'm sorry.
That was a strange thing
for me to say.
Please forgive it.
- [grunts]
You know, Rem,
you keep putting Ram
on a pedestal
while undermining yourself
at the same time.
Putting yourself down.
But I don't think her situation
would be any better
if she were in your position.
Ram is weaker than you.
She can't cook.
She slacks off on the job.
She says mean things.
- Y--you're wrong!
If she had her horn,
you wouldn't say things
like that.
- But Ram doesn't have her horn,
so I don't know that Ram.
I've never seen her
any other way.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm pretty sure you're
the only one who cares whether
she has one or not.
- [gasps]
- And what Ram doesn't have,
you do.
You should just acknowledge
and accept that.
You're kind,
hardworking,
and you always do your best
no matter what.
Your chest is even bigger
than hers, too.
- [grunts]
- But seriously,
if you hadn't been around,
those dogs would have
chewed me to death.
I was saved because
you were there.
As you can see,
I'm alive right now.
Not only because
of everything Ram did...
But because of you.
- My true sister could have done
so much more back there.
- You may be right,
but the one who was there for me
was you.
- [gasps]
- I'm glad you were there.
Thanks for saving me.
- Didn't you hear?
I told you that I'm only
my sister's replacement.
Nothing more.
- Don't define yourself
that way, all right?
It's too sad.
'Course, I haven't actually
heard the details
about how she lost her horn
in the first place,
and I won't ask,
so I'll never know.
Since I don't, that means
I get to talk
as if I know all about it.
Listen carefully.
All you have to do is be
the horn Ram doesn't have.
If you do that,
you two can be a demon together.
- [whimpers]
- Also, you call yourself
a replacement,
but no one could
ever take your place.
- But I--
- Where I come from,
there's an old saying.
"Demons laugh when you talk
about next year."
And you're a demon.
So just laugh, Rem.
Wipe off that sad face
and laugh.
Laugh while we talk
about the future.
Let's talk about things
while we look forward
to making up for all the time
you've wasted by looking back.
We can start by talking
about tomorrow.
- Wait, tomorrow?
- Yep, absolutely.
You can say anything.
Like, uh, whether you'll make
a Japanese,
western, or local style
breakfast tomorrow.
Or whether you'll put on your
right or left shoe first.
It can be something
silly like that.
No matter how it might sound,
you can talk about tomorrow
because you have a tomorrow.
How about it?
- Listen.
I've been very weak.
So I'm certain that I'll end up
depending and leaning on you.
- What's wrong with that?
- I may be weak, stupid,
and scary-looking,
and as I'm sure you've noticed,
I'm pretty dense.
But I never let that stop me.
I still live my life expecting
others to take care of things
for me when I can't handle it.
We can just lean on each other
as we move forward.
- [gasps]
- Let's laugh and talk
about tomorrow
with our arms around each
other's shoulders.
After all, I've dreamed
of laughing and talking
about next year with a demon
since I can remember.
- [gasps]
You are demonically inspired.
♪ ♪
- You know it.
- [crying]
- By the way, Ram,
did you happen to find the one
who was controlling
the mabeasts?
- Yes.
But the trail
has already vanished.
One of the children Barusu
and Rem brought back
from the forest mysteriously
disappeared from the village
the next day.
- Was this connected
to the battle
for the throne as well?
The Bowel Hunter,
mabeast masters,
we've certainly gotten involved
with some bizarre characters,
haven't we?
- No matter how many strange
characters you face,
you aren't the sort of man
who would lose heart
and turn tail, are you?
- My goodness.
You've grown so very audacious.
Come here.
Now then.
Shall we begin?
After all, I was unable
to attend for you
for a whole night.
- Yes, I realize that.
I'm sorry.
Please do.
- You've used quite
a lot of mana.
May the stars protect you.
- [sighs]
- I will be busy again
for a time.
I know it will be difficult
for you.
But I'll be counting
on you and Rem.
- As you wish.
Since that fiery night,
my body has belonged to you,
Lord Roswaal.
- This battle for the throne,
I must win no matter what
it takes to do so.
For the sake
of my ultimate goal.
- [gasps]
- For the coming day
when I kill the dragon.
- I've noticed something.
You're constantly getting hurt,
aren't you, Subaru?
You came to this mansion because
you were injured
in the first place.
And it's only been
four days since then.
- Hey, give me a break.
It's not like I get hurt
because I want to.
The world's a pretty
harsh place.
But I think it's a little
harsher on me.
With that in mind,
you're welcome
to spoil me rotten
since no one else will, Mili.
What do you say?
- Don't joke around.
Puck kept trying to stop me
from leaving the cottage
and going after you guys
to help, too.
Who know what would
have happened
if Roswaal hadn't made it back?
You understand now?
- [grunts]
- Still, I suppose
you saved me again.
- Huh?
- I brought you to the mansion
as thanks for rescuing me
and you've gone
and repeated that favor
without a second thought.
So I just wanted
to say thank you.
- [gasps]
Hey, it's fine, really.
I only did it 'cause
I wanted to.
There's no thanks needed.
- I thought you might say that.
But I don't feel any better
about you
putting yourself in danger.
I should do something
to show my gratitude.
- I see.
Well, I'll take you up on that.
By having you go on a date
with me, Mili!
- And what is a date?
- We'll go out together,
see the same things,
eat the same things,
do the same things,
and share the same memories.
We'll spend our time just
laughing and having fun.
- And that's really
all you want?
- That's exactly what I want.
I want to show you off to those
bratty village kids
and there's this awesome flower
field to walk through, too.
Even if all we do is stroll
around and look at stuff.
It'll be a special occasion
for me.
- [sighs]
All right, then.
I'll go on a date with you.
It sounds like fun.
- [shudders]
Yes!
That's why you're my EMF!
Oh, that's just a cool acronym.
EMF stands for Emilia Major
Faerie!
- [giggles]
- [chuckles]
[MYTH&ROID's "STYX HELIX"]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch ♪
♪ ♪
♪ No don't give up on life
This endless dead end ♪
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I wish I was there ♪
♪ Oh please don't let me die ♪
♪ Waiting for your touch ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Restart ♪
♪ No don't give up on life ♪
♪ This endless dead end ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ For now I'll see you off ♪
♪ And we'll die waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ And we'll start waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]