[ice crackling]
- Now die.
[Subaru gasps]
- Oh, my brain, it trembles.
SUBARU: Puck!
- Be quiet, Subaru.
I don't care what you have to--
- [creaking]
- [Puck groans]
- [gasps]
[warbling]
- My, what complacency
and negligence. That is sloth.
Should have seized the moment
and killed me
when you had the chance,
but it's too late!
Even with the element of
surprise and your immense power,
you failed to do
what you needed to do!
PUCK: Foolishness.
If you truly want to kill me...
then grow a thousand shadows,
half of what Satella could.
- [chanting]
- ♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Grew up in the loneliness ♪
[wind howling]
- Puck, is that...
really you?
- Can't you tell?
Maybe it's cruel of me to ask.
[chorus vocalizing]
- Unbelievable!
[gags] This is unbelievable.
It cannot be. [gags]
It simply cannot be.
[gags] My spirit, my faith,
everything I've devoted
my love to...
[gags] at the hands
of a mere spirit?!
- A human who's only
lived a few decades
shouldn't talk to a spirit
about time.
- Time has
absolutely nothing to do
with the depth of one's faith.
I wish you wouldn't compare me
to a fool like you,
a being that lived for eternity,
but wastes most of it
in idleness,
That's detestable audacity.
[gasps] My brain...
it's trembling-ing-ing-ing...
PUCK: Death isn't
even a punishment.
This is why I hate
all of your kind.
- The Ordeal has
finally been completed.
Even if my body dies,
my wishes will be called
to the exalted Witch's side,
and I shall receive her love!
Oh, how I look forward
to our awaited reunion!
[laughing]
- He quit while he was ahead.
Now, then...
shall we have a little talk?
Subaru, you have
committed three sins.
First, you broke
your promise to Lia.
You don't seem to understand
how important one is
to a spirit arts user,
nor do you seem
to care to learn.
- [shuddering]
- Second,
you ignored her explicit wishes
and came back here.
And third...
you let Lia die.
In accordance with my contract,
I will now destroy the world.
- [straining] But why?
- Lia is...
Emilia is my entire reason
for existing.
There is no point in living
in a world without her.
The fog is coming closer.
Looks like a troublesome one
has been drawn here.
[shatters]
Gluttony.
I suppose they call it
the White Whale now.
You called it here,
let Lia die,
and now it's your turn.
- [crazed laughter]
PUCK: You're so useless.
- [laughter continues]
SUBARU: I've heard
this laughter before,
the voice of a man
I hated to death.
No, it's me.
I'm laughing at myself.
I let Rem die,
killed Emilia,
and now
I'm going to die in vain.
I-I really am so--
PUCK: You're slothful, Subaru.
[chorus vocalizing]
[market chatter]
[bell tolling]
REM: Subaru.
Hey, what's the matter?
- It's you.
- Yes, it's me, your Rem.
Goodness. I'm sorry.
I didn't notice.
This city crowd
is making you tired, isn't it?
- What did you say?
Oh, yeah.
I feel tired. That's it.
I'm out of energy and worn down.
So tired.
[panting echoing]
- Subaru!
[panting]
- Wow, sorry about that.
I was feeling kind of stressed,
so I skipped out on explaining.
My apologies.
Didn't mean to freak you out.
- Really, you mustn't do that.
I know you're giving
a great deal of thought
to our situation when you do
these sorts of things.
Although, I don't hate it
when you're so forceful.
- Sorry I worried you like that.
I'm doing fine now.
Guess you've only
seen me being pathetic
and getting depressed
about everything all the time.
But I finally get it.
- What do you mean by that?
Get what?
- I've bothered a lot of people
with all my contemplating
and agonizing,
but I finally figured out
how to take care of everything.
Honestly, when I
really think about it,
it's what I was told to do
from the very beginning,
but I just wouldn't listen.
I just don't know
when to give up, you know?
- But I think
that's one of the things
I find so wonderful about you.
- [chuckles]
Things I've realized and
been forced to realize,
all kinds of experiences
and choices
brought me to the place
where I am now,
but I've actually had the answer
for a really long time.
[wind blowing]
I've made a decision, Rem.
- Which is?
Eh?
- Run away with me
as far as we can go.
[carriages rattling]
- Huh?
- I'm gonna leave the capital
and head far west
or maybe north.
- Haven't decided yet.
- Wait a second.
- Yeah, I heard it's hard
to get into the south kingdom,
so one of those two.
I don't like cold weather,
so I'd personally recommend
heading westward.
- Hold on. What are you--
- Thing is,
this could turn out to be
a really long journey,
and I know this is
a last-minute decision,
so it won't be easy to pull off.
- Subaru, wait.
- Huh?
- The way you're talking,
it sounds like
you're serious about this,
as if you really want to try
and go to another country
that isn't Lugunica. Oh!
Knowing you, it must be
because you've had
another great idea about
what our next move should be,
something to help Miss Emilia
and Lord Roswaal.
That's it, right?
- That's not what this is, Rem.
- Huh?
- There's nothing
I can do in the capital,
and I'd be every bit
as powerless
if I headed back to the mansion.
That's what I figured out.
So again, run away with me.
Please, Rem.
Staying here is not an option.
That's what everyone's been
telling me this whole time.
I didn't want to believe
that it was true,
so I denied it
with all my might.
But yeah, they were right.
No one ever needed me around
for anything.
- No, that's not--
- It's a cold, hard fact!
It's been plainly
spelled out for me
over and over again.
That's why I've decided
to just disappear.
It's for the best. Anything I do
will just lead to a dead body
or maybe more,
depending on what happens.
I've had enough of all this.
Let's run, Rem.
You and I can't stay here.
[gasps] We shouldn't
be in this country!
- But this is all so sudden.
I can't think straight.
- I'm sorry it's coming
from out of nowhere.
I really am,
but we don't have time.
I know it's not fair to ask...
but you must make a choice.
- What do you mean?
- Choose me,
or choose someone else,
but you have to choose.
Let's get a dragon-drawn
carriage and head west.
We'll leave Lugunica
and go far west to...
Kararagi, was it?
We'll buy a little house
and live there together.
Even if bad things happen,
I can keep going
if you're there.
Just having someone waiting
at home for me with a smile.
No matter how tired I am,
if I know you're waiting for me,
I can make it through anything.
[gasps]
So please, choose me.
'Cause if you do,
I'll give you all that I have
for the rest of my life.
I'm begging you.
Let's run away from here.
Live out your life with me!
- [chuckles]
Subaru.
- [gasps]
- Look, I--
I'm sorry,
but I can't run away with you.
We have a plan.
I mean, we're supposed
to sit around
and laugh together as we
talk about the future, remember?
- [sighs] I remember.
And maybe
we can't laugh now, but,
you know, once we start,
once we actually get moving,
then I bet we can
both find a way--
- I've thought about it,
too, you know?
We would arrive in Kararagi
and rent a place to stay.
As long as we had a home
and some work,
we could manage
to get by somehow.
Fortunately,
thanks to the graciousness
of Lord Roswaal, I've received
a formal education,
so I think
it would be easy for me
to find some kind of work,
even in Kararagi.
You, on the other hand,
might have to do manual labor
or maybe
just take care of things
around whatever work I have,
like an assistant or something.
Once the two of us
had a stable income,
we could look
for a better place to live.
In the meantime,
you could study
for maybe a year or two
so that you'd be able to go out
and find a decent job,
something that would benefit
from your creativity.
We would go to work,
spend our evenings together,
and once we had enough money,
we could buy a house,
maybe even open up
a little shop of our very own.
After all, Kararagi is
a pretty thriving town,
so I'm sure
we could earn a living
on one of your fanciful ideas.
And once our jobs
were on track,
um, it's embarrassing to say,
but we could have a baby.
The child would be
half-demon and half-human,
so I'm sure it would be feisty,
but I know that they would
be completely adorable,
whether we ended up with a boy,
a girl, twins, or even triplets.
I'm sure that it wouldn't be
all fun and games
and good times,
and I know not everything
would work out
exactly the way
I imagined it.
I mean, the two of us
might end up
having only daughters
and no sons,
so if you were hoping
to pass down your family name,
you might end up
being disappointed with that.
- Rem, I--
- But either way,
you've no need to worry.
Even when
the children grow up
and reach the age where they
might begin to treat you coldly,
I'll still be right there
by your side.
In the neighborhood,
we'll be known
as a couple
of old, romantic lovebirds,
the kind who still laugh
and flirt with each other
after so many years...
growing old together.
- Then why don't--
- I would feel bad
for doing such a thing to you,
but I would prefer to die
before you if possible.
I want to die quietly
in the home we'd made together,
lying on our bed
with your hand in mine,
surrounded by our children
and their children,
and I'd say,
"I lived such a happy life,"
then, with all you there,
take my last breath.
If I could do that,
I'd end my life so happily,
so very happily.
- I don't understand.
Then why, Rem?
If you want it that badly,
then why can't--
- Because you're not smiling.
If you really wanted
that future,
one with the two of us
growing old together,
- I would die so happy.
- [gasps]
- I would love
a future like that with you,
and knowing you truly care
enough about me
to want me there with you
when you run away,
leaving everything behind,
makes me happy
from the bottom of my heart.
But I'm afraid I can't do it.
Because I know...
that if we ran away
together now,
the Subaru I'd be leaving behind
would be the Subaru
that I love most.
Now please...
tell me what happened
that's bothering you so.
- [sighs]
- If you can't tell me,
then just trust me.
I swear that I'll
do something to make it right.
- [gasps]
- But for now, at least,
we should return to the manor.
If we can take our time
and consider things calmly,
maybe we can find
a different answer
to whatever the problem is.
- I've agonized over this.
I've thought about it.
I've suffered for it!
And that's why...
I'm giving up.
- Look, it's easy to do, but...
- Did you just say
what I thought you said?
- Subaru, you're shaking.
- Don't give me that crap!
There's nothing easy
about giving up, nothing!
You think
I'm just doing nothing,
thinking about nothing,
cutting myself off
from everything,
throwing my entire life away,
leaving every last thing
I know and care about behind,
and that's all it took
for me to call it quits?!
That's a lie!
It was never that easy for me!
It was so much easier for me
to go on thinking
that there was something I could
do to make a real difference!
But I know now
that there's nothing I can do!
There's no way out! Understand?!
The only path everything
leads to is giving up!
If I could do something,
then I'd do it.
I swear that I would.
- Listen to me.
- [crying]
- It is easy to give up.
But it doesn't suit you at all.
I don't know what painful things
you've been through
or what you've done that
makes you suffer so terribly.
And I know
it would be wrong of me
to say that I understand
whatever it is
you've been experiencing
to make you feel this way.
It would.
Even so...
there's something
that I do know about all this.
I know for certain
that you are someone
who cannot give up on something
when you're halfway through.
And I know for certain
that you are someone
who can smile
when you talk about all of your
hopes and wishes for the future.
And I know for certain
that you are someone who can't
give up on the future,
no matter what.
- I'm sorry, but you're wrong.
- I'm not that kind of person.
- I'm not wrong.
You haven't given up on us,
not Miss Emilia or Sister,
on Lord Roswaal,
or Miss Beatrice
or on anyone else.
That isn't who you are.
- You don't know
what you're talking about.
I have given up.
Carrying it all was impossible
from the very start.
My hands are so small that it
all slipped through my fingers,
leaving nothing behind.
- No, that's not true.
That's not true at all.
You have--
- Bullshit! What do you know?!
What the hell do you
actually know about me, huh?!
Nothing!
I'll tell you
what kind of man I really am.
I have no strength,
but I want it all.
I have no knowledge,
but all I do is dream.
There's nothing I could do but
struggle in vain like an idiot!
I...
I hate...
I hate myself!
All I do is talk a big game
and make myself
sound like a big shot
when I can't do anything!
I never do anything,
yet I complain
with the best of them,
like it's my job or something.
Who the hell do I think I am?!
I'm a fraud.
It's amazing that I can live
like this and not feel ashamed.
You know I'm right!
I'm an empty shell.
There's nothing
inside me at all.
I know there isn't.
Guess that's obvious.
Anybody could see that.
Before I came to this place,
before I got in the situation
that led me to all of you,
do you have any idea
what I did with my life?
I did nothing, that's what.
I've never done
a single thing worth mentioning.
I had all that time and freedom,
but I just squandered it away
on nothing.
I could have done
anything with my life,
but I never did a damn thing,
and what you're
looking at now is the result,
this cowardly, weak,
worthless crybaby.
All of my powerlessness,
all of my incompetence,
it's the product of my rotten
and pathetic character.
Wanting to accomplish
something important
when I've never done
anything to earn it
goes way beyond
the limitations of arrogance.
The cost of my lifetime
of laziness
and all the wasteful habits
I forged along the way
just ends up killing
both you and me.
[inhales]
That's right.
I have no character,
even when I thought
I could go on living here
and nothing changed
about who I really am.
The old man back at the manor
saw that part of me perfectly,
didn't he?
I wasn't trying to get stronger
or trying to make things better.
That was a lie.
I was just striking
an obvious pose
to justify myself, to say
that I was trying my best,
that it wasn't like I
wasn't doing anything,
to able to appear to be
doing everything I could.
I wanted to say
I couldn't help it,
to be told that it
couldn't be helped.
I was only pretending
to push my body to the limit
so that all of those excuses
would be possible!
Even when I had you
help me study,
I was just posing to cover up
how embarrassed I felt
to be such an incompetent idiot!
Deep down inside,
at the core of my heart,
I'm just a small, cowardly,
filthy piece of trash
who's always worried
about how others see me,
how they'll accept or judge me,
and nothing--nothing
about me has changed!
[crying]
I've known it
since the very beginning.
Everything that was happening
was my fault.
I'm the lowest of the low.
I absolutely...
hate myself.
- Listen to me.
I know that no matter how deeply
you've fallen
into the pit of darkness,
you still have enough courage
to reach out your hand.
I love it when you
run your hand along my hair.
I feel as though
we can understand each other
without ever saying a word,
just through
that bit of contact.
I love the sound of your voice.
Just hearing you
say a single word
makes my heart flutter
and feel warmer.
I love how much of you
I see in your eyes.
Normally they look
so stern and serious,
but in those moments when
you're being kind to someone,
I really love
the way they soften.
I love your fingers, too.
For a boy, they're so delicate.
But when they hold mine,
I know they're the strong,
slender fingers of a man.
They make me feel safe.
I love the way you move
when you're walking.
Whenever we're out
walking together,
I love the way
you occasionally turn
to make sure
I'm keeping up with you
and never leave me behind.
- Stop.
- I love the way
you look when you sleep.
You seem unguarded,
like an infant,
and your eyelashes
are so long.
When I touch your cheek,
you calm down.
And when I playfully
touch your lips,
you don't even notice.
And it makes my heart
ache terribly.
I love you.
- Why would you say that?
- When you said
that you hate yourself
and told me all the reasons
why you feel that way,
it made me want
to counter those reasons
and tell you all
the absolutely wonderful things
I know and love about you.
- You're just seeing
what you want to see!
Those things were all phony!
That isn't me.
I know myself
better than anybody ever could!
- That's not true!
All you know is yourself!
How much do you know
about the Subaru that I see?
[crying] The one I was
just telling you about?
- Why?
Why do you like me so much?
'Cause I'm--I'm nothing
but a small weakling.
I'm running, running away
just like I did last time,
so why do you
even care about me?
- You don't know?
Because you're my hero, Subaru.
[wings fluttering]
Back in that dark forest,
when I didn't even know
who I was anymore
and couldn't think of anything
but violently lashing out,
you were the one who saved me.
- [singing in Japanese]
- When I woke up
unable to move
and Sister was exhausted
after using too much magic,
you faced the mabeasts
all alone
as a diversion
so we could escape.
There was no way you could win,
and your life
was in real danger,
but you still stayed and
made your way back to my arms
so warm from the battle.
When you finally woke up,
you smiled at me
and said the words
I wanted to hear most
when I wanted
to hear it the most
from the one I wanted
to most hear them from.
My time has been stopped
for so very long.
Ever since
that horrible fiery night,
that tragic night
I lost everything
I had in this world
except for my sister,
my time has been stopped.
It was you
who melted my frozen heart,
and through your never-ending
care and kindness,
made the time
that had been stopped for me
for so long start moving again.
I'm sure you have no idea
how you saved me that morning
or just how happy
you made me feel.
There was
so much joy inside me.
I couldn't hold back the tears.
Understand?
That's why I believe,
no matter what painful things
may happen,
even when it looks
like you'll go down in flames,
when no one else in the entire
world believes in you,
when you don't even
believe in yourself
and you think
that you can't go on,
I will still believe in you.
[singing continues]
- [cries]
- The Subaru who came
into my life and saved me
is the hero
that I will always call mine.
[singing continues]
- No matter what I did
or how hard I tried,
I couldn't manage
to save anyone.
- I'm here.
Don't you see?
The Rem you saved
is right here.
- I've never done anything.
I'm empty.
No one will even listen to me.
- I'm right here.
I'm ready to listen
to anything you have to say.
I want to.
- No one expects
anything of me.
No one in the world
believes in me.
I'm no good. I hate myself.
- No matter how you feel
about yourself,
I still love you.
- You really don't mind
that it's me?
- I want it to be you.
I wouldn't want for it
to be anyone else.
If you can't forgive yourself
for being empty
and having nothing,
then let's start from here
right now at this very moment.
- Start what?
- Just like when you
started time for me
after it had been stopped
for so long,
we'll make the time that you
feel has somehow stopped for you
begin to move again.
Let's start over right here...
from square one.
No, we'll start from zero.
- [gasps]
- If it's too hard
for you to walk on your own,
then I'll hold you up.
We can both share the burden
supporting each other,
walking side by side.
Isn't that more or less what
you said to me that morning?
Show me how awesome
you can be, Subaru.
Show them all.
- Rem.
- What is it?
- Emilia is the one I love.
- I know.
- I want to see Emilia smile.
I want to be of help
to Emilia's future.
Even if she says
I'm in the way,
even if she tells me
to leave her...
I want to be right there
at her side.
Using my feelings for her
as an excuse
to get her
to understand everything
was pretty arrogant
of me, huh?
Man, do I feel stupid.
It's okay
if she doesn't understand.
I just want to save her.
If there's a bleak, painful
future waiting for her,
I want to take her away
to a future where we
can all laugh together.
Will you help me?
I need you.
I can't do anything alone.
I'm lacking in everything.
I'm not even sure
I can keep walking straight.
I'm just a weakling,
so fragile and small.
I'm asking to make sure
I stay on the right path,
to help me realize
when I'm wrong.
Will you help me?
- [giggles]
You're a cruel man.
You know that?
You ask this of somebody
who confessed their love for you
and then reject it?
- Hey, it's also hard
for me to ask this
of the one who rejected
my once-in-a-lifetime proposal.
You wanna just call it even
and move on?
- [giggles]
[both laughing]
- I'll be there to help
with whatever you need.
I'll do everything
I can for you.
If it helps my hero,
if you greet the future with
a smile, then it's worth it.
- Thanks, Rem.
And now watch me.
You get a front-row seat...
- [gasping]
[wind blowing]
- You'll see the man
you fell in love with
become the most awesome hero
you and the rest of this world
have ever known!
- [gasps]
[whimpers]
[crying]
SUBARU: I'm watching you.
You're watching me...
so I won't look downward,
not anymore.
Subaru Natsuki's story
will begin right here
at this moment.
My life in another world
starts here...
from zero!
[wind blowing]
- Are you serious?
SUBARU: Yes.
You heard me correctly.
I'm proposing an alliance
between the Emilia and
Crusch camps on equal terms,
and the information I'll offer
for that purpose is this,
the next time and place
you'll find the White Whale.
That's the one card
I can play here.
- The White Whale?
[energy humming]
- [gasps]
- [sighs]
Please forgive my indiscretion.
I suppose I still
have much to learn.
- [chuckles]
- I must say,
it seems a bit out of nowhere
for you to suddenly bring up
the White Whale like this.
- Oh, I wouldn't say that.
When we first began
this negotiation,
I mentioned the magic stones
that were found in Elior Forest,
located inside
Lord Roswaal's domain.
If sharing the mining rights
is an insufficient incentive
to seal this deal,
then I suppose I'm gonna need
to offer up an additional push.
So listen to me.
I'm absolutely certain
that the information
I can provide
will help you in your plan
to bring that thing down.
- There's something
I'd like to ask you about
concerning this matter.
What made you feel
this would be enticing to me?
Since we've never discussed it,
this seems oddly focused
to present.
For the past few days,
I've noticed a few things
that bothered me.
First, the traffic
to and from your mansion.
It's been just a little
excessive, if you ask me.
Also I heard in the capital
that you've been buying up a lot
of weapons and armor lately.
Plus...
- If Miss Crusch's goal
were to be attained,
then, Mr. Wilhelm,
I'm confident
such an outcome
would suit your desires.
- Based on those observations,
it seemed like you were
planning something big.
'Course, I can't
exactly prove that, can I?
Who's to say?
Maybe I only made the connection
because I happen to know
the White Whale
will be appearing soon.
- I have another question,
Subaru Natsuki.
On what grounds do you know
when and where the White Whale
will next appear?
- Because of this.
- And what is this contraption?
- The moment
before that went down,
I happened to notice...
That device is what
you'd call a metia.
It tells me exactly when and
where that monster will appear.
- I find all this
a bit hard to believe.
But I see that you aren't lying.
- I appreciate you believing me,
but I'm surprised
you did so easily.
- Telling lies will get you
nowhere with Miss Crusch.
She has the divine protection
of wind-reading.
- Uh, say what?
- Whenever anyone attempts
to tell a lie,
there's a telling wind
that blows around them.
I'm able to see that wind.
There's no evidence
of it now.
- So then, does that mean
you'll agree
to an alliance in exchange
for all the information
I have on the White Whale?
- Not so fast.
That's not what I said.
Whether or not I agree to
the alliance you just proposed
and whether or not I believe you
are entirely separate matters.
This important decision
will determine
not only the outcome
of the royal selection itself,
but the entire future
of the kingdom.
ANASTASIA: Hey, would you mind
if I listen in
on this little chat, too?
RUSSELL: Pardon us.
CRUSCH: Anastasia Hoshin.
And Russell Fellow?
- [giggles]
Now this isn't fair at all,
if you ask me.
You asked us to come,
and then here you are
starting things without us.
Let us in on this, too.
- I wasn't aware
of this invitation.
Was it Subaru Natsuki
who asked you to come here?
- Well, to be exact,
it was this blue-haired girl
he keeps with him.
I only heard the gist
of what you were talking about,
but if you're really planning
on putting down the White Whale,
I'm all about it.
For us businessfolk,
whether that thing
is around or not is pretty much
a life-or-death matter,
so our mercenary team will help
with whatever you need.
- In addition to all matters
that are concerning
the White Whale,
I'm interested in the concession
proposed by Mr. Natsuki
regarding the possibility
of mining rights
to the magic stones.
If the aforementioned alliance
is formed,
magic stones mined
from veins previously untouched
will be distributed to
the capital through Miss Crusch.
As the merchant guild's
representative,
I cannot let this offer
go unheard.
- Natsuki called you as well?
- I'll say it once more.
What I offer
in return for this alliance
is a share in the magic stone
mining rights
and information concerning
when and where
the White Whale
will next appear.
You'd have everything
you need to locate
and attack
that terrorizing mabeast
and then bring it down.
If what I've said doesn't
have any appeal for you,
then forget I mentioned
anything about it.
On the other hand,
if your goal and my wish
align the way I think they do,
then let's defeat
the White Whale.
Let's go on a hunt together.
[no audible dialogue]
[swallows]
- [sighs]
I still have several questions
concerning this arrangement,
but it was brilliant of you
to uncover my plans.
- So then...
- I have questions,
as well as doubts.
Some things you've said
are unclear to me,
so I'm having difficulty
agreeing immediately.
However, I will choose
to trust your eyes
and the spirit that led you
to create this situation.
- I would say
that the deal is made, then.
- [sighs]
RUSSELL: There may have been
a few touch-and-go moments,
but I'm glad it worked out,
Mr. Natsuki.
I trust the promise
we made earlier still stands?
- Yeah, you bet.
You were a big help.
Once the Whale
has been taken care of,
I'll hand over the metia to you.
- [sighs] Looks like you
laid some groundwork beforehand.
Were you waiting
outside the door
for your moment to enter?
- Yes, but it was entirely
up to us when we interrupted.
Well, far as negotiations go,
I guess that barely gets
a passing mark.
- Took you long enough.
What were you doing out there?
I thought you were
never gonna come in.
- When negotiating,
there's always a perfect time
to make your move.
Right. Well,
as you're getting ready
for the subjugation and such,
don't forget to patronize
the Hoshin Company.
- You paved the way
for everything
before negotiations began, huh?
You're surprisingly shrewd
in your tactics.
I commend you.
- My review and preparation
paid off. That's all.
To be honest,
I couldn't be more relieved.
- You can say that again.
You look completely worn out.
- [sighs]
- [laughs]
[Rem laughs]
- Well, Rem, we somehow
managed to save face
for staying in the capital,
right?
- Indeed. Once again, you were
truly wonderful, Subaru.
The Witch's Cult?
- Yeah. They're on the move
and have got their eyes
on Emilia.
- Coincidentally,
Lord Roswaal had a feeling
like something like this
might happen as well.
- I want to stop them,
but I just don't have
the fighting strength to do it.
I have to start negotiating
if I hope
to pull some together.
You think
you'll be able to help me?
- [chuckles]
- Mr. Subaru.
- Eh?
- I must thank you.
- Huh?
- You have my deepest respect
and most humble gratitude
equal to that
which I offer to My Lady
Duchess Crusch Karsten.
- Oh. Well, that's, uh...
- As perceptive as you are,
I'm sure you're aware,
but if I may introduce myself,
my family name is Astrea.
I took the previous
Master Swordsman,
Theresia van Astrea as my wife,
which in turn gave me the honor
of the lowest seat
in the bloodline.
That is who I,
Wilhelm van Astrea, proudly am.
Thank you for so very kindly
granting this old man
the opportunity
to slay the loathsome mabeast
that took my wife.
- Uh, sure. Of course.
I knew that. No big deal.
I figured Miss Crusch
would weigh that into account
and accept my offer
with that in mind.
- Subaru Natsuki,
the wind of untruth
is blowing from you.
[overlapping chatter]
SUBARU: I get it now.
You bought all the dragon-drawn
carriages for this,
and that's why I had trouble
getting a ride
back to the mansion.
- You're still awake, huh?
- No way I could sleep
through all this.
Everyone else here
is working through the night.
- They have neo choice.
We don't have much time neow.
- That's true. The White Whale's
next appearance
will be tomorrow night
in the area that's
right around Flügel's Tree.
- Given all the traveling
it takes to get there,
we'll just barely make it.
Besides, can't you see it
in all of their faces?
- [gasps]
- [laughter]
FELIX: Not a single one of them
is preparing unwillingly.
Everyone in the entire kingdom
wants to be rid
of the White Whale,
especially old man Wil
over there.
- He said it took his wife.
- Hmm.
Since before you were born,
he's been chasing
after that awful thing.
His wife was
the Master Swordsman.
Even knowing
what her duties entailed,
her death was no less tragic.
- The previous Master Swordsman.
- Well, now you know the story.
You should stop
worrying about things
and try to get some sleep.
Besides, there's
nothing you can do
to help with supply distribution
or organization
of this mission anyway.
- That may be true,
but you didn't have to say it
and rub it in my face!
- [laughs]
[wind blowing]
SUBARU: So I'm supposed
to pick whichever one I want?
- What are you
complaining about neow?
- Don't you like 'em?
- It's not that.
I'm glad you're
letting me borrow one,
but I don't
know enough about 'em
to figure out
what I'm looking for.
I mean, do I look like a guy
who studied ground dragons
for decades or something? Wait.
Are you
the same one from before?
- [grunts]
- [laughs] Well, it looks
like this is the one for me.
- Wow. I'm surprised.
This type of ground dragon
is known for being
really proud and difficult,
yet it took to him right away.
- Felix, I'll take this one.
It's love at first sight.
- That's fine by me.
But don't say,
"Love at first sight."
You're making little Rem
pouty-wouty.
- I'm not
pouty-whatever you said.
I'll be nice to it. I promise.
- I can do it.
- [grunts]
- [crackling]
- [Rem groans]
[overlapping chatter]
- [grunts] Hey!
- My Lady was telling me
about you.
I believe you're the star
of this little show, aren't you?
- That logo.
A demihuman from Kararagi?
So I take it
you're with Anastasia?
- Sure am. What gave it away?
I'm Ricardo,
head of her mercenary team.
It is nice to meet you,
too, little lady.
- Keep it down. Also be careful.
You're huge.
You'll snap my neck.
- Hey, My Lady!
- Easy! [groans]
Holy crap.
CRUSCH: Must be the pride
of Anastasia and the Hoshins,
the Iron Fang.
Impressive. They all do
look rather formidable.
So did you sleep well
last night?
- Yeah, but I nearly died
a second ago.
Oh. Judging by your outfit,
I guess you're fighting,
too, then?
- Well, of course I am.
Do you really think I'm capable
of just sitting in a chair
and waiting for good news?
To be honest, I'm more surprised
that you're participating.
Are you skilled
in the art of combat?
- That would be a no.
But even if I can't fight,
let me tell you,
someone here's
gonna come in pretty handy
in this battle
against the White Whale,
- and that's me.
- Really?
What makes you say that?
- Well, it's not
exactly something
I'm really happy about, but...
I seem to be the type of guy
that attracts mabeasts
like moths to a flame.
- Seriously? [gasps]
- It's the truth.
In fact, Subaru has
saved my life before
thanks to that very ability.
- So I figured I'd run around
under the White Whale's nose
on my borrowed ground dragon
and draw its attention
while the rest of you ride in
and launch an all-out attack.
Eh, at least that's the tactic
I'd recommend, anyway.
- So you'd risk your life
to be the bait?
[sighs] Shockingly,
I don't sense any lies
in that idiotic statement.
Never thought I'd doubt
my divine protection
as often as I have
in the past half-day,
but this is a unique
set of circumstances.
[doors open]
[Crusch and Rem gasp]
- They've arrived.
- Greetings, Miss Crusch.
Reporting as ordered
under your command.
Is this the boy?
- Yes, the very same.
- [gasps]
- You have my gratitude.
- Huh?
- Because of you,
our greatest wish
may come true,
and we couldn't
be happier about it.
I thank you.
- Uh...
- [chuckles]
REM: It's seems
they're all people
who have a history
with the White Whale.
- Those soldiers, are they all
just like Wilhelm, then?
- Indeed. Many of them are men
who have since retired from
fighting on the front lines.
They've donned their armor
and joined our subjugation force
at Wilhelm's invitation.
Their experience is comparable
to those of the capital's
active knights.
- The time has come,
Miss Crusch.
- Right.
[no audible dialogue]
400 years...
since the White Whale
created by the jealous Witch
made the world
its hunting ground,
trampling the weak
and dominating the land
as if it were its owner.
400 years have passed.
Countless lives have been lost
to the beast during that time.
Given the unscrupulous nature
of its fog,
the number of graves we cannot
even inscribe with names
will only rise.
- [grunts]
- But the days of helplessness
and sitting idle end today!
Those of us gathered here
will end it.
We will strike down
the White Whale
and stop any further tragedy.
- [weeping]
- We will give the despair
that fell short of true sorrow
a chance to shed
long overdue tears!
We move out!
Our destination is Flügel's Tree
on the Lifaus Highway!
Tonight, we slay
the White Whale
with our own hands!
- [cheering]
- Yeah!
[steeds galloping]
- [gasps]
- Hey there! I'm Mimi!
- Glad to know you!
- I'm Hetaro.
It's nice to make
your acquaintance.
- Yeah. Nice to meet you.
Anyway, not that I had any
reason to doubt it, but, uh,
you really are the
second-in-command, aren't you?
- Hmm? Wait a second.
Have we met somewhere before?
I'm thinking about it,
but I totally don't remember
seeing your face at all.
- Hey, come on, Sister.
- You have to sit up properly.
- So weird.
I totally don't remember.
- Don't worry about it.
Just talking to myself.
I'm Subaru Natsuki.
From the resemblance,
I guess you two
are brother and sister, huh?
- Yes. My big sister and I
will do our best--
- Mimi and Hetaro
are the strongest!
The captain's here, too,
so we're the super strongest!
[laughs]
- Honestly, my sister
and the captain
tend to be hasty with decisions,
so I'm the one
who usually gives the orders.
- I see.
I don't envy that at all.
RICARDO: What's the matter, bro?
You're looking kind of gloomy.
- And whose fault is that?
The captain shouldn't go around
making trouble for his men.
- Hey, that's a nice
ground dragon you got there.
- Yeah!
Thanks for saying so.
But honestly,
I only borrowed this one
because it kind of
seemed to like me.
Come to think of it,
the ones you guys are riding
look pretty different.
- They're called rigers.
I guess you don't see 'em
too often around here, though.
They aren't as strong
as those ground dragons,
but they're much more lively.
If it comes to a brawl
against the Whale,
that's where they really shine,
so watch closely.
- [laughs]
Well, if that's the case,
shouldn't you have had
ground dragons
pull the cargo, then?
- I hear what you're saying,
but we gotta manage
our luggage on our own.
If you think the White Whale's
our only enemy,
you'll get the rug
pulled out from under you.
- [gasps]
- [chant echoes]
RICARDO: After all,
there's no guarantee
we won't run into thieves
on the road.
- If anybody's got the guts
to take on a fully armed group
like this,
they wouldn't settle
for being thieves.
- You got a point there.
[laughs]
[no audible dialogue]
- It looks like Mr. Ricardo
is doing his best
to try and ease everybody's
nerves a little bit.
Hey, what's wrong?
- [sighs]
I thought I'd fully prepared
myself for this, but...
I want to be heroic.
'Course wanting something
and making it happen
are two different things
entirely.
- [chuckles]
[wind blowing]
SUBARU: Whoa. It's huge.
- It's impressive, isn't it?
You sound happy.
- [laughs]
[sighs]
Oh, man. Check this out.
Looks like people have carved
their names into the trunk.
We're not on some field trip.
That's just bad manners.
Hey, Rem, give me a chisel.
- Even you
should know doing that
will get you
in big trouble, Subaru,
with me, for starters.
So the White Whale
is coming here?
Honestly, I'm opposed to using
the Witch's scent
to draw it here.
It's much too dangerous.
It worries me.
- I'll use whatever I can
to stop it.
[grunts]
I mean, if it gives us
even a slightly better chance
of winning, it's worth it.
For a guy who's lacking
in pretty much
every way imaginable,
this is the only way
I can pitch in and compensate.
- You're so wonderful, Subaru.
- [chuckles]
- So that metia will tell you
when the White Whale is coming?
- Yeah. I set it
to make noise when it's time.
And to be honest, without this--
- That's a lie.
- [gasps]
What--Hold on!
What are you saying?
If it's a lie, then how am I
gonna help catch
that White Whale in the...
- It sounds as if
you're speaking
like someone from Kararagi.
It doesn't suit you at all.
- No, no, no, no!
I mean, there's no way
I could be lying!
Even Miss Crusch said
I didn't have the wind thing
blowing around me...
- It's all an act, Subaru.
I can always tell
when you're lying,
with or without the power
to see the telltale wind.
I also know every time
that you can't tell me
why you're lying,
so there's no need for you
to try to convince me
to believe whatever excuse
you're coming up with
or wrap everything
you're saying in lies
or try to take the blame
upon yourself like that.
It's not necessary,
because I have absolute faith
in you, Subaru.
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
[swallows]
[gasps]
Man, looking up
at this huge tree
really gets you fired up,
doesn't it, Rem?
- Yes. It certainly does.
- I don't think
that I'll be able to relax
if I don't look up at it
for a long time.
I won't be able to look
anywhere else for a while.
- Yes, I understand.
- Should say thanks
instead of I'm sorry
in these situations.
- Well, in that case,
you're welcome.
Besides, if I look back on
all that's happened between us,
I'm far more grateful
to you, Subaru,
so we're even.
- [sniffs]
[wind blowing]
Uh, Wilhelm.
I heard a little bit
of the story from Felix,
that you've been seeking revenge
on the White Whale
ever since it took
your wife away from you.
- Please forget that.
It was all time idly spent
in an old man's delusions.
- You truly love your wife
with all your heart, don't you?
- Yes. I love her
more than anything,
more than anyone,
no matter how much time
passes without her.
My wife was a woman
who loved to make the time
to look at flowers.
She never wished
she had to carry a sword,
but the sword she wielded
loved her more than anyone.
With no choice
but to live for that weapon,
my wife gave in to her destiny
and accepted her fate.
When I married her,
I made a decision,
she would abandon
the title of Master Swordsman.
I tried to take that life away,
but the sword
wouldn't allow her to do it.
Mr. Subaru, I thank you again.
In the battle before us,
I needn't look any further
than my own sword for answers.
And perhaps I will finally
be able to visit
my wife's grave.
At last I can stand
before her once again.
- Let's do everything we can
and work together
to beat the hell
out of that damn Whale.
I promise to give it
everything I've got.
- [sighs]
[wind blowing]
[ground dragons snorting]
- Only a short time
remains before us.
- [grunts]
[fires crackling]
[gear rattles]
[cell phone ringtone plays]
- [gasps]
Soldiers, be ready!
[gear rattles]
[ringtone continues]
[soldiers gasping]
- I'm looking,
but I don't see it.
- [ringtone continues]
- [soldiers murmuring]
- What's going on?
CRUSCH: It's not coming?
- Behind us! Look!
- [gasps]
[ringtone continues]
[crackling]
- [ringtone echoing]
- [White Whale moans]
[bellowing]
- Soldiers...
- Let him have it!
- El Huma!
- [gasps]
- [soldiers murmuring]
- [music playing]
- [chuckles]
[inhales]
Soldiers, follow those two fools
into battle!
[soldiers yelling]
[music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I stay alive ♪