- Good!
And finally,
victory!
all: Victory!
Victory! Victory!
[all laughing]
All right, line up,
everyone.
[all laughing]
It's time to collect
your stamps.
Okay then, who's first?
- The kitty's so cute!
- The kitty's awesome!
- The kitty's so sad!
- The villagers seem to be happy
and full of life again.
Thanks to you, Subaru.
- [laughs]
Well, what can I say,
you know?
I mean, I did kinda put my neck
on the line to rescue them.
I went into the forest
and got bitten by dogs
to save the kids.
I got bitten by dogs
when I tried to save Rem
after she turned into a demon.
Then I had to be saved
by Roswaal when I was about
to be bitten by a giant dog.
Wait, did I really even
do that much of anything?
- You're obsessing too much
over trivial details.
Stop worrying.
There are those who know
the truth
about what you went through.
That includes Roswaal and Ram,
and especially Rem.
And don't forget
I know everything
that you went through as well.
[wind blowing]
- A dragon-drawn carriage?
- Welcome home, my lady.
I offer my most humble apologies
for parking
in front of your mansion.
[both grunting]
[Konomi Suzuki's "Redo"]
♪ ♪
- [singing in Japanese]
- An emissary from the capitol
is here visiting us.
Lord Roswaal's attending
to them now.
Please join him,
Miss Emilia.
- An emissary?
- I believe it concerns
the royal selection.
- [gasps]
- All right, I know this
is important
so I'll be on my best behavior.
I know I'm a goof but--
- Well, uh,
sorry, but this
is really important.
I think it would be best
if you remained behind, okay?
- [grunts]
- [chuckles]
Aren't you bored waiting
out here all by yourself?
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- It tastes lovely.
Drinking it feels as though
I'm indulging in a great luxury.
- To be honest, it's the most
expensive tea in the mansion.
If the pink-haired maid
discovers that we drank it
without permission,
she'll totally freak.
- I see.
And what exactly is it that you
hope to gain from this old man
using such precious bait?
- I only wanna know the reason
for this visit, that's all.
If you could maybe just give me
a vague idea?
- As I'm unsure as to what
you're standing or status is
in this mansion,
it's in my best interest
not to say anything careless
about our dealings here.
Please understand.
- [groans]
- That being said, however,
I did notice that you seem
to be quite close
to Miss Emilia.
- Oh, yeah?
Did it look like things were
serious between Mili and me?
[laughing]
- Mili?
A steep path you're choosing
to climb.
Need I remind you that
you're dealing with one
who may be the future queen
of Lugunica?
- Future is the keyword there.
Right now we're just
a super cute girl
and a useless servant boy.
You probably think your wife
is the prettiest girl
in the whole wide world.
Am I right?
I mean, isn't that what
you thought the day
that you got down on one knee
and proposed to her?
- My wife, huh?
Why, yes, of course.
Indeed, you're
absolutely correct.
I believed my wife
was the most beautiful lady
in the entire world.
- I'm back,
Old Man Will!
Sorry to make you wait outside.
I bet you were bored, huh?
- Not at all.
In fact I'm passing
the time having
a rather interesting discussion
with this young man here.
- [meows]
- Eh...
Ah, nyow I see.
Of course, of course.
You must be the boy
that Miss Emilia
was talking about earlier.
- She mentioned me?
- Well, looks like you're
totally clueless, aren't you?
Let's go, Old Man Will.
See you in the capitol.
- Listen, we're not going there
for fun, okay?
I received an important summons
and--
- If it's important,
all the more reason!
You're in a battle
for the throne, right?
I wanna be there and help you
in any way that I can.
Pretty please!
- [gasps]
- Based on prior discussions,
it seems there are several
people in the capitol
who helped Subaru.
This may be a good opportunity
for him to thank them.
- Very nice assist, Rem.
She's right, you know.
Some people in the capitol were
a big help to me.
So I need to let them know that
I'm alive and well.
- [grunts]
- Ooh, why not let him?
That can be kept separate
from our royal
selection business.
Subaru should go to the capitol
to thank everyone
as well as receive treatment.
This trip would be
an opportunity for both.
- Huh?
Treatment?
- You overused your
already-exhausted gate
in the mabeast battle out
in the forest.
Your wound will need treatment.
I believe that you met
the emmisary earlier.
Did you not?
- Do you mean the cutesy face
with the cat ears?
- That cutesy face with cat ears
was one of the capitol's
most brilliant users
of water magic,
as well as healing magic.
Felix is a peculiar one
whose cooperation
was difficult even
for Miss Emilia to enlist.
- Wait a minute!
- Is he for real, Mili?
You did that for me?
- Well, it's partly my fault
that you haven't healed yet,
so you could say
I'm repaying a debt.
I consider this
as equal compensation
for what you went through
to help.
I just wanna make things right.
- I must admit,
I was surprised to see you
talking with that boy.
I always thought you'd rather
chop people in half
than talk to them.
- That's a grave
misunderstanding.
- I merely took a bit of
a liking to what I saw there
in that young man's eyes.
- Oh?
- Those are the eyes of one
who has been at death's door
many times.
- Huh.
Now you've lost me.
Either way,
if Wilhelm van Astrea
the Sword Demon
says something like that,
then I'm sure the boy faces
quite a bumpy road ahead.
- Hey, uh, Mili?
Maybe we should stop doing this.
- No way.
Absolutely not.
'Cause I know how
your mind works.
The first moment I look away,
you'll be off doing
something crazy.
Oh, man, I can't believe we're
doing this!
I'm seriously moved!
I'm totally living out
a fantasy right now, baby!
- Subaru's so cute.
- Parallel worlds rule!
[screams]
- [shouts]
- [shouting]
- Subaru!
- Look, I'm really sorry about
all that.
But this chaperoning makes me
feel like I'm a little kid.
- Yet on our date
in the village,
you were the one who wanted
to hold hands so desperately.
- Because I was physically
and mentally prepared
for it then.
This time I'm not.
My hand is sweating like crazy!
- Come on!
Would you two cut out
the flirting already?
All that nonsense is gonna drive
away my customers.
- After I came to make good on
my promise to you,
that's pretty cold, man.
- Just giving you a hard time.
I appreciate you felt obligated
to shop here
now that you're
not broke anymore.
Here you go.
The appas I promised.
- Next will be Felt
and Old Man Rom.
- I assumed we'd wrapped
everything up rather neatly
without blame the first time,
but then right at the end,
Reinhard's expression went dark
and he took the girl away.
- When you say it like that,
it sounds like kidnapping
or an abduction
and confinement.
Those guys have really
got it good.
- If we want
to contact Reinhard,
then we should probably go
to the guard station
that's in front
of the nobleman's district.
- Uh, hey, Mili,
I wanted to ask you about
the royal selection
that starts up tomorrow.
- Don't start, Subaru.
We discussed this thoroughly
before going
on this trip together
and I thought you understood.
I brought you out here
to fulfill your promises
and to get you healed.
You don't have
to worry about me, okay?
- [grunts]
- Well, if it isn't Miss Emilia.
both: Hmm?
- Good to see you again.
I hope that you've been well
since we last met.
- Yes, everything's basically
the same.
And you also seem well, Julius.
- The mere fact that you
remember me is an honor.
And I must say,
you've only grown more
beautiful, Miss Emilia.
- [groans]
- You're very kind.
Forgive me for asking
so abruptly,
but I have business here,
and I'd like you
to act as my agent
while I'm in the castle.
- Is that so?
Does your business
involve this young man?
- [snarls]
- [chuckles]
His attitude is ill-matched
with his attire.
That's no way
to conduct yourself
before one you've just met.
- Thanks a bunch
for the warning.
And while we're on the subject,
I've got a warning
for you, too.
You shouldn't eat curry udon
in that suit.
If the soup splatters,
the stains will
really stand out.
- I have no idea what
this curry udon is,
but I'll certainly
keep that in mind.
- Now, allow me to show you
to the conference mirrors.
- So what's he talking about?
- There's a type of metia
that allows you to have
a discussion with someone
through two mirrors
facing each other.
- Ah.
Cool magic stuff?
Well--
- Subaru, wait here.
- Huh?
- I don't think it would be
a pleasant experience for you.
- Oh, I've already had an
experience that wasn't pleasant.
That bastard taking your cute
little hand
and licking all over it
like a dog.
- I'll try to come back
before things run too long.
Be good, please.
Stay here, okay?
- [sighs]
Geez, I look so pathetic
right now.
[grunts]
Bold thing to do
in front of the guard station.
It's darkest at the foot
of the lighthouse, I guess.
- You little--
- Don't screw around with us!
- You wouldn't want us to mess
up that pretty face of yours,
would ya?
- Don't make such a racket,
you commoners.
Fools with no character at all
pick fights for the most
absurd reasons.
- Hey, honey!
Sorry I'm late.
- Huh?
It looks like there's been a bit
of trouble in my absence.
But remember who I am
and cut me some slack, okay?
- Come on, let's go.
- Get your hands off me,
you filthy pleb!
- Cliffhanger.
- I don't want drooling
commoners following me around.
Of all the nerve!
- Figure out what's going
on here!
It was supposed to be
the classic scenario
where I save a girl
from hoodlums!
Wait.
No way.
Are the three of you the only
hoodlums in the capitol?
- It's the guy from behind
the shopping district.
- The brat from the alleyway?
- The very same,
so for my sake,
could you just let us both--
- Are you dumb?
Forget it.
This just makes it three-on-two
instead of three on one!
- Correction.
It isn't three-on-two.
It's more like three-on-one-
on-one.
- Oh, would you be quiet
for just a second?
I have no choice.
This is the last trick
I wanted to use, but--
Just so you know,
I happen to be good friends
with Reinhard.
If I call for him he'll
come running as fast
as he possibly can.
[all shouting]
Secret technique:
fox in tiger's clothing.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Hmm? It's been a while since
I seen you around these parts.
What brings you back to this
neck of the woods?
- [gasps]
Old Man Rom!
all: Damn you!
We won't forget this!
- [sighs]
Thanks a lot.
You saved me.
I seriously doubt that either
one of us could have handled
those three thugs on our own.
- Speak for yourself.
Whether either of you had
stepped in
to interfere or not,
I was never in the least bit
of danger.
- You're kidding, right?
"I didn't need your help,
understand?
"I'm a super strong, fiery,
independent woman.
I was doing just fine
on my own."
Something like that?
- No.
This world is designed
to operate in the way
that works best for me,
so I'm never disadvantaged
whatsoever.
- Whoa, really?
Well, I guess I shouldn't
have butted in, then.
Sorry to interfere.
- Oh, by the way, boy,
is there any chance you know
where Felt went off to?
- Wait a minute.
You mean you didn't
hear about what happened?
Apparently Reinhard
took her away.
- Now why would he do that?
Well, don't that beat all?
Had to be an Astrea, huh?
- Something wrong?
- No, no, I'm just talking
to myself.
Now you try not to cause
any more trouble
around these parts,
you hear?
- S--sure.
- There you are.
- [grunts]
- Oh, hey, Mili.
Wait, wait, wait!
You can't just go and hit on
Mili while I'm away, you jerk!
- Looks like your buddy's got
a screw loose, little lady.
He's more worried about losing
you to another guy
than happy to see you.
The man's heart is so complex,
it's a thrill to watch.
- You've got a pretty messed up
fashion sense,
don't you, Mr. Helmet?
- Now, that's no way to talk
to someone.
I can overlook that since
I'm a cool, good-natured man,
but some might lop off
your head for that.
- Easy.
Relax, Subaru.
I admit when I first saw him,
his outfit surprised me
a little, too.
- Yeah, well, I was surprised
when she asked for my help
while I was looking
for a lost child.
So there's that.
- You're way too soft-hearted
and trusting.
Most people would think that
a guy dressed like this
who's looking for a lost child
is gonna kidnap them.
- My, my.
How very attentive of you
to wait where you knew
I would be.
I commend you for your
dedication, Al.
- You mean you were
the lost child?
- [scoffs]
- [grunts]
- Well, what do you know?
Looks like we both found just
who we were looking for.
Let's go.
- Just a moment.
Would you mind telling me what
you have in that bag?
- These are appas.
Haven't you ever
seen one before?
- Please, don't make me laugh.
Everyone knows appas
have white flesh.
- Well, I mean, yeah,
the insides are white, but--
hang on, are you trying
to tell me you've never seen
an unpeeled appa?
Here you go.
Now don't go skipping off
after any obvious
bad guys again, okay?
- Subaru,
that girl from before.
- Huh?
I was wondering where you happen
to have met her and how.
- Huh?
What's this?
Are you jealous, Mili?
I can't believe you're actually
feeling that way over me--
or--
- Subaru.
- Uh, Mili, what's
with the serious face?
It's freaking me out a little.
- [gasps]
Nothing.
If you don't know, it's fine.
Forget about it.
- [grunts]
- [chomps]
Oh, wow.
I guess this thing
really is an appa.
- What?
I have to stay here tomorrow?
- Yes, of course you do.
That was our agreement
from the very beginning.
- Well, that was the plan,
but we never got in touch
with Reinhard, right?
If we go to the castle
together tomorrow,
we might run into him.
- There's no need.
I'll be sure to ask about Felt.
- I really think I should go
in person to--
- This is the reason
I can't take you with me.
If I allow you to do so,
you'll just push yourself
too hard again.
I don't want to let you do that.
Understand?
- I hear what you're saying,
but you're the one
who doesn't understand.
If I have to push myself
to help you,
then I'll do it without
a second thought.
I've gotta at least try.
- Absolutely not.
Until your body fully heals,
there is to be no using magic
or pushing yourself.
I want you to promise, okay?
- Okay, you win.
I promise you.
I won't use magic.
Either way,
let me go with you!
- I can't bring an outsider
into this.
So please, just wait here
with Rem until it's over,
all right?
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- I'm asking you, Subaru.
Give me a reason to trust you.
- I know there are those
in the capitol
who consider Emilia an enemy.
That's exactly why I have
to stay close to her.
- What's the matter?
- I'm going to save Emilia.
- Huh?
- And to do that...
- [gasps]
- [stare]
- Wh--what is it, Subaru?
It makes me feel uncomfortable
when you stare at me
with such imposing eyes.
- Stare.
- [sighs[
It's at the castle,
although most likely there
will be heavy security.
- Security isn't the problem.
I can't stand not being involved
in Emilia's important affairs.
- I know, but--
- When it comes down to it,
I'm only of any use
when something happens.
I want to be with her at a time
when she may need me the most.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
I'm going to set about making
a brand new appa recipe
that I just came up with
this very moment.
- What?
- And this culinary adventure
requires intense concentration,
so if someone were
to leave his room,
I most likely wouldn't notice.
- I'm such a scumbag
for relying on Rem
all the time.
But now the problem
is how I'm going
to get into the castle.
I guess times like these call
for hitchhiking!
[dragon roars]
- You sure are lucky, bro.
Be grateful
for this coincidence.
We just happened to be on our
way to the castle, too.
- You are?
Why's that?
- What do you mean?
Today there's only one reason
to head to the castle.
- Huh?
- Oh, you didn't know?
The young lady who's seated
before you is one
of the candidates to succeed
to the throne of Lugunica.
Priscilla Barielle herself.
- Whoa, seriously?
So why did you pick me up?
- For no other reason than
it seemed amusing.
A mere lark, nothing more.
I simply have a feeling that
taking you in there
will make things
a bit more interesting.
- Why do you think that?
- This world is designed
to operate
in the way that works best
for me.
So with every choice I make,
it's a given that all things
will be in my favor.
In the end,
it's only a matter of choosing
whether something amuses me
or not.
- [gasps]
- However, if I had to name
a reason,
other than amusement...
- Huh?
- Did you say your appa handler?
- Indeed.
He's something
of a wretched clown
whose sole priority is to bring
me bittersweet appas
whenever I fancy one.
- [grunts]
- [stammers]
- Everyone is waiting inside.
So please make haste.
- As their superior,
I like to keep
the masses waiting.
[doors creaking]
- [gasps]
Subaru?
- Emilia.
I can explain.
- [giggles]
Is there a reason you're staring
at my man servant?
It's rude to gawk,
you halfwit.
- Get off!
You'll give Mili the wrong idea!
- My, how nice to see you,
Miss Priscilla!
I do hope you'll forgive
my servant
for troubling you so.
- Hmm.
- What in the world are you
doing here, Subaru?
Thought I told you you were
supposed to wait for me.
You remember that,
don't you?
- Attention, the council
of wise men will now enter.
- So that's the council
of wise men, huh?
If I remember correctly,
they're the people managing
the country
in the king's absence,
aren't they?
- Hey, that's where we're
supposed to stand.
- You mean I can stand there,
too?
- Well, what do we have here?
I find this situation amusing,
so you may accompany him.
- Wait, Roswaal!
If Subaru's allowed
to stay here,
I'm sure that he'll--
- Miss Emilia.
The conference is beginning now.
We can't make them wait.
- [gasps]
Move to the center,
but you're going
to explain this to me later.
- [grunts]
So those are the participants
in the royal selection.
Guess one of them will be
the future ruler
of this country.
- So you decided to come
after all, Subaru.
When I heard through
the grapevine
that Miss Emilia would be here,
I had a rather strong suspicion
that you would be here as well.
- Hey, Reinhard.
I've been looking for you.
- Oh, how's it going?
- You, too?
- [laughs]
- Oh, Subaru.
You know him, I take it?
- Huh?
Know "him?"
- That's right.
He's a knight
by the name of Felix Argyle.
and despite all appearances,
he is male.
- You're kidding!
What's the point in looking like
that and even having cat ears
if you're a guy?
- I don't nyow what to tell you.
You're the one who made
the wrong assumption,
silly Subaru.
- [snarls]
- Hey, Subaru,
what's the matter?
- Where I come from,
this is the kind of face you
make whenever you run into a guy
who's a romantic rival.
- Now if I may be so forward,
I Marcos,
leader of the Imperial Knights,
will act as the director
for all of today's proceedings.
It all happened about half
a year ago
when members of the royal family
starting with the king
went into hiding one
by one causing--
- Listen, I get that you
wanna talk things up
and put on a good show here,
but I'm kinda busy, you know?
You may not have heard it,
but we have a saying back
in Kararagi.
Time is money.
- That attitude seems familiar
but I can't place it.
- Evidently everybody who's in
western Kararagi
acts like that.
- I couldn't agree more.
- Miss Crusch,
should the head of the Karsten
family say such a thing?
- I acknowledge it's important
to observe formality.
But it is also a fact
that our time is rather limited.
So it would be wise
to immediately inform us
as to why we're here.
Naturally, however,
I do have a general idea.
- Am I to understand
you already know
the purpose
of this meeting?
- Yes, I do, lord Miklotov.
For a drinking party.
One day soon we'll face each
other as rivals.
But by sharing drinks
and conversing
at the same table,
we'll have a chance to learn
more about one another.
- No, ma'am.
That is not correct.
- [grunts]
Felix.
This is not what you
told me earlier.
- What?
That's not true.
All I said was maybe it'll be
a drinking party.
I never said I knew it
for a fact or anything.
- I see.
Then I jumped to conclusions.
Forgive me.
Please allow me to retract
everything I just said.
- Now just a second.
Even if she backs down,
my opinion on this
isn't gonna change.
There's no need to explain
the royal selection process now.
We already know how it works.
Am I right?
- Well, even so,
I think maybe we should hear--
- Sorry, but I don't remember
asking for your opinion
on any of this business.
- [grunts]
Why, you little--
- Hey!
I don't know what's up
with the royal selection,
so I'd kinda like
to hear the rest.
- Excuse me, but I was informed
that this young man
is your knight, Miss Priscilla.
Haven't you explained
the selection to him?
- Whether I have or not
holds no merit.
You men will still ramble on
about it, won't you?
Please continue, Marcos.
- As you wish.
There's a specific reason
we've gathered you
who are qualified
to be the dragon's priestess.
A new prophecy has been engraved
in the Dragon Stone.
This new insight says,
"From the five capable
of becoming the nations's
"new leader,
choose one priestess
to enter into a covenant
with the dragon."
- Wait, five?
- That's right.
At the moment there are only
four candidates for the honor.
And the royal selection hasn't
even begun as of yet.
But today,
History will be set in motion.
Reinhard van Estraia
come forward. Yes, sir.
Honored members of
the Wiseman Imperial night
Reinhard van
Estraia would like to announce
the completion of my
mission the 5th Contender
the final candidate
mentioned in the prophecy.
Has been located.
The one I myself
Revere as Queen. Her name.
He's Miss felt.
Thank you for gracing
us with your presence mess felt.
It's wonderful to see you.
Hi Reinhard.
You surprised me
what could have brought on
such aggressive behavior?
My kicking ask me.
That happen because I've
had about all I can take of
your surprises do the dress
and shoes not suit your tastes.
They both look lovely on you.
Gimme a Break I'm not
talking about what I'm wearing.
Wait a second.
That's the girl from I guess
it's not that easy to
change somebody at their Roots
glad to see it's not just me.
Oh, no. What in the world
are you doing out here?
Hey there. It's been a while
hasn't it? If you believe.
That then why did you kick
me Miss felt if you finish
rekindling old friendships I ask
that you please step over here.
You want me to do anyway,
if you were asking me I'd say to
act more like
a lady but this comes first.
As you can see
the Dragon Gem has recognized
Miss felt as a priestess now
that her participation has been
approved by the powers
that be I believe it's time
to begin the Royal
selection process in earnest.
Even if the dragons
don't has recognized her don't
you think her selection
is a bit problematic.
So we the Imperial Knights
made a mistake.
Is it just me or is
it getting dicey in here?
Uh-huh doesn't bother me though.
No big deal.
And because no matter
what happens I've already.
Don lady
I feel the same way you do
my sword already
belongs to miss anesthesia.
Well, my feelings
for Amelia won't come in
second to
anybody else's look at her.
She doesn't have
the Healing Treasures becoming.
Silent.
Knight Reinhard Would You Begin
by explaining to us?
Just what steps you took
that led to her discovery?
Of course. I took
custody of Miss felt about
one month ago
while I was in the slums
you mean she's
a gutter rat from the slums.
Sorry for being a gutter rat
you were the one who dragged me
here against my will
all of this long-winded
and pointless blather
could not be more tedious.
But then again
I suppose it's quite possible.
You were living that way because
you could only manage tedious
conversation mind then if
you want to fight you got one.
What insolence who do you think
I am you little urchin princess?
That's not her.
A thousand
pardons Miss Priscilla.
What are you thinking?
Helm down, would
you I was only trying to teach
that undisciplined little bitch
her place you're not apologizing
for that you're kidding
right but out of curiosity,
would you also
apologize for being born?
You silver-haired half-elf.
I've told you I'm not
connected to the which at all.
Princess.
Could you drop it now?
I'll be the one
suffering if you make too
many enemies, seriously.
Well then are
you all quite finished
will the Royal selection
candidates?
Please come for that this time.
Miss Priscilla Boreal
and her attendant owl.
The selection
process is pointless.
I'm the only one
who suited to rule this nation.
All you people
need to do is just grovel
before my feet and serve.
Give me.
The head of the Karsten
family his crew Shake
our state and her attendant
the night Felix Argyle.
Should I become the new ruler?
I vow the dragon will forget.
It's demanded
Covenant the dragons Empire of
Lugunica
belongs not to that beast.
But to its people.
Miss Anastasia
who she of the ocean company
and her attendants
the night Julius Eucleas.
I'm a greedy little now,
so I want everything
no amount of commercials.
Have to satisfy me.
I want to have
my very own Nation.
Miss Amelia
and the man whose endorsing her
Hargrave Roswaal L. Mathers.
I have only one wish
equality for everyone.
I desire to create a nation
where all citizens are equal.
Stew after the very
formal and official sounding
introduction of all
those nights as attendance.
I must admit that I feel
terribly out of place here.
Finally.
Mrs. Felt on her.
Didn't the night
Reinhard van Astraia,
hang on
don't get the wrong idea.
I never said I wanted
to be the next ruler of this
stupid country to be in
a Royal selection Miss felt.
Do you actually wish to
withdraw from the selection?
What a joke, I've overlooked
this because the situation
was urgent but to drag
it out this long as senseless.
He has a point
the Astraia family offers
a gutter rat
to rule us while
Margrave Mathers endorses
a half devil utter foolishness.
No, let's mind our manners.
It's not nice to
call a half L something.
So cruel that silver hair cut.
Not just the appearance
of the witch of Envy
as it has been
described for many generations.
Now, why
do not realize that even
allowing her in
the throne room is Dreadful.
Filthy woman.
That's enough of your crap.
Subaru. It's
all right. Stop this.
No, I can't do that.
You people should be ashamed
of yourself. Apologize to her.
Allow me to
formally introduce myself
to the honored Council
of Elders.
My name is Amelia.
I'm accompanied by puck
a great spirit who controls fire
and I'm
a silver-haired half-elf.
I understand that my
half-elf lineage and other
similarities to the infamous
which subject me to Prejudice.
However,
I adamantly refused to let all
my potential be plucked
out Simply for that reason.
I will not falter.
Amelia.
By the way,
what exactly is the position
of the young man speaking out?
What's that? Oh,
It's okay Amelia.
I've made up
my mind to your mind to do.
What hold on a minute Subaru.
What do you think
you're doing stop?
It's nice to meet you members
of the Council of Elders.
My name is Subaru not ski.
Man serving in Roswaal's mansion
and I serve as this candidates.
I mean this Amelia's best night.
What's that a knight? Is he.
He continues to show us how
little he knows of our world.
Please forgive
this Interruption Council
my apologies, but there is
something I feel I must ask him.
What exactly are you saying?
When you Proclaim yourself to be
miss Emily as night.
And what's that supposed to mean
you just declared before
everyone that you're a night
and you did
so she audacious Lee and
without Reserve before
the nights of Lugunica.
That was a pretty
well coordinated move.
So did you guys practice
that just
for this meeting or what?
Of course we did to make
known the Dignity of our Empire.
We are highly conscious
every day of who we are
tell me do you feel you have
the resolve to match that?
I want to meet
Miss Amelia the next ruler.
No, I will do it and
you believe you have the resolve
and strength to do that,
which you boldly claim.
I may not have
anything as Grand as resolved
and I'm well aware
that I'm lacking strength.
Either way. Amelia will
be the ruler of this land.
I'm going to make her wish
come true. Do you not feel that?
Your answer is far too
arrogant you spoke of weakness.
That's something to
be ashamed of it's not
something
for you to take pride in.
Have you worked enough
to earn the right to stand
there as
a champion have you performed?
Formed enough service to shame
us the Imperial Knights
answer me.
Whatever. I'm still
going to make Amelia the ruler.
I don't understand.
After being so denied.
Why do you continue to
stand there? And two fires.
It's simple
it's because she's special.
I recognize and accept
your reason for standing.
However, I cannot
stand idly by and acknowledge
your claim as a night
when I know it's not true.
What do you mean?
Anyone inspiring such
an expression on the face
of one they wish to
stand beside is not a knight.
He's being
a knight that big a deal.
You just happen to
be born into the chop.
It's the luck of the draw.
Don't use
your daddy's name to act
like a big
shot about do not ski,
that is not a good one.
Quiet Subaru.
That's enough.
I am deeply sorry to
waste the council's time.
I'll make him stand down.
Miss Amelia if that young
man has done nothing else.
He has shown us all that you are
not one to be feared.
You have a fine attendant.
Thank you. However,
Subaru is not my attendant.
Mr. Subaru not ski,
please leave the room.
Now that orders
return to let us discuss how
the Royals
selection will proceed.
What's going on.
I don't know who you are,
but for stealing into
the castle,
you must be executing.
Unfortunately, I cannot comply.
Let me remind you that you are
publicly declared to have no
intention of participating
in the Royal selection
there by I am not
obligated to obey your orders.
I'll tell your stupid selection.
You just want me to try
to be the next ruler, don't you.
On a sec? What are you saying
felt that old man is my family.
So let him go right now
treat him with care very well.
Really.
Sorry felt.
I just wanted to
we'll talk later on. Okay,
Pretty sneaky Reinhard.
So this was all part
of your plan to I take it.
No certainly not miss. This was
something Guided by Fate itself.
This is me. You're
some kind of slave to fate.
Not at all. Tall from
now on I am your night.
Okay fine,
then I'll work you to death.
No Miss felt
and her night Reinhard.
May we conclude
that you both intend to
participate
in the Royal selection?
Sure, you can
Count Me In let me just say
one thing to you clowns.
I hate the nobility.
And I hate night. right.
I hate every last
thing about this damn place.
So I'm planning to tear
it all down to the ground.
How about that?
Wait, what are you saying?
If I become the next roller?
I'll destroy everything.
Do you think I'm kidding?
I'll take down every
single one of you and bring
a little fresh
air into this country.
Your mistress is quite
the intense lady Reinhard Miss
felt speaks
with conviction soon her.
I will be heard by all.
I see. In any case all
the candidates are here at last.
The Royal
selection will now begin.
The time has come
the Royal selection has
finally begun Subaru Hey
you Miss Amelia is nighttime.
Yeah, let's
both do our best for this.
Okay, forgive
me for interrupting.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I wish you wouldn't
make such an unpleasant face.
I didn't expect
you to warmly welcome me,
but if you take
that That attitude then if
I take that attitude,
then what the propriety of
those in your company
will come into question.
I would suggest
that you be careful.
Now that you ask me
why I'm here, correct.
I came to see you. Of course.
I'd like you to
come with me for a bit.
There's something rather
important we need to discuss.
Julius you shouldn't do this.
It's not like you he insulted.
Knights directly in
front of the candidates
to be our future ruler.
He also made
light of the chivalry.
We dutifully
practice I admit he said
some things
that went a bit too far,
but to take proper
measures for such a matter.
He need only
be warned and corrected.
Proper sorry,
but this is not only my problem.
I administer the death
penalty to this insubordinate
man who solely
the Knighthood daughter.
Now it wouldn't
be unusual for you to be
slain for such insolence.
However much to my
dismay you are missing
me and he has attempted.
Therefore. We will
fight using wooden swords.
Right Shall We Begin you got it,
but I warn
you I won't hold back.
As expected it appears.
You truly have no Pride what
a simple and vulgar way to live.
Withholding the night Julius
and Mr. Subaru not skier having
a mock battle with wooden
swords in the training ring.
There's just one thing.
I want to know which one
of them issued the challenge.
Do you have any idea I'm
told it was the night Julius.
Mr. Subaru not ski
accepted the challenge
leading to this
fight kind of figured.
Well, I'm against
stopping them then hold on
your night and my
um friend are fighting
aren't you the least bit
worried about what might happen
worried seriously about
what the Julie is takes things
too far, and I'll have to pay
for your boys medical treatment
if we're questioning the Dilemma
of their mock battle.
Well, I can't agree with
stopping it before they finish
either if they're just
duking it out you could have
waited until it ended
and simply told us who won.
Yes, ma'am.
But the fight was well,
it was just so
one-sided that I never stop it.
We should go to after all.
You like
watching weak creatures being
tormented
by a vicious Beast don't
you misjudge me with your own
unfounded imaginings Al.
Yes, you know I do.
Do why don't you stop
this self-torturing admit
that you've reached her limit.
I'm sure you've now
realized what painful extent
just nights that you insulted
and made light of really are.
I believe continuing
would endanger your life.
I'm gonna break. The nose
of yours. I'll Crush you.
This was the ace up your sleeve.
Sure skill level is far
too poultry such low level
magic will only work on
unintelligent Beasts, boy.
You aren't worthy
to stand at her side.
You are irredeemably powerless.
So I didn't die then.
Subaru that talk with
the Royal candidates Subaru.
I see let's head straight back.
Then. We need to work out
a plan for the selection. Sorry.
Let's talk. Okay. I have
some things I want to ask you.
Many things actually.
Yeah, I guess you do.
Tell me. Why did you end
up? Well fighting with Julius.
I mean there must have
been a reason right knowing you.
I'm sure it was very important.
Wanted to get him
back for what he said.
I was being stubborn.
He said I was pathetic
powerless and not worthy of you.
He was trying to distance me
from you and I hated him for it.
That's why I fought him.
Really just for that.
It's true.
Melee.
And I know that you don't
understand. I see.
Roswell and
I have made arrangements to
head back
to the mansion tomorrow.
You will remain here
in the capital to recover.
Wait a minute.
That was
our agreement wasn't it?
Yeah, but hang on
Earth came to the capital.
So Felix could
heal your exhausted gate.
I was very clear about this. No,
wait a minute.
How can you suddenly.
Because.
When I'm with you?
Do you always push yourself
to do impossible things?
Wait? No, hold on.
That's not what I'm saying.
I just wanted you wanted
what was let me finish.
I just wanted to try and
do something important for you.
Is that right for me?
It was for you, wasn't it?
No it was for you. I swear.
You said that to me
so many times stop telling
lies about how
everything is for my sake.
So coming to the castle
fighting Julius and using magic.
Are you trying to
say that was all for me
why I never
ask you to do any of that.
Now think back. Do you remember
what I asked you to do?
Really?
I let me remind you.
I asked you to stay
behind to the lodging with REM.
I asked you specifically not to
use magic because using anymore.
Would endanger human I'm sorry.
I didn't do as you asked.
It was a mistake,
but you're wrong about
my reasons you're wrong.
Honestly, it wasn't for myself.
Please believe me.
I say that but you won't
believe me. Will you I want to.
I want to believe
you Subaru very much.
With every choice
you make you show me.
I have no reason to.
You made a promise to me, but
you threw it away just like
that and came all the way here.
Despite what you swore to me.
You won't keep
your soul about to me your word
and yet
you ask me to believe you.
I can't do that. I can't.
I still don't understand.
Why do you keep
trying to help me like this.
Because of the many
times that you helped me.
Wait. I helped you. Yes,
that's right.
You don't even realize
how the things you've done
for me if
saved me over and over.
No, sir.
I don't
and I don't expect you to
but it's the truth
you seek me time and time again.
So every last thing
I've done is been to repay
you for your kindness.
I love you.
Maybe you don't I totally
get that but please listen to me
cuz it's the absolute truth.
It was you when
I first came to this world.
You were the one who saved me.
It appears that once again,
you won't tell me anything.
Why won't you understand
what I'm going through?
I thought if anyone
would be able to understand
everything
that's happening to me you.
The version of me that lives
within you must be amazing.
She understands
all of your thoughts.
Even if you don't
explain them to her.
She can feel all your pain
and all of your sadness
as well as
your anger is her very young.
I can't understand.
If you don't tell me Subaru.
Everything.
Everything has been thrown.
Everything that we both face
it all worked out next to me.
Didn't it? When
your Insignia was stolen?
I saved you from an insane
killer at the Lewis house.
I risk my life for
you all because you are
important
to me at the Mansion to
it works out because of
what I did without me there.
We have been a whole lot worse.
Oh all of it all of it,
you are saved
because I was there for you.
Don't you see
you should have a greater
density
than you could ever repay.
Yes.
You're right.
All of these debts
that I owe you so many
they piled up haven't they?
Yeah, that's right.
So do you get
it now then I'll repay
all of them This Moment.
By ending.
You've done
enough Subaru not ski,
You know I had
such high hopes for him.
Thought maybe you only
you wouldn't give me the special
treatment that surrounded
me my entire life and that maybe
he would look at me
in the exact same way.
You look at everyone else.
I'm sorry, I can't do that.
Absolutely no way
I can look at you the same way
I look at other people.
It's impossible.