[music playing]
Subaru: It was
a most fearsome battle.
[chain rattles]
[squelch]
We had all been cursed
by a mysterious force...
[growling]
After experiencing
invasion after invasion
by a herd of ulgarm...
I engaged in mortal combat
with their powerful leader.
[roar echoing]
At last, a well-deserved time
of peace had finally come.
With the looming threat
of those monstrous,
savage beasts eliminated,
the entire village
was saved for good.
But...
a mission still remains,
one that is top secret
and must be executed perfectly
without being noticed
by anyone...
scouting out a course
for my date with Mili.
- Look! It's Subaru!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- And why are you
dressed up like that?
- No! I've already failed!
- [laughing]
- Recognized just three seconds
into my mission!
- What's a "mission," anyway?
- What does "top secret" mean?
- Come on!
- Think I just peed my pants!
- Can't you see
I'm busy right now! Go away!
You better not butt in during
the actual date! You hear me?!
- So what's a "date"?
I've never heard of that before.
- A date
is a secret, awesome time
of pleasurable embarrassment
for two people who are in love!
MILDO: What's
"pleasurable embarrassment"?
Well, we've got
a cool secret, too, you know!
- Yeah! It's that way!
- Hey! Now hang on a second,
all right?!
Mind givin' me
a hand here, Petra?
DYNE: Come on!
- Come on, Subaru!
- Hmph!
- Wait. Why are you
making that face?
MILDO: You're too slow!
Hurry up! Over here!
- [wind blowing]
- [leaves fluttering]
DYNE: Welcome
to our secret place.
- Wow! This is so amazing.
[birds chirping]
This is bizarre.
Just look at this flower, Ram.
RAM: What could have happened?
They just bloomed recently.
ROSWAAL: Oh, my.
What's all this?
RAM: Master Roswaal.
- With the royal selection
now upon us,
this timing
is most unfortunate.
It appears
that something quite troubling
has found its way here.
[wind gusting]
- Huh?
[frost crackling]
[heart beating]
[chorus vocalizes]
[Subaru screams]
[panting]
[sighs]
It was just a dream.
- Is something the matter,
Subaru?
- I'm fine. Thank you, Rem.
Hang on a minute!
What are you doing in my room?!
- I have some time
before my work begins,
so I was just gazing
at your face.
It's to help get my spirits up.
- What does that mean, exactly?
- Anyway, what were
you dreaming about?
- It's the sort of thing
that would become real
if I were to tell you,
so just forget it.
[shivers] Aw, man.
It's kind of chilly today, huh?
- It is, yes. This morning
does seem unusually brisk.
How very perceptive of you,
Subaru.
- Uh, anyone could tell
that it's cold right now.
[lid rattling]
I mean, yesterday
it was so hot outside
that I couldn't stop sweating
the whole day,
so I'd say this is
one heck of a temperature drop.
Don't you have
a uniform for cold weather?
'Cause you've gotta be
freezing in that thing.
- When the Glacial Period
starts in earnest,
then I'll begin wearing
my outfit for the cold.
It's made from a thick fabric
and lined with heavy cotton,
so it's very cozy.
- Hmm.
Wouldn't you be better off
in your "Glacial Period" outfit
for times like these?
If you don't feel comfortable
bringing it up,
I have no problem
asking Roz about it for you.
- Don't worry. My sister and I
are used to this.
It's nothing worth
troubling Master Roswaal over.
- Okay, then. If you say
you'll be all right...
Uh, so where
is your sister, anyway?
- She said it was a bit
too shivery to get out of bed,
so she decided
to sleep in a little.
- Didn't you just tell me
that you were both
used to weather like this?!
Well, I've heard enough!
We gotta go up there
and tell her
that live-in servants
don't get to sleep late,
regardless of what the
temperature might be outside!
- [door opens]
- Come on, Rem!
- But she's exhausted from
her daily responsibilities,
so I don't think
some extra sleep would really--
- Come on, Rem!
- Right! If you insist, Subaru.
[broom sweeping]
[Ram groans]
[grunts]
Just look at all the dust
that you missed. Now try again.
You truly are useless, Barusu.
- Listen, I know you didn't
like being dragged out of bed,
but how long are you
planning on holding a grudge?
Stop being mad, already.
[yelps]
Huh?
Ram, look.
I think I found a secret door.
Do you have any idea
what's in there?
- Not at all.
[floorboard rattling]
Stop that, Barusu.
What if a swarm of bugs
flies out the moment it opens?
You should wait until I've left
the room and locked the door.
- And why would you
need to lock it?
Anyway, it's too late
for that right now.
[gasps]
Oh, man.
This looks
like quite a collection.
So is all of it alcohol?
- Come to think of it,
I've heard stories
about Master Roswaal's
grandmother
being a rather heavy drinker.
I would bet they've been
down here for a while, then.
- Whoa.
Since Roz's granny was around?
It's hard to even picture that.
But if this stuff
really is that old,
then it's gotta be worth
a fortune by now, right?
- I know you struggle
with everything,
but you mustn't drink them
without permission, Barusu.
- I wasn't gonna!
EMILIA: Oh.
Subaru! Ram!
- Eh?
- I wondered what
those rummaging noises were.
I guess it was you two.
- [gasps]
[joyful] Hello, Mili!
- So what are you both
doing in here, huh?
- I was warning Barusu that no
matter how painful his life is,
alcohol is never the answer.
- Oh, really?
Subaru, if you
were suffering that much,
then you should have told me.
- No! You've got it all wrong!
I'm not drinking away
my problems.
In fact, I'm still underage,
so I'm too young
to do that, anyway!
I still have a hard time
getting on adult websites.
- That's strange.
I don't think I've ever heard
of one of those before.
But anyway, here in Lugunica,
the legal drinking age
is 15 years old.
- What?
- Incidentally,
if getting
on these adult websites
is something
that's important to you,
I'll do what I can to help you
with it as much as possible.
- You're the sweetest! E.M.A.!
Emilia, major angel! [laughs]
But an angel like you shouldn't
be saying stuff like that.
Uh, by the way, Mili,
do you like drinking?
A tipsy version of you
would be adorable!
- Sorry. I'm not quite sure
what you're saying,
but if it's about alcohol,
I've never had it before.
- That's too bad!
With drinks, our date tomorrow
would be more
like the kind adults go on.
A glass or two, some flow--
Whoops. Don't wanna spoil
the surprise, now, do I?
- [gasps]
That's right.
Tomorrow's our date, isn't it?
- Yup! And I can't tell you
how excited I am!
I'll get up early
and pack lunch for us, okay?!
- Oh, really?
I'll look forward to that, then!
- Hope the sun comes out
and it gets warmer.
- [giggles]
- And speaking of the weather,
aren't you cold in that outfit?
- Huh? Uh, no, I don't
feel cold in the slightest!
If anything, it's quite toasty.
- Is everything all right?
You're acting kinda weird.
- Well, I have some things
I need to take care of.
They came up really suddenly.
Bye!
[whoosh]
- [scoffs] The things
she needs to do
are simply trivial matters
and not even worth mentioning.
So in other words,
you mean even less to her
than those, Barusu.
- What?! No.
Uh, it's more like, you know,
she's probably
so excited about our date
that she's feeling
all flustered now and can't--
[wind blowing]
[grunts]
Canteen, check.
Bread basket, check.
Date schedule, check.
Handkerchief, check.
Lucky boxers, check.
And...
Got the alarm all set.
Perfect.
[grunts]
[sighs]
No use. I can't sleep.
All right, in that case...
There's one Puck
and two Pucks
and three Pucks...
Wait. I'm getting
some intense déjà vu.
This has
definitely happened before.
It was the night
that I was cursed.
I can't use Puck, then!
Talk about bad luck.
So in that case...
There's one Mili
and two Milis
and three Milis.
It's fantastic!
[groans] But I've
done this before, too!
It's time for me to innovate,
take things in a new direction.
One Roswaal and two Roswaals
and three Roswaals
and four Ros...
[sighs]
How is our date
even gonna have a chance
if it's still this cold outside?
I'm really hoping
the flower field that Petra
and the other kids showed me
hasn't died already.
No. The weather
will be nice tomorrow.
It'll be fine.
I've gotta believe that.
[organ music playing]
- [alarm ringtone playing]
- Eh?
It's freezing!
We'll die in this!
[door creaks]
Feels like
it's gotten even colder
than it was just yesterday,
so what's going on here?
Huh?
- Beatrice?
- [gasps]
- Why are you up
this early in the morning?
- N-No reason at all!
Stop snooping, I suppose!
- Anyway, it's insanely cold.
- Hmph!
- I have a date with Mili today,
but do I even have a shot
if it's like this?
- I wouldn't know
anything about that.
And besides,
I'm exceptionally busy,
so I have no time
to play around, I suppose.
- Well, it's not as if I was
asking you to play with me.
Regardless,
it's easy to catch a cold
when the seasons change,
so be careful--
- I'm not so weak
that I need someone like you
to worry about me.
- Oh, no, it's not you.
It's Rem I'd feel bad for
if you were to get sick.
She'd have to make you porridge,
and then she might
not be able to find you at all.
So if you come down with
something, try and behave, okay?
- Now, why should I
be criticized
over a hypothetical story
with a hypothetical ending,
I suppose?!
In any case, I'm very busy,
so don't make me
repeat myself, I suppose!
- Buon giorno!
- So the date you were looking
forward to with Miss Emilia
had to be canceled?
- Not canceled, just postponed.
This nasty weather
would have ruined it, anyway.
And she said...
- Good idea! Mm, I agree!
I think we should postpone it!
It's so cold after all!
I know you've been really
excited about the whole thing
and I made
a promise to you, but--
Oh! Of course, it's not only
because I promised you I'd go.
In fact, I was sort of
looking forward to it myself,
but if it's this chilly,
then we don't have a choice.
- Though it kinda bugs me
that she came off
as just a little bit relieved
about the whole thing, you know?
- I think
it was a wise decision.
If you two found yourself
stranded out there
and the worst happened...
- It's not like we're
on some snowy mountaintop.
Wait a minute!
Maybe that's what this is!
- What what is?
- We get trapped in a blizzard
and take shelter in a hut,
where we keep each other warm
with our body heat!
A pleasurably
embarrassing situation!
- Right! I understand!
You can count on me
to keep you warm!
- Think you've got this story's
characters mixed up!
But still,
it's not like a blizzard
would hit so suddenly.
Besides, there's no way
it's gonna get that cold.
- [laughs]
- [slush crunches]
Uh...
it just made a crunching sound.
- Yes. It would seem
that some of the water
in the bucket has frozen.
- Huh?
- [ice crackling]
- [sputtering]
[wood creaking]
Okay, something's
obviously going on here!
- [cup rattling]
- [shivering]
- I'm sorry! I should have
come to help warm you up,
but there was no way that I
could leave my sister alone.
- W-Were you
k-keeping each other warm?
J-Just imagining that
has b-brought
my body temperature up
by about th-three degrees.
ROSWAAL: Oh, my, Subaru!
You don't seem well.
Whatever is the matter?
- Well, what do you think?!
It's super freakin' cold!
This goes beyond
natural climate extremes!
- Goodness, I didn't think
you had such a faint heart.
If you keep your mind and body
in optimal condition,
you'll find you can remain
calm, no matter how cool it--
- That's not very convincing
coming from someone
dressed
in as many layers as you!
I'll develop homicidal
tendencies at this rate!
[sputters]
- [sneezes]
- I see.
Yes, we may indeed
be reaching our limit.
- The way you just said that,
do you know
more than you're letting on?
If it's General Winter
causing this,
let's go defeat him,
like, as soon as possible!
Help me out, Sensei! [sneezes]
- Do you have
a rather difficult time
handling
the cold weather, then?
- I complain when it
gets cold in the winter
and then in the summer
when it gets too hot,
also when
I'm sleepy in spring
and when matsutake mushrooms
are expensive in the fall,
like any other ordinary person,
you know?
[sneezes]
- Curious about the outside?
- Well, yeah, of course I am.
If it's snowing, I'm worried
about the village fields
and how they'll
clear it all away.
- You are indeed quite convivial
with the villagers,
especially the little children,
aren't you?
- Just by chance, though.
I don't actually
like kids very much.
As far as I'm concerned,
they're too selfish
and impulsive.
But they like me,
so I don't have much choice.
- Right, right.
I believe this is
what you call tsundere.
- Sniffle!
Aah! My nose is killing me!
Sniffle, sniffle!
Oh, man, this sucks!
- Don't worry!
I'll be right here
to take care
of all your sniffles for you.
- Anyway, you can rest easy.
This chill isn't affecting
the villagers.
It is only occurring
around the mansion.
- Hang on! How in the hell
is that even possible?
- We have two beings here
who are working hard
to ensure that it doesn't
spread beyond this domain.
- Does he mean...
- It certainly
isn't my sister and me.
- I guess that narrows it down,
then, doesn't it?
- That, it does.
So when it comes
to what's causing all of this,
it would seem you don't need
further explanation.
Miss Emilia, forgive me
for the early disturbance.
Do you have a moment to spare?
EMILIA: Roswaal?!
I, um--
Hold on! Just a minute, okay?
- Go ahead, then.
- [grunts]
[yelps] What the hell?!
It's freezing!
Are you okay in there, Mili?
EMILIA: Huh? Wait!
Subaru's there, too?!
- Yeah, I am, but that
isn't the issue right now.
Don't you have
something else to say?!
EMILIA: Let's see.
I, uh...
Right. G-Good morning!
- Hmm, hmm.
What a good, classic,
polite greeting that was.
Wait! Never mind that!
I'm opening the door!
And if you happen
to be changing, thank you!
EMILIA: Don't you mean,
"Sorry"?!
- [wind gusting]
- [gasps]
It's freezing!
What the hell
is going on in here?!
- Y-You shouldn't
barge into someone's room
before they've given you
permission to do so!
You're being very rude!
[gasps] Yes! Incredibly rude!
You know, I mean...
you should--
Just start over, okay?!
- All right, then,
that would be Mili's suggestion,
but does the mansion's owner
have anything else to say?
- You may enter if you wish.
- Hey, Roswaal!
- Now what's the cause
of this intense weather?
- Cause? Wh-What do you
mean by "cause"?
It's not like it's a--
I mean, it's not--
well, not quite "not."
I don't know!
PUCK: It's okay, Lia.
At this point, I don't think
it'd be possible
for us to hide this, anyway.
[sighs] Puck,
you aren't any help at all.
And right when I
almost had him convinced.
- Yeah, another hundred years
wouldn't have gotten you
closer to that.
- Huh?
- [sighs] I'm really sorry,
'cause I'm the one
who's causing the trouble.
Don't be upset
with Lia or Betty, okay?
I mean, after all,
those two have just been
trying to look out for me.
SUBARU: Okay, so I'm confused.
What's a magic release period?
Like your mating season?
PUCK: I'm not an animal,
you know.
Spirits don't even
have those, anyway.
How rude of you.
- I have no idea
how to respond to that.
- The magic release period
is a phenomenon
that occurs
in those with powerful magic.
The strength of one's magic
is affected
by the nature of their od,
and that makes it
highly restrictive.
When you say "od," do you
mean something different
from magic and gates
and all that other stuff?
- I question your common sense
if you don't even know
that much.
You're as simpleminded
as they come, Barusu.
- Man, you're even
more demeaning than usual today.
Can't handle the cold, huh?
- Weaknesses and strengths,
Either way,
it's all quite subjective.
And I refuse
to look at the world
in such a narrow manner.
Don't say things to make you
feel better about yourself.
Just die.
SUBARU: Well,
that escalated quickly!
- We'll never get anywhere
if we leave the explanation
up to you two, I suppose.
It's rather obvious to me
that I'll have
to take over from here.
So od is a vessel for magic,
and its purpose is to store
magic taken in through a gate.
- Oh, cool. It sounds
like a magic container.
Continue. Go on.
- The way you said that
irritates me.
Anyway,
the stronger one's od is,
the more magic
one can use, I suppose.
But every container has a limit
to how much it can hold.
And when one's od
reaches its limit,
the accumulated magic
overflows from it,
so it must be released
before that happens.
SUBARU: Being full
and wanting to get rid
of what's inside
before exploding?
- [sips]
- Oh, like constipation.
- [wails]
Choose better words, I suppose!
- Think I got it.
So this entire thing
is just the result of Puck
letting out some excess mana.
- Yes, that's exactly right.
I'm sorry for not telling you.
- Pretty extreme way
to relieve being backed up.
Does this happen to you
very often?
- I'd say twice a year or so.
Back when I lived
in the forest with Lia,
I was able
to release it at any time,
but since coming here, I've had
to tone it down a little bit,
so I guess this is
the backlash from that.
- [giggles]
- Don't "hee hee hee hee" me!
I can't complain
if releasing your magic
is something you have to do,
but I'm still having trouble
understanding why things
became so intense this quickly.
- At first, I just let out
a little at a time,
but I had quite a bit more mana
stored up than I usually do,
and no one said anything
when it got cold, so I thought,
"Maybe I can get away
with a little more.
"Yes! I definitely can!
Good thing
they're simple-minded."
And here we are!
- SUBARU: What a sloppy job!
- [Puck chuckles]
- For a great spirit
as powerful as Bubby,
this is something that he
can never truly be rid of.
Out of consideration
for how cute and fluffy he is,
you should stop
overreacting like this and...
SUBARU: See?
You're sniffling, too.
And since you figured you'd be
in trouble if you were caught,
I bet you were
trying to put up a barrier
to seal in the cold,
now, weren't you?
And I want you
to be honest with me.
- [snorts]
- Look! She's blowing her nose!
- I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
Listen. As for Puck and me,
we truly feel awful
for letting things
get out of hand like this.
Sorry. But the magic release
period should be over soon.
Right, Puck? Tell them.
- Yeah! With the way
things are heading now,
two more days
should be more than enough.
- Well, if you
keep on going at this rate,
you're gonna find
Ram's frozen body and mine
rolling around the mansion.
And what about you, Mili?
Aren't you freezing
in those clothes?
Because I wanna see the ones
you have for the wintertime.
- Actually, you know
how I have a contract
with Puck and all,
don't you?
Due to that, his magic
influences me differently,
so I can adjust it.
And that means...
even with all
this extreme weather, I...
am completely fine.
Don't you feel a little bad
about putting your daughter
in such a tough spot?
I think we should try
and come up with a plan.
[gasps]
That's it! There's no need
for the rest of us
to stay inside the mansion!
Beako's keeping the cold
contained with her barrier,
so we can just stay outside
until this whole thing
blows over.
- Impressive as always, Subaru!
You have all my respect!
- Plus, this time of year,
the weather's mild, so we--
BEATRICE:
Doesn't seem like it'll be
letting up soon, I suppose.
SUBARU: Come on!
EMILIA: I don't think
we can camp out in this.
- No! If you all have a tent--
- Now, Subaru,
am I somehow mistaken,
or are you suggesting that I,
the master of this mansion,
sleep outside?
- W-w-well, uh...
isn't there something you
can do with your magic, then?
Like maybe mustering up
a fireball or something
and then blasting it at Puck to
regulate his temperature, huh?
- That degree of control
would be difficult.
One incorrect movement
of my hand,
and the mansion
would be engulfed in fire.
- Man! Why does it feel
like our only choices
are a flood from above
or a fire from below?
Wait! That's it!
A flood above us
and a fire below!
- What are you saying?
- It's a riddle that I remember
hearing from back home!
And the answer is a bath!
In other words, the best way
to beat the cold is...
- What is it? Tell me!
- To use the magic stones
of fire we have
to boil the water
in the big bath!
Then...
for the next two days, we'll...
stay in a hot spring!
What do you say?!
- Impressive as always, Subaru!
You have all my respect!
- Unfortunately,
we can't do that.
- What? Why?!
- Is all of this mayonnaise?
- Yes. I've been
making this for you,
since I know
how very fond of it you are.
Remember last time?
[camera shutter clicking]
- [groaning]
- I didn't make
as much as you wanted,
and you ended up
getting pretty angry with me.
So this time,
I used the big bath!
[giggles] If you wish
to praise me now, I won't mind.
- How could you be that stupid?!
- [gasps] Oh, no! You're right!
The mayonnaise has frozen!
- No! Not that!
- But worry not, Subaru!
We can boil it into
a nice, warm mayonnaise bath!
- If you do that,
you're gonna earn the wrath
of every mayo lover
in the world!
It still feels cold
right here next to the fire.
PUCK: But if
it weren't for this,
everyone in the mansion
would be frozen solid.
Wanna test it out?
- Yeah, how 'bout
we don't do that?
Instead of releasing magic
slowly over the next two days,
can't you just unleash it
in one massive blast
and be done with it?
- In that case, does it mean
you plan on giving me...
the permission
to destroy everything
and everyone
living in this world?
SUBARU: That would be a no!
- I was just kidding.
- So, anyway,
does this magic release thing
only happen to spirits,
or do you and Beako
go through it, too?
- In my case, I use my magic
on a daily basis,
which keeps it
well regulated.
My duties require that,
after all.
[Ram moans]
- Uh...
- So my od always
has plenty of leeway.
- Why did you look at Ram
when you said that?
- [sighs]
- SUBARU: Uh, you know what?
Never mind. I don't wanna know.
- I maintain
the forbidden library
and use my Door Crossing,
I suppose.
Oh, right.
And recently, smacking away
a certain noisy human
has been helping also.
- Yeah, yeah. Very cute.
- [growls]
- So what about
the two of you, then?
Don't you have a mating--
uh, I mean, have
a magic release period, too?
- Only certain people with
really powerful magic have them.
For most, it's something
that isn't necessary.
- I'm not a particularly strong
magic user, either,
so I've also
never had to have one.
Oh, but still, I have experience
from dealing with Puck's,
so I'm sorry
about what happened this time.
I feel awful.
- [thinking] Man, Mili's really
beating herself up today.
Well, how about you?
When was the last time
that you got to use
a good amount of magic, Puck?
Just for a reference.
- Hmm. The last time, huh?
It was probably when I fought
that lady in black
in the capital.
I actually ran out of mana then.
SUBARU: I really hope
you're not askin' me
to bring you
another opponent that insane!
I don't wanna be
forced to choose
between being disemboweled
and freezing to death!
- And I think before that
was when Roswaal
came to the forest
to pick up Lia.
It's kind of
embarrassing to say,
but I think I caused
quite a fuss back then.
- Ah, yes. It was
an exhilarating experience.
That was
the very first time in my life
I had participated
in such a large-scale magic war.
At least, I think so!
- You just came
right at me without warning.
I couldn't believe it. [laughs]
ROSWAAL: Indeed. We spent
the full day and night
clashing in earnest.
SUBARU: So what exactly
happened there, Mili?
EMILIA: Afterwards,
I heard they had to redraw
the maps for that area.
SUBARU: Nope! Don't like that!
Operation Pitting Friends
Against Each Other
- is hereby rejected!
- PUCK: Aww.
- Don't give me that!
No changing the geography
by fighting!
Apologize to Ino Tadataka!
PUCK: I am so sorry,
Mr. Tadataka!
Was that okay?
- [sighs] Right now,
our first priority should be
keeping the fire going.
- I really am sorry about this.
When Puck and I
lived in the forest,
there was no one around
to worry about,
so I never realized it could be
this big of a problem.
- Stop. You don't need
to keep on apologizing, okay?
'Cause I can
figure somethin' out.
Every night breaks into dawn.
There's no rain
that doesn't cease!
[rain pattering]
Oh, yeah. The rain.
A little later on tonight,
it's gonna turn to snow.
But even in the daylight,
the weather's so cold,
that'll happen.
- Subaru? Did you just come up
with another strange idea?
- Impressive as always, Subaru!
You have all my respect!
- Listen, you guys
are jumpin' the gun here,
and that's too much respect.
But, yes, I do have an idea,
a way to get through
all this peacefully,
and we can even turn
this magic release period
into something
we can actually enjoy!
- So what is it
you're planning, exactly?
- Back in my homeland,
Hokkaido...
though I do use "homeland"
in a very broad sense here...
we had an amazing festival!
Since Puck's got mana to burn,
we might as well
put it to good use!
We'll call it...
the Roswaal Mansion's
first Wild and Crazy...
Snow Festival! [chuckles]
- Impressive as always, Subaru!
- [gasps]
A Wild and Crazy
Snow Festival, huh?
SUBARU: I know.
Awesome, isn't it?
- [Rem swoons]
- Since you seem so into it...
EMILIA: Is the "wild and crazy"
part necessary?
SUBARU: All right!
Let's get to work!
[music playing]
SUBARU: The driving snow
has enveloped the mansion
and our hearts as well!
A blanket of pure white
as far as the eye can see!
But just as every night
breaks into dawn,
every snow
will eventually cease!
Bid farewell to the frozen sky,
and welcome
our out-of-season Snow Festival!
Now let's go to New York!
Ready?!
- New York?
- [murmuring]
- Huh?
- CHILDREN: Yeah!
- We'll all go to New York,
no matter what it takes!
Are you excited?!
VILLAGERS: Yeah!
- But where is this place?
- It's a big town
back where Subaru's from.
- He said it's "swirling
with love and desire"!
- Yeah! Swirling!
- The rules are simple.
Each of you will try to build
the most unique
and imaginative snow sculpture.
And of course
we have a fantastic prize
for the winner, too!
MILDO: Will we get
to go to New York?
- I'm sorry,
but that'd be impossible.
Don't you worry, though,
'cause I promise it's a prize
that's just as amazing
as a trip out there!
Okay, everyone,
do your best, all right?!
VILLAGERS: Yeah!
[villagers murmuring]
- I never would have
even thought
about putting on
a snow festival here.
- I just figured
that if we couldn't hide it,
then we should all
find a way to celebrate it.
- [chuckles] I'll work hard
to beat the band and
make a fantastic sculpture!
- Nobody says, "Beat the band"
in this day in age.
[villagers murmuring]
- Eh?
Aha! I found you!
Man, this worked out
really great,
and we never
could have done it if you
hadn't adjusted the range
of your barrier for us.
- Honestly, this is
all such a big fuss.
I should have expanded it
a little further
so they could have
their festival
in the village, I suppose.
- That would have been
pretty disastrous
for the village, though...
and even more so
for my first date with Mili.
It would completely ruin
the secret flower garden,
you know?
- I do know. But I also
don't care about that at all.
- Anyway, Beako, don't you want
to come join in on the fun?
There's no need to be shy.
- And just who is being shy,
I suppose?
I'm very busy right now.
Shoo! Shoo!
- [sighs] Come on.
Don't be like that.
Everyone should play outside
now and then,
'specially when it
comes to children.
- [shrieks]
- Buenos Aires!
[snow crunches]
- Hey! Look, it's Subaru!
- Yeah! Where did he come from?!
- Have a taste
of my fearsome strike!
- [children laughing]
- Even in this cold,
you guys have so much energy.
However...
you'll soon come to realize...
that the ones
in danger from snow
were all of you
right from the beginning.
PUCK: There!
- [laughing]
- Want another one?
What do you say?
- Absolutely not!
- Hey, Subaru,
look at what I made.
And I did it
all by myself, too!
- Oh, wow. It's a snow bunny!
- [laughs]
It's really cute, isn't it?
So do you think
I did a good job?
- Yeah, you sure did!
- But how about this?
- Huh?
Let's make it even fancier!
Check this out.
- Wow! Look what you did!
It's just like
a real-life bunny rabbit!
- Just seeing you so happy makes
me feel pretty pumped up, too.
All right, then!
How 'bout we really
take this thing
to the next level, huh?
We'll give it
a tail and wings...
- PETRA: Huh?
- and missiles
a transformation ability,
a cockpit,
and caterpillar tracks.
PETRA: Wait a minute!
J-Just hold on!
- How's that?!
The flying assault form
of the ultra-firepower weapon...
BUN-E of snow!
- [shrieks]
- [groans]
- [huffs]
- Well, I guess Petra's
more into real robots
than super ones.
- [children laughing]
- Hey, check it out.
- Honestly, he simply
can't help himself, I suppose.
- I think that Subaru
just wants you to go
and play with him, Betty.
Actually, I was kinda
hoping you'd do that, too.
- Bubby.
[Subaru and children chatter]
- [sighs]
- Over here!
[wind blowing]
[chuckles]
- [muttering]
- [gasps]
Oh, Beatrice.
- Bubby insisted I do this,
I suppose,
so I'll be joining you
for a little bit.
You should be grateful,
I suppose.
- [chuckles]
Just know I don't plan to lose.
[snow crunching]
[villagers chatting]
- Their sculptures really
seem to be coming together.
- They are.
Although I gotta admit,
it is a bit of a letdown
that they're all
leaning toward realism.
There's no pop culture here,
so I guess it makes sense
it's mostly castles and animals.
Ah. Oh, hey there.
This one looks really...
nice?
- Thank you.
I appreciate that, Subaru.
This ulgarm is my best work.
- Is this saying
that once it swallows you,
you'll forget what warmth is?!
' Cause that isn't funny!
I like art that makes an impact,
and I can tell you put in
lots of effort,
but because it shows
a strong lack of consideration
for your judge,
I can only give it seven points!
- All right. I think
it's looking pretty good.
[gasps]
Wait! That's cheating!
Hey! You know
you shouldn't do that.
- I don't remember seeing
a rule written anywhere
stating that I can't.
- It's not right.
No magic allowed, okay?
You should never cheat.
You have to use your own hands
to grasp victory.
- [groans]
Hmph.
- [giggles]
- [all gasping]
- Look at this one.
- What a beautiful sight.
This is the best.
- By the way, I'm curious
about the sculpture scoring.
Who's in charge
of deciding all that?
- There's me and Roswaal...
and then there's Muraosa,
who's our secret judge.
I figured if they knew
who the judges were,
some people
might resort to bribery
or making under-the-table deals
to make sure they win.
- Do you think
someone would go that far
to nab the prize
you're offering?
- Totally. It's a top-tier,
gorgeous, one-of-a-kind item,
and I'll be
presenting it myself.
- Oh, wow. This wasn't even
your problem in the first place.
You're really generous,
aren't you?
- Other than you,
it's Mili who's dealing
with the most, right?
So of course I'm helping out.
- Ah. As far
as I'm concerned, Subaru,
I think that part of you
is really, you know.
- No, I don't know.
You said a bunch of words,
but none of them
meant much of anything.
- Is that so?
- Subaru, please come
take a look at this.
My sister and I have constructed
this sculpture together.
- I didn't know
you two were participating.
I thought you were
just helping out.
- No, Barusu.
Our supreme artistic sense
must have brought you
toward us both instinctually.
- I'm not sure how I feel
about you treating me
like a moth drawn to a flame,
but show me.
What convinced you to take part
in a freezing-cold
snow festival, anyway, Ram?
- You expected me
to just rot in bed
while Rem and the others
were outside
having an enjoyable time
in the snow?
- That was
an awfully bitter response.
But I suppose that means
you didn't want
to be left out, right?
- I so earnestly wished
to have a little fun with Ram
that I asked her to join me.
- Don't you feel
at least sort of guilty
for making your little sister
beg like that?
- I admit her love gives me
quite the superiority complex,
so go ahead and envy me.
- [sighs]
What is it?
- Now presenting...
our finest work
displaying our strength,
artistic talent,
and sisterly love.
- That's right. And with my
sister's spectacular direction,
I produced
the best work I could.
SUBARU: Pretty sure
you just casually admitted
she didn't do anything!
So what are you
calling your sculpture?
REM: We've titled it "A Statue
of the Magnificent Subawaal."
SUBARU: Well, I can tell
where this is going.
REM: Take a look!
[music playing]
My sister wanted the sculpture
to be of Master Roswaal,
but I wanted it
to be of you, Subaru.
RAM: After searching
for a compromise,
this is the solution we reached.
SUBARU: The only thing you've
compromised is my happiness!
- My, how very interesting.
For what reason
have the three of you
gathered out here together?
And what might this be?
- Uh, Master Roswaal,
I'm quite embarrassed,
but please do take
a good look at it.
- It's what we
worked on together.
But please don't hold back.
We'd like to hear
your unbiased opinion.
[both stammering]
- Okay. Then sorry,
but I can only
give you five points.
- Out of five, right?
- Out of ten!
Why would that have changed?!
Maybe the two of you will be
discovered in the future!
That's all!
- Huh?! Huh?! Huh?!
What? No way. That can't be.
- And you, Master Roswaal?
- BOTH: Hoora--
- Hmm.
- [groans]
F-Four points?
PUCK: So ten points is the max?
- Yeah, individually,
but there are three judges here,
so a total of 30 points
would be a perfect score.
- I will admit the quality
is certainly satisfactory.
That said, it just sort of...
sends a shiver down my spine.
- I know our concept
wasn't wrong,
but the Barusu part of it
ruined everything!
- That can't possibly be true!
It makes no sense
that a combination
of my ideals and yours
could ever fail!
I'm confident
we're simply ahead of our time.
[music playing]
- Oh, hey, how's it goin', Mili?
- My sculpture's
almost finished.
Beatrice is working hard, too.
I still have
a little polishing to do.
Hold on. What is this?
- Don't tell me you actually
see something good
in this monstrosity?
Maybe Roz and I
are behind the times after all.
- It has a really...
strange feel to it.
- Definitely, yeah.
- Ohh.
- Subaru!
- Come over here!
- 'Cause we all made one, too!
- Look! Look, Subaru!
- Not bad, huh?!
- Oh. You guys also sculpted me?
- Stand next to it.
- Sure!
Like this?
- Hmm.
Something's off!
- The real one has mean eyes!
- Super-mean eyes, like this!
SUBARU: No, they are not!
- We gotta make 'em
look angrier, then!
Whoa!
- Ahh! His head fell off!
- Decapitation!
- [laughing]
- Don't laugh!
Being decapitated
is nothing to make jokes about!
Come over here.
If you think it's so funny...
- [laughing]
- let's see how you like it!
Here! [growls]
- ♪ All of you
will be memories ♪
♪ And I want to remember ♪
♪ To the end of time ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ We made a promise
to come back ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ I have been waiting
for you ever since ♪
♪ On this wonderful day ♪
♪ I wish you stayed alive ♪
♪ Even if the sun
never rises... ♪
- I worked so hard on this.
Don't you think it's kinda weird
that I only got nine points
and that Beatrice
only got seven?
PUCK: A competition
like this may have been
a little too hard
for you and Betty.
By the way,
what exactly did you make?
- Just what it looks like.
Both of them are you.
- Those are
supposed to be me, huh?
- Though they could be
more detailed,
I believe
the resemblance is striking.
- It's kinda scary to think
that this is what you see
every time you look at me,
but maybe it's just
too artistically advanced
for ordinary people
to appreciate.
- Maybe so.
Either way, the snow bunny
that ended up winning
is obviously impressive.
I think anybody could see that.
Roswaal and the old man
thought highly of it, too.
I assumed Subaru would have
been a bit more excited,
but he was oddly quiet.
PUCK: Yeah, no comment from me.
But, still, I am pretty curious
about the big prize.
- Oh, right,
from Subaru's homeland.
Now, what was it?
I think...cornpota?
- [sniffs]
[grunts]
So yummy!
- Really?
- Give me one!
- I wanna try it, too!
♪ To the end of time... ♪
EMILIA: All these
snow sculptures,
they'll have melted away
by tomorrow.
There are so many of them, too.
It's really a shame.
- That's just
how snow is, you know?
It stays around
for a little while,
but it doesn't last forever.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- [gasps]
- The party's
just about to get started!
- [giggles]
All right! We're on our way!
[Subaru clears throat]
Thank you all for participating
in the Roswaal Mansion
Snow Festival today.
All of you did great work.
Personally, I thought
it was a lot of fun!
When Puck's magic release period
comes again next year,
let's hold another festival.
We can make it
bigger and better!
With that said...
Cheers!
ALL: Cheers!
SUBARU: Oh, man,
it's finally time to dig in.
- [overlapping chatter]
- BEATRICE: So adorable.
[laughing]
- [burps]
[music playing]
- Thanks for
your hard work, Subaru.
- Hey, right back at you, Rem,
because you helped out a lot,
and I know it wasn't easy.
One way or another,
I'll make sure
that you're compensated.
[laughs]
- Oh, no, don't worry.
I'll simply allow myself
to gaze upon your sleeping face
for a little longer
than usual tonight.
[music stops]
- Huh? Did you
just say something creepy?
- Who, me? I don't think I said
anything creepy to you at all.
- [music resumes]
- Incidentally, Subaru,
how do you feel
about drinking alcohol?
Are you the type to turn
bright red and then say...
"I don't want...
to go back home tonight,"
or perhaps another reaction
similar to that?
- I've heard about parties
where that kinda thing goes on.
But it happens out here, too?
Anyway, I haven't exactly had
much experience with alcohol.
- Oh, is that so?
Given your personality,
I figured you would be the type
to seek out such luxuries
in hopes of appearing cooler.
- Children shouldn't be
drinking alcohol, though,
because it'll end up
stunting your growth.
- Just so you know,
I'm not anywhere near
too young to do that,
according to your laws.
I'll be turning 18 this year,
so I'm totally an adult.
- I don't think an adult would
be acting quite so boisterous,
but I didn't know
that you were 18. I, uh...
assumed you were a lot younger.
- Oh, yeah?
How old did you think I was?
- Uh...
- 12?
- Eh?
- I mean 13! 13!
- Come on! That would
make me younger than Felt!
Man, that's really hard to hear.
More importantly,
what about you, Mili?
I can assure you
that I'm not 13.
And I've never
had liquor before,
but I'm old enough to drink.
- I never doubted it.
And if you were 13,
I'm pretty sure
I'd be considered a criminal.
- What would make you say
something like that?
- Well, it's because...
you're just so darn adorable
that it makes me
want to commit crimes.
- Anyway, about the alcohol,
Puck says
I'm not allowed to have any.
- You just
straight up ignored me!
- Of course I said that.
It's because drinking
is what bad grown-ups do!
And if I see any
put in front of Lia,
I'll guzzle each one
and take 'em down!
[fighting yells]
- That said, I see no problem
if it's just for tonight.
- Hmm?
- See?
It would be such a shame
if all of this well-aged alcohol
that I found in the wine cellar
were to go to waste.
- [sighs]
[Emilia giggling]
[slurring] What's wrong, Subaru?
- You know, You're makin' a...
- [sputtering]
- really funny face right now.
And whoa!
There are so many of you!
- It's no fair!
- Eh?
- I mean, all you Subarus
are tryin' to hog
- all the sweets!
- Whoa!
- [moans]
- [groans]
Hey, now be careful, Mili.
I think you've had enough.
Look. You're getting
crumbs everywhere.
- [hiccups]
But that drink was so yummy!
Not fair! You kept
this secret for so long!
[bells jingle]
You've all been going
behind my back with it
and sneakin' around,
sneakin' without me!
[giggles]
- [gasping]
[chorus vocalizing]
Agh! She's just too damn cute!
- Subaru.
- Yes? What is it you need, Rem?
- [grunts]
- Uh, excuse me, but that hurts.
Guess somebody's
had one too many.
- Hmm.
- [gasps]
- Now, don't make fun of me,
Subaru! Subaru! Subaru!
- You just said my name
three times,
so, uh, what's goin' on?
- I'm usually very serious,
because my job
is so important to me, but...
since today
is all about having fun,
I guess I ended up letting
my guard down a little bit.
Either way, this whole thing
is your fault, Subaru.
- [gasps]
- Mmm.
[meowing]
- You're a cat now?
Given everything
I know about 'em,
I thought demons
would hold their alcohol better.
RAM: Well, that actually is
true for demons, as a race.
In fact, I often drank alongside
the adults when I was smaller.
- Think you just admitted
to underage drinking
like it's a totally normal
thing to do,
but I guess you don't seem
to be turning red
or slurring
your words too much.
- Now, don't be ridiculous.
I have experi--[burps]
- Uh...
I guess if there's anything I've
learned at all from tonight,
it's that maybe certain girls
who normally don't drink
should try
and keep it that way.
- Now, that's quite
an extreme proclamation.
[Puck laughs]
- [chuckles] Eh?
[sighs]
[grunt]
Beako's being
antisocial as usual...
Well, perfect time
to pick on her for a while.
Hey, Mili, you think you
could keep an eye on Rem for me?
- Sure. No problem!
Hey, come here, Rem, okay?
Mmm!
[giggles]
Oh, wow! You're so cute.
- I want a picture.
- I'm burning it
into my eyelids as we speak.
- You gonna stand here
by yourself the whole time?
If you're always alone,
then you'll never
want to do anything.
- That was unjustified slander,
I suppose,
and none of your business,
either.
- Don't say that.
Here. Now drink up.
- [grumbles]
- It's safe.
No booze in there whatsoever.
Just some delicious,
freshly squeezed appa juice.
- Do not treat me like a child,
I suppose.
In fact, next to Bubby,
I'm the oldest one
in this mansion.
- Whoa! Check that out!
Mili and Rem are even
more wrapped around each other
than they were earlier!
- You are being unbelievably
rude right now, I suppose!
- Wait! You've got it all wrong!
Those two are
getting cozy in a way
that would make any guy
really happy,
and it's not like they've
stolen my heart or anything,
but damn, I want a camera!
- That wasn't persuasive
in the slightest, I suppose!
- Anyway, while I don't
actually know how old you are,
based on the way you look,
it'd be weird
if I handed you liquor.
But we can still toast. Cheers.
- [grumbles]
[music playing]
- It's crazy how many stars
you can see from out here.
Okay, since you have
nothing better to do,
I'll tell you
something amazing.
Every star you can see
shining in the sky
has its own name
and its own story.
For example, the giant one
that's sparkling up there,
that's the North Star.
If you get lost,
you can follow it home.
It'll usually
lead you due north.
- That's south.
You're backwards, I suppose.
- Uh, all right, then.
See that M? That group of stars
is a constellation
called Cassiopeia.
- Well, I have
no idea what an M is,
so it still doesn't look
like any shape to me.
- What are you
doing now, Barusu?
- Are you telling secrets?
Come on! I wanna hear them, too!
- Subaru, Subaru, Subaru.
- Oh, hey, everybody.
I was just telling Beatrice
about some
of the stars up there.
- The shiny stars!
- Subaru, Subaru.
- SUBARU: Now...
the challenge that you've
all been waiting for.
You'll work together and...
[snaps fingers]
try your best to find Subaru.
- Huh?
- [sputters]
- Wait!
Don't glare at me like that!
I think there's
a misunderstanding here!
I mean, yeah, Subaru is my name,
but my folks got it
from the constellation, okay?!
- How cruel of your parents
to give you
the name of a group
of brilliant stars
that you could never live up to.
- Forever doomed to be compared
to their great majesty,
yet you don't shine.
It's rather sad.
- Why do you two
have to gang up on me like this?
- Aw, don't worry.
It'll be okay!
After all,
stars are a symbol of hope,
which means it's too soon
for you to give up now.
- Yeah, thanks a lot
for the advice.
- [gasps]
Look, look!
There are so many snow spirits!
SUBARU: Wow.
That's incredible.
[music playing]
Huh?
What did you think?
The snow festival
was fun, wasn't it?
- Well, it wasn't bad,
I suppose.
I'll give you that, at least.
- [chuckles]
- [liquor sloshes]
[grunts]
All right. Then I'll use
the last little bit
of my extra mana
to share this snow
with all the people
who are living in the capital!
[music playing]
[door closes]
- My, what's this?
So have you finally had enough
of your little tryst
with Subaru?
- You shouldn't tease anybody
in that outfit.
I don't find it funny
in the least.
- Goodness!
You can't be honest, can you?
[ice cubes clatter]
This is for you.
Not having a single drop
on a fanciful night
such as this
would be such a crime.
- I'll pass, I suppose.
- Staying faithful to him,
is that it?
- Now, don't get
the wrong idea about this.
My choice to not drink
has nothing to do with
that boy's request, I suppose.
Long ago, my mother
discouraged me from doing so,
and that's all.
[no audible dialogue]
What he says has nothing
to do with me, I suppose.
[no audible dialogue]
[birds chirping]
- I was just thinking...
maybe we should have asked
for Subaru's help
from the very beginning.
That way, neither one of us
would have felt
quite so anxious
about what was happening here.
- Yeah, you got a point.
But then again,
it wouldn't be good
if you grew up to be
somebody who's always
relying on other people
for everything, either,
so even if things seem
way beyond your control,
give it a try first, okay?
- Yes, I understand.
- Good to hear.
[both laugh]
EMILIA: Hey, do you remember
what Subaru suggested
during his toast?
- Hmm. That we should hold
another snow festival
during next year's
magic release period?
Normally, I wouldn't assume
he'd be interested,
but I have a feeling
he could make the next one
even more lively.
- Me, too.
I think that side
of him is just so...
you know.
- Indeed, it is.
I think it's extremely
"you know" as well.
- Next year, huh?
I'm not sure what'll happen
that far into the future.
I wonder how it'll be.
- At this point,
it's pretty hard to say,
but I hope things turn out
exactly how you
want them to, Lia,
even if there's no guarantee
that the snow festival
he was talking about
will actually take place.
- You're not
against the idea now, are you?
- No, it's not that at all.
I had a whole lot of fun,
and it looked to me
like you did, too.
But I'm just wondering
if Subaru will still be happy
staying by your side
until next year rolls around.
The wounds on his belly,
the one from the witch
biting him,
all of those scars
he's gotten,
are the indirect results
of your actions.
It's not as if
you would ever forget that,
but it's still
important to remember.
- [sighs]
- I really hope we can have
another snow festival
next year, though,
because having
the excess mana to do it again
would mean
I didn't have to use it
on anything big before that.
And I can't think
of anyone but Subaru
who could lead
an entire festival.
- Right. That is true.
Uh-huh.
I'm hoping that happens again
as well, Puck.
Uh, is something wrong?
- [gasps]
Mm-mmm. No, not at all.
I'm just fine!
Looks like it'll be hot today,
so take care.
- [chuckles]
- Will do.
See you later!
[music playing]
- [groaning]
[gasps]
- [panting]
Were you waiting long?
- No. I just got here.
[gasps]
Well, all right, then.
Should we get going?
- [chuckles]
Mm-hmm.
[music continues]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ White, white snow ♪
♪ White snow ♪
♪ La, la la la ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ White, white snow ♪
♪ White snow ♪
[music ends]