- [screaming]
[gasping]
M--my arm.
I still have it, right?
I guess I came back again.
No, wait.
Maybe I should say
I made it back.
[both shuddering]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Good morning.
[both shuddering]
[grunting]
Right, I guess you don't
remember me, do you?
[grunts]
Sorry for the trouble
I've caused till now!
Subaru Natsuki
is gonna start over!
both: Huh?
Oh, and what day and time
is it right now?
[Konomi Suzuki's "Redo"]
♪ ♪
- [singing in Japanese]
- It's my third first day
in the Roswaal Mansion.
That chill I felt,
does that mean I died
in my sleep the first time
due to physical weakness?
[distant rattling]
But the second time,
there was an attacker.
So if I was killed,
does that mean the other folks
here in the mansion
were likely targets as well?
'Cause we're involved
in Emilia's royal selection
like at the loot house?
But even knowing that,
I've no proof to explain it
or any way to avoid it,
and what makes things worse
is that I didn't get
a chance to see
the attacker's face
or the other victims.
My death was totally in vain.
- Quit pacing around.
You're really irritating me,
so stop or get blown away.
- Oh, sorry.
It may sound weird,
but walking round in circles
makes the gears in my head
turn a lot easier.
Cut me some slack.
We're close now,
aren't we?
- Exactly what sort
of relationship
do you think we have,
I suppose?
We're not best friends
having only met twice.
- [exhales]
[chuckles]
Listen, I'll be out of your hair
as soon as I can, okay?
Just serve some tea or something
and let me relax.
- As if I'll serve you anything,
I suppose.
[groans]
You are so irritating!
- What's that book
you're reading, anyway?
- It tells how
to get rid of bugs
that have gotten into
my room, I suppose.
- Whoa, you've got bugs here
in the library?
Man, really sucks for you, huh?
So what kind are they?
- You've long exceeded
your welcome here,
so it's time for you to leave.
Your hands have stopped shaking
so you can more easily
disguise your fear now,
I suppose.
- [grunts]
Y--you could tell?
- You are trying to hide it,
I suppose.
It feels rather vexing
to be treated
as a mere convenience.
- You're not very nice at all,
are you?
Well, thanks for helping me.
I'll see you again soon.
- I don't want to see you again,
I suppose.
So refrain from coming
in here anymore.
- [grunts]
- Shoo, shoo.
- Shoo, shoo?
Really?
[grunts]
Wait a sec.
When you said bugs,
did you mean me?
- [grunts]
Just get out
of here this instant!
- [groans]
[shouts]
[shouting]
[groaning]
[gasps]
If not for this flower bed,
that would have been
instant death.
- Um--
- [grunts]
- That looked painful.
Are you all right?
- Eh?
Of course, Mili.
Your kindness is the one thing
that can heal me.
- Just so you know,
Rem spread manure as fertilizer
all over
that flower bed yesterday.
- [shouting]
The three second rule!
That didn't count!
That didn't count, okay?
- You know,
believe it or not,
they say this kind of thing
happening to you
is actually sort of lucky.
- Mili is already shifting
into consolation mode with me.
- [laughs]
Hey, Puck, rise and shine.
[quirky music]
- [yawns]
Hey there.
Good morning, Lia.
- Good morning to you, Puck.
Sorry to ask this of you
being that you only
just woke up,
but could you wash off Subaru?
- Wash him off?
- [groans]
- Oh, okay.
No problem.
- Uh--
- Here!
- [shouting]
- [laughing]
There you go!
All clean!
Not bad, huh?
- [grunts]
[gurgling]
I thought I was a goner.
Wasn't there some other way
you could have cleaned me up?
You enjoyed that,
didn't you?
- That's not true at all,
Subaru.
[shouts]
- [gasps]
- Oh, yeah?
Take this!
[both grunting]
- Oh, now you've done it!
[grunts]
Yeah, you like that?
It's my lethal move called,
"Make that cat cry!"
- Cut it out!
Tail punch!
- You--
- And I'll finish you off
with my bump and grind!
- [laughs]
- Grind, grind, grind, grind!
- [laughing]
Oh, my gosh, sorry!
I just can't--
[laughing]
What in the world?
What are you--
both: Huh?
What are you two doing?
Oh, my stomach.
I'm dying.
[laughing]
- Well, I suppose I bounced back
from my initial bad impression.
I do thank you for your
assistance, dear Father.
- Who are you calling Father?
I won't give you my daughter
that easily.
- Stop that.
You're both too funny.
I--
[laughing]
- You've got a great smile, Lia.
You agree, don't you, Subaru?
- Yes, totally.
To me, Mili's lovely smile
is the first shining star
in the night sky!
- Aw, come on, Subaru.
What did you mean by Mili,
anyway?
Where did that come from?
- Huh?
[chuckles]
It's what's commonly referred to
as a nickname
or a pet name.
Pretty much the same thing
as when Puck calls you Lia.
It's meant to be
a playful expression
of affection that shows
two people's closeness.
- I see, but that would imply
you and I are close
when we hardly know each other.
- [gasps]
You've got a point
and that hurts somewhat,
but I won't lose heart!
Think of it as an advance
in our relationship.
It means I want us to get
close enough to call each other
by playful pet names, okay?
- [gasps]
- [giggles]
- [stammers]
A--all right.
I suppose I can accept that.
- [grunts]
No, please,
don't look at me.
- I really expected her
to cringe,
but I got a positive response.
- What could this reaction mean,
commentator Puck?
- She doesn't have
very many friends,
so she crave things like
nicknames and being playful.
Really easy to please,
you know?
- My main heroine is easy
to please, huh?
- Sister, sister,
it's only been a short time,
and now our guest looks like
a drowned rat.
- Rem, Rem,
in just a short time,
our guest has turned into
a dirty old wash rag.
- I know I'm a mess, okay?
I don't need the two of you
to tell me.
both: Our lord Master Roswaal
has returned to the premises.
Please come inside.
- [exhales]
Here we go.
My third first meeting
with the lord of the mansion.
All I know for certain
in this current loop of events
is that somebody is going
to attack on the fourth night.
It would be ideal
if I could let them know
and warn them,
but I wouldn't be able
to explain where
I got the information,
so they might think I'm working
with the assassin.
If I knew even as little
as the attacker's physique,
it could be a different story.
So this time around,
I'll use these next four days
to gather as much information
as I can
and find out who it is,
and to do that...
- You may have any reward
you request.
So simply name your desire
and it shall be.
- In that case,
I ask that you let me live here
as a house guest
and eat and sleep
as much as I want.
- [yawns]
[grunts]
- How am I supposed to go
about gathering information,
anyway?
Didn't really think
about all that.
Guess I'll start off with
some indirect questioning.
[grunting]
That's the place where I fell.
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
Sorry for all
the trouble I caused.
- Don't mention it.
If you'll excuse me, sir.
- Hey, wait.
We didn't even get
a chance to talk.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
Hmm, nothing out
of the ordinary here.
[distant rattling]
[grunts]
[chains rattling]
- What isn't ordinary?
- Ros!
Don't sneak up
and scare me like that.
It's misleading.
- [chuckles]
- [groans]
[knocking]
Uh, yes?
- Tea time, sir.
Here you are.
- Oh, uh, thanks.
Wanna drink it with me?
- That's very kind,
but no thank you, sir.
- Uh, hey, you know,
if you wanted to be
a little friendlier
that'd be fine by me.
[grunts]
Well, it is my first day.
Guess that's expected.
Yo.
- You come in here every day
without even knocking.
Seems you truly have
no manners whatsoever.
It would be in your
best interest to leave
before you get blown away,
I suppose.
- Whoa, hang on a second!
I just wanted
to ask you something.
That's all!
Is there any magic
that can weaken
and kill someone but makes it
look like they're
just going to sleep?
- If I must answer,
then yes, there is.
- Are you serious?
- But it's not so much magic
as it is a curse, I suppose.
Actually, there are many
such things among the spells
that shamans specialize in.
- So what are shamans?
- Magicians.
Originating in the northern
nation of Gusteco,
they're actually a subclass
of magic and spirit arts users,
I suppose.
They're all quite useless,
to be perfectly honest,
and not to be taken seriously,
but to achieve that result,
there is an easier method
than a curse, I suppose.
- There is?
- I think you've
already experienced
what I'm talking
about firsthand.
- [grunts]
Wait, do you mean--
That mana drain you did
against my will
could actually kill me?
[gasps]
- In case you didn't know,
mana is also one's life essence.
If you continually suck it out
by force,
one could feasibly die
of weakness, I suppose.
- Wait, hold on.
You're not the one
who killed me, are you?
- Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm too busy
for such an endeavor.
I couldn't even spare the effort
to kill you.
It's not worth my time.
[grunting]
- This what you're after?
- [grunts]
- Uh, okay.
Anyway, can pretty much anyone
do that mana-sucking thing?
- That's an absolutely terrible
way to put it, I suppose.
In this mansion, only Bubby
and I are able to.
Even Roswaal is incapable.
- Oh.
Must mean it's actually
a pretty rare skill, then.
Well, now that I know,
don't suck up that stuff
too much,
especially from me.
With everything
I've been through,
I'd die in an instant.
I'm really short
of blood right now.
- Yes, all of your organs
were restored,
but your blood wasn't replaced,
I suppose.
Not that I have any obligation
to do such a thing anyway.
- My organs?
You know, the way you said
all that just now
kinda makes it sound like
you were the one who magically
healed my wounds
and saved my life.
Trying to take credit
for what Mili did
makes you look pretty bad!
- What in the world
are you talking about?
That silly girl doesn't have
the power
to heal fatal wounds yet,
I suppose.
- Huh?
- She and Bubby may have
stabilized you
and brought you here
but I was the one who used magic
to heal you.
- Huh?
F--for real?
You're kidding, right?
Wait, I get it.
You're lying about
this whole thing, aren't you?
It's not nice to lie.
Lying bad!
- Shut up, I suppose.
You're too averse to the truth
which means you should
disappear, I suppose!
- [grunts]
Whoa!
[groaning]
- Uh, once again,
are you all right?
- So in the end,
the keywords
are curse and chains.
I don't know anything else.
If the conditions for Return
by Death are the same,
I died three times
in the capitol,
and survived the fourth time,
but that doesn't mean I intend
to treat this
as a throw away life.
That's why I asked Puck
to keep an eye on Emilia for me.
I don't wanna mess this up.
- Yeah, you got it.
Everything you're saying
is pretty vague,
but I can tell you're asking
out of concern for Lia.
- On the morning
of the fourth day,
I'll leave here and--
[knocking]
[grunts]
[door opening]
- Pardon my intrusion, sir.
You really are studying, sir.
I'm surprised.
- Surprised, huh?
Well, that's a pretty rude thing
to say.
I mean, I am a guest here,
you know.
- You're a freeloader
calling yourself a guest.
Least that's how I perceive it,
sir.
Here you go.
- Thanks all the same.
[groans]
It's still nasty.
- Careful.
You're going to incur the wrath
of the finest tea leaves
in the mansion.
- Slacking off right in front
of your guest?
I've no words
for that nerve of yours.
Having a seat,
drinking tea.
- Well, you were the one
who told me
I should be friendlier,
remember?
So I suppose you could say
I'm only responding
to your demand.
- [grunts]
- How's your studying
coming along so far?
- Not bad.
I'm able to read
some simple fairy tales
like these now.
It's interesting how
the morals differ just slightly
from the ones I know.
It's like true
cross-cultural communication.
Maybe I should import
a few fairy tales
from my homeland
to show you what I mean,
like The Red Ogre Who Cried.
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
- The Red Ogre Who Cried?
- Intrigued, huh?
You want me to tell it to you?
Now, you really need
to pay attention, okay?
This is how it goes.
Once upon a time,
there lived a red ogre
and a blue ogre.
The two were the best
of friends.
Just inseparable.
One day, the red ogre wanted
to be friends
with the people
of the nearby village
He approached but the people
were too scared
to get close to him.
The blue ogre couldn't bear
to watch this happen
so he devised a plan
to help his friend.
"I'll make a ruckus
in the village
"and frighten everyone.
"When I do,
you come and stop me.
After that, the villagers
will be sure to trust you."
[unsettling music]
The plan worked,
and just as predicted,
the red ogre befriended
the humans.
But as time passed,
something he noticed began
to worry him.
His friend,
the blue ogre,
no longer stopped by to visit.
♪ ♪
One day, the red ogre decided
to go to the blue ogre's house.
Abandoned.
The shades were drawn
in the windows,
and the door was shut
and locked.
There was a letter attached
to the door that said...
"Red Ogre,
please have fun with your new
human friends and companions."
"If I continue
to hang around you,
"I'm afraid they might think
you're a bad ogre, too,
and end the friendship
you sought from them."
"Thus..."
"I've decided
to go on a journey.
I'm not sure I'll return,
but I will never forget you."
"Good-bye.
"Take care of yourself.
"Your friend now and forever,
Blue Ogre."
The red ogre red the letter
in silence over and over.
He began to cry and the tears
welled up in his eyes.
That's the end.
♪ ♪
- That's a sad story.
- Yeah, it is.
But even with
an ending like that,
I think it's kind of
a sweet story also.
- If you ask me,
all the characters in it
are just stupid.
The red ogre,
the blue ogre,
and the villagers, too.
- Wow, that's a pretty harsh
critique, don't you think?
I mean, sure,
I'm not denying it,
but that's probably
the reason why I both love
and hate that story, honestly.
The blue ogre's self sacrifice
is really appealing,
but it's stupid because
he gets nothing out of it.
I'm the type that wants
to be rewarded for the effort
I put in.
- Is that really what you think
about the blue ogre?
To me it's the red ogre
that I feel is beyond help
He dragged the blue ogre
into his own desires
and as a result,
he lost nothing.
Only the blue ogre
lost anything.
- Interesting point.
Then what do you think the two
of them should have done?
- If the red ogre truly wanted
to become friends
with the humans in the village,
he should have broken off
his horns and gone to them.
If he had done that
from the very beginning,
the blue ogre might have stayed.
- I--I think you're missing
the point.
That's a pretty extreme opinion.
- You really think so?
Answer this.
Which of the two ogres would you
rather be friends with?
- Which of the two?
- The red ogre who could
only wish
to be taken care of by others,
or the blue ogre basking
in his own self sacrifice?
- [exhales]
[soft guitar music]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
What a boring answer.
If you want to befriend both
of them,
I can only conclude
that you must be
the indecisive adulteress type.
You'll regret it one day.
- How can you say that?
I don't recall it being
that kind of story.
- Putting aside the questionable
fairy tales of your homeland,
did any of these stories leave
an impression on you?
- Well, let's see.
The ones that interested me most
were the one in the middle
about the dragon
and the one at the end
about the witch.
I finally know where the name
Dragon's Kingdom of Lugunica
came from.
- Oh?
- It said the royal family
designed a covenant
with a dragon
so it's more a folk tale
than a fairy tale,
wouldn't you say?
- Yes, I would,
since it's true.
The noble dragon lives far away
beyond a great waterfall.
But even with that distance,
the dragon still upholds
its duty to protect us.
It was in the royal
family's contract
and must be honored
till it's fulfilled.
- Wait a sec.
The royal family that has
the contract with the dragon,
didn't they die out recently?
- They did.
Rather abruptly at that.
No one's sure what the noble
dragon wants to do now.
In the nation's
current situation,
I imagine only the gods
are aware.
No, at this point,
only the dragon knows.
- Hmm.
Oh, by the way,
about this witch story.
- I don't wanna discuss that.
- Uh--
- I've stayed here far too long.
When dinner has been prepared,
I will stop by
to notify you, sir.
- Oh, okay.
[door opens]
- Do me a favor.
That story you told me
about the ogres,
don't tell it to Rem.
I'm certain that she wouldn't
like it very much.
- [grunts]
A scary witch.
A truly terrifying witch.
To even speak her name
would chill you to the bone.
Everybody referred to her
as the Witch of Envy.
- Are you sure about this?
We could call a dragon-drawn
carriage
to take you to the capitol.
It's no trouble.
- Thank you but I'll be fine.
And one day when
I finally become
the kind of strong, smart,
rich man who's worthy of you,
I'll come to you on
a white horse
to take you away with me.
- Do you have a handkerchief?
And water,
and plenty of lagumite ore?
Let's see, and will you be able
to sleep by yourself?
- Do you think you're my mom?
- Safe travels to you, Subaru.
I wish you well.
And don't lose
the gift I gave you.
As an attempt to equate our
three days worth
of memories together,
I gave you a little something.
- [grunts]
Oh, hush money, right?
Don't worry.
I get it.
I won't say anything
I shouldn't.
I swear to the dragon.
- Oh, just talking with you
makes any evil scheme
seem to lose its purpose.
And in case you didn't know,
in this nation,
swearing to the dragon
is the highest form of promise.
Make sure you never forget it,
okay?
- You got it!
The two of you helped
me out so much.
Especially you, Rem-Rem.
Thanks for all the great food.
And Ram, you--oh.
Yeah, you're really good
at cleaning toilets.
- Sister, sister,
what a shame.
Our guest is hopelessly bad
at flattery.
- Rem, Rem, what a shame.
Our guest has a fatal lack
of flattery skills.
- Oh, shut up!
I seriously couldn't think
of anything to say, okay?
Thanks, though.
I appreciate it.
both: Yes, sir.
- [grunts]
- Subaru?
- Thanks for all you've done.
If you're ever in need,
come visit us any time.
- Will do.
- [giggling]
- Thanks a bunch, Mili!
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
[panting]
♪ ♪
Okay, this is it.
I've got a good view
of Emilia's room.
And now I'll just wait around
for something to happen,
then stop it.
Rem-Rem would probably get mad
at me for using it like this.
I hope she does, anyway.
I don't wanna die again.
I don't want them
to die, either.
Now, what did I tell you,
Subaru Natsuki?
Even if no one remembers
anything that happened
when everything repeats,
you remember it clear as day.
Uh, now that I really think
about it,
I didn't go shopping
with Rem this time.
Just because the food meant
for me was left over.
It'll still be a while before
it gets dark.
Come on.
Focus, focus.
[snarling]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[shouts]
[grunts]
Emergency escape!
I saw it.
Yes, I saw it!
I saw where the sound
of chains came from!
What is it?
Coming this way?
[breathing heavily]
[gasping]
Nowhere to run.
Does this mean I played right
into the attacker's hands?
[tense music]
[grunts]
If you're coming,
then come.
[chains rattling]
Now, don't you have the nerve
to face me?
[grunts]
[screams]
All right, show yourself,
you damn coward!
I've gone through hell trying
to see your face,
so come out!
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- Then I have no choice.
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
- The ideal scenario would
have been to finish this
without anyone noticing.
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
[winces]
You're joking.
Right, Rem?
- As long as you do not resist,
I can make your death
a painless one.
- Why?
Why are you doing this?
Look, might be a cliché to ask,
but I gotta know.
- It's simply the rule of maids.
If someone's suspicious,
punish them.
- Tell me.
Does Ram know, too?
- I intend to finish this
before my sister sees anything.
- Is that--is that how little
you trusted me?
- Yes.
- [gasps]
Damn, I'm so pathetic.
And I was so sure that we
were getting along well.
- My sister--
- I don't wanna hear it!
Take this!
[camera shutter flashing]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[blow lands]
[gasps]
[shouts]
[groaning]
[shouting]
My leg!
[screaming]
- Mana of water,
heal this damaged body.
If I let you die too quickly,
then I won't be able to get
any information out of you.
- [whimpers]
- If you had stopped me
with this,
you would have been able
to flee a bit further.
I ask you this.
Are you a faction member
supporting one
of Miss Emilia's rivals
for the throne?
- My heart belongs
to Mili forever
until the end of t--
[screams]
- Answer me.
Who hired you?
And under what conditions?
- Mili's smile did
and it was priceless.
[screaming]
- Let's try again.
Are you affiliated
with the Witch's Cult?
- The Witch's Cult?
[whimpering]
I don't know what that is.
My family's been secular
for generations.
Why--
- Don't you play dumb with me!
Your bald-faced lies can only
take you so far
when the fowl stench
of the witch
is covering you
from head to toe!
- [whimpering]
- Every time I watched you
conversing with my sister,
I felt as if I would go out
of my mind
with anger and unrest.
Someone associated with the one
who has caused my sister
so much agony having
the audacity
to boldly encroach on the place
in which she and I belong.
- [whimpering]
- I can't bear it any longer.
Even if I know deep down
my sister only acts friendly
with you and only pretends
to care for you!
- [whimpering]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Look, I don't cut my hands
when I peel vegetables anymore.
- Huh?
- I can read and I can
even write now, too.
Just the basics, but hey.
I kept my word
and I studied hard.
I can read those fairy tales.
All thanks to you two.
- Fairy tales?
What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about all
the wonderful things
you guys gave me.
- I have no memory
of any of that.
- [crying]
Why?
Why don't you remember?
Why do all you you keep leaving
me behind like this?
What did I ever do to you?
What am I supposed to do?
What did I do wrong?
I don't understand!
Why do you guys hate me so much?
[crying]
Even when you said
you'd cut my hair...
[crying]
All that time, I...
- I--
- I really like you both!
You--
- [shuddering]
My sister is too kind.
- [gasps]
[groans]
[birds chirping]
- Sir, have you awakened?
- Huh?
- Sir, you're awake?
- [breathing heavily]
[screams]
- Subaru, what was that
all about?
Ram and Rem were really worried.
They were unusually despondent
wondering if they'd
been impolite.
- Don't worry about it.
Nothing happened between them
and me.
- Subaru, are you all right?
'Cause if something's
troubling you,
you're welcome to talk
to me about it.
- If I could tell Emilia
that it's no use,
that I can't take anymore...
[gasps]
Wait.
That's it.
- What?
- All this time
I've been struggling
to change things alone,
but what if--
- Subaru,
are you sure you're okay?
- There's something important
I want to tell you.
- [gasps]
Yes?
- Emilia, several 8times
up until now,
believe it or not,
I've die--
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
Whoa, wait.
This is seriously no joke.
What's happening?
♪ ♪
- What is it?
- [gasping]
- Subaru!
What happened all of a sudden?
- [breathing heavily]
My body moves.
My voice works.
My heart doesn't hurt.
But...
The fear is engraved in me.
- Wh--what's wrong?
You've been acting
really strange.
Tell me.
If something's going on--
- I have a favor to ask.
- Yes?
- I want you to have nothing
to do with me.
- [gasps]
- I can't tell anyone
about Return by Death.
I've died in this mansion
three times.
I didn't experience
a fourth time
while I was in the capitol.
If I die again...
I might not come back.
- My, that's quite a cowardly
look on your face, I suppose.
- Why are you here?
- Bubby and the brat told me
I should take a moment
to stop by and check on you.
- You mean Puck and Emilia?
- Since you were acting
so strange earlier,
I believe they suspect
that I did something to you
when you first woke up,
I suppose.
My goodness.
Talk about rude.
- [grunts]
I get it.
I'm okay now.-
You came here to apologize
to me.
That's enough.
- And why in the world should
I apologize to you, I suppose?
I can't leave until I correct
that proposterous notion.
Hmm.
Not only do you look gloomy
but that disgusting scent
I noticed before
is heavier now.
- Huh?
- The stench of the witch,
I suppose.
I feel like
it's bending my nose.
- Wait a second.
You mean the Witch of Envy?
- Well, of course I do.
What else in this world
would somebody mean
when they bring up a witch?
- What are you talking about?
Why do you smell her on me?
- Meh, I dunno.
Regardless, as someone
who received
special attention from her,
you're a burden.
- It's not comforting to hear
I'm getting special treatment
from someone
I've never even met.
- If you have nothing to say,
I'm leaving.
I'll tell Bubby everything
that you told me, I suppose.
Good-bye.
- Hey, wait a minute.
You feel sorry for what
you did to me, right?
- I do not.
- I'm telling Puck.
- [groans]
Well, I might feel just a teeny
tiny bit sorry, I suppose.
- If you regret what you did
and want my forgiveness,
do me the one favor
that I ask of you.
- Fine, let's hear it.
- I'm not sure what's happening
but I want you to keep me safe,
until the fifth morning comes,
the day after tomorrow.
- I don't want you bringing
dissension into this mansion,
I suppose.
For various reasons,
this place is vitally important
to me.
- I have no intention
of doing anything.
I just wanna stop any sparks
from flying.
- What an admirable motive
for one who leaves
even something like that
in the hands of others.
- Strangely enough for once
I have no response to that.
- [sighs]
Hold out your hand.
- [grunts]
[grunts]
I have decided that I
shall grant your wish.
I, Beatrice,
on my honor
am henceforth bound
by this contract, I suppose.
Temporary or not,
a contract must be upheld.
I will grant you the nonsense
favor you requested.
- [shudders]
[weeping]
Come on.
Seriously?
I'm gonna cry because
of a little girl.
- Don't you ever call me
a little girl.
And if you tell Bubby,
you're gonna regret it,
I suppose.
[grunts]
- Is it really that important
to you?
That desperation of yours
is demonically inspired.
- [grunts]
[tense music]
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
No, stop!
[breathing heavily]
- Come on.
You can't keep sleeping forever,
I suppose.
- [groans]
Oh, that hurt.
- I came against my will because
it's the designated time
yet you seem awfully
unconcerned.
- [groans]
Did I really fall asleep
on the fourth day?
What kind of reckless idiot
am I?
- Quit your grumbling,
I suppose.
Sit wherever you want
but do it quietly.
- The forbidden archive.
Did you carry me in here
when I was asleep?
- Given the option,
I'd rather not stay in that room
filled with your stench,
I suppose.
The forbidden library
is the only place for me.
Now, observe proper manners,
I suppose.
- [grunts]
Hey, Beatrice.
I'm sure I'm wrong,
but you didn't hold
my hand while I was asleep,
did you?
- You are absolutely wrong.
Even if Bubby asked me to,
I would still refuse, I suppose.
- Flat-out denial, huh?
I'm not sure what you mean
by proper manners.
So, hey, are you--
[grunts]
- You're annoying me
with all your questions.
Just be still and quiet,
I suppose.
- Hmm.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- They're calling.
- Huh?
- I've been summoned,
I suppose.
- [gasps]
- Oh, that's right.
You're here.
I forgot, I suppose.
- Hey, hold on.
If you go out there now--
- Guess it's fine
if you want to stay.
You'll be safe here,
I suppose.
- [exhales]
[grunts]
Damn it, come on!
What the hell is this?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[dramatic music]
The sun.
Did I make it through
the fourth night?
[laughing]
And I figured that doing so
was next to impossible.
In the end,
it was that easy.
[laughing]
- Subaru?
- [grunts]
Emilia.
- There you are.
Where have you been?
- Oh, I was just, uh--
- You know,
no, never mind.
Here, come with me.
- Huh?
Where are we going?
Uh, Mili.
Why are you making that face?
Everything's gonna be
just fine now.
I mean, look.
I'm still alive, right?
And you're--oh, I know!
Let's go to the village!
There's so much I want
to do and tell you about.
So much has happened.
- Subaru.
[gasps]
- Wait, what's the matter?
- [screams]
- [gasps]
- [crying]
- But how?
Why?
Why is Rem dead?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- Don't you touch her!
Don't touch Rem.
Keep your hands off
my little sister!
- [stammers]
♪ ♪
[shudders]
- It appears that she died
of weakness.
It was as if she just
fell asleep.
- [grunts]
- The method was more
of a curse than a spell.
- [grunts]
I thought it was Rem
who used that curse.
So she isn't the shaman?
- My dear guest,
have you any idea what might
have happened here?
After this has happened
to a dear member
of my staff,
I seem to be a tiny bit angry,
you see.
- Subaru, if you know anything,
then please tell us.
[grunts]
- [gasps]
[winces]
I just want to spill it all
and get it off my chest.
[tense music]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[groans]
♪ ♪
[shudders]
- If you know something,
you'd better tell me!
I'm warning you!
- Wait, Ram,
that's a--
[grunts]
- I always uphold my end
of promises.
As long as he continues
to remain in this mansion,
I am contracted to protect him,
I suppose.
- B--but Miss Beatrice!
- Roswaal, he spent last night
in the Forbidden Library.
So surely he couldn't have had
anything to do with--
- There's no further need
to emphasize
the situation at hand.
However, Beatrice,
if you agreed to guard him
with your life,
you must have taken quite
a liking to him.
- Save the jokes for your makeup
and weird fetishes, I suppose.
[whooshing]
- [gasps]
Stop it!
None of that even matters!
Get out of the way!
Let me through!
I must avenge Rem.
If you know anything,
then you have to tell me.
Help me.
Help Rem.
Say something!
[shudders]
- [crying]
- I'm sorry, Ram.
Despite all this,
I'm choosing to trust him.
- [shudders]
- Subaru, please.
If you can save Ram,
if you can save Rem,
I beg you,
please do so.
[shuddering]
I'm sorry.
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
- [grunts]
- [breathing heavily]
- Subaru!
- [panting]
- I'm going to kill you!
I ran.
As fast as I could.
I ran away from them.
[grunts]
I can't go back there again.
[breathing heavily]
What choice did
I have back there?
What could I have--
And I was having so much fun
with them!
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
This looks like the place
where I died.
Is this it?
[breathing heavily]
If I die...
- Will I be saved
from this whole situation?
Of course.
If I do,
everything will change
If I struggled and fought
so much only to end up here,
then what's the point?
[gasps]
The cliff.
♪ ♪
[shuddering]
If I close my eyes
and take one step,
it'll all be over.
[whimpers]
What will happen to me
if I die again?
♪ ♪
[crying]
It's just one more step.
♪ ♪
I can't even...
do something as simple as that.
[wind blowing]
- I finally found you.
- Why?
- What's the matter,
I suppose?
- Why did you come out here
for me?
Didn't I--
- How quickly you forget.
The contract I entered into
was to protect you.
- You're still my bodyguard?
I thought you were only supposed
to do that until this morning.
- In that case,
you must be mistaken, I suppose.
I don't remember discussing
there being a time limit.
- [shudders]
- Clinging to faint hope just
serves your own convenience,
I suppose.
- [grunts]
- What was lost
can't be reclaimed.
You'll have no more chances
to explain yourself
to the older sister.
That opportunity
has come and gone.
No matter which is lost,
they'll never be complete again,
I suppose.
- But I really cared
about those two very much
and I wanted to do whatever
I could
to protect them.
- Why?
What do you know about them,
I suppose?
Either way, they'll never
be restored to what
they once were.
They can't be.
- So in the end,
what I was really doing
was making a selfish,
disgraceful fuss
without actually
knowing anything at all.
- At the very least,
you need to die
where I can't see you
or I'll just have bad dreams,
I suppose.
So I'll do what I can to help
you escape this territory.
[tense music]
- Huh?
[grunts]
Come to think of it,
back then,
somebody was holding both
of my hands.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Ram, Rem.
If they couldn't bear to see me
suffering and in pain,
and they held both my hands,
- ♪ For my love... ♪
- If that's the kind
of people they are,
how can I leave them?
- I'm going to kill you!
- I heard a voice filled
with hatred.
But more than that...
- [screams]
- Her cries were haunting.
They won't leave my mind.
[MYTH&ROID's "STRAIGHT BET"]
- ♪ Now have a seat... ♪
- All my life I've always been
the type to drift toward
whichever path was easiest.
- [singing in Japanese]
- Hey, Subaru.
You're thinking of something
pretty stupid here.
And after all that
I went through
to save this life...
- [singing in Japanese]
- That's right.
I simply saved my own life.
So then--
What's wrong with taking
the path that's easiest?
That will let me live longer?
I'll decide how I use my life!
- [gasps]
Afraid you were a bit too slow.
♪ ♪
- I finally found you.
I'm not gonna let you get away.
- Stay back, I suppose.
So long as my contract exists,
I won't hold back,
not even against you.
- And you, Miss Beatrice,
you seem to have forgotten
we're not in the mansion now.
We're in the forest away
from the Forbidden Library.
Are you so certain that you'll
be able to protect him from me?
- [singing in Japanese]
- [grunts]
- [laughs]
Pow.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah.
That feels good.
- [snarling]
What are you doing,
you buffoon?
Do you want to die or something?
- Of course not.
Don't be dumb.
That isn't what I want at all.
I only wanna die once at the end
of a long and happy life.
That's how I really feel.
- You've got guts.
So you finally accept your fate?
- That's not a very
accurate description.
If anything,
I would say that now
I've made up my mind.
Sorry.
I caused a lot of grief
for you guys
by being such
a pathetic loser.
- [gasps]
So you do know something
about Rem!
- Nope, sorry, but I honestly
don't know a thing.
Frankly, there's too much
I don't know.
Even so, I decided to learn more
about the things
I don't understand
and to not be in the dark.
- How can you possibly say that?
My sister Rem is already dead.
What can you do by learning
anything now?
It's way too late for that!
- I won't make any cool
statements about what
I'll be able to do.
After all, this is what happened
when I couldn't do anything.
I know better than anyone
that my words aren't convincing
in the least.
But I do remember.
I know parts of you two
that you've forgotten.
- What are you saying?
What is it you think you know
about Rem and me?
- Don't get me wrong.
'Cause in the grand scheme
of things,
what I know doesn't
really matter.
But it does to me,
and you have no idea
what it is, do you?
- Tell me.
- [inhales deeply]
I care for all of you!
Every one of you means
the world to me!
[grunts]
- [gasps]
Wait!
- [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
This is something only I can do!
♪ ♪
- I'm going to kill you!
- I'm going to save you!
[MYTH&ROID's "STYX HELIX"
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh please don't let me die
Waiting for your touch ♪
♪ ♪
♪ No don't give up on life
This endless dead end ♪
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I wish I was there ♪
♪ Oh please don't let me die ♪
♪ Waiting for your touch ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Restart ♪
♪ No don't give up on life ♪
♪ This endless dead end ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ For now I'll see you off ♪
♪ And we'll die
Waiting for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ And we'll start waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]