[music playing]
[wood clatters]
[Subaru yells]
[grunting]
Everything
that we've both faced,
it all worked out
thanks to me, didn't it?!
Without me there, things
would
have been a whole lot worse!
You were saved
'cause I was there for you!
- [growls]
- Don't you see?
You should have
a greater debt to me
than you could ever repay!
[groans]
[panting]
- Perhaps we should pause
and take a little break
now.
- Then I'll repay all of them
at this moment by ending this.
[woman vocalizing]
FELIX: I swear, Julius,
your good nature
is going to waste
playing the villain
for someone like him.
JULIUS: Excuse me?
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
FELIX: Why get yourself punished
trying to protect
a guy like that? It's foolish.
- I acted as I wished,
true to my nature,
righteously, in my own way,
and without shame.
Understand?
FELIX: Are you sure about this?
After all, Old Man Wil
is busy preparing, too.
- It was a request
from our guest,
so I can't ignore it.
- If they're just practicing,
it's neo big deal,
but honestly, it looks to me
like he's
just making up excuses.
- What do you mean?
- He wants to be able to say,
"I'm doing just fine now
and working hard," you
know?
- Well, can you blame him?
- Oh.
[no audible dialogue]
- [chanting]
- ♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Grew up in the loneliness ♪
- Forgive me.
- Whoa, wait a second.
There's no need for that.
What have you got
to apologize for?
None of this was your fault,
so don't try
to shoulder the blame.
- No.
- [gasps]
- I'm a friend to you
as well as to Julius.
I feel that my own
lack of virtue was responsible.
I failed to stop a dispute
between two friends.
That duel,
there was no meaning behind it.
- Wait. What?
There was no meaning?
- Yes.
As nothing of value came
from you two fighting.
You were hurt,
and Julius ended up tarnishing
his career as a knight.
Why not try to have a calm,
open discussion with him?
I'm sure that would clear up
any misundersta--
- Look, Reinhard...
- [gasps]
- I get how you feel,
and I appreciate it, honestly.
- You really are a nice guy.
- So then--
- But I just can't accept
that proposal.
We're done talking.
You should go back.
- Subaru.
Then tell me why?
What was it you gained
from that duel?
You've only suffered
great losses.
- [gate creaks]
- Even Miss Emilia--
- You'd better head back
for today, Reinhard...
before your mistress
gets lonely
and starts yelling for you.
- [gate clangs]
- [gasps]
- Mind your own damn business.
[wood clattering]
[yelps]
[panting]
- Maybe we should stop
and call it a day.
- [panting]
[growls]
- [wood clatters]
- [Subaru groans]
[thump]
[fountain gushing]
- Hey there. You must be
tired after your practice.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
- Let me ask you something, Rem.
Do you think I'm pathetic?
- Yes, I do.
- You do? Seriously?
Then why are you still here
with a loser like me?
Is it because you were told to?
- The fact that I think
you're pathetic
and my staying with you
are not contradictory.
And even if I
hadn't been ordered to,
I'm certain I would have
stayed with you.
- Why?
- That's simple.
Because I want to.
What do you think?
Shall we go out tomorrow?
You haven't gone anywhere
in the three days
since we came here.
[bell tolling]
- Interested
in the royal selection, too, eh?
- Whoa! Easy.
Don't sneak up on me like that.
Uh, wait. Where's Rem?
- [grunts]
- Eh?
[sighs] Don't make someone with
no experience watch your shop.
- So we got five candidates?
Well, it's nothing
short of insanity
to let a half-elf be one of 'em,
if you ask me.
"Emilia," huh?
There's no way
that a relative of the Witch
could become our ruler.
They gotta be crazy
to even consider it.
- Why does everybody say that?
It doesn't mean she has
anything to do with the Witch.
- Huh?
- Uh, don't lump them together
and brush her off just because
she happens to be a half-elf!
- [crowd murmuring]
- [gasps] Hey.
- Look, Emilia really cares.
Uh, I mean, that girl
might really care about
this kingdom's people, too!
- Why are you getting
so worked up about all of this?
- I'm not!
- But it was for you,
now, wasn't it?
- [gasps]
Why is it?
Because of the Witch of Envy?
That's the most ridiculous thing
I've ever heard!
You think
all half-elves are dangerous
just because the Witch was one?!
- That's right.
You listen to me.
Every citizen around here
is scared of the Witch.
That's just common knowledge.
- [sputters]
- As long as people
see her like that,
there isn't any chance
she's gonna win this.
- [crowd murmuring]
- I know, right?
- [scoffs] Who would actually
choose to support her, anyway?
- [gasps]
- Just a word of advice.
Try not say the word "Witch"
too loudly in public.
You never know who's listening
or where.
- [grunts]
Emilia, you never told me...
everyone feels that way
about you.
- I can't understand
if you don't tell me, Subaru.
- You know what?
That goes both ways, Emilia.
[music playing]
[music playing only]
[music ends]
[footsteps pattering]
Hmm?
- Subaru Natsuki,
would you mind
joining me for a bit?
- Miss Crusch, right?
- Yes, that's right.
Oh, of course.
This is probably
the first time you've seen me
out of my business attire,
isn't it?
The breeze
is pleasantly cool tonight,
perfect conditions
for sharing a drink
as we gaze out
upon the night sky.
- Uh, I'm too young
to drink alcohol.
- You're welcome
to have some water, then.
Don't worry. I won't be
drinking
enough to get drunk tonight.
[ice clinking]
- [sighs]
- Tell me,
how's the healing of your gate?
- Huh?
- Neow, neow.
- Hey!
Oh. [chuckles]
I guess not too bad.
- Hmm.
Well, Felix is excellent
with healing magic.
You can put your trust in him.
- What about you?
You seem to be
pretty busy lately.
- Yes, indeed.
My family's currently
gathering people and supplies
in response
to a certain occurrence.
Also, since word
of the royal selection spread,
I've received proposals
every day now.
I'm sure the other candidates
have as well.
- [spits]
Did you say, "Proposals"?
You mean as in marriage?!
Oh, yeah.
I guess they're all single,
aren't they?
- Does that bother you?
- Uh, not really.
It's just--
Oh, wait. That's right.
I remember
Mr. Wilhelm telling me
that he had a beautiful wife.
- Are you aware of why
he's acting as my servant?
Seems rather curious to me.
- Huh? Why is that?
- [squeal]
What are you doing out here
with Miss Crusch, Subaru?!
And, Miss Crusch,
why are you dressed
so vulnerably?
- Is it strange?
I mean, it's no different
from what I wear
when I dine with you.
- Well, yes, I know.
That's exactly the problem.
'Cause men are nothing
but wolves, Miss!
- Don't forget.
You're a man, too.
- That's enough joking around,
Felix.
Everyone who was present
at the royal selection
knows whom Subaru
has real feelings for.
- Yeah, that's true.
I heard they had
a big fight, though.
- [grumbles]
- Aww!
Don't be mad, Subaru.
You're so easy to read.
- [sighs]
- Don't cast your gaze down,
Subaru.
- Huh?
- When your eyes are clouded,
your soul darkens,
your future is closed,
and you lose sight
of your reasons to live.
When you do
what you know to be right,
what is it you possibly hope
to achieve by looking downward.
Lift your head, face forward,
and reach out.
It is not in my preferred stance
to regard you
as an insignificant enemy.
- If Miss Crusch says so,
you have neo choice
in the matter.
The point is, Subaru,
you need to hurry up
and make up with Miss Emilia.
So think about how
you accomplish that, and do it!
Seriously,
it's as simple as that.
- How I can accomplish that,
huh?
There is something,
and only I can do it.
- Huh?
- Oh?
[no audible dialogue]
- [sighs]
Yeah, I know
that's what needs to happen.
It's so clear to me now.
You don't even
have to tell me a thing.
- Hmm.
- [wind blowing]
The wind is picking up.
From the looks of things,
I'd say the weather
will be rough again tomorrow.
[wood clatters]
- What do you say, young man?
Shall we stop for now?
- Come on. You kidding me?
You've seen how far I've come
taking blows
and rolling with it, right?
- Your attitude
seems quite different.
I'm sensing a change in you
this morning.
- It's possible,
'cause Miss Crusch
gave me some much-needed advice
last night.
If I just get a chance,
I can make
any problem I have go away.
- Hmm. I see.
I must suggest
that we call it a day.
- Eh?
- Well, in my opinion,
it's become rather meaningless.
Why bother teaching someone
who's abandoned the option
to get stronger
how to use a sword
that makes him stronger?
- Uh, hang on.
What do you mean by--
- Subaru.
- Eh?
- We need to talk
about something.
- Has Rem told you
what's been going on?
- The feeling I sensed
was something like a presence
through the sense
that I share with my sister.
I wish she could have used
her clairvoyance
to get a clear picture,
but that's all I have.
- So you must have picked up
a nasty sort of synesthesia
from her, I take it?
- We're not sure
of the details yet,
but it's
from the Mathers domain,
which you know
as Margrave Roswaal's territory.
It seems some troubling movement
was seen in the vicinity
of his mansion.
Parts of the domain
are already on high alert
as we speak
- Troubling movement?
- Indeed.
We foresaw this situation
from the moment the margrave
declared his intention
to back Miss Emilia, a half-elf.
- You mean all of this is
happening because of prejudice?
- That is likely
a correct summation.
- [sputters]
The moment I leave her,
this starts happening?
- [gasps]
- Everyone around her
is an enemy.
Only one person
can take her side...
and that would be me.
Okay, then.
We have to go there and
help settle things, right?
- You mustn't, Subaru.
You have to obey
Miss Emilia's orders.
She said that you
should focus on healing,
and I agree with her.
Making sure you're healed
must take priority.
- Rem, no one's
at Emilia's side.
You and I are the only ones
who can help her.
- [gasps]
- You heard what I said,
Miss Crusch.
We're going back to the
mansion,
right back to where Emilia is.
'Til it's taken care of,
my healing will just have to--
- Subaru Natsuki,
if you leave at this time,
I'm left with no choice
- but to make you my enemy.
- Uh...
- Perhaps I need to correct
one idea you have.
I've only allowed you
to stay here as a guest
and receive treatment
because I'm contracted to do so.
- Contracted?
- Yes, that's right.
Emilia and I made an agreement
regarding your treatment
as well as your safety.
However, if you
abandon that yourself,
I am not obligated
to continue protecting you.
The moment
you leave this household,
that deal is broken,
and Emilia and I will
not hesitate to become enemies.
- I was wrong about you.
I thought
that maybe, just maybe,
you and I
could actually get along.
Your advice,
that was just a little joke
over some drinks, right?
I was stupid
to take you seriously
when you told me, an enemy,
to do what I could.
You don't want me to leave,
because getting Emilia
out of trouble
would be bad for you,
wouldn't it?
- I think you seem to have
gotten some things wrong.
- Felix, enough.
- No, I will say it.
The mistake he's making
is a bit too grave.
Even if you leave here
and rush to her side,
nothing will change.
It's a waste of time.
After making a fool of yourself
at the castle
and being clobbered by Julius,
you still don't realize that?
You'll be much better off
staying with us
and finishing up your treatment.
- I've decided.
I'm going back to Emilia.
Thanks for taking care of me,
though it wasn't for long.
- A good man knows
how to take a warning.
I guess that saying's not true.
- It's because of your warning
that I've made up my mind.
Thanks for that.
[ground dragons snorting]
Rem, how long
until we reach the mansion?
- About 2 1/2 days, I think.
- Over two days?
But it took less
than half a day to get here.
- When we came here,
we used a road
that's covered in fog now.
We'll have to use a detour.
- Who cares about a little fog?
- The fog is created
by the White Whale.
If we encounter it,
we'd never get out alive.
- [gasps]
- Thank you
for lending us your carriage.
It is very much appreciated.
In my master's stead,
thank you for all the kindness
you've shown us during our
stay.
- Please,
take care of yourselves.
[carriages rattling]
- Are you getting
anything from Ram?
- Not yet. To an extent,
our shared sense is something
consciously controlled.
I could be wrong,
but I believe
what I felt this morning
was something that exceeded
my sister's control.
- I see.
So Ram didn't even mean
to let us know about it.
Is she trying to keep us
from getting involved?
But why?
She needs me by her side.
- [sighs]
- I know I can save her.
Once I do,
I'm sure she'll understand.
She has to.
[carriage rattling]
[gasps]
Why are we stopping here?
We have to hurry.
- I'm sorry, Subaru,
but the ground dragon
can't go any farther right now.
- [sighs]
I can't sleep.
- [knock at the door]
- [gasps]
- Subaru, are you awake?
- Yeah.
[soft music playing]
- I can't sleep,
so I hoped that we could talk.
- Really?
You, too?
Can't help that, I guess.
You're pretty worried
about the mansion
after what you felt through
your shared sense, aren't you?
Hey, it'll be fine.
We're not the sort
of loveable kids
who get our feelings hurt
so easily.
We'll get right back there,
and I'll fix things.
- Yes. I've put my faith
in you, Subaru.
- [sighs]
[gasps]
You okay, Rem?
Is--Is something wrong?
Why are you holding on to me?
- Because I want to.
[energy humming]
- Hey, I--
I know this feeling.
- Because I'm healing your gate,
just as Felix did, Subaru.
- Oh, right. Healing.
That makes sense.
Yeah, sure. Of course you are.
[chuckles]
Thanks, Rem...
really.
Emilia, she'll be...
angry with me, won't she?
- If you take the time
to properly face her
and communicate
how you feel with words,
I'm sure she'll understand.
You're a truly wonderful person,
after all.
- Yeah?
I am?
[chuckles] I guess so, huh?
Emilia is hopeless without me,
because I...
care about her so much.
- Maybe save a tiny bit
of that for me as well.
Now don't go anywhere,
okay, Subaru?
And sweet dreams.
- [sighs]
Rem, wake up!
We overslept, so--[gasps]
- Well, now, good morning.
How can I--
- Have you seen
the blue-haired girl
who checked in with me?!
- The--The lady you were with--
- Tell me where she is!
- I was just gonna tell you
that she left during the
night.
Here are the things
she left behind for you.
- [gasps]
- What the hell?
What are you thinking, Rem?
I thought for sure
you would understand me.
How could you do this?
REM: Dear Subaru,
I'll be gone by the time
you read this letter,
and when you do, I'm sure
you'll be very angry with me.
I won't ask you to forgive me
for leaving you behind
to go to the mansion.
- ...in there
might agree to your offer.
- But please understand.
It would be very dangerous
to bring you there right now.
- Huh?
- Are you the one
who's named Otto?
- Uh...
Okay, yes,
I'll accept your payment...
- So please just be patient
and wait here for me to return.
- [sighs]
- So that's it, huh?
You think I'm a useless
good-for-nothing, too, Rem?
- Oh, man.
I think
I've just been introduced
to someone who could be
real trouble for me.
- Fine. Whatever.
But if you won't trust me,
then why should I depend on you?
- [shudders]
- [ground dragon wails]
- [grunts]
- I'm sorry, but would it
be okay if we turn back
now?
- What? After coming this far?
- My ground dragon
is frightened.
- [snarling]
- It knows by instinct
that this place
is too dangerous to approach.
- So where are we, anyway?
- Looks like we're already
in the Mathers domain,
right by a village
that's called Arlam.
- Got it.
- Wait! Please!
Don't go out there!
Let's just head back, okay?
- Think you've taken me
close enough, Otto.
You're welcome to take the money
and all my stuff, okay?
- I can't do that.
Please, Natsuki, rethink this.
Come back!
- [panting]
What is this?
It's suddenly so quiet.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[whoosh]
What was that?
[shudders]
[panting]
[no audible dialogue]
Damn it!
[panting]
I'm back.
[chuckles]
[music playing]
[footsteps crunching]
[knocks]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[groans]
[music playing]
[shuddering]
- ♪ The ticket is
all that I have lost... ♪
- [gasps] Where's Rem?
Where is she?
What is this? What happened?
- [singing in Japanese]
- That's right.
Rem. Rem is--
Rem.
Rem. Rem.
- ♪ The dreams rot off
and drop away ♪
[singing in Japanese]
REM: So please just be patient
and wait here for me to return.
When all of this
is taken care of,
I'll come back for you.
Please, be safe.
And I beg you,
I beg you to wait
for my return.
Please.
From your...
Rem.
- [crying]
[music playing]
[door rattles]
[crying]
[chorus vocalizing]
[vomits]
[coughs]
They're dead.
No. No, no.
If I just get a chance,
I can make
any problem I have go away.
This is wrong.
This isn't what I wanted.
Someone...
[footsteps echoing]
[Subaru crying]
[footsteps continue]
[door creaks]
Ram, no.
Petra.
[gasps]
[sobs] No.
It's not my fault!
[gasps]
[woman vocalizing]
It's not...
[crying]
Emilia.
Is she...
[door creaks]
[crying]
[music ends]
[footsteps echoing]
[inhales]
- [crackle]
- [winces]
Huh?
[wailing]
[shattering]
[gasping]
- [vocalizing]
- [gasping]
PUCK: You're too late, Subaru.
- KADOMON: Hey.
- [chorus vocalizes]
- You listening?
- Huh?
- Now, don't you "huh" me.
What's your problem?
It's like
you suddenly spaced out.
- Oh.
[bell tolling]
- Are you okay?
[bell continues]
[sighs]
- Subaru.
- KADOMON: Hey!
- What's wrong? Do you feel ill?
- [gasps]
- Um...
what's the matter?
[yelps]
- Whoa! Wait, Subaru!
- Aw, come on now.
- What's wrong? What is it?
- Easy, easy.
Not in front of my shop.
- Calm down, please.
- [sobbing]
- Are you okay?
[music playing]
- I'm pretty sure
there's neothing any of us
can do to help him.
His wounds are one thing,
but there's neo helping
his mental state.
- Do you know how this happened?
- No clue. I've checked
every inch of him, but...
- What are the odds
of it being a curse?
- Pretty low.
There's neo indication
of any interference using mana.
[Crusch sighs]
If Felix is unable to help,
I'm afraid that no one
in this household
can do anything to heal him.
Sorry we can't assist you.
- No, I can't thank you enough
for everything you've done,
as well
as your generous concern.
He's right.
There's no mana interference,
but...
the Witch's miasma.
Thank you for everything.
I thank you in my master's stead
for your kindness and
hospitality during our stay.
- Please give Emilia
this message as well.
Let us compete for the throne
in a manner that will bring
neither of us shame.
- FELIX: Hey.
- Hmm?
- I understand why you're
going back to the mansion,
but can anyone there heal him?
- He utters our names,
albeit only occasionally.
He says my name,
my sister's name, also...
Miss Emilia's.
I'm hoping
that if he can see her,
maybe his condition will change.
- I realize this is tasteless,
but I must ask you something.
How can you give
so much of yourself
for Subaru Natsuki?
Your relationship with him
is not the same
as that of a master and servant,
like Felix and mine,
but I hesitate to conclude
that your behavior
and the glances you cast
are those a woman gives a man.
I'm sorry.
That's really too forward.
- Forget I said--
- No. No, it's not that.
It's just...
well, how can I put it?
You see...
all of this is because Subaru
is really special to me.
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- Um...
CRUSCH: Please, forgive me.
I was stunned speechless
for a moment.
I'd say Subaru Natsuki
is a lucky man.
- Hah! You can say that again.
If he ever recovers,
I'll have to make sure
to tease him to the max.
- [giggles]
- Safe travels.
- Good luck with everything.
[music playing]
[fire crackling]
- I know I mustn't let
my personal feelings interfere,
but...
if I'm being completely honest
with myself,
I felt happy to have
so much one-on-one time with you
at Miss Crusch's house.
I realize once we
get back to the mansion,
things won't be like that.
Even though I knew
something was troubling you,
I'm sorry.
Even though I heard that you
had quarreled with Miss
Emilia,
causing a rift
between the two of you,
- I'm sorry.
- [ground dragon sighs]
- I know you'll be all right.
Just you wait.
You're demonically inspired.
And so driven.
You're a remarkable person.
[carriage rattling]
It's too quiet.
[gasps]
[panting]
That was Sister! She's...
I have to get back quickly.
[wind blowing]
- [groans]
[ominous music playing]
[stammering]
- Get away.
Don't you touch him!
[grunts]
[gags]
[chain rattles]
[gasps]
Damn Witch Cultists.
Huma!
[winces]
[gasps] Subaru!
Bring him back! [gasps]
You bastards.
You stole my sister's horn
and stole my reason to live.
But that wasn't enough?
Now you've come here to steal
my reason to die, too!
I'll kill you!
[rumbling]
[water dripping]
- [hissing]
- [gasps]
- Yes, I see.
This is certainly
an interesting development.
So tell me...
you wouldn't happen to be
the one known as Pride,
now, would you?
[gasps]
[knuckle creaking]
[muffled] I guess you're
not going to answer me, are you?
[gasps]
Ah, right.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I sometimes forget the social
trivialities when I'm excited.
I am a Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult,
representing Sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti, yes.
[men's chorus vocalizing]
- [stammering]
- Ah, how utterly comical.
What a very entertaining sight.
[squeals] Very, very, very...
truly, truly,
truly entertaining indeed!
My brain trembles.
Now, what has brought him here?
- Dragon...
- Eh?
- carriage.
- Really?!
Ah, aren't ground dragons great?
They obey diligently,
work diligently,
and play their roles
as a species diligently.
They're just fantastic!
- Killed.
- [grunts]
Of course.
Your diligence
is following my orders
brought the ground dragon,
diligence itself, to the ground.
Oh, my brain trembles,
trembles, trembles, trembles!
[hisses] Then again,
a dead ground dragon
is the very definition
of sloth.
Nonetheless,
we must push forward,
clean up the area at once.
With the day of the Ordeal
upon us,
we mustn't allow our existence
to be discovered.
What of his friend?
- Unknown.
- Ah.
Well, that presents
another dilemma.
Unknown if she's alive or dead.
That makes you...
the truly slothful one.
[shrieks] You fool!
With the Ordeal before us,
you let a problem remain?
Is this the sincerity you show
in return for our Gospel?!
[inhales] Such action is sloth.
It's sloth! It's sloth!
Please forgive us the sloth
that has led us
to betray your goodwill.
Ah, yes, love.
We must repay love
with love, with love.
Bring the girl here.
If she lives, then kill her.
If she doesn't,
then bring me her bloody head!
It's love!
We must repay love with love!
[chorus vocalizing]
Now then.
Now then. Now then.
- [moans]
- Now then...
you will look deep into my eyes.
Answer me,
and be sure to choose
your words carefully.
I want you to tell me
why such dense pangs of love
hang with sheer abundance
upon your person.
Do you not own
a copy of the Gospel?
- Huh?
- Oh, it saddens me
to be ignored!
I treated you so kindly,
and yet and yet
and yet and yet and yet
and yet and yet and yet and--
[babbles]
In that case, I will change
the order of my questions.
Let me ask you this...
- [slurps]
- [wincing]
[joints popping]
...as I'm curious.
Why do you pretend
that your mind is broken?
[chorus continues]
- [sighs]
[sighs]
- No, no, no, no.
I truly have my doubts about
your state of mind right now,
which is why I ask why,
for what reason,
for what purpose,
for what resolution,
for what possible outcome
do you act so utterly crazed?
- [shudders]
- Your so-called insanity
is far too sane.
To behave so cleverly
and quietly
as if seeking sympathy
for your situation,
it is a demeaning insult,
a true madness.
- [groaning]
- You are a fake,
a poorly acted madman.
If your insanity was genuine,
you would pay no heed
to the gazes of others.
- [sobbing]
- [laughs] How comical.
How completely comical!
- [laughs]
- [weeps]
- How I pity you.
I pity
your wretched, despicable,
wicked, ugly, lowly,
diminutive, sinful being
from the bottom of my heart.
Yet despite those shortcomings,
you are so loved!
[yelps] You mean
that you'd rather waste away
in stagnation than repay
the goodwill shown to you?
That makes you...
truly slothful.
- [rocks falling]
- Oh?
[chain jangling]
[music playing]
- I found your lair.
What have you done?!
- [wails]
How absolutely fantastic
this is!
A girl, a lone girl,
is so badly injured.
Yet she presses on for this boy!
- That's enough
of your nonsense, Witch Cultist!
You're fools to carry out
your insubordinate acts
in Lord Roswaal's domain
without his permission!
In my absent master's stead,
I will bring
the death penalty upon you!
- And you'll do all that
in your battered state?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you really only came here
to retrieve this boy,
and if that's the case,
you should stop saying
these tempting things
that sound, oh, so attractive.
- Don't you touch him.
- Eh? What was that?
- I said don't you touch him!
- [squeals]
That shot was utterly fantastic,
a work of art,
but tell me, why does such
a believer in love as yourself
adhere to someone like him?
- You know nothing
about Subaru, bastard!
El Huma!
- Oh. Oh. Amazing.
That was nothing short
of amazing.
- [groans]
[chorus vocalizing]
- [moans]
Rem.
[chorus continues]
[no audible dialogue]
[chorus ends]
- My brain trembles.
- [bones cracking]
- [grunts]
[silence]
[robe flutters]
- By the Authority of Sloth,
I summon the Unseen Hand.
Look at her, boy.
- Just look at her.
- [moans]
- This is a result
of your actions.
- By doing nothing,
you practiced sloth,
and because of that,
the girl is dead.
You killed her.
It was all your doing!
Or more to the point,
your lack of doing anything!
How awful! How completely awful!
- SUBARU: You...
- With my arm,
with my fingers, it was you.
It was you. It was you.
[shrill]
It was you! It was you!
You killed her.
- Stop it.
- "It hurts.
"It hurts! It hurts!
"Help me. Help me!
"Agh! Help me!
Help me!"
[shrieks]
[hisses] "Subaru, please help."
- Betelgeuse!
I'll kill you!
- I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
- [laughing]
I finally got you
to call me by my name.
I'm deeply touched
by your kind gesture.
- I'll kill you!
I'll kill you,
you son of a bitch! Die!
- Die, damn it!
- [murmurs]
- [wailing]
- [giggles]
This place has turned
into quite the mess, hasn't it?
I'll just leave it!
All right, men.
Time for you to resume
your previously planned duties
and rendezvous
with the other fingers.
The Ordeal will proceed
on the scheduled day.
- [Subaru wailing]
- Now, as for you and
- your position in all this...
- Bastard, I'll kill you...
- to be completely honest
with you,
I have no idea what it is,
so I shall simply judge you
as our lord sees fit.
- [screaming]
- I will leave you bound here.
Should the Gospel happen
to find its way to you,
I'm sure you'll be saved
in divine intervention.
- Kill you!
- [laughing]
- I'll kill--
I will kill you, you bastard!
- [laughing]
- You hear me?!
- I'll kill you. I'll kill you!
- Oh?
Ah, yes, you were also
a believer in love.
You sacrificed yourself for it,
defying your own faith,
but you fell just before
your feelings reached him,
leaving your love
with nowhere to go,
unknown, unheard,
and unrequited.
- I'll kill you!
- [chuckles]
That makes you
a truly slothful one.
- I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
- [laughing]
I'll kill you. I'll kill you!
I'll kill you.
- [laughing]
- [screaming]
[scream fades]
[weakly] I'll kill you.
- I'll kill you.
- [head thumps]
I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
[gasps] I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
[groans]
[shuffling]
Eh? Rem?
[scrapes]
You're alive?
[music playing]
Rem-Rem.
Rem-Rem. Thank God.
Rem!
I was so worried!
Rem! [groans]
[groaning]
You okay?
Hey, Rem.
- Hu...
- [gasps]
- ...ma.
[metal shatters]
- Rem, wh-what'd you do?
- Please...
stay...
alive.
- Rem, wait.
No. Don't leave me.
- Live...
for...
me.
I...
love you.
- Rem?
[crying]
[crying fades]
[music playing]
Okay, Rem. Let's go.
[music continues]
[gasping]
[snow crunching]
Damn you, Betelgeuse.
[wind gusting]
[crying]
Betelgeuse, damn you!
Betelgeuse!
[rumbling]
PUCK: Sleep...
along with my daughter.
[instrumental playing]
KADOMON: Hey.
- [gasps]
- You listening?
- Huh?
- Now, don't you "huh" me.
What's your problem?
It's like
you suddenly spaced out.
- I, uh...
REM: Subaru.
- Rem-Rem.
- Yes?
What's the matter?
You look like
you've just seen a ghost.
- It's you.
- Me?
What is it?
- Rem-Rem.
- Yes?
- I'm just...
- Look...
I hate to interrupt when you're
just getting heated up,
but I can't do business
with you two flirtin' there.
[market chatter]
REM: Do you think
I could ask you something?
- What is it?
- Well, I may be mistaken,
but it's just, um...
that unpleasant odor.
It seems to have grown
even stronger on you.
- Unpleasant odor, huh.
Well, if that's got you worried,
then you can
just keep holding my hand.
- Huh?
I mean, it feels a lot safer
like this, doesn't it?
- [gasps]
Yes.