- [gagging]
No, this is bad!
Very bad!
- Subaru, what's wrong?
[pop music playing]
♪ ♪
- I see where this is going.
It's how they suck you in.
Run away!
Get out of here!
Uh...
[register beeping]
[door bell chimes]
[grunts]
[sighs]
- [screams]
[pop music playing]
♪ ♪
- Eh, maybe this one instead.
Stay with me!
- That's 363 yen.
[pop music playing]
- Oh, a jagged-edged 10.
♪ ♪
[door bell chiming]
Hang on!
No matter what...
[unsettling music]
I'm gonna save you!
[gasps]
That's what I get for holing up
in my room all day gaming.
Guess my eyes are tired.
Hmm?
[distant foot traffic bustling]
[gasps]
Huh?
[church bells ringing]
[birds chirping]
What's going on?
[distant horse whinnying]
I'd say I was dreaming,
but this is obviously
really happening.
Totally not fake.
[gasping]
So does this mean
I've been summoned
across the universe
to another world?
- [singing in Latin]
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
- [panting]
[giggles]
[animals snorting]
- Well,
from the looks of things,
I'd say this is some kind
of fantasy world
with medieval-style culture.
A realm where demi-humans
are commonplace,
there's always a war
or an adventure to go on,
and in this magical world,
I must have--
- [screams]
- Hey, watch out!
[all shouting]
- This is it.
It's totally happening!
This must be an event pop
where I'll learn
to produce magic!
[shouts]
[animal snarling]
- Look out!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[all cheering]
- [chuckles]
Guess it's a little too early
for me to use magic
in this world.
[grunts]
[quirky music]
I can't read any of this.
- Hey, boy.
- [gasps]
- Those are some
weird-looking clothes.
You're not from around here,
are ya?
- So are these--
- Appas, the freshest
you'll find.
- At least we speak
the same language.
Let's see if...
- Huh?
Where's that money from?
You can't use that stuff
out here in Lugunica,
and if that's all you got,
then you're flat broke,
so don't waste my time,
freeloader.
Get outta here!
- That answers that.
Guess I'll have to stick
to good-old
information-gathering.
[all screaming]
[blow lands]
[grunts]
[groans]
[door creaks]
- This place
is for demi-humans only.
- [gasps]
[door creaks]
Ow, my eye!
I can't see!
[screams]
Is this how it's supposed
to be?
'Cause none of it makes sense!
This is a different world
summons, right?
Where's my main character set-up
and status bar?
Damn.
[scoffs]
Looks like my cell phone
still works.
But there's no point
in even having it now!
And the gear they've started
me off with is a joke.
If you're gonna summon lazy-ass
kids like me to your world,
you'd better overhaul
your crappy welfare program!
Start me off
with an Excalibur sword
or a magic cloak!
[groans]
And besides,
if I were transported
all this way,
where's the cute girl
who brought me here?
Why would she do that
and then bail on me?
[grunts]
Yes, you're finally here!
It's nice to meet you,
cute girl...
[gasping]
- What are you going on
and on about?
- If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
- Aw, crap.
It's already
compulsory event time.
- Move it, move it!
[both gasping]
[panting]
Move it, you guys!
Hurry!
Out of my way!
- Yes!
I knew you'd find me eventually,
cute girl who summoned me!
- Hmm?
Summoned?
I dunno what
you're talking about,
but I'm really busy.
Sorry.
Now live strong, okay?
[giggles]
- Wait, what?
Where are you going?
- [grunting]
[giggles]
[all gasping]
- So, did seeing that
make you feel any less hostile,
by any chance?
- Actually, it rained
on our parade
and made things worse.
- Of course it did.
Calm down, Subaru Natsuki.
Since ancient times,
it's the rule
that anyone summoned
into a different world
displays supernatural powers.
If I just believe
in myself hard enough,
those powers will kick on
and pave my way to future glory!
You loathsome EXP!
- [groans]
[both shouting]
- That's the first time
I ever hit somebody.
Guess I never expected it
to hurt me,
but it doesn't matter
because this world is set up
so I'll be strong!
My adrenaline is surging!
I can do anything!
[gasps]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It was all my fault!
Seriously, forgive me, please!
Spare me!
[screaming]
[shouting]
- [grunts]
- Play games with us, will ya?
Die, scum!
[all grunting]
- [shouting]
- [snarls]
- That's enough.
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- Uh?
- [gasps]
[miraculous music]
♪ ♪
- And just who
in the hell are you?
- Stop now and I'll forgive you,
if you would be so kind
as to give back what you stole.
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
- You can't be serious.
- Please.
It's very important to me.
I'll turn the other cheek
concerning the other belongings,
but I can't let you have that,
so hand it over.
- You mean you didn't come
to save this kid?
- What strange clothes he has.
If you're asking me
if I have any connection to him,
I'd have to say no.
- Well then you've got
no business with us,
little girl.
If someone stole from you,
it was that brat
who just ran by.
- Yeah, what he said!
That way!
She ran that way!
- Hmm.
Those three don't appear
to be lying,
so I need
to go after her.
[panting]
[all sighing]
But regardless of that,
I can't overlook
what's going on here.
[whirring]
[all groaning]
- Magic?
- Hey, mess with us, will ya?
[all groaning]
I don't care
if you can use magic.
I'm gonna kill you!
You think you can win
when it's two against one?
Do you?
- Indeed.
Two against one may be unfair.
- All right, then.
Two against two
should even things up.
[meows]
- [grunts]
You use a spiritual arts?
- Correct.
Retreat now
and I won't chase you.
Decide quickly.
I'm in a hurry.
- You bitch!
Next time I see you,
I won't go easy on you!
- Do anything to her
and I'll haunt you
and your kin forever.
Not that you'll have any kin
if I take care of things now.
[both panting]
- [exhales]
You really saved me.
Thank you.
- Don't move.
- [gasps]
[groaning]
- Ah-ha.
You avert your eyes due
to your guilty conscience.
Looks like my judgment
was spot on as always.
- You sure?
I think it was just
an instinctive male reaction
to avoid tension
or rudeness.
I didn't sense
any malice at all.
- That's enough out of you,
Puck.
Now, listen.
I want you to tell me
who stole my insignia.
- Uh, yeah,
really sorry about this,
but I don't have
the slightest clue,
to be honest with you.
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- Wait.
Oh, no, it couldn't be!
Did I really make a wrong turn
or maybe come around
the long way?
- [chuckles]
If I were you,
I'd hurry after her
before she gets too far.
I could help if you--
[grunts]
- Aww.
You shouldn't have tried
to get up.
What should we do?
- It's none of our business.
He won't die or anything.
We'll just leave him as is.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
- You say that,
but I bet you'll still help him.
- I will not!
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, right.
Absolutely not!
There's no way
I'm gonna save him.
Understand?
- Man, she's even super cute
when she's mad.
That's another world's fantasy
for you.
- [groans]
Whoa, hang on.
Am I in somebody's lap?
- [gasps]
You're awake?
- A little weird for a cute girl
to be this hairy,
but whatever.
Wait!
This can't be right!
[shouts]
- We were just trying
to make you happy
and comfortable
until you woke up.
There's no reason
to get freaked out.
- First of all,
stop talking in that high voice.
Nobody with half a brain
would confuse a cat
for the main heroine.
- Aww, just listen to you.
Seeing you so happy made turning
myself bigger totally worth it.
- I'm not happy at all!
[grunts]
- [laughs]
[quirky music]
- I'm sorry about this.
You stayed with me
the whole time
I was unconscious.
- Don't get the wrong idea.
I only stuck around because
there are some things
I wanna ask you.
I took the time and trouble
to heal your wounds for you.
I also made Puck act
as your pillow
until you finally woke up.
This was for my own benefit,
but now that you're up,
I need you to repay me in kind.
- Well, for such a normal favor,
you're making it sound like
I really owe you big time.
- That's not the way I see it.
Now then, you have an idea
who stole my insignia, right?
- What?
Hang on.
Is your insignia one
of those badge things
that shows your social status?
- A rather crude description,
but that's it,
more or less.
About this big
with a jewel in the center.
- I'm sorry but no matter
how many times you ask,
I still won't know.
- I see.
I guess there's no helping that,
but you've given me
the information
that you know nothing,
and that answer was in exchange
for healing you,
so I'm still somewhat satisfied
with how things turned out.
- Okay.
- Well, I'm in quite a hurry,
so I have to go.
Your wounds should
be better now,
but I highly suggest
that next time
you don't do dangerous things
like wander
into deserted alleys alone.
[gasps]
I'm not concerned.
I'm just warning you.
If anything like that happens
to you again,
I already know that saving you
won't be of any benefit to me,
so don't expect any help.
Bye.
- Sorry.
She's so insincere sometimes,
but don't think badly of her,
okay?
- Insincere, huh?
I think this goes beyond that.
She was in such a hurry
to find what was stolen from her
yet she stopped to help me.
She even came up with that
lame excuse for a favor
so I wouldn't feel I owed her,
even though I'm
a total stranger.
Anyone who lives like that--
[grunting]
[dramatic music]
Is just gonna end up wasting
their whole life!
Hey, wait up!
♪ ♪
- Was there something else
you needed?
Just so you know,
I can only spend
a little more time
with you, okay?
- Figured you
were gonna shut me down.
Anyway, you lost something
important, right?
Well then,
let me help you find it.
- You said you didn't
know anything about my insignia.
- But I can remember her face!
If I see her again,
I'll know!
- [groans]
You're so strange.
Well, anyway,
I won't be able
to offer you any reward.
- Listen, I don't need one.
I'm here because
I wanna thank you
and to show how much
I appreciate your help.
- I didn't do anything
deserving of that.
I told you I've already
received amicable compensation
for healing your wounds.
- In that case,
I guess I'm gonna help you
for my own sake, too.
I should probably set
an objective, so, uh, right.
One good deed per day.
- U--uh...
[groans]
- I don't sense any malice here,
so I think you can
just accept his offer.
After all,
the more shields between you
and the ruffians,
the better.
- A shield?
That's what you want me
around for?
- I meant what I said, though.
I can't do anything
to reward you.
- No problem at all.
Just leave everything to me.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I know what I told you before,
but isn't this town too huge
to find one little thing in?
- This town is the capital
of Lugunica.
How could you possibly
not know that?
Uh...
- Hey, that's right.
How rude of us.
We haven't asked his name yet.
Shouldn't we all
introduce ourselves?
- Oh, yeah.
Guess so.
Might as well go ahead
and get the ball rolling first,
then.
My name is Subaru Natsuki.
Not only am I totally clueless,
I'm also broke beyond compare!
Nice to meet ya!
- And that's how
you introduce yourself.
You really do sound hopeless.
And my name is Puck.
It's nice to meet you!
[grunts]
- It's very unusual
to see someone
who can touch a spirit
so casually like that.
Where are you from, exactly?
- Well, if things follow
the usual pattern,
it's a small island nation
to the east.
- But Lugunica
is the eastern-most nation
on our continental map.
There are no more countries
in that direction.
- No way.
Really?
There's nothing east of here?
- You have no idea
where you are,
you have no money,
you can't read,
and you seem to have
no one around who can help you.
You might be in an even more
precarious position than I am.
Uh, Subaru, right?
- Uh...
[gasps]
Yes, that's my name.
- All that aside,
I gotta admit,
you seem like you're
in pretty good shape.
- I do try
to work out every day.
- You see, when you're
the shut-in protector
of your own house,
you gotta stay fit
as much as possible.
- I'm not sure if I understand
exactly what a shut-in is,
but I assume it means
you're from a reputable family,
right?
- Hey, what are you--
- Your fingers, too.
They're very pretty.
They don't look like
the working hands
of a peasant at all,
and your muscles don't look
like the kind you gain
from doing field work.
- [gasps]
U--um, yes.
So anyway,
I know your cat's name now,
but I still haven't heard
you say your name yet.
- Oh, my name?
- [chuckles nervously]
[wind blows]
- It's...
It's Satella.
[both gasping]
No family name.
So that's the way
you may address me, all right?
- I see.
Satella it is.
That's a nice name.
- [gasps]
- [sighs]
You have got terrible taste.
- Right.
Time to get back
to asking around!
- Subaru,
that child over there,
do you get the feeling
she's lost?
- Uh?
- [whimpering]
- Maybe, but what about
our questioning?
- That's also important,
but if she's lost,
we have to do something.
- [whimpering]
- I'm in no place to talk
after you saved me,
but do you fully comprehend
the position we're in?
- I do,
but there's a little girl
who's crying.
You can see that, right?
- [grunts]
- If you don't wanna do this
with me,
that's fine.
Thanks for your assistance,
Subaru.
I'm sure I can handle things
on my own from here on out,
but first I'm gonna help
that little girl.
- [whimpers]
[gasps]
- Hey there.
It looks like something's
the matter.
Maybe I can help you.
Did you come here on your own
or with your mommy and daddy?
- [whimpers]
- Oh, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to make you cry.
I'm just here to help,
not to do anything bad.
I promise.
- What you see before you
is a rarity around here;
A jagged-edged 10 yen coin.
- [gasps]
- Observe closely
as I take this coin
and clutch it tightly
in my hand.
Tight, tight, tight,
like that.
Now, where'd it go?
- [gasps]
Huh?
- [chuckles]
[quirky music]
Well, take a look at this!
I figured out where
the coin was hiding.
- [gasps]
- Here you go.
It's yours.
Like I said,
it's rare,
so take good care of it.
- [exhales]
[giggles]
Thank you, sir!
- I see.
You got separated
from your mom, huh?
Yeah, that can be kinda scary.
Well, don't worry.
We'll help you.
Me and this
young lady right here,
we'll find them
in no time for you.
Wow, look at us.
People who don't know us
probably think they're looking
at a young married couple
and their kid, huh?
Is that embarrassing or what?
- At best,
I can't really see you
as anything more
than her older brother.
- What makes you think
I'm so young, huh?
- [gasps]
Mommy!
[both gasping]
- [laughing]
- It looks like
she finally found her.
- Yeah.
I'm so relieved.
- Okay, so in my opinion,
that whole string of events
with the little girl
was nothing but a side quest,
but what benefit
will you insist
that you got out of it?
Go on.
Tell me.
- That's easy.
Now we can continue our search
with our minds at ease
knowing we did the right thing.
Anyway, why'd you end up
helping me with that?
Thought you said
you were against the idea.
- Could say I just wanted
to show off my magic trick,
but that'd be a lie.
Like I told you before,
finding your insignia will be
my one good deed for the day.
- I know that was the plan,
but since you helped
the little girl,
isn't your one good deed over?
- You are being super nit-picky!
It doesn't hurt to do more
than one nice thing
in a day,
does it?
I just got tomorrow's out
of the way.
My plan is to get a week's worth
of good deeds
taken care of early.
- If I were to guess,
you're the type that basically
wastes their whole life, right?
- Seriously?
You're the last person
who should be saying that
to anyone.
- I admit you're not
a bad boy, though.
- Why do you act like
I'm so much younger than you?
Honestly, I'm guessing
there aren't that
many differences between us.
- Well, you may think that,
but all of your guesses
would be wrong
because I'm actually half elf.
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
Ah, no wonder.
It makes sense now.
From the moment I saw you,
I thought you were cute.
Elves are always beautiful,
aren't they?
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
What is it?
- Didn't you hear
what I just said?
Listen, I'm trying to tell you
that I'm a half elf.
- Yeah, I heard you.
- [groans]
[grunts]
- [gasps]
- [shouts]
- What the heck did you
do that for?
- I just had to do something
about this unbearable tingle
I'm feeling.
- That's the weirdest reason
for punching somebody
I've ever heard,
though I'll forgive you,
since it was squishy.
- I didn't hit you in the face
out of anger or anything!
In fact,
it was quite the opposite!
- Subaru, you are such
a dunderhead.
- Yeah, so who says "dunderhead"
in this day and age?
And why are you insulting me
in the first place?
- [grunts]
Whatever.
More importantly,
we have to get back
to the search,
so let's go.
- Hey, wait a minute.
Just running around
without a plan
is never a good idea.
There's a basic rule
of searches.
- What are you talking about?
- Yeah, like revisiting
the scene of the crime.
Where exactly
was your insignia stolen?
And then she told me
it was right around here,
so after I insisted that
she leave everything to me,
I valiantly came back
to this fruit stand
to look for some clues.
- I thought I had a customer,
but you're that same broke kid
from earlier.
- You really wanna take
that attitude?
Haven't you noticed I'm not
who I was before?
- Huh?
- Just look who
I brought with me.
I'd bet it's someone who
just might become a regular.
- Uh, Subaru,
I'm not exactly sure
what you expected of me,
but I actually don't
have any money, either.
- Huh?
S--seriously?
- So what did you
wanna ask me about
now that I'm stuck here
with not one
but two broke customers, boy?
- Well, we're actually looking
for someone,
and we were hoping we could
ask you a few questions,
if you wouldn't mind.
- That was a sarcastic way
of saying
I don't have time
for broke losers.
Now get out of here!
Scram!
- Hey, mister!
[all grunting]
- Thanks for your help earlier.
- What brings you back this way?
- It's my husband's shop,
so we just wanted
to stop by.
- [groans]
- Your husband?
Uh...
- [giggles]
- Huh?
- Hey, there's my girl.
Now, wait a second.
How exactly do you know
these two good-for-nothings?
- She got lost
and these two found her
and then helped
bring her back to me.
- [snarls]
- [chuckles]
- Thanks again, lady.
Here.
- [gasps]
- She was hoping we'd find you.
Please accept that token
as her way of showing gratitude
for what you've done.
- Thank you very much.
[dramatic music]
[chuckles]
- [giggles]
- [clears throat]
[both gasps]
Sorry about all that before.
You helped my daughter.
I wanna show my appreciation,
so ask me anything.
[both chuckling]
[both gasp]
- There, you see?
A little bit of extra effort
on our part
came back around
and worked in our favor.
[uneasy music]
♪ ♪
- The air,
the atmosphere,
and most likely the attitudes
of the people living here
are awful.
Are you sure
she's really out here?
- You're saying she's
a nimble little blonde, right?
'Cause it might be
that Felt girl
I see around from time to time.
She's well-known in the slums.
Dunno where she lives, though.
That's about all I can tell you.
- Maybe someone will tell us
if we ask.
- No one would sell out
their own,
especially to a couple
of strangers,
so asking would be useless.
- Maybe we should just
come back later.
- Whatever it is you wanna do,
I suggest that
you decide quickly,
'cause I've just about run out
of time here.
- Out of time?
What do you mean?
- I'm able to take on
this cute appearance
but I'm a spirit.
It takes a lot of mana for me
to appear in physical form.
So when the day becomes night,
I return to the crystal
I was summoned from
and prepare for the sun
to emerge.
[sighs]
On average,
my ideal time to stay out
is roughly 9:00 to 5:00.
- 9:00 to 5:00?
Sounds like you work
in an office.
Employment terms for spirits
are pretty severe.
- We'll be fine without Puck.
We need to keep moving forward
on this.
- Sorry, but I'm at my limit.
Good luck, you two.
- It's almost like he's dying
when he disappears.
- Sorry to have worked you
so hard today, Puck.
We'll handle things from here,
so settle in
and get some rest.
- [exhales]
Don't do anything reckless,
all right?
If it comes down to it,
you can always use the od
to summon me again.
- [grunts]
- I'm leaving things
in your hands, Subaru.
Good luck.
- [gasps]
[whooshing]
[gasps]
Hey, wow.
I don't think I've been in one
of these
alone-with-a-girl situations
since I was in grade school.
- Don't get any pervy ideas,
Subaru.
I can use magic, you know.
- I won't, okay?
The more important issue at hand
is how we find Felt now.
- I'll contact
the lesser spirits.
- Lesser spirits?
- Precisely.
They're beings
that haven't quite
become full fledged spirits yet.
They grow little by little
over time,
and when they gain
enough strength
and self awareness,
they become full spirits
just like Puck.
[dramatic music]
- Huh?
♪ ♪
Uh...
Oh.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- It's getting more desolate
and quiet.
- Hard to believe that
she actually lives out here.
- I know, but the lesser spirits
specifically said
they saw someone who looked
like Felt headed
in this direction.
- Excuse me, man.
Know if a girl named Felt
lives somewhere up this way?
- Huh?
You're looking for Felt?
- Mm-hmm.
- There's nothing that way
except Old Man Rom's loot house.
[chuckles]
I guess she must have stolen
something pretty important
for you two to come out here.
Well, I wish you luck
on bargaining
to try to get it back.
Live strong, okay?
[both gasping]
[distant wolves howling]
- What was he talking about?
Why do I have to pay money
to get back
something stolen from me?
- Don't worry about a thing.
Just leave everything to me.
I can handle the negotiations.
- All right, then.
I'll just leave everything
in your hands.
- You agreed
to that pretty easily.
I figured you'd
say something like,
"You want me to leave this
to a useless boy like you?
"That's such a ridiculous idea,
it actually hurts my stomach."
And although that would stomp
all over my feelings,
I'd still decide
to keep helping you anyway.
- I'd never say something
that mean to anyone.
Of course,
to tell you the truth,
I'd be lying if I said
you haven't been holding
me back a little bit.
- Oh, great!
That's good to know!
- But again,
I'm leaving this in your hands.
- [gasps]
- If it actually goes well,
I'll consider it a bonus.
- Now, you know,
if you said something more like,
"Work hard for me, okay?"
I'd probably feel
a whole lot more motivated.
- Sorry, I can't force myself
to say something like that.
However, please do your best.
- [exhales]
[chuckles]
Yeah, you got it.
I'll go in first.
You stay outside
and keep watch.
I won't be back too late,
but you can have dinner
without me
if you get too hungry.
- Don't say dumb things
like that.
- Okay, let's see here.
- And be careful.
- Sure, sure.
Now, don't come in until
I say it's all right, Satella.
What's the matter?
- [gasps]
[grunts]
Nothing, never mind.
If you can manage
to get my insignia back,
then I'll apologize.
- Anybody here?
Nope.
[floorboards creaking]
So, am I walking into
a demon nest or a snake pit?
In a fantasy world,
either is totally plausible.
This is all stolen loot?
Impressive.
Why isn't anyone here?
A shack full of stolen goods
and no one around to guard it?
[splashing]
[grunting]
[shuddering]
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, dear.
You found that?
- [gasps]
- Well, I have no choice, then.
No choice at all.
- [shouts]
[slicing]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
That burns.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Oh, crap!
Is all of this my blood?
[gagging]
No, this is bad!
Very bad!
[gagging]
[thuds]
- Um, Subaru,
what's wrong?
Are you okay?
- Don't come in.
Run away.
Get out of here.
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[slicing]
[screams]
♪ ♪
- [breathing erratically]
[gagging]
[gasping]
Stay with me.
Hang on.
No matter what happens,
I'm gonna save you.
- What's the matter with you,
kid?
It looks like you've seen
a ghost or something.
- Huh?
- You were asking about these,
and I told you they were appas.
So are you interested
in buying some or not?
- Huh?
Stop screwing around.
Do you want one or not?
Do you even have any money?
- Oh, no.
Like I said before,
I don't have any money on me.
I'm just browsing.
- I figured as much.
Should have known better.
Go on.
Beat it.
I run a business here.
I don't have time
for window shoppers.
Understand?
[unsettling music]
♪ ♪
- What's going on?
It was nighttime just
a few minutes ago, right?
[gasps]
The wound on my stomach is gone.
Oh, that's right!
Satella!
Damn it.
Puck asked me
to take care of her
and I totally blew it.
I have to find my way back
to that shop.
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
Huh?
- What's got you so spooked?
Why are you in such a hurry?
- If you don't wanna get hurt,
the cough up whatever
you've got.
- You guys again.
Trying to get revenge
for what happened before.
Is that it?
- Huh?
The hell are you talking about?
- I think he must have hit
his head or something.
- Nah, he'll be all right.
Just give us everything
you've got.
Understand?
Put it on the ground
and we'll let you go.
- Fine, whatever.
Everything I've got, right?
I'm in a hurry
so I don't even care.
- Now start acting like a dog.
Just get on all fours and howl,
"Help me," like a mongrel.
- [grunts]
Don't get cocky, you bastards!
- [groans]
- [shouts]
[both grunting]
- Don't ever underestimate
a truant kid
with too much free time,
'cause I usually end up
swinging around
a wooden sword all day
for no reason
which has given me
a significant bump
to my grip strength!
- [whimpers]
[groaning]
- I'm in a hurry, okay?
So don't get in my way again!
[tense music]
Easy now.
Don't freak out.
[grunting]
[whimpers]
[shuddering]
Am I stupid?
After coming this far,
I can't just leave
without answers.
♪ ♪
[knocking]
Hello, is anyone there?
Look, I know someone's in there,
all right?
Just answer the door
and show yourself!
Come on!
[grunts]
- Shut your trap!
Why don't you use a signal
or a password
instead of knocking
my damn door down?
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- Wait, you're...
[distant birds chirping]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- What are you acting
all fidgety for?
You got a wedgie,
or are your balls chafing?
- Why don't you stop worrying
about the condition
of my privates, okay?
This is no time
for potty humor!
- You're already interrupting
my evening booze.
[gulping]
Start talking about boring stuff
and I'll pass out.
- And if you drink that hard
while the sun's still up,
you'll die young.
By the way,
you think I could ask you
a dumb question?
- Huh?
- You didn't happen to--
I dunno--
die recently, did you?
- Huh?
[laughing]
Well, while I do admit
to being an old man
at death's door,
I'm still here.
Alive and kicking.
- Okay.
Then have you seen a girl here
with long silver hair?
- Silver hair?
I ain't seen nobody
that fits that description.
I'd remember.
- Was it all a dream, then?
If it was,
how much of it?
And why am I in this world
in the first place?
- So what are you doing here,
anyway?
You never made that clear.
- Oh, right.
I'm out looking
for a small insignia.
It belongs
to a silver-haired girl
who helped me out earlier.
Don't know why exactly,
but it's really important
to her.
Let's see.
I think she said it had
a jewel in the middle.
- Insignia with a jewel, huh?
- Sorry,
but I ain't got anything
that fits that description.
- Are you positive?
Think long
and hard about it.
Maybe you're just old
and senile.
- I'm at my best full of booze,
so if I don't remember it now,
I must not know anything
about it.
But I've got somebody
bringing in
a few goods later on.
I'm told it's a pretty fine
pile of loot,
and there's a good chance
that what you're looking for
is mixed in there somewhere.
- Would the one bringing it
happen to be a girl named Felt?
- Well, Mr. Know-It-All.
You even know who swiped it.
Of course, whether or not
you'll be able
to afford it
is a different matter.
Money talks
and BS walks.
- Well, you're out of luck.
There's no use playing
these mind games
and trying to size me up.
I'm about as broke
as they come, buddy.
- Then there ain't no use
talking about it.
- Just a second.
I told you I was broke,
but what about the option
of trading?
- Hmm.
Now that you mention it,
you do have a lot
of unusual stuff there.
- That I do.
For example,
this is a corn potage snack.
You've never tasted
anything like it.
- That's food?
[quirky music]
[pops]
Hmm?
♪ ♪
[chewing]
I see now.
Yeah.
What an odd flavor.
These things would go great
with booze.
- That's right.
Now you're talking.
Hey, don't just start
eating them!
- I don't know what
you plan on trading,
but you'll have to come back
after Felt gets here, okay?
Mmm, this is good stuff.
[gnawing]
[crows cawing]
[crickets chirping]
- I guess no matter
what world you're on,
there are always people
with money and people without.
I will say,
the difference here
is pretty stark.
- Hey, what are you doing there?
You're in my way, you know.
- [gasps]
Felt!
- Hang on a second.
Have we met before?
- Not formally, no,
but I've been waiting for you.
- Oh, yeah?
Why's that?
- Come on.
Try and think about this.
Do you really not remember
seeing me before?
- Huh, nothing's ringing
any bells.
Listen, I'm a busy woman, okay?
So if you don't leave
a huge impression,
there's no way
I'm gonna remember you.
- I'd say it was
a pretty huge impression,
but whatever.
Just forget about that.
I want to negotiate
for the insignia
you're bringing in there.
- Hmm.
So that's all you wanted, huh?
In that case,
I guess I'll hear you out.
[giggles]
[knocking]
- For a rat!
- Poison.
- For a whale!
- A harpoon.
- To the noble dragon lord!
- We're bags of shit.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting,
old man.
My target was more persistent
than I thought.
Took a while to shake 'em.
- Eh?
- [grunts]
- [gulping]
Hey, did you water down
this milk or what, Old Man Rom?
'Cause there's definitely
something wrong with it.
Pretty nasty stuff.
- I give you something out
of the goodness of my heart,
and you call it gross?
- You two are a whole lot closer
than I'd either hoped
or expected.
Feeling kind of left out
over here.
- Come on.
Don't start talking
like a wuss
when you've got a face
that looks almost
as scary as his.
- Telling me I look like
an old man at my age
is the most savage thing
anyone's ever said to me.
- Okay, yeah, I probably went
a little too far that time.
I'm sorry, dude.
- If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you two
were in some contest
to try to piss me off.
- All right,
well, then,
what do you say we get down
to business, huh?
How much are you willing
to pay for it?
- Wow, you don't waste
any time at all.
Before I give you an answer,
you do have the insignia, right?
- Yeah, of course I do, silly.
Satisfied?
- Hmm?
Hmm.
- This one not only
has a cool design,
it's got that jewel in it,
so I had to work pretty hard
to get a hold of it.
If you can pay enough to match
all the effort involved,
we'll both be happy.
- I don't have any money.
- [grunts]
Then it sounds like we don't
have anything more to discuss!
- Hmm, tisk, tisk.
I don't have any money,
but I have a few things
worth money.
- Huh?
- What I have in my hand here
is a magical device
that can stop time
for everyone everywhere.
It's called a cell phone!
- What's that?
- Never seen one
of those before.
- Take this.
Nine shots per second.
Continuous shot!
[clicking]
[both groaning]
- Hey, what's that
clicking sound?
And that was way too bright!
- Stop!
What are you trying to do?
Kill me?
Don't you go trying
to trick this old man
with your dodgy tricks!
- Now, hold on.
- Huh?
- [grunting]
- Wait, is that...
- Those are me and Felt's faces.
What sort of magic is that?
- It's like I was telling you.
It's a mystical item that
can freeze a moment in time.
With this unique device,
you can capture moments in time,
store them inside of it,
and look at them later.
- Oh, wow!
That's amazing!
- Never seen the like.
Is that one of the "metia"
I've been hearing about?
- What's a metia?
- It's the name for devices
that allow people
whose gates aren't open
to use magic
in the very same way
that real magic users do.
- I'm more concerned
with the price.
How much do you think
I'll be able to get out
of this thing, anyway?
- Don't ask me.
It's my first time having
to deal with one
of these metia, too,
but I feel pretty confident
that it'll fetch
way more than that insignia.
- Then that settles it!
The cell phone for the insignia.
Negotiations complete.
Thank you for your business.
Hey!
- Uh, not so fast.
- What's the problem?
- You're not the only one
I'm negotiating with
for the insignia.
- Huh?
- It's not like it
was just some random grab.
Somebody specifically asked me
to get it for them.
In exchange, that same client
said I could get 10 holy coins.
- You've already got
a deal set up for it?
I have no idea
what 10 holy coins
are worth to compare.
- Judging by what it can do,
I'd say your metia is worth
at least 20 holy coins.
Actually, I'm guessing there
are people out there.
Who'd be willing
to pay even more.
- Really?
Then that means I
can get away
with overcharging for it!
- So when and where
are you planning
on meeting this client of yours?
- Hey, no need to worry.
Negotiations will take place
right here.
If a little thing like me
dealt with them alone,
I'd be screwed if a client
decided to cheat me,
but with Old Man Rom
standing there,
that's not a concern.
[chuckles]
[knocking]
all: Hmm?
- The password?
- Oh, I didn't mention it
to them.
That's probably for me.
I'll go check.
[grunts]
[door opens]
- You're okay with letting her
use you like this?
- It ain't like we're
total strangers or anything.
I've known her
for a long time,
so I help her out
whenever I can.
- Even I have to smile a little
when I see somebody
who looks like such a barbarian
standing right here
in front of me.
- Well, look at where we are.
Everyone around here
is desperate
just to survive each day.
Normally people join forces
with others
to try and keep themselves safe
when things get rough,
but Felt ain't cut out for that.
That's why I gotta look out
for her
and keep her outta trouble.
[groans]
[door closes]
- Yep, I was right.
It was for me.
Over here.
Care to sit down?
- There seem to be several
outsiders here.
- Well, I'd be in trouble
if you gypped me.
We weaklings have our own way
of playing it smart.
- I know this older fellow,
but I'm afraid I don't recognize
the young man.
- He happens
to be your rival.
So he'll be the other person
negotiating with you today.
- [grunts]
- [gulps]
[slurps]
I see now.
Believe I understand
the situation.
- I'm pretty sure
he's only interested
in the insignia,
so that means you two
will be bidding
against each other.
I honestly don't care
who ends up with it,
so I'll sell it
to the highest bidder
and be completely satisfied
doing so.
- I think I like
that personality of yours.
Exactly how much
did this young man bid
for the item?
- I'm putting up this metia.
It's pretty rare, too.
Probably the only one
of its kind
in this entire world.
It can capture moments in time.
The big muscle man over here
tells me it's worth
no less than 20 holy coins.
- A metia.
[chuckles]
Well, luckily for me,
the client sent along
extra funds
in case anything came up.
That way I'd be prepared
to sweeten the deal.
- The client, huh?
So I suppose that means
you were asked to fetch it,
too, then,
weren't you?
- Yes, that's correct.
The client is the one
who wants to acquire it.
Would you happen to be
in the same business?
- Doubt it, unless your client
is gainfully unemployed.
- So this unemployed guy
has named a price
that puts him pretty far ahead
in the lead,
and that brings us to this.
What price is your master
putting on it?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[both gasping]
[coins clinking]
- Hmm.
20 exactly.
- These are the holy coins
my employer sent with me
to seal this deal.
So, do you think
they should be enough?
- [stammers]
- What's wrong with you?
Don't you know how to bargain?
Stop looking so pathetic.
Your metia's worth no less
than 20 holy coins, remember?
- [gasps]
- The way I see it,
victory in this deal
is definitely leaning
toward the boy.
Sorry for all the trouble
for you and your employer,
but you'd better bag up
those coins
and be on your way.
- [shuddering]
Yeah!
[stammers]
What?
What's wrong with
a little victory pose?
I'm totally psyched about this!
- So, no one said anything.
Go as crazy as you want.
I don't care as long
as I get my profit.
- Uh, sorry Miss Elsa.
You'll probably get in trouble
for this, won't you?
- These things can't be helped.
The way I see it,
this was my employer's fault
for trying to underpay.
[swallowing]
It ended in disappointment,
but at least I got
to have a drink,
so I'll be taking my leave now.
[slurps]
By the way,
what do you intend to do
with that insignia, anyway?
- Oh, I'm gonna look
for its owner
then return it to her.
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- I see.
So you're with them, then.
- [stammers]
[grunting]
What's going on here?
- Do you want to die?
- Oh, my.
- [gasps]
- It seems you've dodged
my strike.
- [gasping]
[chair clatters]
- [shouting]
[grunts]
- This is my first battle
to the death with a giant.
- Quiet, jumpy little girl.
I'll grind you up
and feed you to the rats!
[grunting]
[pounding]
- Crap.
- Don't worry.
There's no way Old Man Rom
will lose.
- Take this!
[grunting]
[slicing]
[groans]
- Old Man Rom!
- [groans]
Damn it!
[breathing heavily]
- I forgot to say--
- I'm gonna take you with me!
[stabbing]
[groans]
- Thank you for that nice glass
of milk.
- [gagging]
♪ ♪
- I suppose I should return
this now.
♪ ♪
- What have you done?
How dare you put
your filthy hands
on him, you bitch?
- Oh, my.
Seems you have more courage
than your friend,
but I would advise against doing
anything stupid
unless you want to get hurt.
- As if you didn't intend
to kill me either way.
You psychopathic monster!
- Wouldn't move around too much,
dear.
My hands might slip.
Believe it or not,
I'm not the best
at handling blades.
- I'm sorry you got caught up
in all this.
- Wait, I...
- Divine protection of wind.
- [shouts]
- How wonderful.
I can see that you're loved
dearly by this world.
I truly envy you.
- [gasps]
- The old man
and the girl have fallen,
yet you remain frozen
over there on the floor.
I take it you've given up?
- [gasping]
Damn it.
[dramatic music]
- There we go.
You finally stood up.
'Course it's less fun
since you took so long,
but still,
not bad.
♪ ♪
[stammers]
[shouting]
[grunting]
[blows landing]
- It's no use.
I see you're a novice.
You've no divine protections
or techniques.
I'd hoped to squeeze wisdom
out of you,
but you lack that, too.
- Shut up!
I do have my pride!
I can't believe you,
after you put me
through all this.
- I do acknowledge that you have
extraordinary determination.
If only you could have stood up
and done that sooner,
things might have gone
a bit differently for these two.
[slurps]
- [snarls]
[stammers]
[gasps]
- I think it's time
to end this little game.
I'll send you
to meet the angels.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[shouting]
- [exhales]
You're full of surprises.
I certainly felt that one.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Didn't feel it?
I managed to open up that belly
of yours
when we passed by one another.
The one thing I excel at
when using a blade.
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
- Just as I thought.
Your entrails have such
an interesting shape to them
and such a lovely color, too.
- It hurts.
It hurts.
- Does it hurt?
Are you suffering?
- It doesn't hurt.
- In pain?
Do you want to die?
- Die?
Am I dead?
Am I still alive?
When will I die?
When?
- Now slower and slower
and slower.
- I'm scared.
- Yes, slower and slower
and slower and slower.
- I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die!
- Yes, you're slowly losing
body heat.
- I'm gonna die!
[gasping]
- Your slowly growing cold.
- Oh.
I'm dead.
- What's the matter, boy?
You look like you've seen
a ghost.
Say something.
Are you okay?
- [sighs]
I have no idea.
- [stammers]
[dramatic music]
- [groans]
- That woke you up.
You feeling better?
Just forget about the money.
Here, I'll give you these.
Take them.
- [grunts]
- ♪ No don't give up on life
This endless dead end ♪
[MYTH&ROID's "STYLE HELIX"]
- [gasps]
Hey.
Wait up.
[grunts]
Hang on!
Please, wait for me!
Wait up!
Satella!
- [singing in Japanese]
- [gasps]
Please don't ignore me!
My disappearing and not doing
what you wait were my fault!
I was desperate!
I didn't know what else
I could do!
So I went back to the loot house
after that
but I still couldn't find you.
- [singing in Japanese]
- I'm sorry for only thinking
of myself,
but I'm glad you're all right,
Satella.
- [singing in Japanese]
- What in the world
is wrong with you?
- Huh?
- Now listen,
I don't know who
you think you are,
but don't ever call me
by the name
of the Witch of Envy.
What were you thinking?
- ♪ No don't give up
on life... ♪
- [gasps]
- ♪ This endless dead end ♪
- [gasping]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ My time is spinning around ♪
♪ Your deep black eyes ♪
♪ I forgot what time it is ♪
♪ And our memories are gone ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ I wish you were here ♪
♪ Oh never close your eyes ♪
♪ Searching for true fate ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Restart ♪
♪ So let us try again
from the very first time ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ For now see you again ♪
♪ Fading in ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Fading out ♪
♪ Fading in ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Fading out ♪
♪ I wish we were there ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ Restart ♪
♪ No don't give up on life ♪
♪ This endless dead end ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ For now I'll see you off ♪
♪ And we'll die waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
♪ And we'll start waiting
for a new day ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Oh please don't let me die ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ah, oh ♪