[ground dragon
and rigers galloping]
- Just neow getting around
to joining us, Julius?
Thanks so much for gracing us
with your presence.
- Please. You're going
to ruin my reputation.
Now listen.
You seem to be mistaken.
I am not the man called Julius.
Let me see.
Perhaps I'll go by something
like Jules instead.
Even if it is temporary,
a man who has
the status of a knight
must never lower himself to
the rank of a common mercenary.
The man you see
standing here before you
is not Julius Euclius,
the knight.
I am but a simple wanderer
by the name of Jules.
- [groans]
- A proper household's
code of chivalry can be
a real pain sometimes, huh?
- What an utter load of crap.
- It would seem you're doing
better than I expected.
Tell me, how are you feeling,
Subaru?
- [gasps]
Well, it was
just some scratches.
A little spit fixed
everything right up pretty much.
And how have things
been with you
since our
little disagreement, huh?
Busy apologizing for fighting
so seriously with an amateur?
- That's not
what I was asking about.
I was referring to the damage
to your honor
by the mabeast subjugation.
[sighs]
But I'm glad to hear your wounds
from our previous encounter
have healed.
[both laugh]
- [chanting]
- ♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Now let me open the scar ♪
♪ Tokeatta virus ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Grew up in the loneliness ♪
SUBARU: Thanks to all of you,
we succeeded in taking out
the White Whale.
However, it's not over yet.
I have a score to settle
with those weirdoes
in the Witch's Cult
who decided
to pick a fight with me.
Once that's done,
the White Whale subjugation
will be complete.
- The Witch's Cult is up next?!
- You think we can
trust the allegations
that the White Whale
and the Witch's Cult
are actually connected?
I mean, after all, we just
came here as reinforcements
- for the--
- Enough!
- Ow! What was that for?
- If you can't believe him,
ever after everything he did
to help stop the White Whale,
then you just need
to believe me.
- I'd prefer it
if you believed me
without you bashing
his head in, though.
[fists creak]
I don't like to recall it,
but I've run up against
the Witch's Cult once before.
I found out then.
- Didn't you look into
that connection before,
Old Man Wil?
- I wouldn't call my findings
definitive evidence,
but instances
of Whale appearances
and cult activities seem
to coincide in many respects.
- I'd say that makes it
doubly credible.
And on that note,
we're going to make our way
to the Mathers domain.
That cult is hiding
in the forest there.
The way to defeat them
is as simple as it gets.
We'll raid them before they
can read our movements
and crush them.
- I'm concerned.
Is there a way
to keep the villagers safe?
- Already taken care of.
I asked Miss Anastasia
and Russell
to talk to the merchants
along the highway.
Under the condition
that Margrave Mathers
buys their cargo
at the asking price,
they'll ask the merchants
to evacuate
the villagers of Arlam
as well as the residents
of Roswaal's mansion.
For those in the mansion,
a messenger
from Miss Crusch's household
will deliver them
a handwritten letter.
Nobody there
knows about the alliance.
If we don't notify them
about it,
then there's bound to be chaos.
- Sounds like we can get
the ball rolling, then.
BOTH: Yeah!
- We've quite
the upper hand here.
We've never had
such an advantage
battling the Witch's Cult.
- Yeah. And now with Julius
and his crew joining us,
there's no way
we'll be outnumbered.
Hmm?
- I'd like to offer
one correction.
Remember my name is Jules.
Just be sure
to keep that in mind.
- Back off with that!
It'll just be a hassle
in informal settings
like this one!
[sighs]
The battle with the White Whale
was a rough one.
I thought I was gonna die.
Unfortunately...
some of us did.
Some others vanished,
never to return.
Let's take them down
without another death,
not one person.
Let's win this thing
and all go back home alive!
[steeds galloping]
- I still can't believe
- that you actually defeated it.
- Huh?
- The subjugation
of the White Whale
has been a wish
the Imperial Knights
have held for as long
as anyone can remember,
but were never able to fulfill.
- [gasps]
- It would seem
I owe you my thanks.
- Look, you don't
have to force it, okay?
- For putting an end
to what seemed
like an unstoppable calamity
that all nations ignored
for far too long,
I sincerely thank you.
- [gasps]
[grumbles]
I'm grateful to you,
too, I guess,
for coming to back us up,
even after what happened.
About that, I was--
Aw, damn it all! Crap!
Listen, I know! I know, okay?!
I know it now, all right?!
[groans]
It was all my fault.
Sorry. I--
I apologize.
- As do I, genuinely.
I can't take back
my words and actions.
But I want to make amends
from the bottom of my heart
for belittling you
the way I did.
- Look, I'm sorry, but...
- Hmm?
- I still hate
your freakin' guts.
I feel bad for what happened,
and I'm really grateful
you're here to help us out.
That said,
I honestly can't stand you.
I seriously hate you
from the bottom of my heart!
So there! [grumbles]
- [chuckles]
Understandable.
I'm quite certain I could
never befriend you, either.
Some things aren't meant to be.
- [chuckles]
- [snaps reins]
[Patrasche grunts]
- All right.
As I say every time,
let's get this fight started.
Bring it on, fate.
[birds chirping]
[doors open]
[doors close]
- [energy warbles]
- [gasps]
You must be exhausted, Lia.
You should lie down
and rest for a bit.
- Mm-mmm.
I don't think that I'll
be able to fall asleep.
Aren't you
getting tired, though?
- No way. I'm fine.
The forest barrier
is all fixed up, too.
You don't have
to worry about anything.
- [sighs]
Even so...
[brush rustling]
- This feels a little bit
like the time
I found a big, ugly insect
in the corner of a quiet room.
So you guys are drawn
to the smell, huh?
Looks like I'm
perfect cockroach bait.
Man, I must reek.
Thank you for meeting me.
I know you
just got here and all,
but the business
that I need to discuss,
it's really more a matter for
me
and your boss, not you guys,
so don't get in my way.
[sighs]
If they'd hung around and
waited
for just a little bit longer,
I could have told them
to pack up and go home.
Guess we'll do it
the hard way.
[panting]
[men's chorus chanting]
- I've been waiting
ever so patiently for you,
believer in love.
I am a Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's cult
representing Sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti.
[babbles]
I welcome you,
beloved child blessed with love.
[laughs]
Wonderful! [laughs]
Wonderful!
[chorus vocalizing]
- Hey.
I really appreciate
the unexpected welcome,
but I gotta admit
I'm not sure I really feel
all of this love
you keep bringing up.
- It always begins
suddenly out of the blue.
Everyone on a certain day
comes to the realization
that they're indeed loved.
They feel it...
the love, the love, the love,
the love, the love,
the love, the love, the love...
- So what exactly
am I supposed to do now?
- Ah...
the most generous
love of the Witch.
Now tell me something, boy,
you wouldn't happen
to be Pride, would you?
Out of the six Sin Archbishops
in total,
only the seat of Pride
remains unclaimed and vacant.
A query for you.
You have received the Gospel,
have you not?
- The Gospel?
[chorus continues]
- My brain... [sputters]
trembles! [groans]
- Eh?
- Presentation of the Gospel.
- [flipping pages]
Where is the proof of love?
[cackles] The proof!
The proof! The proof! The proof!
The proof! The proof!
The--[babbles]
Huh?
There doesn't seem to be
an account of you
anywhere in my Gospel.
- That book is the Gospel?
- [wails] Explain yourself.
Why appear here before me?
Why visit
this place in particular?!
What fortune are you here
to bestow upon me, boy?!
Huh?!
- Oh, wow.
So that's the Gospel.
Yeah, I see. I see.
Of course.
I understand completely.
You should have just said so
in the first place.
[patting]
Ah, darn it!
My bad. I'm sorry.
- About what?
- My Gospel is, well...
you see...
I used it as a coaster,
and it got messy...
so I threw it in the trash.
[music playing]
- Proof of love, nay!
Authority of Sloth!
Behold the Unseen Hand!
- [grunts]
- How did you...
- Oh, wow. Crappy trick.
An Unseen Hand
isn't all that great
if I can see it and evade it.
- What did you say?!
You can see my Unseen Hand?!
- Okay, I'd say I'm
just about done buying time.
- [gasps]
- [Mimi and Tivey yell]
[rumbling]
- [gasping]
[both yell]
[chorus vocalizing]
- Prepare to be buried alive!
Suffer in darkness
for all the terrible things
you've done!
- How? How can this be?
My fingers so cruelly,
so mercilessly,
so chaotically,
so arbitrarily,
so artlessly,
so very meaninglessly...
[wailing]
My brain.
My brain trembles!
- Scary.
That guy's
completely out of his mind.
- Pretty sure all the Witch's
Cultists are like that,
scary and crazy.
- Yes, of course.
It all makes sense.
Yes, of course.
It all makes sense. [gasps]
Yes. Fine!
Yes. Fine! I understand.
Let's do this!
I'm ready to do this!
I'm not afraid.
The time has come
to find out which one of us
is worthy of her love!
Worthy of her love, yes!
Her love!
- Sorry to interrupt
your screamy fun, but...
- Eh?
- I've got someone else
lined up to take you on.
- Hyah!
[thump]
SUBARU: I-It's over, right?
He's dead?
- Oh, yes, he's very much dead.
The most powerful healer
in the capital
personally guarantees it.
- Right. Good.
Thanks for that, Wilhelm.
I hope it wasn't
asking too much.
- Really? What do you mean?
- Isn't cutting someone down
from behind without warning
like the worst thing
a knight can do?
- Chivalry is a code of conduct
that's long dead.
You need not concern yourself
with that.
- Hmm.
It doesn't look like this weirdo
was carrying
anything useful on him.
- Wow, you two little guys
are ransacking his corpse
like it's not a big deal.
Kinda creepy.
- Look, I'm not little,
and the name's Tivey.
I believe
it's our right as victors
to search out
the spoils of battle.
Hmm?
What is this?
Some kind of book?
SUBARU: Well, I think
that particular book
is the one Betelgeuse
called the Gospel.
- [both gasp]
- You mean this is the Gospel?!
Oh, no! I-I touched it!
- I can't read it.
Do you know
what this says, Felix?
- [both gasp]
- No, wait!
Don't you point
that thing at me!
Why in the world
would you do something
as stupid as trying to read
the Gospel, huh?
- Is it really that dangerous?
Huh?
WILHELM:
The Gospel is the proof
that one belongs
to the Witch's Cult.
It's basically what you'd call
their sacred text.
SUBARU: Their what?
FELIX: From what
the rumors say,
one of these is delivered
to anybody with the potential
to join the cult,
and once a person gets it,
guess what.
They're neow a devout member
of the Witch's Cult,
just like that!
SUBARU: Man,
how shady can you get?
Well, I guess
I'll take this with me.
If I can decipher it,
maybe I can figure out what
the Witch's Cult really is.
- [gasps] Hey, hey!
Oh, listen, I know we've
killed the enemy here,
but shouldn't we
take a look around and make sure
there aren't any other ones
to make dead, too?
- Yeah. You know,
as adorable as you might look,
you sure say some pretty weird
and disturbing things.
- [laughs] I'm adorable?
You're making me blush.
- So the subordinates
that Betelgeuse called fingers
number ten in total, correct?
That makes things easier.
- I think one of those creeps is
pinned under this pile of rocks.
- Ten creeps minus one is nine!
That means nine creeps are left!
- Well, then,
shall we find the others?
- [grunts]
Now, this freak of nature
is actually dead, right?
He's not gonna come back
the second we look away,
is he? [groans]
- Fine! If you're
that worried about it,
we'll make extra sure!
- [gasps]
[overlapping chatter]
JULIUS: We crushed two
of the ones called fingers here.
A few of the cultists
were skilled,
but in the end,
they weren't a threat.
It would seem we made no errors
in driving them off.
- I'm glad it went well
for you guys, too.
JULIUS: Given your demeanor,
I can only assume
that your news is good as well.
- Yep. Our group
took out Betelgeuse.
- That Subaru, he's a worrywart.
so that's why
we blew him to bits,
blasting that creep kaboom-style
after we killed him!
- Whoa!
- Nice work.
So that just leaves
the simple task
of mopping up
the remnants then, huh?
- We'd better hurry
and take care of 'em
before my beautiful lady
turns into an old granny.
Hey, what's going on?
That was my best joke.
[Mimi laughs]
JULIUS: We rendezvous soon
with the dragon-drawn carriages
you arranged.
Let's eliminate
the remaining fingers
and greet our victory
over this cult together.
- 'Kay, Subaru,
time for the bait.
Put out that smell.
Neow breathe in.
- [inhales]
- And out.
- [exhales]
- And out!
- And out! And out!
- [gasping]
Stop that!
I gotta breathe in, too!
- [laughter]
- So I guess...
- once this is all done,
we'll just go back to being
friend and foe, won't we?
- How confident of you to worry
about what's yet to come.
- Hey, give me a break.
It's going almost too well,
so maybe I let
my guard down a little.
[gasps]
Get down now, all of you!
[Authority warbles]
- What the hell?
What's going on here?
- The Unseen Hand.
Betelgeuse should be dead.
So who's using--
[warbles]
- [yelps]
- [all gasp]
- WILHELM: Subaru!
- Damn it! Agh!
[gasping]
WOMAN: Agh!
My brain, it trembles.
- [gasps]
Who are you? Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Wait a second.
Are you Betelgeuse's...
- His finger?
Yes!
- [warbles]
- [Subaru groans]
[straining] Let me... go.
- I am a finger that carries out
whatever needs to be done,
one who reciprocates love.
I am a disciple, a faithful
and diligent one, to be sure,
and I will carry out the Ordeal
following love's guidance!
- [creaking]
- [groaning]
A copy.
A replica
of the original Betelgeuse.
If that's true,
this couldn't possibly
get any worse for us.
- [gagging]
- Sniff, sniff.
The love I smell
that wraps itself around you
does not compare to that
of a mere lowly follower.
It is equal to that
of a Sin Archbishop.
It is exceedingly displeasing,
dissatisfying, disturbing,
disagreeable, discomforting,
disproportionate, discordant!
But that is the proof
which tells me you are Pride!
- [gasps] Don't make me
keep saying it.
I'm not even close
to being Pride!
I've never even gotten a free
book as a membership perk!
- Ah! My, aren't you
a stubborn one?
Even so, soon enough,
you will quite readily receive--
Eh? The Gospel.
[gasps] My love's guidance.
The Gospel that allows me,
inexperienced though I may be,
to reciprocate love!
What happened?!
Why is not with me?! No!
Wait a moment.
Was it you?
Was it you? Was it you?
Was it you, you, you,
you, you, you, you?!
Did you steal
my copy of the Gospel?!
- Eh?
- What is--
- A spirit!
[Subaru winces]
- [gasping] A spirit.
Begone. Begone!
Begone! Begone!
[wailing]
- [Authority warbles]
- Damn it.
[both yell]
- Ohh. Is that
the best you can do?
If that's the case,
be dismayed,
disappointed, dejected!
Tell me, children!
Are you two slothful?!
- [grunts]
- [yelps]
My life is spilling out.
My blood is running dry.
[gasps] My diligent
and constant pulse,
my precious life support,
it's stopping, disappearing.
[gasps] Oh, my brain...
trembles!
[wind blowing]
- From what I can gather,
the first Sloth we defeated
was a double,
and the one dead on the ground
is the real one?
JULIUS: No.
I believe this may not
even be a matter
of knowing which of them
is the real one.
- You don't mean
the Sin Archbishop of Sloth
might actually
be more than one person?
- Possibly,
or all hundred followers,
including the fingers,
are the Sin Archbishop of Sloth.
- I dragged you into this.
It's all my fault.
- [steeds growling]
- [carriage jostling]
[wind blowing]
- [gasps]
If I'd realized it sooner,
I could have avoided this.
Damn it.
[sighs] I knew
what kind of power it was,
so I-I just...
- Subaru, sir.
- [gasps]
- I'm sure many thoughts
are going through
your mind right now,
and I am certain
none of them are superficial,
but while it may be
somewhat
inelegant of me to say so,
I feel rather compelled
to speak from my heart
and my mind on this.
- [gasps]
- Keep fighting!
- Even if you have regrets,
even if you're
completely remorseful,
you must fight on.
If you've committed,
if you've made the decision
to stand against them,
struggle and fight
with all you have.
- [gasps]
- Don't give up for one second,
one moment, or one instant.
Cling greedily to the victory
you have within your sight.
If you can still stand,
if your fingers can still move,
if all your teeth
haven't yet broken...
then stand tall
to the bitter end.
You mustn't ever stop.
- Are you telling me
to get stronger?
- Hardly.
I'm telling you to be strong.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Lend me your wisdom
and your strength!
We're gonna start
evacuating
the mansion and village.
Don't waste a single second!
As of right now,
the Witch's Cult
hasn't had enough time
to notice
that we've gotten away,
which means we can get Emilia
and the rest in carriages
and get them to safety
in plain sight.
- With Miss Emilia and
the others out of harm's way,
we won't have to worry
about them anymore,
so we can focus
on conquering the Witch's Cult.
Going into battle isn't easy
when you know
you have a weak point.
- You're making my ears hurt,
but, yeah, that's exactly right.
- And while I'm at it,
there's one more thing
I want to say to you.
Subaru, you should
really settle things
and make up with Julius soon.
Understand?
- Soon?
What are you talking about?
We already reconciled
after our fight. Didn't you see?
- But that was
just the first step.
Subconsciously
you're still harboring
- some resentment towards him.
- [grumbles]
- You should kneow
you can rely on Julius.
Though I admit
he's a bit unapproachable
and incomprehensible.
Go on. Hurry up.
- Uh...
[groans]
Okay, fine!
So, uh...
hey, listen.
There's something that--
something that I wanted
to say to you,
but it's hard for...
[gasps]
Huh?
[music playing]
- [shudders]
What in the hell's
going on here?
Did the Witch's Cult do this?
Hey, anyone!
Is anyone there?!
Hey, answer me!
[soft buzzing]
[winces]
Wh-What is that intense smell?
[buzzing continues]
[gasps]
[gagging]
Patrasche.
Hang on a second.
A flower like this
couldn't actually exist.
And Patrasche
wouldn't just let me die.
Which means that this
is just an illusion.
It's all just make-believe!
[spirit warbles]
- [yelps]
- A lesser spirit?
Did you come here
just to help me out or...
- Subaru.
- [gasps]
So you saved me?
- I can tell
from that spiteful tone
it's definitely you.
I may have a vivid subconscious,
but it could never make such
a realistic imitation of you.
It's a bewitching spell.
We seem to be the only ones
who have returned to normal.
How did you make it back?
- In my illusion,
I fought and burned a flower.
- Is that so?
Someone put a suggestion spell
on the flower's scent.
- Hold on a sec.
What's that glow?
It's the light
of my little buds.
I will now teach everyone
how to break out of the spell.
In. Nes.
[energy pulses]
- [overlapping yelling]
- [groaning]
- There's nobody here!
- Where am I?!
[chatter continues]
JULIUS: Is his affinity
really this strong?
My apologies, but I'm
afraid
you'll need to endure it.
I can't spare the energy
needed
to fine-tune it just for you.
Bringing them all back
is our priority.
[Subaru groans]
- [whoosh]
- [gasps]
[yells]
[gasps]
- [gasps]
- Afraid that'll be
quite enough out of you.
- [yelps]
- You need to kill me.
I won't accept this disgrace.
Well, what is the meaning
of all of this?
You'll explain it to me,
right, Barusu?
- I'd like to ask you
the same thing.
We were just riding up,
and you attacked us
out of nowhere.
What were you thinking?
- You shouldn't have to ask
what I was thinking.
That's rich,
coming from an ingrate like you.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Don't you try to deny it.
And after everything
that Lord Roswaal did for you,
it's simply disgraceful.
Once you're done with him,
you rush to wag your tail
for another master.
- Hang on. I think you've got
your stories all mixed up
here.
- You dare to bite
the hand that feeds you.
Mangy mutt.
- Listen to me.
I wrote a letter,
a handwritten letter
explaining all this.
Wasn't it
delivered to the mansion?
- Yes. I did receive one
from the capital.
But I found it laughable
and despicable
that you would have the
gall
to send me a blank
letter.
- Wait. It was blank?
- The act of sending
a blank letter is a metaphor.
It means that you
have nothing to discuss
and have no intention
of speaking to the recipient.
It could easily be interpreted
as a declaration of war.
- Uh, look,
that was an accident.
You think I'm even
remotely clever enough
to do something like that?
- You dare to bite
the hand that feeds you.
Reprehensible.
- Stop saying that!
- I can't say it enough.
But now I get the idea.
The blank letter
was some kind of mistake,
and you're still
Miss Emilia's dog.
Is that correct?
- Not exactly, but okay, fine.
I mean, after all,
they're like family anyway.
I'm cool with being a dog
if I'm Emilia's.
- Wouldn't you say
that such a low standard
is a bit demeaning
and degrading?
- In any case,
these guys are reinforcements.
They're friends of ours.
I pulled them together
as a special team
designed to wipe out
the Witch's Cult.
There's not much time now.
We need to start evacuating
the villagers.
[villagers murmuring]
- Subaru, they seem
rather uneasy and skeptical.
Remember to be considerate.
- [grunts]
Hey, everybody!
How's it going?
I haven't seen you guys
in quite a while,
so thanks for showing up!
Sorry to get
right to the point,
but now that I
have your attention,
I have a favor to ask.
It seems that mabeasts
are up to no good
out in the forest
near here once again.
So I've brought in
a few specialists
from outside the village
to help exterminate them.
But while they're here working,
I'd like for all of you
to leave for the time being.
- Don't try to fool us.
- [gasps]
- I know you're trying to
sound
calm and cheerful about this,
but everyone
in the village is frightened.
We feared all along
that the Witch's Cult
would try something.
- Wait. The Witch's Cult?
What are you talking about?
- Hang on a second.
- Why lie about this?
- Maybe he's trying
to hide something.
- [murmuring continues]
- [sighs]
- So you don't deny it, then?
- Then that means
that it's all true, isn't it?
- Why would they bother
a place like this?
- Come on.
The reason is obvious.
It's 'cause of that half-elf.
MAN: That's right.
The lord of the domain
endorses a half-elf
for our ruler.
- Why do you
have to make it about that,
the half-elf thing?
Look, Emilia has
nothing to do with it!
- She has everything
to do with it.
If you keep company
with a half-elf,
then the Witch's Cult shows up.
Even the children
of this village know that.
- You're kidding me.
You guys seriously believe that?
All of this is the fault
of the half-elf in the mansion?
[gasps]
- To the village?
It does sound nice,
but it might cause
trouble for you
if we went there together.
- [gasps]
So does that mean
I'm just being selfish again?
Serving my own personal needs?
Agh!
[gasps]
- Lift up your head,
and don't look down.
That's exactly what Miss
Crusch
would say to you right neow.
- What do you mean?
- Do you believe anything
you were trying
to get them to do was wrong?
If your answer is neo,
there isn't any reason
to look down.
Or is it somehow harder
to lift your head up here
than it was to throw a tantrum
in front of everybody
back at the castle?
- Come on. That's--
Wait. You're right.
Compared to what I did
that day, this is nothing.
I understand your feelings
and concerns very well!
I'm not gonna try to convince
you to change your minds now.
Obviously you'll have
your own beliefs about things.
It hurts, but I understand.
- [grunts]
- But whatever you believe,
please accept my request.
I need you all
to clear out of here!
It's dangerous
to stay in the village,
and that's the truth.
[villager murmuring]
- The words
of my household's employee
are those of our master,
Lord Roswaal himself.
- What are you...
- So follow his instructions
immediately.
- [overlapping chatter]
- Hey, come on. Let's Move.
- Tell him we're here.
SUBARU: You saved me back there.
Thanks a lot.
- Even so--
- What is it?
- I've gotta admit having you
take my side so easily
is something
that's never happened before.
So does that mean
you've acknowledged me?
- [scoffs]
PETRA: Subaru!
- Oh, hey, Petra.
What's going on?
Do you need something?!
- Well, i-is--
is the lady from the mansion
gonna run away with us, too?
- Wha?
- She was here.
She came to the village
yesterday.
She told us we should all
come to the mansion
and stay with her because it's
dangerous here right now,
just like you said.
She warned us,
but no one in the village
would even listen to her.
- [gasps]
- It's all right.
She'll be fine.
Don't worry about a thing.
So go on and get moving now.
- Okay.
- What happened
to Emilia after that?
RAM: You should know her
well enough to realize
she's not so perceptive
as to back down
the moment someone denies her.
- That's true, but I also know
she isn't the kind of girl
who wouldn't be hurt
by mean words hurled at her.
- She came down and tried
to convince the villagers
to leave or join her
in the mansion,
but they all refused.
She couldn't do nothing,
so she repaired
the forest barrier,
because she feared there
might be another mabeast attack.
Well, doing all that
wasn't a bad decision
in and of itself, but still...
[footsteps crunching]
- Hey, Julius.
- [gasps]
- I was hoping you'd join me.
I'm gonna go and explain
things to Emilia
and the little girl
in the mansion.
Think it would be
a lot more convincing
if you were
to come along with me.
I mean, after all,
you are a knight.
Just take it as my way
of trying to make up
for going nuts in the castle.
- I see.
If that will help the discussion
to go more smoothly,
then don't hesitate to use me.
- And another thing.
That little spirit I had on me,
you were the one
who put it there, weren't you?
So how are you able to do that?
I get that you're
a spirit arts user,
but I don't get
how it all works.
- To be more precise
about it,
I prefer to be called
a Spirit Knight.
I do use the spirit arts,
of course,
but that hasn't prevented me
from also training with a
sword.
- Then you're the one
who set that helpful
little red thing on me?
- "Set it on you"
is a harsh way to put it.
That was Ia.
I was only having her
secretly guard you
and keep you safe.
- Oh, by the way, what was
that other thing you did
when you broke
the illusion earlier?
- It's a high class of magic
known as Nect.
It connects the gates
of everyone who is in range
so they can easily
communicate with each other.
It appeared to work
a bit too well on you, though.
- Yeah, no kidding.
I thought my head
was gonna split open.
- It's unusual for the spirits
to mistake the tuning.
It could be something else.
Perhaps you have
a strong affinity
towards the spirit world.
- [scoffs]
Sadly, the only spirit
I ever made friends with
was a little gray cat
with a lot of attitude.
- Well, did you patch
things up with Julius?
Fill me in.
- Uh, I'm gonna take
that matter back with me
and mull it over carefully
before making
an optimistic decision.
I think you should come
down to the mansion with me.
I'm gonna need
at least one person there
from the Crusch camp.
I've gotta smooth over
the misunderstanding
with the letter.
- [sighs] Fine.
I'll do that
after I finish up my work,
Come to think of it,
I could use your help here.
It involves the Witch's Cult,
so it's kinda dangerous.
The contract said he'd buy
their cargo at the asking price,
so we need to inspect
the goods thoroughly.
- Wait. Really? A task like that
shouldn't be our job, should it?
Don't we have more impor--
- Oh, come on. It'll be fun.
- Hey, hey.
Now take it easy, you two.
No lovers' quarrels
in my carriage.
- [giggles]
Looks like you're
in trouble neow, Subaru.
Goodness.
I can't take him anywhere.
You let your guard down.
- Eh?
[groans]
- This guy is one
of the Witch's Cult.
I touched him earlier
to confirm it.
There's some weird spell
implanted in him
just like the fingers
of the Sin Archbishop's.
- There was one
among the merchants?
- That's the reason
I snuck into his carriage,
so I could get under his guard.
- Neow, then, I want you
to tell us the details
of what your little cult's
been plotting.
My hands happen to be some of
the gentlest ones in the world,
but they can do
some nasty things, too.
- It's...
- It's what?
- over.
- [gasps] Ia, quick!
- That's right.
- Protect him!
- It's the beginning of the end.
[all screaming]
[Subaru groans]
[gasps]
- Oh, thank goodness.
I was wondering
when you'd wake up.
- Why are you dressed like that?
- I had neo choice.
It isn't as if I can reproduce
clothes with healing magic.
- Regardless, given our
horrific circumstances,
I'm glad the two of you
are all right.
- [gasps]
[scattered yells and wailing]
[swords clashing]
- Bastards. How'd they
get into the village?
- By stowing away
in the carriages.
There was a finger
hiding among the merchants,
and we didn't know
'til it was too late.
I failed in my mission.
- Now is not the time
to dwell on regrets.
Tivey and Madame Ram
are in the mansion.
They evacuated with the injured.
Felix, join them,
and heal those you can.
- Understood.
- Right.
Now let's get out there
and crush all the fingers
that are left.
[rumbling]
- To think, to think, to think,
to think, to think, to think,
to think that you
would resist us this much.
- [yells]
[Authority warbles]
- Such tenacity!
Such driven persistence!
Clinging so
to this ever-increasing love!
As a diligent disciple,
I cannot begin to express
my respect for your dedication.
Agh! My brain trembles!
- You're mine.
- [screams]
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
If one only focuses
on what the unseen arm
does in battle,
one will fail to see
the visible possibilities.
That is sloth, yes?
- [gasps]
- Yes.
[rumbling]
- The finger self-destructed.
- Wilhelm!
- [gasping]
- We can't leave you like this.
Gotta get to Felix
before it's too late.
- FINGER: But why?
- [both gasp]
- But why? But why? But why?
But why? But why?
I don't understand.
Why are you still
alive and kicking?
After the attack
that you just endured?
Tell me. Tell me why.
Why do you not simply bend
to my diligence?
- A time like this, and these
nut-jobs just keep coming.
- Hey, look here!
It's a special gift
from your precious Witch!
This is what you're
looking for, right?
- Eh? [gasps]
No-good thief. How could you?!
Those words were not meant
for your unworthy eyes!
- Enough with the shouting.
'Cause if you keep on
yelling at me like that,
it's gonna make
my brain tremble.
- You must die!
- [warbling]
- Get moving, Julius.
We can handle things here.
You just keep up
with your end of the plan,
and be sure
to take care of Wilhelm.
- Not too specific
with your orders, are you?
- But very well.
- [sighs]
- Hey, listen.
- Huh?
- Never mind. It can wait.
[grunts]
[warbling]
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait right there!
- [panting]
- You cowardly, foolish,
insolent little man!
No matter where you try
to run, it's futile.
- [gasps]
- What do you expect to find
wherever it is
you're running to?
- [stone clinks]
- [warbling]
- [gasps]
[groans]
- Now, at long last,
it seems the ending's
finally arrived.
- Question.
Do you know what this is?
- Huh?
- It's a magic stone
used for creating barriers.
See, they were all stashed away
in trees throughout the forest.
What, you didn't
even notice them?
- Magic stones?
What are you
blathering on about?
[brush rustling]
Huh?
- [growling]
- [gasps]
- This entire area
is a mabeast breeding ground.
People like you and me
are a prime feast for them.
Unless you happen to be holding
one of Emilia's barrier stones.
- [snarls]
- [screaming]
- [snarling]
- Only one finger left
among them now.
Once that one's gone,
it's all over.
[villagers screaming]
[Subaru panting]
Damn it.
We need to hurry this up.
- [laughs]
- [wails]
- Yes!
[laughs] Yes!
My brain trembles!
[laughing]
- [growls]
- Sloth!
- [laughing]
WOMAN: That's quite enough
out of you.
- [gasps]
- Eh?
[music playing]
- It's Emilia.
- Now stand down this instant.
I won't allow this wickedness
to continue anymore!
- [sobs]
[wails] How grand!
Oh, what a grand day!
What a lucky day indeed!
What a grand destiny!
- Emilia!
- Wait!
- Let go of me.
I can't wait around right now.
Do you want to make Emilia
fight him herself?
- Try to calm down, and have
a little faith in her, okay?
- [sputters]
- The people you want to protect
aren't just
the ones behind you,
and I believe Miss Emilia's
a lot more capable
than you think.
- [ice shatters]
- [gasps]
- [warbling]
- Oh, my glorious Witch!
My Witch, my love's guide!
Show me more
of your incredible abilities!
- Now, I don't
blame you at all
for being charmed
by my beloved daughter,
but I won't let
unwanted freaks near her!
- [gasps]
Naive!
Naive! Naive! Naive!
Naive! Naive!
[chorus vocalizing]
Behold, this is
love's true ending.
The ripened fruit of my love,
proof that the Witch
has accepted my love
and returned it in kind!
- Sorry to be
the one to tell you,
but that proof doesn't exist.
Your crush is purely one-sided.
- [yelling]
[ice crackling]
Ah, this is true diligence,
the true diligence
I know and love.
[laughs]
- Thank you.
Now accept defeat.
- [laughing]
[laughter stops]
- [sighs]
- [grunts]
[villagers murmuring]
- [gasping]
- It's her.
FELIX: See?
What did I tell you?
- We've eliminated
all the fingers.
Victory is ours now.
- [sighs]
It's finally over.
[yelps]
- Go see her, already.
- Oh, yeah. Right.
[grunts]
- [Julius gasps]
- [gasping]
- What's wrong, Subaru?
- Huh?
[Subaru panting]
I have to get away
from Emilia.
From everyone.
[yelps]
- Subaru, wait!
Where are you going?
- Stay away! I'm...
- What's going on?
- Julius, stay away from...
You're too late.
- Huh?
- The moment
Ia was flung from his body,
I had a bad feeling about
what might have been the cause.
- What are you talking about?
- That is not Subaru.
- That's right.
I'm a Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult,
representing Sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti.
Yes!
- [chorus vocalizing]
- [gasps]
- [laughing]
What a fantastic body this is!
It's been decades since
I
had one that fit me so
well.
- You madman.
Get out of that body right now!
- Madman?
Yes, what an apt way to put it.
I've been driven mad
with love. [chuckles]
Generous love!
Respectful love!
Pure love! Tender love!
Erotic love! Friendly love!
Love, love, love, love,
love, love, love, love,
love, love, love, love, love,
love, love, love, love!
[inhales]
Love!
[panting]
JULIUS:
Subaru, come on. Wake up!
- It's no use.
I already have this body
and its will firmly
under my subconscious control.
- I know you're still
in there, Subaru.
You have to find a way
to fight this.
Remember what you
were so determined
to come back here and do!
- What's that?
I told you.
It's too late, you fool!
SUBARU: [gasps] Let me go!
BETELGEUSE: No.
I am Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti!
This body has already
become my finger! [gags]
SUBARU: Shut up!
I'm Subaru Natsuki!
Kill me, Julius.
Use your sword, and kill me.
- No, don't ask me
to do such a thing.
- If you don't stop me now
while I'm in control,
we can't win.
You have to hurry.
- No, Subaru.
I will not do that.
You told me it could wait
earlier, remember?
Wasn't there something
important
that you wanted to say to me?
- I'm sorry, but it
looks
like I won't get the
chance.
Felix, please.
- [gasps]
- [singing in Japanese]
- Kill me.
- I'm sure you'll resent me
for doing this.
I know I will.
[Subaru screaming]
- ♪ Stay alive... ♪
- Stop this!
- No one else can do it,
can they?
This is what Subaru wants.
He begged for it.
- But we can't just--
- You think this is
what I want to do?!
To use the power
meant for Miss Crusch,
the power I swore
to our leader for this?!
BETELGEUSE: Ah, it can't be.
It can't be!
Just when I found such
a perfect vessel to inhabit.
SUBARU: Sorry!
- With the completion
of the Ordeal at hand,
I've been given
one final task to carry out.
I'll be punished
for it someday.
[Betelgeuse gagging]
Do as you will,
for I will never die!
- [gasps]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪ Oh, stay alive ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Stay alive ♪
- ♪ Stay alive ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I stay alive ♪
♪ Stay alive ♪
- ♪ Stay alive ♪