[MARTINET]
Looking for something, Madam?
Too bad for you.
[RITA] Don't worry about me.
I was just about to leave.
[MARTINET] Ha. As if I'd
let you leave here alive.
[RITA] You don't have to
worry about that, either.
I mean, since I am a zombie.
[MARTINET] Oh really? So the
nosy girl already died?
Well then.
Perhaps I'll slice her up
and add her to my collection.
[MARTINET grunts]
[MARTINET cackles]
[AMIRA giggles]
He said she'll
recognize me if we hug!
What?
He said she'll know
that I'm her daughter.
because it's a special power
all mothers have! Right, Fava?
Yeah. That's what Fava told you.
I'm so excited to see her!
I hope we find her soon!
Never fear, my lady.
I'm on the job. And trust me,
ahe's very close and we'll
get there before you know it,
and when we do...
Then we can change our fate!
Favaro.
You're the one who opened
our eyes to this path.
You opened our eyes, yeah!
Right.
It's more like I
opened my big mouth.
[FOREST DRAGON] If you truly
want to stop Bahamut,
and the world's destruction.
You must kill the girl.
[FAVARO] Can't someone
give me a break, for once?
Why's it gotta be me?
[CITIZENS shouting]
[CITIZEN 10B]
This has to be a mistake!
[CHARIOCE]
People of Anatae!
This woman bound before
you is not a saint!
She is an agent of
darkness and evil.
bent on destroying this kingdom!
She is a serpent
in human guise!
She has infiltrated
the capital...
It's hard to tell if the
man's a heretic or a fool.
[CHARIOCE] We must act!
As king of this land,
I hereby sentence
Joan D'Arc the witch
to be burned at the
stake for her sins!
[CITIZEN 10C]
Stop! Jeanne isn't a witch!
[CITIZEN 10D] She's our
savior! The Holy Knight!
In these purifying flames
may your sins be atoned.
In the name of the Holy Spirit,
may your soul be cleansed.
[CITIZENS scream]
[CITIZENS shouting]
They defy their holy king?
Any person who sides with that
witch is a coconspirator!
Kill them! Crush the rebellion!
What is the king doing?
[JEANNE]
Gods in heaven, stop this!
All these innocent lives.
How can you let this happen?
Why aren't you protecting
the people you claim to love?
[JEANNE]
Why, Gods?
[GABRIEL] A Holy Knight
is an offering to the gods,
nothing more.
[URIEL] We only wanted you as
a vessel to bring back Zeus,
then we would throw you away.
[RAPHAEL] Humans are only pawns
to be used for our purposes,
your little lives
mean nothing to us.
No! But we worship you!
[MICHAEL]
Don't delude yourself, Jeanne.
The gods have no love
for humans whatsoever.
[JEANNE screams]
It's time you accept the
world as it actually is.
If you want salvation
for your fellow humans,
you'll have to take it by force.
[CITIZENS gasp]
[CHARIOCE]
Finally, I'm rid of that pest!
[CHARIOCE laughs]
Uh?
Stop her! Somebody
slay that monster!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[roars]
[yelps]
[CHARIOCE, MINISTER 8A whimper]
Look at that.
The saint went and
turned into a demon.
[RITA] So, any chance
you're marginally sober?
[BACCHUS]
It's you again.
Yeah, me. And I've got
another favor to ask you.
[FAVARO]
That'll do. I hope.
Considering the barb's power,
that should make quite a weapon.
Heh... This place feels dead.
You sure we're
goin' the right way?
[KAISAR] Of course I'm sure.
I'm following this compass.
Lady Amira's mother
should be very close.
--[rumbling]
--[yelps]
[FAVARO yelps]
Fava!
Just hang on!
[FAVARO yelps]
What's your little
compass say about this?
[KAISAR] Everything's changed!
What is this place?
[FAVARO]
That fog!
It must've been just like
that stuff in Nebelville!
[MARTINET]
Can you hear it?
That beautiful moaning
in the wind?
It's the voice of the
Demon Key crying out
to fulfill its purpose
and become one with you now.
Amira.
[BACCHUS] Hm. A spell that
turns humans into demons?
[RITA] That's what happened
to Jeanne D'Arc at the stake,
you saw it for yourself.
I've seen humans make pacts with
demons to get magic powers.
But this...
You've been around
a long time, you ever
heard of a human, who was turned
into a full-fledged demon?
Now that you mention it,
there are rumors.
Some claim there's
a guy with a bounty
who mastered a spell
that can do that.
[RITA]
A bounty?
Yeah. No one knows if
he's a human or a demon.
But the rumors all agree:
he's obsessed with death.
He can change his
appearance at will,
and he's an expert
at manipulating others.
He's left a mountain
of corpses in his wake.
But his most fearsome
power of all...
...is a spell that
turns men into demons?
[BACCHUS] Yeah, but like
I said, they're rumors.
As the story goes, no one's
ever met him and survived
which makes it hard to verify.
So, does this
ghost-story-bounty man
have a name?
Yeah. Word is he calls himself--
[HAMSA, BACCHUS yelp]
Did we just hit something?
[BACCHUS] Watch where
you're goin', dumbass!
[gasps] Um. Oops?
Martinet. My teacher.
What is he doing here?
Teacher?
My teacher told me
I'd be with her again one day,
as long as I held onto this.
[FAVARO]
That's the guy?
[MARTINET] I've been
waiting for you, Amira.
Somewhat impatiently, to be
honest. Right here, in--
H-E-L-heim.
What? Helheim?
So you are joking, right?
That can't be true!
We followed the compass
the whole way here.
It's been leading us
straight to Prudisia!
[gasps]
And you trusted that?
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Just because it was
pretty and glowed?
The fact is you've
been heading here
from the moment you
stepped out of Anatae!
Teacher. What are
you talking about?
Allow me to make
an introduction!
[KAISAR, FAVARO, AMIRA grunt]
[gasps]
[MARTINET]
Meet the handsome gentleman
who shall rule the world!
Since the Demon Lord Satan
is about to be gone forever,
he will soon lay claim
to the Demon Throne,
and be crowned Lord Beelzebub!
[KAISAR]
Beezlebub?
[KAISAR grunts]
What the hell is this?
I can't move!
Amira. It is time to
fulfill your purpose.
As an instrument for
breaking Bahamut's seal.
Sorry, but no.
Oh?
[AMIRA]
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to change our fate!
I'm taking my mother
and leaving this place!
She's going to take
the key out of me
and then we'll be happy again!
[MARTINET] Hm. That's an
interesting idea. Yes.
Why don't you try
asking her right now?
[gasps]
[MARTINET] Dear Mother and
daughter, reunited at last.
[yells]
[pants]
[RITA]
Oh. You did survive.
[AZAZEL]
Necromancer Rita.
I'm a zombie now.
[BACCHUS]
I'm warning you to behave.
If you try anything
funny in here,
we'll finish you for good.
What are you playing at?
Why bother dragging me in here?
We have some questions
to ask you, that's all.
[AZAZEL]
And you're stupid enough
to think I'll answer them?
It might be in your interest.
It's about the people
behind this plot
with Amira and the God Key.
And I get the sense you've
been left out of the party.
[AMIRA]
Mother? Are you okay?
[MARTINET]
Go on, what are you waiting for?
Go to her! Isn't that
what you want?
I thought you missed her
with all of your heart!
[KAISAR]
Is that really her?
Prob'ly. They sure
do look alike.
Oh!
Perhaps you're worried
it's too good to be true!
Well let me reassure you.
She is the real deal.
[MARTINET]
That's it, don't be shy!
Let the reunion commence!
What is this?
He's clearly playing her
but I can't figure out why.
[AMIRA]
Can you hear me? Mom?
Say something. I need to
know if it's really you.
Please, answer me. Mom?
[screams]
What's wrong? Don't...
Don't you want to see me?
[cackles] Why the frown,
Amira? Are you surprised?
Is this not the fairytale
reunion you expected
after going through so much
trouble to get here?
Go on, ask her
to remove the Key!
Ask the woman who despises you
more than anything
else in existence!
No, you're lying!
I know you are,
because I remember.
My mother loved me!
I know she...
[AMIRA gasps]
Now you've seen
what really happened.
You weren't born
from that angel.
You were extracted.
Like a parasite,
you bored into her soul
and ripped out the
parts we needed.
If anyone is responsible
for your birth,
it's the great
Beelzebub, not her.
Liar.
[MARTINET]
And that pendant.
No!
[MARTINET] You know why it
helped you remember your mother?
Because that's what
I designed it to do!
No--
[MARTINET] I used magic to
implant those memories in it --
all false, of course -- and it's
been feeding them to you!
Liar.
Though I have to admit, I hoped
it would do the trick
but I never dreamed
it would work that well.
I mean you ate those memories
like candy, didn't you!
You liar, you liar,
you liar, you liar, you liar!
If you're interested
I'd be happy to create
more memories for you to enjoy.
I consider myself
something of an artist
and I just love it when
someone appreciates my work!
[gasps]
[AMIRA]
Liar!
Heartless monster!
[KAISAR screaming]
You bastards!
[MARTINET] Truth is, you're
not really a person at all.
You're a tool we created.
A means to an end, nothing more!
You're the vessel for
the Transcendent Key
that will soon revive Bahamut!
Transcendent Key...
That's what this is all about.
[AMIRA]
I'll hug her.
[gasps]
[AMIRA]
That's all I have to do...
And then she'll know.
[gasps]
She'll know that I'm hers.
'Cause that's how
mothers are, right?
Don't do it.
Amira! No! It's
a trap! Stay away!
[screams]
[yells]
[NICOLE]
Amira.
Mother?
[gasps]
[AMIRA]
Mother!
[gasping]
Amira!
[screams]
[gasps]
What the hell is that?
Damn it!
If things keep going like
this, we'll have no chance
of stopping Bahamut's awakening.
Tell me everything you know
about who's behind
this, and fast.
I'd laugh if it didn't hurt.
Whoever heard of a zombie trying
to stop the world from ending?
Don't give a damn
about the world.
I only care about those boys.
They're too young to die.
[AZAZEL chuckles] Well I agree
with you on the first part.
But the only life I care about
is my own. Make a deal?
What kind of deal?
Not much. Passage to Abos
is all that I'll need.
[MARTINET] The Transcendent Key
is now complete, my lord.
And now we will wake Bahamut.
Those devils.
How could they do that?
[FAVARO] Guess this means
there's only one option left.
[KAISAR]
What option? You've got a plan?
Yeah. Hey!
[MARTINET]
Huh?
Question for you.
How 'bout we team up?
[FAVARO] I'm serious-- please!
I wanna switch sides!
Favaro! You rat!
You're willing to
abandon your friends?
Just to save your
own miserable neck?
Hell yeah!
They were never really
friends to begin with!
I know when I'm on
a sinking ship!
He amuses me.
[FAVARO grunts]
[MARTINET]
Drink this, if you're ready.
Ah, heh.
Catching others off guard
to gain the advantage.
I'm obviously far more familiar
with your tactics than
you realize, my dear Favaro.
[FAVARO groans]
[FAVARO groans, gags]
[KAISAR grunts]
[KAISAR] A defeated demon.
I think he's gone mad!
[FAVARO]
Just don't make eye contact!
[FAVARO, KAISER] On the next
Rage of Bahamut: Genesis:
All Roads Lead to Abos!
[FAVARO]
Run!
[MARTINET]
My de--