[AMIRA screams]
Lady Amira!
[URIEL] I feared the
humans would not be able
to protect the
God Key on their own.
[RAPHAEL] Jeanne D'Arc
may indeed be capable
of becoming a Holy Knight.
[MICHAEL] Yes, and this
conflict surrounding Bahamut
will surely resolve through her.
[GABRIEL] No. We will
be the ones to end it.
She is merely an instrument.
We've yet to identify
the demon masterminds,
or their end objective,
but that will soon come.
What matters now is that
we assert our control,
as our kind should.
We must reclaim the God Key.
[CHARIOCE] Saint Jeanne,
holiest of maidens.
You've served your king in war
magnificently, once again.
As a reward, I shall grant
you a territory of your own.
What would you like?
Baruzo? Ruelle?
I'm grateful, sire.
But I must humbly decline.
Decline? Are you sure?
I have no doubt, sire.
There is, however, one
request I would make instead.
[AMIRA]
Ah...!
[KAISAR] Are you
all right, my lady?
[AMIRA]
What happened?
[KAISAR] You fainted by the
statue. We're not sure why.
I'm pretty sure I know why.
She drank a whole barrel.
It's not helpful
when you talk.
I, uh... I had a dream.
About when I came
out of my cocoon.
Cocoon?
I was sleeping there.
Growing inside it for
who knows how long.
[MARTINET]
Wake up, Amira.
You are one of the most special
beings in all of creation.
I am... special?
[MARTINET] You must fulfill
your mission, my dear Amira.
Do so faithfully,
and your greatest wish
will most certainly come true.
She waits for you now, in
the promised land of Helheim.
Go to... Helheim?
[MARTINET] She is the
key to your happiness.
She is all you desire.
Go to her.
[AMIRA]
My mother...
You said before that pendant
helps you remember her, right?
[KAISAR] I'm sure you miss
your family a great deal.
[AMIRA]
Father!
Hey now, no more disappearing.
Where are you going?
My father was calling
for me when I fainted!
Calm down. You want to see
your dad; I can understand that.
But it's not safe to
go wandering around.
[door creaks]
What about her father?
What are you talking about?
Oh, nothing. We're just
telling stories.
You come here for a reason?
The king wants to see you.
At the steps of his throne.
[FAVARO]
Wha...?
Anyone want to guess
what this is about?
[RITA]
How would I know?
Maybe he's going to send us
to the gallows after all.
That's easy to joke
about for a zombie,
since you're already dead.
[AMIRA yelps]
Huh? Now what?
That's my father!
By the woman!
[RITA] Are you kidding? That's
Jeanne D'Arc's lieutenant.
Father!
Can we talk before you
cause a royal scene?
Do you seriously think
that big shot is your dad?
If that's true, it's
significant. For starters...
it would mean he's
not really a human.
A demon in disguise?
I'd buy that.
[KAISAR]
No.
He can't be a demon.
Yeah. That'd be crazy.
--[FAVARO yells]
--[RITA] Make up your mind.
I met him once before,
in the city of Wytearp.
I was close to giving up.
Desperation is a powerful force.
It can make a man stronger.
Don't ever forget that.
[KAISAR] He inspired me
when I needed it most.
He's a proud and
honorable knight.
[CHARIOCE] Favaro Leone.
Kaisar Lidfard.
My kingdom is in your debt.
For your heroics against
the demon raiders,
I confer on both of you
the title of knight.
[FAVARO]
Huh?!
[KAISAR]
Knighthood? For us?
[FAVARO]
Your Maj....
Thanks for the gesture, but that
sounds like way more hassle--
[KAISAR] We gratefully
accept, sire!
[FAVARO gasps, groans]
[MINISTER 8A]
Hear ye!
The ceremony of knighthood
shall now commence.
[CHARIOCE] As king of this
realm, I hereby appoint you both
to the royal order of
the Orléans Knights.
[KAISAR] You honor
us too much, sire.
Yeah, you shouldn't have.
[FAVARO chuckles]
[KAISAR]
Hm.
At long last,
I have fulfilled my oath.
I'll never have to
hunt bounties again.
That's too bad. Cause you
can't take off that bracelet.
I mean, you can't even
break it with a sword.
[KAISAR]
What?
Not unless you're in
that drunk's presence.
Who knows what tavern he's at?
--[BACCHUS sneezes]
--[HAMSA] Bless you!
[CHARIOCE] Saint Jeanne, these
are the courageous warriors
who fought the demon invaders
with us. I have no doubt
they will make my royal
Orléans Knights even stronger.
[JEANNE] Most wise,
Your Majesty.
[CHARIOCE]
The angel Michael!
You have battled magnificently,
o valiant humans.
You are serving the gods well.
Of course. It is our
honor to serve.
As long as the God Key
is on human ground,
there will be more
activity from the demons,
and you must be well-armed.
Thank you.
[MICHAEL] The Précieuse, a sword
capable of both blessedness
and malevolence.
It can even slay a god.
I bestow it unto you,
Saint Jeanne.
May you use its
power righteously.
I swear that I shall.
Michael. And what about me?
Yes, Your good faith
will be rewarded.
Continue to serve us piously,
and your endeavors
will have the
blessing of the gods.
[AMIRA gasps]
[AZAZEL groans]
[BEELZEBUB] You are
truly pathetic, Azazel.
[AZAZEL]
Beezlebub!
You deceived me!
[AZAZEL yells]
[AZAZEL screams]
The puppet's usefulness
comes to an end.
[AZAZEL] What end are
you trying to achieve?
Why are you betraying
Lord Lucifer?
[BEELZEBUB] All realms
will know soon enough,
for the moment is nigh.
Moment? What moment?
[BEELZEBUB]
The moment of judgment.
[CHARIOCE]
Curse that usurping woman!
The king of Anatae is
the proxy for the gods!
They should only
be speaking to me!
She rejected my
offer for land,
which would have gotten
her out of my city!
And now Michael
openly humiliates me
by giving her that
holy sword instead!
Oh, tell me, Mother, please!
Who is the most revered
in the capital? Who do
the people love more?
[IZVELLIA] You must
be careful, my son.
[CHARIOCE gasps]
[CHARIOCE]
Mother!
[IZVELLIA] There is a
traitor in your midst.
A viper who wants
to take your life.
Who wants to kill me?
Who is it, mother?
You know the
answer, son. Look!
[CHARIOCE]
Jeanne D'Arc?!
[CHARIOCE yells]
This is a warning.
A vision of what will
very soon come to pass.
Jeanne will come.
She will strike you down and
steal your kingdom for herself.
I won't let her!
I don't want to die!
[CITIZENS' VOICES] Saint Jeanne!
Saint Jeanne! Saint Jeanne!...
[CITIZEN 8A] All hail
the maiden saint!
[CITIZEN 8B]
She's the light of Anatae!
[CITIZEN 8C] The king
is dead! Good riddance!
[CHARIOCE] I won't
allow it! I won't!
I'm the king.
It's not right!
[FAVARO]
Hey.
[FAVARO chokes, grunts]
I can't breathe!
[AMIRA]
Oh, it's you.
[FAVARO grunts]
Damn it...
I said to stay put!
How was that not clear?
I'm sorry, it's just...
[RITA] You can finally
see your father,
and it's hard for you
to pass that up.
[FAVARO sighs]
[FAVARO]
Come on. Let's go.
[RITA] This isn't the
way to our quarters.
[FAVARO]
Yeah, yeah, I know.
If my information's right, then
your old man should be up there.
You won't be happy till
you see him, right?
[AMIRA]
Mm.
Then go up and do it
already, would ya?
[AMIRA giggles]
Thank you, Fava!
I'll be damned.
That's the first time
she ever said my name.
Well, she forgot the "ro,"
but you know, baby steps.
Hey, what are you doing?
This isn't a group trip!
[RITA] If you think I'm going
to miss this, you're insane.
Yeah, fair point.
[AMIRA]
Um... Father?
You're here,
Amira. I'm glad.
I had to come.
It's hard to believe you
were a baby five years ago.
[FAVARO]
Five years? Uh...
[FAVARO laughs]
Sorry about that. My bad.
Leone. From what
I understand,
you've saved her life
more than once.
I'm sure this was more
than you bargained for.
Thank you for
keeping her safe.
He had help.
Amira. We need
to talk now.
It's high time you learned the
truth about you and your mother.
The gods of war
have been wiped out?
[MICHAEL] It doesn't appear
to be the work of Azazel
or his lord.
But whoever did it--
[GABRIEL] Is the
mastermind behind
the theft of
the key, obviously.
[MICHAEL] Gabriel,
what should we do?
[GABRIEL] Instruct the
humans to increase
security in their capital.
We must prevent the key girl
from being abducted while we
prepare for our next move.
[GABRIEL] If Lucifer isn't
behind this, who could it be?
It's been a long time,
Beelzebub.
[BEELZEBUB] Azazel has
failed you miserably.
Demonkind cannot afford
more blunders, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] A real pity. I'll
just have to send someone else.
[BEELZEBUB] No need.
I will take over from here.
[LUCIFER]
Is that so?
[BEELZEBUB] Do you
object to that?
No.
[BEELZEBUB]
Once I retrieve the girl,
we will have both
sides of the Key.
Then the re-manifestation
of Lord Satan can begin.
[LAVALLEY] As the angels said,
Amira is remarkably special,
born from a union
between demon and god.
Yeah! I've been
wondering about that,
So a demon and a god
actually hooked up?
Do their parts
even line up right?
Do they even have parts?
So what does
that make you?
[FAVARO groans]
[FAVARO]
Eh?
I do know Amira,
but I'm not her father.
I am an ordinary human.
[AMIRA gasps]
[LAVALLEY] It was five
years ago. I was assigned
as a bodyguard for an angel
who needed assistance.
Her name was Nicole,
Amira. Your mother.
She had been cast out of Heaven,
forbidden to ever return
to her kind. Despite this,
she looked so happy.
Because she had
you in her arms.
As her guard, we faced
relentless demon attacks,
and we were exhausted.
But seeing the two of you
in our camp gave us the hope
we needed to survive.
But then...
[LAVALLEY] After you
were kidnapped,
Nicole left for the
demon realm on her own,
determined
to get you back.
She left this pendant
with me, to keep safe.
I was reassigned, and continued
fighting in other campaigns.
For a time I searched for Nicole
on my own, but to no avail.
And then, that day
at the bridge...
The pendant told me
all I needed to know.
You had grown, but there
was no mistaking it.
You were Nicole's daughter.
Fascinating tale. So the demons
kidnapped her as a baby
and sped her growth so
they wouldn't have to wait.
That explains why
she's so childish.
I just thought she was weird.
So what now? I was told over
and over I could see her again.
As soon as I took
the key to Helheim!
[LAVALLEY] And now
that you know the truth,
you're right not to
trust those words.
Helheim is a demon stronghold;
a god couldn't survive there.
But if she's not there,
where is she?
Your pendant.
Let me see it.
Well, I certainly didn't know
her little keepsake
could do that.
That's it. Her true location.
In the valley of Prudisia.
You know that place?
No.
If you let this be your guide,
then you can reach
your mother at last.
Please take it with you.
Another compass. I won't
break it this time.
Your mother had a power that
was unusual, even among gods.
and I believe
that's another reason
the demons were after her.
If it's possible to
free you of the God Key,
then she's the one
who can do it.
It's settled.
Of course I'll go.
What? Seriously?
That should mean
she'll remove your tail.
Oh, yeah! I think
it's a great plan.
Believe me, Amira, I would
go with you if I could.
Yes, I know that. Your soldiers
need you here. I understand.
I'm sorry. When you find her,
be sure to thank her for
the faith she had in me.
No.
I'm going to bring
her back with me.
So you can thank her in person!
Sounds good.
[FAVARO sniffs]
I didn't know you
were such a softy.
[FAVARO]
Yeah.
Just the thought of finally
getting rid of this tail...
And you'll go with me.
Right, Fava?
[FAVARO] Hell, no! I'd rather
jump in a damn fire!
Wish I could. I bet
your mom's a real looker.
It'd be great to meet
her at least once.
But I've got other plans
I just can't get out of!
You sure?
[FAVARO] Yeah, I mean,
it breaks my heart,
but I've got
responsibilities, you know.
Well, too bad.
[FAVARO sighs]
That's nice. Are you gonna
tell Kaisar about this?
He's back to being
a fancy tin can now.
He's got no reason to hang
around with us anymore.
Guess that means
the three of us'll
have to be your
send-off party.
Though I highly doubt we
can sneak her out of here
without some
serious distraction.
[FAVARO]
Heh.
More demons?
[RITA] Honestly.
Just 'cause I'm a zombie
doesn't mean they can
work me like a slave.
[FAVARO] Sneaking out the
underground water channels.
Lavalley's clever,
I'll give him that.
[FAVARO breathes deeply]
[FAVARO] I still can't
believe that tiny little lie
got me into all this crap.
But now it's finally over!
Now get this tail off me!
Oh, no. What's with
the wavy hand?
Well, you did say you wanted
to meet my mother, didn't you?
[FAVARO]
Aahhh...!
[CHARIOCE] The soldiers are in
a frenzy! What's going on now?
What? Who's there?
Oh, it's you.
Thank goodness.
[CHARIOCE screams]
[JEANNE]
Should I get dreadlocks too?
[LAVALLEY]
I don't think so.
[JEANNE] On the next
Rage of Bahamut: Genesis...
[LAVALLEY] Decision
in the Wailing Woods.
[JEANNE] Your answer
wounds me deeply.
[LAVALLEY]
Eh?