We must endure!
Reinforcement from Heaven
will arrive soon!
But until they do,
the barrier must hold!
[ARCHANGEL A]
All this power,
and these are
nothing but tremors
from the mere
possibility of revival.
This beast surpasses
gods and demons alike.
If Bahamut should
actually awaken...
[ARCHANGEL A] ...what will
happen to the world?
Where'd they go?
[grunts]
[RITA]
Stop gawking like a fool.
[FAVARO]
Ow!
You're that damn necromancer!
[RITA]
That monster's name is Gregor.
He's a living, flying
castle for Azazel.
Which century did
you learn that one?
You know I'm escaping
with you, doncha?
[RITA]
Escape? I'm going after them.
[groans] You want to chase
a flying beast-castle?
In a dinghy?
Are you freaking stu--
[grunts]
[RITA] If you're not planning
to help me, then get lost.
[growls]
[FAVARO]
We're talking about a demon girl
who put a curse on me, and a
guy who wakes up every morning
chanting, "Must kill Favaro."
My life would be a hell of a lot
easier without 'em.
Do you want one?
So what's the
big plan here, Rita?
I mean, how you gonna chase 'em?
You do know rowboats
aren't exactly
high-speed transport, don't you?
[sighs]
You feel that?
Strong wind.
[AMIRA gasps, coughs]
[PAZUZU]
Talk!
Who ordered you
to steal the God Key?!
[DOGS mumble]
[PAZUZU]
Who sent you into the Ark?!
Answer me!
[KAISAR]
Stop, you foul demon!
Torturing a defenseless
girl--have you no shame?!
[AMIRA groans]
[PAZUZU] Abandon all
hope of escaping this.
Gregor's poison has
sapped your strength!
[AMIRA screams]
Stooop!
[AMIRA whimpers]
[PAZUZU]
Hmph. Not again.
Come on, aren't you done yet?
Let us have a turn at her, ARF!
Your torture sucks!
[BOTH] You need less bark
and more bite, ARF!
Maybe she's an ignorant pawn
who doesn't even know her king.
[MALE DOG]
Let us torture her, ARF!
[FEMALE DOG] There's all
sorts of things to try, ARF!
Fire and bullwhips!
Stab em with a stick!
[MALE DOG]
Torture chairs and boots!
[FEMALE DOG]
Iron maidens!
[MALE DOG]
Pendulums and Pears of Anguish!
[FEMALE DOG]
Scavenger's Daughter!
Hot irons and bone saws!
Neck violins!
That does sound
painful! I love it!
[KAISAR] How many times
do I have to tell you?!
That girl hasn't done anything!
She was manipulated
by a demon named Favaro!
That's it!
[CERBERUS giggles]
--[PAZUZU laughs]
--[DOGS chuckles]
[AZAZEL]
Priceless, isn't he?
Now you can see why
I've kept him alive.
--He's hilarious!
--[laughter continues]
Stop, my sides hurt ARF!
[KAISAR]
What's so funny?!
Relax, my human plaything.
I'll let you in on the truth.
Let's see how you feel
after you know what she
really is and what she's done.
[sighs]
[BACCHUS]
Funny way to say hello.
What is this, Puff Ball Head?
We need you to
lend us your carriage.
People ask a god for a
favor with an offering,
not a blade at his neck.
I had to make sure
you'd pay attention.
I'll never ask
for anything else.
Please, just hear us out.
I don't think so.
[gasps]
[BACCHUS] Unless you bring
me some Helheim booze.
I might listen to you then.
[FAVARO] If I could go to
Helheim for booze
I wouldn't need your help
getting to freaking Helheim!
And you owe me!
Your tip about the boats
going there was bogus!
[BACCHUS]
Oh, really?
[FAVARO] Damn it, what kind of
god just screws with people?!
All right!
If you want a ride,
let's see you pay the fare.
The fare?
[BACCHUS]
The price is conviction.
[BACCHUS chuckles]
[BACCHUS] Can you show me
how serious you really are?
[BACCHUS gasps]
Hah!
That serious enough?!
[gasps]
But-- You--
YOU IDIOT!
That was dangerous, damn it!
[RITA]
You're a bore, you know that?
You should at least have
chopped off your arm
to show him how serious you are.
And how would
I play the heroic,
sword-wielding rescuer
with a stump, huh?
[RITA sighs]
Kids today.
[sighs]
This is pathetic.
The great Bacchus
has lost his edge.
What's pathetic is your
decision-making, boy!
Now that you've
shattered your bracelet,
you're just a common outlaw
and can never go back
to being a bounty hunter!
You talk way too much, duck.
[HIMSA screams]
So what's your plan?
How are you going to
make a living now?
Well, if I live
through this rescue,
I'm sure I'll come up
with something.
You sure are a
happy-go-lucky bastard.
I'd like to meet the parents
who brought you up.
Humph!
I wish you could.
My old man did teach me a lot.
[BAROSSA]
Feel that, Favaro?
You know which way
the wind is blowing?
Toward tomorrow.
Get it?
[RITA]
No. Do you know what he meant?
[FAVARO]
No idea.
[KAISAR]
Lady Amira's a traitor?
It can't be...
She stole this God Key from...
...from Heaven's sacred ground?
[AZAZEL] While her actions
could be beneficial to us,
we have to be careful.
I can't believe this girl
could have pulled off
such a feat on her own.
[PAZUZU] Someone else is pulling
the strings from the shadows!
And we need to know who
so we can plan our next move.
If that's true, then I know the
schemer that you're looking for!
It's that demon Favaro!
He must've tricked her
into stealing it!
[chuckles]
[CERBERUS, PAZUZU laugh]
[MALE DOG] Favaro,
the demon mastermind, ARF!
[PAZUZU] I've been
a demon a long time,
I can't believe
I didn't know about him!
[CERBERUS]
What a joke!
You can laugh out of
ignorance all you want!
Till he ruins you!
That's right, just like
he ruined me!
I thought Favaro Leone
was harmless, too.
But he betrayed me and
set a trap for my father!
He drove the Lidfard family
into poverty and shame!
He's evil!
[AZAZEL]
Did you say "Lidfard"?
[grunts]
[AZAZEL]
I see.
So, you're the son
of Laurus Lidfard.
How'd you--?
[AZAZEL]
Which means this Favaro of yours
must be the son of
Barossa the thief.
[AZAZEL chuckles]
[gasps]
[KAISAR grunts]
Just who in the hell are you?!
When your die, you'll have
accomplished nothing.
Exactly like your
pitiful father.
[AZAZEL laughs]
[BACCHUS] Azazel is
the right-hand of Lucifer,
chief of the fallen angels.
There's no question
where he's headed:
The demon capital of Cocytus.
Far to the west, in a barren
land called Sword Valley,
there's a demonic gate
that leads to Cocytus.
I'll take you that far, but then
I'm washing my hands of this.
The rest is up to you.
Best of luck, Puff ball head.
This is the last time
we'll meet.
You're light!
[RITA]
All zombies are.
What's wrong?
Ah, nothin'.
Here we go!
I still can't believe
I'm in this mess.
[FAVARO]
This is all her fault.
Never should've
asked her to kiss meeee!
My...
mo... ther...
Lady Amira!
Just hold on.
I'll save you and
these demons will pay.
I swear it.
[CERBERUS] Are you sure we
should be relaxing out here?
[FEMALE DOG]
What about torture?
[FEMALE, MALE DOG]
We're happy to try!
After all, we still
haven't gotten
a lick of information
out of her yet.
It doesn't matter.
Even if we don't learn
who she's allied with,
we have possession
of her body
and that means
we have the God Key.
There's no reason to brood.
[CERBERUS barks]
[whispering]
You know what to do.
Are you sure we're going the
right way in this maze?
[RITA] I'd say so,
judging by the smell.
Zombie nose, huh?
[sniffs]
[RITA]
You never told me.
Why'd you decide to save them?
[FAVARO]
Beats me!
[FAVARO grunts]
[CERBERUS]
I'm surprised.
How'd they even get on board?
[PAZUZU]
They're like rats on a ship.
I'll take care of them myself.
[AZAZEL]
Well, I think it's amusing.
It's what makes humans
so enjoyable.
[KAISAR grunts]
[AZAZEL] I'm going to give you
a special opportunity,
son of Laurus.
The opportunity to avenge
the father you loved so much.
[KAISAR]
Huh?!
[AZAZEL chuckles]
[FAVARO pants]
[RITA] He told me you tricked
him, and got his father killed.
And yet here you are
risking your life to save him.
Even though he still
wants to kill you.
[FAVARO] Don't worry about that,
just focus on your steps.
There's no telling what
kind of trap door or--
[FAVARO squeals]
[screams]
[FAVARO]
Eww!
Rita?
You here?
Hello!
Well, this is some
charming décor.
--[AMIRA] Why are...
--[FAVARO grunts]
--...you here?
--[gasps]
[FAVARO]
Amira!
Hang on, I'll get you down!
--[KAISAR] FAVARO!
--[FAVARO gasps]
[KAISAR yells]
[FAVARO gasps]
Whoa! Whoa, buddy, hold on!
At last!
I'll reclaim my father's honor,
and glory of my house!
[FAVARO] We've gotta
get out of here first!
Do it for Amira!
Oh, I'll save her!
Don't you dare
even speak her name!
--[FAVARO gasps]
--[KAISAR yells]
[AZAZEL chuckles]
That's it, humans, dance.
It's about time
I had some entertainment.
[FAVARO pants]
[KAISAR yells]
[KAISAR] It's your fault.
My father's downfall...
And my family's ruin!
It's really not a
good time for a recap!
Whoa!
Me stooping to the humiliating
life of a bounty hunter!
Yaargh!
Lady Amira's capture!
Being abused by demons!
[coughs]
All because of you!
[grunts]
[FAVARO]
Huh...?
Your revenge will have to wait.
It's time to go.
[gasps]
Rita? How did you get here?
[growls]
[CERBERUS] The gate to
Cocytus is up ahead.
We're about to pass through.
[MALE DOG]
Enough playing around, ARF!
[FEMALE DOG]
Kill 'im already, ARF!
[roaring]
[FAVARO]
Huh...? What the--?!
[AZAZEL]
Hmm?
[PAZUZU]
What the hell happened?!
[CERBERUS]
The gate!
Something caused it to collapse!
[AZAZEL] It seems we have the
Orléans Knights to blame.
They've been waiting
like snakes in the grass.
Catapults!
Now! Fire away!
[CERBERUS screams]
An ambush!
Isn't that the kind of thing
you're supposed to be
looking out for?!
[MALE DOG]
You screwed up, ARF!
[FEMALE DOG]
We're telling on you, ARF!
[CERBERUS]
Good luck, you're gonna need it!
[AZAZEL]
Tch. Mangy dog.
Pazuzu. Bring me
the girl, quickly.
[LAVALLEY] It seems our
patience has been rewarded.
How did you know the
demon's castle
would come through
this valley to get home?
We have our intelligence and
reconnaissance operations
to thank for that.
And you're certain
she's there?
I would hate to
waste our resources
if the one-winged demon
isn't on board.
Yes. I swear on my
good name, Saint Jeanne.
Then I'll leave the
next orders to you.
[LAVALLEY]
Archers! Release!
Dragon Knights! Take flight!
[LAVALLEY] Find the one-winged
demon, and bring her to us!
[LAVALLEY] Catapults and
sorcerer divisions,
fire at will to give the
Dragon Knights sustained cover!
Keep those wyverns at bay!
Sounds like some
serious action out there.
Would you two hurry up?
[PAZUZU growls]
[FAVARO] Aw, damn,
he's a big one!
[PAZUZU]
Playtime's over, human scum.
What?! Where is she?
Miserable wretches!
Where did you hide the girl?!
[gasps]
Hey, Kaisar.
Help me, just this once.
What? Some nerve!
You actually think that I'd--
[FAVARO] You wanna
save Amira or not?
Huh?
And as soon as we get
out of this flying horror show,
we can settle things between us
once and for all, okay?
I won't run this time.
I promise.
[KAISAR] You'd better not
forget those words.
[PAZUZU sniffs]
There you are.
[FAVARO, KAISAR yell]
[FAVARO grunts]
[PAZUZU]
You dare challenge me?!
Goodnight, you ugly
son of a bitch!
[PAZUZU grunts]
[PAZUZU] You lowly,
bottom-feeding worm!
It looks like we're not
out of the fire yet.
[AZAZEL]
That's far enough.
I'm afraid I can't
let you take the girl.
[RITA]
Azazel.
Don't tell me...
[AZAZEL chuckles]
Can't be... No...
[AMIRA grunts]
Amira!
Leave her alone!
Now then.
Come to me.
[AZAZEL grunts]
[AZAZEL]
I see.
So that explains it.
[RITA] Does anyone have
a clue what that was?
O, Michael, angel of war!
Bless this holy spear of Maltet
with thy heavenly grace!
[FAVARO]
Nice one, Rita!
I didn't know you could
control one of these puppies!
[RITA]
As long as they're dead.
Don't move her.
It'll take time for
the poison to wear off.
[KAISAR] Those flags--
They're the Orléans Knights!
Favaro, don't tell me
you sent for them!
[FAVARO]
'Course not.
The wind just happened
to blow our way.
The wind?
[chuckles]
[FAVARO]
Yeah. The wind of tomorrow.
[AMIRA] I shopped on my own
for the first time.
[RITA]
What'd you buy?
[AMIRA]
Meat.
[RITA]
Meat?
[BOTH] On the next Rage of
Bahamut: Genesis:
Legendary Saint.
[AMIRA]
I'm sure you eat meat.
[RITA]
Is that a zombie joke?