[BEEZLEBUB cackling]
Bahamut has awakened,
and I herby pass my judgment!
Hear me, o gods.
Our long-standing war
is over, and it is time
to accept your defeat!
I find you unfit to rule!
Bow before me!
And demons! Hear me, as well!
You will etch my name into
eternity! I am Lord Beezlebub!
Our kind will stand above gods,
but I will be the
master above you all!
Now witness my power!
I control Bahamut itself!
[gasps]
[AZAZEL groaning]
No, it isn't possible.
[LAVALLEY]
Pure poetry.
Lavalley! What is this?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you see?
He was behind everything.
Gaining your trust, then
misdirecting you to Helheim.
Framing Jeanne D'Arc, and
turning her into a demon.
It was all part
of his deception.
And this was the goal.
He manipulated
everyone at once--
gods, demons, and humans alike.
All so he could
bring back Bahamut.
[LAVALLEY cackles] Who knew a
zombie could be so smart?
t's all over, arf!
We're gonna be toast, arf!
[DOGS yelp]
But I don't wanna die!
[DOGS, CERBERUS scream]
Lavalley! Who are you, really?
His true name is
Gilles de Rais.
He's a sorcerer with a bounty
and some kind of death wish--
and he's taken countless
lives with his magic.
He's a bounty?
Yes.
I mean that's according
to the god of hangovers,
but it does seem to add up.
You used us!
Could you two please
keep it down?
I really can't have
you ruining the mood.
[growls]
This has taken me a great
deal of time and effort.
And now I want to savor
the end of the world.
You scoundrel!
[yells]
[LAVALLEY]
Did you not hear me?
Get away from him!
[KAISAR groans]
When someone asks nicely,
it's polite to oblige.
But you seem determined to test
the sharpness of my blade.
His face is changing!
Don't you understand how
lucky you are to be here?
You fool. This is
the biggest moment
this reality has ever known.
[KAISAR grunts]
[LAVALLEY, MARTINET]
This is the world's destruction!
Can't you finally acknowledge
that life is pointless and
enjoy the beauty as it burns?
Let me go!
Damn.
Seems my body has
become a bit unstable.
Sorry for that.
I think you've taken
one too many
of your dubious concoctions.
We're both stuck in
strange bodies now.
[grunts]
[LAVALLEY] So the silly man
insists on playing knight
for a little longer. Fine.
If you refuse to sit still,
then maybe I'll have your
old friend keep you busy.
[gasps]
Well, now what? I already
used up all my antidotes.
[BEEZLEBUB] I bore Amira
from my own demonic essence
and magic power.
And used her as the vessel
that would unseal Bahamut.
You promised me if I did, that I
could bend the beast to my will.
Curse you, Martinet, you lying--
[AZAZEL]
There, you fool. We're even.
Although, it hardly matters now.
[CHARIOCE] No! I don't want
to die! I want to be the king!
Please, Mother!
You have to protect me!
Mother! Mommy!
[CHARIOCE screams]
[KAISAR grunting]
[gasps]
[inaudible]
Rita! I'm going to settle
things once and for all!
Stay out of this fight!
You idiot! This is hardly the
time for your stupid feud!
[KAISAR grunting]
[RITA gasping]
[RITA screams]
[KAISAR grunts]
[KAISAR screams]
Kaisar!
Now, that's the sort
of entertainment
I've been looking for.
[FAVARO]
Got some advice for ya.
[LAVALLEY grunts]
[FAVARO] When you're walkin'
around with a bounty
on your head,
there're a few things
you should probably watch
out for. For example...
Seel Soh... Cetom!
[gasps]
[gasps, screams]
...getting too close to a knight
who's still walkin' around
with a bracelet from his
old bounty hunter days.
[KAISAR groaning]
[RITA]
Okay, talk.
When exactly did you
turn back to normal?
What, you can't guess?
It was when Kaisar gave me
that bi-otch of a wake-up call.
But how did that work?
I managed to catch
one of your antidotes
that you dropped.
Then I stuck it in the head
of the crossbow bolt.
And then Kaisar and I
just put on a little show
to convince that freak I was
still his faithful servant.
Though, I swear when we
started, I didn't think
I'd be lopping off your hand.
I have no regrets.
It was the only way
to convince that trickster.
So amputation was seriously
the best idea you had?
Idiots.
[KAISAR groans]
[BACCHUS]
Nice work.
[FAVARO]
Damn!
Looks like you got thrashed.
[BACCHUS] Yeah, I have the
lunatic to think for that.
His reward better be
down right handsome.
That's an understatement.
This bad boy's worth more than
even you can spend in a day.
If that's a dare, then I
gladly accept. Although...
[FAVARO] I doubt I'll be hitting
the taverns anytime soon.
[KAISAR] You think you
can reach Lady Amira?
[FAVARO] Don't know.
But it's up to me to find out.
Does that mean you've decided
what you're going to do?
I'll go with you, Favaro.
Are you delusional,
or did you forget
you're down to one hand?
Hey, Kaisar.
I have to kill Amira.
Cut it out.
Now's not the time for
your foolish jokes.
You see me laughing?
How could you even
say those words?
She fused with Bahamut--
it was permanent.
She'll be a part of him
as long as she's alive.
So I'm going to have to kill
her. It's the only option left.
There must be some
other way to save her!
We have to keep trying!
[FAVARO]
There's not. It's too late.
The dragon in the
forest told me.
[KAISAR]
But I swore.
I swore that I'd save her,
no matter what it took.
I can't let you kill her.
I have to bring her back alive!
[FAVARO]
We can't get her out, Kaisar.
But I can save her, in a way.
Save her from suffering inside
that beast for eternity.
That's why I need
to do this. For her.
Bacchus. Any idea how
I can get up there?
We can think of one way.
Right, Hamsa?
What?
You'll carry him there yourself!
[HAMSA squaks]
[KAISAR]
Wait. I'm coming, too.
Did I change your mind?
Never! I'm going to bring
her back from Bahamut,
no matter what you say!
Be back soon! Either that
or we'll be dead!
[groans]
--[HAMSA grunts]
--[FAVARO, KAISAR yelp]
[FAVARO, KAISAR scream]
[HAMSA yelps]
This is nuts!
I can't get closer!
Then You have to
keep trying! Please!
[HAMSA grunts]
[HAMSA yelps]
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Can't it stop breathing
fire for a freakin' minute?
Look at that!
That's our cue!
[FAVARO, KAISAR grunt]
[FAVARO, KAISAR groan]
[KAISAR grunts]
[FAVARO]
Gotcha!
[KAISAR, FAVARO yelling]
[FAVARO, KAISAR panting]
[FAVARO, KAISAR yelp]
[KAISAR, FAVARO grunt]
[BOTH grunt]
[FAVARO yelps]
[KAISAR grunts]
[FAVARO grunts]
[gasps] Hey! Favaro!
[FAVARO grunting]
So it's you?
[BAHAMUT roaring]
[yells]
Amira!
[gasps]
The Holy Knight. It's you.
[KAISAR grunting]
[FAVARO yelping]
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[FAVARO yelping]
[FAVARO]
Oh... ah, ha...
Come on.
Don't'cha know it's
rude to stare?
[FAVARO]
Amira.
[AMIRA]
You finally came.
Well, yeah!
Ha! I couldn't let you run
off when you still haven't
taken this tail
off me, now could I?
Ah! Don't cry, that a was
a bad joke! Look, Amira.
I came despite the
odds 'cause I care
and can't stand to
see you in trouble.
It's always been that way.
Ever since we met.
You're lying.
I'm not lying!
And I'm sorry things didn't go
better with you and your mom.
You deserved more.
Don't be sorry. She really
did recognize me.
At the very end,
when I was hugging her.
Seriously?
It was just like you said!
Well, I am smart guy.
[AMIRA giggles]
But listen, Amira.
You got a good trip
ahead of you.
This time I'm taking you
to a way better place
than stupid Helheim.
It's gonna be full
of beautiful things.
I can't wait for you to see.
Liar.
I am not lying! Look!
Are these the eyes of a liar?
Hmmm!
Thank you, Favaro.
Hold on a second.
I don't think this is over.
[HAMSA]
Hurry! Jump on so we can go!
I can't! He's still
down there!
[growls]
[KAISAR grunts]
[FAVARO grunting]
[FAVARO screams]
Favaro!
[LEAD KNIGHT 12A]
Sir Kaisar.
If you're going to address
the troops as my lieutenant,
you'd better come now.
[LEAD KNIGHT 12A] Today is the
coronation of our new king.
And we, the royal Orlêans
Knights, are tasked with...
Is Lieutenant Kaisar here yet?
[BARTENDER 12A]
They say that just when Bahamut
was about to destroy the world,
The Holy Knight
of legend showed up
and banished it to some other
realm or dimension or something.
You think that means
the monster's dead?
Not a chance.
Bahamut can't be killed.
Not now. Not ever.
[FAVARO]
One day he'll come again,
so let's not get
too comfortable.
[FAVARO]
Still alive. Just like me.
You know which way that
wind is blowing, Favaro?
Toward tomorrow!
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[FAVARO]
Uh--
You think I'd let you run off
while I'm still in your debt?
Ha!
Hya!
[FAVARO]
Ha!
--[KAISAR] Hya!
--[FAVARO] Ha!