Fall back, fall back,
go! Retreat!
[roars]
[SOLDIER 1A] Please, Your
Majesty! You have to flee!
[gasps]
[ANCIENT KING gasps]
[KAISAR]
Yah!
[FAVARO]
[KAISAR grunts]
Ha!
[KAISAR yells]
[laughs]
[grunts]
Heh.
[KAISAR grunts]
Favaro!
[TAVERN GIRLS panting]
[OUTLAW 1A] Quit running,
damn it! Get back here!
[OUTLAW 1B]
We're not done with you!
[FAVARO laughs]
[TOWN MAN 1A yelps]
You coward.
Sayonara.
[TOWN WOMEN gasp]
[grunts]
Uh... Heh, heh.
--[whip cracks]
--[horse neighs]
[KAISAR grunts]
Whoa, don't do that!
Not funny, man,
I could get hurt!
Yep, one of those days.
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
Oh! Hey, Kaisar,
welcome aboard!
Steering sucks,
but I love the view!
[TAVERN GIRLS groan, whimper]
[OUTLAW 1A]
You girls are coming with us.
[KAISAR, FAVARO grunting]
[FAVARO]
Oh! Nice! Thank you!
Huh. Here ya go sweetie,
from my heart to your lips!
[KAISAR grunts]
Your jokes will not save you.
[FAVARO] Aw, now you're
just playin' hard to get.
Silence, Favaro! All you
speak is nonsense and lies!
Your attitude's all wrong.
See, that's your weakness.
[grunts]
So focused on one thing.
Ya can't see the
bigger picture.
[groans]
[sighs] Including what's
right behind you.
Oh, well, your loss.
[TAVERN GIRL 1A]
No! Let go of me!
[TAVERN GIRL 1B]
Help!
[OUTLAW 1B] Shut up,
no one's gonna save ya.
[OUTLAW 1C]
Huh? Look! What is that?
[FAVARO] Oh crap, oh crap.
Yep this is happening.
[FAVARO screams]
Don't like this!
[FAVARO groans]
[OUTLAW 1A]
Hey! Who the hell are you?
You come to save them wenches?
They're gone!
You idiot! How'd you
let them get away!
[FAVARO] Sorry, guys,
did I scare off your dates?
[OUTLAW 1A]
That bracelet!
[FAVARO]
Huh? Oh, this old thing?
[OUTLAW 1A]
He's a bounty hunter!
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[OUTLAWS yelp]
[OUTLAW 1A] Now there's
a prince on a white horse?
I think we nabbed
the wrong girls.
That's no prince!
That's a bounty hunter, too!
[gasps]
--[FAVARO] Huh?
--[OUTLAWS grunt]
Stop!
[OUTLAWS]
Uh...
--[FAVARO] Outta the way!
--[TAVERN PATRONS gasping]
[FAVARO] Who brings
a horse into a tavern?
Y'know you're losing
those bounties
--while you're chasing me!
--[KAISAR] Silence, dog!
You dare talk to me
about bounty hunting,
when you're the only reason
I was forced into this
wretched life to begin with!
Right. Pin it all
on me. Real mature!
[neighs]
[TAVERN PATRONS gasp]
Wait! You are deplorable!
[growls]
[FAVARO]
Eh.
[KAISAR] Come back!
Barina Shuttle Lidfard!
Heh. Poor guy. He needs
some friends.
Uh-- Ah!
Ah!
Now that is the good stuff.
Hey!
Don't worry about
your place, buddy,
I'll take care of it.
Frowny guy's bounty'll
cover the repairs.
And my large tab.
Are ya serious?
Always.
[OUTLAW 1A]
It ain't good, boys.
If we go back empty handed,
after taking the
horses out all day...
[OUTLAWS]
Sir Garth will kill us!
--[horses neigh]
--[OUTLAWS yell]
[OUTLAWS groan]
Did the wagon hit somethin'?
[OUTLAW 1A]
Look! What's that?
It's a woman!
[OUTLAW 1A] Who are you?
How'd you get up there?
And why are you naked?
[OUTLAW 1B]
Did you fall from the sky?
[OUTLAW 1C] You idiot, since
when do girls fall from the sky?
[OUTLAW 1B]
Don't you call me an idiot!
[OUTLAW 1A]
Hey! You gonna answer me?
[AMIRA] The compass is broken.
I can't find Helheim.
[OUTLAW 1A] What's she
talking about? Ah, who cares!
Boss's gift just
fell in our laps.
Yeah, but I'm thinking she can
fall into our laps first.
[OUTLAWS cackle]
[AMIRA grunts]
[GARTH]
I want my girls! Now!
[OUTLAW 1D]
Boss, I heard a bounty hunter
was in town this mornin',
causin' all kinds of trouble.
So, I'm thinkin'--
[GARTH growls]
[OUTLAWS whimper]
[GARTH] You're gonna bring that
damn bounty hunter to me.
[FAVARO] I'll save you
the trouble, boys!
[OUTLAWS gasp]
The damn bounty hunter
just brought himself.
[GARTH] He thinks he's funny.
Tear 'im apart.
Bastard!
[FAVARO, OUTLAWS grunting]
[OUTLAW 1E]
Where'd he go?
[OUTLAW 1F]
Huh?
[GARTH]
Look down!
Huh?
[FAVARO]
One. Two. Three.
[FAVARO groans]
[GARTH]
Not bad, hunter.
[FAVARO]
Huh?
Shabale Seta Ruge.
[FAVARO gasps]
A Summoning Spell, huh?
Well, in that case.
[FAVARO yelps]
After him!
[MONSTERS roar]
What happened to--
[coughs] Blasted dust.
I said what happened to your
jokes and bravado now,
bounty hunter?
I dunno!
But here's an even
better question.
Where'd that big puddle
come from, I don't remember
it raining today, do you?
Who the hell cares?
Burn him to a crisp!
What? But how?
[FAVARO]
Oh! Wait! Now! Now I remember!
The plants out here
looked dry but I didn't
have any water, so I gave
'em some alcohol instead.
You bastard! So you knew
about their skill?
About their fire attack?
Yup!
Now here's some advice,
free of charge.
Don't have a blabber-mouth
for a pet.
[grunts, growls]
Damn you!
[yelps]
[GARTH groans]
Miserable scoundrel.
Well, that's not very nice.
It's not my fault you're clumsy.
Seel Soh Cetom.
Heh. And that makes 20!
[BACCHUS snoring]
Wow.
I'm surprised.
[HAMSA] Hey, Bacchus!
Wake up, ya drunk!
We've got a visitor!
Huh? Get off
my back, would ya?
Don't you know who
you're talkin' to?
The god of booze hounds, right?
Maybe you should think about
cutting back a little, chief.
It cannot be good
for your health.
[FAVARO sighs] Always freaks
me out how much bigger it is
on the inside.
Don't come bargin'
in just to complain!
[FAVARO]
Here you go. Prey of the day!
[BACCHUS]
Hm?
All right, Puff Ball Head.
Eight hundred Rupies.
[FAVARO]
Would you stop calling me that?
And why are you only
giving me half the reward?
Those posters said "1600,"
and yes I can read!
Shut your hole, human,
don't you know who--
Are you gonna puke?
Careful. It's a fancy couch.
[FAVARO]
Hup, uh--
[BACCHUS groans]
Are you kidding me?
It's my policy to spend
every Rupie I make
before the next morning.
It's the only way to live!
[TAVERN GIRLS giggle]
So! Let's drink the
house down, girls!
And don't expect to get
any sleep tonight!
You must be strong
to capture them.
Yeah, I guess. Today was
a milestone for me.
My 200th bounty.
[TAVERN GIRL 1C]
That's amazing!
So. You must've faced
all sorts of danger.
I've battled things
that would make
a pretty lady like you cry.
Exciting, right?
I bet you've seen
beautiful cities, too.
Not as beautiful as
the girls inside them.
Girls like you.
[TAVERN GIRL 1C]
All you talk about is women.
[FAVARO]
That's right!
Women are the best gods
and worst demons, too!
I won't stop 'til I've
drunk with 'em all!
That's why I'm going
back to Helheim!
--[AMIRA gasps]
--[TAVERN GIRL 1A] Where?
[FAVARO]
Helheim, my next stop!
Oh, is that a place?
Well, yeah. You never
heard of it?
I've heard of it.
Heard it's covered in
snow and ice so cold,
it can freeze ya
where ya stand.
Yeah, that's right!
It's not for the weak!
That's if you can even survive
the journey, of course--
I can't tell ya how many
warriors and bounty hunters
have lost their lives just
tryin' to get there!
[TAVERN GIRLS]
Scary!
It's really no problem
for me, though.
I'll get there fine!
'Cause I know
a special shortcut!
A Helheim shortcut?
That's perfect.
[KAISAR grunts]
[KAISAR]
Forgive me.
Hm. Unusual design.
Are you a foreigner?
Well, if you're lost,
it would be my honor
to show you around.
Thanks, but there's no need.
I've chosen my guide.
[gasps]
[FAVARO laughing]
[KAISAR growls]
Hey, pal. Took ya long enough.
Ladies, meet Pompadorable.
D'ya find your horse?
My name is Kaisar!
[FAVARO] Ah... I'll take
that freak-out as a "no."
Too bad, I hear
he's a good horse.
[KAISAR]
Yes.
Barina Shuttle Lidfard
is a great horse.
He was all that remained
of my family fortune.
Now you've robbed
me of him, too!
[TAVERN GIRLS gasp]
[KAISAR grunts]
I'll kill you!
Aw, relax, would ya?
Life's too short for this
grudge crap. Everyone!
This guy's way more rich and
loose with his coins than me.
Cozy up to barret
head and you'll be
--drinkin' for free all night!
--[KAISAR] Wait, what?
[TAVERN GIRL 1C]
Hey, handsome.
[TAVERN GIRL 1B]
Hey, cutie.
You should come
have a drink with us.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Oh. Just look at
that strong chin. Ah.
You must be a knight,
I can tell.
They're always the sexy ones.
You ladies are far too kind.
[TAVERN GIRLS sigh]
[TAVERN GIRL 1A] Can I
play with your barrettes?
[TAVERN GIRL 1B]
Can you show us your sword?
[TAVERN GIRL 1C]
I get to sit in his lap first!
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
Honestly. That guy
never gives up.
He's really gotta get
himself a new hobby.
Or a girl. Or three.
[AMIRA]
You there.
What the hell, man,
give me some space!
Can't you see
I'm tryin' to piss?
Hm?
Hold on, that is
definitely not a guy.
That's weird.
Why are you dressed up
like one, then?
You just into that kinda' thing?
Not a deal breaker, though.
So.
Is it true that you know
of a shortcut to Helheim?
What?
I heard you say
that at the tavern.
[FAVARO]
Ohhh. I get it.
She heard me spinning one
of my little stories, huh?
Please tell me.
I must get to Helheim.
Do you know the way? I'm lost.
[FAVARO] Okay...
How should I play this?
Keep making stuff up,
or run for it?
Are you listening to me?
[FAVARO]
Or I could...
Yep, that's it.
Oh, sure, I practically
blazed the trail.
But I can't tell ya
just 'cause you asked.
Nothin's free, dear.
Then what do you want?
That's a great question!
What I want is pretty
simple. It's love.
Love?
Yes. Romantic, right?
Love from a beautiful girl.
In one passionate kissy-kiss!
A kiss? From me?
[GHOS]
There you are!
[FAVARO growls]
The hell, man?
Things were just
starting to get good!
Seriously, Kaisar, you are
a monumental pain in the--
Uh. What?
[GHOS GIRL laughs]
Who're you?
The name's Ghos.
And you're gonna suffer
for what you did
to my kid brother, Garth!
Ghos? Kid brother? Hang on.
Oh, I get it!
So that's why Bacchus only
paid me half of the bounty!
Listen.
I don't have time for this,
just tell me the way to--
Hold your horses, honey.
I gotta take care of some
unfinished business here.
And then, we'll get
back to that kiss.
Fool! The only thing
you'll be kissing...
...is your ass goodbye!
[roars]
You're joking, right?
You think you can scare me
with that puny thing?
Your kid brother could
summon way better than...
Nevermind!
Tear him apart,
one limb at a time!
[FAVARO grunting]
You got some serious
power there, bud!
You should get work
as a castle crusher!
[FAVARO yelps]
[FAVARO grunts]
[FAVARO yells]
[MONSTER groans]
[FAVARO yelping]
[FAVARO grunts]
Big bastard.
[FAVARO]
My sword!
[FAVARO] Run, you idiot!
You'll get killed!
You can't be my guide
if you're dead.
[FAVARO]
Huh?
[AMIRA] Stay back and find
some cover. I'll handle this.
[gasps]
[growls]
The hell?
[gasps] She's a demon?
[MONSTER groans]
[GHOS]
Huh?
[gasps, groans]
Tch.
[GHOS groans]
You bastard. You fight dirty.
Making that mountain-sized
demon look tiny
at first was a way
dirtier trick, in my book.
So. You two come as a package?
[GHOS GIRLS gasp, scream]
Aw, come on, I haven't
done anything yet!
[FAVARO]
Ugh. That was close.
[FAVARO groans]
Spoke too soon.
[FAVARO pants]
A demon?
[FAVARO chuckles]
Seein' things.
This is where I realize
I have a drinking problem.
[gasps]
[FAVARO gasps]
[yelps]
[panting]
Jeez. Crazy dream.
Oh. You're finally up.
About time.
[FAVARO]
Where am I?
[TAVERN GIRL 1A]
You're in the tavern's attic.
Found you on the ground outside.
Hauling you up here was no
easy task, I'll have you know.
Don't you remember?
Huh...
Oh...
Heh. I guess I had too much
of that ale and blacked out.
Had some weird dreams, too.
Well, I ran a bath
for you, earlier.
You should splash water
on your face.
Yeah, thanks.
Maybe I'll wash the rest
of me while I'm at it.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[FAVARO] Not the reaction
I usually get, but uh.
Heh. I'll take it.
[TAVERN GIRL 1A]
That's... That's a tail!
[FAVARO]
Wow. Uh, thanks, I guess?
[screams] Demon!
Huh? A demon?
Where? Where?
Uh--
[FAVARO]
What the hell?
Hey, Kaisar, know what's bad?
[KAISAR]
What's bad?
[FAVARO] I've gotta read
the next episode title
and I don't think
there's enough time!
[KAISAR]
Well, you're wasting time, now!
[FAVARO]
Right!
Rage of Bahamut: Genesis:
Escape From Livian!
[KAISAR]
That wasn't hard at all.