Brace yourselves, humans.
The time for fun
and games is over.
More demons.
They want the God Key!
The angel Michael commanded
me to keep it safe.
Tell them our
defenses can't fail!
That's a lot of riders.
[FAVARO yelps]
Hey! Where've you been,
and why'd you sneak out?
Old man!
What?
I met the old man!
Look, that's pretty vague.
And it sounds creepy at night.
Hold on--old man? Are you
talking about a dad? Whose dad?
My dad, he's here!
I met him just now!
You're saying your father
is in the capital?
[sound of stomach rumbling]
I'm really hungry!
Tch! You can't just say
something crazy like that
and run off!
[SOLDIER 7A]
Lower the drawbridge!
You're late.
[LAVALLEY] I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
What's our strategy,
Saint Jeanne?
[JEANNE] You'll
defend the outer wall
with the sorcerer and catapult
divisions, Sir Gaurin.
Sir Lavalley, you'll
lead the dragon knights
against invaders
at the second wall.
I'll remain here, and protect
the castle with His Majesty.
[LAVALLEY and GAURIN]
Sir!
Move out!
[FAVARO]
Amira, where'd you go?
That girl needs a collar...
with a bell. Eh?
[FAVARO groans]
Found him.
Favaro.
[FAVARO]
Great, we're all here.
Um, where's Lady Amira? Hm?
Oh, good. Did she
say what happened?
[FAVARO] Well, according
to her, she met her father.
And now she's all hyped up.
What, her father?
In the castle?
[RITA] So it's a
celebration meal?
There, you satisfied now?
[AMIRA sighs]
[AMIRA hiccups]
[AMIRA giggles]
[FAVARO] How big
is your stomach?
[GIANT GHOUL roars]
Don't give up!
We must stop the demon
invasion, no matter what!
Don't tell me...
Archers release!
Meddlesome flies.
Decent work. Seems she
poses the only real threat.
[PAZUZU]
Leave her to me.
Just don't botch it up.
[PAZUZU]
Hm.
Get out of our city!
[JEANNE]
The bridge!
[PAZUZU] Compared to us, you're
little more than pond scum.
It's time for you to learn
exactly how trivial
your human powers are.
[AMIRA] I don't wanna, I don't
wanna, I don't wanna!
I'm not done eating--let go!
You already ate enough
for ten people, come on!
Lady Amira,
the city's under attack!
We need to make
sure you're safe!
[all three yell]
Man! Ow! What the hell?
She really is like a little kid.
I doubt she's even aware
of the situation she's in.
[FAVARO]
Hm?
You saw how worried those
angels were about her safety.
We must prevent the
revival of Bahamut,
no matter what the costs.
Keep the God Key safe.
It's up to you, o valiant ones!
[RITA] Clearly these
demons have come for her.
Clearly.
So, what should we do?
I'm not sure.
But for now, let's try to move
her to a better hiding place.
Too late for that.
[FAVARO and KAISAR gasp]
It's you again!
[FAVARO] It was him.
Now I'm sure of it.
There's no need
to struggle.
Just be good little humans
and hand over the God Key.
Not a chance!
[AZAZEL] Oh, dear, is that
your "chivalry" talking?
Noble to a fault,
just like your father was.
You still haven't explained
how you knew my father.
And what if I told you
I was the reason
he was sent to the gallows?
[FAVARO gasps]
[AZAZEL]
Oh, I remember it well.
[indistinct distant screaming]
[AZAZEL] The vicious jeers the
people showered on your father.
That delicious fire
in their eyes...
That contempt in their voices!
"Let that pathetic
knight swing till dead!"
If I could bottle that malice,
I would drink it all day.
You arranged it? Why?
Those gemstones were
toys of mine, actually.
When I planned it,
I thought Amon's betrayal
would be the best part.
Those villagers...
They made your
father's death so fun.
I'll never forget those shouts.
[KAISAR shudders]
[FAVARO] You got a real gift
for storytelling, wing-boy,
but let's get
the facts straight.
The bastard who got
his old man killed...
That bastard
is right here.
Am I supposed to laugh?
What are you doing?
He just said...
Listen, Kaisar, I've got
a little mission for you.
Take Amira and run for it.
I'm leaving it to you to
get her safely to Helheim.
Go on, get out. This is a
battle between two demons now.
--He'll kill you!
--[RITA] Hey.
Do what he says.
Between two demons,
you say? How interesting.
[FAVARO grunts]
Seize the God Key, darlings.
Hey! Come on, that's cheating!
I am a demon, aren't I?
[PAZUZU]
What's the matter?
Is the human's heralded
warrior already done?
[JEANNE]
Ngh!
[JEANNE grunts softly]
[PAZUZU] Fighting you is beneath
me, but it's almost over.
This is the end of your baseless
bravado. This is when you die!
[SOLDIER 7F]
Saint Jeanne!
[PAZUZU]
Barely a fight.
Come! Maltet!
[PAZUZU]
Impossible!
[JEANNE yells]
[PAZUZU groans]
Now tremble before
my sacred power,
you abomination of
darkness and impurity!
[SOLDIER 7G]
She got him!
[PAZUZU laughs]
Does your death amuse you?
[PAZUZU] I wouldn't count this
as a victory if I were you.
We'll get what we came for.
The God Key!
Saint Jeanne.
Lavalley.
Are you injured?
It's fine, I'll live. The only
thing that matters is the girl.
Yes, captain, understood.
[FAVARO pants, grunts]
[FAVARO]
A... Ah!
Aw, great! A fork's
not gonna work here!
For a moment I thought
you'd actually challenge me.
But since you're so
disappointing,
I guess I'll just
take the Key now.
Kaisar!
[KAISAR] I swiped one
of your bombs earlier.
Thought I'd use it on you.
Guess even knights can get
a case of the sticky fingers.
So where's Amira?
In good hands.
[moaning and roaring]
[FAVARO] Not that
I'm ungrateful,
but why'd you come back?
[KAISAR]
For revenge, Favaro.
[FAVARO]
Uh-- Uh...
Can't let this demon kill you.
Or I'd never have
my vengeance for what you
did to my father, would I?
[AZAZEL laughs]
Oh, Favaro, that's right!
You're that thief Barossa's
son--I almost forgot!
This is almost too
hilarious for words!
Your little dynamic is
starting to make sense.
So you took on this
role of "sworn enemy"
to give him a reason to live!
What?
Only humans can
manage such touching
and melodramatic nonsense.
That's why I like to come here.
You could say it's
my guilty pleasure.
This makes me feels proud.
I'm responsible for
both your father's deaths
and you've been fighting
for years because of me!
Very well, we can
play for a little bit.
I am busy, but this theater
is too good to resist!
You got a screwy
view of things, pal.
My old man's dead because he
messed up, simple as that.
Avenging him, giving
Kaisar a reason to live--
I don't give a damn about that.
I don't live for some ideal.
I'm not wasting my time
trying to fix an old wrong or
make somebody else feel happier.
[FAVARO] I live for myself.
And that's it.
Favaro.
[FAVARO] You're not
my arch-enemy.
You're not my anything.
You're just a stupid demon
who happens to be in my way.
You'll pay for
that disrespect.
I suppose that's what
makes us so different.
I have my way of seeing
the world and you have yours.
Well I'll give him one thing--
he's right about
you being dramatic.
I can't change how I am.
Yeah, I know.
Yet another
desperate smoke screen.
[AZAZEL]
Nice try.
You okay, Kaisar?
Perhaps you should be
more worried about yourself.
Now you die.
You know what?
I'm finally learning
how to use this thing.
You have a tail?
It's like I told you.
This is a fight between demons.
[FAVARO]
Boogedy boogedy boogedy...
Don't let a measly contract
spell go to your head.
[KAISAR]
No.
This is a battle between
human and demon!
Two humans and a
demon, to be exact!
[KAISAR yells]
[AZAZEL groans]
Did that kill him?
Just kidding.
[KAISAR and FAVARO gasp]
[AZAZEL] So sorry
to disappoint you,
but I can't be killed
with human steel.
[FAVARO snarls]
[AZAZEL] Seems that
overgrown flying cat
has failed me;
how disappointing.
No matter. I'll simply
have to kill you both now
and finish this myself.
Son of a bitch.
Gotta be somethin' we can
do to kill this jerkoff.
[KAISAR]
I'm changing the plan.
[FAVARO]
Huh?
[KAISAR] You take her
to Helheim, Favaro.
I'll take care of him.
[KAISAR yells]
Get ready to
join your father.
[KAISAR grunts]
[KAISAR grunts, yells]
[FAVARO gasps]
[FAVARO]
Kaisar!
The shortcomings
of my own kind
are what caused
my father's death.
You're not his killer.
You're a coward
whispering from the shadows.
A little demon in the dark.
And now, you'll meet the light.
[AZAZEL screams]
[AZAZEL groans]
Miserable humans!
[AZAZEL screams]
[JEANNE exhales]
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Your Majesty,
the demons are defeated!
We must give
thanks to the gods.
We did it, Saint Jeanne.
Good work.
Those two bounty hunters we
captured with the girl...
Tell me their names again?
[FAVARO groans heavily]
Favaro...?
Can you hurry up and
climb, you dumbass?!
I'm about to split
in friggin' two!
[FAVARO yelps and whimpers]
[KAISAR] Right.
[LAVALLEY] Amira.
You need to wake up.
[AMIRA] Father?
Is that you?
Finally.
It's over. Now let's
get you back to your...
Perfect.
[AMIRA] Father? Father?
Where'd you go?
--[BACCHUS] Admit it!
--[HAMSA] What?
[BACCHUS]
You're a damn duck!
--[HAMSA] I am not a duck!
--[BACCHUS] Nonsense!
[HAMSA] What if
I talk like this:
On the next Rage of Bahamut:
Genesis: Beyond the Storm.
--[BACCHUS] Still a duck.
--[HAMSA] Drunk.