These look so tasty...
Hey. Keep up, would ya?
I thought you were in a rush.
I am.
And you never said
anything about us
having to sail to
get to Helheim.
Ah! Yeah, well... uhhh...
[FAVARO]
Did I just hear you right?
You sure did, they've got
some killer booze there!
No! Not that part!
[HAMSA]
Stop it!
I mean the route!
Do you really know
how to get there?
'Course I know the way.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
A "G-O-D" God.
[sighs]
And you're a dumbass.
Because I just remembered
an even shorter shortcut,
that's all!
All we need to do
is get on the boat,
and then we'll be in
Helheim in no time!
[FAVARO]
I know that death stare.
You still don't trust me.
Look in these eyes and you tell
me they're the eyes of a liar.
Ow!
A merchant ship
going to Helheim?
Not that I know of.
What's a Helheim?
If it tastes good, I'll try it.
--How would I know?
--Don't ask me!
Which boat?
Keep your hair on,
I've got this under control!
It prob'ly just
hasn't sailed in yet!
[growls]
[FAVARO] Bacchus,
you lousy drunk.
Did you give me a bogus tip?
[gasps]
I love seafood.
[FAVARO]
Great...
If I don't come up with
something quick,
she's gonna know I've been
lying to her this whole time!
[YOGI] Did I hear you
need passage to Helheim?
The boat's right over there.
Uh... Oh, of course!
Silly me, I remember!
It's right over there, yeah!
What a relief.
[AZAZEL]
They lost them?
[CERBERUS] They followed the
trail all the way to Nebelville,
that's worth something, right?
Then their scent
just vanished, ARF!
It's strange, ARF!
[PAZUZU]
That's what you get for relying
on those glorified mittens.
[MALE DOG]
He's talking trash, ARF!
[FEMALE DOG]
He is trash, you're right, ARF!
[PAZUZU]
What?!
[BOTH squeal]
[AZAZEL]
That's enough, children.
Someone must have intervened
to help cover their tracks.
It could have been the gods.
Or one of their human pets.
Or perhaps it was a demon.
[PAZUZU] You think someone
could be making a move
against Lord Lucifer?
It is possible.
With dear old Satan
out of the picture,
the God Key could be a big deal.
Maybe someone wants to use it
put their butt on the throne!
Send down your dogs to
resume their search.
You look, too, Pazuzu.
We will find her.
And then we'll learn
exactly what she's planning.
Oh yeah, here we go!
This is the boat
to Helheim, I knew it!
That's reassuring...
The Celephales. Yes.
And that's her captain.
The one with the beard.
[FAVARO]
Hmm...?
[CAPTAIN]
Hm?
[FAVARO growls]
[CAPTAIN]
Hmmm...?
[gasps]
[yells]
[BOTH laugh]
Amon! You bastard,
you're alive?!
[AMON]
Hey, that's my line!
What in the hell, Favaro?!
What are you doing
in these parts?!
[AMON grunts]
[FAVARO growls]
Who's that? Is that your mother?
--Of course he's not!
--Of course I'm not!
Been three years, huh?
What're you up to these days?
So you're not following in
your old man's footsteps?
'Cause that's what Barossa
would've wanted for you.
Yeah, well, too bad.
[FAVARO]
I was never into the whole
leader of the "honorable,
merry bandits" career path.
"Rob from the rich,
to give to the poor?"
Sorry, but that's
not really my thing.
I like being in
business for myself,
it keeps life simple
and doesn't cramp my style.
Well, then who's your friend?
Dragging a young girl
around while bounty hunting
doesn't sound simple to me.
[FAVARO]
True.
But I kind of just
fell into it, you know?
[KAISAR]
Have you seen this miscreant?
Yeah, I have, actually.
Looking for a boat.
[growls]
A boat to where?!
[MAN A]
Uh, I forget.
But he's probably
long gone by now.
Well, that's a shame.
Sounds like we
got here too late.
[KAISAR growls]
[KAISAR]
Why are you following me?
[RITA]
To pass the time.
[KAISAR growls]
I'm just kidding.
I was alone in that
village so long--
you can't know what that's like.
There's nothing left for me
there, and you seem nice enough.
So what will you do?
[growls]
Whatever it takes!
I don't care if it takes me
to the far edge of the world!
I'll hunt him down.
I swear it!
For it to matter that much
you must really hate him a lot.
How come?
It's a long... story.
[YOGI]
Pardon me, Sir.
I think I can help you.
For a... fee.
[FAVARO grunts softly]
[snarling]
[roars]
[gasps]
Enough with that dream.
[squeals]
You don't look tasty.
[FAVARO] Hey you, Miss
Catch-and-Release-Fisherman.
Does This creature
look familiar to you?
[AMIRA]
A duck?
[FAVARO]
Tch! What?! No!
It's like huge,
and scaley, you know?
[AMIRA]
An alligator.
Aw. Come on, no!
It's way bigger!
Like, like the size
of a mountain!
And it breathes fire, and it can
burn whole cities to a crisp!
[sighs]
It doesn't look tasty.
Honestly, how hungry
is this girl?
[AMON]
Favaro.
How 'bout we knock one
back together?
I got some food in there, too.
--[gasps]
--Yeah, sure!
As luck would have it,
I am feeling parched.
Hey, slow down!
He asked me!
You were going to say something
about that nemesis of yours?
For an undead girl,
you're certainly curious.
[KAISAR]
Whoa! [yells]
Okay, fine!
Favaro and I were
childhood friends.
[growls]
[AMON]
What do you remember?
About that final heist
we did with Barossa?
Stealing that hefty
tribute to the king.
And all that followed.
I belonged to a
family of knights.
His family were carpenters.
Despite the difference
in our classes,
we got along very well together.
We saw each other
almost every single day.
[KAISAR] I told him everything,
including about my father,
because I... thought
we were best friends.
That snake!
[HORSES whinny]
He used me.
Deceived me for all those years.
His father was
actually a thief.
And he'd just been waiting
to get information from me!
I failed.
He used me to
sabotage my father.
He ruined our lives!
That night.
My old man was
killed on the road.
[AMON] Part of the tribute was
a case of strange gemstones,
containing powerful magic,
and just by handling
the damn things,
we summoned a horrible demon.
[gasps]
[thunder cracks]
[AMON] Our whole raiding party
was slaughtered in minutes.
I was the only one
who made it out alive.
It was your old man who saved
my life, that heroic bastard.
[FAVARO]
Hmph.
Favaro.
I'm gonna get you to Helheim;
it's the least I can do
to repay my debt.
[FAVARO]
Thanks, Amon.
[AMIRA]
Who's this "old man?"
[FAVARO]
What old man?
That wrinkly guy
back at the port?
Not him!
The one you were talking
about in your story!
[FAVARO] Oh. That's what
I call my father.
Your father?
Yeah, my freaking
father, okay?!
You got one, right?
I'm not sure.
What is a father, exactly?
Now how the hell
do I answer that one?
You know, it's just
your parent who's a guy!
It's your dad, your pops,
your mom's husband!
[AMIRA]
Husband?
What's that?
Okay...
You're just messing
with me, aren't you?
My old man. My husband.
Oh boy. No, not
your husband, your mom's!
My father...
[yelps
What's that?!
[gasps]
[SEPER] Sorry to interrupt
this heart-to-heart.
But it's time you went
for a little dip in the sea.
What are you talking about?
[SEPER] Hand over your
valuables before you jump.
And we'll take the girl.
She'll fetch an even higher
price than your sword.
So you're pirates?
I should've known.
You'll regret this.
You can carry on that
tough guy act all you want--
from the bottom of
the sea floor.
[yells]
[grunting, yelling]
You bastard! Yaah!
[grunts]
[SEPER]
Nice moves, Bounty Hunter.
But that's enough.
Throw down your sword.
[KAISAR growls]
[SEPER]
Sorry to break it to you, pal,
but your luck has
finally run out.
[KAISAR] It seems like
you're the unlucky one.
If you ask me.
Huh?
[snarls]
Whoa!
Giant freaking crab!
Oh, delicious!
[FAVARO] Huh?! I mean it
does have nice color to it,
but it's also tryin' to kill us!
[AMON]
It's called the Shipwrecker!
They say it's sunk
countless vessels!
[FAVARO]
We've gotta fight it!
Where are your weapons?!
[AMON]
We don't have weapons!
--She's a damn cargo ship!
--[FAVARO] Oh, right!
[gasps]
Oh, come on!
[FAVARO screams]
[DOGS barking]
[CERBERUS]
Look what we found!
[retches]
It's not tasty...
Oh. Good to know.
What in the hell was that?!
[FAVARO]
Huh? Oh, it was nothing!
Uh...
Or it was something
but not a bad something,
it's just kinda hard to explain.
[AMON] Does it have anything
to do with that tail?
[FAVARO]
What?
[gasps]
Uh, I can explain that, too.
It's not really a tail, see?
I mean it is, but, heh--
Well, color me surprised.
So you've been dancing
with demons, too.
[gasps]
[AMON]
Surround them!
[FISH FIGHTERS howl]
[whimpers]
[AMON] You stay right
where you are, little lady.
Amon! You dirtbag!
[AMON]
Had myself a career change.
I went from being a thief.
To a demon's ward!
[AMON laughs]
[AMON] It was all
planned from the start.
Lidfard's execution
for failing to protect
all of that beautiful treasure.
And the slaughtering of
Barossa and his men
by a mysterious
demon on the road.
That same demon
granted me magic powers.
I arranged the
whole thing for him!
Their blood was the price I paid
and it was worth
every last drop!
You betrayed my old man?
Got him killed?
I'm not cut out to be an
honorable bandit either, boy.
You're dad was always
such a goodie-goodie
when I just wanted to get rich.
It was suffocating,
just being around the guy.
So, anyway, imagine
how surprised I was
when I heard you were at
the port, looking for a ride.
Now I get to profit off
the father and the son!
[gasps]
Of course you're really
more like the appetizer.
In terms of bounty,
the girl's definitely
the main course.
Who is this million-Rupie girl?
I don't know who she is,
I just met her, okay?
[AMON] Fine. Then there's
no reason to keep you alive.
[FISH FIGHTERS blubber]
No! Run, Favaro!
Get out of here!
And how would I run?
I'm tied up,
surrounded by fish people!
[grunts]
[KAISAR] You can control zombies
without your spell book?
Unfortunately for my victims,
I have more than
one tool for the job.
But you're a zombie
yourself now.
Why aren't you
mindless like them?
[RITA]
You should hold on tight.
[KAISAR yells]
[AMON coughs]
That damn kid!
Where the hell did he go?!
[AMON]
Don't let 'em escape! Move!
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[KAISAR grunts]
Where is that demon?!
Favaro!
[FAVARO]
Kaisar?
Wait. You?
Aren't you Lidfard's son?!
I am. Who are you?!
So you're a
bounty hunter, too, now?
Well, hands off!
Those two are mine!
[FISH FIGHTERS blubber]
--[ZOMBIES groan]
--[FISH FIGHTERS chatter]
[FAVARO]
Well, this is a first.
Who knew zombies liked fish?
[SEPER groans]
[AMON]
Favaro!
I will be taking the girl!
This guy's mine.
[yells]
Know what your dad...
hated... the most?!
He hated rich guys and
the people in charge.
And demons!
And that's why he refused
to learn about magic,
despite its power!
It's because of
that stubbornness
that he wound up dead!
--[gasps]
--[AMON chuckles]
[AMON] And now you're
going to join him!
[FAVARO grunts]
[FAVARO]
Would you be careful?!
I could've died, man!
Hah! It's over now, Favaro.
Curse your bad luck.
The same way that Barossa did
that night on the road.
You're the one
with the bad luck.
You ran into me!
[AMON grunts]
[AMON screams]
[AMON]
What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
[AMON screams]
[FAVARO]
So long, you bastard.
[TOWNSPEOPLE]
[YOGI giggles] Managed to con
four suckers by sundown.
Must've been my lucky day!
[YOGI grunts]
Hey! Watch it, you--
[grunts]
[BACCHUS] Hamsa. Did I just
hear you say something?
[BACCHUS]
We gave 'em a lift here
so they wouldn't
attract attention.
--But now listen.
--[WOMAN A shrieks] Demons!
[MAN C] Fish-people!
Washed up on the shore!
[HAMSA groans]
[BACCHUS]
Sounds like we wasted our time.
[thunder rumbles]
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[KAISAR grunting]
Great.
[KAISAR]
En garde, Demon!
We settle this
once and for all!
Oh, come on.
Are you sure I can't
get a rain check?
[thunder cracks]
--[gasps]
--[growls]
[gasps]
Whoa... What the hell's that?
Come to me, girl.
[KAISAR]
Lady Amira, watch out!
[BOTH scream]
Amira! Kaisar!
[CERBERUS] Well, looks like
we have an extra guest.
Ooh, can we kill him?! ARF!
Barbecue him, ARF!
[AZAZEL]
No.
[ALL gasp]
[AZAZEL] This will allow
for an even better show.
[FAVARO]
You're plotting something.
--[KAISAR] No, I'm not!
--[FAVARO] Don't play dumb.
You wanna read
this preview solo!
[KAISAR]
Hmph, nonsense!
On the next Rage of Bahumut:
Genesis: Rescue in Sword Valley!
--[FAVARO] Happy now?
--[KAISAR] Very!