[gasps]
Well, shall we be
going, my lord?
[gasps]
Let her go!
[KAISAR groans]
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
Michael!
Don't lose focus!
But, this means.
I know what it means.
The moment we feared has come.
The Transcendent Key
has been formed.
[BACCHUS] Beezlebub? He's a
high-ranking demon, right?
In charge of overseeing Helheim?
He was the one pulling the
girl's strings from the start.
[RITA] But this has been
too big of a puppet show.
He must've had some help.
[AZAZEL] His lackey,
Martinet, has been helping.
Ah? Martinet?
What an elegant name,
I bet she's a cute one!
[AZAZEL]
She's a he.
[HAMSA groans]
You think that could be
another name he uses?
[BACCHUS]
You mean that bounty guy?
It's possible, I guess.
If anyone can turn
humans into demons,
I'd say he'd have the best shot.
[RITA] Or maybe he's not a
demon, he's just posing as one.
After all, if a little zombie
girl from nowhere-ville
can figure out his spells, how
sophisticated can he really be?
We should hurry.
I don't think saving existence
is the sort of thing
you should be late for.
[HAMSA squaks]
[MICHAEL]
No need to despair!
The key must make contact
with Bahamut for it to work!
As long as we maintain
this barrier, we'll prevail!
Jeanne D'Arc?
[MICHAEL gasps]
[RAPHAEL gasps]
[URIEL, MICHAEL]
Raphael!
But why? How could
Jeanne do that?
No. That isn't Jeanne.
Or rather, it is and it isn't.
Her soul is in there,
but she's changed.
She's overflowing
with demonic energy.
[URIEL]
But how did this happen?
Uriel! She's coming your way!
[URIEL gasps]
[URIEL grunts]
[grunts] I can't
keep fighting her off!
No!
[grunts]
[URIEL gasps]
It's breaking!
[gasps]
Well, that was certainly close.
[KAISAR yelps]
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[KAISAR gasps]
[KAISAR grunts]
What? That's Abos.
[KAISAR yelps]
I have what you
need, Bahamut.
The key to your
awakening is here!
[KAISAR grunting]
[yells]
Favaro! You can't be a demon!
You can't have stooped that low!
Are you really going to let
those worthless monsters
conquer your spirit
with a lousy spell?
What about Lady Amira?
What about changing our fate?
[growls] Say something!
Favaro!
That's Kaisar!
[KAISAR grunts]
Damn kid, it's a
good thing we came.
Thanks, Bacchus.
Fair warning.
We're a bit over
capacity right now.
[KAISAR grunts]
[BACCHUS, KAISAR gasp]
[KAISAR]
That's the angel, Michael!
Who's that with him?
[KAISAR]
Saint Jeanne?
But why does she
look like that?
She's not a saint now.
She's been turned into
a demon through sorcery.
[KAISAR gasps]
Not her, too.
That's what happened to Favaro.
Oh, crap. Hey guys?
We've been spotted.
The moment of
judgment has come.
[BACCHUS]
Hamsa!
Huh?
Can't we do something?
[AZAZEL]
The Lidfard boy?
How in the world
are you still alive?
[KAISAR]
Azazel! What are you doing here?
I'd love to stay here and chat
while I methodically
slice you into pieces.
Sadly, I have a prior
engagement up there.
It's tragic, being too
busy to crush a bug.
Fine then.
If you can stomach
leaving things this way,
well that's your choice.
What does that mean?
If you run off now,
that makes your loss
to us permanent.
First, you pitiful
humans never beat me,
I simply regrouped.
And the next time we meet--
[KAISAR]
If there is a next time.
The world's on the
brink of destruction.
We may never cross paths again.
You insufferable man.
If the world does end, I hope
you're the first to go.
[RITA]
Hold onto one of these.
[RITA] If you can get it into
your old pal's bloodstream--
[KAISAR, RITA gasp]
--[HAMSA yells]
--[KAISAR screams]
--[RITA] You stupid duck!
--[HAMSA groaning]
I'm getting tired of this.
That makes three
falls in one day.
I've changed my mind.
I am going to give you the
ending that I think you deserve.
Are you ready for it?
Do your worst. I'm not afraid.
[KAISAR groans]
Well, I'm definitely
going to be sore tomorrow.
If I'm still alive.
[RITA] My last antidote.
Better make it count.
[yells]
Now or never!
[HAMSA screams]
[sighs] I guess it's never.
Well, I'll have you
for my last meal, duck.
Roasted in olive oil and garlic.
[BACCHUS] Throw in some booze
and that'd be a decent meal.
[HAMSA growls]
[JEANNE grunts]
[RITA screams]
[HAMSA yelps]
[JEANNE grunts]
[gasps]
--[MICHAEL grunts]
--[JEANNE gasps]
[JEANNE grunts]
Is that--?
[JEANNE grunting]
Forgive me, my holy maiden.
[gasps] What have I done?
It's all right, Jeanne.
This is our punishment.
For losing Zeus,
and for treating
humans as beneath us,
instead of working with
you as trusted partners
like we did 2,000 years ago.
We bear the blame for
these consequences, not you.
[JEANNE] I should have been
stronger! I failed you!
[MICHAEL]
No, Jeanne.
You are a strong and pious
maiden blessed by the gods.
You shall guide your
people in days to come.
Know this in your heart.
Though my physical
vessel may fade away,
my spirit will
always be with you.
You will not be
alone, my Jeanne.
Michael, no!
[BACCHUS] At least we don't have
to worry about her anymore.
Bacchus, look!
They're closin' in!
There's still time.
All right.
Just have to figure out
where to park the carriage.
[RITA] Actually, we're
not parking it at all.
--[BACCHUS] What?
--[HAMSA] Say what?
We're going to run it
right into those bastards.
They still think they
can make a difference.
Angels are such
a stubborn breed.
But it's time for them to go
and let the new age begin.
Beezlebub!
[AZAZEL]
You gave me some pretty bruises.
Now it's my turn!
[BEEZLEBUB] So you're in league
with the gods and humans now?
You are a fool to the
very core. Azazel.
[HAMSA squaking]
Great. You know what?
As a demon, you're
even more of a pain.
[gasps]
[BACCHUS]
You dumbass!
[HAMSA squaking]
A god riding a god --
I'm honored to be attracting
so much divine attention.
[BACCHUS] You and those
damned concoctions.
[KAISAR gasps]
[KAISAR] We've crossed swords
so many times in our lives.
We've been through
so much together.
I know you better than anyone,
and I can tell, Favaro.
By your moves alone.
You really have become a demon.
[KAISAR]
I do this for you, old friend.
Lady Amira.
[LAVALLEY]
Hello, Kaisar.
Lieutenant Lavalley.
What are you doing here?
The Orléans Knights
followed Jeanne to Abos,
and boarded this castle when
we saw they held the Key.
In a few more minutes,
we'll seize control of it
and that will be the
end of the threat.
So we're safe?
That's right.
You've served us well.
Take a look at what's happening.
[KAISAR] The gods!
They're all descending!
Everything's going to be fine.
Come on. Let's get
her back home.
[RITA] Don't trust him!
He's just buying time!
--Time for what?
--[rumbling]
[yelps]
--[RITA yelps]
--[roaring]
[KAISAR grunts
[KAISAR]
Lady Amira!
[KAISAR groans]
[screams]
Desperation is a powerful force
that can make a man very strong.
And when I take away what
they're desperate for,
it's the greatest
pleasure in the world!
Fava...