[SOLDIERS yelling]
Oh, it's you. Thank goodness.
[whimpers]
[CHARIOCE screams]
[RITA gasps]
[MARTINET chuckles]
[KAISAR] Favaro. Rita.
What have you done?
Royal Knights of Orléans!
If we fail to recapture
that girl. Our city--
No, the entire world
will be doomed!
Bring her back at all costs!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[LAVALLEY]
Sir Kaisar.
[KAISAR]
Lieutenant Lavalley.
I'm giving you a
squad to command.
Your mission: make sure you're
the one who finds Amira.
Me, sir? I've barely
broken in my armor.
[LAVALLEY]
Gaurin's been murdered.
--[gasps]
--Sh!
Your friends are not
the ones to blame.
I want to help them. But I must
stay and guard the king.
Take this with you.
Get to her before
the other squads do.
And help her
complete her journey.
But, sir...
Good luck.
[FAVARO yelling]
[gasps]
[FAVARO yells]
[FAVARO screams]
Hey. So you can
fly with one wing?
Not really.
[FAVARO, AMIRA scream]
[AMIRA humming]
--[ANIMALS shriek]
--[FAVARO gasps]
It's kinda spooky here, huh?
Not to me!
Why am I not surprised?
So, my mother...
[FAVARO] One day I'm
gonna make a decision
with my actual brain. I gotta
get outta this forest.
There's prob'ly at least a dozen
types of monsters
waitin' to gut me.
--This girl's bad for my health.
--Hey! Are you listening?!
Relax! Sure she'll know you!
How could she?
[sighs] One good hug and
she'll instantly know.
That's a Favaro guarantee.
[gasps]
--[AMIRA] Really?
--[FAVARO] Huh?
If I hug her, then she'll
know that it's me?
You're sure of that?
Of course! That's how moms are.
It's like their special power.
--[giggles] Like this?
--[FAVARO] Hey! Easy! Come on!
[MISTRESSES, CHARIOCE
whimpering]
[footsteps clacking]
Gaurin. What a tragic
fate to suffer.
How could my guards allow this?
[LAVALLEY] All dead.
Their throats were slit.
[whimpers]
[LAVALLEY grunts]
[LAVALLEY] There's something
in his hand. Is that hair?
[CHARIOCE]
Let me see.
It's blond! I knew it!
It must have been her!
That witch... tried to kill me!
[JEANNE]
This is madness!
I would never try to
hurt you, Your Majesty!
Silence, the proof
is right here!
This hair matches yours exactly!
Someone could've taken
it from my quarters!
That proves nothing!
Don't you try to fool me, woman!
You came to murder
me in my sleep!
But Gaurin discovered you,
so you killed him and fled!
I had nothing to do
with this, I swear!
You can save all of your
lies for your inquisition.
[JEANNE]
I demand to see Michael!
My guardian angel
will exonerate me!
Think again!
The three angels have
returned to the Heavens!
They have no time for you!
[gasps] That can't be.
[CHARIOCE] You've also allowed
the girl to escape the city!
With a failure this
profound, the angels
will soon forsake us completely!
You want to ruin me.
Any way you can!
It's all your fault!
You filthy, godless witch!
[FAVARO]
Something wrong?
[FAVARO yelps]
[blows land]
[FAVARO]
Huh?
There's still more.
Wh-Where?
[FAVARO]
Oh... Uh...
How'd they track
us down so fast?
Aw, come on!
Favaro! We're going
back to Anatae.
Don't make this hard.
[FAVARO]
Ugh. What's your problem?
Are your feelings hurt
'cause we left without you?
We have a perfectly good reason!
Yes. I'm sure you do!
[FAVARO, KAISAR grunting]
[gasps] What the hell,
man? Not cool!
This is only for show,
so just play along.
Huh?
Fava!
[SOLDIER 9A yells]
[SOLDIER 9B grunts]
[SOLDIER 9C grunts, groans]
The rest of you
stay back, he's mine!
Uh...
[FAVARO]
U-Uh, um, ah... Ha, ha...
Oh...
Ha, uh...
Stop! Don't kill him!
Yeah! Your boss has a good plan!
--[AMIRA grunts]
--[SOLDIER 9D groans]
No, no, no, let's not do that!
[FAVARO yelps]
[FAVARO grunts]
[KAISAR] That mark
on your-- It's glowing.
[SOLDIER 9E gasps]
[ARCHANGEL 9A yells]
[ARCHANGELS shouting]
They've lost the girl.
She's no longer in the capital.
We'll take over from here.
Get to Heaven as
quickly as you can.
Tell Gabriel to send
us reinforcements!
Understood.
[MICHAEL] The seal is becoming
too far out of balance.
Move quickly. O' maiden...
You must return
the girl to safety.
[MARTINET] Oh, you poor,
abused, little saint.
[JEANNE]
Who's there?
[MARTINET]
It breaks my heart.
The dutiful maiden,
abandoned by the gods.
You're less of a maiden now,
and more of a sacrificial lamb.
Or, should I echo the King?
And call you a powerful
dark witch, instead?
[JEANNE] I assume you're
the one who slew Gaurin?
[MARTINET]
Oh. What an ugly thing to say.
You treat me as your enemy
when I'm the only
one on your side.
I've gone to a lot of trouble
to get here and save your life.
You think I am a fool?
Quite the opposite.
I think you're wise enough to
know when you've been betrayed.
I am not betrayed.
I have been chosen,
as a halberd and
shield of the gods.
And as a Holy Knight,
I will have no regrets
in giving my life in
service of the Divine.
A Holy Knight, she says!
Is that how they've
tricked you into this?
Why, you're nothing of the sort!
So who exactly told you that
remarkable lie, I wonder?
It wasn't your beloved
guardian angel, Michael, was it?
[JEANNE whimpers]
[MARTINET] Wouldn't you
like to know the truth?
The truth the gods
are hiding from you
and all the other
pitiable sheep?
Drink this elixir.
It will lift the veil and show
you the world as it truly is.
I will not listen to the
filthy words of a demon!
[MARTINET] All right, all right.
No pressure, of course!
Unlike those puppeteer gods,
I respect you,
and I want you to make
your own decisions.
But let me leave you
with a little advice.
No matter how much you suffer,
no matter the depths
of your agony, or the
shrillness of your screams,
don't expect your "merciful"
guardian angel to save you.
Because he won't! He won't!
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[SOLDIER 9E]
What was that? Where'd they go?
What sort of place is this?
--[SOLDIER 9E] Retreat!
--[KAISAR] Wait!
[KAISAR] Can't you see me?
I'm right here! Help us!
Oh, great.
Well, that's hired
help for you, right?
Can't be trusted.
[FOREST DRAGON roars]
[FAVARO gasps]
[KAISAR]
What's that?
[FAVARO]
You got me.
[KAISAR grunting]
[chuckles]
[AMIRA grunting]
It won't budge.
[yawns]
Ha...
Okay, why not.
I don't even know why
we're doing this,
and there's no way
I can pull it ou--
Uh? I'll be damned.
Don't be sad, most people
are wimps compared to me.
Hey. What's wrong?
Now, don't get hostile.
That was only a joke.
You loosened it for--
[FAVARO coughs]
[FOREST DRAGON]
You have my thanks.
[FAVARO gasps]
[FAVARO yelps]
Dangit.
[FOREST DRAGON] I feel so much
better without that barb in me.
[FAVARO]
A barb?
[FOREST DRAGON]
It's been bothering me
for the last 2,000 years.
Who is this geezer?
You should probably be polite.
Who are you, uh, geezer, sir?
[FOREST DRAGON]
I am a dragon.
[FAVARO, KAISAR, AMIRA]
We knew that.
[FOREST DRAGON] What you pulled
from me has a great power.
So we're skipping
introductions, huh?
[FOREST DRAGON] It is a
barb from Bahamut itself.
Wow. Really?
[FOREST DRAGON]
All those passing centuries,
yet it was never
removed until now.
It seems it was fated
to guide you here.
That's crazy.
[FOREST DRAGON]
Bahamut has appeared many times,
over the long span of existence.
And each occurrence brought
death and ruin to the world.
Its last appearance
was around 2,000 years ago.
That time, in what could only
be called a miracle,
the gods and demons
allied to seal Bahamut,
thus preventing
a greater destruction.
It was in that moment
that this barb
lodged in my foot.
It tore through the very
fabric of space-time,
and reached me in
this alternate plane.
Bahamut's power is
like nothing else.
The world has been spared
the destroyer's wrath all
this time, but now Bahamut
is on the verge of awakening,
and wreaking havoc once again.
And it is this young girl
who would unseal it.
[KAISAR]
Then you know about Lady Amira?
[FOREST DRAGON]
Indeed I do.
I am an eternal
observer, after all.
She is now half the Key,
and will soon become the whole.
[AMIRA gasps]
[FOREST DRAGON] If the
completed Transcendent Key
and the seal are brought
together, Bahamut will awaken
and destroy the world, just as
it has so many times before.
We won't let that happen.
[FOREST DRAGON]
The gods and demons
are amassing forces as we speak.
Destruction has a
momentum of its own.
[GABRIEL]
The humans have failed us.
They have lost the Key.
If the girl reaches
her demon allies,
I'm convinced they'll
march on Abos
and put the whole world at risk!
Heroic warriors of light!
We cannot let this happen!
Prepare yourselves for battle!
[BEEZLEBUB] The God Key
has left the human city!
The scheming angels have
decided our damnation
is not enough, and they
plan to use Bahamut
to destroy us completely!
My fallen brothers and
sisters of the darkness!
We must take up our
swords and fight!
What exactly are you
scheming, Beezlebub?
[BEEZLEBUB] This time, when the
gods try to crush us under foot,
they will find they are
stepping on our blades!
So, we're doomed?
Relax would'ja?
Any back-alley fortuneteller can
predict the end of the world.
[FOREST DRAGON]
Destruction is your fate.
And fate cannot be changed.
[gasps]
Favaro, what is it?
It's nothing, okay?
[AMIRA] So the whole world's
going to be ruined,
because of me?
Everyone's going to die?
[FOREST DRAGON]
Yes.
And my mother, too?
[FOREST DRAGON]
No one will remain.
[AMIRA whimpers]
[FOREST DRAGON]
But it was also fate
that you stumbled
into this place.
And so, there may be one way
to prevent your lives
from unfolding down
their destructive path.
You mean it?
[FOREST DRAGON]
You can remove yourselves
from your own destinies,
by remaining
in this separate plain
of existence, forever.
Live here? For good?
But, if I do that,
then what about my mother?
[FOREST DRAGON sighs]
How will I ever see her?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[sobs]
[FAVARO]
That same damn image.
What's it mean?
[sobbing]
[FAVARO]
Okay, screw this.
Listen, dragon.
I say to hell with fate!
[FOREST DRAGON growls]
Easy.
I didn't go through
all this for nothing,
we're too close to finding
your mom to give up, Amira.
If I go on, then
she'll die. He said so!
[FAVARO] Forget that!
These are our lives!
We call the shots!
Listen up, you wrinkly lizard!
I'm tired of all
this destiny crap!
We can change our
so-called fate.
Whenever and however
we want! You got that?
We can change it?
[FAVARO]
Of course! And we will.
Our future's not
written in stone,
it can change like
the breeze. Ha!
That's what my old man
meant all along.
[BAROSSA]
Feel that, Favaro?
Know which way the
wind is blowing?
Toward tomorrow!
[FAVARO]
Heh.
[FOREST DRAGON]
My word.
That actually worked.
[AMIRA]
Fava!
Favaro. For once,
I agree with you.
I couldn't have said it better.
[FOREST DRAGON laughs]
You surprise me, young human.
That was wonderful!
[FAVARO] There I go
being impulsive again.
Hope I don't regret it.
[FOREST DRAGON]
I understand.
Now go forth,
and meet your future.
[AMIRA]
You won't stop us?
[FOREST DRAGON] I am only
an observer, nothing more.
It is not my place to stop you.
Take that barb of
Bahamut with you.
If it can tear through
the planes of reality,
perhaps it can tear
through fate, as well.
Well, thanks for your
help, ya old bastard!
We won't forget you, Mr. Geezer!
We'll make you proud.
Oh, great one.
[FOREST DRAGON] You and I have
more to discuss, bold knight.
[CITIZEN 9A] Saint Jeanne is
being burned at the stake?
[CITIZEN 9B]
But that's madness!
[CITIZEN 9C]
Can't possibly be a traitor!
She's the Holy Knight!
She's supposed to save us!
[SOLDIER 9B]
Shut up, all of you!
Oppose the king's decree, and
you can burn right next to her!
Huh?
[BACCHUS]
Hm?
[burps]
Gross!
Please have mercy, Your Majesty.
This must be a mistake.
She would never act against you.
[CHARIOCE]
Silence!
From now on, anyone who praises
that witch is a traitor!
Seize every last one of them!
And if they don't recant,
then kill them, too!
I'm in.
[RITA]
Fungus, Foxglove, mandrake root.
Cockatrice gizzard?
Basilisk heart?
[RITA] These are pretty
shady ingredients
to be stockpiling
in a royal castle.
[RITA]
Hm?
Someone's been
performing magic here.
And it looks like
a powerful spell.
[MARTINET]
Looking for something, madam?
Too bad for you.
This is it? The place
where my mother lives?
[KAISAR]
Prudisia.
What's the matter, Favaro?
Losing your nerve?
[AMIRA]
Don't worry. I'm strong!
[KAISAR]
You certainly are.
[FOREST DRAGON] You and I have
more to discuss, bold knight.
As long as the girl
is the Key's vessel,
the miracle of 2,000
years ago cannot repeat.
What? What's that mean?
[FOREST DRAGON] Zeus and Satan
now exist only as Keys.
Bahamut's seal has
become unstable,
the god and demon lords
must be restored to their
bodies to seal the creature.
But only the blood of a
human vessel can restore them.
Since the girl has
no human blood,
she cannot make this happen.
Well, that's great.
So 'cause she's a god
and demon halfbreed,
she could steal the Key, but she
can't use it the right way?
[FOREST DRAGON]
Correct.
And if the Transendent Key
and Bahamut come together
with that girl as the vessel,
they will be permanently joined.
Zeus and Satan will be lost, and
a new seal will be impossible.
That much is certain.
So how come you're
tellin' me all this?
[FOREST DRAGON growls]
[FOREST DRAGON]
You're the one who's convinced
he can change his fate.
So you need to know the facts.
If you truly want
to stop Bahamut,
and the world's destruction...
Hey! Can you hear me,
Mother? I made it!
I'll be there soon!
[FAVARO gasps]
[FOREST DRAGON]
You must kill the girl.
[LUCIFER]
I'm Lucifer.
[AZAZEL]
I'm Azazel.
[LUCIFER, AZAZEL] And we're
the Fallen Angel Brothers!
[LUCIFER]
But I'm still your boss.
[AZAZEL]
I love your feathers.
[LUCIFER]
Don't change the subject.
[LUCIFER, AZAZEL] On the next
Rage of Bahamut: Genesis:
Helheim, Land of Lies.