The God key.
It's been stolen?
Yes.
If the two are brought together,
all could be lost. The
destroyer will rise again.
[MICHAEL]
Fear not.
I already took measures
to retrieve our key.
Those valiant humans
will not disappoint us.
[RAPHAEL] Hmph. So, we'll be
relying on your beloved
maiden saint once again?
We do have to tread carefully.
As gods, it's unwise to offer
the humans too much support.
So, she will be our hands.
Jeanne D'Arc, of the
Orléans Knights.
We will repel the demons!
[KNIGHTS cheer]
[JEANNE] We have the blessings
of the gods to shield us!
[LAVALLEY grunting]
Unleash the Golems!
Bahamut is stiring.
[FAVARO]
No way. No way!
No freakin' way!
It can't be. I'm dreaming.
Yeah, it's a dream.
Oh, I love crazy dreams!
I'm the prince of all demons!
Hello, Demon Princess,
care to dance?
Since it's a dream,
this won't hurt! Ow!
[gasps]
[yelps] This isn't a dream!
[FAVARO grunts]
Okay, just chop it off, and
get back to your normal day!
[grunting]
Well, that didn't work.
Huh?
Hey! I'm kinda busy here!
[AMIRA]
You made a deal with me.
Huh?
You said, if I kissed you,
you would tell me about the
shortcut to Helheim in exchange.
Huuuuh?!
[AMIRA] So, I cast a spell.
A contract spell.
So, that's what this is?!
I'll lift the spell
once you tell me.
[FAVARO]
Uh--! Heh, heh...
Wow, it's stuffy in here,
don'tcha think?
That's the problem with attics.
Just gonna get some fresh air
outside, uh, yeah.
[FAVARO] Oh, crap!
Crap, crap, crappy, crap!
I really screwed
myself this time!
Me and my big, stupid mouth!
I just gotta stay calm.
I can figure this out.
First, deal with the tail.
And clothes might be good, too.
[TAVERN GIRL 1A]
It's upstairs!
It's a demon, I'm
telling you! I saw it!
All right, I'm coming!
Kaisar?!
[FAVARO] Damn it, this is
the worst possible time.
[KAISAR]
So, it looks human?
[FAVARO grunting, groaning]
[groans] I totally just
broke something, I know it!
[FAVARO groans]
Where are you going?
Tell me about the shortcut.
I can't just
tell you, okay, lady?
It's not that simple!
Why not?
Don't tell me you lied.
That is not what I'm saying!
Just look in my eyes!
Are these the eyes of a liar?
It's down there! Hurry!
[FAVARO] Great, now I'm
an "it!" Let's go!
Just get on, quick!
[gasps]
Where is it? Where is
the vile demon?
Hey, that hurts!
You're squishin' me,
barrette head!
[KAISAR] Are you joking? That
is not how you ride a horse!
Favaro!
Have you stooped to kidnapping
young ladies now, too?
We can't all fit here at once!
Are ya stupid?
[TAVERN GIRL 1A]
Look! It's getting away!
[KAISAR gasps]
[FAVARO]
Yah!
Don't just stand here
starin', go kill it!
You're a knight, aren't you?
[FAVARO]
I've gotta break this curse,
or every idiot with a sword
will come after me.
Should I kill her,
right here and now?
No. I'll wait...
...for the perfect
moment to strike.
Okay, tell me the shortcut
to Helheim, now.
I've got a better idea!
I'll take you to Helheim myself,
to make sure you
get there all right!
You'd do that?
Of course!
It's too complicated
to explain, anyway.
'Sides, this'll
be good, trust me.
How?
How could he fool me
all these years?
A demon in disguise.
I should've known;
I should've slain him!
It's the Orléans Knights!
But they serve
the royal capital.
Why would they come
to this little town?
We've come to you
on orders decreed by the exalted
Saint Jeanne D'Arc herself.
We are looking for a demon.
A demon in human disguise!
You there, Knight!
Have you seen anyone
suspicious here?
[KAISAR]
Forgive me, but I cannot say.
What?
I'm on my own quest
for this demon.
It's a quest for vengeance,
sworn on my family name.
However, I will bring
this demon to you.
After I've captured it myself.
You have my oath as a knight.
I will not fail you.
Liar! You're no knight!
That's the bracelet
of a bounty hunter!
I wear this now, yes.
You're right.
But I descend from the house
of Lidfard, a proud line--
--[GAURIN grunts]
--[KAISAR groans]
[GAURIN]
You've got some nerve, commoner!
What "proud" and "noble"
knight would have
a coin-chasing hunter for a son?
[VILLAGER 2A]
Where's your pride now, knight?
[VILLAGER 2B]
You're a damned disgrace!
The demon who cursed
me to this fate.
This life... of shame!
Desperation is a powerful force.
It can make a man stronger.
[gasps]
Don't ever forget that.
[KAISAR] I will reestablish our
house, no matter what it takes.
I will catch him,
with my own two hands.
I swear it.
This can't be the
road to Helheim.
Take it easy, sweets.
It's gonna be a long
and pricey trip.
First, we need some funds.
Ah, man. That is just
bad taste. Tacky...
Hello.
It looks like we came to
the right place, though.
[gasps]
[FAVARO]
Two thousand Rupies...
Is this you? Are you
a ram? Or a goat?
I guess ram? What's the
difference, right?
[roars]
[yelps]
[FAVARO]
Okay, there's a difference!
Son of a bitch.
You better keep your distance,
this guy's way stronger
than he looks.
Huh?!
[FAVARO]
Ew...
So, yesterday wasn't a dream.
She's a full-on,
real-deal demon.
And a freakin' strong one, too.
[AMIRA]
All right. It's time to go.
[FAVARO]
Huh? Y-Yeah.
[FAVARO] Trying to kill this
girl might be a bad idea.
At least, if she sees it comin'.
[BACCHUS]
Okay, here's your reward.
Took down a big
one this time,
you've impressed me.
[FAVARO]
Yeah.
Hey. Look, uh...
Stop starin' at me like that?
I'm getting nervous.
You look tasty.
Hands off, sweetie.
That's Hamsa the talking duck.
And he's Captain Drunkard's
favorite pet.
Eating him is not allowed!
[HAMSA] Stupid, clueless
human, how dare you!
I'm not a duck or a pet!
I'm a god! A god, incarnate!
[BACCHUS]
Where you going, Puff Ball Head?
[FAVARO]
Gotta run. See ya, Bacchus!
[BACCHUS]
Yeah whatever,
[FAVARO]
Just ignore him.
[BACCHUS] Hey, close
the door! Damn human...
Puff Ball Head's keeping
strange company these days.
[FAVARO] We've gotta get
you some new clothes.
You smell like a sweaty bandit.
[AMIRA]
Well, you smell like that ram.
Oh yeah, and who's
fault is that, huh?
[FAVARO]
Hm...
[laughs]
Uh...
Huh.
[stomach growls]
[FAVARO]
Hm...
[AMIRA]
What's in the cup?
This? It's just a little wine.
Hey, hey!
[gasps]
Ah, it tastes good.
Wait, don't tell me
this is the first time
you've ever had wine.
Ah...
Then you've got some
catching up to do!
Hey! More drinks,
keep 'em comin'!
[hiccups]
And that's why
I love this town,
the drinks can't be beat!
[gasps]
What are they doing?
That's called dancing.
The way they dance in this
town can't be beat, either!
[AMIRA giggling]
[AMIRA]
Whoa!
--[AMIRA giggling]
--[FAVARO laughs]
[AMIRA giggling]
Ah!
[TAVERN PATRONS cheer]
[AMIRA laughing] Drinking is
great! And dancing is the best!
[AMIRA sighs]
The water feels so good.
Hey. You think that's nice?
Check out all those stars.
Beautiful, huh?
You're right. They are.
Gotcha.
[FAVARO]
Now's my chance.
If I kill her, I break
the curse for sure.
Then it's goodbye, tail!
What the--? Of all
the times to mess up!
What's messed up?
Oh, uh. Nothing!
Everything's fine!
I just said it's messed up
we've spent all this
time together and haven't
introduced ourselves.
My name's Favaro. Favaro Leone.
And you are?
I'm Amira.
Ah, Amira!
A beautiful name for
a beautiful woman!
Well, it beats the hell
out of my mom's name,
she got stuck with "Bunyon."
Bunyon?
So, now that we're
getting familiar,
why do you wanna go
to Helheim, anyway?
It's an icy hellhole,
most people
would choose any other
town in the world,
which would be fine
with me, by the way,
if you wanted to
change our deal.
[FAVARO]
Crap, that wasn't smooth.
Did I make her suspicious?
I have to reach Helheim.
That's where my mother is.
Your mother?
She has one just like this.
This pendant, I mean.
When I hold it, I can
see her, just barely.
A memory I've half-forgotten.
The gentle look on her face.
My teacher told me,
I'd be with her again one day,
as long as I held onto this.
So, that's why-- that's why
I have to get to Helheim.
I need to see her!
Teacher?
--[yelps]
--[KAISAR] Favaro!
[FAVARO]
Damn it, where'd it go?
[KAISAR]
Now you're a kidnapper, too!
You fooled me
all these years!
I should've known
you were a demon!
Huh? No you got it
all wrong, Kaisar!
Silence, wretch! On my
honor as a knight!
I'll make you pay!
[AMIRA]
Stop!
[grunts, gasps]
[KAISAR groans]
[FAVARO]
Let's go!
Beautiful. So beautiful.
[FAVARO] Hm... So can
you cut me a deal?
[MARKET MAN 2A]
Hm?
Whoa. Knights from
the capital, huh?
People of Livian.
We are on the hunt for
a one-winged demon!
--A girl! Have you seen her?
--[FAVARO gaggs]
We'd better keep moving.
I think we should split up
so we can cover more ground.
Yes, sir. Two groups, men!
Half with me!
We don't rest until
that God Key is found!
Demon girl? God Key?
[FAVARO]
'Scuse me!
[GAURIN]
Hm?
[FAVARO] I think I can help
you with your demon hunt.
[rattling]
Do you miss your mother, too?
Huh?
Over there! That's her!
[FAVARO whistles]
There's no doubt about it,
now. She's the one!
The miserable thief
who stole the God Key.
Enchantment formation!
Say goodbye, vile demon.
[FAVARO]
All right, look at 'em go!
Once those armored
goodie-two-shoes
take care of the
demon girl for me,
I'll be back to normal again.
And the reward money's
not bad, either. You get it.
[AMIRA]
I have to reach Helheim.
That's where I'll
find my mother.
Yeah, likely story.
Like demons have moms!
[FAVARO]
Hey, No-Not that way!
Hey! We're taking
that road, dope!
I wanna go that way.
[gasps] What's wrong?
The enchantment isn't working!
It tingles.
[growls] It's not enough!
Increase the power!
[KNIGHT 2A]
We can't! This is all we have!
[FAVARO screams]
Stupid crazy horse!
[FAVARO yelping]
[FAVARO groans] Those knights
are not gonna be happy.
I better sneak out
while I still can.
[yelps]
What the--?
They didn't kill you?
No, it just tingled!
It tingled?
[GAURIN] Find her, men!
Find the demon!
Don't let her get away!
Okay, whatever--
just come with me!
[AMIRA panting]
[FAVARO yelps]
That's a problem.
Only a bounty hunter
would have the nerve
to scam royal knights.
Now, you will die.
Ha! I don't know what
you're talking about!
But you'd better not move!
[gasps]
[FAVARO] I know, I'm surrounded,
outnumbered, blah, blah, blah.
But you don't wanna risk
losing your little
treasure, right?
That double-crossing liar!
Liar?
[FAVARO]
Hey, Amira.
You with me?
'Cause I say we take
another dip in the water.
Yeah!
This is gonna be fun!
[growls] You die, now!
Wait! Don't shoot!
[FAVARO, AMIRA yelp]
[FAVARO panting]
That was dumb.
Why did I just risk
my neck to save her life?
If I'd stayed out of it,
that damn curse would be broken.
And I'd be rid of
this freakshow tail.
[AMIRA]
He called you a liar.
Are you? Are you a liar?
Forget what he said!
Just look into my eyes!
Am I lying?
[FAVARO giggles]
[slap]
[BACCHUS]
See ya around, Senor Barrettes.
[KAISAR]
Lady Amira.
Favaro's made them think
you're an outlaw, too.
I'll save you from
that demon. I swear it.
[CERBERUS] Hmm. She doesn't seem
to be in this town anymore.
We've gotta track
her down! Arf!
Yeah! Grab her
and stab her! Arf!
[PAZUZU] No need to rush.
She'll turn up soon enough.
The most important thing
is that we learn the truth.
Where is she taking the God Key?
And to whom?
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[FAVARO]
Kaisar!
[KAISAR]
Favaro!
[FAVARO]
You're making my ears bleed!
[KAISAR] On the next
Rage of Bahamut: Genesis:
Fog of Nebelville!
[FAVARO]
Inside voice.