[MARTINET] You must
fulfill your mission.
My dear Amira.
Do so faithfully,
and your greatest wish
will most certainly come true.
She waits for you now, in the
promised land of Helheim.
My mo... ther...
No sleeping, Amira.
You gotta hold on.
We're right
here with you!
Take me... to her.
What?
I can't hear you.
Easy on the hair! Easy!
Take me to her. Please.
Take me to... Hel... heim.
Quickly!
I'd love to, but I'm
thinking that won't fly.
Just once I'd like
to escape a crisis
without falling into another.
Sir Gaurin. Why am I not seeing
Sir Lavalley in the line?
He left the ranks earlier
to check on something,
Saint Jeanne, but I believe that
he'll catch up with us soon.
What is he checking on?
[KAISAR] Favaro,
where is your bracelet?
Oh, yeah!
Must've slipped off!
He destroyed it to
get help from Bacchus.
So we could reach
Gregor and save you.
You should work on
keeping your mouth shut!
He's the one responsible for
your father's death, right?
So why don't you
kill him already?
I don't have my sword.
Then strangle him,
it's not that hard!
That's for thieves,
and I'm a knight.
Besides...
We have an agreement.
Isn't that right?
[FAVARO]
Hm.
So what's the agreement?
Not your concern.
What about her, why's she
want to go to Helheim anyway?
From what I understand
it's an inhospitable place
completely covered in ice,
so I hardly see the appeal.
Well, apparently that's
where Amira's mother is.
Don't ask me what
she's doing there.
[MARTINET] Fancy
seeing you here.
[AZAZEL]
Martinet.
[MARTINET] Do you intend
to have an audience
with Lord Lucifer, Azazel?
Is that why you've come? Mm?
If I were you I would watch
where I stick my nose.
[AZAZEL shudders, gasps]
[MARTINET laughs]
I'm amazed you have
the gall to waltz back
to the capital like this
after being ambushed
and thoroughly humiliated
by those humans.
Do you honestly think
Lord Lucifer would deign
to meet with such
an abject failure?
You're an
embarrassment, arf!
Yeah! Get lost, arf!
I see the news
has traveled quickly.
Then I'll skip the conversation
and move straight to the task.
Getting back the God Key.
His Royal Majesty
Charioce the Eighth.
King of our land!
Good tidings, Jeanne D'Arc.
Our maiden saint blessed
by the gods in heaven.
I'm told you have accomplished
another great feat.
Your King is as grateful
and as proud of you as ever.
[JEANNE] I'm pleased
to hear it, sire.
Present the prisoners
to the king!
[KAISAR and FAVARO grunt]
[FAVARO] That's the king?
[LAVALLEY] Silence! You're
in His Majesty's presence!
She's the thief
we've been after.
[AMIRA groans]
Her? Are you sure of that?
Certainly looks like
an ordinary girl to me.
[AMIRA trembles]
I can't explain it, the gems
we use to spot demons
don't react to her, sire.
Oh...
And that is precisely
how the key was stolen.
[JEANNE gasps]
[CHARIOCE] Three angels...
descending at once?
Well, well. Get a load of
the fancy-ass cloud-dwellers.
[RITA]
Shh!
And I thought
Bacchus was classy.
[BACCHUS snores]
[HAMSA squawks]
[MICHAEL] Even we, the gods,
were fooled by this girl.
For that is her talent.
[AMIRA shudders]
[AMIRA screams]
[MICHAEL] This is how she
circumvented our defenses.
With the forbidden
power to transform
between god and
demon, at will.
So Lady Amira...
is an angel?
She's a demon, dumb ass!
Guys, she's both.
[AMIRA wails, whimpers]
Although she's only half,
the fact that the key is now
entangled with demon blood
means we cannot take her
back to the sacred Ark.
King Charioce. You will
keep her under heavy guard
in your royal
capital of Anatae.
[CHARIOCE] Yes, of course.
I shall guard her with my life.
But what of them? The vagabonds
who were traveling with her.
I assume we should treat
them as co-conspirators,
and put them to death?
What? Put to death?
How could one stupid lie
get me into so much trouble?
And now I'm gonna die for it?
So not fair!
[MICHAEL] You must
not take their lives.
[CHARIOCE] Indeed,
your wish is my command.
They will be dead
by the morning.
Lock them up and
prepare the gallows...
Wait. what did you say?
All four of them must
remain in your city.
It is imperative that
your forces protect them.
Protect them?
Yes! I knew you angels were
decent, I always said so!
Ow!
[MICHAEL]
Behold!
[CHARIOCE]
What? What is that?
[MICHAEL] Signs of
Bahamut's revival,
which grow ever more intense.
Bahamut? Who's that?
[RAPHAEL] Though it gains
strength, it cannot wake yet.
Its unsealing requires
the Transcendent Key,
the union of the two keys
that the Supreme God Zeus
and the Demon Lord Satan
formed from themselves.
[URIEL] Should the Transcendent
Key be brought to Bahamut,
horrendous catastrophes will
befall creation on a scale
your minds cannot fathom,
and life will be pushed
to the brink of extinction
as it was so many years ago.
[MICHAEL] It is thus
unwise to take the lives
of her companions.
The girl's emotional strain
could have unforeseen
consequences.
We must prevent the revival of
Bahamut, no matter the costs.
Keep the God Key safe.
It's up to you, o valiant ones!
[CHARIOCE]
As you command!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Release them at once!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sire!
Now, freedom is yours as long
as you remain in the city.
May our hospitality
soothe you weary travelers.
[FAVARO sobs]
[GAURIN]
Insolent cur!
Thank you, your
merciful majesty-ship,
I promise you won't regret this!
[SOLDIER 6B] Fool, you
don't touch the king!!
[FAVARO] Thank you, thank you!
Long live the king!
[AMIRA]
I hate this place!
I need to get to Helheim!
I have to see my mother!
[FAVARO] Come on, can you
tone down the crazy?
You're in no condition
to go anywhere right now.
Does your word
mean nothing to you?
You promised you'd
take me to Helheim!
Yeah, but...
You promised, you
promised, you promised!!
And I've been trying, okay?
But just so we're clear,
it's only 'cause you
put a dumb curse on me!
What? I'll be damned.
Isn't that interesting?
He's almost like a demon.
Almost?
[RITA] Don't you
listen to anything?
She cursed him, with some kind
of contract spell, presumably.
He's a run-of-the-mill
human, after all.
Favaro's human?
You're sure?
Of course I'm human, stupid,
you grew up with me!
Just a normal
former bounty hunter
who's had enough
of this crap!
And I'm not taking
you to Helheim.
I'm tired of risking my neck!
[AMIRA gasps]
So if you wanna go to
that wasteland so bad,
then go by yourself!
But first...
You need to get this damn
tail off me, right now!
Then a "thank you"
would be nice!
You liar!
[AMIRA sobs]
Oww... Something feels broken.
[GAURIN]
Fiores Mondo Malit.
She can't leave these
quarters now. We'll keep her
under guard here until her
wounds have fully healed.
The rest of you can
use the room next door.
Actually, I would rather
have a private room as well.
[GAURIN]
Don't push your luck.
Under any other circumstances
we'd have hanged you.
Of course, we'll be
keeping your weapons
while you're in the castle.
[KAISAR]
Huh?
[FAVARO]
Damn it...
[bell rings]
What is that?
Some kind of signal?
It's a warning bell.
Means demons are approaching.
[bell continues ringing]
[GIANT GHOUL roars]
[JEANNE]
They're ghouls?
[LAVALLEY]
That's the report--
and they're much
larger than before.
[JEANNE] Then I'll
destroy them with Maltet.
They're nothing against
the spear of the gods.
[LAVALLEY] I'm not
sure that's wise,
going into battle by yourself.
[JEANNE]
I'm sure.
I can hear the gods
speaking to me now,
and their message is plain.
They're telling me to
attack without fear.
[GIANT GHOUL roars]
[JEANNE yells]
Those shots only
targeted the demons.
Her strength
keeps increasing.
She seems more powerful
now than ever.
[LAVALLEY] Maybe it's the
presence of the God Key.
It's hard to believe.
Demonkind is no
match for us now!
We have the blessings
of the gods to shield us!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
The gods want
an only Maiden Saint.
[CHARIOCE sighs]
[RAPHAEL] Containing Bahamut
has been more manageable
since her rescue.
It definitely seems
the girl's well-being
is now vital to maintaining
the ancient seal on the beast.
Indeed. But we still
can't afford to leave
the Key in the human's
custody forever.
[RAPHAEL] The human, Jeanne
D'Arc, was chosen to serve us
in the resealing,
should it come to that.
You'll have a grave
price to pay, Michael,
if that half-god,
half-demon keeps us
from carrying out our plans.
She surprised me.
She was protected
by powerful magic.
I believe someone
else was behind it.
[GABRIEL] The one
scheming to steal the key
and break Bahamut's seal.
[MICHAEL] I've received
word from the knights.
They say the girl was
on her way to Helheim.
To the location of the
other key, as we suspected.
If we continue
to hold the girl
within the royal
capital of Anatae...
the schemer will almost
certainly make a move.
This is the perfect chance
to expose who's behind this.
We will use her
to our advantage
and draw our enemy
from the shadows.
[FAVARO]
Now this is the life!
When they caught us,
I expected hell!
Ah, yeah. And instead I'm
in heaven with you angels.
It's great!
[RITA]
Enjoying yourself?
I don't understand
either one of you idiots.
If you hate him, why
aren't you doing anything?
[RITA sighs]
--Rita.
--This is boring.
I'm going to bed.
No, I swear! I've been through
all kinds of danger and seen
tons of beautiful women, but
none are as pretty as you two!
You are too much!
So tell us, what's the most
dangerous place you've been to?
[FAVARO]
Let me think.
It's too hard to pick.
Hey. This could come in handy.
[LAVALLEY]
Poor thing.
[AMIRA]
Huh?
[LAVALLEY] Both mind and body
tortured, from inside and out.
[AMIRA]
Who's there?
[LAVALLEY] You seek answers,
don't you? You wish to know
the real reason you were
brought into this existence.
And I am someone who
can grant you that wish.
No! Come back!
[FAVARO] Aw, man, I could
not drink another drop.
[sound of footsteps]
[KAISAR sighs]
[FAVARO]
Whatcha waiting for?
[KAISAR]
Huh?
This is the perfect
chance for revenge.
That's what you
want, isn't it?
[KAISAR]
I'm not so sure. Maybe.
[FAVARO]
Huh...
I don't even know what
the truth is anymore.
I don't know how I should feel
or what I should do, and...
the more I think,
the more I get confused.
Tell me. Why did you
come to my rescue?
I've been chasing you all this
time. I'm clearly a hindrance.
And... And it seems
Lady Amira is too. So why?
What kind of person
are you, Favaro?
What's the truth?
[FAVARO] Isn't it obvious?
You know what I am.
[KAISAR]
Huh?
I'm a lying trickster
and a rogue,
a nefarious, backstabbing
villain. aren't I?
Yes. Exactly right!
[FAVARO grunts]
You're arrogant and crude.
A snake-tongued devil.
A repugnant womanizer!
And you're a narrow-minded
fool who spends
entirely too much time
screaming his lungs out!
Silence!
Meet my blade!
[FAVARO and KAISAR yell]
[FAVARO grunts]
[KAISAR grunts]
[KAISAR and FAVARO groan]
[RITA] You'll have to put your
little game on hold, boys.
Amira's missing. I just
checked her quarters.
[FAVARO]
Seriously?
[LAVALLEY]
This way, Amira.
[FAVARO] Aw, man. That girl
is so high-maintenance.
What is this place, anyway?
[FAVARO]
That rings a bell.
It's the same monster
from my dreams.
[JEANNE] What
are you doing here?
[FAVARO] Great.
Jeanne D'friggin' Arc!
Of all the people in the
capital, I had to run into her!
[FAVARO] Oh, just taking a
stroll to clear my head. See ya!
You came to Bahamut.
Do you know about it?
Uh-- Wait, did
you say Bahamut?
The great destroyer.
The one that would bring
about the end of our world.
Neither god nor demon,
its power surpasses us all.
It is said that mountains
will crumble, seas will boil,
and all realms will
be reduced to nothingness
once its power awakens.
That's Bahamut?
That's what they meant?
It happened many
centuries ago.
Bahamut appeared from
the skies without warning,
and turned the world
into a living hell
in the blink of an eye.
It set the lands ablaze,
nearly exterminating all
life in its merciless fury.
But then, just
as gods, demons,
and humans alike
had abandoned hope...
a miracle was performed.
[JEANNE] The Supreme God Zeus
and the Demon Lord Satan
transformed themselves
into a God and Demon Key,
sacrificing their physical
forms to seal Bahamut in Abos.
This stone statue was
carved in remembrance.
Now it's a mecca.
People come here
to offer prayers and
achieve inner peace.
[FAVARO]
They pray to a monster?
Not at all. They pray
to a knight. Up there.
A holy knight,
prophesied by the gods.
[FAVARO] And what's
the prophecy?
[JEANNE] When Bahamut revives,
a knight of high valor
will appear to face the doom,
and restore peace to the land.
The citizens of
the royal capital
believe in
this prophecy.
They also believe the
awakening is coming soon,
and that I am that knight.
It is my earnest hope that
I will not let them down.
I pray I can be their promised
savior if that day does come.
[FAVARO] Good, then it
has nothing to do with me.
[JEANNE]
Why do you say that?
I wound up here
'cause I got mixed up
with a weird demon girl
and I stupidly tried
to play for some action.
The three things I care about
are women, freedom, and booze,
and life as a bounty hunter
was perfect for me
before I screwed that up.
All this stuff
about holy knights
and world-ending monsters...
that's a world apart from me.
[JEANNE]
I wouldn't be so sure.
Huh?
I began my life as
a simple farm girl,
in a small, remote village
you couldn't find on a map.
Despite that humble
start I received the light
and revelation of the gods
and was awakened to my mission.
We're all born into
this world for a reason.
We're all meant to play a role.
And I believe that
yours is a crucial one.
It was no accident
that you met the girl.
Your destiny is
already calling.
Destiny, my ass.
Yeah, right.
There's no reason
to any of this.
Who are you? Tell me!
Why do you have
the same pendant?
[LAVALLEY] I was asked
to keep it safe...
by your own mother.
By my mother?
Then you know her?
Does that mean...?
Yeah, my freaking father, okay!
You got one, right?
[bell rings, AMIRA gasps]
[bell continues]
[FAVARO]
Great, demons again?
[AZAZEL] Brace
yourselves, humans.
The time for fun
and games is over.
[FAVARO]
I love machinery.
My clock sword
is my masterpiece.
[KAISAR] But your
clock's broken!
[FAVARO] Shut up!
What are you into?
--[KAISAR] Oh! Uh--
--[FAVARO] Nobody cares!
On the next Rage of Bahamut:
Genesis: The Storm Rages!
--[KAISAR] I love meat!
--[FAVARO] Good for you.