[CHILD WU QING] Father! Mother!
Let me go! Let me go!
Father! Mother!
[WU QING sobs]
F-Father...M-Mother...
[LORD BIAO] Much blood has
been shed on both sides...
since the Wan Castle
massacre was ordered.
[LORD BIAO] Wu Qing...
So it is at last we meet.
[WANG YI giggles]
[WU QING growls]
[LORD BIAO growls]
[WU QING yells]
[LORD BIAO yells]
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of
war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[LORD BIAO &amp; WU QING yelling]
[WU QING grunts]
[LORD BIAO grunts]
They are evenly matched?!
General!
[LORD BIAO growls]
[WU QING] Lord Biao!
[LORD BIAO] Wu Qing!
[BOTH grunt]
This is getting heavy...
Hang in there, General Biao!
[BOTH grunting]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasping]
[LORD BIAO grunts]
[WU QING yells]
[grunting]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasp]
[WEI SOLDIER 22A] W-W...
Wu Qing! Wu Qing!
[WEI SOLDIERS] Wu Qing! Wu Qing!
Wu Qing! Wu Qing! Wu Qing!
[WEI ARMY] Wu Qing!
Wu Qing! Wu Qing!
[chanting continues]
This is... This is just...
That can't be good at all.
Their cheers give Wei's
general more power!
[WU QING yells]
[XIN] I thought he'd flipped
under pressure or something,
but he thought he could win?
[BOTH grunt]
[XIN] He must've been
counting on this boost
from the crowd all along!
[WEI SOLDIERS chanting]
[XIN] The commanding
generals are fighting.
Whoever wins this
will win the whole war!
[chanting continues]
Hey!
Let's cheer for our general;
let's give him a boost!
He won't be able to reach
full power like this on his own!
[QIN COMMANDER 22A]
But our general does not need
this kind of help.
His victory was assured the
moment this became one-on-one.
Huh? What do you mean?!
In all of the Middle Kingdom,
there are at most
a handful of men
who can hold a candle to
Lord Biao in single combat.
[WU QING yells]
[LORD BIAO grunts]
[WU QING growls]
[QIN COMMANDER 22A]
Wu Qing doesn't come close
to matching Lord Biao's prowess.
[XIN] So you mean the general's
just toying with him right now?!
[QIN COMMANDER 22A]
No, that's not it at all.
Our general quite simply
wants to know Wu Qing.
[BOTH grunt]
[XIN] Know him?
Lord Biao truly is
an unusual man.
[LORD BIAO growls]
He will make his move
any time now, though.
[horse whinnies,
LORD BIAO yells]
[horse whines,
WU QING yells]
[LORD BIAO growls]
[WU QING grunts]
[yelling]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasp]
[WEI SOLDIERS] Wu Qing!
General! General Wu Qing!
The first stroke of your sword
showed me your spirit
and displayed your resolve.
But then,
at the second stroke,
I lost sight of
your soul completely.
Wu Qing, it was not the stirring
of your warrior's blood
that made you duel me!
What inane reason
did you challenge me for?
I'll let you tell me
that before I kill you.
Huh...?
[LORD BIAO grunts]
General!
[WU QING] Lord Biao, I'll
teach you here with this blade
that I have something
in me that burns hotter
than mere warrior's blood!
How intriguing.
[WU QING yells]
[LORD BIAO grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[WU QING yells]
What's wrong?
Done now?
[WU QING] Lord Biao...
[WEI SOLDIER 22B] General.
[WU QING growls]
General, please stop this fight
and order the army
to slay Lord Biao.
If we slaughter all
of Qin's soldiers
and you give us
a command of silence,
it can be as though this
duel has never happened.
General, I beg you leave this
to us and withdraw to safety.
[XIN gasps]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasps]
General, but why have you...
General!
[WU QING chuckles]
[WU QING] I confess
that even I'm surprised
that a few invaders have made
me reluctant to yield ground.
Man can never be master of
his own emotions, I suppose.
Oh? I took you for
a cool-headed man,
but I see waters run
surprisingly deep.
Was all your family murdered
by a bunch of invaders, then?!
[WU QING yells]
[LORD BIAO growls]
It wasn't just my family!
It was my country.
That itself was murdered!
His country... was murdered?
[LORD BIAO growls]
Thirty years ago,
a small kingdom
to the east of Wei called Jia
was wiped out solely by Zhao.
And I am its rightful royalty!
[BI] A surviving royal
from a perished nation?!
[WU QING] I changed my name
and tattooed my face.
I became someone else,
and wandered the land
until I ended up in Wei.
And there, thanks to
Lord Xinling's protection,
I regained my name, and Wei
became my second homeland.
But I have never, for one
moment, forgotten the sight
of our castle going up
in flames that day!
I understand.
So your obsession
with that grudge
gave you the impudence to go
ahead and challenge me, then?
Someone like you
could never understand
what it's like to
lose your country!
[LORD BIAO] You have a loser's
worthless sentimentality.
[XIN gasps]
[LORD BIAO] In these warring
times, nations fall every day.
The Middle Kingdom
is rife with men
who suffered the
same thing you did.
Your life story means absolutely
nothing on the battlefield!
A soldier thinks of how
to conquer the enemy
in front of him.
A general thinks of
how to win against the army.
He doesn't let his mind
be ruled by anything else!
All that awaits a man like you
who puts his personal feelings
before his duty as
general is defeat!
Come, Wu Qing!
On my honor as
commanding general of Qin,
see to your dynasty!
[WU QING]
So the mood has changed...
No, it was Lord Biao
who changed it.
[WU QING] I realized something
when I saw my castle burn.
[WU QING] There is something
mighty in this world
that bows to no justice
mankind could ever conceive of.
For me, right now, that
something is Lord Biao.
Fighting him spells
certain death for me.
But even so...
[WU QING] Even so...
[WU QING] ...I shall not yield!
[WU QING yelling]
[LORD BIAO grunts]
[WU QING grunts]
[WU QING whimpers]
[WEI COMMANDE 22A gasps]
[XIN gasps]
[BI &amp; QIN SOLDIERS gasp]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasp]
Your cleverness made this
a hard-fought battle for me
and your fierce passion
for the sword at the end...
I must say that you truly did
blaze brightly, Wu Qing!
[LORD BIAO growls]
Shout our victory!
[QIN SOLDIERS cheer]
[cheering continues]
[NARRATOR] While Qin's soldiers'
cheers rang in his ears,
Xin's gaze was captured not
by the triumphant Lord Biao,
but by the tragic figure of
Wu Qing laying on the ground.
This was because even in death,
a tiny flame still
smoldered in his eyes.
[NARRATOR] At the sight, Xin
murmured silently to himself,
"So this is what a general is."
[NARRATOR] And so the tide
of battle was determined.
The Qin soldiers who had served
under Lord Biao numbered 3,000.
The Wei soldiers surrounding
them numbered over 50,000.
However, in Wei's army
there was not a single man
who raised his
slumped shoulders.
[WEI SOLDIERS sobbing]
[WEI COMMANDER 21A]
General Wu Qing...
[sobbing continues]
[NARRATOR] To Wei's armies,
that great general
was simply too
important a figure.
[WEI SOLDIERS sobbing]
[NARRATOR] His
second-in-command, Bai Guixi,
could restore
their will to fight.
And in his path
stood this man...
Wait, you are...
That was the first good battle
I've seen in quite a while.
To drag the battle out
any longer would just be
somewhat gilding the
lily, now, would it not?
Or are you telling me
that you are confident
that you can now perform
an even greater battle
with myself, Wang Yi?
[BAI GUIXI whimpers]
W-Wang Yi...
Look at that!
[WEI PING gasps]
[WEI PING]
Wei's armies are... retreating!
We won...
[WEI PING] We won.
I-I think we...
--We won the battle!
--[GROUP cheering]
[WEI PING grunts]
B-Brother?!
[WEI PING] We survived...
We survived, you dingbats!
So many people died...
The Fourth Army infantry, and
guys from the other armies, too.
And Battalion
Commander Fu Hushen!
Damn it! Damn it!
We won, damn it!
[WANG YI chuckles]
It's been a pretty long time,
General Biao, don't you think?
[LORD BIAO] Ah, Wang Yi!
It was a big help,
you exerting pressure
from the hilltop like that.
I thank you, Wang Yi.
[WANG YI] Oh, no no, I simply
happened to be passing by,
so I decided to watch.
By the way, General,
what do you plan to do now?
[LORD BIAO] Huh?
[WANG YI] Do you intend to
go straight on to the castle?
Or...
Nothing is more difficult than
bringing an inferno
back to life after it's gone.
Attention all units!
We're going home!
[QIN SOLDIERS cheer]
[NARRATOR] In the second year
of Shi Huangdi's reign 245 BC,
one battle between the
kingdoms of Qin and Wei
reached its conclusion.
However...
[NARRATOR] For Xin, who aimed to
be the world's greatest general,
it was only the first
small step on his path.
In this world of seven
fiercely warring kingdoms,
the seeds of countless other
conflicts had already been sown.
Generals, huh?
I'll be one... soon!
[WOMAN A sobbing]
--[WOMAN B sobbing]
--[DIAO gasps]
[sobbing continues]
[DIAO] Why are there
so many corpses?
I thought they
won the battle...
[sobbing continues]
[SOLDIER 22A] Oww!
[DIAO screams]
Y-You're alive!
Yeah, I'm alive!
Huh?!
Why the heck were you
pretending to be dead?!
I was not!
We barely made it back here
after that, we all fell over.
[DIAO] Barely made it?
But didn't you win?!
Yeah, but unfortunately a
lot of our men were killed.
The Fourth Army that got
dispatched from here
was... wiped out!
[DIAO gasps]
Wiped out, you say...?
[DIAO whimpers,
WOMEN sob]
[XIN] Well, look who's here!
What'd you come
all the way here for?
[sobbing continues]
See? I told you
he dresses funny!
Huh. It's true...
Huh? What's wrong?
[DIAO] "What's wrong"
my butt, you dumb jerk!
[XIN grunts]
[XIN] Ow! Ugh, that's right
where Ma Gui got me!
You okay, Xin?
Hey, that hurt!
[DIAO] Shut up!
Xin, you better have
scored some major glory!
You bet I did!
Okay! Good work!
[XIN] Um, right...
[CROWD talking]
[DIAO giggles]
This place is great!
They're selling all kinds
of tasty-looking food!
Right, Xin?!
Don't be in such a hurry.
[DIAO] Oh Xin, look over there!
That stall's stuff looks yummy!
Come on, Diao.
Food can wait!
[DIAO] Huh?
Are you sick or something?
I've already told you.
Today I am going to
buy some armor
with this giant bounty
I got, all right?
[DIAO] Oh really?
You, prioritizing
something else over food?!
Wow, you've really matured!
That's a squadron commande--
[XIN's stomach growls]
[DIAO giggles]
[XIN] Hmph.
We'll need energy
for armor shopping!
I guess we better
eat up first!
Welcome!
Oh, I've never
seen you two before.
Well, we came all the way
here from three villages over!
This guy here
wants to buy armor.
Armor?
YOU want to?!
Are you going to wear armor
for your first war?
My first war's done.
I'm using the reward money
from that war to buy some armor.
What?!
The last battle was
that one against Wei
three months ago, wasn't it?
The men from this neighborhood
who did join the Fourth Army--
Almost all of them died!
That's not even a good lie.
[XIN yells]
I'm tellin' ya that I fought in
the Fourth Army and I got paid!
Hey, the place is noisy today.
Wait up, isn't he...?
See?! Right there is a real
and true Fourth Army hero!
[TIAN YOU gasps]
Uh?
[TIAN YOU] Oh!
Hello there, my lord!
[XIN] You're that guy everybody
wanted most for their squad!
[CROWD murmuring]
You are looking
very well, my lord.
[XIN] Call me Xin.
You're looking pretty
good yourself, Pops!
Hey, chief,
is this brat--I mean this
young man--really him?
[XIN] Hm?
Yep, this is Xin,
the man from that war
who fought like a demon
and went from foot soldier...
...all the way to a
real squadron commander!
[CROWD gasps]
But a squadron commander
leads a 100-man unit!
This kid climbed that
high in just one war?!
[TIAN YOU] It's the kind of
thing that hardly ever happens
but it's more than justified.
Without Xin, that war
might've been lost,
let alone the
Fourth Army's part of it.
You exaggerate.
Everyone was telling stories
about you on the way back home.
When I heard that you had
made squadron commander,
I could not have
been happier for you!
[XIN] Seriously?!
I've never looked forward to
the next war this much before.
But I'm sure that
I'm not the only one
who wants to try fighting
for you in your unit, Xin.
[XIN] Hmph!
My unit's gonna get worked
to the bone, you know!
Ha, ha!
[XIN hums]
[DIAO] I'm glad you
got to buy your armor, Xin.
[XIN] Heh, heh!
I look cool, huh?!
[DIAO] Mmm-hmm...
No you don't! Quit bragging.
Are you a child?
Huh? Which is it, then?!
Um, what I'm saying is...
Uh...
Xin, you've really
grown up... Mmm-hmm.
[XIN] It's you!
Qiang Lei!
[QIANG LEI] I am alive
for one reason only, you see.
[NARRATOR] A secret past.
On a night spent alone together,
their souls tremble.
Next Time: "An Evening Story."