[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A] Heh, heh!
Pesky little fly...
I'll take his life myself;
just watch!
[XIN] With a horse's mobility
and this steel spear, I can...
...do it!
[XIN growls]
[XIN] I don't
care about you guys.
My opponent is this
freakin' annoying chariot!
[XIN yells,
CHARIOT SOLDIERS scream]
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A screams]
The counterattack starts now!
[XIN yells]
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war, hatred,
and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[WEI PING] Xin!
[XIN] Got it!
[XIN grunts]
[XIN gasps]
[XIN] So the others weren't
completely wiped out, then.
Okay!
[XIN] Well survived, men!
Just as I'd expected of the
valiant warriors of Qin!
We have a fresh force
over there battling hard!
All of you hurry over there
and fight by their sides!
Yes Sir! Where will
you be going, my lord?
[XIN gasps]
I'll join you after I bring
down the chariot that fled!
Come on! We have not
lost this battle yet!
This fight is just beginning!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[Right, let's join
our brother army!
Lend the injured a hand!
Hey, Tian You.
That cavalryman wasn't wearing
armor. He was in rags!
Come to think of it, he reminded
me of that loudmouthed brat.
What in the world is
going on over here?
[horse whinnies]
[BI] We've lost too much
of the infantry.
[BI] Do you really think
we can bring down Wei
and all his troops like this?
Letting our soldiers
die in vain?
They are not dying in vain!
[BI gasps]
They're honorable deaths
for the sake of our victory.
Fu Hushen,
look at our circumstances.
Why do you not
doubt our victory?!
Is Lord Biao truly a general
worthy of such trust?!
Heh!
[FU HUSHEN] I do not
know any other general
who is so talented.
[NARRATOR]
After its attack on Xin
and the Fourth Army infantry,
the chariot squadron was now
exercising a crushing offensive,
attacking the Second
and First Armies.
Saying that the gap between
Qin's fighting strength and
Wei's had already determined
the outcome of the
battle would be fair.
In truth, Xin and the others
had only brought down one unit
of the main chariot squadron.
Theirs was an extremely
localized success.
It had no effect on the
larger picture whatsoever.
Now, Qin's forces clearly have
no strength left to resist us!
Leave a small
defensive force.
All other troops
descend from the hill!
And take that foolish
General Biao's head now!
[NARRATOR]
The Fourth Army's resistance
was like a stone
fighting a tide,
and Gong Yuan, Wei's
second-in-command,
did not even take notice of it.
Their cheers of victory
seemed entirely drowned out
by the greater army's
mobilized footsteps.
[NARRATOR] However...
Huh-huh, so part of the
Fourth Army's infantry
defeated a chariot?
Yes, my lord, but soon there'll
be an enemy counterattack.
Gong Yuan's army
is on the move.
I believe we should... withdraw.
[LORD BIAO] Look at this.
M-My lord?
It looks as though the battling
on every single front
is the same, but the pieces rock
the chessboard's balance
in many ways.
The movement of one
makes ten move,
and one thousand
can break ten thousand.
A small chain reaction
can lead to a conflagration
that brings the war
rapidly to its end.
And today, one place
on the board stands out.
When that happens, you know
there's something there.
That is exactly how war works.
Isn't it, gentlemen?
Oh?
Order the entire Fourth Army
cavalry to charge now!
Charge now!
Hey! It's the cavalry!
[WEI DAO] They... They finally
came, those cavalries!
[CAVALRY yelling]
[WEI DAO] We're saved!
[WEI PING] We survived!
[WEI SOLDIERS whimpering]
[yelling, screaming]
[BI yelling]
[XIN] Hey, Bi, my man!
[BI] Xin! I'm glad
you're all right!
[FU HUSHEN grunts]
[FU HUSHEN] I see.
This lot drove
Lord Biao to action.
[BI] Bring your horses
and crush them!
Foot soldiers, spread the
defensive wall to the right!
The chariot squad's
main force'll be back!
[FU HUSHEN] That over-serious
brigade commander
from the capital...
I see he's quick-witted.
But he obviously doesn't
understand the meaning
of the cavalry's charge.
What the general wants is to
turn the tables of this war.
Fu Hushen Brigade, attack!
[FU HUSHEN]
I congratulate you on surviving
Wei's chariot attack!
Not only that, but you
launched a counterattack!
That makes you the pride of your
battalion, and the pride of Qin!
You're men who, in despair,
escaped the jaws of death!
You can overcome
even deadlier dangers!
[gasping]
Our battalion will go to the
enemy's infantry and take the
head of Gong Yuan Wei's,
second-in-command
who sits atop that hill!
Prepare to charge!
[gasping]
[FU HUSHEN] Foot soldiers
follow behind the cavalry!
If you don't want to die,
run with all you've got!
Come on, I thought we were saved
when the cavalry
came to join all of us!
Why do we have to push
our luck like that again?!
[WEI DAO groans]
We've got less than a hundred
men--left out of a thousand.
It's impossible to get
through that massive army
of ten thousand like this!
Nope, not necessarily.
What do you mean, Xin?
Do you think we have a chance?
Huh? Oh, nah, I have a feeling.
[WEI PING] Excuse me?!
[QIANG LEI] Xin is right.
We have a chance.
[ALL] Huh?
[QIANG LEI]
The enemy has momentum
from coming down the hill,
and they'll act fast.
Our path upstream
against that tide
will be an incredibly cruel one.
[QIANG LEI] But at that speed,
we won't have to
cross swords for long.
Yeah, yeah,
exactly what he said!
If we get through them,
the hill will be wide open.
We can take the enemy
in one swoop!
And then, this battle
will be ours!
As I said,
it's a cruel path
Anyone who pauses
will then be met with a
certain death.
What's gotten into you?
You've been mighty talkative
since the chariots came here.
I thought you said
you hated talking?
[QIANG LEI] I'm just like you.
[XIN] Huh?
I simply cannot
afford to die here.
Uhh... is that so?
Anyway, that settles it!
I'll drive off the enemy!
Okay, now prepare to charge!
[WEI PING] You don't
give orders, moron!
Commander Fu Hushen,
one of the foot soldiers
is riding like a cavalryman.
[FU HUSHEN] Leave him to it.
[FU HUSHEN]
That brat must be the one
who's been leading
what's left of the men.
He should come in
handy at some point.
[NARRATOR] On the front lines,
Qin's 1,000-man cavalry
was sorely testing
Wei's 40,000-man army.
The raid ordered by Lord Biao
had indeed succeeded.
[LIAISON OFFICER 19B] Still,
they're outnumbered.
They're sure to be
pushed back eventually!
[LIAISON OFFICER 19A] A report!
The chariot squadron is
attacking the Fourth Army again!
Now order the First and
Second Army cavalries...
[LORD BIAO] ...to storm the
Fourth Army's battlefield!
[NARRATOR] Lord Biao thought it
was the fight's moment of truth,
and this was his swift response.
[FU HUSHEN] Go! Go!
Don't stop for anything!
What is that
battalion doing now?!
They're going too far!
That's Fu Hushen.
He probably means to break
through the enemy's center,
and storm that hill!
[BI] That's crazy!
They'll be wiped out even
before they make it!
[laughing]
If he wants to die,
leave him to it!
I can't do that!
Bi Battalion!
Form a wedge formation,
and cut into enemy lines!
Back up the Fu Hushen
Battalion's advance!
[XIN yells]
[XIN] You okay, Ze?
Y-Yes, yes I am.
I'm managing!
It's a big help that you're
taking the lead, Xin!
[WEI DAO] Darn it, Commander
Fu Hushen is going too fast!
Who does he think
we foot soldiers are?!
[FU HUSHEN yells]
Foot soldiers were never
important to him to begin with!
[WEI DAO yells]
Dao, are you okay?!
I'm okay!
Keep running!
Right now, just keep--
[WEI PING gasps]
--[XIN screams]
--[BOTH gasp]
[WEI PING whimpers]
Brother!
[slashing,
weapons clanging]
[XIN gasps]
[WEI SOLDIERS scream]
You did...
Wei Ping, get up! Quickly!
If we don't hurry,
we'll be left surrounded by
the enemies, and we'll die!
It's okay! I'll cut us a path!
--[WEI DAO] Xin!
--[ZE GUI] Xin!
[XIN] We're gonna catch up
with our commander!
No more tripping, Wei Ping!
G-Got it!
[XIN yells,
WEI SOLDIERS screaming]
[XIN] Qiang Lei...
I thought he
was just brains,
but he's pretty good
with a sword, too.
There's more to
this guy than it seems.
[XIN grunts]
[XIN] Fine by me.
Looks like I can forget
about the rear
and concentrate on
what's in front of me!
[FU HUSHEN yells]
[screaming]
[FU HUSHEN] What, Wei soldiers,
is that all you've got?
I will give whatever it takes
to win this battle!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
We... We got through!
[FU HUSHEN] The guards stationed
halfway up haven't noticed us.
How many men left?
[SUBORDINATE 19A]
About forty, Sir.
[FU HUSHEN] All right.
[XIN] Hold on there.
[FU HUSHEN] Huh...?
Five more makes
that forty-five.
[FU HUSHEN] This boy cut his way
through that death trap
even after falling
behind us... But how?
We'll now storm this hill
and kill General Gong Yuan!
--[XIN growls]
--[SOLDIERS whimper]
Know that our battle
will be a critical one
to Qin's ultimate victory!
I am aware that you have
used up all of your strength!
But I won't go soft on you!
Anyone who doesn't
make it to the top,
I'll kill you later myself!
[SOLDIERS groan]
[FU HUSHEN] However,
whoever makes to the top
will have the
chance to be honored
for their distinguished service
and effort during battle!
Honored and rewarded.
[gasping]
[FU HUSHEN] The ones
stationed on this hill
are Wei's highest officers.
And the prices of their heads
are extremely high, of course.
Kill one of them and
I pledge ten times that reward!
[XIN gasps]
Brother, you and I could be the
village heroes if we succeed!
[WEI PING laughs]
I sure can't turn that down!
[FU HUSHEN] Hey, kid!
Leave your squad
and come to the front.
We need all the
cavalrymen we can get.
[gasping]
All ri-- Ah!
[XIN] But if I do that,
Ze and the othe--
[WEI PING] Just go, idiot!
You don't have to worry
about us anymore, cavalryman.
It's very clear that a five-man
squad isn't enough for you, Xin.
You're gonna be one of
the world's greatest generals.
Go out there and
outdo them all, Xin!
[FU HUSHEN]
Ah, good dust clouds.
If we get behind the rock,
they won't see us.
Go, and make sure all the men
stay out of sight and hearing.
Yes!
Hey, kid.
Do you want a great achievement?
Of course.
[FU HUSHEN] Then cut your way
straight through
and don't look back.
Hey! Wh-What are you doing?!
[QIANG LEI] Let me
ride for a while.
Say what?!
Looks like it's time to go.
Hey! Listen when I'm talking!
Fu Hushen Battalion, move!
[XIN] What do you want?
Oh, I know.
You're just coming with me
to steal my glory away!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing's wrong.
[horse whinnies,
XIN shouts]
Be careful!
Shut up!
[BI yells]
[screaming]
[HEAD OF THE DEFENSE 19A] Who
knows what could be happening
in that cloud...
We still have far
greater numbers than they do.
Nothing that happens will
affect the big picture.
In the end, our generals
are simply better than theirs.
The outcome of this
battle has always been
a foregone conclusion.
Soon, this dust will settle
and the soldiers of Qin
will become extinct.
Is this the power of Qin
known as the nation
of tigers and wolves?
I'm so very disappointed!
[gasping]
Enemy atta--!
[GUARD 19B] Enemy's attack!
There are more of these
guys than we thought!
[FU HUSHEN] Don't let their
numbers distract you!
Let's break through!
If we each kill ten each,
we'll pass them!
Gotcha!
Report for General Gong Yuan:
The defense halfway up
is at war with a Qin squad.
Fetch Huang Lixian!
[HUANG LIXIAN] I'm here.
Leave this to me.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Crap, we need
way more than ten each!
[QIANG LEI]
Leave the rear to me.
[XIN gasps]
[soldiers gasp]
[QIANG LEI] Go. Don't stop!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[GUARD 19A] What is it?
After him!
Is it the brat?!
[GUARD 19B]
Pin him in from both sides!
Leave him nowhere to run!
[yelling]
[GUARD 19A] I-Impossible!
Who is this brat?!
He's quick on his feet.
Let's go again!
Wait, do not underrate him.
--[GUARD 19B gasps]
--[GUARD 19A gasps]
[QIANG LEI]
Pum, pa-rum. Pum, pa-rum.
What's he saying?
Don't know!
[QIANG LEI]
Pum, pa-rum. Pum, pa-rum.
[XIN] We're through!
We'll break away
from the infantry here!
Cavalry, full speed ahead!
[XIN] Hey, hold on!
Without any cavalry support,
the guys in the rear'll--
No way!
You brought them to
buy us time at the rear?
Was that really your
plan all along, Sir?!
[FU HUSHEN] I thought
I told you not to look back!
But, Sir--
The vanguard, rear guard,
cavalry and infantry--
We're all at the door of death!
All of it is for our victory!
That's the way an
army really works!
[XIN growls]
[FU HUSHEN] And you don't have
time to worry about anyone else.
The vanguard always has
the cruelest path to travel!
[XIN grunts]
Hang in there!
Your legs are
everything right now!
Look! The top is right--
[SUBORDINATE 19A screams]
We've got archers ahead!
[FU HUSHEN] Scatter!
[XIN] You're kidding me!
[screaming]
[XIN grunting]
[XIN] Dammit!
Open fire!
[FU HUSHEN]
A crossbow squadron...
The sort of last defense a
damned tactician would like.
[FU HUSHEN]
But arrows are nothing.
Hit me all you want!
I won't even feel the pain!
Don't waver, men!
The top is right over there!
So that's their general.
Stop now! He's all mine.
[GONG YUAN] Don't get full of
yourselves, Qin suicide force.
A few dozen men
can make no difference
in the face of thousands!
[GONG YUAN]
War is never that easy.
[FU HUSHEN grunts]
[gasping]
Oh, S-Sir, wait a moment please!
[GONG YUAN growls]
[FU HUSHEN growls]
[FU HUSHEN chuckles]
[HUANG LIXIZN gasps]
[HUANG LIXIAN] Well,
will you still be able to laugh
with an arrow
through your brain?
[HUANG LIXIAN gasps]
I'm going to kill you!
[XIN yells]
[HUANG LIXIAN] A child soldier?
Pitiable...
Is Qin that short on soldiers?
An enemy is an enemy.
I'll shoot him dead!
[XIN grunts]
[HUANG LIXIAN] What? Impossible!
He could read the path
of my arrow?!
[HUANG LIXIAN] Then I'll
make a certain kill.
[XIN] I'm almost
at their unit, but...
I'm too close to read
the arrow's path!
[HUANG LIXIAN] Don't take
this personally, boy.
[XIN] If he doesn't hit a
vital organ, I could strike!
[HUANG LIXIAN]
I'll be the winner here!
[XIN shouts]
[XIN screams]
[HUANG LIXIAN]
You didn't reach me, kid.
This is what war is like!
[XIN gasps]
[horse whinnies]
[XIN snarls]
[XIN yells]
[HUANG LIXIAN gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[FU HUSHEN]
Gong Yuan, we meet at last.
[XIN growls]
[BI] General Wang Yi is here.
Something is about to happen!
[NARRATOR] An interloper
no one could have expected.
A fearless smile will
rock the battlefield!
Next Time: "Wang Yi Intrudes."