[LORD CHANGWEN] The great
general Liao was a woman.
What's more...
[LORD CHANGWEN] ...the woman
who was to be Wang Yi's wife.
[NARRATOR] The time:
The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
Xin, a nameless boy
who rose to the rank
of squadron commander,
is currently at the center
of a historic battle.
[NARRATOR]
A duel between Wang Yi
the commanding general of Qin,
and Pang Nuan the
commanding general of Zhao.
Their fated battle held sway
over the destiny
of the kingdom!
[ZHENG] Liao was to be
Wang Yi's wife, then?
No, one of
the six great generals
was a woman, you say?!
Yes. Now I shall
tell you everything I know.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
It was quite a long time ago
that I first met Liao.
Qin was in a
very heated conflict
with Zhao back then, as well.
While Qin had
emerged victorious
from the Battle of Changping,
another regional battle
could easily spark
at any time it seemed.
Such was the era.
[SOLDIER 36A] My young lord!
Lord Changwen!
Hm?
General Wang Yi's
army has just arrived!
[SOLDIER 36B] Wh-Why is that
army so oddly dressed?!
Hm. They're fools who
want to attract attention.
Hm?
[LORD CHANGWEN] A woman?
[LORD CHANGWEN] It was Liao,
the "woman soldier"
[LORD CHANGWEN] heralded as
a warrior whose beauty
belied a power
that put men to shame.
[LORD CHANGWEN] I was later
told she was the daughter
of one of Wang Yi's servants.
[ZHENG]
The daughter of a servant?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Yes.
Apparently she grew up
at Wang Yi's side
from a very young age
and honed her own battle skills.
I truthfully didn't
trust this, of course, but...
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Hm?
What's this commotion?
[SOLDIER 35A] Well, sir...
[LORD CHANGWEN] She killed
Zhao Lei and Guo Yao?!
[SOLDIER 35B] T-They were
the enemy's general
and his lieutenant!
[LORD CHANGWEN] After that,
we took the field together
several times.
Each time, I was made
acutely aware
of the power of
the girl called Liao.
[LIAO] Gramps!
You take their left flank!
Y-Young lord...
Don't call me Gramps.
Come on! To the left!
Yes, Sir!
[SOLDIERS yell]
--[LIAO] Huuuh!
--[SOLDIERS holler]
[ALL gasp]
[LORD CHANGWEN] She was a
veritable genius at war,
both in might and
in strategy as well.
And then...
[WANG YI] Our king
is so very fond of war
that he often visits the
front lines or so it appears.
He has a
long history of leaving
the Royal Court on campaigns.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Encouraging to hear.
Yes.
However the wars we men
wage in the field out there
are not the only
wars occurring.
There's another in Court.
Huh?
[LORD CHANGWEN] As Wang Yi
said, the Royal Court was
especially turbulent
in that age.
There were
endless bloody battles
over who would
be the successor.
And King Zhao's
many frequent absences
only added fuel to the fire.
And in that setting,
a beautiful court maiden
who was in the king's
particular favor
became pregnant.
However, she was of a
lower-class warrior family.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
She couldn't expect support
from any of
the king's concubines.
She had no hope of being able
to protect her child.
And so she chose...
Sorry... I'm sorry...
It is the only choice!
[WOMAN sobbing]
[WOMAN] I'm so sorry.
Please, grow up healthy...
Liao.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Liao's mother
put her child in a place
that she felt she
could really trust.
A place far from the Court
and with someone
whose rank allowed him
to understand the ordeal.
[LORD CHANGWEN] In other words,
Wang Yi's manor.
Her father had been Wang Yi's
father's brother in arms.
Still, to adopt the baby
would've attracted attention,
so she was
"the daughter of a servant."
[ZHENG] And to think
that general Liao was
King Zhao's daughter...
[LORD CHANGWEN sighs]
[ZHENG] Did the king
or Liao know the truth?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Of course they did not know.
However...
[SOLDIER 36C]
The High King has come!
Everyone fall in
on the double!
Don't just stand there!
[LORD CHANGWEN] One day,
King Zhao made a personal visit
to the battlefield
to show the Wang Yi Army
his thanks for leading Qin
to victory at Nan'an.
[KING ZHAO] Brilliant as ever,
Wang Yi, my prized sword!
I must admit, that for many
years I have been unable
to conquer this land of Nan'an!
You have truly done well!
I am so very grateful for
such undeserved praise, sire.
Hm? What's wrong, Liao?
[gasps] Uh. Mm.
Oh, it's nothing.
[KING ZHAO] So now, Wang Yi,
where is the fair one
whose name I hear
so often of late?
[KING ZHAO] Your trusted woman
soldier named Liao, I believe.
She achieved more
great things in this battle.
Where is she now?
Liao, step up.
Yes, sir!
Mmm.
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS murmur]
Liao, how old are you now?
S-Sixteen, sir.
I see...
I see. You've done
well for yourself.
[KING ZHAO] Liao...
You are my treasure,
just as Wang Yi is as well.
[KING ZHAO] And all the
rest of you, of course!
You shall be rewarded
upon your return!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
--[KING ZHAO] Wang Yi.
--[WANG YI] Sire.
[KING ZHAO]
We must speak later.
[WANG YI] Yes.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
From that day forward,
Liao always wore a mask
on the battlefield.
The official reason
was to disguise
the fact that she was
a woman before she became
famous in other kingdoms,
but it was also forbidden
[LORD CHANGWEN] for anyone
to speak of Liao's identity.
And almost immediately,
she officially took her place
among the generals.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Liao, do you have a moment?
[LIAO] Oh Gramps! Come in.
Who are you calling Gramps?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Are you all right?
Ooh.
Mm.
[LIAO] I'm finally coming
to terms with it, I think.
I'm not really angry or sad.
I mean by rights
I should have just been
killed right at birth.
[LIAO] I'm just
grateful to be alive.
Yeah. I've been
lying to you.
General Wang Yi
told you then?
Yes.
I see.
You always draw
the short straw.
I see why you
do not get promoted.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Be quiet, you.
[giggles]
You are a woman.
It would be a loss
to the military,
[LORD CHANGWEN] but you could
lay down your sword now.
That is going in
the wrong direction.
What would I have left
without my sword, huh?
I cannot be a noblewoman.
I am just a servant's daughter.
[LIAO] I won't quit.
But then, what will you gain
by continuing to fight?
I'll be the
world's greatest general!
Huh? Excuse me?
[laughing]
The reason I fight is a very
silly, childish promise
that I had made so many
years ago, you see.
[YOUNG LIAO] Lord Wang Yi!
Are you going to be one of
the world's greatest generals
and take lots of castles?
[WANG YI chuckles]
That's right.
Then I will become
a great general as well!
[YOUNG LIAO] And when I've
taken a hundred castles,
please, can you make me
your wife then?!
[WANG YI laughs]
All right.
[gasps in awe]
[LIAO] Ungh!
[LIAO] No telling me,
"Ugh, that's ridiculous!"
I was so incredibly
dead serious back then.
And I still am I think.
[LIAO] This is where
I truly belong, Gramps.
And I've got comrades here.
Plus from now on,
my father will be watching me.
I am doing this!
[LORD CHANGWEN] When Liao
launched an attack,
she didn't stop until
the enemy was annihilated.
Her relentless fighting
won her victory after victory.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Soon after
she became a general,
she was so powerful
that people said
she rivaled the
five great generals.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
And so Liao eventually became
the sixth great general.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Then some
time after that happened...
[SOLDIER 36D]
It's my lord Wang Yi!
General Wang Yi!
Lord Changwen as well!
[WANG YI] We're coming in.
It's been a
long time... Liao...
[WANG YI] Hm!
[chuckles]
Oh! My lord Wang Yi!
[LIAO] U-Um I...
I can do that
for myself, you know.
[WANG YI chuckles]
I used to bandage you
just like this
all the time, you see.
[LIAO]
And how long ago was that?
I am not a child anymore,
I will have you know!
We haven't seen each other
in a long time, have we now?
Unlike someone else,
those of us who have risen
quite high in rank
have little freedom anymore.
Yes.
[grunts]
[WANG YI] There.
S-Say now,
my dear lord...
[gasps] Never mind.
So what... brought you
all the way here then?
[WANG YI] I traveled here
from very far just to see you.
[WANG YI] No, I just jest.
I'm here for the next battle.
[LIAO] The next battle?
[WANG YI] It's been decreed that
the battle to conquer MNyáng
will be conducted by
our two joint armies here.
[gasps] You and I
will do it, my lord?
[LORD CHANGWEN] My army will be
there, too, in case you care.
[WANG YI]
I'll be second-in-command,
and you'll be
commanding general.
[WANG YI] Liao...
[inhales deeply, exhales]
[WANG YI] Soon you'll have
the last one, won't you?
The last one, he said?
What is it?
What's wrong, Liao?
[LIAO] I can't believe
he remembered.
And he even kept track...
You mean--
[YOUNG LIAO] And when
I've taken a hundred castles,
please, can you make me
your wife then?!
[WANG YI chuckles]
All right.
[LIAO] Yes I do.
The castle of MNyáng...
will be my hundredth.
[LORD CHANGWEN] But the night
before the raid on MNyáng,
he appeared suddenly.
That man, like a disaster in
human form, materialized.
[grunts]
[XIN] What's wrong?
General Wang Yi isn't moving!
[heart beating]
[heart beats rapidly]
[yells]
[XIN] Aah!
[YUAN] Wh-What's this?!
[PANG NUAN] This is it.
I came to fight
with this right now.
The power I fell to
nine years ago...
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I don't know what Pang Nuan
was trying to do that night
to be honest with you.
Cut down the soldiers
at our campground
and then attacked Liao after.
It was as if he were
merely seeking strength...
[PANG NUAN grunts]
[LIAO gasps]
[groans]
[SOLDIERS] General Liao!
General Liao!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS] General Liao!
General Liao!
[PANG NUAN] There is only one on
Earth whom the heavens fear.
That is only me.
[LIAO SOLDIER 36A]
General Wang Yi!
[PANG NUAN] There was
another here as well?!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[PANG NUAN] Whence came
this man's power?!
[yells]
[groans]
Fire!
[PANG NUAN groaning, gasping]
Why... Why did I lose?
Was it because
that woman wounded me?
[PANG NUAN]
No! It's irrelevant.
He was better than I was.
My battle strength
was no match for his!
Or so I fear!
Come, Wang Yi!
I came to crush thee
as thou art right now!
Pang Nuan, too...
And General Wang Yi is moving!
[commotion]
[PANG NUAN] It took my body
three years to fully heal.
Then I trained myself for
six years in the mountains.
And then, the man called
Li Mu appeared.
[PANG NUAN] I agreed to his
proposal because I was certain
that I had far surpassed
this man's ability!
[PANG NUAN] I'd reached heights
of warfare beyond any human!
Yet now, why?!
[PANG NUAN]
Why are his blows so heavy,
I cannot seem to even
repel his blade?!
What is this?!
From what source within him
flows this power?!
You seem quite
incredulous Pang Nuan.
Generals are a troublesome
lot I'll have you know.
[gasps]
[WANG YI] Since I was
thirteen I have been on
too many battlefields
for me to even count.
[WANG YI] I have lost
thousands of comrades
and slain millions
of enemies as well.
All their desires
snuffed out along with
the flame of life form an
incredible weighty mantle
on my shoulders.
Naturally, that includes
Liao's desires.
[WANG YI] I imagine that's
beyond the understanding
of a mountain recluse
like yourself.
The desires
of the dead are now
resting on his shoulders?
[XIN] Yeah, they are.
That's how we grow stronger,
and a general who's been
through it all is real strong.
[ALL gasp]
[PANG NUAN] A waste of breath.
Your kind hath always held
this misapprehension.
To "carry on"
the will of the dead
is but a fantasy
of the survivors.
A dead man quite simply
turneth to dust.
[PANG NUAN]
The defeated fall to Earth,
the victors
draw near to heaven.
That is the world's
only true law!
[WANG YI] Pang Nuan...
It would clearly appear that we
are at odds to the very end.
Of course we are!
[ZHENG]
Wang Yi deeply loved Liao,
and Pang Nuan killed her.
The Zhao army
made him general
precisely because of
the weight of that history.
Just in order to lure
Wang Yi into battle...
Your Highness?
[ZHENG] I can't believe it...
[ZHENG] The aim of
this five-day battle
has purely been
to kill Wang Yi.
[LORD CHANGWEN] But slaying
the enemy's general
is just one of
the basics of war, sire.
[ZHENG]
No, that's not what I mean.
This war is something
more bizarre than that.
They are not targeting
Wang Yi for victory's sake.
Taking Wang Yi's
head seems to be...
[ZHENG]
the purpose of this war.
It can't be...
[ZHENG]
It's not easy to believe.
But, if Li Mu has
strategized all of this
as thoroughly as I fear...
[weapons clanging]
[AIDE 36A]
We've been breached!
Third position is down!
Who is that man, exactly?!
Uh! Unbelievable...
[ZHAO ZHUANG] I had no idea
he was such a monster!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[ZHAO ZHUANG] You deliberately
kept him a secret,
didn't you, Wang Yi?!
[PANG NUAN] I am faster
and more powerful,
this time around as well!
His techniques cannot
even compare to mine!
Uh! General Wang Yi!
[PANG NUAN] So why then
can I not slay him?!
Deep in the afterworld,
[WANG YI] have Liao
explain to you why you lost!
[grunts]
Go!
Wh-What's wrong
with the general?
[XIN] Why did he stop?!
[WANG YI] Hmm.
Just wait.
Why has the ground
been rumbling nonstop?
[ZHENG] The trap that
you have been ensnared in
is indeed immensely great...
But do not die, Wang Yi!
[intense music plays]
You are earlier than...
I expected.
[ZHENG] Xin, change
Wang Yi's fate! Do it!
[WANG YI] It's been a long time
since my blood
stirred in my veins!
[NARRATOR] No way out!
The strange bird who shook
the world falls to Earth!
Next Time: "I Stand
on the Verge of Death."