[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Brigades 2 and 3 charge!
Time to eat a hole through the
Wang Yi infantry's flank!
[yelling]
[weapons clanging]
Sir, this is...
Oh yeah. This is all
going according
to General Wang Yi's plan!
[rumbling]
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] Your formation has
broken down quite a bit.
I'll be taking your
headquarters now, Zhao Zhuang.
[NARRATOR]
The time: The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
Xin, a nameless boy who rose to
the rank of squadron commander,
carried out a string of exploits
in the midst of fierce battle
that brought the
Qin army an advantage.
However, the enemy's commanding
general has appeared at last,
and has proven to be
beyond all imagination.
That man, said to have a
previous tie to Wang Yi,
is named Pang Nuan.
The war situation is on
the verge of great change!
[JIE SHEN]
My lord, it's Wang Yi.
Wang Yi is now
personally charging!
Say what?
[ZHAO SOLDIER 35B]
It's Wang Yi! Wang Yi is coming!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 35C] Infantry to
the front! Spears at the ready!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 35B]
Kill him!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[NARRATOR] When Wang Yi
personally spearheads an attack,
the men he leads
become utter demons.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARRATOR] Few could stop
them, but the Zhao army
with its formation in disarray,
had no chance at all.
The Wang Yi Army
cavalry is amazing!
Hurray for General Wang Yi!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Meng Wu's group,
which had essentially been
saved by Wang Yi's arrival,
watched quietly
from the sidelines.
Oh no...
What exactly is the matter, sir?
This absolutely is not
my lord's normal
fighting style...
What's going on?
Why is he rushing this battle
so aggressively like he is?
We're changing formations.
Move headquarters
back right now!
Sir. Fall back!
Fall back now!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Wang Yi is
taking the vanguard himself
this early in battle?
[ZHAO ZHUANG] There's no need
to head off our escape.
We have our backs to the cliffs.
Why is he in such a hurry?
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Don't tell me that he knows?!
[LI MU]
Once you are in the mountains,
lure General Wang Yi over here.
The soldiers I'll have
ready will go there
to ambush him.
A pretty simple plan.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Li Mu, rather, High General.
[LI MU] Yes? I still can't get
used to being called that.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] I can understand
everything that you are saying,
General, but it rests on
far too many assumptions.
Frankly, I'm not persuaded.
To begin with, what are the
chances that Wang Yi will appear
when we invade Qin?
[GONGSUN LONG] And sir,
even assuming Wang Yi comes,
I'm afraid I can't believe
your "sure-fire strategy"
will work on him.
Wang Yi is unpredictable.
You say you will
join the battle late,
but Wang Yi is sure to
notice you moving an army
of that massive size south,
like you are planning to.
He won't notice it.
After all, you two haven't
noticed, have you?
[BOTH gasp]
An army of 130,000
gathered north and crushed
a Xiongnu army of 200,000.
What? That cannot be...
Impossible! I haven't heard
any word of it at all!
[LI MU] Because I'm
suppressing the information.
Though it would be fair
to call it "manipulating."
On that note, I've already
leaked to General Wang Yi
that Pang Nuan will become
Zhao's commanding general.
[LI MU]
That is bound to make him come.
You see, they have a history.
History?
[LI MU]
Fear not, my good sirs. Listen.
I guarantee you...
that we can win this war.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] This new Great,
calling himself Li Mu,
appeared out of nowhere,
yet everything he predicted
has come to pass.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] On his orders, no
one but myself and Gongsun Long
has been told of
the northern army.
Not even our own
commanding officers
like Li Bai and Feng Ji knew...
It's inconceivable that
Wang Yi could know.
Attention all,
infantry units, now charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
The left army's advancing!
Say what?! Oh, darn!
So now that we're
done being decoys,
we've got nothing to do?!
[COMBAT COMMANDER 35C]
Foot soldiers! Fall in now!
[WEI PING]
Huh?
Listen up!
We are all about to charge
into enemy headquarters!
The time starts right now!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Ha! Now that's more like it!
[JIE SHEN] Ahead of us, the
enemy infantry is advancing.
The entire Qin army
is poised for attack.
[ZHAO SUBORDINATE 35A]
I can't believe they're taking
such a gamble when the
battle has only just begun!
Has Wang Yi lost his mind?!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] It's much too
unnatural for this to happen.
He does know Li Mu's strategy!
[NARRATOR] On the contrary, Wang
Yi did not know the strategy.
That's how perfect Li Mu's
suppression of
information had been.
However, by this time,
Wang Yi had predicted a Zhao
ambush in the works as well.
He sensed the truth
as he arrived
at the site of this showdown.
On the face of it,
this bell-shaped terrain
seemed to have Zhao trapped,
but if a different Zhao force
were to come in from behind,
Qin's army would be
the one trapped.
At that very moment, though,
Qin's combat commanders
in the mountains,
were holding off Zhao's
various other forces.
Push them all back!
We defend this land
to the death!
[NARRATOR] Thanks to these
commanders' furious fighting,
at a glance, it seemed
that no Zhao force
could get behind Wang Yi.
However, there was
an unseen enemy
somewhere in
these mountains.
When Wang Yi concluded this,
it answered the
suspicions he'd harbored
since Zhao headquarters
had entered the mountains.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
From there, he extrapolated.
[NARRATOR] Ever since
his headquarters' flags
had gone out of sight,
Wang Yi had searched for
the enemy's location.
His search party had not come
across the Zhao ambushers.
This was no surprise;
he knew how thoroughly
his enemy strategized.
These reinforcements would have
dispersed and hidden themselves,
outside of his search radius.
This meant the mountain
terrain worked against Zhao
at the moment.
[NARRATOR] Wang Yi felt
confident that he could
settle the battle before
the ambush party arrived.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] Whoever is behind this
plan, it's an interesting one.
Still, you weren't careful
enough in the final stages.
If I choose to...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WANG YI] ...I can slaughter
Zhao Zhuang's army
in an instant.
[ZHENG] Yang Duanhe
told us of a Zhao army
we had no knowledge of.
This ambush must be
Li Mu's primary objective.
If I can see that from
here in Xianyang,
Wang Yi would have
already realized it.
[LORD CHANGWEN] This Li Mu
individual has no name
for himself.
I'm sure he can't outdo
Wang Yi's battle experience
and instinct.
[ZHENG]
What bothers me though is this:
Why exactly is Pang Nuan
Zhao's commanding general?
If you are indeed right
that he is not the sort
to lead an army of men,
isn't the rank of commanding
general disproportionately high?
You're right, sir.
I'm unsure...
Could Li Mu have
known everything
when he chose him
to lead for us?
[JIE SHEN]
What's the matter with you?!
Halt, Wang Yi!
Move the Three Greats flag!
Send the rear force
to the front and defend...
We withdraw!
[ZHAO SUBORDINATE 35A]
Zhao Zhuang, sir!
What now?
G-General Pang Nuan...
General Pang Nuan is missing!
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
What?! Jie Shen!
Where is General Pang Nuan?!
[JIE SHEN]
I-I-I don't know, sir!
He was here just a moment ago.
[ZHAO ZHUANG gasps]
Don't tell me...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
The units near headquarters
are in a formation change!
We have to stop
him here or then...
I know that! But how can
we stop that monstrosity?!
Commander Qing Yu!
Wang Yi is coming!
Your orders, Commander?
[QING YU growls] Wang Yi, the
cursed great general of Qin...
He's worse than the rumors say!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[WANG YI chuckles]
[SOLDIERS yell]
Wh-What's that?
[TENG SUBORDINATE 35A]
Sir, what's that sound?
[JIE SHEN] What's that? There's
shouting at the front lines!
It's General Pang Nuan.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Your Highness...
Do you suggest Li Mu
deliberately gave Pang Nuan
this rank, knowing of his
history with Wang Yi?
[ZHENG] He's more likely
a "commanding general"
in name only.
In truth, he's the bait
to lure Wang Yi
to the battlefield.
[ZHENG] Wang Yi, the last of
the six great generals...
A man feared as the
"Strange Bird of Qin,"
yet once thought to have
abandoned the field for good.
[ZHENG] But, this Pang
Nuan drew him back
into the field once again.
What could drive
Wang Yi to that?
Yes, I was right, indeed.
[ZHENG]
Lord Changwen.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Sire.
Who was Liao, the great
general felled by Pang Nuan?
Who was he, exactly?
Do I assume correctly that Liao
was someone quite special
to Wang Yi, then?
[WANG YI]
Nine years, huh?
I'm glad we meet
at last, Pang Nuan.
How have you been?
[WANG YI]
I must say, you surprised me.
I thought you were dead,
and yet suddenly,
here you are before me,
commanding over
100,000 troops of men.
Since when are you Zhao's clown?
I care not what
means I employ.
All that mattereth
is my godliness!
Wang Yi, I shall
kill thee here
and show the heavens
that I am a god of war!
I am relieved to see that
you have not changed.
So now...
[WANG YI] Shall I take
my turn and declare
that I will kill you here
and bid farewell to the
fetters of my past then?
[WANG YI] Well?
[PANG NUAN]
Here I come, Wang Yi!
I shall kill thee!
[WANG YI chuckles]
It is I who shall
kill you, Pang Nuan!
Th-The duel between
our commanders
is about to begin!
[ZHAO SOLDIERS]
Pang Nuan! Pang Nuan!
[WANG YI SOLDIERS]
My lord!
Th-This is just...
You make this
surprisingly easy,
dear Pang Nuan.
[SOLDIER gasps]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[XIN]
What's got them so fired up?!
It's General Wang Yi
and Pang Nuan?
It's gotta be.
Dammit, I need to be over there!
[COMBAT COMMANDER 35C]
Infantry, keep moving!
Remember, our goal is to
take enemy headquarters!
To slay Zhao Zhuang,
the man commanding their army!
All troops forward! March!
Xin, sir?
[WEI PING]
Xin!
[XIN growls]
Qiang Lei.
Who's stronger,
General Wang Yi or Pang Nuan?
It's Pang Nuan.
That is just a load of bull!
How could you say that?!
You call yourself
a Qin warrior?!
Then don't ask me ever again.
We all lost a lot of
comrades because of him.
He is right.
We have every right to watch
him die there then as well.
Do you not agree?
Yeah.
As I remember,
you said that we were
a very special unit directly
under general Wang Yi, right?
The only orders we got
from the general
were for the feint!
I believe we're free now.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Right! Fei Xin Force,
follow me right now!
[QIN SOLDIER 35C]
He's strong...
General Wang Yi is
stronger than Pang Nuan!
[QIN SOLDIER 35D] No one
is a match for our master!
Huang Lou Sir, this is--
Oh yes...
It's just like watching the
battle between General Liao
and Pang Nuan nine years ago.
It was exactly the same then:
Pang Nuan drew out his
opponent's full power
before he got...
genuinely serious.
[PANG NUAN growls]
[PANG NUAN] Don't hold back
on me now, Wang Yi!
Surely thou art far
better than this.
Of course I am.
This battle is insane!
Their weapons are
moving too fast to see!
So, Pang Nuan
has a slight lead now...
My lord!
Look!
Our accursed enemy
is bleeding right now!
Yes! General Pang Nuan
is strong.
He's so strong!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
We will take headquarters
straight back!
[JIE SHEN]
Don't break your ranks!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] To think
Wang Yi would take part
in a duel like this...
[SUBORDINATE 35C]
Sir Zhao Zhuang!
General Pang Nuan
is in the middle of a duel
with Wang Yi.
Should we really pull
back to headquarters?
The winner of this duel
will win the entire war!
What meaning is there in this?!
It's just not that simple.
Don't forget the
pinnacle of our army
isn't General Pang Nuan,
but our headquarters, with me
at the very center of it.
Even assuming that
Pang Nuan fells Wang Yi,
if our headquarters
has fallen as well,
we won't be able to
counter Qin's moves.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Conversely, even
assuming Pang Nuan is felled,
if our headquarters is intact,
Zhao can regroup.
What you need to
understand is that for Qin
to win this whole war,
they have to fell us first.
And Wang Yi knows
that quite well of course.
That's why his cavalry
is coming for us
instead of rushing to him.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Take care.
They're tough opponents.
[FEIXIN FORCE 35A]
Er, excuse us...
Maybe it wasn't fair
to the other foot soldiers
for us to come watch
instead of fighting.
Don't be stupid, Wei Ping.
If things go wrong,
the bloodiest fighting
will happen exactly right here.
Y-You're right...
Who really cares about that?
Right now, the important thing
is the generals' duel!
[XIN] General Wang Yi
seems to be losing?!
That Pang Nuan...
Wound my body and the pain
just vanisheth with time.
But, wound my soul and the pain
never fully vanisheth,
no matter how many years pass.
Wang Yi, it must be
the same for thee.
That is why thou art here!
Rage is power.
Remember how thy comrade
died that very--
Drew blood!
General Pang Nuan!
[QIN SOLDIERS] General
Wang Yi! General Wang Yi!
[XIN] "Comrade"?
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI]
Rest easy, Pang Nuan.
My wound has not healed either.
I am sure you will be
very happy to know.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Very well, Sire.
I shall tell you everything.
There is a reason as to why
so uncommonly little
is known about Liao.
King Zhao forbid
anyone to speak of it.
[ZHENG] King Zhao?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Liao's secret was a truly
highly complicated one, you see.
What's important at
the moment, however,
is that Liao was someone
dearly important to Wang Yi
personally at that time.
[LORD CHANGWEN] The great
general Liao was a woman.
What's more...
The woman who was
to be Wang Yi's wife.
[WANG YI] Soon you'll have
the last one, won't you, Liao?
[NARRATOR]
A future trampled underfoot.
When the blood can't
be shed in tears
it comes back as a bloodbath.
Next Time:
"Wang Yi and Liao."