Xin, who is this guy?
Keep quiet.
[MU TA] You'd be the one who cut
down that hooded assassin, yes?
And so, what is it to you?
I won't kill you the easy way.
Just prepare yourself,
little fella.
You're probably angry
your friend got killed,
but give it up.
An old guy like you
can't beat me.
Qin people just do not
understand anything at all.
But even among them, your
stupidity truly stands out.
First, the Vermilion Slayer
wasn't my friend.
Also, killing one of your kind
is actually incredibly easy
and simple for me, Mu Ta.
[MU TA]
For example, like this...
[XIN]
What's that?!
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
A storm of war and
strife had been raging
across the entirety of China
over the unthinkable
span of five centuries.
Desire. Pleasure.
Suffering. Terror.
Unmistakably in this
world rife with cruelty
lived a dragon...
...a dragon named "the era."
Scorched by that
dragon's flames,
more than 100 nations fell,
one after another,
winnowed away, into seven
that now remained.
These were Yan, Qi, Zhao,
Wei, Han, Chu...
...and Qin.
These 7 large kingdoms,
as though each was trying
to devour the others,
lunged at their enemies'
throats again and again
with ambition-fueled swords.
This was the era of the Spring
and Autumn Warring States.
Now from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
the great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[XIN panting]
Hm, you have a real
talent for combat.
Your body's
responding instinctively
to Mu Ta's poison darts.
Poison darts?
But you can relax, young fellow.
Since you killed the Vermilion
Slayer, I won't use a blow-dart.
[XIN]
What?
[MU TA] That Vermilion Slayer
upset me before, you see.
He insulted Mu Ta, and called
my blow-darts "cowardly."
He didn't seem to
recognize Mu Ta's ability.
Blow-darts are the ultimate
weapon of my people,
"the Basha of Yue."
But Qin people are stupid
and don't understand that,
and I can't help that.
[MU TA] I'll show you
strength without a blow-dart.
I'll shred you, who was
somewhat strong
than the Vermilion Slayer
you killed...
...with these axes,
and show Mu Ta's might
to Qin fools who don't
get my sheer prowess!
[XIN]
He's fast!
Xin!
[MU TA yells]
[XIN]
But not faster than me!
Huh?
[XIN gasps]
Xin!
Damn you...
[MU TA] You dodged Mu Ta's
attack and wounded me.
I find that quite surprising.
As a great warrior
of the Basha,
I can't let this
stand whatsoever.
With the pride of the
Basha as a whole at stake,
I'll spill out your
innards, little fella,
and I will kill you.
[XIN]
Try it, man with square head!
Foolish brat!
[DIAO gasps]
All three of the little
heads I seek right here...
Zheng! Pursuit's here!
A killer of Cheng Jiao.
Why the heck are you
just standing here?
Hurry and go stand by Xin,
or he's gonna be killed!
Do you need a hand?
[XIN grunts]
Nope! Not a chance.
Just hold on a sec!
That old man's extremely
good, understand?
I know that. I was watching.
But if he can't win this
fight even with nine lives,
it won't be enough for
what's coming. Xin!
That's easy to say, but...
he is really scary.
[DIAO screams]
Wait!
Does "three little heads"
include me? M-M-My head!
You three...
Are you making fun of
Mu Ta behind my back?
That upsets me.
[XIN growls]
[MU TA yells]
The brat has good eyes.
[XIN] What is this?!
Crap, I can't see!
[MU TA]
You're mine.
[XIN yells]
Xin!
What a shocker.
So he managed to block
it with his sword...
Oww...
Feeling weak?
[DIAO]
Huh? Something's strange...
Like Xin's... lost his edge.
He looks smaller than when he
fought the Vermilion Slayer.
This has grown quite
tiresome for Mu Ta.
Die!
Don't back off, Xin!!
[XIN gasps]
[XIN]
Back off? You're saying...
...I was intimidated? Me?
Your strong nature
is your weapon!
That I know!
[XIN yells]
[XIN groans]
[DIAO gasps] They're hurt,
but Xin looks different.
He's freed from the spell
of Mu Ta's killer instinct.
Now, the real contest begins.
[SI SHI] I'm sorry for summoning
you so early in the morning,
but there's something
that concerns me.
I beg for your understanding.
It regards what you
delivered to us last night
General Wang Yi;
Lord Changwen's head.
[MEN gasp]
With the severity of the wounds,
we can't verify that
it is Lord Changwen.
I'd request a detailed telling
of how you specifically
engaged with Lord Changwen
and how he ended up
in this gruesome state.
--General...
[WANG YI] Mm-hm?
What is it?
[WANG YI] Then you must have
major doubts on me, Si Shi?
I-I do not doubt you whatsoever.
It is simply my duty
to understand the
circumstances, General.
[WANG YI]
Mm-hm.
If that's how you put it...
Very well.
It's not a particularly
interesting war-story, though.
[WANG YI] Please do wait
for us, Lord Changwen.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I'll hold back Wang Yi.
You men protect
His Highness. Go!
Lord Changwen!
Forgive me, Piao.
[WANG YI]
Why, you've come, Lord Changwen!
[LORD CHANGWEN yells]
Wang Yi!
[WANG YI] Riding side-by-side
like this brings back memories,
huh, Lord Changwen?
We're true enemies now.
You think I'll fall
into reminisce?
Wang Yi, you were
never interested
in the strife between
Lü Buwei and Jie Shi.
Why have you suddenly
got involved?
[WANG YI]
Just seeking out a fight
that can get my blood all astir.
You're speaking nonsense!
All of you people
would understand.
[WANG YI] Since Qin
fell under the control
of Lü Buwei and Jie Shi,
war became horribly dull,
and I really miss the days
of King Zhao unbearably,
to be honest.
You know the feeling,
don't you, huh?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Certainly in today's battles,
money and goods circulate
behind the scenes,
and events often
directly profit Lü Buwei.
But that should have
no bearing upon you
on the battlefield at all.
Oh, how you jest.
Do you think that
sort of cynical warfare
gets my blood boiling?
My heart is so incredibly
delicate, you see...
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Are you saying fighting
a mere civil servant
like myself does, in fact,
get your blood boiling?
It's possible, you know...
[WANG YI] You were once
known as a warrior
who excelled on the field
and had an actual backbone.
At a chance to trade
blows with that man...
...one might get
hot-blooded for a change.
[GUARDIAN 5A]
My lord!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Whoa!
Victory is ours, Wang Yi!
We're here! It's Shu Da Hill!
[SI SHI]
Shu Da Hill, you say?
What is that?
And what happened next?
Truly some handiwork
befitting his manliness.
Shu Da Hill is really the ideal
place for concealing troops.
That's exactly right, Wang Yi.
[COMMANDER 5A] Unit 1, Unit 2!
Protect His Highness's carriage!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[COMMANDER 5B] Unit 3, Unit 4!
Let's aid Lord Changwen!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
So you're saying Lord Changwen
mobilized all his
personal troops.
In those circumstances,
how did you...
But isn't it painfully obvious?
Shu Da Hill is an ideal place
for concealing troops.
I'd prepared my own
ambush, you see.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Wh-What's that?!
[WANG YI]
Well, Lord Changwen...
...we've ourselves a battle!
And for you,
a very special tête-à-tête
with yours truly!
[WANG YI]
Well, the result was--
which I handed over to you.
Bad of me, though, to render
his face unrecognizable.
Still, those who
fight with Wang Yi
generally do end up with their
heads in total shambles, huh?
If you think I'm lying...
Shall we try it with a
few heads around here?
May I at least ask
you one question?
As many as you like.
What is it exactly that you
want now, General Wang Yi?
I can't believe someone
like you would join us
merely from a desire for
Lord Changwen's lands.
[WANG YI] A world that
excites and sets nerves in.
[SI SHI gasp]
[WANG YI]
Or failing that,
at least a hot,
blood-stirring fight!
[WANG YI]
Of course, I jest.
Such a world really does
no longer exist now,
but however...
If such a world could come
about, though I would be...
[WANG YI]
...beside myself with joy.
[SOLDIER 5A]
Here's one!
[CAPTAIN] No mistake. That
belongs to Mu Ta. He's close.
Right! Let's keep on, huh?
Captain, what is
the matter, sir?
I must be imagining
things... Let's move!
[SOLDIER 5B]
Captain!
[SOLDIER 5C] The mountain folk?
[SOLDIER 5A] What's this?!
[SOLDIER 5A]
No! Soldiers!
[CAPTAIN] That's madness. A
hostile force this deep in here?
A hostile... there aren't
forces hostile to us.
But... But you are...
[XIN yells]
[MU TA yells]
Oh, wow! That Xin
suddenly got stronger!
When he fought
the Vermilion Slayer,
Xin lost himself in his rage.
It's very likely that he
himself doesn't recall.
So one could call this battle
he's fighting right now
his first genuine
clash of blades.
Oh, so this is really
his first, then.
[ZHENG] Apparently,
him and Piao went all-out
more than a thousand times.
[DIAO]
A thousand?
[ZHENG] From that, he has sword
skills to equal most warriors.
But there's one thing
he hasn't cultivated:
The strength of spirit
to throw back
a killer intent flung at him.
But Xin realized he was being
pushed back by killer intent,
and he charged.
That assassin is good,
but who Xin's becoming
will no doubt handle this.
He will? He'll handle himself?
[MU TA]
This little fella...
Even this bloodied his
heart remains unbroken.
On the contrary...
[XIN yells]
[MU TA] On the contrary, he
keeps coming on and coming on!
[MU TA] He's getting...
stronger and stronger!
[XIN]
What's this?
What's this I feel?
[XIN]
My body...
It's like it's gotten lighter!
[XIN]
This again?
Your visual tricks won't work
anymore! I see it all clearly!
[MU TA screams]
[XIN grunting]
[MU TA] He's getting
sharper and sharper...
[MU TA]
This little fella...
...is fearsome.
[XIN]
I did it.
I did it now!
He did it!
[DIAO]
Don't push it.
I'm gonna tend to
your wounds right away.
[MU TA grunts]
[XIN, DIAO gasp]
As a Basha warrior,
I cannot simply
end things like this.
I will take this King's
life before I go.
Run now, Zheng!!
Prepare to die.
[XIN gasps]
What would you do to
His Highness? Scoundrel!
[LORD CHANGWEN grunts]
[MU TA groans]
Why, you are...
[DIAO]
Xin!
[LORD CHANGWEN] I claimed
your means of escape
were foolproof...
[LORD CHANGWEN] The
responsibility for everything
that has happened is only mine.
Order it, and right now
I'll smash my head on
these rocks and end it all.
First... firstly though,
above all else...
I'm glad you're safe!
The same for you.
[LORD CHANGWEN sobbing]
[SOLDIERS]
Oh, your Highness...
[XIN]
Are you kidding me?!
What's to be glad about?
You, and you, and you!
With all your carrying on!
Listen, old man!
[XIN]
Piao is... Piao is...
Piao is now dead!
[XIN] So tell me...
How can I become a general?
[NARRATOR] He's set to stake
his life for his advancement.
He won't forget the dream
he swore to his friend.
Next time: The Path
to Becoming a General