[ceremonial music plays]
[NARRATOR] Four month
after the war with Wei,
after Xin made a splash
in his first campaign
on his quest to become
a great general...
[NARRATOR] Qin sent a great
force of over 200,000 men
to march against Han,
another kingdom located
on its eastern border.
Go! The ladder's been put up!
[SOLDIER 25C] Climb!
[SOLDIERS groaning, yelling]
[NARRATOR] Under the command
of General Meng Ao,
this army was composed of
Qin's most famous warriors.
They stormed Han's castles
one after another
and the people of Qin were
overjoyed to hear the news
of the quick succession
of victories.
[cheering]
[gasps]
Dad! I see
a bunch of banners!
[laughs]
Let's have a look!
[NARRATOR] However, in the
midst of this rejoicing...
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] ...an unprecedented
danger was bearing down
upon the kingdom of Qin.
[NARRATOR] Ancient China.
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of
a nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yells]
[MESSENGER 25A]
I have an urgent report!
Open the gate!
[LORD CHANGWEN] You say
Zhao's forces are invading us?!
[MESSENGER 25A] Yes, sir!
[ZHENG] The Kingdom of Zhao?!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
What was their point of entry?
[MESSENGER 25A]
MNyg, to the northeast!
[LI SI] How many soldiers?
[MESSENGER 25A]
A hundred thousand!
That many?
[MESSENGER 25A] We got
a report of a signal fire
requesting
reinforcements at MNyg,
but the rain quickly
put it out.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
We're powerless...
General Meng Ao is off invading
Han with 200,000 of our men.
[LORD CHANGWEN] That means
there's no standing force
in the kingdom
we can deploy now!
[LI SI] First MNyg,
and then MNyáng after it...
If Zhao manages to
take the border castles
on our front lines,
their armies will be able to
surge straight into
the heart of the kingdom,
with no way to stop them!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
What on Earth do we do?
We don't even have enough
time to call back
General Meng Ao's forces.
[LORD CHANGWEN] They've already
penetrated too deeply into Han!
[sighs]
[ZHENG] This is no time
for us to sit by idly!
[MEN gasp]
Issue an emergency draft
of men from our heartland
including those exempted
from conscription
for the war with Han.
Raise a hundred
thousand troops!
We'll send them
to relieve the front lines!
[LÜ BUWEI] One moment,
Your Majesty.
Such important matters
must be decided properly
in a council of war.
[LÜ BUWEI] We must first
summon our military's
high commander,
Lord Changping.
Make him be quick, then!
We are facing
the kingdom of Zhao.
[ZHENG] And in case
you've forgotten,
we were the ones who buried
400,000 of their soldiers alive
in the Battle of Changping!
You think they've forgotten?
[ZHENG] The hatred Zhao's people
hold for the kingdom of Qin
is implacable and unstoppable.
Unless we hurry,
every last man, woman,
and child in our borderlands
will be put to the sword.
[NARRATOR] An emergency draft
order was immediately issued,
and the conscripted men
set out for the battlefield.
[NARRATOR]
Here, in Cheng Hu Village...
[WEI PING]
C'mon, let's go, guys!
[YOU LI] Hey, Wei Dao!
Bring home a nice
big bounty, 'kay?
[WEI PING snickers]
[DONG MEI] Wei Ping...
Dong Mei! You came!
Please promise me
you'll come home safely.
Dong Mei...
[WEI PING]
Wait for me, Dong Mei!
Wait for me!
[XIN groaning]
Hey, Yuan.
How long's it been
since I got
kicked off the cliff?
[YUAN] About...
four months, I think?
[XIN] I see.
That took a little bit
longer than expected, huh?
[STATELESS PEOPLE]
Long live Lord Xin!
Long live Lord Yuan!
[XIN grunts]
This time I'll get General
Fatlips to train me himself!
I've earned it, dammit.
It's time to collect!
Ta-da!
Hmmm...
[XIN] Hold it right there,
General Wang Yi!
[YUAN] Xin, sir, please don't
give orders to generals!
[XIN] What do you mean my
training is gonna hafta wait?!
We managed to conquer
the stateless area
just like you asked!
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] Circumstances
have changed a bit
in the meantime, you see.
[XIN] What is that
supposed to mean?
[WANG YI] It means
that war has broken out.
What?! A war...
is going on now?!
Then are we all heading
straight to the battlefield?
Ha ha! Right on!
I'm gonna do this,
just you wait!
[DIAO] An emergency draft?!
Gotta mean something big.
What the heck is going on?!
I'd better go pay Zheng
a visit and ask him.
[BOY] Wait right there,
He Liao Diao!
[DIAO] Huh?
If you've come
to see His Majesty,
I'm afraid you can't.
Sorry to disappoint you.
[BOY] Not even you
would be allowed
to enter the
Throne Room right now.
Oh, don't look so worried.
I'm not an enemy or anything.
Not at the moment, anyway.
Huh?
[BOY] I came here
with my teacher.
I was hoping to listen in
on the council of war.
But as soon as I got here,
they told me to wait
here in this room.
My father scolded me, too.
He said this was
no place for children.
Uh... who are you, exactly?
[BOY] Oh, sorry.
I suppose I haven't
introduced myself yet.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Meng Yi.
[DIAO gasps]
So, you're a
scaredy-cat, then?
Got a problem with that?
Hm! Not at all.
[MENG YI] It's a
valuable trait to have,
both here at court
and on the battlefield.
Huh?
[MENG YI] Oh, I get it!
That boy you live with...
Xin, I think his name was?
You think it's likely
he'll take part
in the war with Zhao, right?
[DIAO]
He knows about Xin, too...?
[MENG YI]
And you're worried about him,
so you came looking
for information.
[DIAO] Who is this guy?
[MENG YI] You certainly
read the situation right.
Huh?
The council of war
they're holding
at the Jeweled
Throne right now,
it's definitely one
of extreme importance.
It will affect the
whole course of this war.
[LI SI] Everyone in
MNyg was slaughtered,
down to the last newborn child.
Their corpses were
left to the elements,
and our enemies
spilled a river of blood.
[LI SI] We must not
stand by and allow Zhao
to get away with this outrage!
[ALL gasp]
We know all of this already.
How long are you going to
keep repeating yourselves?
Leave this matter to me.
I'll handle it.
[LÜ BUWEI] Hm.
We are most
fortunate to have you here
at Xianyang while our
renowned warriors
are away in Han. Your presence
must be considered
the silver lining
to this cloud, Meng Wu.
[LÜ BUWEI]
Given that, Your Majesty,
I urge you to
commission Meng Wu as--
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I beg you not to.
[ALL gasp]
Yes, Lord Changwen,
did you say something?
Yes. I said General Meng Wu
should not be appointed
commanding general.
I'll repeat myself if needed.
[LORD CHANGPING]
Hold, Meng Wu!
I will not let some mere
civil servant interrupt us.
[LORD CHANGPING]
He is no civil servant.
Lord Changwen is
also a veteran warrior
who's spent long years on the
front lines fighting with
bow and halberd in the time
of our own King Zhao.
Lord Changwen,
it appears you have
some concerns on your mind.
[LORD CHANGPING]
May I ask what they are?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
When it comes to battle,
there are two types
of strength:
[LORD CHANGWEN]
offensive and defensive.
Certainly, General Meng Wu's
offensive power is outstanding.
Indeed,
in that area, he may be
the best Qin general
of our time.
However, when it comes
to defensive strength,
he does not have what it takes.
[MENG WU grunts]
[LORD CHANGWEN] In a war where
the borders around our lands
are steadily crumbling,
and our ranks are already
thinned almost to nothing,
there can be no doubt
that defensive strength
is necessary for survival.
Therefore, we cannot afford
to leave this war
in the hands of
General Meng Wu.
[LÜ BUWEI] I see your point.
Your argument does sound
most reasonable.
However, having said that,
the larger question remains.
Is there anyone else now
in Qin capable of leading
100,000 soldiers to victory?
Who else could manage it?
There is one such man.
[ZHENG] Hm?
[LORD CHANGWEN] He's a
veteran warrior who's been
resting his wings away from the
field of battle for some time.
[MENG WU grunts]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Nevertheless,
the most powerful
of Qin's warriors.
Moreover, he's powerful in
both offense and defense.
Impossible...
You can't mean...?!
[WANG YI chuckles]
My, my, I see
the Court is livelier
than it's been in a long time!
Hello, everyone.
And how are all of you
on this fine day?
Xin?
Uh... hey, Zheng.
You're interrupting
our council of war. Leave!
What an odd thing to say.
I came all this way
because I was invited
to take part in this
very same council.
That's nonsense.
Who in his right mind
would invite you?
I invited him,
General Meng Wu.
[MINISTERS gasp]
[MENG WU]
Why would you do that?!
Answer me!
[LORD CHANGPING]
To commission him formally
as commanding general
of Qin's forces.
[MINISTERS] What?!
[XIN] Wang Yi will be
the commanding general?
Does that mean I get to see
with my own eyes
how the last of the six
great generals does battle?!
Is this my big chance?
[MENG WU] Lord Changping.
Do you think I will stand by
and accept this insult,
just like that?
You had better.
My reasoning is exactly as Lord
Changwen has already outlined.
Battle isn't about
offense or defense.
It's about crushing
the enemy in front of you
'til nothing's left!
That's all there is!
[LORD CHANGPING]
Enough, Meng Wu.
As Qin's commander, this is
my decision, and it's final.
It shall not be overruled.
You're nothing more
than a relic of the past.
I hold no respect for you!
Oh, that's such a shame.
You see,
I respect you, Meng Wu...
To a certain extent.
[MENG WU grunts]
[WANG YI chuckles]
Well, it seems that
matter has been settled.
[WANG YI] Now, if you
gentlemen don't mind,
would the rest of you
please leave as well?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Wh-What?!
What on Earth is the meaning
of this, General Wang Yi?
[WANG YI]
There are certain...
...old rules of etiquette that
apply in times like these.
The King and I must
go through certain formalities
in private before we can hold
the formal rite of commission.
I confess, I'm a
stickler for tradition.
I could never consent
to lead Qin's armies
without following
the proper protocol.
[MINISTERS grunting]
[ZHENG] Why do you
remain silent, Wang Yi?
You told a patently
transparent lie
in order to drive out
the others, didn't you.
[ZHENG] I assume you wish
to say something to me.
[laughs]
Well, then...
[WANG YI] Your Majesty,
I told you something
when your younger brother
Cheng Jiao rebelled
and turned the Royal Court
into a battlefield.
Do you remember
exactly what I said to you?
"Build up the
corresponding strength,
if you're going to speak
so grandly." I remember.
[WANG YI laughs]
It seems that will take you
a bit more time
to accomplish that.
I won't deny it.
After all, I have yet
to accomplish anything
truly kingly by myself.
Hm.
Wang Yi. On that same day,
I challenged you to accept and
move past King Zhao's death.
[ZHENG] If you're now willing to
accept command of our armies...
does that mean that
you have been able to do it?
King Zhao was
an illustrious ruler.
Believe me,
I'm well aware of that.
[WANG YI] Your Majesty...
you suffered a great misfortune
in that you never
had the chance to see
with your own eyes
the king who should've
been your role model.
You lived as a hostage
in the kingdom of Zhao
until you were nine.
And unfortunately, the only
king you saw in the four years
between your return
and your coronation
was your father,
King Zhuang Xiang,
who was merely
Lü Buwei's puppet.
If you had seen even one
glimpse of the old King Zhao,
and known what
he was capable of,
perhaps we would find ourselves
in slightly different,
slightly better circumstances.
What you say is true,
but nothing can
be done about it now.
I will simply have to
grope my own way forward.
[sighs]
What is it, Wang Yi?
If I am going to accept the
responsibility of going to war
as Qin's commanding general,
then there's a vital piece of
information I just remembered
that I need to tell you about.
[ZHENG] What is it?
Just that I have a message
I must give you.
[WANG YI]
It's from King Zhao.
[gasps]
[ZHENG] A message...
from King Zhao?
[ZHENG] The castle at MNyg
has already fallen prey
to Zhao's sudden invasion.
Its people have
been slaughtered
and the entire area demolished!
Now MNyáng castle,
the key to our kingdom's
first line of defense,
is under attack as well!
If MNyáng falls,
tragedy will sweep through
all the lands of Qin.
[ZHENG] Know that
this crisis threatens
our country's very survival!
[ZHENG] General Wang Yi,
I appoint you
as the commanding general
of over 100,000 Qin troops!
[ZHENG] Save MNyáng castle,
and annihilate the Zhao army
seeking to trample our kingdom!
Those are your orders!
I hear and obey you,
Your Majesty.
[MENG YI] So Wang Yi is
the commanding general...
I doubt Father is pleased.
My teacher made the
right decision, though.
General Wang Yi
really is the best one
to handle this war. It makes
sense to appoint him.
[DIAO] I don't
know much about him,
but if he's in command,
and if he's really that much
of a big shot, maybe we
can rest a little easier.
Know what I mean?
[MENG YI]
It's too soon to tell.
Huh?
[DIAO] Wait,
what do you mean by that?
I am thinking about
Zhao's forces.
There are things we
do not know about them yet.
For example... oh, hey!
Xin!
[YUAN] Lord Xin, why don't we
stop by at home first?
I think we should
at least tell poor Diao
that we're marching soon.
[XIN] No need.
He already knows
without me telling him.
[ZHENG] Xin!
[XIN] Huh?
[YUAN] Your Majesty!
[ZHENG]
Are the two of you leaving?
[XIN] Yeah, I gotta go.
Sounds like the others
are already marching.
I heard General
Wang Yi's gonna
stay a little longer, though.
[ZHENG] I never imagined you'd
be training under Wang Yi.
[XIN laughs]
Well, not like he's
actually bothered to
teach me anything
himself yet!
So, what?
The great king himself
came out here
just to say hello?
Be careful out there, Xin.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm way ahead of you!
Or, at least,
that's what I wanna say...
But what is with you, Zheng?
You look way gloomier
than usual.
It's just that
this attack by Zhao,
it took me
completely by surprise.
[XIN]
Well, they say overconfidence
is the greatest enemy.
[ZHENG] Certainly
the kingdom of Zhao was once
a mighty rival power.
But that was because
they had three great generals.
[XIN] Three great generals?
[YUAN gasps]
[ZHENG] Lin Xiangru,
Lian Po, and Zhao She.
They were illustrious
ministers and warriors
who fought for Zhao.
They were on the same level
as the six great generals
who were the pride of Qin.
They were as good as
the six great generals?!
[ZHENG] However, none of the
three are alive any longer,
and we knew of no one
qualified to succeed them.
Based on that, the Court
and I believed Zhao was
currently incapable of
mobilizing a large force
and attacking Qin.
[XIN] But now they are attacking
after all, aren't they?
[ZHENG] I'm told
King Dao Xiang of Zhao
is an extremely cautious man.
He would not have
authorized the attack
if he weren't confident.
[XIN] Don't you worry.
We have General
Wang Yi on our side!
Ah! W-Wait, sir!
And we got me, too.
[sighs]
[XIN] That was pretty
awesome back there, Zheng.
Hm?
The rite of commission.
That was actually
a pretty cool feeling,
getting commissioned by you...
with all the ministers
watching, in that big room.
[reins snap]
[horse neighs]
[XIN]
All right. I'll see you later!
Wait! Xin, sir,
please, wait for me!
Fortune be with you!
[DIAO panting]
[MENG YI] He's left, huh?
[DIAO] Yeah.
--[MENG YI] He Liao Diao...
--[DIAO] Huh?
Do you want to go
into battle as well?
Huh?
[NARRATOR] In the meantime,
the Qin soldiers who were
gathered by
the emergency draft
were marching
haphazardly northeast,
without even stopping to
organize their regiments first.
[WEI PING]
Look! There he is!
Ah! Hello, Wei Ping, Wei Dao.
[WEI PING, WEI DAO]
Corporal Ze!
Glad to see you again!
[ZE GUI] Good,
you're both looking well.
[laughs]
Yes, sir, we sure are.
[MAN] Ugh, the weaklings
are all coming together again!
[BOTH] Huh?
[WEI PING] Oh!
So you guys are here, too!
[XIE CI] 'Course we are!
We've all been itching to have
another proper dust-up again!
Look.
[XIE CI] Tian YRu and
Zhong Tie are here, too.
Yeeehoo!
All us boys who got
through that bloody battle
against Wei
are together again!
With the gang all here,
there's no way
we're gonna lose to anyone!
Say, where's that kid?
I thought he might be
hanging out with you guys.
Hmm? You mean Xin?
Yeah, we kept
an eye out for him
on the way here, but no luck.
Don't tell me
the brat didn't come.
I'll kick his butt
if he hasn't.
[WEI PING laughs]
Hey, no need
to worry, you guys.
[WEI PING]
If the rest of us are here,
there's just no way
he won't show up.
I may not know why
he's taking his sweet time,
but trust me, he'll be here.
[WEI PING]
He's gotta be, right?
He is our squadron
commander, after all!
[YUAN] Lord Xin, sir, we don't
have to be in such a rush!
[XIN] Whaddya talking about?
I ain't rushing, Yuan!
[YUAN] Huh?
[XIN] I'm just excited
to see everyone again!
[YUAN] What?!
[XIN] He-heh. Guys...
Hya!
[XIN] ...I'm on my way!
[LORD CHANGWEN] Impossible...
That can't be!
He died!
[NARRATOR]
That man is not human.
The heavens fear him,
and the earth
trembles before him.
[NARRATOR] Next Time:
"Pang Nuan, God of War."