[XIN] Qiang Lei!
[DIAO] Who's that?
Someone I fought with
in my five-man squad.
What?!
[DIAO] But that person is...
[XIN] A heck of
a fighter as well,
with some really
out-there moves!
One swing and ten huge
guys went down at once!
Are you serious?
So what are you doing
over here, Qiang Lei?
[QIANG LEI] Taking a walk.
You liar!
[QIANG LEI] I happened
to be in the neighborhood,
so I came to tell you one thing.
If you don't change,
sooner or later, you will die.
[XIN gasps]
[QIANG LEI] See you.
[XIN] So that's it?!
[QIANG LEI] Yes.
[XIN] Hey, hold on!
I've got a ton of things
I wanna ask you!
[QIANG LEI] Well?
[XIN] U-Uh...
about before... um...
When you were
riding behind me...
[DIAO] Hmm?
[XIN] So-So anyway...
...you're a girl, right?
[QIANG LEI] Yes. So what?
[BOTH gasp]
[XIN] W-What's
a girl doing fighting
with a bunch of guys?!
[QIANG LEI]
It's none of your business.
[DIAO] W-Wait!
I bet you must be hungry, right?
I'll cook us some
dinner before you go!
[QIANG LEI] I don't need--
[QIANG LEI's stomach growls]
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of
war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[DIAO]
Okay, dig right in, everyone.
All right, let's eat!
[BOTH gasp]
[XIN stammers]
[QIANG LEI gasps]
So good!
[DIAO] She could
fit in with the men...?
Anyway, how did you
not figure out
someone this cute was a girl?
Sh-She was hiding her
face the whole time!
How could I know?!
[DIAO sighs]
[DIAO]
C-Can I ask you something?
What is it?
[DIAO] What did
you mean by "so what"?
A young girl who
is living as a boy
is no trifling thing,
I will have you know!
[XIN] Why are you so interested
in her all of the sudden?
Be quiet!
It could be a bother if
people knew I was a woman,
so I don't tell them.
You are really confident
about your skills
to do what you do, Qiang Lei.
[QIANG LEI] There is no one in
this world stronger than I am.
Hey, hold on!
That's going too far!
Do you want to try me?
[XIN laughs]
Anyway, I gotta say
I'm relieved.
I thought you were a cold fish
who didn't care
about other people,
but it turns out I was wrong.
Excuse me? You thought that?
You went out of your
way to visit,
even though I don't
really get it at all.
[XIN laughs]
[QIANG LEI] That's because--
I have been wanting to
fight together again,
I'll have you know.
We're comrades after all!
[QIANG LEI gasps]
Stop it!
[DIAO &amp; XIN gasp]
That is not why
I joined the battle.
There just happened to be...
a battle while I was
working toward my goal.
That's all it was.
A goal, you say?
I'm not interested in
"togetherness"
or "comrades" at all.
[XIN] What is your goal then?
How did a girl like you
get so incredibly strong?
I-I want to know, too!
Please do tell us!
Uh... Diao?
I want to be
very strong as well!
You and I have the same--
[crashing, DIAO grunts]
[XIN] Hey, what are
you doing?! Put Diao down!
[QIANG LEI] Lay off!
We were just born into
absolutely different worlds.
Words like "I want
to know," "Tell me..."
Makes me sick when
people take me lightly!
[QIANG LEI] I'm alive for
one reason only, you see.
Being born Chi You
decided my life and my fate.
Born Chi You?
[QIANG LEI] A group of assassins
that has lived for
centuries in shadows.
[BOTH gasp]
[QIANG LEI] At least, that's
how people describe our tribe.
[laughter]
[CRONE] You shall all be
delicious food for our young.
[BANDIT 23A] What is this old
crone going on about?
[BANDIT 23B] You wandered into
the wrong neck of the woods.
[BANDIT 23C] None of you are
getting outta here alive!
I take it you do
know of the Chi You?
[BANDIT 23A] "Chi You"?
The sword was not
originally meant for slaying--
It was made in the ancient world
as a sacred object
for holy rites.
The Chi You are priestesses
who dance with swords
housing much divine power.
[BANDIT 23B] So what the heck
does that even mean, exactly?
[CRONE] As they dance, they slay
with the power of the gods.
Mere human power can
never ever compare to it.
[BANDIT 23C] Oh, is that so?
[BANDIT 23A] Okay, Granny,
whatever you say.
[CRONE] Dance, daughters
of the Qiang clan.
Xiang! Lei!
[BANDITS gasp]
[BANDIT 23A] What is that?
[BANDITS laugh]
You're offering a dance
to spare your life?
[grunting, gasping]
[QIANG LEI] The Chi You tribe
divided into specific
and individual clans,
which scattered themselves
all across the mountains,
and the gifted ones were
forced to train hard early on
so towns could make many capable
of carrying the Chi You name.
The clans staked everything.
[QIANG LEI] That was our law.
[QIANG LEI]
When I turned thirteen,
a Chi You had to be picked.
Two candidates were selected
from each of the nineteen clans.
My clan picked Xiang and
me--We were raised as sisters.
All the candidates must fight
for the title of Chi You
until one was left.
Until just one of the
candidates was left...
That is the tribal law
that is known as the Ritual.
That is the Chi You.
Our fates are simply sealed
as we are born into this.
[QIANG XIANG] That's
Lian of the YMu clan.
And this one's Jing of Yi.
They're both extremely strong.
You don't need to worry.
You will definitely
survive tomorrow, Xiang.
[QIANG XIANG] You do realize
that would mean
you die tomorrow?
Remember, it might possibly be
even me who kills you!
That does not bother me at all.
We have been told since babies
that we'd live until the Ritual.
Well, I don't like the idea.
I do not want to die
at just fifteen...
There are so many things
I still want to do.
I want to see those "nations"
down in the flatlands,
and I wanna see
the people who live there!
And I want to have children
someday, and before that...
I want to know the warmth
of a man's touch.
[QIANG XIANG gasps]
[QIANG LEI stammers]
[QIANG XIANG laughs]
[QIANG XIANG]
I guess you're still too young
to talk about that.
The truth is, I don't want you
to die tomorrow either, Lei.
I want you to survive
and carry the Chi You name,
and learn lots
about the outside world!
[QIANG LEI] It can't happen.
We are not allowed to join
forces despite our same clan.
Only one will survive.
That is what the law states.
That's the reason
we both have to fight hard
for our own sakes tomorrow!
Even if we end up
fighting against each other!
Don't you dare
go easy on me, Lei.
Understand?
Understood.
[QIANG XIANG] Lu Sui... you
protect Lei well tomorrow.
Hear me?
[QIANG LEI] Sister...
My Lei...
I've always thought of you
as my real sister and family.
[QIANG LEI]
I feel the same way, Xiang.
[QIANG LEI] There are thirty-six
other candidates besides us.
[QIANG LEI] I'll go all-out
the second the Ritual starts.
If I kill ten of the
strongest-looking tough ones,
that will surely be enough.
[QIANG LEI]
Xiang will do the rest
and then she'll
become the Chi You.
[QIANG LEI] It's okay, Lu Sui.
I decided on this.
Let's go to sleep.
We'll have an early day.
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[QIANG LEI] It's... evening...?!
[QIANG LEI] I overslept?!
No, I couldn't have!
Something happened...
Incense?
I was drugged!
By who?
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[QIANG LEI] Sister...?
[QIANG LEI] The Ritual--What
happened there?!
And Xiang...
[QIANG LEI] What about Xiang?!
[QIANG LEI] Xiang...
[QIANG LEI] Xiang!
[QIANG LEI] She's not here...
Xiang's not here!
She's not here,
she won the--
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[QIANG LEI whimpers]
[QIANG LEI screams]
[DIAO whimpers]
[QIANG LEI] Don't misunderstand:
Xiang wasn't weak at all.
She far surpassed
the rest of those girls.
[DIAO] Then why did she...?
[QIANG LEI growls]
[QIANG LEI sobs]
[QIANG LEI] Why, Elder?
Why did this happen to Xiang?
There was not a single person
here she would have lost to!
Xiang was carefully targeted
from the very beginning.
Targeted, you say?!
[CRONE]
The second the Ritual started,
a whole group attacked her
simultaneously.
[ELDER 23A] In accordance with
our laws we'll start the Ritual.
Begin!
[yelling]
[grunting, shouting]
[YLULIAN] Hmph. Little wench...
[CRONE] All while
Lian of YMu simply looked on.
[QIANG LEI] That can't be!
It's forbidden to join forces
with anyone in the Ritual,
even a member of your own clan!
That is our law!
Isn't it?!
Lei!
It was clear to all that your
and Xiang's power was greater.
The Elders of all the
clans acknowledged it, too.
That's why they
turned a blind eye.
To the others joining forces
and... to your absence, too.
[QIANG LEI] A blind eye...?
Elder, wait,
what about the law?
Isn't the law
absolute after all?!
Is it really such a
trifling thing?!
[CRONE growls]
[QIANG LEI] Elder!
Then why...
Then why did they
do this to her?
Why did Xiang have to die
if it isn't absolute?!
[ELDER 23A] What are
you doing, Elder of Qiang?
That one is but
walking dead, I believe.
[QIANG LEI gasps]
[ELDER 23A] Just slay
yourself, Qiang girl.
The Ritual's victor
has been decided!
Each and every loser
must die promptly.
That is the firm law
of Chi You,
which has stood unbroken
for a thousand years!
[ELDER 23A grunts]
[ELDERS gasp]
[QIANG LEI] You hags
think I'm stupid?
Thousand-year law?
Don't make me laugh.
[BOTH sigh]
I thought about killing
all the old crones
and then dying myself
afterwards,
but I didn't.
I changed my mind.
There's one more thing
I have to do before I die.
You're talking about
that YMu Lian?
I am... talking about her...
[QIANG XIANG grunts]
[YLULIAN laughs]
[YLULIAN] Sleep tight.
[QIANG LEI growls]
[QIANG LEI] The one who
plotted to have them
gang up on us...
and who killed Xiang
ended up the new
Chi You and left our lands.
I'll make her pay if
it's the last thing I do.
I lost Xiang and I abandoned
the Chi You homeland.
The only reason I'm alive now
is to kill that woman
and that's it.
[XIN growls]
[DIAO] It must eat at you.
[XIN] Hm?
[DIAO] That you were
at the mercy
of some stupid baseless law...
that you lost Xiang to
people fighting really dirty...
And also the girl
who killed her is
living the wonderful life
as Chi You, but...
The worst part...
...is that when the one
you loved was killed,
you couldn't be there
to help her.
What makes you think that, Diao?
Because that's what...
scares me most of all.
Diao...
[XIN] Wow, it's
already nighttime!
Stay with us tonight,
Qiang Lei.
[QIANG LEI] All right.
[DIAO grunts]
[XIN] What's up?
[DIAO] I cannot sleep at all.
I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
[DIAO] Back in Heibei Village,
all I ever thought about
was how I could escape.
[DIAO] But when I met Xin
and Zheng and the guys,
and then got in the fight
to take back the capital...
I don't know why,
but I felt so excited inside.
Even though every day was
really a brush with death...
[DIAO] But now, calming down
and thinking about things,
I kind of get it all.
Xin... I think because
I was with you.
We started living together, and
even though nothing happened,
happy days started to come.
It was the first time life
had ever been fun for me.
And I thought it'd stay
that way forever...
But I was very wrong.
[DIAO] You keep moving forward.
Not just you.
Zheng, and Bi,
and Lord Changwen, too.
You're all risking your
lives to move forward.
All of a sudden, I'm the only
one sitting somewhere else,
facing a different direction.
At this rate,
it's just like before!
So what am I to do, then?!
[XIN growls quietly]
[XIN grolws]
[QIANG LEI]
You're keeping me awake!
Quit staring;
it's very oppressive.
Hehe, sorry, sorry!
But you know what,
now that I look at you,
you're actually really cute!
You are an idiot.
Someone who was just
like a brother to me
got killed as well.
He was Piao.
To me, he was just like a--
You do not have to tell me.
I was sort of listening while
you were telling
Wei Ping and Wei Dao.
Okay, fine, never mind then!
I felt like it was not right to
let you spill your guts alone.
[QIANG LEI] Xin.
[XIN] Hn?!
You are...
really a strange one.
[XIN] Huh?! Where did
that come from?!
[QIANG LEI] I'm strange as well.
You were simply lucky in
that war, and that is all.
[XIN growls]
Xin, even in that last fight
you had with Wei,
there were plenty of men who
were much stronger than you.
[XIN] I know that already.
The experiences I had in
that battle made me realize
that if I just go racing ahead
on nothing but momentum
and high spirits alone,
I cannot win a real fight.
I realize my shortcomings.
I've thought it
through thoroughly.
Sounds like you've
made up your mind.
[XIN] So what are you
going to do now?
[QIANG LEI]
I'll head for Wei on my own.
That's all I... have left...
Well, when you're done, you
get your butt back here, okay?
[QIANG LEI gasps]
You say you've got nothing
but revenge or whatever,
but that's a gigantic lie.
Someone like that
wouldn't risk herself
to help other people out
in a battle that wild.
Listen up, Qiang Lei!
You're a comrade who
fought hard and bravely
in my five-man squad,
which means
you've been one of my
hundred-man unit from the start!
So you get back here before
the next war. No excuses!
That's an order, you hear me?!
[QIANG LEI] Don't sign me up.
Shut up! Answer me!
[QIANG LEI] I'll think about it.
[XIN growls]
[XIN] Whatever.
I'll always save
a space for ya.
Qiang Lei, you must
have learned a lot
from that battle you
were in with us.
[QIANG LEI] I suppose.
[XIN] Well, then you
better come back here!
[QIANG LEI] Knock it off!
Oh, I see you are awake?
[XIN] Is she... gone now?
[DIAO] Yeah. Come on,
it's breakfast time!
Xin, please listen to me.
[XIN] Hm? Say what?
Do you remember
about my ambition?
It is to become super-rich
and spend my life partying hard.
Oh yeah, I do remember you
telling me about that one time!
I have no intention of
living in this shabby hut
just making ends meet.
Yeah, I'm on it!
I'm gonna climb up the ladder
and get us one huge estate!
Originally, I figured
I'd rely on you,
but I've changed my mind.
I mean, you could
really die at any time.
[XIN] E-Excuse me?
That's why I have
decided to go to battle
and earn my fortune now!
Huh?!
You want to go to
battle and fight?!
I know that I
don't have the muscles
for much of anything, really.
But then, even if
I don't know what it is,
I know there is going to be
something that I can do, Xin!
So...
When the fighting starts again,
are you going to go to war?
You bet.
I will leave here
promptly then as well.
To find the place
where I belong.
Oh, I see...
[DIAO] We might not see
each other for a while,
but I promise to come back.
I will come back to you.
I'll be waiting for you.
[DIAO giggles]
[XIN] Okay! Let's work
like crazy today!
[DIAO] Yeah!
You help clean up then!
[XIN] You do that.
[DIAO] Say what?!
Pitch in once in a while,
why don't you?!
[XIN] I told you, I'm terrible
at cooking and cleaning!
So that's why
I just stick to eating!
[DIAO] Don't just
decide that on your own!
[XIN] I want the world's
greatest generals to train me!
[NARRATOR]
A step toward the future.
In order to follow his path,
he seeks to better himself!
Next Time: "A New Trial."