[NARRATOR]
After Pang Nuan's attack,
the Fei Xin Force scattered
and went on the run.
Meanwhile, the Gan Yang
Army's surviving soldiers
were taken in by
the Lu Wuwei Army.
When morning dawned, fewer than
half the Fei Xin force remained.
They now had 36 men left,
all of whom took up their
weapons again and began walking
while their wounds
were still fresh.
And then...
[PEI LANG] No doubt about it,
that's a Qin flag.
They're assembling our soldiers.
We should go, commander.
Yes.
Our allies!
No.
[XIN]
Those guys ain't from Qin!
They fell for it right away.
Kill all those
Qin apes, immediately!
Run, now!
Scale the cliffs,
horses can't climb them!
Move it! Send the injured first!
[rumbling]
Wh-What's this rumbling?
Behind us!
[SONG ZUO] There's a huge
cavalry incoming from the rear!
[WEI PING]
Darn, more Zhao soldiers?!
No way, that is...
...General Wang Yi!
Our general has now
taken to the field!
[NARRATOR]
The time: The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
Xin a nameless boy who rose to
the rank of squadron commander,
carried out a string of
exploits in the midst of battle
that brought the
Qin army an advantage.
However, the enemy's commanding
general has appeared at last,
and has proven to be
beyond all imagination.
That man, said to have a
previous tie to Wang Yi,
is named Pang Nuan.
The war situation is on
the verge of great change!
[WANG YI] I assumed
She Meng must be the one
who came up with
that asinine plan.
It seems I was right.
Yes. Quite asinine.
[WANG YI] He's not the man who
decimated our Fourth Army,
but one can't have everything.
For now, let's have She Meng
shoulder all of this sorrow
that we have all
had to suffer since...
[YUAN]
Wang Yi's moved out in front!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SHE MENG] Wang Yi,
the "Strange Bird of Qin"!
Oh, how I've longed
for this day to come!
[SHE MENG chuckles]
Wang Yi!
[SHE MENG] The six great
generals are legends now.
There's no doubt
of their strength.
But I wasn't around
in those days.
I'll show you all
that I am a monster
who surpasses the
six generals easily!
[SHE MENG] Now I will reign
over all the battlefields
of the Middle Kingdom.
You will see!
Wang Yi!
[TENG]
She Meng, someone like you
could never hold a candle
to our leader.
Wha--?
[SHE MENG screams]
[ALL gasp]
[YUAN] Th-That's the p-power
of our commanding general?!
But look! The enemy's
falling back!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 33A]
Retreat! Retreat!
[WANG YI] I see the Fei Xin
Force has been more than halved
in one night. That's a pity.
Are you distressed,
my young Xin?
I'm not gonna
think about it now.
Otherwise I feel like
I might just drop here
and not be able to move forward.
However, that's not what those
who have passed away
before us want!
I know it.
So right now,
I'm only thinking about
how the 36 of us standing
right here, right now
can fight and win.
I had a pep talk
all ready today,
but it doesn't seem
necessary now, does it, Teng?
No. Quite a boring child.
I must say, you have a
fine attitude, young Xin.
The path to generalship
is one of sacrifice.
And with every single
sacrifice overcome,
the warrior and his unit
grow in greatness.
In fact, growth is essential.
Men, it was worth my while
to name you the Fei Xin Force.
Now it is time to go.
The deciding battle
is approaching.
[ZHAO SOLDIER 33B]
My lord Zhao Zhuang!
General Pang Nuan has returned!
I am glad to see
you are safe.
I acted alone, thinking
Wang Yi had appeared.
Forgive me.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] General,
as long as you are safe,
this does our strategy
no harm, really.
However, in the future,
I would be grateful if you'd
tell me of your plans.
Otherwise I'm afraid this
may have all been for naught.
I understand.
You've nothing to fear.
[MESSENGER 33A]
Zhao Zhuang, Sir!
The rear guard has
sent up a smoke signal!
It's the signal that She Meng
has been slain in battle!
Say what? She Meng
has just been slain?!
Yes, Sir! And there
was one more fire--
The one that means
Wang Yi's appeared!
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
So you're here at last, Wang Yi!
General Pang Nuan's
night raid ended up
drawing that cautious old fox
into the mountains, then?
She Meng's loss is a
blow to Zhao's armies,
but it is certainly
not a fatal one.
Now our armies will
intercept each of Qin's
to halt their advances promptly.
Wang Yi's army will be
isolated as a result,
and if they come after
our headquarters,
Zhao will be victorious!
[ZHAO ZHUANG laughs]
[MENG WU]
Is that their headquarters?
I'm certain of it.
[MENG WU]
Your name is Long Guo, isn't it?
You've guided me
here brilliantly.
Thank you, sir.
The enemy should be
off-guard right about now.
I suggest we have
one of our forces
circle around behind them.
No need. Now that
we've come this close,
I won't let them get away!
Here we go!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[DIAO]
Look, smoke signals.
I wonder if
something happened...
I am not an insider,
so I don't know
which army made them.
However, what I do know now,
I can't imagine
how harsh war is.
For instance,
to relay information
to an allied force
of unknown position,
smoke signals are
your only option.
But as a tradeoff,
you reveal your own position
to the enemy.
Those fires that you see
wouldn't be set
without a very good reason.
Yes, a very good reason...
There is another way to
deliver messages, you see.
What way is that, Li Mu?
[MENG YI]
Flags...
[LI MU]
The flags at Qin headquarters
have changed since
early this morning.
What does that mean, then?
[LI MU] You can use flags'
colors and relative positions
to convey very
detailed information.
Still you see,
they have the drawback
of only being visible
within a limited range.
[NARRATOR] These particular
flags were announcing
that Wang Yi had entered
the mountains finally.
And from Wang Yi's
own vantage point...
[WANG YI]
Look there, Teng.
It's the signal telling us
where Zhao's headquarters is.
Courtesy of Long Guo, I assume.
Yes, Long Guo is good.
However, it's deeper
into the mountains
than we originally thought.
I believe that's down
to Zhao Zhuang
pulling back early, rather than
to Long Guo being late.
Yes. He's a skilled tactician.
I'm sure Zhao Zhuang
is the one in command
of headquarters,
but if Pang Nuan were to
involve himself somehow...
This will be
quite unpredictable.
[WANG YI] Now I'm a bit
concerned about Meng Wu.
I'm positive his battle
has already begun.
[NARRATOR] Just as Wang Yi
surmised, at that very moment
the battle between
Zhao Zhuang's army
and the Meng Wu-Long Guo
Armies was at fever pitch.
Meng Wu and Long Guo initially
tore through the enemy
with their sudden attack,
but the Zhao Zhuang Army's
adroit interception
halted their momentum,
leaving the two sides closely
matched in strength.
Nevertheless, with Meng Wu
taking the lead,
Meng Wu and Long Guo's
armies steadily
pressed Zhao Zhuang's men back.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Attention, Meng Wu
and Long Guo Armies!
That big man with the
long black hair is Pang Nuan!
[LONG GUO]
Zhao's commanding general
has had the nerve to
show himself before us!
Surround him and take his head!
[MENG WU]
So that's the famous Pang Nuan.
That explains why he
struck me differently.
I never met a man who
reeked so strongly of war.
[MENG WU]
Me, in a cold sweat?
Interesting!
[MENG WU yells]
What's this?!
H-He just ran?
How dare you do that!
Don't tell me you think
I'm not strong enough
to go to battle, you!
[MENG WU] Do you think
I'll let you escape?!
[MENG WU'S SOLDIER 33A]
Follow General Meng Wu!
[LONG GUO]
No... what is this?
Something is wrong.
Even so, this is
still a good chance
to slay Pang Nuan.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
We netted a different fish
than we were hoping for,
but this is just fine.
They cannot possibly
have guessed
that we used our commanding
general as a decoy.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Wang Yi,
in the end you'll have no choice
but to show yourself.
[LONG GUO] This terrain
is bad! It's clearly a trap!
General Meng Wu--
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[MENG WU'S SOLDIER 33B]
My lord!
[LONG GUO]
General Meng Wu!
[MENG WU]
How many casualties?
Even at a rough estimate,
I would say half, sir.
[MENG WU]
Half...
It's enough. Let's go.
Sir, please wait!
The strategist Zhao Zhuang
is trying to reel you in
with Pang Nuan as bait.
We should withdraw
for the moment
and try to regroup.
I think that is a big mistake.
I will not be
stopped by strategy!
[NARRATOR] At the same
time that Meng Wu rode
into Zhao Zhuang's trap,
Wang Yi was dividing his forces
into cavalry and infantry.
He and the cavalry searched out
a route the horses could travel
while he took advantage of the
infantry's maneuverability
and sent them sprinting
along a direct route
that gave them almost
the same speed.
[XIN] Wei Ping, Chong Yuan,
just don't overdo it, okay?
General Wang Yi said
anybody who couldn't keep up
was allowed to bow out.
[WEI PING]
Don't be stupid, Xin.
You want us to lie napping
after we've come this far?
N-Not a chance. Let's go.
I may not have fight left in me,
but I'm seeing this war
through to the very end!
With my own two eyes!
You heard the man.
I am not sure all
this rush is a good idea.
We're defenseless like this.
If we were to get ambushed now,
I think we're all done for.
[SONG ZUO laughs] I get why
the general's in a hurry,
but this is a bit much.
[QIANG LEI] General Wang Yi
knows the enemy isn't here.
Hence the plan.
Well how can he with all
of these mountains?
[QIANG LEI]
Don't ask me.
Our lieutenant's as gruff
as ever, or so it seems.
[QIANG LEI]
Be quiet and just run.
[SONG ZUO]
Okay.
[NARRATOR]
Just as Qiang Lei said,
Wang Yi knew that there was
no Zhao army presence
where they were going.
The reason, of course,
was the flags.
Even as Wang Yi
continued his advance,
he periodically raised flags
toward Qin headquarters.
These were messages for
the various commanders
scattered across the mountains.
His remaining subordinates
at headquarters
faithfully relayed these
messages with their flags.
The combat commanders
in each location
kept an eye on those flags
to exchange information.
Naturally, their messages
were also conveyed back
to Wang Yi via headquarters.
This meant that as long as
he kept headquarters in sight,
Wang Yi was aware of the
overall positions and states
of both Qin's armies and Zhao's.
The exception: he did not
know the movements
of Meng Wu and Long Guo's armies
which had made contact
with Zhao headquarters.
Neither of these armies
had answered Wang Yi.
Therefore, he hastened
his advance even more now.
Well the flags have changed
positions once again.
Which means the war
situation is changing?
[LI MU]
Exactly so.
[DIAO]
Kaine.
Here, I made lunch.
It's your share.
Tasty, isn't it?
Yes.
--[KAINE] Fine!
--Huh?
[DIAO]
Hey Kaine...
You are a woman, correct?
[KAINE]
Obviously!
Yeah, totally! Ha, ha!
But you know, um,
you don't seem too womanly
so I thought you
might be a man...
[KAINE]
What?!
[KAINE gasps, growls]
[KAINE]
Oh, so you're a gi--
I see...
Well, it's not too rare these
days for a woman to survive
by dressing as a man, you see.
So did you get carried away
and decide to be a
"male" tactician?
[KAINE]
Am I wrong?
Am I wrong, Kaine?
[DIAO]
I don't know yet.
I just thought if
I didn't do something,
I'd get left behind...
I didn't know
what to do exactly,
but being here, I feel like
I've started to figure it out.
[KAINE] If that's what
you're thinking forget it.
Huh?
You do not understand anything.
If you're going
to be a tactician,
you need to grasp what
being one really means.
What it means?
That's right.
It's more stressful and
painful to be a tactician
than a soldier bleeding
on the front lines.
Painful...
[KAINE]
...and terrible as well.
[JIE SHEN]
Sir, they're here.
That's Wang Yi's army.
There it is:
Zhao headquarters...
But, why then...?
That's right...
[XIN]
The place is totally empty!
This will do.
Let's just stop here
and do some real
information gathering,
shall we, Teng?
Yes.
[MESSENGER 33B]
I have a report!
[OFFICER 33A]
Madness!
Zhao trapped him in a rockslide
and took half his troops,
and still pursued them
on Long Guo's watch!
[OFFICER 33B] We can't
fault him for the pursuit.
With the commanding
enemy general
in front of him, anyone
would have pressed on.
The larger issue is
the missing Zhao army.
They have stockade
around headquarters;
why leave it behind?
To go and exterminate
Meng Wu simply.
[OFFICER 33B]
My lord?
[WANG YI] I imagine Zhao Zhuang
has units lying in ambush
along Meng Wu's path to
slowly whittle down his army.
Once the army's been gutted,
he intends to bring him down
with Zhao's main force
from headquarters.
In which case, we can all
go to the Meng Wu Army's aid
by following Zhao Zhuang?
But if we go any further,
we will lose sight of
our own headquarters.
By extension, that would mean
losing our overall picture
of an enormous battlefield.
[WANG YI]
We likely have no choice.
I imagine that
Zhao Zhuang's strategy
is to lure me away from Qin
and our headquarters here, men.
So if we stay here, they
won't make a single move.
Moreover, Zhao Zhuang
surely laid the traps
Meng Wu is facing
in order to kill me.
I'm afraid Meng Wu may well
lose his life in this battle.
Listen, men...
Let's take the field.
[MENG WU yells]
How many fell?
[MENG WU'S SOLDIER 33C]
Around 2,000!
You little...
Pang Nuan!
Get him, General!
[MENG WU yells]
[ALL gasp]
[SOLDIERS cheer]
General Meng Wu, you did it.
[MENG WU]
No.
This man here isn't
Pang Nuan. He's a fake.
[LONG GUO]
Sir?!
On your guard, men.
They're coming.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ZHENG]
A night battle?
[LORD CHANGPING]
Yes, Your Highness,
if the last smoke signal
is to be believed.
It would seem that Pang Nuan
has now re-appeared.
Pang Nuan?! But why now?
A nighttime attack is no
fit tactic for a large army.
I believe something unexpected
must have occurred.
[LORD CHANGWEN] And that
"something" was Pang Nuan?
Yes.
The other day,
you described Pang Nuan
as not a general, but a man,
crystallization of warfare,
right, Lord Changwen?
Yes.
Can such a man be suitable
for the position of
commanding general?
And yet he is, in fact,
in that very position
at this moment...
This war is peculiar.
Wait! Unless...
[BUREAUCRAT 33A]
Your Highness!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
What is it?
[BUREAUCRAT 33A]
We have an emergency.
That is...
Lord Changwen, let's go.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Sir.
Naturally, I'm happy
to see you again,
but what brought on this visit?
Yang Duanhe.
Zheng king of Qin,
you look well.
I realize this is
a hectic time,
but I have come here because
there is something very urgent
I must tell you immediately
about the current war.
[ZHENG]
Something you must tell me...?
[WANG YI] So, shall we
finally settle this then?
[NARRATOR]
Bloodlust fills the air.
The path opens
at his demonic smile.
Next Time:
"The Main Attraction."