Go ahead, Xin.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Go after the King! Please!
[BI] My lord is bowing his head
to another beside the King...
[BI] And to a no-name
serving-boy, at that.
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[XIN grunting, panting]
[DIAO screams]
[XIN] Little Lord Bi, now,
why'd you come along again?
Because only you two
going alone worries me.
And don't you call me
"Little Lord"!
[XIN] Ha! Whatever, but hurry up
or we'll leave you behind.
[BI]
Damn it. Damn it!
[BI] Don't you belittle
the warrior class!
[XIN laughs]
[DIAO]
Hey guys, I wonder what
the mountain king's
nation is like.
Do you think... there are
big castles and all of that?
No. To be blunt, I doubt
there is much to it.
[BI] Judging by their dress,
their standard of living
isn't at all high.
It's likely on the order
of a country village,
rather than a nation.
If we can only sneak in,
the rescue shouldn't be hard.
I see. If so, this climb
can't be that hard.
[XIN grunting, panting]
Huh?
[DIAO gasps]
What is it? Oh. Whoa...
Uh, how is this like
a country village?
Just how are we
supposed to save Zheng
from a place like this,
Bi, my man?!
This is, ridiculous...
I am Ying Zheng;
31st sovereign, of Qin.
[WOLVES growling]
[YANG DUANHE] I am the
mountain king, Yang Duanhe.
[XIN grunting]
[XIN]
That's hrrrd...
Right! This is where I come in!
[DIAO screams]
[DIAO, XIN scream]
[DIAO, XIN groan]
[DIAO] Oh! I think he's the guy
you knocked out cold earlier!
You! Did you come
to get back at me?
Wh-What are you clowns doing?
[DIAO yelps]
No way... Hey, Xin! Xin!
Stop crying! These
clowns are nothing!
Just watch...
If they stab those things at us,
I'll catch one with feet
and ropes, and raise hell!
You don't really
think you could?!
Yeah, leave it to me.
Piao and I trained at
this stuff all the time.
[DIAO]
Seriously?!
[DIAO screams]
Did you train at this, too?
Crap, Holy crap...
D-Did you...
[XIN] Did you...
just save the three of us?
[BA JIO] Tajifu only protected
you by his king's order.
[DIAO]
Oh! It's that troop-leader guy!
[BA JIO]
Between the mountain realm
and the flatland realm,
the boundary is unclear...
In those areas, a lot
of things happen.
That bunch are
men whose families
were killed by plains folk.
[BA JIO] The warrior Tajifu
is paying his respects to you,
who broke his horns.
The warrior Tajifu...
[BA JIO]
Tajifu finds it regrettable
that you three will soon
be judged by our king,
and then you will be killed.
What?!
What did you say?!
What about Zheng, then?
[BA JIO]
The King of Qin, too.
[YANG DUANHE]
Ying Zheng, King of Qin...
...the powerless boy king,
driven from the throne
by his brother,
with few followers to rely on.
He flees from
place to place alone.
Then he turns his steps
into this alpine land
to meet with me.
Let us hear why you came.
I came to borrow your strength.
[MEN chuckling]
[WOLVES growling]
[YANG DUANHE]
Incorrect, King of Qin.
We brought you in
order to judge you.
Judgment for what?
[YANG DUANHE] You won't get
away with claiming ignorance.
About what you people
of Qin have done to us!
[YANG DUANHE]
400 years ago, when Duke Mu,
famed sovereign of Qin, and the
mountain lands formed a pact,
our forefathers saw
in that goodwill
the promise of a new
broadening of our horizons.
[YANG DUANHE]
However...
[QIN CHILD 8A] Go home to
the mountains, monkeys!
[QIN CHILDREN shouting]
Go home! Go home! Go home!
[YANG DUANHE]
We were forced to realize
that it was all an illusion.
[YANG DUANHE] Those who'd
been living in contact
with the flatlanders
took to the road home.
But even there, they encountered
persistent torment.
[QIN SOLDIER 8A]
There they are!
[YANG DUANHE] The tragedies they
endured were all unthinkable.
[YANG DUANHE]
We understand each other?
To settle our
forefathers' grievances,
we must take the head of
the current king of Qin.
Have you anything to say?
We are the ones to blame.
As a native of Qin,
I sincerely apologize
for that past stupidity.
However, everything
you have said
is not enough reason
to take my head.
[MEN murmuring]
[YANG DUANHE]
Oh? Why is that?
If there's error in your answer,
your head comes
off this instant.
[ZHENG] In the 400 years'
history since Duke Mu,
and in the millennium,
and even more before then,
where different nations,
races, cultures,
and beliefs have
mixed among people,
does a case exist where not
a drop of blood was spilled?
Have the accumulated prejudice,
contempt, and grudges
of many years ever
simply vanished?
[ZHENG]
If you look at human history.
you'll soon see what a
daunting task this is.
It was naive to believe
that, hundreds of years
of friction vanished with
the coming of Duke Mu.
[YANG DUANHE]
You...
Do you call our ancestors fools
for dreaming of peace and
meeting with betrayal?!
[ZHENG]
I certainly do not.
I say only this:
Believing you'll solve
this deep-rooted problem
by taking my head is a mistake.
[MEN growl]
[YANG DUANHE]
"It won't solve the problem,
so don't kill me," you say?
You'd tell us to
simply let it go
when entire clans were killed?
There are dozens of things
that should take
priority over revenge.
[YANG DUANHE laughs] He plays
at the role of wise sovereign,
this crafty young king.
But it looks as though
you don't understand
people's suffering very much.
[DIAO, XIN, BI grunting]
What on earth
are you doing here?
That's enough!
We just screwed up a little bit.
A little bit?
[YANG DUANHE]
Do it.
[DIAO screams]
I'm first?! No!
[ZHENG]
There's no need to do that.
I know, that pain
well enough myself.
[ZHENG]
Mountain king, hear me.
If a king takes up the sword
driven by grudges or enmity,
his hate will then drives
his kingdom to fall.
A king's duty,
is to take a sword
to cut out a path
to give only life.
[YANG DUANHE]
What does this mean?
It is because they are divided,
that there's friction between
mountain folk and Qin folk.
Yet, because it's
always been so,
it's come to seem
entirely natural.
The same is true of
all the Middle Kingdom.
The plains folk, who must
seem all one people to you,
keep endlessly pillaging
and killing one another.
As the turbulence worsened,
we've built long walls
on the borders,
making inside and outside,
friend and foe,
all the more explicit.
A rare leader, like
Duke Mu, did indeed appear
becoming leader over many
lands, yet ultimately,
even he provided no more
than temporary stability.
But that alone
isn't good enough.
What's not good enough?!
What do you think you
know about Duke Mu?
If peace was achieved even
temporarily, that's amazing!
What more are you
saying he could've done?!
The abolition of all borders!
Eliminating borders?
[YANG DUANHE]
King of Qin, look around.
Do you think even a single
kingdom will accept that notion?
If they can't, I'll do
it by cultivating power.
As suits a world at war.
[YANG DUANHE] That sounds
like the very opposite
of "a path to give life."
[ZHENG]
No!
For 500 years,
turmoil has reigned,
which means it could
go on for 500 more.
I take up the sword
to prevent those sacrifices
of the next 500 years!
Just hold on!
What in the world are
you talking about?
[ZHENG]
I'm talking about my aims.
[XIN]
Your aim is the throne stolen
by your younger brother, right?
Didn't you come to ask
for reinforcements
to take the throne back?
The jeweled throne is just
the first step on my path.
You have a path?
What on earth do you
mean "your path"?
I'll become the first King
to unite the Middle Kingdom!
Unite the...
...Middle Kingdom?
Does that mean destroying
the other kingdoms
and bringing them under Qin?
It does.
That cannot possibly happen...
In 500 years-- No, going
back even further...
Such a thing's never,
ever been attempted!
That's what I'll do.
With all united, there'll be
no conflict anymore,
and people of every land will
see their horizons broadened!
[YANG DUANHE]
Their horizons broadened...
[YOUNG YANG DUANHE]
Grandfathers, why don't we
conquer Qin?
[ELDER A] O-ho!
That's our Yang Duanhe!
[ELDER B] That ambition
is admirable, Your Highness.
But please be a little more
patient for the time being.
In order to conquer Qin,
we must further strengthen
the mountain kingdom's power.
[YOUNG YANG DUANHE]
In that case, let us seek peace.
Wh-What are you saying?
Peace with the hated
Kingdom of Qin?
You must not utter such
words, Your Highness!
[ELDER A] All are glad that
for the first time in centuries
a king's arisen who binds
the mountain realm together.
[ELDER B] Our hopes are that
you, great Yang Duanhe, will be
the one to purge the regrets
of our ancestors and of today.
[YOUNG YANG DUANHE]
Grandfathers...
With each passing year,
the mountain kingdom's defenses
grow much sturdier.
[YOUNG YANG DUANHE] But with
this, I feel the constraints
of these mountains.
Whether by battle or peace--
by whatever means,
I simply want to
broaden my world.
[ELDER A]
What is taking so long, my king?
Now is the right time to pay off
the long-standing
grudges of our folk.
[ELDER B] This excess of
dialogue is unnecessary.
[ELDER A]
Since we elders remember deeply
our kindred's grievances
against Qin's people, though...
...allow us to make
this a fair judgment.
Let us skin Qin's
sovereign alive
and bare him to the sunlight.
[ELDER A] These three we'll
chop up and use as pig feed.
Who's gonna be pig feed?!
I'll kick you into tomorrow,
you old windbags!
[DIAO screams]
I'm first again?!
[XIN yells]
Ohhh...
Xin! When did you manage--
We figured this might happen.
Piao and I trained rope
escapes to perfection!
Are you serious?
How 'bout it, Zheng?
You nervous?
Not especially.
[XIN]
Huh?
Well, what are you all doing?
Seize them quickly!
Xin...
[YANG DUANHE]
Heh, heh.
An amusing boy, just as
Ba Jio's report said.
And? What will you do next?
[XIN]
Me? I won't do anything.
[YANG DUANHE]
What?
[XIN] If you won't
lend us your strength,
we'll head back down the
mountain and find someone else.
[XIN]
Granted there is no one left...
[ELDER A]
You fool!
You believe you can just
descend unharmed from here
just like that?! [screams]
[XIN] Or I could steal
a sword and raise hell.
But there are guys here
I really don't wanna fight.
There's no choice.
Guess I'll take you hostage,
old man and descend.
Eh?!
Hey! Guy in the
fancy general's mask!
You've been talking
all this complex talk
this whole time,
but to put it simply, this guy's
in trouble right now!
Just think of it
as a helping hand
and lend him support, huh?
That's the crudest persuasive
speech I've ever...
It's all over.
What's more, hook him up
with an agreement now,
and you just might get
a bigtime payback!
With treasures and
tasty food, too...
Stop with your cockiness,
flatlander monkey!
We'll slice the
lot of you up here
as sacrifices for our
forefathers' grievances--
[ELDER a screams]
Shut up with all
your "grievances!"
The greatest grievance of all
is when a dream ends up as
no more than an illusion.
If you really care about
the ones who died,
then turn what they dreamed
of into something real
and concrete, do you
all understand?!
[XIN] Whoa! What just
happened to the air in here?
[ZHENG]
Don't be dismayed.
For you, that was good work.
[ZHENG] Yang Duanhe,
king of the mountains.
For now, I am what you see: a
weak king, powerless before you.
But unifying the Middle Kingdom
is no empty delusion of a dream.
It is with certainty my path.
If you join me, you'll see a
broadening of your horizons
even greater than your
forefathers' spirits sought!
Revive the alliance
of four centuries ago
between Qin and
the mountain lands,
and lend me your strength.
[YANG DUANHE] I have
one question, King of Qin.
We are savage.
In your regaining the throne,
the Royal Court
may become a sea of blood.
You don't mind this?
Does that mean...
That's how it was taken from me.
Why should I balk at the same?
You can't!
You cannot, Your Highness!
Our forefathers--
[YANG DUANHE]
Silence!
Never again open your mouth
to spout nothing but
ancient grudges!
[XIN gasps]
Hear me, one and all, now!
Yang Duanhe, king of
the mountain realm,
binds herself to Ying Zheng,
King of Qin, in a firm alliance.
She... She's a woman!
[YANG DUANHE] In that
alliance's name, we will go
to regain the throne from
which he was unjustly driven.
Gather troops from the
surrounding heights!
All troops prepare to march,
with intentions to
fight to the death!
Our target is Qin's
capital at Xianyang!
[MEN cheer]
[ZHENG]
It begins now...
[XIN]
It's 3,000 against 80,000!
We haven't nearly enough!
[NARRATOR] Facing an
overwhelming disadvantage,
in their hearts lies only
an unshakeable readiness.
Next Time: Onto Xianyang