[NARRATOR] Concerned
about the loss of contact
with Meng Wu's party,
Wang Yi advanced his
soldiers at a fast clip,
and ultimately captured
the enemy's headquarters.
However, it was obvious
neither Meng Wu's
nor the enemy's
forces were there.
Meanwhile, Meng Wu and the
others were in dire straits,
thanks to an enemy ambush when
they entered the mountains
to pursue Pang Nuan.
Wang Yi suspected
that the Zhao Army
had abandoned
its headquarters
to launch an effort to
slay Meng Wu's forces,
and he immediately
began pursuing them.
But even in this critical hour,
Wang Yi continued to feel
a certain "offness."
[WANG YI] I still detect
the faint whiff of a plot.
[WANG YI] But given
Zhao's current positioning
as well as their battle tactics,
they can't possibly
launch anything
large-scale at the moment.
The fact that they make
me uneasy nonetheless
means the trap laid for us is
an awfully elaborate one.
[NARRATOR]
The time: The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
Xin, a nameless boy who rose to
the rank of squadron commander,
carried out a string of exploits
in the midst of battle
that brought the
Qin army an advantage.
However, the enemy's commanding
general has appeared at last,
and has proven to be
beyond all imagination.
That man, said to have a
previous tie to Wang Yi,
is named Pang Nuan.
The war situation is on
the verge of great change!
[ZHENG] What is it that you
must tell me so urgently,
Yang Duanhe?
[YANG DUANHE] Zheng, it has been
about a year since we fought
and won alongside you
against the rebellion of
your brother Cheng Jiao.
We returned to
the mountain world
and spent all our
time waging war.
As a result, my influence
now extends further
than ever before,
wide enough even to border
the land of the equestrian
peoples of the north as well.
The northern equestrian
peoples, The Xiongnu?
That's right.
[YANG DUANHE] The Xiongnu
and the other northern nomads
are nothing at all
like the mountain folk
that we have fought previously.
They possess a great
combat potential,
their profound
understanding of strategy,
the large scale
of their armies...
These warring tribes
are on a different level
by every measure.
I'm aware of it.
That is precisely
why Qin, Zhao and Yan,
which fully border their
sphere of influence,
have built a long
string of fortresses
on our frontiers for defense.
We don't underestimate them.
This is why we raised
an army of 80,000
and invaded Xiongnu lands
to finally wipe them out.
But you are here now.
Does that mean you
routed the Xiongnu?
Did you, then?
[YANG DUANHE]
No. We weren't able to.
You weren't able to?
Then you lost in battle?
[YANG DUANHE]
Well, no, we did not lose.
We went to the land where
the Xiongnu's main force
was supposed to be,
but they weren't
there, apparently.
They were not, apparently?
In their place, we saw
something truly terrible.
Namely...
[YANG DUANHE] ...the corpses
of well over 100,000 Xiongnus.
Over 100,000 corpses...
Maybe then someone else must
have routed the Xiongnu people
before your people arrived?
But who? Another
equestrian tribe?
We call them by
the umbrella name
"equestrian peoples
of the north,"
but in truth there are
many different tribes
such as the Yuezhi,
the Donghu, and the Xiongnu,
all fighting for dominance.
[YANG DUANHE] That was exactly
my first guess as well.
But it seems that I was wrong.
The force that took
down 100,000 Xiongnu
was a Zhao army, you see.
What?!
[YANG DUANHE]
We found the Xiongnu corpses
near a fortress called Yanmen,
the strategic cornerstone of
Zhao's northern border defense.
In other words, a Zhao
army deployed in the north
invaded their lands and then
crushed them. Quite mercilessly.
Impossible!
We have carefully placed
all sorts of spies in Handan,
Zhao's very capital.
Zhao went to war against
an army of 100,000,
even one in the far north,
we would get word of it
here in Xianyang!
I imagine. And yet,
the fact is that
you did not know.
Doesn't that strike you
as frightening now, Zheng?
[YANG DUANHE] Why do
you think you didn't know?
Because, Zhao is
suppressing the information.
To what purpose?
[ZHENG] To hide that they
have a force in the north
powerful enough to
strike the Xiongnu.
But why would they hide it?
Well, because...
[ZHENG gasps]
So why bother to hide
that fact then, Zheng?
[ZHENG] In order to...
send it to join the war
between Qin and Zhao.
Unscrupulously.
[YANG DUANHE] Well then,
if Qin and Zhao are now
perfectly evenly matched
finally, this new army's
appearance would likely
end the war in short order.
The results go without saying.
[LORD CHANGWEN growls]
I can't believe this!
[YANG DUANHE] It's definitely
a pure assumption on my part
that the army will head
south, but if I'm right,
the one who came up with
and executed this whole plan
is a formidable tactician.
As is, the man who
commanded Zhao's slaughter
of the Xiongnu.
It was not the number
of Xiongnu killed
that shocked me that day.
It was how they were killed.
There was just no
indication of resistance.
It was a one-sided slaughter.
They weren't fallen
by military might,
but instead they were destroyed
by strategy, you see.
The two tacticians are the same?
[YANG DUANHE]
Very possibly.
According to the few
surviving warriors,
his name appears to be...
[YANG DUANHE]
...Li Mu.
[rumbling]
[LI MU]
Ah, here they are.
What is that sound?
It can't be...
[DIAO]
That's... a Zhao cavalry!
What are they doing here?!
[WEI JIA] We have come to
escort you, General Li Mu.
Huh? A general?
[LI MU] Thank you, Wei Jia.
I appreciate it.
You tricked us, huh, Kaine?!
I thought you were
a good person!
But you're the enemy!
[DIAO grunts]
[KAINE] Quit talking like
this is a playground fight.
Because what is happening
here is an actual war.
Will you kill us? Can I know?
Rest easy. My lord Li Mu
won't slay anyone
that is not directly connected
with the battle now.
When the war is over,
you will promptly be released.
[KAINE] Well, He Liao Diao,
this is where we part.
If you really do end up
becoming a tactician,
we may meet again
on the battlefield.
As enemies, obviously.
[KAINE] Oh, and that food
that you gave me was good.
See you 'round!
[MENG YI]
Wait!
Please just answer
one question, Kaine.
Who exactly is Li Mu?
How is he involved
in this war now?
That's two questions really.
Very well. I'll just
answer the first one.
Have you ever heard of Zhao's
"Three Greats" or not?
Why yes of course.
Lin Xiangru,
Zhao She and Lian Po.
They were great heroes,
fierce in battle.
Even against Qin's
six great generals
they still held up to them.
[MENG YI] But Lin Xiangru and
Zhao She are no longer alive,
and Lian Po fled to Wei.
So the "Three Greats"
should no longer exist...
Why speak of the
past like this then?
It's true that the
former Three Greats
are long gone these days.
But what if a new generation
of the Three Greats
is being formed currently?
Don't say Li Mu is one?!
You've got it.
[NARRATOR] An area with
some very unique terrain
lay to the southeast of where
Zhao headquarters were located.
Steep cliffs encircled
a vast plain there
on three sides,
in the shape of a bell.
An army was currently
being surrounded there,
pressed against the cliffs.
The surrounding army was Zhao
Zhuang's army of 12,000 men:
The very core of Zhao's forces.
Naturally Zhao Zhuang and Pang
Nuan were at its headquarters.
The army being surrounded
belonged to
Meng Wu and Long Guo.
On their way here,
their forces had been split up
and continually attacked,
leaving them with less than
a thousand horsemen.
Furthermore, each
of these horsemen
was wounded and exhausted.
[LONG GUO] I can't see
any way out of this...
The cliff cuts off any
escape route behind us.
We can't break through
them at this moment.
Not even Meng Wu has
enough strength left,
let alone our men.
I'm afraid we're done for.
This is...
[ZHAO ZHUANG] He's come...
General Pang Nuan.
[NARRATOR] On the exact
fifth day of the war
between Qin and Zhao,
their commanding generals
faced each other at long last.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] It's taken
quite a long time for us
to finally get here,
wouldn't you say...
[WANG YI]
...Liao?
[WANG YI yells]
[WANG YI] You've been anxiously
waiting for this, too,
haven't you, Pang Nuan?
Five days-- No, nine...
...years!
So, shall we finally
settle this, then?
I think it's finally time, sir.
Yeah.
Raise the flag
of the Greats now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
What's with them,
cheering all of a sudden?!
[PEI LANG]
That's the flag of the Greats!
Are they saying one of Zhao's
Three Greats is with them?
I see the name "Three Greats"
has its effect
even if the Greats are fake.
But of course.
That name is engraved
deeply inside the hearts
of all of their
people, you see...
Along with the
magnificent war record
of those three who
fought hard on even terms
with we six notorious
great generals of Qin.
Naturally morale will rise
if they unfurl a flag
of the Greats and
call up those memories.
So then, let's raise the flag
of the six great generals
of Qin right now, my lord.
[WANG YI] Oh, Teng,
there's no such thing!
How very nostalgic,
battling an army
that flies a flag like that.
And since I'm feeling nostalgic,
perhaps I'll do my
old routine again.
[XIN]
This is really bad news!
They got us just
totally overwhelmed...
We gotta get our spirits up
somehow as well now!
[yelling]
What's this shouting now?
I think it is coming
from our army!
[SOLDIERS yelling, cheering]
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] I haven't heard
these particular shouts
in a long time.
Well then, shall we finally
just get right to it, then?
[ZHENG] There was a particular
mystery to this war with Zhao.
[ZHENG] Who was it in
the post-Three Greats
of Zhao who led that large
army to invade our borders?
Ultimately we learned
that the name
of their commanding general
was indeed Pang Nuan.
And yet, just as you said,
Pang Nuan was a pure
crystallization of warfare,
not the sort to lead people
as a general does.
I can't imagine such a man
is a suitable commanding
general at all.
However, if we
assume this "Li Mu"
that Yang Duanhe told us of
has been secretly
mobilizing his army...
[LORD CHANGWEN]
That would solve the mystery.
[ZHENG]
But, if that's true...
Li Mu is no ordinary man.
He can successfully
bring down 100,000 Xiongnu,
yet he waits in secret for
the most advantageous time
to strike Qin.
[ZHENG] Why bother
to use such wiles then?
What exactly is Li Mu after?
Now then, might I
just kindly ask you
if you could battle us first,
dear Zhao Zhuang?
[TENG'S OFFICER 34A]
Cavalry move out!
Follow Lieutenant Teng!
[JIE SHEN] Wang Yi's
cavalry is approaching now!
Archers, take aim!
[ZHAO COMMANDER 34A]
Fire!
Dodge to the right.
Circle right!
[ZHAO ZHUANG'S COMMANDER 34A]
They're heading left!
Fire arrows in that direction!
[ZHAO ZHUANG'S COMMANDER 34B]
No time!
They've gotten in close!
Infantry, at the ready!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
They're in!
[XIN] But, that lieutenant
took 'em in way off-center!
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI]
That will do.
It's exactly what Teng is after.
[FEI XIN FORCE gasps]
[WANG YI] Now, it appears
it's the infantry's turn
up next, young Xin!
You have a big job ahead.
[XIN gasps]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MESSENGER 34A]
My lord!
The left army is
requesting relief!
[MESSENGER 34A]
They are unable to slow
the Wang Yi cavalry's charge!
Keep your heads!
It's a tactic for troops
in the next formation
to prevent an enemy breach.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Put another unit in the path
of the enemy as reinforcement!
[TENG'S OFFICER 34A]
Lieutenant Teng!
They've fortified
themselves to the rear!
[TENG]
Deploy into line.
We're going to dispose of
the enemy archers now.
[WANG YI] I'm counting on you;
dearest foot soldiers.
[WANG YI]
All troops charge!
[XIN]
Charge now!
[JIE SHEN] Sir, the infantry
is now advancing
from the Wang Yi Army's
right side.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Darn Wang Yi...
So he's realized
that our left flank
is the crux of our defense,
and decided to assault it.
He's attempting to
take away the shield
protecting headquarters first.
But if he thinks he's
driven a wedge into us
with that attack...
...he's underestimating us!
Left army, defensive stance!
Repel the enemy--
don't concede a single step!
[ZHAO ZHUANG'S COMMANDER 34B]
Here they come!
Forward infantry, close up ranks
and prepare for
the enemy's charge!
All archers behind them,
at the ready!
Arrows coming any second!
[ZHAO ZHUANG'S COMMANDER 34B]
Fire!
Okay, Fei Xin Force!
Circle left, right now!
[XIN]
Don't stop for nothing!
Run! Run!
Hm. Those foot soldiers...
They're coming for headquarters.
[JIE SHEN] So Wang Yi has
been after our headquarters
from the beginning.
But showing the enemy
your side makes you
the perfect target for archers.
There are more arrows?
What are the left army's
archers doing right now?!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Do you
take me for a fool, Wang Yi?
If a sudden rush on
headquarters actually worked,
everyone would do it.
It's because that
seldom succeeds
that armies attack from the
sides. Perhaps you believe
that you have taken me
off-guard with this right now,
but a surprise attack
on foot will not touch me!
The left army is the
crux of our defense.
But lying in wait is
not the only way to defend.
Zhao infantry charge!
Eat a hole through the Wang Yi
infantry's flank immediately!
Great, we've divided them
successfully it seems!
[YUAN]
Sir!
The enemy has now
made its decisive move.
Yeah.
It's all going exactly according
to General Wang Yi's plan!
[XIN]
"Big job"?
[WANG YI]
As a feint.
Or in this case, perhaps "decoy"
would be the clearer term.
The most efficient way
to break down an
enemy formation,
is to prompt the enemy
itself to make a move.
You're telling us to be decoys
and draw the enemy
out afterwards?
I predict many lives
will be lost in this,
but I do believe it's
the only way Zhao
will definitely come to us.
[XIN]
Many lives...
We are way past being
scared of losing lives,
but if all us foot soldiers
are just decoys,
who the heck will actually
attack their headquarters then?
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI]
Who do you think?
Me, of course!
[PANG NUAN]
Wang Yi, I shall kill thee!
[WANG YI] It is I who shall
kill you, Pang Nuan!
[NARRATOR]
Time for the violent clash.
Unrelenting murderous
intent fills the air!
Next Time: "Commanding
Generals Face to Face."