[XIN]
That means...
...this is the place?
But... Piao, it's just
an ordinary hut!
What's the story here?
[XIN] I come all this way,
without avenging your death,
without even knowing why...
...and this is what I find?
[XIN] Tell me, Piao...
[XIN]
Why?
Why did you die?
Why did you use your dying
breath to guide me here,
to this decrepit old shack?
[XIN] What... What in
the world could be here?
It can't be!
It's not possible!
Piao?!
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm
of war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
Who the hell was that kid?
Little monster!
In all my days of
doing this gig,
never seen a kid that tough.
I-I think my rib is broken!
[VILLAGER 1B] You were sloppy,
you stupid lowlife.
Heibei village is supposed
to be feared by everyone!
You call yourself one of us?
[VILLAGER 1C] Oh yeah,
because you're one to talk.
[VILLAGERS laughing]
You got that right...
Ugh... huh?
[VILLAGER 1C] Hey, what's up?
Over there...
Someone's coming.
Who's this joker?
Hey! What's with you,
Mr. Cool? Huh?
Huh?
[VILLAGER yelling in pain]
W-Wait just a minute!
That outfit...
I've heard of
that uniform before.
[VILLAGER 1A] It can't be...
Then he's...
a Vermilion Slayer!
Vermilion Slayers are
from a clan of assassins
said to have a 200 year history.
He's one of them?
Oh crap!
They say if they target you,
your life is literally over!
You look just like him,
but you're not Piao.
But... But why?
I-I can't look away!
So it's true.
If you've come, that must
mean that Piao's dead.
[XIN] How do you know Piao?
I don't get it!
Who are you?
Why do you have
the same face as Piao?!
And how do you
know Piao and me?
Look, would you tell me what
this is all this about?!
[ZHENG] It seems there
isn't time to explain.
Wh-What was that?
An enemy?
Who the hell are you?
There's no escaping me now.
[XU WAN] Your life is mine,
High King Ying Zheng.
[XIN]
Did... Did he just say...?
You're...
...the king of Qin?!
[ZHENG] I am.
[XU WAN] Ahh, so you're not
one of the King's retinue,
little one?
Yes, you're standing
beside the King,
who's managed to keep himself
alive a little longer
thanks to a very
excellent stand-in.
A stand-in?
[XU WAN] It's surprising
that two different people
could look
that much alike.
Even I was fooled,
if you can believe it.
What's more, that stand-in was
quite an amazing boy.
He's the first prey who
ever managed to escape me,
even though I struck
him a mortal blow.
[XU WAN] Ironically, though,
that same stubborn streak
ended up betraying him.
It allowed me to
track you to this place.
Xin... We're both the same...
...in both ability and spirit.
The two of us have
always been one at heart.
If you spread
your wings and fly...
I promise...
I'll be there, too...
Xin... take me with you...
...and conquer everything
under the heavens.
Piao!
[XIN] Piao... Piao...
[XIN screams]
Damn you... It's all
falling into place now!
You're the King...
...and you're an assassin!
[XIN] That's why Piao
was taken to court
in the first place,
wasn't it?
[XIN] He was supposed
to be the stand-in
because he looked
just like the King!
And when it worked, he was
mistaken for you and killed!
You knew that your half-brother
would rebel against you!
So you ran away here to
hide yourself, safe and sound,
and left Piao in your place!
You left him at court,
making him pretend to be you,
knowing that he'd be attacked!
Yes, that's exactly right.
Damn you...
Well, well, things
have gotten interesting.
Little one?
If you wish, I'll
relinquish the pleasure
of killing
the King to you.
His head, however,
still belongs to me.
[XIN] I'll kill him.
I'll cut him to pieces.
[XU WAN] Good, little one.
I'll watch and see
what skills you have.
[XIN] You'll sit back and watch?
Oh, no, you won't!
You're the one who
killed Piao, after all!
I'll tear your guts out!
[ZHENG] This boy's
swordsmanship is extraordinary.
But still...
[XU WAN]
You're good, little one.
Your strength,
quickness, and skill
are all on par
with that stand-in,
Piao, or whatever his name was.
[XU WAN] But when
it comes down to it,
your sword's never
tasted real blood.
[XIN] He's huge!
You'd need at least another
hundred years of training
before you could challenge me!
[XU WAN] What a pointless
waste of my time.
Now, Ying Zheng...
Prepare for your end.
My half-brother's
head isn't here yet.
Give it more time,
honored lord.
The one who's pursuing him
is a Vermilion Slayer.
He should return with
your brother's head soon.
"Should?" That's your
excuse of an answer?
[PO SHI groaning]
[JIE SHI] Now now, please,
try to calm yourself,
most honored lord.
Rest assured,
no other assassins
can surpass the
Vermilion Slayers.
I see.
However, there's still
another obstacle
besides my half-brother.
You're taking the
necessary measures, I trust?
[JIE SHI]
In all things, Lordship.
A-Another obstacle?
Mmm. Did you not know?
[JIE SHI] To deal
with that Lord Changwen,
I decided it needed
a special touch,
so I sent the men who turned
the Battle of Changping
into Hell itself.
[chuckles]
[PO SHI]
Th-The Battle of Changping?
At Changping, our Qin army
drove the Kingdom of Zhao's
forces back into their castle,
then cut off
their food supply.
[PO SHI] They say that
in the madness
and pangs of starvation,
the soldiers of the Zhao army
began to kill one another
as meat to eat.
[PO SHI]
That was how our kingdom
gained the final
victory in the battle.
But our commanding general,
General Bai Qi,
wasn't satisfied.
He had 50,000
prisoners of war beheaded,
and 400,000 soldiers
buried alive.
That was the hell known as
the Battle of Changping.
A-And now...
The ones who did that...
[yelling in pain]
Kill every last
person who opposes me.
Understood.
That's my good Minister.
[laughs ominously]
[XIN] Wait, you...
[XU WAN] Huh?
[XIN] Do you think that
you've already beaten me?
[XU WAN] What?
Oh, you're still
breathing, are you?
But now your will's
been completely broken.
I doubt you can even stand.
[XIN] He's good...
No, he's impossibly good.
He was able to defeat Piao.
[XIN] I can't pretend anymore...
I'm no match for him.
There's no way I could
hope to beat him.
[XIN] I'm sorry, Piao...
I'm so sorry.
[ZHENG] Xin.
Don't keep
over-thinking things.
Or, if you must think,
then concentrate on purging
your regrets over Piao.
My regrets over Piao?
[XIN] Don't you ever...
He's standing!
Don't you ever speak
Piao's name again!
[XIN] Piao...
Piao's life was just beginning!
And you tangled him up in
a petty brothers' quarrel!
Petty, you say?
Yes, it was petty!
You think us people
on the bottom
give a damn
about who's King?!
None of that matters!
And as for you...
You... curse you!
Because of you, he's dead.
And now he's never...
He's never coming back again!
[ZHENG] He's fast.
And the blow was heavier.
This little one...
[PIAO] Yes, it's true
that Xin's ability and mine
are about equal.
But still...
When it comes down to it,
Xin might be stronger.
[ZHENG] Xin is stronger?
[PIAO] Yes, Your Majesty.
What a strange thing to say.
You just finished
claiming you were equals.
When I spar with Xin,
we're exactly matched.
Just the same if an
opponent were too strong
for me to beat,
Xin could still win.
[ZHENG] Does that mean
that he was holding back
in all your bouts?
[PIAO] No, Your Majesty.
Xin always goes all out.
For some reason,
when we fight, he's my equal.
But whenever I got
one victory ahead of him,
Xin would always
win the next day.
What a tiresome fellow.
Sounds annoying.
Well, I can't deny that!
[laughs]
[PIAO] He can be
tiresome, but still...
[PIAO] ...Xin truly
is strong, Majesty.
[XU WAN]
Time to die, little one!
[XU WAN] Now the horror
is just beginning for you!
[ZHENG] No...
[ZHENG]
Xin's reading his attacks!
What's this?
Is that all you got,
Mr. Red Guy?
[XU WAN] Enough words!
[XU WAN] Huh? This little one...
He's dodging my blade.
But still,
if that's all he does...
[ZHENG] ...then he can't win.
What will you do, Xin?
[XU WAN] This is the end!
[ZHENG] You're getting
flustered, assassin.
Now you're mine!
[XU WAN] Little one!
[XU WAN] Impossible!
I've been cut!
Die, little one!
[XU WAN] He's vanished!
[PIAO] Your Majesty...
If anything should happen to me,
please, trust in Xin.
[PIAO] I'm certain...
[PIAO] ...He'll soar
higher than anyone!
[XU WAN] It can't be...
This little one...
could beat me?!
[ZHENG] So... this
is Xin's strength.
[XIN] You... You killed Piao...
I'll show you!
Now who's laughing,
you damn monster?!
You're finished!
[XU WAN] W-Wait!
Please, I beg you!
I have family.
I have four children!
If I die, they'll become
orphans and sold into slavery!
Please, let me live!
Just spare my life,
for my children's sake!
Orphans?
Ah... Thank you.
Thank you so much,
from the bottom
of my heart.
[XU WAN] Thank--
Your children
have no bearing
on your crimes.
[ZHENG] So what's next?
Do you wish to kill me?
[ZHENG] If so, know that I will
not just stand here and let you.
More than a few
people have already died
to protect me
this far, after all.
Your friend Piao
was among them.
[XIN] Damn you...
You knew he'd be
attacked by this fiend.
Why did you stand by
and let Piao die?
[ZHENG] A life belongs
to no one else.
Only to the person
who lives it.
[XIN] Wh-What?
[ZHENG] Every person has a path.
How a person chooses
to live their life--
That is their path.
Stop trying to trick me
with your stupid blather!
[ZHENG] You probably can't
understand right now.
But in order to become
a great general,
Piao agreed to
become my stand-in.
That was the path he chose
for himself at the time.
And as for you, it seems you
haven't found your path yet.
My path... huh?
[XIN] Piao, you entrusted
this country's King to me.
But... it's almost as if
he killed you himself!
[XIN] Damn it!
What am I supposed to do?!
Tell me what to do, Piao!
[XIN] What...
What are you doing?
[ZHENG] Be silent.
[ZHENG] This is bad.
Can you feel it?
[XIN] The ground...
I felt it tremble
a little, just now.
Shoot!
Everything that moves
is a target!
Loose arrows!
[XIN] Hey, what is that?
What's going on?
Soldiers... and a lot of them.
Soldiers?
Oh man, what's with all
the noise so late at night?
[distant yelling]
They're over there!
And over there, too?
Crap. We're surrounded.
We're gonna have
to take the river.
[ZHENG] That won't work.
[XIN] When did they show up?
What is all this?
[ZHENG] It seems
my brother's influence
has tainted the
entire army hierarchy.
[ZHENG] Perhaps the outcome of
this fight was already decided
back when I
anticipated this revolt,
but lacked the
strength to suppress it.
[XIN] Damn it...
Well, wanna raise
a ruckus one last time?
You...
You mean to fight with that?
Of course I do!
You won't catch me dying here!
You could also take the
path of trading my head
for your survival.
That's ridiculous!
There's no way Piao would have
ever wanted that to happen.
I see.
And I don't have enough strength
left to fight my way uphill,
so I'll have to go
along the river.
Stay right with me!
Fool.
It's impossible for you to break
through this encirclement...
Wait, "stay with you?"
[XIN] Once we break
through these troops,
I want to take my time
deciding whether or not
to kill you.
So don't leave my side.
[ZHENG] Well, no help for it.
Guess I'm with you.
Right. Let's go!
Hey! I know you!
[giggling]
I know a way through.
Come with me.
[ZHENG] He knew the risks,
and yet, he still tried!
He accepted, knowing it
might even mean death.
[NARRATOR] Xin, can you find
a new light for yourself
beyond the endless
flow of tears?
Next time: "For a Friend."