[ZHENG]
We're here, at last.
It took us an
awful long time.
[DIAO] Then...
you're saying that's...
That's right.
That... that is the
capital of Qin... Xianyang.
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm of
war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[XIN]
Wh-What is that?
It's so huge, I can't even
make out which part is which!
Holy crap!
Stop falling to pieces, dummy!
A place that big?
I mean... who could...
why would...
How could we do that?!
[DIAO]
Calm down!
That's impressive.
Hey, Zheng, you're telling
me that we're gonna
try to storm that?!
We are.
How the heck are we supposed to
attack something so huge?
I can't even see the far
edges of it from here!
Stop raising a fuss.
[XIN]
Huh?
[ZHENG]
Can you see further in?
There's a row of
larger buildings
standing out from the rest.
[XIN]
Huh? Yeah, I see 'em.
[ZHENG]
That's the Royal Court.
Our reports say that
news of this rebellion
hasn't been publicized
outside its walls.
That means those
outside the Court
aren't tainted by
my half-brother.
[DIAO] So that means
we only need to strike
at the Royal Court,
and nothing else?
[ZHENG]
Correct.
[XIN]
Hold on a second!
The Royal Court's still
smack dab in the middle
of Xianyang, isn't it?
[ZHENG]
Of course it is.
Xianyang has tier
after tier of walls,
as well as residences
for the nobility,
warriors, and commoners,
with the Court at the
center of it all.
In short, Xianyang itself
is an enormous castle.
[XIN] Oh good, you at
least acknowledge it.
Well, now that's
been cleared up,
how do we get through
all that to the Court?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
That's why we spoke about
creating a stratagem.
[XIN] That's easy to say,
but there's more
than just those high walls!
There's a legion of troops
waiting in there, too, right?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
That's the key to our plan.
80,000, eh?
[JIE SHI] That's not
nearly enough, Si Shi.
[SI SHI]
My humble apologies, my lord.
We still haven't found
the Royal Seal,
so this was the greatest number
we could muster in time.
[JIE SHI] You do not need
some worthless Royal Seal
just to muster troops, you fool!
Use bribes, use threats,
use whatever means
necessary to light fires
under the rear ends of the
cowards playing wait-and-see!
This is no defensive war.
We have but one aim:
To annihilate Lü Buwei's
200,000 men!
And to do that,
we are going to need
far more men than this.
Raise another 100,000
troops immediately!
Do not disappoint me again.
Is that clear, Si Shi?
[SI SHI growls]
[XIN]
80,000 is too few?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Yes.
In his initial plans,
he almost certainly counted on
raising an army
of about 400,000.
[LORD CHANGWEN] But only
80,000 responded to his call.
Mark my words, Jie Shi
will be feeling worried.
So if some troops
offering to support him
were to appear unexpectedly...
That would be us!
Yes.
Convince him we're allies and
have him invite us inside...
...then we can get past the
walls without any injury.
[XIN, DIAO]
Ohh...
Now... let's go!
[yawns]
Huh? Whoa!
[SENTRY 10A]
What is that?!
[ZHENG]
At long last.
Yang Duanhe, I am grateful
you're fighting by our side.
[YANG DUANHE] Words of
gratitude should be saved
for after the battle's won.
[ZHENG] After our victory,
I won't just give you words,
but a castle and a warm
welcome for your people.
[YANG DUANHE]
I'll look forward to it.
[JIE SHI] You say a
throng of mountain folk
appeared at the west gate?
[JIANG]
Yes, my lord.
[JIE SHI]
How many?
[JIANG]
Between two and three thousand.
They're strangely dressed,
but they're all
mounted and bearing weapons.
[JIANG] Still, they're
apparently showing
no signs of aggression.
Did they not send a messenger
to announce their intentions?
They did, but all he said
was that the mountain king
had come down from the hills
to renew the old alliance.
Then he returned to his troops.
[JIE SHI] The mountain king...
an alliance?
Makes you wonder if
that legion of 80,000
is gonna make a
sudden appearance.
Oh, like I wasn't
already nervous!
Why do you keep saying
things like that?
Everything will be fine.
They'll take us up on it,
without a doubt.
[XIN]
I sure hope you're right!
[OFFICIAL 10A] If we're going
to confront Lü Buwei soon,
any gain in allies would
be welcome at this point!
It may only be 3,000 men,
but if they're descended from
the Horse &amp; Liquor forces,
they'll be a force
to be reckoned with!
[PO SHI]
Wait! Why would people
who've been isolated
for so many years
suddenly seek to
renew an alliance?
Mark my words, they must
be plotting something.
[OFFICIAL 10B] But...
they're already at the gates,
waiting for our answer!
What would you have us do?
Are we about join hands
with mountain monkeys?
We should deploy 30,000 men
and go slaughter them!
[OFFICIAL 10C]
Huh...
That actually would be a
good training exercise
before facing Lü Buwei's army!
It's taking forever!
They're opening.
[XIN gasps]
Please enter,
most honored guests.
The Kingdom of Qin welcomes you
and yours to the Royal Court.
Now you're inviting monkeys
into the Royal Court?
Why have you made this decision
without consulting me first?
To seal a useful
alliance, my lord.
You said you would give me full
responsibility over governing,
and so I made my own decision.
If it is not to your liking,
please forgive me,
my honored lord...
But first, please consider...
Would it not be a pleasure
for you to watch
the wild mountain folk
fight Lü Buwei's forces
and tear them to pieces?
Pitting rabid monkeys against
raccoon dogs, you mean?
[JIE SHI]
Just so, my lord.
[CHENG JIAO] Still, I refuse
to speak with monkeys.
You don't need to.
All you need to do is sit on
the throne as King of Qin.
Leave everything else
to me, your Minister.
[XIN]
Ha, ha! That was too easy!
Everything's going well for now.
[BI]
But just imagine...
What if we had had to
breach this many walls
in order to get in?
Frankly, the thought
of it gives me chills.
[XIN]
Even you think so, Bi, my man?
Of course I do.
Storming a stronghold
normally requires
two or three times
the enemy's numbers.
We're talking about
taking it with only 3,000.
You could call this the most
outlandish stratagem ever.
[XIN]
Really?
Now I'm kinda getting
all pumped up about it!
It's good that you're eager,
but don't get careless.
We may be outside
the Royal Court,
but this is still hostile turf.
Yeah, sure, I get that.
[DIAO]
Huh?
Look, Xin! It's the town!
[DIAO, XIN]
Whoa...
[BI]
Something's strange.
[XIN]
What is it, Bi, my man?
This is different from
the Xianyang I know.
There's a subtle tension
hanging in the air.
Do you think they might
be onto us already?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I doubt that.
Look carefully among the crowds.
[XIN] There's a lot
of guys wearing black.
[BI]
They're gendarmes.
[XIN]
Gendarmes? What are those?
[BI] They're officials
who arrest people
who step out of line.
Now I see...
The prince's followers
and partisans
are keeping the people
of the city muzzled.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Cheng Jiao's kingship
must be seen as legitimate
and enabled by the King's
"sudden demise,"
not as something usurped
or taken by force.
The bad rumors
leaking from court
must be firmly sealed
up before they spread.
According to the
reports from our spies,
anyone who speaks openly
about the Court now,
is immediately
arrested by gendarmes
and is never heard from again.
That's despicable.
[ZHENG]
That's only the beginning.
Both Cheng Jiao and
Jie Shi will stop at nothing
to achieve their aims.
This is no more than a
fraction of the oppression
those two will enact.
They're monkeys, aren't they?
Knock it off!
We have got orders
not to provoke them.
[ZUO CI]
Hey!
[GENDARME 10B]
Huh?
[ZUO CI]
You're in the way.
If you think you
can get away with
acting like that towards us...
[ZUO CI]
Huh?
[GENDARME 10A]
That's Zuo Ci! And Wei Xing.
They're upper-level
army officers.
And that third guy...
If he's being accompanied
by those two...
Then that man has got to be the
strong arm of Minister Jie Shi:
Si Shi!
You men can leave now.
[GENDARMES]
Yes, sir. By your leave!
Isn't the Minister acting
a bit too desperate
by inviting this
rabble to court?
I mean, it's just to get his
hands on a mere 3,000 troops.
It's not just 3,000.
That man there is the conqueror
of the mountain realm,
Yang Duanhe.
If we forge an
alliance with him,
we gain the support of
over 100,000 mountain folk.
[WEI XING]
I see.
The Minister made the decision
based on that expectation.
[SI SHI]
Yet one thing still troubles me.
Why now?
For hundreds of years
they've been isolated.
Why now have they
suddenly shown up?
Bah, my hand got dirty.
So, this is it?
The Royal Court.
[XIN] It's bigger than it looked
from the top of that cliff.
Guess that's a given...
What's wrong?
Are you finally losing
your nerve, Zheng?
I was thinking about
how it all began here.
At Court, Piao spoke
of nothing but you.
[XIN]
H-Huh?
His eyes used to gleam when
he was talking about you,
like he was showing
off his treasure.
He told me about the
training you two did,
about how you used an ox instead
of a horse to practice riding,
and about how you both dreamed
of becoming great generals.
Generals...
That's right!
We'll dress in golden armor,
and ride all across the Earth!
And in the end,
we'll become the greatest
generals in all the world!
Yeah... the greatest generals!
And then, our names
will go down in history!
[ZHENG] If not for
Cheng Jiao's rebellion,
I never would have
met Piao, or you.
But then, Piao wouldn't
have died either.
[ZHENG] And now, the ringleaders
who started this rebellion
are on the other
side of this wall.
It's time to settle
things... Xin!
Yeah!
If things go wrong, don't die.
[XIN]
Me, die?
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
No way!
This is my first
step toward becoming
the world's greatest general!
You think I'm gonna
stumble now?!
[JIANG] Minister, why do
you not excuse yourself
from going to greet
them in person?
After all, they are barbarians.
You really are a fool.
You understand nothing
of this, Jiang.
It's Yang Duanhe
that I'm meeting.
Huh?
[JIE SHI] In the past, I've
conducted some private trading
with the mountain folk, enough
to learn a little of them.
They have countless
different tribes.
Even I knew nothing of
this latest congregation.
But I have heard of this
mountain king, Yang Duanhe.
My sources say he has
a strong interest
in the flatlands
and was seeking an opportunity
to come down here.
Since Yang Duanhe
ascended the throne,
the mountain folk's strength
has grown by leaps and bounds.
Now is the moment we need
that strength for ourselves.
[BA JIO] They say the
king and up to 50 envoys
may proceed into court.
Just 50?
How can only 50 of our guys
fight against 80,000?!
You can be quiet.
[ZHENG] There's no chance
that all 80,000 soldiers
and militiamen are
within the Court.
The troops are
stationed to the east,
some distance from here.
[XIN]
Oh. Well, why didn't you say so?
Once they get wind of any
strange events at Court,
they'll soon come pouring in.
We must strike down
Cheng Jiao and Jie Shi
before they do.
Lord Changwen, select ten
men with knowledge
of the Court's layout.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Yes, sir.
[BI]
When the fighting starts,
should we have the people on
the outside break the gates?
[ZHENG] No, that would bring in
the enemy forces from outside.
Our only hope of
winning this battle
is to keep it inside
the walls of the Court.
To that end, those waiting
outside the gates
will guard all exits and
capture anyone who comes out.
Pick the other 40 from
among the mountain folk.
[BA JIO]
Understood.
Hey, I'm coming, too!
Obviously.
[TAJIFU grunts]
[XIN yells]
[XIN] Why are you trying
to come along with us?
[DIAO]
Whoa!
Get outta here!
[DIAO]
Well, that's impossible now!
[XIN]
I can't believe this!
Don't you understand
what's about to happen?
[DIAO]
Yeah, I understand.
But if you guys fail inside,
everybody else on the outside
will be killed anyway.
[DIAO] Besides, there's
no place for me among
that bunch out there.
Huh?
[DIAO] They don't really
interact with me at all,
even after seeing how I dress.
It just seems like they're
not really my kin.
Which means... I'm with you.
I'll come with you guys...
That way, I can achieve great
deeds and become massively rich!
[XIN] Well, not my
fault if you get killed.
[DIAO] The great He Liao Diao
of Heibei Village
won't die so easily. Ha, ha, ha!
[JIANG] At the Red Turtle Gate,
we'll confiscate their weapons
and let only the
mountain king
and one attendant pass.
The king himself
has agreed to come,
so it's unlikely this
is just part of a plot,
but if something does happen,
that gate is our best defense.
So as a precaution,
we've positioned a large
contingent of guards there
to reinforce it and keep
the mountain folk in line.
[JIE SHI]
Mmm.
[XIN]
Wait...
They're gonna confiscate
our weapons?!
[BA JIO]
Yes.
But then we're not gonna
be able to fight, are we?
Precisely.
That's why this is the place...
The place where battle begins!
[JIE SHI] Look. The mountain
folk are almost here.
Oh man...
Looks like this'll be a flashy
start to the fighting...
[DIAO] Is it... is it
about to start now?
[XIN]
That's right.
[DIAO]
This is bad!
They've got twice as
many soldiers as us!
[XIN]
It doesn't matter.
[DIAO gasping, panting]
[DIAO]
Wait, Xin... please...
Can't breathe.
My chest is hurting...
I can barely walk.
Diao!
Whatever happens,
don't leave my side!
You hear me?
I... I understand!
I won't leave you,
for even a second!
People of the mountain!
We'll collect your weapons here!
Set aside your arms, all of you.
[SOLDIER 10A]
They're acting strangely...
[BA JIO]
No.
The right to strike the
first blow in this war...
[CAPTAIN OF THE GUARD 10A]
What do you think you're doing?
[BA JIO]
...belongs to one man!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
M-Minister! What on
earth is going on?!
Minister Jie Shi?
What are you monkeys doing?!
Kill them! Kill them all!
[YANG DUANHE]
Blood for the gods!
[DIAO]
Xin!
Here it goes! Diao!
[DIAO]
Ah... right!
Minister Jie Shi, we should
take refuge within, now!
Stop panicking so much.
So Yang Duanhe, you think you've
put one over on me, do you?
But you've underestimated
the Red Turtle Gate,
you mountain monkeys!
[XIN, DIAO yelp]
Bi, my man, the gates
aren't opening! What do we do?
[BI] The Red Turtle Gate
is so strongly built
that it can't be smashed
by anything less
than a catapult!
That's why they chose this
spot to make their stand!
Don't even try to
scale the walls!
You'll just be a target!
But what else can we do?
If we can't break the gate,
the only way is
to climb the wall
and open it from the other side!
[BI]
You're right!
But the wall's way too high
for us to scale it safely
in a single go.
Then what do we do?
That's a good question.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Fortify a
position beside the wall!
We'll build a human ladder
and climb over it!
My lord, as things stand,
we'll only sacrifice more lives!
[LORD CHANGWEN] I know.
But there's no other way.
Don't flinch!
There's no chance of victory
unless we surmount that wall!
[XIN growls]
[JIE SHI]
Jiang!
Choosing the Red Turtle Gate
as the entry point
and increasing the number of
guards was a very wise call.
Yes, sir!
[JIE SHI] Reinforce the troops
and concentrate the attack
from the rear.
Kill them all in the
shadow of the gates!
[DIAO] No good!
This was a mistake, Xin!
There's no way past the gate!
It's impossible! Fighting
it out here is pointless!
[XIN]
There's no choice but to do it!
There's nothing
left but to do it!
Another one's trying
to go up the wall!
It's madness! Come back, Xin!
[BI] Even the mountain folk
can't make it up that wall!
[XIN yells]
[DIAO]
Xin!
[XIN]
Let's do this!
That hurt!
[BI]
He...
He made it!
No! Protect Xin!
Time for you to die!
Uh-oh!
[GUARD yelping]
I got him...
[JIE SHI]
Wha...
What's this?!
So, did you see that?
[XIN] Oh, there's a
big old guy up here.
Kill this insolent monkey-boy!
[XIN]
Here they come.
You're too late, boys.
I'm sorry...
...but this fight is
a memorial for Piao,
so there'll be no mercy.
[BI]
We'll move to the inner sanctum
and strike at Cheng Jiao there!
[NARRATOR] The lives and
resolves of two sides clash.
Don't hang back, Xin!
Next Time:
A Fierce Battle Begins.