It--It's impossible,
Your Highness!
Our strength is quite feeble.
What's more,
there's now no force in Qin
not bound to Lü or to Jie Shi
that would even
consider aiding us!
Do you think so, Xin?
Can you suggest some
way to do this, Zheng?
Huh? Hey, that blowgun!
That's that old guy's, right?
[DIAO] What about it?
He gave it to me!
[XIN] Let me see it!
[DIAO] No! It's mine now!
[LORD CHANGWEN] There is...
[XIN] I won't take it.
I said let me see!
My lord, did you
say something?
There is one.
There is one significantly
large force
not bound to Lü or to Jie Shi.
I have been thinking of that
ever since we
first arrived here.
[ZHENG]
The likelihood is small.
We can only go to meet them...
The mountain folk, and the
mountain king who rules them.
[NARRATOR] Ancient China.
The time of the
sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries
an endless storm
of war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away
until only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
[NARRATOR] This is
the tale of a nameless boy
and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
Yaaah!
[birds chirping]
[DIAO panting]
Hey! Wait, Zheng!
[sighs]
I'd never heard about
mountain king's
existence before.
Does that mean in the
mountains there's a country
just like Qin, with a king,
too, and everything?
No. It means something
a bit different.
As you are well aware,
the mountain folk all live
their lives as separate tribes,
but it's said that
they sometimes unite
for the benefit of all.
The one who speaks for and
advises that confederation
is the one we call
the mountain king.
[XIN] Hey, Zheng.
[DIAO gasps]
[SOLDIERS breathing heavily]
Some of them are
starting to fall behind.
None of that
shuffling along, men!
[XIN] We're not
out here for a stroll!
[BI]
How can you say that, Xin?
You haven't the least idea
how exhausted we truly are.
[XIN] So what? Slow is slow!
If we're shuffling
along like this,
that Cheng Jiao or whatnot
is gonna become King!
[LORD CHANGWEN] Uh!
Blasted little one.
But if we don't hurry now...
[LORD CHANGWEN] We must
bring our King before
the mountain king
with all possible haste.
[LORD CHANGWEN] And more,
there may possibly
still be pursuers.
[PLATOON LEADER 7A]
Don't lose focus.
Minister Jie has
rigorous expectations.
Who knows what punishment
we may all face
if we do not find the boy!
[SOLDIERS] Yes, sir!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIERS sigh in relief]
[exhales deeply]
SOLDIERS groan]
What the--?
[yelling]
[commotion]
What--What? What in the...?!
[squelch]
[groans]
[whistles]
[DIAO] Whoa!
[DIAO] Wow, amazing view!
[DIAO] But still, Zheng,
how is it you know the way
through these mountains
to the mountain king's keep?
[ZHENG] Duke Mu's
summer retreat was built
at the halfway point between
Qin's capital Xianyang
and the mountain king's keep.
So the general
direction is clear,
[ZHENG] and if we rely
on the appearing markers,
we'll come to the
mountain king's keep.
[DIAO] Ooh.
[XIN] Oh, I see.
[groans]
C'mon, get up!
Huh? What the
heck's going on?
I'm just fine.
Someone give him
a shoulder to lean on.
[LORD CHANGWEN] No!
Huh?
Those who can't keep up
will return to Duke Mu's
retreat and stand by.
[BI] My lord?
Hear me, everyone!
I'll have those
who slow our march
drop out immediately.
Burn it into your brains!
[ALL gasp]
Wait, my lord!
Holding to that, you realize
that most of the men
will drop out
on the road ahead!
There's no other way.
Just as Xin says,
if Cheng Jiao ends up
taking the throne,
everything will be for nothing.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
We must all make haste.
Pardon me,
but no one will then remain
to guard and protect the King
against those
fearsome mountain folk
if we don't protect the King
with every last soldier...
They're fearsome?
Just think. If the mountain
folk attack us all in earnest,
it will definitely not
make a whit of difference
whether all these men
are there or not.
[XIN] Just hold on!
What's this about
"fearsome mountain folk"?
Aren't the mountain folk
the nice guys who
carefully preserved
Duke Mu's place
for 400 years?
I see.
You don't know the tale of
the "Horse &amp; Liquor Force."
"Horse &amp; Liquor Force"?
[BI] About 400 years
before the present,
the sovereign of our land
of Qin was so open-hearted
that he presented liquor
to the mountain folk
who'd unknowingly
hunted a horse he owned.
[XIN] I know! Duke Mu, right?
[BI] That's right.
It was the 13th year
of Duke Mu's reign.
There had once been
a Kingdom of Jin.
[XIN] A Kingdom of Jin?
[BI] Yes.
At the time, that kingdom
to the east of Qin
had been visited
by a great famine.
[BI] Jin was an enemy kingdom,
but to save those suffering
from hunger, Duke Mu sent food.
[XIN] Whoa!
What a guy, that Duke Mu!
[BI] Then, in the next year,
our land of Qin
was visited by famine.
[BI]
But when Duke Mu sought aid,
Jin attacked, attempting
to overrun our land.
What?!
But who would do that?!
[BI] At this,
even Duke Mu was so furious
he stood at the head
of the army and fought.
The men of Qin, though,
lacking substantial food,
grew weaker and weaker.
And Duke Mu was surrounded
by Jin's great army.
[XIN] Uh! Oh no!
Duke Mu was in a real pinch!
[BI] It was certain death.
But just then
they came forth...
[groans]
[BI] The fabled ones we call
the "Horse &amp; Liquor Force."
300 mountain folk enshrouded
in a strange aura of death.
[XIN] Mountain folk?
[DIAO] But why?
They had all come to repay
their debt to Duke Mu...
For the horse and the liquor.
I understand. They're the
"Horse &amp; Liquor Force"!
But then that would make them
really great people,
wouldn't it?
They certainly took
their duty seriously.
However...
[yelling]
[BI] It's said that their
fighting was so savage
that even the Qin soldiers,
whose side they'd taken,
felt terror.
[XIN] Huh?
[BI] What's more,
after a mere 300 of them
routed thousands of enemy
troops and saved Duke Mu,
they seized the enemy king.
[BI] The mountain folk are
a fearsomely warlike people.
It's wishful thinking
to believe because
they preserve Duke Mu's
retreat that the mountain folk
bear goodwill toward
the people of Qin.
Since we were the ones
who cut off relations
after Duke Mu's death,
a more natural
assumption might be
that they detest us.
And now we are all
setting foot in their realm
without their
permission, you see.
What'll become of us
if we are seen as enemies?
I now get it.
Now I really understand
how fearsome
the mountain folk truly are.
[BI] You understand?
And that's why--
And that's why making
allies with them is worthwhile.
[gasps]
That's it, right, Zheng?
Indeed it is.
[DIAO] Hey, Zheng's way
ahead all alone!
[XIN] Hey, wait up, Zheng!
[BI gasps]
[intense music plays]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Even in
becoming an official,
I've always thought myself
a warrior at the ready.
Aging is a
frightening thing.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Just the same,
this is no time for whining.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
The only sword His Highness
can rely on is me.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
That one can't do it.
His temperament is too direct.
The path out of
this warring world
can't be cut simply
through martial skills.
[LORD CHANGWEN] No, only I...
What the--?
Uh!
[gasps]
[ZHENG] The mountain folk?
It's them!
Go defend the King, now!
[LORD CHANGWEN] Form a
circle around the King, now!
Don't do it!
[gasping]
If they were so inclined,
they would have
attacked already.
You're saying they
came out to greet us?
They're carrying some
wicked gear to do so.
[BA JIO] This is our realm.
That's our language...
..he's speaking.
[BA JIO] When flatlanders
willfully enter,
we gouge out their eyes and
drop them down a waterfall.
--[XIN] Wh--?!
--[DIAO] Aah!
[BA JIO] But you have
come to see our king.
We'll decide what to do
depending on your reasons.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
But how exactly do you know
that we have all
come here to see the--?
[BA JIO]
Our king knows all things.
Young King of Qin,
our king awaits you.
We will take you
to his keep from here.
We'd been scared!
Well this makes
things real simple.
Right! Let's get moving!
[chuckles]
[XIN yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[XIN] Ow...
[BI, DIAO] Xin!
Er! What's with you,
jerk-wad?!
[BA JIO] You misunderstand.
It's your king alone
we'll take with us.
The rest of you
go back immediately.
[ALL gasp]
[LORD CHANGWEN]
What did you say?!
What if we say no?
[BA JIO]
We will kill you all.
[BA JIO] Swiftly.
It's a hot-tempered bunch
gathered here today.
[grunts, growls]
Uuh...!
[grunting and growling]
[XIN yells]
[gasping]
[XIN grunts]
We certainly understand
your position.
Now we'll have our say.
[growl]
[XIN] If all of you guys don't
want to get yourselves killed,
you would be wise
to take us all
to your king immediately,
understand?
[yells]
[yelling]
Hold it!
[snarling]
Both sides,
throw your weapons.
[ZHENG]
As the mountain folk bid,
I will go alone
to meet their king.
Wait, Your Highness.
To leave you all by yourself
and then descend...
Descend, all of you,
and you shall await my return.
This is, the King's command!
[gasps]
[XIN] Hey, Zheng!
Are you
sending me back, too?
I thought I was supposed
to be your sword and all?
A sword isn't needed
for a discussion.
Have it your way.
[MESSENGER 7A]
General Wang Yi!
Orders have come
from Minister Jie
for you to assume command
of the garrison at Hangu Pass.
[WANG YI] Tell him a passive
role isn't to my taste,
and that I decline.
[MESSENGER 7A] Yes, sir!
[WANG YI]
The Hangu Pass, huh?
[NARRATOR] The Hangu Pass
is an important barrier,
the keystone of
Qin's eastern defenses.
[NARRATOR] To prevent Lü
Buwei's army from returning
to Qin from its
expedition in Wei,
Jie Shi's side must
hold this Hangu Pass.
[WANG YI] Sounds like Jie Shi's
started preparations
for an all-out fight with Lü.
Now that the King is gone,
things have started moving...
His returning
to center stage now
would be a difficult feat,
wouldn't it, Teng?
Yes, a difficult feat.
[WANG YI] Ying Zheng...
an unlucky king born
in a peculiar context.
Prince Zheng will
surpass King Zhao!
[WANG YI] Hmmm...
In what way could he
surpass King Zhao,
the "god of the battlefield"?
[WANG YI] I would
sure like to see that.
In the end,
his Highness went on alone
out of concern for us.
But Zheng, being invited
counts for something.
He'll be okay, right?
You don't call that
an invitation.
It's an abduction.
He is gonna
get himself killed now.
[DIAO] Hey! Don't say stuff
like that so casually!
[grunts]
[XIN] He's definitely
gonna get himself killed.
[DIAO] Hey!
[grunts] What on Earth
was he thinking?
"Get the support
of the mountain folk."
--[LORD CHANGWEN grunts]
--[XIN yells]
[DIAO yells]
[LORD CHANGWEN yells]
[yells]
What are you doing you...
...you crazy,
insane old man?!
[groans]
[XIN] Ha! I knew you'd
injured your leg, old man!
My lord!
Whatever is the matter?
Go ahead, Xin.
Huh?
It pains me to say it,
but the truth is you're
more useful than me now.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Go after the King! Please!
[BI] My lord is bowing his head
to another besides the King...
[BI] And to a no-name
serving-boy, at that.
[XIN] Bowing your head
is pointless, old man.
Zheng said a sword isn't
needed for discussion.
[XIN] That means if the
discussion doesn't go well,
he will need a sword, right?
[XIN] Hm!
That's why from the get go,
I meant to give it some time
then go after Zheng
and protect him.
I see.
In that case,
go quickly, you fool.
[XIN]
Quiet. I am going now!
[grunting]
Heal your leg in Duke Mu's
house while you wait.
See ya!
Wait! I'm going, too!
[LORD CHANGWEN] Xin.
What? Do you ever quit?!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I'm sorry about Piao.
[LORD CHANGWEN] It wasn't
supposed to be this way.
Forgive me.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Ward the King well!
[XIN] Yeah...
[XIN] What on Earth
do you mean, "your path"?!
[NARRATOR]
Carrying the burden of a
bloodstained history of spite,
two kings now
confront one another.
[NARRATOR] Next Time:
"Each One's Dream."