[NARRATOR] The five
centuries of strife:
The Spring and Autumn and
Warring States periods.
Months and years of battle
winnowed more than
100 nations down to seven.
We now know these as
the Seven Warring States.
[NARRATOR]
Such unbearably long upheaval
led the people to despair
of peace ever returning.
[NARRATOR] However,
in the year 246 BC,
a young king with
a great destiny
ascended the throne of Qin.
[NARRATOR] The 31st King
of Qin, Ying Zheng,
later to become Shi Huangdi.
[NARRATOR]
With Ying Zheng's appearance,
a wind of change began to blow
that, while slight,
would usher in the future.
[NARRATOR]
Xin was riding that wind.
Hehe, this is really something.
[NARRATOR] Right now, battles
for control of Xingyang,
which was near the border
between Qin and Wei intensified.
Xingyang lay along the Yellow
River and was a gateway to Wei.
It would be one of the
most crucial strong points
for either kingdom.
Wei sent three armies to meet
at Xingyang from the rear,
and Qin gathered forces from all
over the country to march on it.
Each kingdom's forces
was just over 150,000.
This, the largest battle of the
year, would be Xin's first war.
Finally, my first war.
The first step to becoming
one of the greatest generals!
[XIN squeals]
I'm doing this thing, Piao!
[XIN grunts]
[laughing]
[BOY] You're as
loudmouthed as ever.
What the hell?!
Huh...?
Long time no see, Xin.
Whoa! Wei Ping! Wei Dao!
Hey! It's the thug brothers!
I didn't know you'd be here!
[WEI PING] Hey don't call
us thugs, you stupid brat!
[ALL laugh]
How's everyone
back in the village?
Good. Li Dian's
sarcastic as ever.
Wow, you haven't changed
since you left the village
because you're still
saying that stupid stuff
about being the world's
greatest general!
[XIN growls]
It's not stupid!
I'm gonna be the greatest!
That's exactly the
stupid part! Stupid brat!
[GUARDS gasp]
[DIAO] I am called...
He Liao Diao!
[GUARDS gasp]
[GATE GUARD 17A]
You may enter!
[DIAO] Are we gonna
do this every time?
[ZHENG] I see.
Xin's first campaign?
Yep. He was really raring to go.
I don't think he'll be able
to score a victory
right off the bat.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Ah, here you are.
[DIAO] Huh?
The Fourth Army
has just taken the field now.
[ZHENG] The Kingdom of Wei...
They've barred Qin's path to
the east for generations.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Wei is
surrounded by enemy nations,
and for centuries, they've
spent all of their time on war,
so their entire army
is battle-seasoned.
Their chariot squadron is one of
the best in the Middle Kingdom.
Th-The squadron?
That country is a powerful foe.
[DIAO gasps]
X-Xin'll be okay, right?
[LORD CHANGWEN] It's sure
to be a fierce battle.
I only hope he is
able to survive.
Don't say unlucky things!
You know Xin would
never die that easily!
It's just like him...
Huh?
[ZHENG] I predict this
fight will be harsh.
[XIN] What's everybody
all grouped up for?
Form five-man squads!
All corporals gather!
Huh? Five?
[BOTH] Huh?
[NARRATOR] During this period,
the system was to
divide foot soldiers
into groups of
"five-man squads."
Squad leaders were
called corporals,
and in Qin this squad was the
basic unit of the infantry.
These five men would
all share a common fate.
Tian You! Come join my squad!
[FOOT SOLDIER 17B] Hey wait, he
was with you last time, jerk!
He's in my squad now!
Tian You! Wait a minute!
It's Zhong Tie!
Zhong Tie the Killer is here!
Perfect!
Please join my squad, Sir!
You'll get the
red-carpet treatment!
Huh?!
Okay, I get it!
The strongest-looking ones
get picked first, right?
Damn it!
But none of these people
don't know about me!
Right!
Everybody listen up!
I'm Xin from Cheng Hu Village!
I may be a bit small, but I'm
the strongest guy around here!
Take me seriously, clowns!
I'm gonna be one of the
world's greatest generals!
Cut it out! You're
embarrassing yourself!
[XIN] Let me go, you jerk!
--I'm gonna beat them up!
--[TOUGH GUY 17A] Hey!
You must be new recruits.
You've got some muscle on you.
[TOUGH GUY 17B]
You the big brother?
All right,
we'll let both of you in.
That makes five.
Hey, is that little guy
your kid brother?
If you don't wanna
split up your family,
then we'll just find others.
[WEI PING] Nah, he's just
someone from our hometown, Sir.
No relation.
[TOUGH GUY 17A] Okay.
What crap!
Absolute crap!
Five burly guys all together?
That's just gross,
those dumbasses!
I'm gonna fight as hard as
the five of you combined.
You hear me, dumbasses?!
Hey! Didn't get picked either?
[XIN laughs]
You're even smaller than me!
It's no wonder.
Have a seat.
Us leftovers gotta get along.
Hey!
Do not ignore me when
I'm being nice to you!
[XIN growls]
[XIN growls louder]
Hey, you jerk,
I'm tellin' you to sit down!
You listenin'?!
[WEI PING] We're back.
Eugh! Why are you here?!
They found some guys who
looked tougher, so we're out.
Well, well.
Cap'n Zegui is all
by his lonesome.
No surprise there!
Who'd want to trust his life
to the hands of a wimp,
because that's what he is!
[ZEGUI sighs]
[FOOT SOLDIER 17G laughs]
[FOOT SOLDIER 17G] Hey,
Mr. One-Man Squad!
[ZEGUI] Once again,
nobody teamed up with me...
Let's see who the
leftovers are...
Oh... two of them
are still children!
I wonder if we'll make
it back home alive...
Cut it the hell out already!
Shut up! I'm fightin'
those guys, I told you!
[ZEGUI] Excuse me...
Hello, I'm Corporal Ze Gui.
Pleased to work with you.
Why the hell not?
Hey, you! What's your name?
Bastard, you'd better--
[XIN gasps]
[PERSON] Qiang Lei.
[QIANG LEI]
My dislikes include talking.
The end.
[XIN] Hmph!
[ZEGUI] Anyway we are comrades
who'll entrust each
other with our lives.
Let's help each other
out and do our best.
[XIN]
Hmph!
[XIN] Man! This is a great day
for marching huh?!
If only that annoying brat
wasn't here,
then it'd be perfect!
Why do you suppose he
isn't more nervous?
I'm sure as heck worried 'bout
being in a squad
full of newbies.
[WEI DAO sighs]
What happened?
[XIN gasps]
It's the Qin flag!
[XIN] So we're not
the only infantry here?
That's actually the
Fourth Army's main force.
We will all be absorbed
into their ranks from now on.
The Fourth Army?
Does that mean there
are three more forces
this big as well then?!
[ZEGUI] Five more, actually.
There are six forces in total.
[WEI DAO] Six forces?!
[XIN] That's... that's awesome!
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Forward, men! Forward march!
[FOOT SOLDIER 17G]
Who's that guy?
[FOOT SOLDIER 17H]
Quit it, brat!
[XIN] C'mon, men!
What kind of kid is this
Xin exactly like?
Just as idiotic as he seems.
Oh...? Huh? What is it?
Well, I just started imagining,
and then I felt a bit sick.
[WEI PING] Imagining? What?
I was just thinking about
what it would look like
if this many people started
killing one another...
[WEI PING] D-Don't
imagine crap like that!
B-But I...
[MESSENGER 17A] Fall in!
Everybody line up!
[XIN] Hm? What's up?
Battalion commander
coming through!
Everyone fall in!
Battalion Commander?
[XIN] Let's get out in front!
--[WEI PING] Hey, Xin, hold on!
--[XIN] Come on!
All right!
We're in the front row!
Be real careful not to
break formation, okay, then?
Huh?!
The Qin cavalry is very
strict about discipline,
and a lot of the
battalion commanders
have really fiery tempers.
Just, please, don't break
formation, whatever you do.
Oh, how cool!
Stay still, stupid!
Four-horse chariot.
That's a battalion commander.
[XIN gasps]
I gotta get a look!
Stop it!
Xin!
He is dead...
Halt now!
That guy's as stupid
as they come.
Heh, heh... His head'll
roll, just watch this.
[COMMANDER]
Figured you'd be here.
Hey there, Bi! Long time!
You're still the same Xin.
Glad to see you are doing well.
[SHAN HE] Who the hell
is that brat?!
He was acting way too
friendly with the commander.
He was probably the commander's
servant way back when.
[XIECI] The kid
talked like his equal!
What's that?!
What kind of kid is this Xin?
[WEI PING] Just as dumb
as he seems...
I'm thinking...
You seem to have bulked up
just a little.
I hardly recognized you,
my man!
Battalion Commander?
Real impressive!
So this means we get to
fight together again!
We don't know that just yet.
There are 30,000 men
in the Fourth Army,
and I command
1,000 of them right now.
Whether I'll be the general
above you will be decided
when we organize the troops
as we arrive at Wan Castle.
So you're just one of many
battalion commanders?
Nonetheless,
it is an important rank.
You'll need to speak
politely from now on,
or it will set a bad example.
Fine.
So then, Xin.
What does your
five-man squad look like?
A worn-out corporal.
An amateur bunch.
The others make fun of us
and call us the Weakest Five.
[BI gasps]
The "Weakest"?
Well, but a squad will be stable
if it has two skilled warriors.
And you can count
for two by yourself.
That's right!
I'll just do five
men's work, that's all!
[BI chuckles]
Right, then I'll be waiting
in Wan Castle.
Yeah, Commander Bi!
[ZEGUI] So the Fourth
Army got Wan Castle.
Now we're real trouble.
The lord of the castle,
Hei Gang,
is feared as the
"Blinding Black Dragon."
He's a bold general
who's wiped out an army of
30,000 with only 2,000 troops.
Now he's in charge of
the toughest battlefield,
so he's burning
for battle even more.
Yeah, aren't we all going
to combat as his infantry?
Isn't that exciting?
For real, that's great!
Isn't it, Wei Dao?!
Gah... Well, my stomach's
starting to hurt...
If it's the
toughest battlefield,
that means we'll
get major glory!
Yeah! I'm all fired up!
[NARRATOR] However,
the maelstrom of war
would soon end Xin's plans
and give rise
to even more chaos.
[NARRATOR] In Wan Castle,
at the time...
What?!
Wan Castle just fell?!
How come?!
We're the ones
gearing up to attack them,
so how is it possible...
we've lost a castle?!
General Hei Gang is strong!
He was slain in battle.
[XIN gasps]
It wasn't just the general.
Everyone inside the
castle was killed.
Even the elderly and
the women and children.
[BOTH gasp]
[WEI PING] This is my first
time, so I don't know...
Do people always go
that far in a war?
[ZEGUI] No--It's the first time
I hear of something like this.
[XIN] Who attacked them?!
Who could've pulled
this thing off?!
General Wu Qing
of Wei, I think.
If he defeated
General Hei Gang,
he must be
extraordinarily gifted
even more than people say.
[BOTH gasp]
[XIN] No matter!
I don't care how tough he is.
I'll kill him!
[ZEGUI groans softly]
[WEI PING] B-But anyway,
since the castle we'd camp in
has just fallen, where are we
supposed to go then?
Yashui.
We'll meet up with the First
and Second Armies there,
and then we'll have to
make a frontal attack
on Xingyang next.
That sounds
pretty dangerous...
It couldn't be worse.
[XIN] Okay, then, let's go to
that "toughest battlefield"!
Suits me, General Scumbag!
[XIN] The mood's getting
weirdly tense right now.
[XIN] So this is... what it
feels like when battle's near...
[FOOT SOLDIER 17E] Hey, you!
You stepped on my foot!
Huh?
Well, if it it's not one
of the Weakest Five!
You're a nuisance!
Just go home before
you drag us down.
Wh-Why you--!
Um, pardon...
What? So you punks
wanna go, then?!
[XIN]
Wh-What?
[FOOT SOLDIER 17E whimpers]
[ZEGUI] N-N-N-No, you mustn't!
A feud during a march
is a court-martial offense!
Please. A-As a favor to me...
[FOOT SOLDIER 17E]
Damn!
--[ZEGUI sighs]
--[WEI PING sighs]
[XIN] I figured he was
no ordinary fighter, but...
Hmph.
This guy's got
a lot of secrets, huh?
General Wu Qing, I am
grateful for your support.
With you here amongst all of us,
Xingyang is indestructible now!
We are not support.
[LONG TAI] Sir?
I just came here to take all
of the troops in Xingyang.
[LONG TAI] All troops?
Wh-What do you mean?
I refuse to allow
those filthy invaders
to even dare to set foot
on Wei's lands.
[LONG TAI] G-General,
do you mean...?
[RED MESSENGER 17A]
Urgent report!
Wei forces have just made
a sortie out of Xingyang.
150,000 troops,
led by Wu Qing!
They are coming
straight for Yashui.
150 thousand?!
That's Xingyang's
whole garrison!
[BATTALION COMMANDER 17C]
That Wu Qing--
First Wan Castle,
and now Yashui?!
[BI] What's going on?
The First and Second Armies
are stationed here in Yashui.
It's unlike Wan Castle
which didn't have an infantry.
Does he have
a trick up his sleeve?
[LORD BIAO] Don't be afraid.
[BI gasps]
Wu Qing isn't
after this place at all.
The backbone of Wei's forces
is their chariot squadron.
He wants to bring this battle to
flat land where they benefit.
She Gan Plain?
Sounds interesting...
Abort the attack on Xingyang!
We'll now go to war
on the plains!
We'll hold the key battle
on the She Gan Plain!
Take up your
positions quickly.
We leave immediately!
[BATTALION COMMANDER 17A]
Immediately?
[BATTALION COMMANDER 17B]
But my lord,
we haven't finished
organizing the regiments!
And the Fourth Army
hasn't even entered the cas--
Take care of those things after
we reach She Gan Plain!
And send the Fourth Army
straight to She Gan as well!
[BI] It's an agile response.
In a plains battle, I understand
us wanting to take positions
on the hills with a good view.
But it's too facile.
She Gan Plain is three days'
run from here, and four
days' run from Xingyang.
[BI] We'll be facing the Wei
forces three days from now.
But our armies aren't ready.
The plan was to make
our move in ten days
and storm a castle.
Is this general truly
a good leader?
Lord Biao...
Just what kind
of general is he?
All troops move out now!
[XIN] Why are we marching
double time all of a sudden?
[ZEGUI] I don't know.
But our destination has
changed from Yashui
to She Gan Plain now.
[WEI PING] What?
It has changed again?
[XIN] What the hell?!
This is the second time!
I imagine it's because Wei must
have made another sudden move.
Listen to me, all:
I want you to prepare
yourselves mentally.
We were supposed to
be the attacker,
but we've been forestalled.
When that happens,
lots of people die.
[WEI PING] X-Xin, you jerk!
Quit sprinting!
Think of your squad, will you?!
[WEI DAO] We've passed the
rest of the army in no time!
I'm not sprinting!
I'm just matching
your slow pace!
[WEI PING] C-Corporal,
we're on our fifth day!
Shouldn't we be at
She Gan Plain by now?
Am I right?
Yes, that's right, I believe
we're almost there.
[XIN gasps]
[XIN grunts]
[XIN] The air just changed
all of a sudden.
There's something up ahead.
[WEI PING] Hey, Xin!
What is it?!
[SOLDIER 17A]
H-Hey you!
Do not pass the car!
[XIN] It's getting hotter...
[XIN] Getting heavier...
What is this sensation?
It's not what I felt
with Mu Ta or Lan Kai.
But one thing's for sure...
There's something
right up ahead!
[XIN] Something serious!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What... What the hell is this?!
[XIN] Dammit!
We can't do a thing!
[NARRATOR]
There's nowhere to run.
Lives are crushed at
a shocking speed.
[NARRATOR] Next Time: "The
Chariot Squadron's Menace."