[XIN] The air just
changed all of a sudden.
There's something up ahead...
Hey, Xin! What is it?!
H-Hey, you!
Don't pass the leading car!
[XIN] It's gettin' hotter...
[XIN] Gettin' heavier...
What's this sensation?
There's something
right up ahead!
[XIN] Something serious!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What... What the hell is this?!
[yelling continues,
weapons clanging]
[SOLDIER screams]
[yelling continues,
weapons clanging]
[WEI PING gasps]
So this is a... battlefield...
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Xingyang: A land
that lay near the border
of the kingdoms of Qin and Wei.
[NARRATOR] It was the
western gateway to Wei,
and a key strategic strongpoint.
[NARRATOR] And now,
the two countries' anticipated
battle over it had begun.
[NARRATOR] Qin, using
Yashui as their base,
planned to attack Xingyang
from three points
and take the castle.
However, Wei's
commanding general Wu Qing
sallied forth from Xi Castle
and tore holes in
Qin's defenses immediately.
[NARRATOR] Outfoxed, Xin and
the others in their first battle
as foot soldiers changed course
from Wan Castle to Yashui
before finally arriving at the
site of the deciding battle:
She Gan Plain.
Fourth Army, fall in!
I am the battalion
commander, Fu Hushen!
We will begin organizing
our formation!
Five-man squads, line up!
[WEI PING] Huh?
What's going on?
I thought we were supposed
to storm a castle!
[FU HUSHEN] Line up!
Get moving, worms!
[SQUADRON COMMANDER 18A]
One moment please, Commander!
We haven't been told anything
other than that...
our meeting point
changed from Yashui
to She Gan Plain!
Sir, wasn't the plan
to storm Xingyang?
A lowly foot soldier has
no need to know everything!
You worms only need to follow
your superiors' orders!
B-But Sir, we--
[SQUADRON COMMANDER 18A screams]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[BI] Hold it!
The war situation has
changed at a dizzying speed.
We should explain it to them,
foot soldiers or not!
[WEI PING] Hey, isn't that the
battalion commander from before?
It's Bi!
Newcomers shouldn't
stick their noses in!
[BI] Whether I'm a
newcomer is irrelevant!
We're both commanders, and
I will make my opinion heard!
Excuse me?!
[SHANG LU] You cannot fight
in front of the troops.
Settle down, you two.
It's shameful.
Keep out, Shang Lu.
I'm talking to him now.
[SHANG LU]
Sorry, I can't do that.
This guy's a childhood friend,
and you see,
we have a tradition of
working things out together.
[FU HUSHEN] Hey.
Keep being fresh with me
and I'll kill you both.
Huh...?
Wei's forces
caught us off guard
with a sortie out of Xingyang!
In response, we moved
our troops from Yashui here
to She Gan Plain!
It was yesterday that the two
armies faced off and battled.
The Third, Fifth,
and Sixth Armies
have not yet arrived here,
which leaves our
forces outnumbered.
The Wei troops arrived
a short time before us
and covered the hills, giving us
a geographical disadvantage.
In order to win,
we need to take the hills!
The Second Army battles as we
speak, but it's a bitter fight.
They await our reinforcements!
After we unite our troops,
the Fourth Army must aid
the Second Army and do whatever
it takes to seize that hill!
That is our current situation!
We just gotta take the hill?
That'll be nice and easy.
[WEI PING groans]
[BI] The armies of our great Qin
are brave warriors feared
throughout the Middle Kingdom!
Go out there; prepare to bleed!
Go out there; prepare to die!
Kill, kill, and kill again, for
as long as you have strength!
Dye this field red
with the blood of Wei!
May the fortunes of war
be with you!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[FU HUSHEN] Fourth Army, Fu
Hushen Brigade, fall in!
[WEI PING]
We just had to get stuck
in that scary
commander's battalion!
[WEI DAO] I hear he makes his
men fight nasty battles...
A-And to top that...
...we're in the front row.
Such good luck...
[yelling]
[weapons clanging]
We-We're just about to
march right into that, huh?
[WEI DAO gasps, whimpers]
[WEI PING gulps]
--[WEI PING coughs]
--[WEI DAO] Brother!
[XIE CI]
Those guys are so pathetic.
But this waiting part...
is always a great thrill,
isn't it, huh?
I agree!
[ZE GUI]
Most of the men in the front
lose their lives in
the very first clash.
[gasping]
Let's work real hard
to make it past that part.
It's no use, Corporal.
Even if we make it
through the beginning,
we're weak, we're sure
to die fast like that.
It's all right.
My free-for-all skill is small,
but it will
definitely help us out.
[WEI PING] Experience?
[ZE GUI] Yes.
My squad may always
get called as the weakest,
but not one of my men
has ever died.
[BOTH] Not one?!
[ZE GUI] Yes.
The weak have their own ways
of fighting, too, you see.
The five of us will stay close,
standing back to back to each
other to cover our blind spots.
We defend as five
and attack as five.
Even against a single wounded
enemy, we attack as a group.
They're not dirty tricks,
they're tactics!
"Five men as one."
Let's all survive this
with squad solidarity.
"Five men as one."
Squad solidarity...
Oh, I get it!
[XIN] I was wondering
why I felt so good.
I bet it's 'cause
being at the front
feels like I'm leading an army!
[WEI DAO groans]
[WEI PING] What?
Are you stupid?
Dreaming right now?!
I see. So this is what a
general must feel like!
[WEI PING stammers]
H-Hey, Xin,
take a look around us.
A-Aren't you scared?
Me? Scared?
Nah. See, I've been waiting
for this moment all my life.
Xin...
[gong crash]
[WEI PING] Wh-What's that?!
They're about to
order the charge.
Don't get too eager and trip.
You'll be trampled
to death by your own.
Uh... it is starting!
Okay, I can do this.
I'm gonna do this!
[XIN] It's finally starting.
You watching this, Piao?
All troops ready!
--[gong crashes]
--[WEI PING &amp; WEI DAO whimper]
[gong crashes continue]
[XIN] And you just wait, Zheng!
Troops ready to charge!
[yelling]
[WEI PING] H-Hey, look at that!
[PEI LANG] Damn,
I thought this might happen!
A rock formation!
Jump up onto the corpses
of the guys in front
and get over that wall,
or else we'll get
penned in and crushed!
[XIE CI] Yes, sir!
[WEI PING] Xin!
[WEI DAO] What are you doing?!
[ZE GUI] Hey, Xin!
[WEI SOLDIER 18B] Just kill him!
Huh?!
[XIN growls]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[WEI SOLDIER 18D] K-Kill him!
[XIN yells]
[WEI SOLDIER 18E]
He's going for the front!
[WEI DAO] Brother!
[XIN yells]
[WEI PING] Xin!
[QIN SOLDIER 18A]
Look, there's an opening!
[QIN SOLDIER 18B]
Their wall opened!
[QIN SOLDIER 18C] It's open!
[XIN] Heh!
Come on!
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
Brother!
Dao!
Corporal!
[ZE GUI] So now, both of you!
[WEI SOLDIER 18F]
You dirty cowards!
Shut up! This is how we fight!
[WEI SOLDIER 18F screams]
[WEI SOLDIERS gasp]
[XIN] What is this?
I'm already breathing hard.
[XIN] Am I tight because
it's my first battle?
No, that's not all...
[XIN] My body feels
heavier than normal.
No... the air feels heavier.
Is this what a
battlefield is like?
Well, it's no big deal!
[XIN yells]
[NARRATOR] Wei's rock formation
was considered perfect.
But the soldiers poured through
the crack Xin made on their wall
without losing momentum,
and the tide of this early
battle turned in Qin's favor...
[NARRATOR] ...or so it seemed.
[WEI PING] Xin!
Hey!
[WEI PING] You're all right!
[XIN] Heh heh,
so you survived, Wei Ping?
Don't you "heh heh" me!
You tore off
on your own, you jerk!
Brother...
[WEI PING] Weren't you
listening to the corporal?!
Squad solidarity is--
[ZE GUI] Wei Ping.
It's all right.
Corporal...
If he had not charged
on his own like he did,
I think we might have probably
all died during the first clash.
"Doing what you can
for the good of all"--
That's another fine
squad strategy.
[WEI DAO] Guys...
Do you hear something?
[WEI PING] Huh?
It is almost
like an earthquake.
Well, the Wei soldiers
are gone, too.
I can't tell; there's
too much dust in the air!
This sound must be...
Look out, everyone! This is...
[XIN gasps]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
W-W-What is this? W-W-What?!
Chariot squadron.
[gasping]
Wei's armored chariot squadron--
The best one in
the Middle Kingdom!
[XIN] Didn't think they'd
bring it out so fast!
[XIN growls]
[XIN] If we go at those
stampeding horses head-on,
they'll pulverize us!
[XIN] If we attack
from an angle,
the guys on top still
have the advantage!
Plus, if we mess up,
those wheels will eat us alive!
[XIN] We can't do a thing!
[XIN] Hey, pay attention!
[WEI PING screams]
[ALL grunt]
[XIN] You guys okay?!
I owe you. Thanks.
[WEI PING] Please get off me!
Ow, ow, ow...
[XIN] Ugh, damn,
those bastards are cocky!
[WEI DAO]
The ground stopped shaking.
Was that the last one?
[WEI PING] More than half
of our men are now dead!
Damn it!
[ZE GUI] I suspect
it's only the beginning.
[WEI PING &amp; WEI DAO gasp]
I've heard that the
chariot squadron's main force
is the "second wave."
My guess is they'll mop up
and bring so many,
there'll be no escape!
Th-That is...
[low rumbling]
[gasping]
[WEI DAO] Th-They're coming!
Wait, they're all chariots?!
[WEI PING]
Wha-Wha-Wha-What do we do?!
[WEI PING whimpers]
[WEI PING] What do we do now?!
[XIN growls]
[QIANG LEI] I have a strategy.
You do?
You're alive!
We didn't see you anywhere,
so we thought--
Never mind that. What is
your strategy, Qiang Lei?
[QIANG LEI] A defensive wall.
[QIANG LEI] By piling bodies.
B-B-Bodies...?
Pile 'em...?
[PEI LANG] Interesting.
[ZE GUI] Pei!
That's not a bad idea.
The rest of you, help!
Go get more shields and spears!
[XIN] Hah!
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A laughs]
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A]
Kill, kill!
Make mince meat out of every
last one of those Qin dogs!
Huh...?
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A laughs]
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A]
Look! There's a puppy!
After him! Run him over!
What are you playing at?
Did you think you could
stop a chariot like that?!
Try us, push-cart bastard!
Xin, get your head down!
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A] Die!
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A growls]
They avoided it?!
You men okay there?
We are okay!
It only scratched us!
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18D]
I'll be damned.
The others are all clear, too!
That's right!
As long as we stay behind these,
they cannot touch us!
Good work, Qiang Lei!
We owe you!
[WEI PING laughs]
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18C] Wait!
There's a group coming back!
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18D]
They're circling?!
They're coming after us!
Oh, no. If they attack us
from behind, there's no wall!
[PEI LANG] Idiots!
The ones circling won't come
until the main unit's passed!
Keep your eyes on the front now!
[ZE GUI gasps]
We've got spears coming!
[PEI LANG growls]
[WEI PING whimpers]
That was close!
[WEI PING gasps, screams]
[XIE CI] Damn!
Ying, don't die! Hey!
Dammit!
No!
[QIANG LEI]
The chariots are slowing down.
Due to the obstacles, our walls.
Right now we have a shot.
[XIN gasps]
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18C
screams] There's more!
[PEI LANG] Don't get scared!
The main unit's almost past us!
[XIN growls]
[XIN] Wei Ping, hold this.
Uh, what are you gonna do?!
Hey, Xin, a chariot is coming!
Get your head down!
[XIN] Quit underestimating
us, you jerk!
--[XIN yells]
--[WEI PING] Xin!
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18D]
He did it!
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18C]
They're still alive!
Finish them off!
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18E] This
is for Ying, you bastard! Die!
[XIN gasps]
[XIN] He's...
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18C]
All right!
We beat Wei's chariot squadron!
We did it!
[QIANG LEI] Quiet!
The unit that circled
is coming back.
[low rumbling]
[FOURTH ARMY SOLDIER 18C] These
guys took care to come back...
They're making sure
none of us escapes!
Dammit, we've only got
protective walls in front!
So we'll die after all?!
What the hell is
our cavalry waiting for?!
Did they just abandon us
to die here?!
[XIN] Don't start a battle
hoping those guys will save you!
[horse whinnies]
[XIN] We'll carve out the path
to our survival on our own,
that's all!
[WEI PING]
Wh-What are you doing?
Can ride a horse, kid?!
Heh, heh...
You can say that.
More importantly: listen up!
To make it out alive, we gotta
fight the chariot squadron!
But how are we supposed
to fight that?!
Beats me!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Well, I don't really know,
but the only way out
is to fight!
Anyway, I'll go buy some time!
Expand the walls far and
make somewhere to hunker down!
That's the first thing!
H-Hold on a second!
Don't tell me you plan
to fight all those chariots
all by yourself?
Don't you worry!
I'm not goin' there to die.
We will win this fight
no matter what! Yeah!
All right, men,
move and make the
other squads help, too!
[XIE CI] On it!
[PEI LANG] Get more
shields and spears!
We'll make these walls
as big as we can!
[ZE GUI] We ask for
your help, everyone!
[WEI PING] Xin,
you're really something.
[BI] What's happening
on the front lines?!
I can't see anything
through the sand!
There's no order
to charge yet?
The standby
flag is still up!
[NARRATOR] While Xin
and the Fourth Army
were locked in fierce combat
with Wei's infantry
and chariot squadron,
none of the Qin cavalry
at the rear had moved an inch.
[NARRATOR] This was due to dust
obscuring the situation
on the ground,
but the main reason was
that they had not received
orders from General Biao
at base to attack.
I'm going to assess the
situation at the front!
Battalion--
[FU HUSHEN] Halt!
That is definitely
not your job.
Don't leave your
post without consent!
Fu Hushen.
That order makes no sense.
It is possible something
happened to the messengers!
Don't assume things.
This all falls within
Lord Biao's strategy.
What strategy is that?!
He'll leave the soldiers to die?
[FU HUSHEN] Hey.
Did you come out
to this battlefield
just to save some
foot soldiers?
Or did you come to
defeat Wei's forces?
What is it?!
[BI growls]
[WEI SOLDIER 18H]
Run, little rabbit. Run now!
[WEI SOLDIER 18I] Go left!
Close in from his left!
[XIN] Damn, these chariot jerks
are really pushing their luck.
[XIN] That was close!
If this pole was wood,
I'd be done!
[screaming]
[XIN] They widened the walls
but they haven't
closed them completely.
We'll be wiped out soon
at this rate.
We have to be offensive!
[XIN] It's no good!
On the ground, I could have
easily taken a million of 'em,
but a chariot and a man
on horseback aren't fair!
Should I jump there?
No, I can't get close enough
because of those wheels!
[WEI PING] So... it's no good...
Even Xin is no match for
chariots. Am I right, guys?!
[QIANG LEI]
Don't get distracted!
[XIN] It's him!
[QIANG LEI] Remember who
you brought down before!
Your opponent is
the chariot itself!
[XIN] The chariot itself?
Huh...?
That's right. With a
rider's mobility--
[XIN] The one before?
[XIN] Got it!
[XIN] I was fighting
the wrong opponent!
[horse whinnies]
[XIN yells]
Captain.
The brat is coming back.
[CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A] Heh!
Pesky little fly...
I'll take his life myself.
Just watch!
[XIN] With a horse's mobility
and this steel spear, I can...
...do it!
[XIN] I don't care
about you guys.
My opponent is this
freakin' annoying chariot!
--[XIN yells]
--[CHARIOT SOLDIERS scream]
[gasping]
The counterattack starts now!
[XIN yells,
CHARIOT CAPTAIN 18A screams]
[FU HUSHEN]
Fu Hushen Brigade, attack!
[NARRATOR]
Run, and don't look back!
While there's life left in you,
look only forward!
Next Time: "Raging Battle."