[NARRATOR] The Qin forces
led by General Wang Yi
numbered 100,000.
The rival Zhao forces
led by Pang Nuan
numbered 120,000.
The two sides encountered
each other at MNyáng.
Now the battle
has transferred
to a vast plain nearby
called Gan Yuan,
and their confrontation
is about to begin.
[NARRATOR] The time:
The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
The place: Qin.
Xin, a nameless boy,
met Zheng, a young King,
distinguished himself in battle,
and rose to the rank
of squadron commander.
In the midst of this,
the neighboring
kingdom of Zhao invaded,
and Qin faced
unprecedented crisis.
What manner of battle
will Wang Yi wage
as commanding general?
And what growth
will Xin accomplish?
[DIAO] It's amazing!
Wang Yi is truly amazing!
Wow, there are countless
soldiers fighting for each side!
You don't have time
to be distracted.
Get a firm grasp of the war
situation before things start.
[MENG YI] The linchpin
of Zhao's attack
will be the 60,000 men
in those three rifts,
the left-hand force.
[MENG YI] Each division
has about 20,000 men,
and each plans to attack
Qin's right flank.
Qin has a total of 40,000 men
in its right-hand force
defending against that
while Qin's left force
and Zhao's right force
feel cut off from
the rest of the armies.
See, they're both surrounded
by physical obstacles.
So victory'll be
essentially decided
by the attack
as well as the defense
to the right of center, right?
Exactly. Zhao's key
are the 60,000 in their left.
And Qin's key men
are in the center:
Wang Yi's lieutenant
Meng Wu and his army of 20,000,
plus the 20,000 men of the
First Army, totaling 40,000.
Meng Wu? "Meng"...?
[MENG YI] He's my father.
[DIAO gasps]
[LI BAI] So that's Meng Wu?
Meng Wu. Son of Qin's
"White Elder" Meng Ao,
and Lü's most trusted
general, apparently... Well.
[GANG LUAN] Rumor has it his
offensive power is formidable.
Ah, Gang Luan.
One fights power with power.
I beg you, my lord,
please let my heavy cavalry unit
take over the front lines.
[WANG YI] So Zhao wants to have
a contest of strength, it seems.
All right, let's see all
of your power then.
It's time to show it off.
Army charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
There he goes!
I-It's starting now!
[GANG LUAN] Kill them now!
Meng Yi!
Are you confident that
your dad will be okay?
[MENG YI]
You underestimate him.
[GANG LUAN]
Prepare to die, Meng Wu!
[GANG LUAN choking]
[MENG YI] Now you see the power
of the general called Meng Wu.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
That... that animal...
[QIN SOLDIERS]
General Meng Wu!
General Meng Wu grabbed
the battle's momentum!
Think he can keep it?!
No. Zhao's vanguard
won't take this quietly.
Their left force is
lead by General She Meng.
[QIN SOLDIER 27C]
Here they come!
What?!
Our right force!
The vanguards
are evenly matched.
Yes.
Isn't it our turn
right about now?!
General Li Bai, we aren't
slowing Meng Wu down.
Put the heavy
infantry diagonally.
Deploy 500 archers to the left.
[ZHENG] Is it time?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Yes, no
messenger has reached us yet,
but General Wang Yi
and our forces
should definitely combat
the Zhao army
without fail today.
General Wang Yi...
Do you feel impatient?
Yes.
If only it were possible,
I would watch these events
unfolding in detail.
And yet...
Here I am merely sitting
daily in this high throne.
I have no choice but
to leave the battles
to my top generals.
I guess that is the
nature of kingship.
[LORD CHANGWEN] As you say.
It looks like Meng Wu's army
is slowing down somewhat.
It's the Zhao guard's strategy.
[MENG YI]
By firing from one side
and setting their
infantry diagonally,
they're managing
our cavalry's momentum.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Meng Wu is even
stronger than the rumors say.
But pure force of arms is not
enough to make it past Li Bai.
Now, what will you
do next, Wang Yi?
The right and center forces
are operating as planned.
Now we're only waiting
on our all-important left force.
[NARRATOR] Even as its
center and right forces
battled fiercely,
Qin's left force had not yet
received any direct orders.
Is there any meaning at all
in protecting
this steep terrain?!
Should we not go to support
our central force instead?
[GAN YANG]
Battalion Commander Bi.
Please understand
that crux of our attack
isn't the central force...
...it is the
left force instead.
What do you mean,
sir, that we are the crux?
We can't strike the
enemy's core from here,
and we've waited too long
to target their center.
The war has only
just begun, however.
No one could go straight
after their core and reach it.
[BI] However...
I received a strategy
from General Wang Yi.
It's from General Wang Yi?
I'm sure it'll be
a hard battle,
but desperate battles are
my specialty, I assure you.
[TENG] Sir, the left force
has begun its advance.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] Now the stage is set.
Perhaps it's about time
to release the archers.
[WANG YI] I'll leave
this post to you for now.
[TENG] Sir.
The left force is charging!
Heh heh! Looks like it's
finally our turn to act.
It's about time, isn't it?
[XIN] General Wang Yi!
[QIN SOLDIER 27D]
It's General Wang Yi!
[QIN SOLDIER 27E]
General Wang Yi!
As you can see,
our left force of 10,000
just attacked Zhao's
right force of 20,000.
Ten thousand?
Twenty?
[WANG YI] In truth, this is
the most critical fight
to the initial stages
of the campaign.
Oh, young Xin, my boy,
it's time for you to show me
the fruit of your training.
Leave it to me!
I can see that you're
irrefutably undaunted.
[WANG YI] Very well. I shall
give this squadron a mission.
The typical rule for
fighting efficient battle
is to first of all make sure
to seize advantageous terrain.
[WANG YI] However, there is
another sound method as well:
Killing off the enemy's
best commanders firstly.
[gasp]
[WANG YI] The general
leading the 20,000 men
in Zhao's
right force, Feng Ji,
has an exceptional gift
for tactical analysis.
[WANG YI] As a battle
approaches its climax,
that sort of commander
becomes more
and more troublesome.
So listen carefully.
Let's begin by firstly
removing Feng Ji, shall we?
Young Xin.
It's time for
your squadron to act.
Take advantage of
the confusion there
to capture the head
of Feng Ji.
The head of Feng Ji...
[WANG YI] This is an extremely
important mission, young Xin.
Can you do it?
There is something I
realized from that training
I did in the stateless area.
In a giant battlefield with
tens of thousands of soldiers,
one hundred is merely
just a pebble-sized
tiny number, after all.
But even a pebble has its own
kind of strength, however!
[XIN] We can squeeze
through openings,
and together we can be a
rock that nobody can break!
My squadron will surely
take on that mission!
I'll repeat myself.
This is a really crucial battle.
Whatever happens,
you are not allowed to fail.
I will be counting on you, then,
Squadron Commander Xin.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] It relieves my mind to
see that you've grown somewhat.
Very well, let me
give you a little reward.
I give your squadron
the name "Fei Xin Force."
[XIN] Fei Xin Force!
[MENG YI] Give it up.
You cannot possibly
pick Xin and the others
out of so many people.
That is...
There's a group
coming from over there!
There, there by the woods!
Do you see?
I'm right! It's Xin!
[YUAN] Let's lay out
a strategy, Sir.
I'll start by explaining the
situation, so listen closely.
Our target, the 20,000
led by Feng Ji,
is fighting 10,000 Qin men now.
The Zhao army is sure to be
focused on the Qin troops
in front of them.
That's our opening.
We'll circle around and
charge them from the side.
[YUAN] The plan is to
take the enemy unaware
and go for their core.
But will this really work
just because
they will be surprised?
I have done
similar things before,
though not up
against a whole army.
[YUAN]
But we've got a big problem
in the run-up
to this maneuver.
Namely, whether or not we
can go to our entry point
next to them
without being noticed.
No problem.
That's precisely where
being a small unit
actually comes in handy.
[WANG YI]
Thank you very much, Teng.
How are we faring?
Sir. The right force
has been pushed back a bit.
Meng Wu's center force
hasn't regained momentum,
faced with Li Bai's guard.
What about the left force?
The left force
is fighting bravely.
Thanks to Gan Yang,
the Fourth Army's general,
their fighting spirit is high.
Still, though, they're
on shaky ground, aren't they?
Feng Ji is baiting
them then, Sir.
[WANG YI] If my arrow
doesn't hit home soon,
I believe there's pain
in store for the left force.
We should be
just about there.
That went very well.
All right, get ready.
Pass the message down the line:
"We are charging soon."
[TIAN YOU] Got it.
[GUARD SOLDIER 27B] Pests.
[metallic slicing noise]
Damn, these woods
are thinning out now.
Fei Xin Force,
come to a halt!
Right, there they all are.
[XIN chuckles]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Onward, men!
The enemy is faltering!
Heh, how nice!
Qin's got them on the back foot!
[WANG YI] Half the left force's
momentum comes from talent.
The other half is
thanks to Feng Ji's trap.
Pull back the front line.
Send Hei Li and Hei Ling's
infantry to the front,
and take your positions.
[ZHAO MESSENGER 27A]
Wu Fang Squadron withdraw!
Wu Ying Squadron follow!
Everyone withdraw!
[BI] The front line
fell back... Why?
[BI] We were pressing them, yes,
but not that much, really.
[BI] Could this be...?
[QIN SOLDIER 27G]
After them! Kill them all!
Bi Brigade!
Halt, for this may be a trap!
All squads to halt now!
[QIN SOLDIER 27H] Follow them!
[INFANTRY COMMANDER 27A]
So they came.
Foolish amateurs.
Men, it's time now
for the slaughter.
[QIN SOLDIER 27I]
W-Wait! Stop, stop!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Commander, look right!
[BI] Oh no!
[NARRATOR] Feng Ji's
trap closed at last.
The heavy infantry's spears
and the arrows
pouring down like rain...
Their ruthless attack
brought down
almost half
of the left force
and soon most of the foot
soldiers were rushing to escape.
Huh, that's not good...
Th-That's brutal...
[YUAN] This is bad, sir.
If everyone's spirits
aren't high,
we can't draw power
from our unity!
Fei Xin Force,
let's get in formation.
[XIN] For a group of 100
to get to the leader of 10,000,
we can't afford
any pointless fights.
That's why we're
using a file formation
and making a beeline
for the enemy general.
Issue is gonna be
when we make the breach.
'Cause when we move,
they'll know we're here
and they'll guard against us.
To tear through their defenses
and to get a point of entry,
I'm putting four corporals
with good strength in the front.
[XIN] Zhong Tie!
Shan He! Tian You!
And corporal for the
16th squad Long Chuan!
Long Chuan, it's our
first time fighting together,
but I've high hopes.
Tian You told me you've got
twice the strength he has.
I wanna see it.
[TIAN YOU]
Long Chuan! What's with you?
You better not be getting
cold feet right now!
[SONG ZUO] Can't blame him!
Word came his wife
had a baby last month.
And it's his first kid.
Put yourself in his shoes.
If he dies here,
he'll never see that cute face.
So back on topic!
You can think of the Fei Xin
Force as a single arrow.
[XIN] If we fly to the enemy
general we can take him down,
but if we fall short
we'll get broken
and we'll die pathetically.
If we fail, everyone
on the left force
that you can see getting
shot at will die as well then.
And so will every single
person that's waiting for you
back in your villages!
Did you guys forget?
If we lose this battle here,
the Zhao army's just
gonna pour right into Qin!
[XIN] If that happens,
the massacre at MNyg
gets repeated
everywhere!
These guys are serious!
Long Chuan!
If we don't win,
your kid gets killed, too!
[XIN] Drum it right
into your heads, men:
That's exactly
what's on the line here!
[yelling]
Let's go, then!
Let's score today's
first victory, Commander.
[INFANTRYMAN 27A]
Enemy attack from our left!
[WEI PING]
Crap, they're onto us.
Doesn't matter!
We just gotta go!
Heavy infantry to the front!
Build us a wall, now!
[WEI PING] Damn it!
[XIN] Long Chuan!
Long Chuan, wait!
Don't go out on your own!
[TIAN YOU] Long Chuan,
don't tell me you're not--
[LONG CHUAN] Tian You, you've
got one thing terribly wrong!
I'm afraid I must correct you...
[LONG CHUAN] I've got three
times your crazy strength!
You brought some serious
muscle with you, Tian You!
Here we go!
Fei Xin Force,
it's time to charge!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 27B]
Pen them in from both sides!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 27C]
Pick 'em off and slice 'em up!
They're closing in! Hurry up!
If we don't move faster,
the path we cleared
is gonna disappear!
Go now! Chong Yuan Five!
Oh wow, that mongrel's
not bad for a pretty boy!
And the rest of
his squad's tough, too!
[WEI PING] All right! Go!
[BI] Don't fall back!
It's an enemy trap--
If we fall back
they'll kill us!
The way out is forward!
Commander Bi said...
[BI'S SOLDIER 27B]
Commander!
The way out is forward?
That's right!
If we make it to those
Zhao soldiers up ahead,
the archers won't shoot us!
[BI] We need to all band
together to break through!
[SOLDIER 27B]
Get everyone together!
It's Gan Yang...
He'll strike their core unit!
[BI] Bi Battalion,
follow our commander!
General, a unit is
advancing toward us head-on!
[NARRATOR] Feng Ji was
untroubled by this news.
In truth, only about
1,500 men in the center
were actually advancing.
The rest were running away.
For now he'd follow his plan,
sending a mop-up brigade
of 3,000 to kill the runners.
[NARRATOR] At that point,
Qin's left force
would effectively be destroyed.
Then only the 1,500
advancing troops would be left.
Naturally, they wouldn't
be difficult opponents.
However, this is
where we catch a glimpse
of Feng Ji's battle viewpoint.
[NARRATOR]
"How can I defeat the enemy
as effectively and
efficiently as possible?"
Feng Ji's mind
was busy searching for
the best way to dispose
of the remaining 1,500.
As a result,
he did not notice at all
that the Fei Xin Force was
closing in on him from the side.
[ZHAO MESSENGER 27 A]
Report!
We're under attack
from the left!
There are a hundred of them.
They're on their way
to Formation 2.
Say what?!
Other signs of them?
[ZHAO MESSENGER 27A] No, Sir.
The hundred-man
squadron's operating alone.
A squadron acting alone?!
What is going on here?
[FENG JI] I see. So that's it.
[FENG JI] Wang Yi, I understand
you're after my head.
[FENG JI] Interesting.
Let's see you try to take it!
[yelling]
[XIN] Split up the squadron?!
[NARRATOR]
For the sake of victory!
Xin, your path lies
ahead of you now!
Next Time:
"Wang Yi's Flying Arrow."