Let's do this!
[XIN]
That hurt!
[BI]
He... He made it!
Kill this insolent monkey-boy!
[XIN]
You're too late, boys!
This fight is the
memorial for Piao,
so there'll be no mercy.
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war, hatred,
and strife raged
across the land,
consuming everything
in its wake.
Desire. Pleasure. Suffering.
Terror. All without end.
In a time filled with so much
cruelty and destruction,
small wonder that this
era was known as...
..."the dragon."
As though scorched by
the flames of the dragon,
over a hundred nations fell,
one after the other,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Yan... Qi... Zhao...
Wei... Han... Chu...
...and lastly, Qin.
Like lions trying to
devour their rivals,
these seven kingdoms lunged
at each other's throats
again and again,
their swords stained
with ambition and blood.
This was the era of the Spring
and Autumn Warring States.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
Defend the gate!
[GUARDS yell]
[XIN yells]
[XIN grunting]
[JIANG, JIE SHI gasp]
[JIANG] At this rate, the Red
Turtle Gate will be breached!
[JIE SHI]
The scoundrels...
[XIN grunting]
[XIN]
Ta-daaa!
That was amazing work, Xin.
No sweat.
Hurry! Get us out of here!
Target that carriage!
That's Minister Jie Shi!
Wait, that's Minister Jie Shi?
Isn't he one of the ringleaders
of this whole plot?
[XIN]
Why didn't you just say so?!
[LAN KAI growls]
What's with you?
What is it, Lan Kai?
Go faster! Push the
horses harder!
Oh no! Sir, they're
going to catch us!
Wh-What are
you doing?! My lord?!
What's that guy's problem?
He threw his own
underling at us!
[DIAO]
That's just sick!
That old guy's the
scum of the earth!
It's not only Minister
Jie, unfortunately.
[BI]
Aside from Lord Changwen,
most of the ministers who
hang around the Royal Court
are just that sort of person.
[XIN]
Oh man! Those guys got a horse!
They're gonna get
to the fun before me!
What on earth...?!
[DIAO] This battle is finishing
up faster than I thought.
It's thanks to His Majesty
and my Lord Changwen.
Their scheme to draw out
Jie Shi was a success!
It kinda stings to
see somebody else
take the ringleader's head,
but at least that
old man is finished now!
[YANG DUANHE]
Halt!
That's Si Shi!
[DIAO] Th-There's even
more soldiers now.
I'm getting scared again, Xin...
Well done, Si Shi.
My lord.
Your timing is impeccable.
But how were you able to figure
out they were deceiving us?
When they first arrived
in the capital...
[SI SHI] I noticed that
a few of them were wearing
something shiny under
their straw coats.
[SI SHI]
I suspected it was armor.
Meaning there are
flatlanders among them?
It's very likely that the
mountain folk came down
because someone from the
flatlands prompted them to.
However...
There are very few flatlanders
who could hope to inspire
mountain folk into action.
It couldn't be!
If his head hasn't
turned up by now,
then it most certainly could be.
I know you are there,
Ying Zheng.
Reveal yourself, King of Qin!
Si Shi's troops are
on a different level.
They're all
battle-hardened veterans.
This time, our disadvantage
in numbers will matter.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
It will, indeed.
[ZHENG]
Split off Bi's wing.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
[SI SHI]
What's the matter?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Bi!
My lord?
We know Your Majesty is there.
Don't bother
concealing yourself.
We will find you!
Aye, sir.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I pray you'll succeed.
Right.
[SI SHI] Come forth and show
yourself, King Ying Zheng!
It is Ying Zheng!
Have you enjoyed
your fleeting glory,
Minister Jie Shi?
So, was it enough for you?
Coming forward
with no escort, huh?
Unwise of you.
What is that idiot doing?
He's gonna get
picked off from there!
[BI]
It's fine.
The crossbow bolts can't
reach him from there.
[XIN]
Bi, my man...
Ba Jio?
Everyone from here to the right
will break off on my mark.
When I give the command,
follow me.
[BA JIO]
Understood.
Wait, we're gonna break off?
[BI] That's right.
Let's do this, Xin.
Hey, hold on!
These new troops have
a totally different aura
than the last bunch we took on.
If Zheng doesn't have the
commander or me with him,
he'll be in real trouble!
That's actually
part of the plan.
[BI] While the King draws
the enemy forces to him,
we'll strike at Cheng Jiao
in the inner sanctum!
[XIN gasps]
[WANG YI] Hmm...
isn't this King admirable?
Things have certainly
gotten interesting
all of a sudden.
Charge forward!
Fill those who oppose
you full of holes!
And glory to the man who
chops off the King's head!
[JIE SHI]
Huh?
That bunch is headed
for the corridor.
There may only be a few of them,
but isn't it dangerous
to lose sight of them
and let them run amok inside?
Do not worry yourself, my lord.
Zuo Ci is waiting in
the corridor for them.
[XIN]
All right! Go to it, Tajifu!
Ow!
He did it!
Right. We're going in.
[BI]
He'll be fine.
Lord Changwen and the mountain
folk are with His Majesty.
It's time for us to
play our own part
in this battle, Xin.
Yeah, I know that.
[XIN]
Speed it up, Bi!
Let's get this show going!
Ready a volley!
Wei Xing's crossbowmen
are known and feared
far and wide,
all over the realm.
Before they get our range,
let us fall back and reformulate
our tactics, Your Majesty.
[YANG DUANHE]
There's no need for that.
Yang Duanhe...
[YANG DUANHE]
The blood of the mountain folk
is just getting stirred up.
[panting]
[BI]
This way.
[XIN]
Hey, Bi, hate to ask...
but are you sure that
we're going the right way
to find that little
jerk, Cheng Jiao?
Well, the route from this
corridor to the inner sanctum
is a pretty complex labyrinth.
Most people couldn't
hope to ever traverse it.
[XIN]
What?
[BI] But don't worry,
we'll be fine.
We used them to lead
Lord Piao to escape before.
I know every route
to the throne room.
I know where we're going.
Oh-ho!
So you're the go-to guy for all
this stuff, eh, Bi, my man?
You're all fired up
for this, aren't you?
[BI]
Of course I am!
From the moment we led
Lord Piao out until now,
countless lives
have been sacrificed.
I was the lieutenant.
The blame for those
losses weighs on me
too heavily for words.
I'd give my life to
ensure all those deaths
weren't in vain; to take down
Cheng Jiao once and for all.
[XIN] You can't take down
Cheng Jiao if you're dead!
What is it, Yang Duanhe?
Let's pull back.
The mountain folk are strong...
but even they can't fend off
that many crossbow bolts.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
We must fall back!
[YANG DUANHE] We mountain
folk do not give ground
to mere arrows!
[YANG DUANHE]
Prepare to charge!
This is madness! Don't do this!
Stupid monkeys.
Seems they are
intent on taking on
my elite archery
forces and dying.
[WEI XING]
This will be fun.
All forces, approach
closer to the targets!
Make sure every single
arrow hit its mark!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
They'll be wiped out.
Pull them back, Yang Duanhe!
[ZHENG]
No. We should follow them, too.
Your Majesty...
[WEI XING] All of you,
loose a volley! Shoot!
[YANG DUANHE]
Charge!
Impossible!
Those three men were
playing dead all this time?
[WEI XING]
Damn you! You were still alive?!
What are you waiting for?
Move forward!
Release a volley into them!
What the...?
What is the meaning of all this?
Si Shi!
Don't just stand there
looking blank!
You have to come up
with some sort of plan!
Messenger!
[MESSENGER 11A]
Yes, sir!
Assemble all the guards
of the Royal Court!
We will settle
things right here!
Only this many?
Zuo Ci?
What, you know this guy?
He's Si Shi's right hand man
and Jie Shi's chief executioner.
Chief executioner?
[BI] In the power struggle
between Lü Buwei and Jie Shi,
there've been tit-for-tat
assassinations
of each faction's
strongest players.
One of the main culprits
behind the scenes was Zuo Ci.
A number of my dearest friends
have been struck
down by his hand.
So he's kind of a
killer for hire, huh?
Not to worry. I got this.
I'll cut down
this bastard myself.
Don't underestimate Zuo Ci.
Yes, he can wear an assassin's
mask and be shadowy and sneaky,
but he's also a warrior
by nature, born and bred.
On the other hand...
Right now, Zuo Ci and Wei Xing
are the only people at court
who are capable of leading
soldiers into battle.
If we can break through here,
the way to the
throne room is clear!
This is the moment
of truth, everyone!
Oh yeah! You heard
him, Commander!
[BA JIO]
I will kill every one of them.
[yelling]
[LORD CHANGWEN] This is the
might of the mountain folk.
I thought I knew what they were
capable of, but I had no idea...
Yang Duanhe, it seems
I underestimated
the true strength
of your people.
I was rude in telling you
to fall back. My apologies.
[YANG DUANHE]
No apologies needed.
Your judgment was sound,
given the situation.
However...
[YANG DUANHE]
The mountain people
have our own
way of fighting!
A woman?!
The mountain king,
Yang Duanhe...
...is a woman?!
Taking her out would be
a huge achievement!
Rewards and promotions
are ours for the taking!
We'll slit that
white throat of hers!
Don't leave a
single enemy alive.
It's a festival of blood!
[XIN yells]
[DIAO] Incredible...
this is too amazing for words!
[DIAO]
Get 'em! Get 'em all!
[MOUNTAIN FOLK 11K]
He's not here...
Where did he go?
[ZUO CI]
Here I am.
[XIN gasps]
Next.
[ZUO CI] You've
overestimated yourselves...
... you worms.
[BI]
Dammit... How can this be?
With only two strokes,
he's completely turned
the tide of battle.
S-So this... this is Zuo Ci!
[BI]
Wh-What am I doing?
I-I should set the example
and stand before him,
rally our men's fighting
spirit... but still...
Even though I-I know what to do,
my body won't move!
I can't move!
[XIN]
Hey, hey.
Overestimating ourselves?
I think that's more your style.
Idiot-face!
[BI]
Xin!
That powerful aura...
is it Ba Jio?
No. I suspect
it's from that boy.
By the feel of it,
it looks like the real fight
is about to begin in there.
[XIN] This is the sword
bequeathed to me by Piao!
[NARRATOR] He's given
his blood, sweat, and tears.
Only one last measure
can be taken...
Next Time:
The Ultimate Sword-Blow.