[WANG YI] I simply came
to take your life.
Do you understand?
[WANG YI] However, it is
contingent upon your answer.
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[WANG YI]
There is only one question
I would like to ask by your
leave: What kind of king
does Your Highness
aim to be, exactly, then?
Please, think carefully
before answering me.
My prized blade does not
forgive insolent words...
...no matter who
the speaker may be.
The only King of
Middle Kingdom.
[gasping]
The only King?!
Those are bold words...
In all the past five
centuries as of late,
I know only one monarch who
spoke such foolhardy words
as you have.
He was once feared as
a "God of Battle"--
It would behoove you never to
utter King Zhao's name again.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Hold on,
Your Highness.
It's dangerous to speak of
King Zhao in front of that man!
The "God of Battle", King Zhao,
my great-grandfather,
most of his 55-year reign
was spent at war.
You were not the only
one to cherish him as a King.
Warriors from all over Qin
gave him their utmost loyalty
offering their lives.
Yet, in the seven years
after King Zhao fell,
Wang Yi, you would have then
lost your cherished lord,
and became a
hollow-hearted bird,
flailing, suffering
with nowhere to land.
If you keep chasing
after King Zhao's shade,
there will be no place
for you to land.
[ZHENG] However,
I haven't the least desire
to become a perch
for you whatsoever.
If you wish to
fight on my side,
then accept King Zhao's death
and finally set your feet
on the ground where they belong.
Then "Strange Bird of Qin"
will soar over all
the Middle Kingdom!
[WANG YI] Soar over
the Middle Kingdom...
[WANG YI chuckles]
So it's beyond me...
[KING ZHAO] Ahh, indeed, the
Middle Kingdom was too large.
[KING ZHAO coughs]
[KING ZHAO] I entrust you
with my dream then, Wang Yi.
Your Highness.
If I were to lose my King,
I wouldn't be able to fly again.
[KING ZHAO laughs]
[KING ZHAO] Don't say
such pitiful words now.
Even after I die, there will
always be battlefields.
However, there will be
no field on which to fight
for a dream with real heat.
Is that so?
There are any
number of other kings
who also want a unified
Middle Kingdom.
They do only in talk.
I can tell when I see them,
whether burning with love
for the Middle Kingdom
if they've planned this dream.
The real thing carries
a gleam in his eyes
like a boy as
Your Highness does.
[KING ZHAO laughs]
Like a young boy, you say?
[WANG YI] No other king truly
wants a unified Middle Kingdom.
They're all nobodies
avoiding the hard path,
scrapping and scrapping content
preserving the status quo.
[KING ZHAO]
That's a little harsh.
There's not a single
one anywhere...
No praiseworthy king who
is willing to devote his life
to that dream.
A praiseworthy king, huh?
[KING ZHAO chuckles]
[KING ZHAO] If I could live
for another twenty years, I...
might have realized my dream.
Ah, Wang Yi.
Even if you give up flight,
just keep your talons sharp.
It would be unforgivable
for a warrior of your caliber
to die and be forgotten.
Even if there is none
now, in the future,
a king like myself
may appear again one day.
[KING ZHAO]
If that time comes, Wang Yi,
you must beat your wings
even harder than now!
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI]
After King Zhao passed away,
many kings tried to enlist
me, but all tossed around
the words "Middle Kingdom" or
"all under Heaven" too lightly.
Not one was the real thing.
But this young King's not bad.
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] He's still different
from King Zhao,
but he's not bad.
That lovely gleam...
This young King's eyes
are nothing like King Zhao's
burning love for the nation,
but is focused on the path
to a unified Middle Kingdom.
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] One might call it
arrogance born of youth,
but there hasn't been
a single King
who's stared down at unified
Middle Kingdom with those eyes.
The 31st King of Qin;
Ying Zheng...
[WANG YI] Lord Changwen...
Now I understand a little
why you've gotten yourself all
hot and bothered, if you will.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Hmm...?
[WANG YI giggles]
This was quite an
interesting conversation.
I guess, for today,
I will be taking my leave.
[gasping]
[WANG YI laughs]
Your Highness, thinking that
I want to fight at your side
betrays certain
self-absorptions...
[WANG YI] Please build up
the corresponding strength,
if you are going to
speak so grandly now.
This is no time to be fumbling
with your little brother,
do you understand?
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] With that,
we will withdraw!
[TROOPS] Sir!
[WANG YI]
You'll withdraw, too, Teng.
[TENG] Yes.
[WANG YI] King Zhao...
A heated time may be on its way
once again, Your Highness.
Well, Wang Yi...
I can't overlook your
killing of Wei Xing,
but the reality is you've
brought things to a halt.
I will put things in
order before it is known
that Minister Jie Shi is dead.
[XIN panting]
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[CHENG JIAO yells]
[SI SHI gasps]
[CHENG JIAO screams]
[SI SHI] Lord Cheng Jiao!
Wait, my lord!
What is this?
The battle has stopped?!
[ZHENG gasps]
[ZHENG] Xin!
Huh? Well, hey there!
You're still alive.
[CHENG JIAO whimpers]
[CHENG JIAO screams]
[SOLDIER 15A] Lord Cheng Jiao!
[SOLDIER 15B]
Why's Lord Cheng Jiao here?
Ying Zheng!
This is Ying Zheng!
Go kill him! Kill him!
What are you all doing?!
Hurry up and kill him! Cut him!
What is going on here exactly?
--[gasping]
--Huh?
[SOLDIERS whimper]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
This is insane!
Have we lost the battle, then?
C-Come on, lowborn!
I, the powerful High King,
will cut you down in a flash.
You just watch!
[CHENG JIAO whimpers]
Cheng Jiao.
You're a common fool
who mistakenly believes
that a person's value
rests solely in high birth.
You are completely unfit
to be a King!
[CHENG JIAO sighs]
[CHENG JIAO] You speak
above your station...
Then are you saying that
you're fit to be a King instead?
You are semi-royalty
and your blood is half
from a mere commoner.
Can you rule over the people?
[ZHENG] I can.
I won't concede to a commoner.
I, the pure blood,
will rule the people
and make the kingdom strong!
[CHENG JIAO YELLS]
You've received a
twisted education, Cheng Jiao.
The people are not as simple
minded as you or I think.
They don't much care
about us royals.
Yes, it was petty!
You think us people on
the bottom give a damn
about who's king?!
None of that matters!
[ZHENG] You only
look down with arrogance,
knowing nothing
about people's hearts.
Looking down on others
is your only ability!
[CHENG JIAO grunting]
Ignorant about the world,
ignorant about people...
That is why
you are always alone!
You are truly unfit
to be the King!
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[CHENG JIAO sighs]
Silence... You be silent!
I am the only King...
I am the only king of Qin!
[slicing]
[XIN gasps]
[LORD CHANGWEN gasps]
Heeh...
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[CHENG JIAO screams]
[CHENG JIAO whimpering,
squealing]
--M-My arm! Bleeding!
--You are so concerned about
--I'm bleeding!
--a little bit of blood?
--[CHENG JIAO screams]
--So many people have bled
or lost their lives
in vain over your whims.
Can you understand this,
Cheng Jiao?
Do you understand this?!
[CHENG JIAO squeals]
You!
I cannot believe
you did this to me!
Don't think you'll
get away with this!
Dingy low-life half-made
born-of-a-commoner thug!
That is all you want to say?!
[CHENG JIAO grunts]
[CHENG JIAO screams]
[ZHENG] Cheng Jiao, learn a
little of the pain others feel!
[blow lands,
CHENG JIAO grunts]
--[blows landing]
--[CHENG JIAO] I'm sorry!
--I'm so sorry! Sorry!
--[blows landing]
--Oh, don't--! I'm so sorry!
--I'm sorry! Gahaaa!
[ZHENG sighs]
[CHENG JIAO whimpers]
Those who died in the
battle felt pain thousands,
--tens of thousands times worse.
--[CHENG JIAO sobs]
[ZHENG]
Now that the victory's won,
there's no value in killing you.
Too much blood
has flowed over trifles!
We don't need
more bloodshed now!
I guarantee the safety of your
lives. Surrender immediately!
I'll will end this revolt
with the fewest
possible lives sacrificed!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
H-He'll guarantee our lives?
[XIN growls]
[XIN] Didn't you hear him?!
Toss away your weapons
immediately and surrender!
In this battle...
victory is ours!
[cheering]
[XIN] Hey!
[XIN] Diao!
Xin...
[XIN] Bi, my man...
How's Diao doing?
Diao is just fine.
More importantly, how are
things in the courtyard?
Is His Highness well?
And how about my lord?
And what about
the Mountain King?
[XIN] Everything is
settled there now.
Don't worry;
everyone's all right.
Is that so...
That is good. That is good.
Oh, that's right!
Listen to me, Xin.
Huh?
[BI] The fact is that Diao
is--Ah, Your Highness!
Your Highness,
I'm so glad you're safe!
I am glad you are both, too.
It seems this was a gory fight.
Not a big deal at all.
[XIN laughs]
[XIN] You look like an old guy!
[ZHENG] Hmph.
Let me be...
[laughing, cheering]
Ooh, it's so lively out here!
Huh? Where are Xin and others?
[BI] Diao!
[DIAO] Hey, Bi!
What'd you bring me
all the way here for?
I'm hungry, you know...
[BI] Yang Duanhe's folks are
going home to the mountains
in the morning.
Going home?
After we finally
became friends...
[BI] Although she's called
the mountain king,
apparently she doesn't have
control over all the tribes.
She is going to keep
strengthening her power
until His Highness sets out
across the Middle Kingdom.
[DIAO] Huh...
[BI] Go back to the
mountains with them.
[DIAO] Huh?!
You have to give up all
this pretending to be a boy
and living on your own.
[DIAO gasps]
[XIN] Huh? Hey!
Seems like Diao
is doing just fine now.
[BA JIO] It's been
decided that Yang Duanhe
will take the child in.
What? You're letting
Diao join you?
[BA JIO] Correct.
[XIN] Guess Diao is originally
of the mountain folk...
He's a rotten little punk,
but look after the kid for me...
Commander.
[BA JIO gasps]
Hey.
[ZHENG] I heard that you're
leaving the Court
in the morning.
Yeah, because old
man Lord Changwen
said that he is going to
get a house ready for me.
Considering your success,
I can promote you to a
guardsman of the Court.
[XIN laughs]
You're joking.
You honestly think I could stand
doing something that boring?
I'm setting out
for the battlefield!
Piling up wins,
then I'll become a general!
I guess things'll be tough
for you, too, from here on, huh?
[ZHENG] I left Jie Shi's forces,
but it's clear that
they're weakening.
Lü's power will grow
greater now.
But that is only
until I come of age
for governing this kingdom.
When I reach 20
and get crowned,
I'll strip Lü of
his power without failing.
And then...
...I'll set the Middle Kingdom!
[XIN] That's it.
[ZHENG] Xin... until then,
rise up the ladder.
[XIN] Yep.
[LÜ BUWEI] I see.
So they've been pacified.
[AIDE 15A] Yes, sir!
[LÜ BUWEI laughs]
[LÜBUWEI] Time to go
then... to Xianyang.
[ZHENG] You truly did us
a great service.
I am grateful to the valorous
mountain folk with all my heart.
The fight's just begun.
We'll share our knowledge,
of the moves of both internal
and external enemies.
In the future, I'll send
messengers regularly.
I'll send them, too.
I also want to further our
exchanges of technology.
You have a clear vision.
I look forward to when
you become the King
of Middle Kingdom.
We'll meet again!
[DIAO] Isn't it great, Xin,
that we can get our own house?
[XIN] There is no "our".
It's my house.
And why the heck are you
coming along with me anyway?!
[DIAO] Dummy.
If you were all alone,
what would you do for food?
[XIN] Food?
That's so simple, I...
Um, I can't handle it, I guess.
[DIAO laughs]
See, that's why
I'm so generously
coming along with you.
Show some gratitude!
Whatever.
Do what you want.
[DIAO] Hey!
The house Lord Changwen
gave us isn't that way!
[XIN] This is the right way.
There's a place
I'd like to stop by.
[DIAO] Huh?
[DIAO] Where are we?
[XIN] The village where
Piao and I grew up.
Piao is... the guy who
was a stand-in for Zheng?
Yeah.
The reason why I am
what I am now
is because I met Piao
in this village.
Xin...
Take me with you, and conquer
everything under the Heavens.
Piao!
[XIN] I've made it
this far, Piao.
Along the road you and I
chose, I made it far!
[DIAO] So it's because
you met Piao
that you became as
strong as you are...
[XIN] Yeah.
[DIAO] It sure is
mysterious, huh?
[XIN] Huh?
[DIAO] That Piao met Zheng,
and Zheng met you as well...
[DIAO] Who could've imagined it?
Me, too.
I feel like my fate changed
in a big way by meeting you.
Nope, that is
just totally wrong.
[DIAO] Mmm,
what's wrong about that?
It didn't change, you see.
You just changed it yourself.
Fate changes if we
carve out the path
Oh, then I guess
that's true!
[XIN] Piao, I'm burying
my memories with you
in this village...
...so that I can
forge ahead with the dream.
--[XIN yells]
--[DIAO screams]
[DIAO] Hey, where did
that come from?!
[XIN] Go, go, hurry, hurry!
[DIAO] Xin,
don't leave me behind!
Wait for me, Xin!
[DIAO] Wha... What is this?!
[XIN] Well, it looks
like a house to me.
What makes this a house?!
This is a shed!
That old man stingied us
out of a house!
Say something, Xin!
It's perfect.
Huh?
[XIN] Because I originally
had nothing whatsoever.
Now at last,
I own land and a house.
I'll win more acclaim and
get bigger lands as well!
To start with a
broken-down shed is fine!
This is our first castle,
Diao! Our first castle!
Yeah! We made it! [XIN laughs]
[DIAO] No we haven't, you dummy!
[laughing continues]
[XIN] I can't speak!
What is it... this sensation?
[NARRATOR] Displaying
an unfathomable smile,
that man quietly pays obeisance.
Next Time: "Lü Buwei."