[XIN grunting]
Ohhh, come on!
We've been walking for
three days already.
When the hell are we
gonna get back home?
[PIAO] Don't waste
your breath, Xin.
You'll just tire yourself out.
But Piao...
Three more days' walk
and we'll get to the village.
Just think of it
as good conditioning.
[XIN] Usually for this
distance and this load,
you'd use a horse-cart.
What, do servants
rate lower than horses?
[PIAO] Yeah, and
that's why we're doing
all this conditioning...
to break free of being servants.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, I get it, but still...
[rumbling]
Huh?
What the heck
is that sound?
[PIAO]
Is it an earthquake?
[XIN] No, wait...
it's coming from over there!
[PIAO] It is!
[NARRATOR] Battle.
The scene unfolding
before the two boys' eyes
was the first glimpse they had
ever had of real warfare.
[NARRATOR] In truth,
it was nothing more
than a mere border skirmish,
a small, unremarkable fight
with a neighboring country.
But in it, the two men
could see their own futures
clear as day, and together,
they had the same thought...
"This is the world where
we will live out our lives!"
[XIN] Piao!
This is a real battle!
[PIAO] Yes!
And one day, you and I will be
the heroes of a fight like this!
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife raged
across the land, consuming
everything in its wake.
Desire. Pleasure.
Suffering. Terror.
All without end.
In a time filled with so
much cruelty and destruction,
small wonder that
this era was known as...
"the dragon."
[NARRATOR] As though scorched
by the flames of the dragon,
over a hundred nations fell,
one after another,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
[NARRATOR] Yan, Qi,
Zhao, Wei, Han, Chu...
...and lastly, Qin.
[NARRATOR] Like lions trying
to devour their rivals,
these seven kingdoms
lunged at each other's throats
again and again,
their swords stained
with ambition and blood.
This was the era of the Spring
and Autumn Warring States.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
[NARRATOR] This is the tale of
a nameless boy and a King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
Yah!
[PIAO] Take that!
[XIN] It's not over yet!
[XIN and PIAO continue sparring]
[XIN] You missed again!
You and your brute
strength... huh?
[PIAO] Over here!
[PIAO] Hey.
Hooray!
That makes 333 wins,
332 losses, and 587 draws!
That means I'm up by one!
Damn it! One more match!
Just one more!
[PIAO] Huh?
Gotcha!
No, wait!
Someone's coming.
--[XIN groans]
--[PIAO] Huh?
Oh, that actually hit you?
What are you
lookin' at, old man?
[XIN] Yeah, that's right!
[PIAO] Stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid!
[PIAO] You idiot!
Look at his clothes,
and that carriage!
He's got to be a warrior
of high stature!
That doesn't mean
anything to me!
It means he could
have you killed!
What's with you boys?
Weren't you just
squabbling a minute ago?
[XIN] It wasn't a squabble,
it was a match!
And thanks to you,
old man, I lost!
Old man?
Out of 1,253 matches, I've won
332, lost 334, and tied 587!
Now, thanks to you,
for the first time this year,
I'm two behind!
1,253 matches?
[laughs]
So now the truth comes out.
You're a little boy who likes
to tell some tall tales
and make yourself look good.
[laughs]
You... you mean to tell me...
...that the two of you
have fought
over a thousand bouts
of that intensity?
That's not the sort of
thing normal people do...
[laughs]
I'm not surprised
you're shocked, sir.
A distinguished person like
yourself might not understand.
The two of us are orphans.
[XIN] Yeah, that's right.
We lost our families in the war
and were sold as slaves.
Now, we only
rank as servants.
[PIAO] As you can imagine,
we haven't inherited anything
from our parents...
...unless you count the
strength in our bodies.
But that's all the
inheritance we need!
Right. So long as these bodies
can still swing our swords,
Xin and I have enough!
[XIN] Warfare took
everything from us,
so we'll use warfare to
take just as much back!
[PIAO] That's right!
[XIN] We're gonna go into battle
and achieve greatness!
[PIAO] With the strength
and technique
we've built up together,
we'll win fortune and fame!
[XIN] We'll rise up
from the very bottom
and build our own houses!
[PIAO]
Yeah, magnificent mansions
with huge gardens
and giant gates!
[XIN] I'm gonna get a pretty
bride from a good family,
and make lots of babies,
and employ more household
servants than you can count!
[XIN, PIAO]
And most importantly...
...we will make our names
echo across all of China.
And together, we'll become
the most powerful generals
in all the world!
[laughing]
Ugh! He's laughing at us again!
I'll kill him!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
This encounter...
could be the one
that finally sweeps away
the dark clouds surrounding Qin.
[NARRATOR] Xianyang, the capital
of the Kingdom of Qin.
[NARRATOR] At that time,
the royal court was divided,
consumed by the swirling
flames of ambition.
On the one side, there was
Lü Buwei, aide to the King
and Minister of the Right,
the highest Court post.
On the other side, Jie Shi held
the second-highest post,
Minister of the Left.
With these men as the
hubs of their factions,
the Court had split in two.
[NARRATOR] The rivalry
escalated quickly.
Soon, blood washed
away blood,
and the conflict continued
day and night.
[NARRATOR] And then...
The King's younger
half-brother, Cheng Jiao,
joined together with Jie Shi
to claim the throne as his own,
and tensions in the Royal Court
seemed poised to bubble over.
[coughing and groaning]
[LI DIAN muffled]
Water! Water!
What in the
world is this?
You call this food?
It's not even edible!
It's so nasty!
[LI DIAN]
Which of you made this?
Xin. I knew it.
[YOU]
I thought it was you!
[YOU] You're not good for
anything, not like Piao.
You can't cook, can't clean...
We got a word for stupid
servants like you...
..."useless!"
Ah, he glared at me!
Father, Xin's being mean
and glaring at me!
He what?!
Why you ungrateful brat!
[LI DIAN]
What are you glaring at?
Are you saying you've got
some cause for complaint?
We don't need
the likes of him!
He's not like Piao.
He can't do anything!
[LI DIAN] Have you forgotten
who to thank for being alive?
You're war orphans!
You only survived
because as this village's chief,
I provided for the two of you!
And this is what I get for it!
[XIN] Dammit!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
[PIAO] They'll hear you, stupid!
Your voice is going to carry.
Dammit! Dammit!
I don't care!
I've reached the end of my rope!
I'm gonna thrash 'em all and
leave this house for good!
It's too soon.
Do you really think
we have what it takes
to put food on the table
for two of us?
We'd just end up starving.
[XIN]
Then we'll become bandits!
And this house can be
the first place we strike!
[PIAO] Xin!
Huh? What is it?
[PIAO] We haven't been
training this long
in order to become
something like that.
Are you that foolish?
I know that. It was
a joke, okay? That's all.
What's your problem?
What, you still want something?
[YOU]
Piao, come right away!
Quickly! Hurry!
This is really big!
Huh?
[PIAO, XIN] Huh?
Hey, that's...
...from earlier.
[LI DIAN] Piao, my lad!
Where are you?
"My lad?"
Ah, Piao, my boy!
Come along now, hurry up!
Hey, what about me?
What about you?
Go do your chores in the barn!
Huh?
Ah, Piao, this gentleman's
name is Lord Changwen.
He's a powerful man of very high
station in the Kingdom of Qin,
one of the Ministers
who serves in the Royal Court.
[PIAO] A Minister...
...from court!
Piao. As of today,
Lord Changwen will be taking
you under his protection.
What... did he say?!
That's correct.
Beginning tomorrow,
you will be working for me
in the Royal Court.
[PIAO] Me, at court?
That's right.
[PIAO] I, I don't...
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I cannot speak here about
affairs of the Royal Court,
but I would have you
accept a special post
and take on an important duty.
[PIAO] So wait,
are you saying...
Does this mean I could
be an official at court?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Correct.
P-Piao, in the Royal Court?
Oh wow, amazing!
[PIAO] What about Xin?
[PIAO]
Can... can he come with me?
He's got just as much
potential as I do!
Denied!
I am taking one person,
and one alone.
[LORD CHANGWEN] You!
Only you, Piao!
[LI DIAN]
What's the matter, Piao?
Why don't you hurry up
and accept, already?
[PIAO]
I beg your pardon.
Please give me one day's time
to consider your offer.
I need to sort through
my feelings on this.
Wha--Wait,
what did you say?!
I understand.
I'll return tomorrow.
Xin!
Xin...
Xin, where are you?!
Xin!
Why didn't you accept
his offer right away?
A small-town servant suddenly
becoming a court official?
That's beyond our
wildest dreams!
How can you turn that down?!
[PIAO] I don't have
the slightest idea
what this is all about.
I should say I've trained all
this time so I could rise,
step by step,
by my own ability...
...and that I haven't been
competing with you this long
just so I could slip
in the easy way.
[XIN] You idiot!
But I'm not gonna
say that, Xin.
Huh?
That's right. I'm going.
Of course you are!
[PIAO] You are
really good, you know!
[XIN] Damn right I am!
[PIAO] With your skills,
you'll be following me soon!
So hurry up and
catch up with me!
I know we're gonna
end up in the same place.
I know it, too!
I'm gonna surpass you
in no time!
[MERCHANT] Fresh meat!
Come right up and
get your fresh meat!
[MERCHANTS chatting]
[OPEN-AIR MERCHANT]
Xin! Here's a tip.
Hey, thanks!
Yeah, you did good work.
So it's been, what, a month
since Piao went to the Capital?
You know, I think you've
changed since then, Xin.
I have?
Yeah, you're like
a baby monkey
who's grown
into a monkey-boy.
What'd you say?!
[laughs]
So you're adjusting okay, then?
I wonder how
Piao is doing.
I can't really see
how a mere servant
could manage palace duties.
That's 'cause you're a fool!
It doesn't matter if it's
in the Royal Court or not.
Piao'll learn in no time!
[MERCHANT B]
This is a nightmare!
If I'm shut out
of the Royal Court,
where the hell am I
supposed to hawk my goods?
[MERCHANT B] This is
more than I can stand!
Huh?
[MERCHANT A]
I'm having the same problem.
The talk is that
the Court's in no state
to be doing any
business at all right now.
Huh...
So maybe that rumor going
around is true, then.
The rumor?
You mean the one about an
uprising happening at Court?
About the King and all his
loyal followers getting killed?
[MERCHANT B]
Then you know about that, too?
Rumors sure seem
to spread quickly, huh?
What did he say?!
[OPEN-AIR MERCHANT]
Don't worry, Xin.
There are rumors
like that all the time.
Pay it no mind.
Oh... yeah.
[JIE SHI] What's that?
Are you absolutely certain?
[HERALD] Yes, sir.
There's no doubting the report.
There's a swift horse
on its way to Lü Buwei,
who's on expedition
against the Kingdom of Wei.
Oh, is that so?
I take it that you dispatched
someone to pursue this horse?
[HERALD] Yes.
O-Of course we did, sir.
[JIE SHI] That horse might
be carrying a message,
and if it reaches
its destination,
that scoundrel Lu Buwei will
know what we've been up to.
If he joins the King's side,
this won't just be
a simple coup.
The entire kingdom
will break in half!
We've got no more
room for delay.
Order all our forces
to move into action,
with every possible haste!
[HERALD] Understood!
[CHENG JIAO] Calm down.
It's getting way
too heated in here!
This is likely something
he's already accounted
for in his plans.
I wouldn't get so
worked up over it.
[JIE SHI]
Yes, my honored lord.
Understood.
[CHENG JIAO]
Still... I won't lie,
the prospect of speeding
things along does interest me.
After all,
I do want to see
my half-brother's head
presented to me soon.
[JIE SHI] Yes, my lord.
Please, leave it to me.
My friends... the time has come!
[ALL FOLLOWERS] Aye!
[LI DIAN] This gentleman's
name is Lord Changwen.
He's a powerful man of very high
station in the Kingdom of Qin,
one of the Ministers who
serves at the Royal Court.
[LORD CHANGWEN] I cannot
speak here about affairs
of the Royal Court,
But I would have you
accept a special post
and take on an important duty.
[MERCHANT A] The rumor?
You mean the one about an
uprising happening at Court?
About the King and all his
loyal followers getting killed?
[XIN] Piao, you're
still okay, right?
[LI DIAN]
Piao! This is Xin.
He'll be living with
you from now on.
He's a war orphan like you.
Teach him how to do
his chores, all right?
Hey there!
Your name's Piao, right?
Nice to meet you!
You, too.
Hey, do you wanna have
a sword fight with me?
Huh?
Sounds fun! I'm in!
[PIAO] Xin, you may think
you're lucky to get taken in,
but... well, not really.
In the end, you and I are just
servants in the chief's house.
[XIN] What are
you trying to say?
[PIAO] A servant's
a servant forever,
even when he grows up.
He marries a female servant,
and his children end up
as servants, too.
I hate the thought of it!
[XIN]
I hate it, too!
But there's nothing we
can do about it, right?
[PIAO] We'll break free with
our sword-fighting skills!
[XIN]
Our sword-fighting skills?
[PIAO]
We'll go to war!
If we can get famous
on the battlefield,
we can break away
from being servants.
[XIN]
Piao, you're amazing!
We've always
got our swords.
We've got our swords!
[XIN] Piao...
What are you doing right now?
I swear I'll catch up to you.
Wait for me...
I'm home, Xin...
[XIN] Piao!
[XIN] Stay with me, Piao!
Open your eyes!
I said open your eyes!
Wha-What's all this
about, Xin?
Is it a thief?
Chief! We need a doctor,
quickly! Please, hurry!
P-Piao!
Where's all that
blood coming from?
Forget that! Get a doctor!
[PIAO] Xin...
It doesn't hurt.
There's no need...
for a doctor.
Piao...
how did this happen?
What happened in the capital?
[PIAO] The King's brother...
he staged an uprising.
I got caught up in it.
[XIN]
His brother?
The King's younger
half-brother? He's rebelling?
What are you saying?
The rumor?
You mean the one about an
uprising happening at Court?
About the King and all his
loyal followers getting killed?
[PIAO] The King...
His side only had that
minister, Lord Changwen...
...and just a small
handful of troops.
His brother's forces...
They were too many,
and too strong for us.
They were unstoppable.
They've taken
over the capital.
Try not to talk too much.
There are people after me.
If they follow
the trail of blood,
they'll find their way here.
Wha... What?
[XIN] People after you?
[PIAO] When they get here...
chief... please,
just tell them some
stranger came by
and died in the barn.
And... leave my body.
Don't do anything with it.
Oh... Got it...
I won't let 'em touch you!
I won't let a single one
of 'em go back alive!
Not a single one!
It's good to hear
that spirit again, Xin.
[XIN] Don't try to speak.
[PIAO] Wait, no, there's
something I have to ask of you.
[XIN] A map?
[PIAO] Yes.
It's of a village west of here
named Heibei Village.
[LI DIAN] Heibei Village?!
It's a village of outlaws,
a place where thieves
and murderers
from every kingdom
come together.
They say it's a place
of pure horror,
and that any normal
person who goes there
will never come back alive!
Xin!
I came to pass this on to you.
You have to go there
right away, for me!
Wha-What is this?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand any of this!
[PIAO] Listen, Xin.
I entrust it to you!
[XIN] I understand.
I understand, Piao.
I'll do it.
[soft sobbing]
So don't die, Piao!
You can't...
You have to...
You've gotta...
We've gotta...
You and me have gotta
become the greatest generals
in the world!
Isn't that what you said?
[PIAO] We will.
Xin...
[PIAO] We're the same...
in both ability and spirit.
The two of us have
always been one at heart.
[PIAO] If you spread...
your wings and fly...
I promise...
I'll be there, too...
Xin...
Take me with you...
And conquer everything
under the heavens.
Piao!
[XIN] Piao...
[XIN sobbing]
[XIN screams]
[XIN] Why?!
Why did this happen?
[LI DIAN] Stop! Xin!
[screaming]
[XIN] I'll kill them all!
The ones that did this to Piao!
I won't give them
a clean death, either!
I'll rip them apart!
Every last one of them!
I won't stop 'til
Piao's killers are dead!
I'll kill them!
I'll kill them all!
All...
[XIN] I'll kill them all!
I'll kill them!
Kill them all!
Kill them!
--[XIN] Kill them all!
--[LI DIAN] H-Hey!
[XIN] I'll kill them all...
I'll kill the--
[YOU] Xin!
Don't you dare let Piao's
death be in vain!
Xin! Do you hear me?
What'd you say,
you little piece of--
[YOU]
You know something?
Yeah, I admit,
I've always hated you.
But the truth is,
I always loved Piao!
So you're not the only
one who wants revenge
on Piao's killers, you know!
I wanna find the bastards
who did this and... and...
I want to carve them into
little bloody pieces!
But... you have to
go and do this, Xin.
I don't understand any of this
any better than you do.
But I know this, for sure...
If you don't want Piao's
death to be in vain,
then the only thing you can
do is go to this village!
[PIAO] I came to
pass this on to you.
You have to go there
right away, for me!
Listen, Xin.
I entrust it to you!
[LI DIAN] You really
intend to go, Xin?
Please, don't do this!
Heibei Village is supposed
to be a village of killers!
It's a horrible place.
They say once you
set foot in it,
you'll never come back alive!
And besides, there's all
this about the uprising,
and the King's
half-brother, and...
[XIN] None of that
makes a difference.
[XIN] I don't care that
it's a den of killers.
I don't care what's
happening in the capital.
[XIN] Piao told me to go...
[XIN] And so...
...no matter what,
I'm going!
[CHENG JIAO] Jie Shi.
[JIE SHI] My lord?
I am well aware of how desperate
you are to have this kingdom
all in hand, but you see, I have
no interest in such matters.
All I want is my
half-brother's corpse
covered in his own
tainted blood,
as proof that he's dead at last.
[JIE SHI] Yes...
and you will have
it soon, my lord.
How polite of you.
But surely you're secretly
smirking into your sleeve?
After all, you must consider
both me and my
half-brother upstarts,
who owe our stations
entirely to Lü Buwei.
What are you saying,
honored lord?
Your esteemed father,
King Zhuangxiang,
ascended to the throne
by his own virtues,
not just due to Lü Buwei
like the groundless
rumors might suggest.
Skip the play-acting.
We've come too far for games.
In any event, it's that shameful
connection that I want to sever.
That's why I've
allied myself with you.
[CHENG JIAO]
Dun! Come forward.
[DUN] My lord!
[JIE SHI, ATTENDANT]
Huh?
[CHENG JIAO] This man is from
a poor artisan's household.
He was abandoned by his parents,
but he has some talent with both
a sword and a writing brush,
and thanks to that, he's
managed to advance to a post
working for me here in Xianyang.
He now has his
own residence.
He even sends an allowance to
the parents who abandoned him.
[JIE SHI, ATTENDANT]
Ah...
[CHENG JIAO]
He's no equal to Lü Buwei,
but he's scraped his way
up from the bottom.
[snaps fingers]
[CHENG JIAO] I can't stand
people like that.
They make me nauseous.
No matter how
precious the clothes
they drape themselves in, they
can't change what's underneath!
And it's the same
with my half-brother!
His mother is a vulgar woman,
with no connections or ties
whatsoever to the royal house!
To think the spawn
of such a wretch
could come ahead of me
to take the throne...
It will not be tolerated!
I have a mother of
the royal blood.
I am the one worthy to be King!
[CHENG JIAO]
When my half-brother
took the throne from me,
I came to understand
the Royal Court's
true feelings toward
him... and me.
In the end, they were all
only interested in kneeling
to the position of kingship.
Every last one of them,
bowing and scraping.
That's all that matters
to people of their "caliber."
That is why I don't
count on people anymore.
[CHENG JIAO]
There are a few things
that can be counted
on in this world:
Greed, lust for power,
ugly human desires.
I take advantage of them and
move things along as I like.
Arranging to send Lü Buwei
away on an expedition
is just one example.
[JIE SHI] It's dangerous to
underestimate Lü Buwei, though.
With him as your enemy,
you may need to raise
tens of thousands
of men for your army.
I suppose you're trying to say
that I need the royal seal.
That thing is no
more than a token,
but do whatever you must
to simplify matters.
[JIE SHI]
Yes, honored lord.
[CHENG JIAO] Soon, we can
reverse the sands of time
back to the way things should
have been five years ago.
[WANG YI] So...
What has become
of Lord Changwen?
It's exactly as you
expected, my lord.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] It looks like things
are about to get interesting.
[YOU] Hey, can't we do
something for him?
We can't just leave
him here like this!
Poor Piao!
Don't you care about him?
Uh, yeah...
But remember,
Piao said there would be
people coming after him,
and to do nothing with his body.
But what on earth...?
[XU WAN] Ying Zheng...
You people...
Did you speak with him?
No, no, no!
There was a noise,
so we came out and
we found this guy here,
and, well, he was already dead!
[XU WAN] Is that so?
Well, that saved your life.
[YOU] Stop!
[XU WAN] Hmm?
[XU WAN] Well, now...
What happened
to this man's sword?
[LI DIAN] We don't know!
We don't know anything!
[XU WAN] It's obvious
you're hiding something.
[LI DIAN] N-No!
We're really not!
Not a thing!
[YOU] Father!
--You!
[sword slicing]
[YOU screaming]
[LI DIAN, WIFE] You!
Speak quickly.
Or next, I'll stab him
in the heart.
Hey, look, someone
came to visit.
Showing up at a place like
this at such a late hour?
This punk must have no brains.
[VILLAGER 1C] The sword at
his hip's a wooden one,
but the one on his back looks
awful nice, don't ya think?
[VILLAGER 1B] That was
some good scouting, Diao.
Here!
[XIN] Hey.
So I take it I've arrived
at Heibei Village?
[VILLAGERS laugh]
If you're just realizing
that now, it's too late!
If you hand over that sword
on your back quietly,
then we'll leave you unharmed
for when we sell
you off to the slavers.
But if you resist, your corpse
will take a swim in the river.
Which do you--
[pounding noise]
[VILLAGER groaning]
[VILLAGER yelling]
[XIN] Sorry about that.
I'm in a hurry.
[VILLAGERS groaning]
[VILLAGER 1B]
That little piece of crap...
Diao! Call everyone
in the village together
and have them
go after that punk!
Don't let that little
snot-nosed wannabe brat
leave here alive!
[VILLAGER 1G] They got beat up.
So it wasn't just
one kid after all?
What the heck?
[VILLAGER 1G] Here he comes!
[VILLAGER 1G] That's him!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Wha--What's up with this kid?
[VILLAGER 1G]
Go call everyone together!
Surround him!
Don't let him get away!
[VILLAGER 1G] He's crazy fast!
Hey, grab him!
Maybe if we get
a hold of him...
That's some crazy brute force!
What is he,
some kinda monster?
[XIN] That's right.
[XIN]
Compared to the swordsmanship
of half-assed
scum like you,
mine is different!
[PIAO] Xin!
Uh huh?
Someday, the two of us
are gonna be famous generals!
[XIN] Huh? What,
do you have a fever?
There's no way that's
ever gonna happen!
We can do it!
If we win like crazy...
...rack up some achievements,
get recognized,
and climb to the top,
we can become generals!
Generals?
That's right!
We'll dress in golden armor,
and ride all across the Earth!
And in the end, we'll become
the greatest generals
in all the world!
Yeah... the greatest generals!
And then...
our names will
go down in history!
[PIAO] Exactly, Xin.
Right now,
we may be just servants,
but we'll carve our two
names into future history!
[XIN]
So exactly how long
will our winning
streak have to be?
[PIAO] It's simple.
We'll just have
to be invincible.
We won't lose... to anybody!
[XIN] That's right.
[XIN] My sword...
[XIN] No, our sword...
[XIN] will resound
over all the world!
Nobody... Nobody will defeat us!
You want to keep at it?
Bunch of fools.
[XIN]
I've arrived...
[XIN] ...at the place...
where the rivers merge.
[XIN] That means...
...this is the place?
[XIN]
But... it's an ordinary hut!
Piao, it's just an ordinary hut!
What's the story here?
[XIN] I come all this way,
without avenging your death,
without even knowing why...
...and this is what I find?
[XIN] Tell me, Piao... Why?
Why did you die?
Why did you use your dying
breath to guide me here,
to this decrepit old shack?
What... what in the world
could be here?
It can't be!
It's not possible!
Piao?!
[XIN] You're the one!
You killed Piao!!
He's never...
he's never coming back!
[NARRATOR] When a man makes a
choice about a burning issue
in his life, a road
opens up before him.
Next Time:
An Encounter with Destiny