[MESSENGER 27A] Report!
We're under attack
from the left!
There are a hundred of them.
They're on their way
to Formation 2.
I see. So that's it, then.
[FENG JI] Wang Yi, I understand
you're after my head.
Interesting. Let's see
you try and take it!
[NARRATOR] The time:
The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
The place: Qin.
Xin, a nameless boy,
met Zheng, a young King,
distinguished himself in battle,
and rose to the rank
of squadron commander.
[NARRATOR] In the midst of this,
the neighboring
kingdom of Zhao invaded,
and Qin faced
unprecedented crisis.
What manner of battle
will Wang Yi wage
as commanding general?
And what growth
will Xin accomplish?
[yelling]
[XIN] We can do it.
If we keep this up,
we can do it!
[XIN] Yuan and I
used sneak attacks
to take the enemy by surprise
a bunch of times
in the stateless area.
[XIN] The tribe we protected
only had a hundred people,
so we pretty much had no choice.
[XIN] But thanks to that,
I know the power of surprise!
[yelling]
[WEI PING] We got through...
B-But the hard part
comes next.
Surprising them
got us this far.
[LU YAN] Its effects
have worn off now, though.
The rest of our fight will be...
...pure force against force!
Be careful!
These guys are all
exceptionally good!
[yelling]
Form five-man squads!
We can't!
Sir, look!
[SOLDIERS choking]
[YUAN] Qiang Lei!
We...
...just have to do it!
Fei Xin Force,
let's follow our commander!
[NARRATOR]
At this point in time,
Qin's left force's battle
had become one sided.
[NARRATOR] The Qin soldiers
fleeing for the rear
amidst the storm of arrows
were harshly shot from the back
by the Zhao mop-up brigade.
Though the 1,500 men
in Gan Yang's and Bi's units
escaped them
by advancing forward,
most of Qin's
left force was slain
by this attack from behind.
The remaining force is a
third of its original number.
Zhao's soldiers picked off
the survivors at their leisure.
Nevertheless, Wang Yi
made no move at all.
[WEI DAO] Darn!
The enemy
is just too strong!
[WEI PING] Not to mention
we're exhausted.
My mind's getting fuzzy!
[WEI DAO] Everything's blurry...
I feel like I could pass out.
[WEI PING]
But... But still...
[gasp]
[yelling]
[WEI DAO] Every time he cuts
somebody down, my energy rises!
[WEI DAO] Each time our leader
slashes apart an enemy...
[yelling]
[WEI DAO] ...my body brims
with power again!
What's up with these guys?
So wonder boy there,
is he really the
squadron's leader, then?
And the amazing thing is
he's propping up the
morale of his whole unit.
But we are the elite guard,
and they absolutely
cannot defeat us
on fighting spirit alone!
That's right.
If they stay in this
war of attrition,
they'll eventually
be worn down to nothing.
Therefore, they're
no threat to our victory!
[XIN] Onward! Onward! Onward!
[XIN] Damn... we're getting
nowhere like this!
[XIN] But what else do we do?!
[LU YAN] Lieutenant!
[YUAN] What is it, Lu Yan?!
[LU YAN] We won't accomplish
anything like this!
I know that!
But if we don't crush
the enemy right here...
[LU YAN] Hence my suggestion.
Y-You're right,
that's our chance.
[YUAN] Xin, Sir! Pardon!
What was that?
We're in the middle of a battle!
[YUAN] My apologies, Sir!
I need to speak with you!
[XIN] Split up the squadron?!
[YUAN] That's right.
If we keep fighting
this war of attrition,
we'll run out of strength,
and we will never
make it past them.
So we should act now
and split up the squadron,
putting all our best men
all on one single team.
We ought to send the
elite team after General Feng Ji
and have the other soldiers
hold these enemies' attention
over here.
"Hold these enemies'"...
Wait a second!
If we do that, the guys who
stay here will surely all die!
But that's fine!
What'd you say?!
[YUAN]
The Fei Xin Force's mission
isn't to kill the enemies here,
or to bring all one hundred
of us back alive!
It's to slay General
Feng Ji of Zhao!
As long as we manage that, the
Fei Xin Force will be victorious
even if few survive it!
We will all happily stay here
if it lays the foundation
for that victory!
"We will all"?!
I am staying.
And the men who
are fighting here
will need a leader to
motivate them, after all.
Yuan...
Xin!
Lieutenant Yuan is quite right.
Please go, don't trouble
yourself about us.
[XIN] But Ze Gui!
[ZE GUI]
You said it yourself, Xin:
This is a battle
we cannot afford to lose!
And many of us are close to
our limits, including me, too.
Once the elite team
gets through,
we'll have no more
business here.
The rest of us will desert
this place by then, as well.
Even we can handle a mission
where all we have to do is run,
so please go!
But Ze...
[YUAN] That's bravado.
[YUAN] Escaping an enemy
formation like this is not easy.
But since it's Xin's
former commander telling him,
now Xin can go! Free!
[XIN]
Squads who can still run...
Pei Lang! Tian Yong!
Squads who can still fight...
Zhong Tie! Qu Hai!
Long You! Bang!
Squads who aren't
out of energy yet!
Tian You! Long Chuan!
Wei Ping! Wei Dao!
Bring whichever of
your men who can fight
and come with me immediately!
You want to split up
the squadron then?
[WEI DAO] It's the right call.
It's our only choice!
[XIN] Qiang Lei!
Where is Qiang Lei?!
[XIN] Yuan!
[YUAN] Sir!
No matter what, once
we're gone, you get away clean!
We will meet up again later!
And you'll see Feng Ji's face!
Good fortune!
You, too.
Here we go!
[ELITE GUARD 28A] You're not
going anywhere, you Qin dogs!
Oh, yes they are!
[SHAN HE] You guys better bring
us the general's head here!
[PEI LANG] You bet we will!
[ELITE GUARD 28B] Captain!
Feng Ji!
[WANG YI] Just as sword-fighting
is a matter of distances,
so is command.
Each commander specializes in
a particular fighting distance.
Within that range,
the commander's talents
are displayed to their fullest.
Feng Ji's specialty is
mid to long-range battle,
is it not?
[TENG] It appears so, Sir.
Yes. That battle is
outside of his range.
Am I correct in saying so?
[chuckles]
Yes. It's too close.
I am counting
on you, young Xin--
My flying arrow.
[FENG JI] What of the
squadron that attacked us?
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
We're still engaging them, Sir,
but I see half their
original number now.
It's over now.
Yes, Sir.
[XIN] So that's the
general's camp, huh?
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
I-Impossible!
Was the elite guard
breached or what?!
No, they're engaged
with the enemy!
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
What does this mean?!
[FENG JI] I see they divided
their squadron in two
and sacrificed half
their men's lives to come here.
It's his camp.
We finally made it here!
Time for murder.
Qiang Lei,
how many are there?
Two or three hundred.
Thirty against three hundred?
[PEI LANG] Don't worry.
150 of them are
between us and Feng Ji,
lined up in ten
fifteen-man ranks.
If we fight our way
ten men deep,
we have the general's head.
All right!
We can handle that!
Yeah!
[XIN] Okay.
Hold out Yuan and the others.
And say your prayers, Feng Ji!
Here we go, everyone!
General Wang Yi said
this was the first stage's
most critical fight!
We're gonna end
this one personally!
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
They're charging.
Do they really think they
can make it all the way here?
Or do they just want to die
in a blaze of glory?
They'll make it.
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT] Sir?
I said they'll
make it over here.
[SHOU] I can't believe
they'd come at our main camp
with only thirty men!
[SHOU] Infantry men, ready!
They're late for their date
with death, so kill them!
[FENG JI] There are times,
though, few and far between,
when in war, people
have superhuman strength.
The more theoretical a general,
the easier it can be
for such things to throw him.
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
Huh?
[FENG JI] This is the
first time an enemy has ever
closed in on me to this degree.
But the occasional battle like
this makes for a nice change.
[ZHAO SOLDIER 28I]
What are you doing?!
Don't let them through!
[ZHAO SOLDIER 28J] Stop them!
Out of my way!
I'll send them straight
to hell myself right now!
[ZHAO SOLIDER 28I] Lord Shou!
[yelling]
[SHOU] You little brat!
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT] Zhao Jue
and Gao Force to the front!
You have a cavalry!
Why can't you stop
a measly thirty people?!
Take them down now!
They may be a
mere few dozen men,
but riding that much momentum,
they're unstoppable now,
aren't they?
Feng Ji's camp,
primarily cavalry,
is working against him, too.
[WANG YI] A cavalry's
strength is in motion.
When densely
packed in and still,
it displays
no power whatsoever.
Will Feng Ji the
tactician devise a plan,
now, you think?
I doubt it.
Cornered at such close range,
one doesn't have time
to devise any plans.
[WANG YI]
Especially not Feng Ji.
Yes, he showed brilliant skill
in halving Qin's left force,
but at the cost of letting
the Fei Xin Force
get deep into his territory.
[WANG YI] For Feng Ji who is
inexpert at close-range battle,
that failure to notice
the Fei Xin Force
did irreparable damage.
Are we nearing
checkmate then, Sir?
[WANG YI]
Interesting question...
There is one way Feng Ji
can still recover
from this mess.
[XIN] Okay, we're through!
We're through!
We're... through?
[WANG YI] The one and only way
Feng Ji can possibly recover...
[WANG YI] ...is to
regain his distance.
[WEI PING]
You... You're kidding...
H-He's supposed to be a general,
and he's got 150 men...
But he's running away
from thirty of us?!
How does that make sense?
Stop now. This is enough.
[FENG JI'S LIEUTENANT]
Halt, men!
[WANG YI] Well played.
In one move, young Xin
is cast into the jaws of death.
If he deploys cavalry
from that distance,
our foot soldiers
will then be helpless.
[WANG YI] Yes, quite...
[laughs]
It's bad! They're coming
from front and back!
[TIAN YOU] What? Now?
[XIN] Damn, we're totally stuck.
We gotta get out quick...
But...
[XIN] Maybe Qiang Lei and I
could manage somehow, but...
[XIN] ...these guys can't!
G-Go then, Xin.
You and Qiang Lei could
get through, maybe... so...
Go!
What are you saying?!
If you keep
kidding around, I'll--
I'm not kidding!
I'm telling you to go,
you stupid jerk!
You know you
can't die here with us!
You're gonna be the world's
greatest general, aren't you?!
[XIN] Forget it.
Xin! If you stay,
it's all over! Get going!
How can I?
I'm sorry, Qiang Lei.
Don't apologize.
It is not over yet.
Wh-What's that?!
General Feng Ji! Straight ahead!
[WEI PING]
It's our left force...
Our cavalry is coming through
Zhao's defensive wall!
[ZHONG TIE] Forty... fifty...
More keep coming!
It's Gan Yang!
You know him?
[XIN] He's one of General
Wang Yi's inner circles.
I bet he's the
left force's commander!
We've come for
your head, Feng Ji.
What impudence.
Call half the right flank!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What is it now?!
Support Gan Yang's unit!
Keep the enemy infantry away
from them and from Feng Ji!
Even my man Bi...
[GAN YANG] All troops charge!
They broke through at last.
[WANG YI chuckling]
We're all going, too!
[yelling]
It turned out just like
the general said, Xin!
He told us at the start, when
the left force fought the enemy!
He said to benefit from the
confusion to get Feng Ji's head!
[WEI DAO]
This is the moment he meant!
Don't match
your speed to ours!
Just ride at full speed
and then just go get his head!
Wei Dao...
[WEI DAO] Get moving! You have
to be the one to take it, Xin!
Got it.
His head will be mine!
[XIN] But listen up, you guys!
I will get the credit,
but we will all be
splitting the reward!
Alive or dead,
all one hundred of us here
get the exact same cut!
Go then!
[yelling]
[QIANG LEI] Xin.
[XIN] What?
When we're close to the general,
go for the small opening.
There will be a chance.
Don't let it pass by.
Yeah, I know.
[QIANG LEI]
"Comrades", huh?
[FENG JI] Why does the
general of their left force
look so triumphant?
Does he think
he's cornered me?
My strategies are flawless.
Still, there will be a slight
margin of error,
even in the most
flawless plan.
[FENG JI]
That's the nature of warfare.
They simply got lucky
in that those tiny errors
stacked up to their advantage.
[FENG JI] Lucky?
No, it's too hard to swallow.
Would I allow enemies to get
within striking distance
by sheer luck?
Does this mean there was
a fault in my strategy?
[FENG JI] It's him.
That little unit that
attacked from the side--
They broke my camp.
[FENG JI] But in a war strategy
with thousands fighting
on each side,
a steady advance by
a hundred-man squadron
falls within
the margin of error.
It was coincidence that
let them reach my camp
in the first place.
If I hadn't advanced both flanks
to wipe out Qin's left force,
they could have
never made it in.
[gasps]
[FENG JI] Was the squadron
sent after me
because both flanks
would advance?
I was manipulated
into advancing them?!
That man ordered
10,000 of his troops
to charge me
just so I would do it!
[FENG JI] The squadron's
charge wasn't a coincidence.
I played into his hands
with my very first move!
Feng Ji's love of strategy
was his downfall,
wasn't it, Sir?
He wasn't attentive enough
to carry off truly
magnificent moves.
Feng Ji loves to dominate.
But one must give thought
to the opposite role, too.
[TENG] The way you
manipulated that arena
without taking command
was genius, Sir.
[WANG YI chuckles]
Well I'm surprisingly fond of
long-range battles myself,
as you can see.
I'm pulling back!
General?!
I don't care
for their removal.
You join the defensive wall
and clean this yourselves.
I'm taking the
soldiers in the rear
and withdrawing
to the woods for now.
Yes, Sir!
It's over now, Feng Ji!
You'll need a lot more
practice before you show off
your schemes to my master.
Ridiculous!
You're the ones done in
by your own scheming!
The fact that only few
of you made it here is proof!
[FENG JI] I'll kill you,
kill all your survivors,
and consign your entire
left force to hell!
No, I don't think
you will be able to.
Your time's up.
No, your time has run out!
Kill that man right now!
Feng Ji.
My master's flying arrow...
...is about to strike home.
[yelling]
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[XIN] I... I got him...
[DIAO] Li Bai's men
are changing formations!
[NARRATOR] All is now in place.
The strongest man
shall devour the battlefield!
Next Time: "The Tides
Of War Suddenly Turn."