[FU HUSHEN] Gong Yuan,
we meet at last.
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife raged
across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Your Highness,
I just received a report.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Our forces led
by Lord Biao are still engaged
in battle on the She Gan Plain
with the Wei forces
led by General Wu Qing.
However...
Not only were many
of our men lost
in an attack by
Wei's chariot squadron,
but Wei has also
made camp on the hills.
Our forces are
now in dire straits.
I see.
[DIAO] "Dire straits"?
Does that mean...?
[DIAO] You're okay, right, Xin?
You're gonna get glory
and come back home?
[ZHENG] If you lose this
battle, you won't carve
a path to the Middle
Kingdom's unification.
I'm counting on you!
[GONG YUAN] I see, then...
So you have made
your way over here
through a series of amazing
miracles, I understand.
[GONG YUAN] How meaningless.
Miracles are when the powerless
happen to come across good luck.
It's because you rely on them
that thousands of your
soldiers die dogs' deaths.
You stupid fool!
Take that back!
[FU HUSHEN]
They are not dogs' deaths.
[XIN] Huh?
[FU HUSHEN]
Every single one of our dead
served to build the bridge
that I made my way here on!
[GONG YUAN] Ha! The
sacrifices of your comrades?
Men who bring touching stories
like that into war
are the sort I hate
the most of all.
Battalion commander of Qin...
Your faith in miracles doesn't
change that you got this far.
Still, what good
does it do you?
You'll change nothing...
unless you kill me
and take this hill over us.
[GONG YUAN] Which you can't,
and that means all
you have achieved...
...is a dog's death!
[FU HUSHEN grunts]
Commander Fu Hushen!
Did you really believe
that I was merely a tactician?
I am a warrior who once
ravaged the front lines
with the great Wu Qing!
[FU HUSHEN]
You call yourself a warrior?
I'm already a dead man.
I can't even see properly,
yet you feel the need to
run me through with a sword?
So then, Gong Yuan,
is my power now
just a mere miracle too?
If that is what you think,
your army stands no chance
against Lord Biao.
Gong Yuan, second-in-command...
[FU HUSHEN] Your life is mine!
[XIN gasps]
[FU HUSHEN chuckles]
[QIN SOLDIER]
Commander Fu Hushen!
[WEI SOLDIER]
General Gong Yuan!
[XIN growls]
[XIN yells]
[QIN SOLDIERS yell
[WEI PING gasps]
[grunting]
[WEI SOLDIER 20A]
Who the hell is this kid?!
[WEI SOLDIERS yell]
Qiang Lei's something else...
Yeah. With that skill,
he might be able to
slay all Wei's soldiers...
[grunting]
[WEI PING gasps]
[QIANG LEI] I'm out of breath.
[QIANG LEI]
Guard the rear until I get back.
[WEI PING &amp; WEI DAO]
What?!
[WEI SOLDIERS] Now!
[ZE GUI whimpers]
That's how it is.
[SUBORDINATE 20A]
Commander, we've killed most
of the Wei soldiers, and the
rest of them have fled now.
Our unit has overpowered
Gong Yuan's encampments
successfully, Sir!
[SUBORDINATE 20C] However, the
defensive corps we broke through
on our way here is closing in.
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
We have less than ten men
to face a force
of over one thousand.
[SUBORDINATE 20A] I hate
to say that we should withdraw.
We'll oust Wei's flag
and bring Gong Yuan's head!
[XIN] Don't be stupid!
[BOTH] Huh?
If you jerks want
to leave, go ahead.
I'm gonna stay here
and fight them!
How dare you, brat?!
[SUBORDINATE 20B] Know your
place, you foot soldier!
The commander said he made it
here 'cause of our men's losses,
meaning they died
to take this hill!
Look around!
Their deaths won't be in vain,
I'm telling you!
I'm not just gonna let it go
for some little pathetic
thousand-man unit. I refuse!
Are you a fool?!
They're a thousand!
[FU HUSHEN laughs weakly]
[SUBORDINATES gasp]
Your name, little boy...?
It's Xin.
Xin...
Listen, Xin. Fear and
recklessness are different.
If you confuse the two,
you'll die early and
leave nothing behind.
[FU HUSHEN] Withdraw from the
hill with everyone else.
That's an order!
[XIN growls]
[GONG YUAN coughs]
You are a true fool.
[SUBORDINATES gasp]
Do you really think you can make
it down from this hill alive?
Don't shame yourself with lies!
We know there are no guards
on the far side
of the hill for certain!
We'll stroll to the bottom,
and take your head with us!
All you people understand
nothing whatsoever...
We'll slaughter all Qin's men
just like at Wan Castle.
You're ours!
[SUBORDINATES gasp]
[XIN gasps]
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
What is it, kid?!
[XIN gasps]
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
I can't believe it!
[SUBORDINATE 20A]
It's a massive force!
That hill further back!
[SUBORDINATE 20B] I'm sure Wei's
main force made camp there,
but there's no soldiers!
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
Which means the man himself
has made his move.
Wei's commanding
general, Wu Qing!
[XIN] That place
with all the big flags...
[XIN] That's Wei's
chief general?
That is exactly right, boy.
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
That is Wei's great general...
[SUBORDINATE 20B] ...Wu Qing!
Wei's great general...
I wanna fight him!
[SHANG LU]
What is Lord Biao thinking?
I don't understand!
We will not last long
if we keep on like this!
Commander Shang Lu!
The flag of Wei
atop the hill has fallen!
Say what?
Looks like Fu Hushen
has made it to the top.
[SUBORDINATE 20D]
Commander! A red messenger!
[SHANG LU] An emergency
order from the General?
What is it now?!
[RED MESSENGER 20A]
Attention, First, Second,
and Fourth Armies!
Ascend the hill and
form a battle array!
I repeat: All forces ascend
the hill and form an array!
That is crazy. They are almost
crushing us as it is!
We cannot get even
near the hill
at the rate we are going at!
Right, Bi?
What is wrong, Bi?
You're looking the wrong way.
[BI] What does this mean?
[BI] What are
you doing here now...
[BI] ...General Wang Yi?!
Hey, Bi!
It looks like we might as well
go and take the hill, too.
Wait, Shang Lu!
General Wang Yi is here...
Something is about to happen!
[WANG YI giggles]
Lord Biao's battle style
is as rough as ever.
Isn't that right?
Yes. But that is exactly what
makes him a fearsome general.
[WANG YI]
In which case, Wu Qing...
That hill seems to command
a better view than this one.
Wouldn't you agree, Teng?
Yes, you are quite right.
However, my lord,
it's a crime to join a
battle without permission.
Unfortunately, I'm afraid
this is the closest we can get.
No one made any
mention of joining them.
I quite simply really fancy
climbing that hill myself.
Though I'll eliminate anyone
who happens to get in my way.
A flawless excuse,
and as usual, my lord.
[WANG YI] Well, then...
[BOTH gasp]
[SHANG LU] They are racing
down a slope that steep?!
Which cavalry is that?!
That's General Wang Yi
accompanied by his
personal soldiers.
What?! General Wang Yi?
That is crazy! I thought
he retired years ago!
General Wang Yi!
[gasping]
[SHANG LU] Then the...
Strange Bird of Qin
has taken to... to the
battlefield again?!
Battalion! Follow our
new reinforcements! Ride hard!
That goes for the
Shang Lu Battalion, too!
Let's go!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Ugh, Commander, let us
decend on the opposite side
of Wu Qing's main force.
[SUBORDINATE 20C] We'll have to
battle the defensive force
midway down. Bear with us.
[FU HUSHEN] Fools.
Just leave me here.
[SUBORDINATE 20B]
We can't leave you in a place
we know the enemy will come!
If you must go, Sir,
let it be on our shoulders.
I'll lend my shoulder--
No, you'll take this!
This is the enemy
general's head, isn't it?
Right.
It's proof of the Fu Hushen
Battalion's achievement.
Do whatever it takes to
bring this to the Qin camp!
Failure is not an option.
[XIN] Am I the right choice?
This is a direct order
from the Commander,
and we have no objections!
I'll see to it.
Okay! Now let's
get down this hill!
Going down's easier
than climbing up!
[SUBORDINATE 20A gasps]
--Huh...?
--[WANG YI] Leaving so soon?
Who--?!
And here things
are just starting
to grow more interesting...
[WANG YI giggles]
[XIN gasps]
[WEI DAO] My legs
can't take it anymore!
[ZEGUI] They'll overtake
us... at this pace!
[WEI PING] It's all over!
Th-The cavalry?
We're saved...
Everyone, look over there now!
[gasping]
We did it...
We finally did it.
We managed to...
take Wei's hill!
Our flag now
stands atop the hill
that Gong Yuan
was holding before!
It was your valor that
blazed this path for us!
[SUBORDINATES sobbing]
That fool...
[BI] I have the feeling that I
had more to learn from you...
[BI] I regret to
see you go, Fu Hushen.
[XIN] Who...
Who the heck is this guy?!
[XIN] From the way
everyone's acting,
I guess he's not
an enemy, but...
[XIN] ...he doesn't feel
like an ally, either.
I don't know!
He's too strong,
and too intimidating...
[XIN] I just don't know
what to think!
[XIN growls]
[WANG YI] Ah, so are you
in fact the child
that Lord Changwen
spoke of before to me?
I recall your name is... Xin.
Are you... one of
old Changwen's comrades?
Not so much his comrade...
[WANG YI chuckles]
...as his lover.
[XIN gasps]
[WANG YI giggles]
Just a joke.
A Wang joke.
I suppose this
explains it all.
You stood out even from afar.
[XIN groans]
[WANG YI] However, if you're
the child Lord Changwen meant,
that changes things
ever so slightly.
[XIN] Huh...?
To put it plainly, you are a
terrible disappointment to me.
[XIN growls]
[XIN] 'Scuse me, old man?
Are you calling me weak?
Indeed I am.
[XIN growls]
[XIN] How about you fight me
and find out, fat-lipped giant?!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[WANG YI giggles]
"Fat-lipped giant".
A nice turn of phrase.
I warn you, every last person
who wields a sword at me
is cut in two by this
treasured blade I have.
Are you fully prepared
for that, child?
Like one that big
could touch me!
I'm crazy fast. You don't know!
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] See,
it's things like that.
Your enthusiasm is
getting the better of you.
Do you realize that you've
been standing at death's door
all this time?
Why, you--!
Don't lose your head, Xin!
[XIN grunts]
[XIN growls]
[XIN] Bi!
Now is the time to battle Wei's
forces with all our strength!
It is no time to be waving your
sword at anyone you come across!
[XIN growls]
[WEI PING] Xin, you're okay?!
[WEI DAO] Thank heaven!
[WEI PING whines]
[WEI PING] You did a
fine job just surviving!
You, too. You're all okay?
[WEI PING sobs]
Where's Qiang Lei?
Well, the truth is
that Qiang Lei...
[QIANG LEI] ...is right here.
[WEI DAO] Qiang Lei!
When did you get here?
[WEI PING] More importantly,
where have you been?
[XIN] Hah!
General Wang Yi, we are
grateful for your aid.
It must be divine providence
that brought you all the way
here to us in our hour of need.
I feel it only right
to put you, a general,
in command of the troops
that are on this hill.
[BI] Please, lead us,
lead our armies
in an immediate charge
against the Wei forces!
With our new geographical
advantage and our men
led by the great
General Wang Yi,
I am certain we can win!
[XIN growls]
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] I see you're as
earnest as ever, Lieutenant Bi.
But I'm afraid we
didn't come down here
as your reinforcements, however.
[BI gasps]
[WANG YI] We quite simply only
wanted to come up to this hill.
Right, Teng?
Yes. The view is
excellent, my lord.
[WANG YI] And so, Lieutenant,
you said you were
rather certain of a win.
You seem to be taking General
Wu Qing a bit too lightly.
Nine fold Spear Walls!
[WANG YI] There, you see?
[SOLDIERS gasping]
He observed us and then
promptly changed his
formation accordingly.
He senses the smallest
changes in a war.
His movements are bold.
He is absolutely
the best strategist
in all of Wei by far,
I understand.
On top of that, he has the
valor to lead from the front
as he demonstrated
at Wan Castle.
Make no mistake.
General Wu Qing of Wei
is a master general
who will pose a
threat to all nations.
Oh, no!
If they've got lots troops
and their general's amazing...
[WEI PING growls]
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] Oh, the numbers
are irrelevant.
This has never been
that sort of battle.
It's hung on the
general's fighting styles.
[XIN gasps]
[horse whinnies]
[WANG YI] I believe that there
are two types of generals.
On one hand, you have the
clever type like Wu Qing.
On the other, you have
the instinctive type
who fights on feral intuition.
[WANG YI chuckles]
Would you like to
make a bet with me,
young Xin, about this?
Will cleverness win,
or will instinct win?
[XIN] Instinct?
[WANG YI] I mean, the Qin
armies' commanding general,
of course, Lord Biao, naturally.
[XIN] So you're saying
you want to make a bet
on who's going to win?
Our leader or... Wei's leader?
[WANG YI] Precisely.
[XIN growls]
[BI] General, I must ask you
to stop this jesting!
[WANG YI] "Jesting!"
Oh, how you wound me.
The question of
cleverness versus instinct
is the eternal debate
of generals.
[XIN] The debate of generals?
[BI] Even so, General,
now is the time for us
to consider how we will
slay the enemies below!
It is certainly not the time
to dissect Lord Biao,
who is not even here
presently with us!
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI]
Are you so sure of that?
[SHANG LU] Bi!
A part of Qin's cavalry is
circling this hill right now
at an all-out gallop!
I've just noticed it myself!
[BI gasps]
[SHANG LU] Lord Biao
is commanding them!
[BI] Say what?!
[XIN] Where?!
[XIN] I can tell with one look.
That man is Lord Biao.
Our highest officer is
leading the charge...
He plans to charge straight
into that Wei army!
[WANG YI giggles]
It seems Lord Biao has
not changed whatsoever.
He is still reliably
the exact same.
For in the end,
he has to make sure he's right
in the thick of the flames.
[WANG YI] He's expanded
his army over these long wars,
and now he fights with
tens of thousands.
[WANG YI] But the larger an army
grows,
the more its battles are swayed
by the talent and
strength of its general.
[XIN gasps]
In the end, wars
belong to the generals.
Lord Biao?
Surprise attacks do not
work on Wu Qing's army.
[WANG YI] Wu Qing has
changed formations once again.
A stance meant to take
Lord Biao's charge
head-on and stop it.
[XIN gasps]
[WANG YI] Wu Qing thinks of
war as logical reasoning
like in a board game.
Lord Biao's battle,
on the other hand,
is a great raging bonfire.
He could never
let this moment
when flames leap
their highest slip past him.
You can't understand that?
[WANG YI giggles]
Wu Qing cannot understand
Lord Biao's way of battling.
However, Lord Biao
has not seen through
all of his tactics, either,
I'm afraid to say.
Who is right...
and who is wrong?
We can't say for certain until
one of their heads rolls,
now, can we?
[XIN] I have been talkin'
to a real general?!
[NARRATOR]
Xin sees the future there.
And he learns the
true weight of his goal.
Next Time: "The Meaning
of a General."