[LAN KAI roars]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[BI gasps]
Commander!
[LAN KAI roaring]
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war,
hatred, and strife
raged across the land,
]
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling]
[PIAO] Xin... Xin!
[XIN grunts]
Huh...?
Piao?
[PIAO laughs]
Are you conscious now?
Say what?
Ah... I got hit
on the head real bad...
Now we're tied again.
Oh, crap!
Look there, Xin.
[PIAO] A dead body.
A Vermilion Slayer,
I recall...
Now I did this.
Another guy finished him,
but he would've died from
the wounds I caused anyway.
Hey, I took out your killer!
But it's not over; now
I'll take down the real--
The Vermilion Slayer's
enough revenge.
[XIN] What?
The future is not supposed
to be about all that, Xin.
[XIN gasps]
[XIN] Piao, where are you going?
Piao, wait for me!
[ZHENG] Piao?
Huh...?
[XIN] Zheng?!
What's up, Xin?
[ZHENG] How long
do you mean to lie there?
[XIN] Shut up.
My entire body's a wreck;
I can't move.
The world's greatest general
would be surprised to hear that.
[XIN] Uh... What'd you say?
I'll knock you out!
[ZHENG] If that rankles,
then get on your feet.
[XIN] I told you, even if
I wanted to move, my body's...
Xin...
[LAN KAI roars]
Insane...
He's lost his will to fight,
but at a word from Cheng Jiao...
[CHENG JIAO] "A baby
of a rare breed of simian
I've never seen."
So the black-marketeer said
when he was selling Lan Kai.
At first I kept him as a pet
to amuse myself,
but lo and behold,
in just a few years,
he grew into this monster.
[CHENG JIAO] Thanks to
my careful training,
this creature does anything
I say since infancy.
Anything!
[CHENG JIAO laughs]
[DIAO gasps]
What the--?!
Where do you get off
talking like that?!
[CHENG JIAO] Hmm?
At Heibei, I saw a
real rogues' gallery,
but there wasn't
anyone as low as you!
[CHENG JIAO laughs]
A little dung-beetle
is chirping.
Hey, insect, don't spew out
any more of your foul breath.
You'll pollute the
Royal Court.
Commoners are vulgar creatures:
stupid and selfish,
devoted to cheating,
murdering, stealing,
and climbing over everyone else.
A kingdom is naturally made up
of the rulers and ruled ones
as you can see.
When you worms are
brought lower,
we're raised up,
the kingdom prospers,
and stability is achieved.
All you worms need
to do is grovel before us.
That's the proper role
for the ruled.
Our duty is to keep
our bloodlines rock-solid,
rise to loftier heights,
and build a robust kingdom.
But Zheng tossed ME,
of purer royal lineage aside
and ascended to the
Jeweled Throne.
That's why I've
removed him!
[XIN grunts]
[CHENG JIAO] The
successor of royalty
must be the one who
fits to BE royalty!
[CHENG JIAO] This is...
A MATTER OF STATE!
[XIN grunts]
Have you any rebuttal
then, you little brat?!
[DIAO gasps]
[XIN] What are you calling...
a "matter of state"?
[DIAO] Xin!
[XIN grunts]
What's this little worm?
You're still alive, I see.
[XIN grunts]
I'm alive and kicking.
[XIN] Cheng Jiao, you
jumped on Lü Buwei's absence,
assailed Zheng and
stole the Jeweled Throne.
Cheating, murdering, stealing...
you're exactly the ignoble sort
you just described!
Any pure and true royal
would be shocked to hear you
talk about bloodline this,
bloodline that,
but the truth is, it's
just a grudge
since Zheng took the
reign from you!
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
You speak nonsense,
ignoble fool!
Eliminating Zheng put the
kingdom back to right!
I don't follow all this
exasperating talk you spew!
What I do understand
quite clearly...
is that no matter how
grandly you talk,
not a single man will risk
his life to protect you!
[COURTIERS gasp]
[XIN] In the end, the
only one who obeys you,
is a single know-nothing ape!
I find you extremely repulsive!
The barking of a mere
feckless dog, lord Cheng Jiao!
[CHENG JIAO growls]
Someone bring them
over to me.
The King shall behead
them himself!
Oh. Bu-But he does
have a sword, my lord!
[CHENG JIAO] He's a fool who
doesn't even know when to die.
Or would you all...
like to be feed for
Lan Kai then?
[JIE SHI] It is my lord Cheng
Jiao's command.
Capture those men immediately!
Heh...
[gasping, yelling]
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[COURTIERS whimpering]
[COURTIER 14B] My eyes!
[COURTIER 14C] What happened?!
[COURTIERS screaming]
Well, it's time for you
to move, Cheng Jiao.
Zheng's outside and
he's quite angry!
I'm not done yet!
[SOLDIER 14B rasps]
[SOLDIER 14A yells]
My King...
forgive me...
[ZHENG yells]
[slicing, grunting]
Du Ji, Fu Ji!
Guard the King of Qin!
The unthinkable mustn't happen!
[DU JI &amp; FU JI] Yes!
The rear is yours, La Mau Ji.
[LA MAU JI] Yes!
[grunting]
[LORD CHANGWEN] My odds
aren't good fighting on foot.
Hey, Lord Changwen!
[yelling]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Even if we keep
Wei Xing at bay, we'll lose.
With this numerical
disadvantage,
the morale the King inspires
is about to reach its limit.
[LORD CHANGWEN] There's no time.
Hurry up, Xin!
[DIAO screams]
Careful!
[grunting]
[XIN] You're in my way!
Stay clear now!
Where's "clear" supposed to be?!
This ape-thing is
rampaging all over!
[XIN yells]
[LAN KAI roars]
[XIN gasps]
Ah, darn it!
It's no use.
What is it MADE of?!
[LAN KAI roars]
[XIN shouts]
[XIN grunts]
[CHENG JIAO chuckles]
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO] Are you okay, Xin?!
[XIN groans]
[XIN] He just did in
one of my ribs a little...
Oww-oww.
Lan Kai!
Finish him now!
[LAN KAI roars]
[XIN] Crap...
What can I do?
That ape's on his last gasp,
but my sword...
I guess a sword won't do it!
[BI] That's not true!
[BOTH] Huh...?
Put more faith in the sword!
But swords haven't worked
against this freak before!
That's only because you're
still too inexperienced!
Say what?!
[BI] The sword is the
strongest weapon,
the product of five
centuries of contention!
Of all the many weapons,
the sword evolved solely from
the single-minded pursuit
of a way to defeat enemies!
It all depends on its user!
That's the essence of
the sword as a weapon!
You ought to understand that!
[XIN] Depends on the user...
[XIN gasps]
[XIN] The edge, the point.
[XIN] I see.
Not bad!
[DIAO] Hey, you're gonna
go with the sword again?
Diao, tie up my right hand
with the scabbard cord.
Huh?
[LAN KAI roars]
By the way Diao, how much?
What kind of reward
are you asking Zheng for
after this is all over?
Huh?
Um, I have not thought
as far as how much.
Why mention it right now?
Say what? You haven't?
Well then, start thinking now!
[DIAO] Huh?
[XIN] Commander!
Keep that big ape still somehow!
[SHUN-MEN grunts]
[XIN] For 10-- No, just count
to 5 and I'll nail him.
[BA JIO] Very well.
Shun-Men!
[LAN KAI roars]
[BA JIO growls]
[LAN KAI yells]
Crush them all, Lan Kai!
[LAN KAI roars]
GET AWAY!
[blow lands]
[BA JIO &amp; SHUN-MEN gasp]
[XIN gasps]
[XIN] Tajifu!
[TAJIFU grunts]
[BA JIO] How is this, boy?!
[XIN growls]
[BI gasps]
[LAN KAI roars]
[XIN] That'll do!
--[DIAO gasps]
--[XIN] It's not the strength...
it's merging with the sword
without the slightest waver...
just straight on...
all into this single point...
[XIN yells]
[LAN KAI screams]
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[XIN] Thrusting through!
[screaming continues]
[XIN grunts]
[TAJIFU retches]
[XIN] If you don't want
to fight, stay down.
[LAN KAI growls]
What?!
Lan Kai, Get up!
Not getting up? You monstrous
ape, stand up and smash...
those insects or
it's punishment!
[LAN KAI whimpers]
[XIN] You think threats are
gonna work now?
He CAN'T get up anymore.
It's over, Cheng Jiao.
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[JIE SHI] Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
[JIE SHI] Ying Zheng, Lord
Changwen, Wang Yi, Yang Duanhe,
the mountain folk,
the commoner brat...
How can they possibly win?
[JIE SHI] It's everything.
If even one element
had been lacking
it wouldn't have gone this way.
One might say they walked
a tight rope to get here...
[JIE SHI] It rankles to kneel in
front of such a churl
as Cheng Jiao...
[JIE SHI] No, the tribulations
of exhausting every means
rising as high as Minister...
My dreams of
killing Lü Buwei,
having the Kingdom of Qin
as mine, have all vanished.
All vanished...
[COURTIERS screaming]
Y-You lot!
Don't flee!
You won't fight?!
Execution!
I'll sentence you all
to execution!
[COURTIER 14D]
What are you doing?! Hurry!
[COURTIER 14F]
Open! Open the door!
[COURTIER 14E] Don't push!
I can't pull on the doors!
[COURTIER 14D] We're finished!
[CHENG JIAO growls]
[JIE SHI]
"Finished" did you say?
No, not finished.
I... I am NOT finished at all!
[COURTIERS grunting]
Clear the way!
Pipe down!
I am NOT finished yet!
If I get out of the palace,
an army of 80,000 awaits!
Open!
Open these doors!
[XIN]
You're really pathetic now.
Huh...?
[CHENG JIAO] You scum...
Are you mere commoners,
thinking of striking ME,
one of the royal blood?!
What else would we be thinking?
Madness!
You moronic boy!
How can you think you will
ever get away with that?
Because I am the King of Qin!
And you will NEVER
get away with this!
We will.
Because it's a war.
[CHENG JIAO gasps]
[JIE SHI growls]
[JIE SHI gasps]
[COURTIERS gasp]
[screaming, whimpering]
Regrettably, sirs, I cannot
allow you to pass from here.
By orders of my lord, I shall
cut down any of you gentlemen
who approaches the doors.
[JIE SHI whimpers]
Wh-Why is Wang Yi's
lieutenant...
No, more importantly...
Don't let Jie Shi escape!
Ending this fight
will require his head!
[BA JIO] Understood.
[JIE SHI] I refuse to die...
I refuse to die...
[BI] Oh no!
Beyond that door is a maze! If
he gets in there,
we'll certainly lose him!
[JIE SHI panting]
Out of the way, worm!
I'll trample you!
Please don't miss, Diao!
[DIAO] Why would I miss?!
[JIE SHI screams]
[JIE SHI] Are you mad?!
Ugh.. I am Minister Jie...
of the Kingdom of Qin!
[BA JIO growls]
[JIE SHI screams]
[XIN gasps]
[BI] It's done.
It's done at long last.
That Jie Shi, whom even
Lü Buwei couldn't slay...
we've killed him!
[COURTIERS scream]
[COURTIER 14H] An-An exit...
[screaming continues]
[COURTIER 14H whimpers]
[COURTIER 14H]
I refuse to die...
[DIAO gasps]
[DIAO grunts]
[XIN gasps]
[BI &amp; XIN] Diao!
Y-YOU!
[CHENG JIAO whimpers]
[BI gasps]
[CHENG JIAO pants]
[BI] Xin! He will get away!
Go after him!
[COURTIER 14H whimpers]
[slicing]
Xin, go after Cheng Jiao!
The guy has nowhere to go now.
[DIAO grunts weakly]
[XIN] He has a pulse.
C'mon, Diao, that big reward
that you've dreamed of
will be yours soon.
An amazing life, different
from one in that village,
is waiting for you now.
Don't you dare die
from this wound.
Bi, my man,
take care of Diao!
Right.
[CHENG JIAO] It's a mistake...
This is surely
some kind of a mistake.
I am Cheng Jiao, King of Qin.
I'm King. I'm King.
I AM THE TRUE KING!
[BI] I am sorry,
I let this happen to you,
my dearest Diao...
Do not die now, Diao...
Dammit, I have to
stop the bleeding...
At least I still have t---
[BI gasps]
[BI laughs]
[BI] A chain hauberk!
[BI] Frankly you kids
are too much.
They're actually
some amazing boys.
[TAJIFU grunts]
It is really fine, Tajifu.
The wound is not deep.
Diao, I will stop the
bleeding for you now.
[BI gasps]
[BI] Diao, you're...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
My lord Cheng Jiao!
Why are you in a place
like this alone?
What happened?
Did something happen
in the Throne Room?!
Please answer!
Why are you here by
yourself, my lord?
What happened to Minister
Jie Shi and the other officials?
The Minister...
was murdered.
What?
What are you saying?!
The Minister could not
have been murdered!
That's impossible!
Who on Earth can possibly...
kill the Minister?
MONKEYS WHO ENTERED
THROUGH THE CORRIDOR!
[SI SHI whimpers]
[SI SHI] This means
they got past Zuo Ci?
That can't be!
My lord Cheng Jiao,
I'll ask once more:
Minister Jie Shi has
lost his life you say?
Might he still
possibly be aliv--
[CHENG JIAO] IS THERE A PERSON
WHO CAN LIVE
WHEN HE'S ONLY A HEAD?!
[SI SHI] Minister Jie is dead...
this means we have been beaten!
[CHENG JIAO grunts]
Si Shi! You're one of
his staff officers!
Won't you do something?!
[SI SHI] Stop this please,
my lord Cheng Jiao.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[LORD CHANGWEN] Cheng Jiao.
Why has he come then...?
It can't be...
[gasping]
[MAN] ♪ Hmm... Hm, hm, hm. ♪
[SI SHI] General Wang Yi...
General Wang Yi!
Did I hear Wang Yi?!
[SI SHI] Wang Yi!
When did HE come to...
Or rather, what's his
purpose of being here?!
[WEI XING] General Wang Yi!
I wish to ask you
only one thing!
Why did you present us
a counterfeit head?!
Surely your answer
must satisfy me;
if not, I'll see you
dead right here.
[WANG YI] Hmph.
[SI SHI] It's now very clear to
me that Wang Yi,
who sent a false head of our
Lord Changwen is our enemy.
Wei Xing, my worthy
right hand,
if it's to be a fight
with Wang Yi's force...
His head is our sole
chance at victory.
Now it's cavalry
against on foot.
There's no possibility
of Wei Xing losing!
Even though your foe is
a general...
Kill him!
[WEI XING yells]
[gasping]
[WEI XING yelling]
[SI SHI] So this is...
[SI SHI] Wang Yi...
[WANG YI] These lowering
clouds threatening rain
without letting it fall, I
don't dislike them at all.
What's your purpose
of being here, Wang Yi?
Does this mean you've
betrayed Cheng Jiao,
and plan to join us now?
[WANG YI giggles]
You're a kidder.
Your too adorable game of
play fighting kept going on,
so I just popped in to
muddy the water a little.
What did you say?
Does your derision
know no bounds?!
[ZHENG] General!
If you have business
here, speak now.
[YANG DUANHE gasps]
[ZHENG] We are busy.
We have not got the time to
be concerned about you.
[WANG YI giggles]
[WANG YI] I simply came
to take your life.
Do you understand?
[WANG YI] What kind of king
does Your Highness
aim to be exactly, then?
[NARRATOR] A young King
staring down the future.
Can he become the light that
brightens a war-torn world?
Next Time: "The
Qualities of a King."