[ZUO CI] You've overestimated
yourselves, you worms.
[BI thinking] S-So this...
this is Zuo Ci!
[BI thinking] What am I doing?
I should set the example
and stand before him,
rally our men's
fighting spirit...
But still...
Even though I...
I know what to do,
my body won't move!
[BI] I can't move!
[XIN] Hey, hey.
Overestimating ourselves?
I think that's more your style,
idiot-face!
[BI thinking] Xin!!
[NARRATOR] Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of war, hatred,
and strife raged
across the land,
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin, the
westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[yelling, fighting sounds]
[shocked sounds]
[ZHENG]
Yooooo!
[YANG DUANHE thinking]
A worthy King of Qin,
heading right into
the thick of the fray?
[MOUNTAIN FOLK 12A]
Don't you sense something?
[YANG DUANHE] Hmm?
Is it Ba Jio?
No. I suspect, it's that boy.
[YANG DUANHE] It seems the
time is ripe over there, too.
[pants]
You're overestimating
yourself, dimwit.
[ZUO CI] Oh?
[gasps]
"Oh?" I'll give you "Oh"!
Yaaaaaaaahh!
Ouch.
[XIN] You're quick, jerkwad...
...and you're dead!
Hyaaaaah!
Who is that kid?
Against Zuo Ci, who finishes
every foe with a single cut...
He's trading blow for blow!
Oh, wow...
Xin. Fight hard.
[BI thinking] Why, Xin?
[BI thinking]
Why is it that you, a boy,
can stand up to Zuo Ci?!
Aren't you terrified?
Where do you draw that
hidden strength from?
You two...
[BI] Lord Piao...
That's right.
Lord Piao took the lead
without blinking, too,
in cutting a swath
through Wang Yi's force.
[XIN] I'm gonna become
the world's greatest general!
[BI gasps]
The world's greatest general?
That's an absurd dream.
[DIAO] Considering
how stupid he is,
he's got huge dreams
and attitude to match.
And him, a commoner,
who didn't even know
how one becomes a general
until just recently.
[XIN] Shut up!
If I say I will
become one, I will!
What's more, this
isn't just my dream!
[ZHENG] It's a rugged road.
Ha! I'll thrive on whatever
kind of path--Whoa!
[ZHENG] I just said
this is a rugged road...
You... don't play
games with me!
The road to a generalship
will be much more rugged.
Heh. Ha!
Well I sure hope so.
And hey, just for the record...
Not just a general,
but I'll be the
world's greatest general!
Don't get it wrong!
[ZHENG] Is that right?
[XIN] Hey, Zheng, you just
mocked me, didn't you?!
Dammit, you just watch!
I will definitely do it!
[BI] You really mean
to achieve that, Xin?!
[BI] If so...
[BI] If you,
a nameless servant boy,
are to become the
greatest of generals...
[XIN] I got you.
That must really sting!
The real fight begins now!
Whoa... Ah...
Well, hey, there!
Lost your concentration?
Are you a bit scared?
[XIN] Wh-What just happened?
I never saw it coming.
Xin!
[BI thinking]
Xin, if you're soaring toward
becoming the
greatest of generals,
the right hand of a King,
who seeks to unify the
entire Middle Kingdom...
[BI thinking] If you are...
Die.
[BI thinking]
I already let one die.
I won't let you kill this boy!
[BI thinking] That was shallow,
but I've cut him twice!
If I take one step closer,
I'll have him!
No, Bi!!
[ZUO CI sighs]
Let's continue, young one.
Your Highness!
Are you all right?!
Pay no mind. This doesn't
even qualify as a scratch.
[SOLDIER 12A] You're too far in.
Your Highness should
be behind the rest of us.
Gaaah!!
[ZHENG] Huh?
Your Highness... prepare to die.
Wei Xing...
[XIN grunts in pain]
You... What you did to Bi...
[XIN thinking] What the...?
Is it 'cuz of that blow
to the head I took?
The sword is about power.
And about speed.
Xin!
[XIN] My strength is...
I, who have attained the
pinnacle of both of them...
...am the mightiest in the land.
[ZUO CI] You, a young one,
dared to wound the flesh
of the great Zuo Ci now?
Tell me, how do you plan
to make this right again, hmm?
That's it. Zuo Ci
has completely snapped.
Of course he has.
After all, he'll cut
someone in two
just for dirtying his clothes.
[ENEMY GUARD 12B] That kid
will be tortured to death now.
He will.
This fight now has
been settled. Let's go.
Kill them all!
Huh?
He's alive!
[DIAO] Bi! Wake up, Bi!
What? Did you
say something?
How's the battle?
Huh?
They're all hard pressed...
...especially Xin.
The battle's terribly one-sided.
Terribly.
But it'll be okay.
I mean, we do
have Xin after all!
[XIN grunts]
[DIAO] No matter
how much he gets torn up,
he won't lose!
No matter how much
he gets torn up...
...he'll always win!
That's the truth, Xin!
Huh?
Die!
Well now, who said
you could squat down?
On your feet, worm!
What's the matter?
Your scheme was to break away
and strike at the
throne room, correct?
If so, then go on!
Defeat me.
What's wrong?
What's the matter, young one?!
C'mon! C'mon! On your feet!
[ZUO CI]
You're done already? Huh?
Xi-Xin... Xin!
[XIN] Finally.
[XIN] You fool,
yammering on and on...
[XIN] I wasn't listening at all,
so say it again for me...
Who's the mightiest
in all the land?
Thanks to your
meaningless jabber,
I've completely recovered now.
So get up.
I'll teach you who's
mightiest in all the land!
[WEI XING thinking]
Oh?
So young and yet, not shrinking
from me mounted before him.
Royalty, but a warrior's
heart resides within?
Or is he a second
coming of King Zhao?
But the time and place
you were born into
are just too harsh!
Forgive me!
What was that?!
[LORD CHANGWEN] For someone who
sits on his horse so arrogantly,
your blows are quite
lightweight, Wei Xing!
Lord Changwen!
[LORD CHANGWEN thinking]
Until the breakaway force
reaches the throne room...
[LORD CHANGWEN thinking]
Until they strike down
Cheng Jiao and Jie Shi...
[ZHENG thinking]
We hold out here at all hazards!
We're counting on you, Xin!
[WANG YI laughs]
Tastefully handled as
always, Lord Changwen.
But, it's too bad
there's one place
where I can't watch from.
Teng, are you here?
Yes. You called, sir?
Would you kindly go see what the
situation is in that corridor?
Hey, someone go
down to the right--
I'm speaking to you, Teng.
But Zuo Ci is the one
supposed to be guarding there.
Won't the breakaway force
already be destroyed?
[WANG YI] If they get
through that corridor,
there's nothing to keep
them from the throne room.
Si Shi likely posted
Zuo Ci there
with the aim of
winning at all costs.
But Lord Changwen
and the King
sent the breakaway force
in full awareness of that.
[gasps]
They are sure of
getting past Zuo Ci?
[WANG YI] Well... setting
questions of confidence aside,
what I'm saying is that without
a shadow of a doubt the person
in whom those two trust
the most is fighting there.
[chuckles]
[ZUO CI] I see. While I was
having my fun, you recovered.
What of it then?
We're merely back
to where we started.
You no longer have a
mask to protect your head,
with my next blow,
I'll spatter what little
brains you have all over.
[XIN thinking]
He's right: one more blow.
With cuts all over,
I've lost too much blood.
I've lost feeling
here and there.
I only have strength left
for a single blow.
But that's enough...
This is not a wooden sword.
[XIN thinking] This is the
sword bequeathed to me by Piao!
[slows down breathing]
[XIN] Watch this, Bi!
[ZUO CI] In speed or in power,
no one can match me whatsoever.
Xin!
[ZUO CI] Huh?
[XIN] Old man,
seems like the blood rose
to your head and
you didn't notice.
After Bi cut you twice,
your speed and your power
are lessened by half.
Now I've made
things right for Bi.
Time to take in
what happened.
[ZUO CI] I, Zuo Ci...
by a punk like this...?
Who are you...?
I am Xin.
[XIN] We did it, Bi.
[BI] Why cry...
...when you've won?
Did someone close
to you die or something?
[XIN] Bi! You're alive?!
[BI] Guess my holding back meant
he wounded me a
little less deeply, too.
[XIN] You stupid jerk!
You scared the heck out of me!
[BA JIO]
The warrior Tajifu says,
"That man is alive.
It is okay."
[XIN] It's too late
to tell me that now!
[everybody laughs]
It would seem
that it's over now.
I just wonder what sort of
person he is in whom the King
and Lord Changwen
have placed their trust.
[chuckles]
[BI] They're all
torn into pieces.
But those two only paid
the ultimate sacrifice
against so many and Zuo Ci
speaks volumes
for the fearsomeness
of the mountain folk.
[XIN] Well, if someone
can just bring down
the commander,
this is how it goes.
[DIAO] More importantly Bi,
shouldn't you be lying down?
[XIN] When we've come this
far he's gonna lie down?
[XIN] Right, Bi, my man?
[BI] Exactly.
[BI] Passing through
this corridor will take us
immediately to the throne room.
In the throne room
is the ringleader of this
whole affair, Cheng Jiao.
[PIAO] Listen, Xin.
I entrust it to you!
[BI] Are you ready
for this, Xin?
Damn right!
[XIN] Now we strike
down Cheng Jiao!
[XIN] Wha-What are you?!
[NARRATOR] Is that
grotesque shape a man,
or a beast?
Swords become powerless.
Next Time: "Lan Kai Roars."