[BI]
They're all torn into pieces.
But those two only paid
the ultimate sacrifice
against so many, and
Zuo Ci speaks volumes
for the fearsomeness
of the mountain folk.
[XIN] Well, if someone can
just bring down the commander,
this is how it goes.
[DIAO] More importantly, Bi,
shouldn't you be lying down?
[XIN] When we've come this far,
he's gonna lie down?
Right, Bi, my man?
Exactly.
[BI] Passing through this
corridor will take us
immediately to
the Throne Room.
In the Throne Room,
is the ringleader
of this whole affair,
Cheng Jiao.
[PIAO] Listen, Xin.
I entrust it to you!
[BI]
Are you ready for this, Xin?
Damn right!
[XIN]
Now we strike down Cheng Jiao!
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five long and
harrowing centuries,
an endless storm of
war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young king
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[LAN KAI grunts]
[COURTIER 13A]
Hm?
Something noisy is
happening outside, I think.
You do not suppose
there's a quarrel
with the mountain folk, do you?
[CHENG JIAO panting]
Unusual for you
to get flustered.
What is it, Jie Shi?
[JIE SHI]
The mountain folk have not come
in order to seal an alliance.
The 50 we admitted
have breached
the Red Turtle Gate
by force of arms,
and are presently battling
300 of Si Shi's troops
in the Gong Long Courtyard.
Say what?
Why, that is--
[JIE SHI] Furthermore, King
Ying Zheng has shown himself
amidst those mountain folk.
The-The King, you say?!
What on earth
is the meaning of this?
King Ying Zheng,
amongst the mountain folk...
Is that possible?
Can it be that
the King's brought
the mountain folk to his side
and has come to take
back the Jeweled Throne?
Do not panic. They will
not make it this far.
[CHENG JIAO laughing]
Is that so? So he
was alive after all?
Ying Zheng... you say
that cut off, isolated,
you come to retake the Court
in the company of base
mountain monkeys?
This crude approach
truly befits you.
But did you think
you could wrest
the Jeweled Throne back from
me with such a feeble force?
You fool. Let death
itself teach you
that you have no
claim to kingship.
I... am King!
[SOLDIERS yelling, grunting]
Hear me, all!
Oh!
His Highness...
[ZHENG] Everyone, don't lose
your will to fight!
Victory is right before you!
Victory, before us?
This is a fight between
Cheng Jiao and me,
and it is also a
fight with Jie Shi,
who's become Cheng Jiao's
protector and plans to rule Qin.
No one besides
them is responsible
for instigating
this foul rebellion.
Stripped of those two,
our opposition
will, without a doubt, collapse!
The Throne Room where those
two are stands now exposed!
It's certain that
our breakaway force
will attack and
strike down those two!
We just need to hold out!
Even if your sword breaks,
even if you lose an arm,
even if all the blood runs
from your veins, hold out!
If we can hold out,
we'll definitely win!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[DIAO]
Hmm... aren't we there yet, Bi?
[BI] A little further.
We're halfway there.
Still only halfway?
[MOUNTAIN FOLK panting]
[DIAO]
Hey, commander...
You should let that guy rest.
He can't go on-- he'll die!
[BA JIO]
He himself is trying to go on.
We will not stop him.
If he dies as a result...
...then so be it.
What are you saying?
Commander, how can you
say such a thing?!
Diao, you know what
Ba Jio is saying, isn't wrong.
Why Bi?
It all depends on this.
Huh?
[BI] The lives of the
King and the others
fighting in the courtyard,
the lives of our 3,000
companions who wait outside...
Victory in this battle depends,
entirely on us,
the breakaway force.
He knows that too, so he's
trying to go on until the moment
his strength gives
out completely.
A little further;
come on now.
[DIAO]
Xin...
[BA JIO] Leave him, boy.
He'll slow us down.
Enough of that.
[BA JIO sighs]
[bells jingling]
[XIN]
So there was this guy, Piao,
and he was an orphan like me.
I was raised with him;
we were just like brothers
I say raised, but actually
we were servants...
[XIN] They say that he
looked just like Zheng,
but I really don't think he did.
[XIN] Piao was so cheerful,
and always smiled.
While Zheng is
dreary by nature...
[XIN laughs]
[XIN] Sounds like there
were a lot of casualties
of this revolt,
and Piao was one of them.
Thinking of it that way,
the place we are all heading
right now is where
the real enemy is.
[XIN] So do you,
have siblings or no?
Well, I guess you
can't talk now...
Hey, look. That's it at last.
Everything must have
started over there.
Xin...
Um, we're falling behind? Right!
Let's speed it up!
[DIAO]
Xin.
That man...
Huh?
[DIAO]
He's... already dead.
[XIN panting]
[XIN yells]
[XIN]
Out of the way!
Who are those guys?
They're not soldiers.
They're attendants
of the Royal Court.
From here on,
everyone's unarmed.
[DIAO] That means the
Throne Room's close?
[BI] It's not only close...
it's right before our eyes.
[XIN growls]
[XIN]
Yah!
[COURTIERS gasp]
It's over... evildoers!
[COURTIERS yelping, gasping]
How did you scumbags
manage to get here?
Did Zuo Ci bungle things?
So you're Cheng Jiao?
I'm surprised.
I thought you would've run
away crying and screaming,
but you look relaxed.
You've made peace
with dying, jerk?
Execution.
[XIN]
Huh?
For the crime of
lowborn riffraff like you
setting foot in the
exalted Royal Court--
Execution.
[CHENG JIAO] For the crime
of you dung-beetles
breathing the air in
the same place as me--
Execution.
[XIN chuckles]
That sounds just about right.
The way you're being
right now, strikes me
as the most "royal" reaction.
I was with him this
whole time, so I'd forgotten.
How dare you
address your King
as simply "you"? Are you
just wrong in the head?
Hey now, the one who's
wrong in the head is you.
Zheng is the King of Qin.
You are no more
than a measly traitor!
Do not expect to
die quickly, little worm.
I'll tear your limbs off
while you're still alive.
Just try it.
[CHENG JIAO cackles]
Lan Kai!
[LAN KAI roars]
[LAN KAI growls, roars]
Wh-What are you?!
[XIN]
It doesn't cut...
[LAN KAI roars]
Xin!
What is he, then?
[BI]
What is he?
Lan Kai is his name.
[WANG YI]
Teng, are you here?
Yes. Here, sir.
Did you go down to the corridor?
Yes, I was just
about to head there.
No need to there.
There's another place I'd
like you to go instead.
[TENG]
Yes, as you wish, sir.
[WANG YI]
I mean right away.
[TENG]
Sir.
[COMMANDER 13A]
It's taking too long.
What on earth is
happening inside?
She said stand by,
but wouldn't it be
better to make a move?
Correct. If we breach the gates
and shut them before that
army of 80,000 comes...
Absolutely.
[bells jingling]
Don't take matters into
your hands, you fools.
If the order is stand by,
then stand by, you fools.
[LAN KAI yells]
If the strength of
Tajifu and the others
can't hurt that thing,
how are we gonna hurt him?
[BA JIO]
Don't lay a hand on him.
Ba Jio... what are
you trying to do?
[BA JIO] I'm reverting to
the past for a moment.
Since these words
come from the elders
of the mountain-folk,
we would like to obey, but--
We have deep
faith in our king.
W-We have faith
in ours, too.
H-However--
Every single one inside
was cleverly handpicked.
The 40 taken were the most
experienced of each tribe,
and leading them all
is the mountain king,
the great Yang Duanhe.
[ELDER A] What's more,
Ba Jio is there too.
[LAN KAI growls]
My, what amazing movement...
The monster is recoiling.
The situation's shifted.
[DIAO]
Amazing, Commander!
Amazing, but scary somehow.
[DIAO]
He's not a human; he's a beast.
Ba Jio... the man Xin
calls "Commander"?
Ba Jio was a
real pitiable boy.
We'd just set out on a campaign
to unify the mountain realm...
[ELDER A] When we split up to
enter the remote northern peaks,
three lookouts vanished.
[ELDER A] Searching nearby
turned up three dead bodies,
all of them brutally damaged
as though ravaged by a beast.
In that land, we still
had an unseen enemy.
We formed a squad of 20,
and had them search the area.
But as the days passed,
not a single one returned.
Feeling an ill foreboding,
we elected to move our
main force to search
for the missing squad of 20.
Soon after we began the search,
we were able to find
the terrible, vicious beast.
And around it were the
savaged husks of the 20 men.
[growling]
[ELDER A] Ba Jio's tribe
had perished in a battle
some years before.
Only he survived.
In living for years
and years all alone
in the mountains, he became
something other than human.
Capturing him was
a real struggle, actually...
[ELDER A chuckles]
[YANG DUANHE] If you
were to remain a beast,
I'll end your
misery here and now.
But if you restate
your humanity
and swear loyalty to me,
we'll take you in as family.
[ELDER A]
At that time, Ba Jio didn't
understand human language.
[ELDER A] But he nonetheless
cried at the top of his lungs.
Then Yang Duanhe welcomed
Ba Jio into our tribe.
[ELDER A] Ba Jio steadily
regained his humanity,
learned language, and
became an able warrior.
But to this day,
the beast of those times
still resides within his soul.
If ever that
beast is released,
it would truly be nothing short
of formidable, to put it mildly.
Whoa...
He's fast...
Incredible.
That monster is
completely at his mercy.
So this is Ba Jio's
truest form.
Way to go, Commander!
[ALL gasp]
The monster is retreating!
[LAN KAI screams]
Lan Kai! He's being
pressed back now!
That monster couldn't
be losing. Am I right?!
He won! Amazing, Commander!
You beat that monstrosity!
What an amazing power...
All that's left is to
strike down Cheng Jiao!
[CHENG JIAO]
Lan Kai!
Who said that you could rest?!
Why do you think I've kept
a freak like you as a pet?
I've taught you this:
The only worth in your existence
comes from you killing people.
Smash them quickly.
If not, you will be punished.
[LAN KAI yells]
Do it! Finish them
off like I said.
[LAN KAI yells]
Commander!
[XIN]
The edge, the point...
I see. Not bad!
[NARRATOR] Every means
has been exhausted.
Not a single one can stand.
Next Time:
The Strength of the Sword