So then... did my lord
give your squadron
an actual name, young boy?
Fei Xin Force.
[GAN YANG]
Xin of the Fei Xin Force
has taken the head of
the Zhao general Feng Ji!
[yelling]
Very well done, Xin.
You truly never
cease to amaze me.
I can't take all the credit.
You're the one who held off
the enemy infantry, Bi.
[YUAN] Sir!
You did it!
You really did it!
[XIN] Hey, the guys are okay!
[XIN] Sorry,
I gotta take a rain check.
I see, then...
You really are a leader now,
aren't you, Xin?
[WANG YI] This is
absolutely not the time
to let your mind
linger in the past.
Do you understand, young Xin?
General Wang Yi.
My goodness.
Your general is here to
personally show appreciation
for all of your efforts today.
Look a little bit happier
about it, won't you?
You're not being very sweet.
[WANG YI chuckles]
Young Xin, do you know
why I even gave your unit
an actual name?
Think about it.
[WANG YI] It was to
make you easier to remember,
for enemies and allies alike.
Enemies?
When you finally killed Feng Ji,
Gan Yang declared the Fei Xin
Force's name and yours loudly.
Feng Ji was a renowned warrior.
As the one who slayed him,
your name will soon be known
to Zhao's armies and
the whole Middle Kingdom.
My name to the
whole Middle Kingdom?
[WANG YI]
However, it's only for a moment!
[laughs]
[XIN] A moment...
My name, even if
just for a moment...
[XIN] Okay, this works.
[XIN] If I keep
making this happen,
my name will leave its mark
all over the Middle Kingdom!
[XIN] That's how
I'm gonna become...
[XIN] ...the world's
greatest general!
[NARRATOR]
The time: The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
The place: Qin.
Xin, a nameless boy,
met Zheng, a young King,
distinguished himself in battle,
and rose to the rank
of squadron commander.
In the midst of this,
the neighboring
kingdom of Zhao invaded,
and Qin faced
unprecedented crisis.
What manner of battle will Wang
Yi wage as commanding general?
And what growth
will Xin accomplish?
[NARRATOR] The war
reached its second day.
Qin's army concentrated
its resources
on the battle in the center.
Today, that battle
would be the focus
and its leading player
would be Meng Wu.
This is the same as yesterday.
Foot soldiers, follow me!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
My, their spirits are high.
Teng, how many casualties
did Meng Wu's army
suffer yesterday?
Well, approximately
six hundred, I'm told.
[WANG YI] Six hundred...
For such a long
and fierce battle,
that seems like a
really small number.
I see, so that's it.
[MENG WU] Meng Wu Army, charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Put the heavy
infantry diagonally.
It has started!
But at this rate...
Sir, will it be
the same as yesterday?
Not quite.
I believe we'll soon see
something very interesting.
[MENG WU] I have heard
of you extensively, Li Bai.
They say defensive battle
is your forte--
That you've never
been defeated.
The Middle Kingdom acknowledges
you as the "Defense General."
[MENG WU] Don't make me laugh!
[MENG WU] You've just been
blessed with weak opponents!
[DIAO] That diagonal formation
had held his force off,
but today they broke through!
What's going on?
Maybe he could have
done so yesterday as well
if he wanted to.
Then he chose
not to break through?
[DIAO] Why?
[TENG] He was training
his infantry?
[WANG YI] Yes.
Most of the Qin foot soldiers
that are in this campaign
were gathered in haste,
meaning that morale
was low and there was
a great gap between them
and Meng Wu's own cavalry.
Men cannot fight as
a single army in that state.
And so...
Yesterday he chose a method
that dodged going in deep
and kept Qin casualties low.
To us it seemed
Li Bai's formation
took the wind
out of his offensive,
but how must it have felt
to his foot soldiers?
[DIAO] Hmm... maybe
like they were the ones
attacking the enemy position
and the enemy was just
standing in place defending...
I get it! The infantry
got their confidence!
Greater confidence
equals higher morale.
Meng Wu's infantry is a
completely different force today
than it was yesterday.
[yelling]
[WANG YI]
Not bad, Meng Wu, not bad.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
But still, it is not enough
to break past Li Bai's
defense, isn't it?
You really need to
show them just how fearsome
your formations are, Li Bai.
We'll use the Snake.
[LI BAI'S LIEUTENANT]
Yes, Sir!
Now what?
Li Bai's men are
changing formations!
[MENG YI] The last
of his diagonal formation
broke sideways
to thicken ranks
at the point of the charge...
[MENG YI] Meanwhile, the top
section made a sharp turn
and blanketed the turf
behind Meng Wu's army.
They are not in
defensive formation.
Li Bai's army means to surround
Meng Wu's and just destroy it.
[WANG YI] Oh, dear. Just when
it looked like you'd make it,
Li Bai turned out
to be a cut above you.
[chuckles]
[WANG YI] You're completely
surrounded now.
What is your next move, Meng Wu?
All troops,
continue the advance!
Now things are
getting interesting.
General, that man...
No matter. Keep going.
A single warrior
can only be so powerful.
[DIAO] It's no good! That way
of fighting can't last long,
no matter how strong
your dad is!
[DIAO] Meng Yi?
This is it.
[MENG YI]
My teacher told me once...
"To defeat a powerful warrior,
devise a strategy.
On a battlefield where
tons of soldiers fight,
strategy is everything.
But for that very
reason sometimes we long
to see the exact opposite."
[MENG YI] You and I
are witnessing that now:
[MENG YI] A warrior's power
outdoing strategy!
That damned monster...
We'll pull back for now!
[LI BAI] Meng Wu, you can
exercise all the power you want,
but it won't get in my head.
[MENG WU]
Bad assumption, Li Bai.
[MENG WU] I don't give
a damn about your fool head.
Meng Wu Army!
Lay them to waste!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WANG YI chuckles]
They may be straggling soldiers
left without a general,
but there are
at least ten thousand.
If he gets rid of them
for us, it will be a big help.
Right, Teng?
Quite.
As the army who needs to shrink
its numerical disadvantage,
this is a great harvest.
[WANG YI]
Meng Wu, the world says
you're a self-satisfied loose
cannon on the battlefield,
but I see the real you is
something quite different.
[WANG YI] Still, I will
watch another battle or two
before I judge your power.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
He forces Li Bai,
known for his strong defense,
to attack Meng Wu, Qin's
strongest offensive warrior.
A tactic not only sensible,
but quite playful, even--
Reminiscent of Wang Yi.
[ZHENG] But the fact remains
that we're at a disadvantage.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
This is Wang Yi.
I'm sure he's already
planned his next move.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Nonetheless...
The battling will
continue to be harsh.
[DIAO yawns]
[DIAO] Your dad really put up a
heck of a fight, huh, Meng Yi?
[MENG YI] Yeah.
I mean he brought
the enemy to its knees
on sheer force...
[MENG YI] That isn't something
easy for me to admit, though.
[DIAO] Huh...
You don't seem
too happy about it.
How come?
This is the era of strategy.
He is out of step
with the times,
hung up solely on individual
sheer fighting strength.
[DIAO] But um, your dad dares
to follow that path anyway,
am I right?
[DIAO] Gotta support him...
[MENG YI] Of course...
I support him.
[MENG YI] I decided
to become a strategist
because I wanted to make up for
the areas where he's lacking.
[MENG YI]
But I suppose I didn't need to.
Watching him, I realized:
Meng Wu is strong, and he's
not lacking in anything.
It looks like this war will
revolve around my father,
Meng Wu, for a while.
[NARRATOR] The third day.
[NARRATOR]
To oppose Meng Wu's army,
Zhao's forces
changed battle arrays.
[NARRATOR] Li Bai and Gongsun
Long's armies joined forces
and countered Meng Wu's army
with their
collective 40,000 men.
[NARRATOR]
Nevertheless, Meng Wu...
...remained unstoppable.
[NARRATOR] The presence
of the exceptional power
that was Meng Wu
was about to radically
change the war situation.
Gongsun Long! Li Bai!
[SHE MENG] What exactly
are you two doing?
Don't place blame on them.
This is my fault.
I failed to recognize
Meng Wu's power.
Then fix this by
outmaneuvering him
like the tactician
you are, Zhao Zhuang.
I plan to.
We'll strike
Meng Wu in full force.
[laughs]
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
We will lure him in firstly
by taking exactly the same
formations tomorrow,
to mean we'll fight
the same way.
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
When he makes his charge,
I want She Meng and Wan Ji to
attack from the rear and flank.
How do we respond
if another army
takes advantage of
that time to attack us?
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
No need to consider that.
We will slay Meng Wu
before they make a move!
[MENG WU] You want to talk?
About what?
No need to act menacing.
Please just have a seat.
I'll stand! Get to the point!
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] Very well.
I'll skip the formalities, then.
I anticipate that Zhao's armies
will make a real
drastic move tomorrow.
[MENG WU] What do I care?
[WANG YI] I had faith
that you'd say just that.
[WANG YI] Normally we'd
consider the enemy's next moves
and set up
various countermeasures,
but in this particular case,
I wholeheartedly agree with you.
What are you trying to say?
Now is the time
for us to attack.
[NARRATOR] The next morning,
the Fei Xin Force
was incorporated into the
Fourth Army led by Gan Yang.
[GAN YANG]
Here you are, Fei Xin Force.
[GAN YANG] I expect heroic
fighting out of all of you.
[FEI XIN FORCE]
Y-Yes, Sir!
Get ready, boy,
today's battle will be
another fierce one.
That's how I like 'em!
[NARRATOR] And so the fourth day
of battle was about to begin.
[NARRATOR] On this battlefield
filled with heroic warlords,
each side with a hidden agenda,
the one to set things off
was of course... this man.
Men... Let's charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WAN JI]
Meng Wu has made his move.
I'll be paying you
a visit soon.
Look forward to it!
[ZHAO ZHUANG]
Not yet, Wan Ji, She Meng.
Move when Meng Wu's army
passes the halfway point exactly
between their side and our side.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Now!
First Army, move out!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What?!
Another central army
is making its move
right now, too?!
[LONG GUO]
Second Army, into battle!
[LIN FANG] Third Army, let's go!
[TONG JIN] Fifth Army, charge!
Qin's main army, as well?
Damn these country bumpkins!
They have changed
their strategy!
Do not fall behind!
[GAN YANG]
Fourth Army, here we go!
And what they want is...
[WANG YI]
...the Zhao army headquarters.
Whaddya figure
it's like, Wei Ping?
What do I figure what?
Being on the
other end of this attack
that's taking even
our breath away!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] We're the ones
who crossed their borders
and then invaded...
Your Qin dogs should
be on the defense.
And yet you're attacking us
with all your armies, Wang Yi?
[DIAO]
Things are getting pretty crazy!
Is this really
a good idea, though?
[ZHAO ZHUANG] There will be
absolutely no coming back
from this if you fail, Wang Yi!
Oh, no, we won't fail.
Will we, Meng Wu?
Piece of cake!
This one'll be an easy win, Xin!
Yeah!
They are so scared
of Meng Wu's army,
they're paying
no attention to us!
We can take this chance to
go straight for headquarters!
A unit from the left
made it into the mountains!
Can they actually storm
Zhao army headquarters
in one single charge?
[MENG YI]
Do you really think so?
Well, no.
The enemy saw them and
didn't even try to stop them
whatsoever.
Which means...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WEI PING]
Wh-What the heck is this?
I-It might...
It might as...
as well be a fortress!
Hey guys, no turning back!
If we get through here,
we're at headquarters!
Our only choice is to advance.
Expect to shed blood!
Fei Xin Force, forward!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] My original plan
was to reduce Qin's numbers
through repeated battles,
then ask Pang Nuan to come in,
and then take Wang Yi's head...
But now, it turns out
that in just four days,
we are the ones whose
headquarters are being stormed.
I was confident
that not even Wang Yi
could best me
in matters of strategy.
But I guess I'm
no match for him...
However, I'm not finished.
This battle won't end yet!
We're moving the headquarters!
[NARRATOR] Zhao Zhuang's order
was immediately relayed
to the front lines.
He's mobilizing headquarters?
You're taking the
plunge early, Zhao Zhuang.
But under these
battle conditions...
It's probably a wise decision.
[ZHAO ZHUANG] We can't afford
to lose any more of our soldiers
until we launch
our next strategy!
[ZHAO ZHUANG] Whatever I have to
do, I'm in this war to win it!
[XIN] Huh? What?!
What is going on?
[XIN]
Zhao seems to be retreating?!
[NARRATOR] The tides of war
were on the verge
of yet another sudden turn!
[grunting]
[crashing noise]
[KAINE] Shouldn't we have taken
the long way on horseback?
[LI MU] No, I heard
this way would be faster.
[LI MU] See?
Yep, they're going at it!
We did make it in time.
[LI MU]
Take a look at that, Kaine.
[KAINE] Oh, I'm looking.
Okay, everyone!
Li Mu has just arrived!
[YUAN] I have to go help them!
Our men are all dying!
[NARRATOR] Is this a nightmare?
There is no escape from
this one-sided destruction.
Next Time: "An Act of God."