Hear me,
one and all, now!
Yang Duanhe, king of
the mountain realm,
binds herself to Ying Zheng,
King of Qin, in a firm alliance.
She... She's a woman?!
[YANG DUANHE]
In that alliance's name,
we will go to
regain the throne
from which he was
unjustly driven.
Gather troops from
the surrounding heights!
All troops prepare to march,
with intentions to
fight to the death!
Our target is Qin's
capital at Xianyang!
[MEN holler]
[MEN cheering]
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China.
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm of
war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale
of a nameless boy
and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[birds chriping]
[squeaking]
[rumbling]
[commotion]
[hollering]
[DIAO] Wow... Things have
sure gotten crazy!
"Things" are only
just beginning.
[MOUNTAIN FOLK hollering]
[XIN yelling]
[BI]
Xin! Pull the reins!
Pull on the reins! Xin!
I am pulling them!
What do you think I'm doing?
[yelling]
[BI]
Xin!
[BA JIO] Behold, the amazing
riding technique
even Tajifu raves about.
I guess having him around
is good for
breaking the tension...
Huh...
He really is hopeless.
[birds chirping]
[MAN yells]
[yells]
[whimpering]
[MAN growls]
[MEN laughing]
--[MAN growls]
--[MEN whimpering]
Ah! G-Gods above!
In the name of all
that is holy,
how can you let these
cowardly rebels do this?!
[thud, squelch]
[BOTH gasp]
[CHENG JIAO]
Hey...
Just to make things clear,
minions of Changwen,
my actions do not count
as rebellion at all.
[SOLDIER 9D]
What?!
I've just returned things
to their proper state.
[CHENG JIAO]
The way things should be.
The way they were
five years ago.
[XIN]
Ya!
Hngh! Ha!
[XIN chuckles]
[XIN] So this is
riding a horse...
[BI] Good, Xin!
You're getting the hang of it!
Bi, my man,
I know all about it.
All about what?
How warfare changed
when people started
riding into battle.
King Wuling's the one
that started that!
I'm impressed! You know
King Wuling of Zhao?
[XIN laughs]
I'm just remembering...
Piao and I used to
long for the day
that we'd be able to
sit astride horses.
[PIAO] Xin, someday, we're
gonna have our own horses.
[gasps] Oh, cool!
I always wanted to
try eating horse!
We're gonna ride them,
not eat them!
I heard something interesting
at the market today.
[PIAO] Apparently, until the
era of King Wuling of Zhao,
nobody rode horses to battle.
King Wuling?
[PIAO] He was the king
of Zhao 80 years ago.
He's the one who created
the Middle Kingdom's
first mounted cavalry.
[horse neighs]
[PIAO] He got rid of
the idea that horses
were just for pulling carts.
Huh...?
But Piao, can...
can people really fight well
when they're mounted
on those animals?
[PIAO] Actually,
they're super powerful!
Tian was telling me
about the time
he was on the battlefield.
He said that a whole
troop of foot soldiers
was scattered by
a single horseman.
They're that powerful?!
Man, now I wanna try!
[XIN]
I wanna ride one too, Piao!
Me too!
But first, we have to
follow the order of things.
[XIN]
What do you mean?
[PIAO] Only regulars
from the warrior nobility
are allowed to be cavalry.
We must start off
as foot soldiers
and build the skills
to join the warrior class.
Only after that are
we allowed to ride.
[XIN]
Seriously?!
That's way too far
in the future!
I wanna ride a
horse right now!
--[XIN] They sound so cool!
--[PIAO] Oh! That reminds me!
Isn't there a horse
over at Xi's place?
Uh, no...
I think that's an ox.
[moos]
Well, okay, then...
Shall we try riding
an ox for starters?
Sounds good.
[BOTH]
Hmmm.
[XIN]
Piao, are you watching?
At long last,
I'm riding a horse, Piao!
[XIN] You might've beat me
to it by a little bit...
...but now,
I'm riding one too!
Yah!
[hollering]
[CHENG JIAO] Lan Kai's run
out of toys to play with.
Bring in the
next ones, Si Shi.
Your Majesty, I would,
[SI SHI] but the previous
men were the last followers
of Lord Changwen
that we captured.
Well then, you can bring in
his entire family...
Wait, no, that won't be enough.
I know. You can
do that for a start.
[CHENG JIAO] Then seize all
the tenants from his land
and bring him here!
We actually attempted
that already, my lord.
We tried to capture
Lord Changwen's family.
But I'm afraid to report that
[SI SHI] someone prevented
us from doing so.
[CHENG JIAO]
And who would that be?
That would be the man
who currently rules over
Lord Changwen's lands,
Your Majesty.
[WANG YI]
Turn over Lord Changwen's
wife and children, you say?
[chuckles]
Except his dominions belong
to me now, don't they?
[SI SHI grunts]
[WANG YI] That means all the
people in those dominions
belong to me, as well.
Telling me to hand them over
is rather amusing of you.
If it's so important
for you to have them,
[WANG YI] well then,
you can put your wife
and children in my keeping.
Once you've done that,
maybe I'll think about it.
[laughs]
Til next time.
[CHENG JIAO]
That Wang Yi...
Taking down Lord Changwen
has gone to his head.
Now he's pressing his luck.
Once things
have been settled,
I'll reward him by making
him one of Lan Kai's toys.
[CHENG JIAO]
Which reminds me, Si Shi...
My lord?
Ying Zheng's head
still isn't here yet, is it?
My patience is reaching an end.
[SI SHI]
Of course...
We're still searching
for him, Your Majesty.
[CHENG JIAO] Si Shi,
I'm letting you and yours
do as you like
with the kingdom.
In return, you and yours must
deliver Ying Zheng's head!
That is my only command.
But make no mistake...
If it's not obeyed,
your lives are at risk.
[JIE SHI laughs]
Please try not to
worry yourself so much,
my young lord.
As Minister of the Left,
I give you my word--
no, I promise
on my very life,
that you'll have
the King's head soon.
[JIE SHI] Now that
Lord Changwen is gone,
the King has nowhere to go.
He must be suffering in
anguish even as we speak.
When you think
of things that way,
isn't it a pleasure
to draw out the wait
for the day he
shows himself again?
More importantly,
the King's existence is
but a trifling matter now.
The bigger picture
demands our attention.
Lü Buwei...
[TROOP 9A]
You're safe!
[TROOP 9B]
Show me...
[TROOP 9C] Where are
the water and rations?
[CAVALRY COMMANDER 9A]
Company Six.
31 members have returned.
[SOLDIER 9E]
Oh! So you're all okay, too!
We have some injuries.
Please, take care of them.
[SOLDIER 9F]
Yes, sir.
Nonetheless...
[SOLDIER 9E]
Huh?
[CAVALRY COMMANDER 9A]
To be honest,
it surprises me
that this many survived.
[SOLDIER 9E]
Yes. We've sent out scouts
to round up the routed
and scattered troops.
Still more will join us.
I see.
What of our lord?
I heard he was safe,
but where is he? Did he leave?
He's up above.
Above?
Huh?
[rumbling]
[LORD CHANGWEN] The mountains...
they're trembling.
[SOLDIER 9F]
Wha... What's that?!
[SOLDIER 9G]
What is that sound?
[XIN yelling]
[XIN]
Ha, ha! I win!
Huh?
We've returned.
Thank you for the welcome.
[LORD CHANGWEN] We've been
waiting for you anxiously.
[XIN] Diao, hurry over
here with that grass!
The poor thing must be
absolutely starving! Huh?
Commander?
[TAJIFU grunts]
[BA JIO] Boy, Tajifu
says he's surprised.
That there is our most
temperamental horse.
He says it's an
impressive feat.
Even among the mountain folk,
few have been able to ride it.
[XIN laughs] Well, you know, for
someone like me, it's... huh?
Wait, you purposely dumped
a wild horse on me?!
Hey!
[DIAO]
Xin!
[XIN]
You're slow!
[DIAO] Ugh, I swear,
you're so hard on people!
I noticed something.
[XIN]
Hm?
Aren't there more of Lord
Changwen's troops than before?
[DIAO] They're overflowing
from that cave.
[XIN]
Yeah...
[XIN] Looks like old Lord
Changwen hasn't been
sitting on his butt
and waiting around.
It feels like things
are livening up.
Gotta admit,
I'm getting pretty pumped!
[SOLDIER 9H]
Xin!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[XIN]
Uh--
You did a great job
rescuing His Majesty.
Not only that,
but you came back
at the head of
the mountain folk...
I was wrong about you!
[SOLDIER 9I]
So was I!
At first I thought you were
just a kid with bad manners,
but I take it back!
What's this?
Who are those kids?
That's Xin and Diao.
After our troops
fell back in the mountains,
those two pursued
the King with Lieutenant Bi
as far as the
mountain folk's stronghold.
[CAVALRY COMMANDER 9A]
Huh...
[door creaks]
Heya! Is the strategy
council already over?
[BI] Xin! We haven't
even begun yet!
And more importantly,
you can't just traipse
in here as you please!
[XIN] What's wrong?
[BI] Huh?
[XIN] Your face is
really red, Bi, my man.
[DIAO] I get it...
he's got a crush!
[BI]
What are you talking about?
[DIAO]
Oh, I think you know...
[TAJIFU grunts]
[BA JIO] Tajifu says
your face doesn't match
our king's tastes or standards.
[BI]
Just what are you saying?
Can we talk about this later?
The point is, we should
head out right away!
We've got a lot of
momentum right now!
Warfare's all about momentum!
Who needs detailed plans?
Let's power it on
out of here! Let's go!
Oh boy. Here we go again.
[YANG DUANHE]
He has a point.
As Xin says,
maintaining momentum is an
important factor in warfare.
But... momentum alone
would only win
perhaps a single battle between
small kingdoms, at most.
We are about to attack
the capital of Qin,
so we must know our enemy well.
We must know how their
forces are deployed...
and we need a stratagem
for surmounting the walls.
The capital of Qin... oh man.
If the four of you
would like to
join the war council,
sit right there
and don't say a word.
[ZHENG]
Hmph.
[XIN]
Stop it, Zheng!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Your Majesty...
In the time since our army
descended from the mountains,
I've been sending
my men into Xianyang.
They had been ordered to gather
as much information as possible.
[ZHENG]
Tell me.
My liege.
To begin with,
there's been a large shift
in the enemy
forces' deployment.
The word is that,
for some reason,
there's been a
report of my death,
so their attention
has shifted from
Your Majesty over to
dealing with Lü Buwei.
[ZHENG]
Jie Shi has begun to move?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Yes.
They say that recently,
an army of 80,000
has been mustered in Xianyang.
Huh?!
80,000?!
C-Commander, how many
tribesmen do we have?
[BA JIO]
About 3,000.
That... That's not
even close to enough!
[DIAO]
80,000...
--ZHENG] Hmph.
--[XIN] What?
The numbers
will be adequate.
[XIN, DIAO]
Wha--?!
[XIN]
3,000 against 80,000?!
What's adequate about that?!
Have you completely lost it?
Old Man Changwen,
you tell him!
It's just as
His Majesty says.
[XIN]
Huh?
The numbers
will be appropriate
for carrying out our stratagem.
A stratagem?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
But before we depart,
there's something I will
need you all to make.
To make?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
To begin with...
Huh?
Ah. Risen already, Your Majesty?
[ZHENG]
Yes.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Finally we come to it.
[ZHENG]
Mm-hm.
The preparations
seem to be coming along.
Yes.
[DIAO, SOLDIERS laughing]
[DIAO] Whoa, that mask
is amazing, Xin!
[XIN]
Shut up!
[laughing]
[ZHENG]
You're finished, then?
[DIAO]
Zheng!
Look at this! It's the mask
Xin made! Isn't it amazing?
[XIN] Quiet, you.
I made it funny on purpose!
[ZHENG] That's good work,
by your standards.
[XIN]
Don't laugh at it!
[DIAO] I made one for you
as well, Zheng. Here it is.
Honestly...
Ordering us to make
all this weird stuff...
What are we supposed
to do with it, anyway?!
You'll understand later.
More importantly,
have you finished preparing?
Preparing what?
I already made the mask.
[ZHENG]
I mean preparing this.
[XIN coughing]
This is going to be
a real pitched battle.
[XIN]
Tch. Don't patronize me.
I've been ready for that
kind of fight for a long time.
I've trained for it, after all.
All those years with
Piao were for this.
[ZHENG]
Bi!
Gather everyone up!
Prepare to depart immediately!
Yes, sir!
We're going home...
to Xianyang!
[SOLDIERS]
Huzzah!
[JIE SHI]
Our adversary is Lü Buwei.
If things go badly and we lose
this decisive battle to him,
that merchant
spawn will end up
taking the throne
from you, my lord.
Just thinking about it
makes me nauseated.
We must return the Royal Court
to its pure and proper state,
no matter what the cost.
[laughter]
[FLUNKY 9A] That minister
of Zhao who came to court
the other day, was gushing with
praise for my lord Cheng Jiao.
He said he expects
you'll become
an esteemed king of rare worth.
[FLUNKY 9B] Because of you,
my lord Cheng Jiao,
the future of Qin's
next generation is secure!
[FLUNKIES laughing]
[FLUNKY 9A]
What's the matter, my lord?
[CHENG JIAO]
There's no bridge.
[FLUNKY 9C] My lord,
there's a bridge over there...
I want one here.
[CHENG JIAO laughs]
[FLUNKIES murmuring]
[FLUNKY 9A] Cheng Jiao
isn't the heir to the throne!
[FLUNKY 9C]
They say it's Ying Zheng.
[FLUNKY 9D]
Ying Zheng?!
[CHENG JIAO] Ying Zheng?
I don't know anyone
by that name!
Who is he?!
[FLUNKY 9E]
Ah... Apparently, he is
my lord Cheng Jiao's
elder brother.
[CHENG JIAO]
Elder brother?
I never heard
I had an elder brother!
[FLUNKY 9E] Ying Zheng's
mother is of low station,
so she'd never come forward.
But despite that,
the word now is that
there's been an informal
decision to make her
the King's official consort,
and to install
her son, Ying Zheng,
as the new heir to the throne
instead of you, my lord.
She's of low station?
You're saying
the next king will be
the brat of a woman like that?
[FLUNKY 9E] Please, keep
your voice down, my lord!
Ying Zheng is
already here at Court.
You must be careful!
[FLUNKIES laughing]
[CHENG JIAO]
He looked down on me.
That bastard...
He looked down on me!
How dare he humiliate me?
Me, the most royal of royalty!
[CHENG JIAO] What do you mean,
I can't see my mother?
[LADY OF THE COURT 9A]
My lord...
She's fallen ill, and no one
may see her, not even you.
Leave at once, please,
my lord Cheng Jiao.
[CHENG JIAO]
My mother was sick...
I thought it was just an
excuse for her not to see me.
But my mother's
"illness" was genuine.
When her throne and
position were stolen
by a woman of low birth,
she grew sick at heart.
My lord Cheng Jiao.
Please, stand right over there.
Our troops are
gathered for the war
that will strike down Lü Buwei
and make you King of Qin.
Your men stand ready
to fight for you.
[SOLDIERS yell]
Yes, this is how
things should be.
[SOLDIER whooping, yelling]
[DIAO]
Yahoo!
[XIN]
Hiyaah!
[BI]
Xin?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Churlish little fool,
riding out in front of
His Majesty like that...
It's fine. Let him
do what he likes.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Is something the matter, Bi?
[BI]
No... it's nothing.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Hm...
[BI]
Xin... Piao...
The two of you
really are the same...
[ZHENG] We're here, at last.
It took us an
awful long time.
[DIAO]
Then, you're saying that's...
That's right.
[ZHENG] That... That is
the capital of Qin...
...Xianyang.
[XIN] There's no
choice but to do it!
There's nothing
left but to do it!
[NARRATOR]
An impregnable wall.
The stratagem for breaking
through it begins to fall apart.
Next Time:
"Storming the Capital."