[XIN]
What's to be glad about?
You, and you, and you,
with all your carrying on!
Listen, old man!
Piao is... Piao is...
Piao is now dead!
Hey! Say something!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Piao isn't the only one.
A many great others died. This
is a war. Lives will be lost.
[XIN growls]
What did you say?!
I've had enough
of your nonsense!
[DIAO gasps]
Oh no...
[XIN]
You bastard!
I regret the commotion,
Your Highness.
[BI] What shall we do
with this person?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Let him lie
somewhere out of the way.
[BI]
Yes, sir.
[NARRATOR]
Ancient China...
The time of the sages was over,
swept away by base human greed.
Over five centuries,
an endless storm
of war, hatred, and strife
raged across the land.
Over a hundred nations fell,
winnowed away until
only seven remained.
Now, from Qin,
the westernmost kingdom,
a great wind of history
is about to blow.
This is the tale of a
nameless boy and a young King
who ran the gauntlet
in this age of strife.
[DIAO]
Kept you waiting. Here it is!
If it's good, say "yum,"
or if it's bad say "yuck."
At least say that much.
Guess it's not
that kind of a mood.
[SOLDIER 6]
That was a hideous fight.
[SOLDIER 6B] Never imagined
things getting that bad.
[SOLDIERS]
Yeah.
[SOLDIER 6C]
Our master, Lord Changwen,
has had a rough time of it, too.
Lord Changwen?!
Diao you, just said
"Lord Changwen," huh?!
Huh? That wasn't me!
That bastard. Where did he go?
Ow! Ouch, ouch!
That son of a--
Settle down!
You shouldn't be moving!
Though, you are not the
only one who cannot move,
I'll have you know.
[DIAO] All these soldiers
came here for Zheng.
I'm just truly glad.
Absolutely. What really
matters is that
His Highness is safe.
Did you see
Lord Changwen's face?
I have never seen him
shed a tear before this.
I'm so glad I risked my life
to get all the way here.
[BI] In this escape drama,
our biggest slip-up
concerned General
Wang Yi's appearance.
We simply didn't anticipate
that he would show up.
Taking his personality
into account,
we presumed him being
completely uninterested
in the Court's power struggles.
[LORD CHANGWEN] On that day,
I may have foolishly played
right into Wang Yi's
entire scheme.
[ZHENG]
Scheme?
Yes. In the middle
of that brutal battle,
our combat somehow drove us
all the way up to Shu Da Hill.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
And there...
What the...
[LORD CHANGWEN screams]
[LORD CHANGWEN] In this way, I
pulled myself from Death's jaws,
but I'd been forced to
leave the battlefield.
A blunder... But now,
as I think about it
why was I able to hold my own
that long, solo against Wang Yi?
With the prowess
that he possesses,
he could've sliced
the likes of me in two
without breaking a sweat.
That was clearly a scheme of his
to draw me away
from the battlefield.
Wang Yi has many riddles,
the Kingdom of Qin's
mysterious bird, who flies by
his very own, strange callings.
A legendary general,
who served my grandfather,
the great King Zhao.
[door creaks]
[DIAO] Um... I thought
that you'd be hungry.
Thank you for that, Diao.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Your Highness, who is this?
[ZHENG] He's He Liao Diao.
He saved my life at Heibei.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Is that so?
And yet you dress in an awfully
unique outfit, little one.
[DIAO] Because I'm of
the mountain folk.
Really?
In which case you have a true
connection to this place,
isn't that right?
Maybe.
Your Highness, may I speak now?
What is it?
[BI] This means you also met
the other at Heibei Village?
That's right. His name is Xin.
It's thanks to him
that I'm here today.
Xin was also
a friend of Piao's.
He was... Was Lord Piao's...?
[DIAO]
Lord Piao?
[BI]
Excuse me, your Highness.
If I may have your permission,
I would tell that young man
of Lord Piao's demise.
[DIAO]
Xin! Hey, Xin!
Zheng's calling for you.
Says he wants you to
hear something important.
[DIAO] What's with you?
Zheng's calling you!
Are you feeling down, Xin?
Shut up with your jabbering!
So what if Zheng's calling?
Can't you see I'm
thinking right now?!
He can come here if
he wants something!
Who the heck's Zheng?
Do we even have a Zheng?
[SOLDIERS]
Zheng?!
You can't possibly
mean His Highness?!
[XIN]
Yep.
Who do you think you are?!
To utter the High King's name
is an inexcusable offense!
But Zheng said it was all right!
You're still gonna say it?!
The King is calling
for you, Xin.
Hurry up! Bi says he has
something to tell you.
[XIN]
Oh, so what?
It's about Piao's last moments.
Oh. I see.
Hey, wait for me!
[DIAO] The blowgun...
Where are the darts?
[DIAO]
Ah, there he is!
[DIAO] I'm used to seeing
corpses in the village,
but touching one's nasty!
Where are they?
Not there, nope.
[DIAO screams]
The undead!
[MU TA]
Do not make a fuss, now.
If they hear that I'm alive,
they will finish me
off most definitely.
[DIAO] What, old guy?
You're still alive?
Mu Ta's life force is
powerfully fearsome.
This is what I would like to
say, but I will be dead soon.
So please keep it
hush-hush, understand?
[DIAO] Well I'll hush,
but in return give me
some poison darts.
You want Mu Ta's poison darts?
Yeah. I wanna be... formidable.
[XIN]
So you are Bi?
[BI]
Yes I am Bi,
Lord Changwen's
retainer and lieutenant.
I heard you have something
to say about Piao.
Correct. I would very much like
for you to know of this story.
[XIN gasps]
[BI]
My lord!
[PERSONAL GUARDSMAN]
Lieutenant Bi! What orders?
Defend the carriage!
Even if it means
being cut to pieces--
Defend that carriage!
[BI] Only two knew about the
stand-in: Lord Changwen and me.
To make this ploy succeed,
I raised my voice and strove
to rouse up the troops.
But Wang Yi's force...
was simply too strong.
Don't waver! Don't waver!
[BI] Our lines began
to break, and the carriage
was cut off from us.
[SOLDIER screams]
[PERSONAL GUARDSMAN 6A]
Lieutenant Bi! The carriage!
[BI] It was over.
We would be annihilated.
I gave up all hope.
But just then...
Don't give in!
Re-form your lines!
We'll tighten the ranks
and break through!
[TROOPS 6A]
Yes, sir!
[TROOPS 6B]
Muster 'round the King!
[TROOPS 6C]
We'll break right through!
We'd abandoned all hope,
but our will to
fight was rekindled
by Piao's strong words.
I truly couldn't believe
it that before us
was Wang Yi's force
feared in every land,
while the one who
led us, unflinching,
was a boy of unknown
name of low station.
[BI gasps]
It's Piao...
[BI] But his bearing
was that of a king.
[BI] With this momentum,
we could break through--
I was certain of it.
However...
[PIAO]
Lieutenant!
Split the force and send part
to Lord Changwen's aid!
[BI]
But, Your Highness--!
With this momentum,
we can break through!
The King.
He needs Lord Changwen!
[PIAO]
Hear me: this is an order!
[BI]
Yes!
[BI] Your Highness!
A new force from the right!
[PIAO]
Still so many more?
From the looks of it,
it won't be so simple.
[PIAO]
Xin... give me strength.
Here I go, Xin!
[WANG YI'S TROOP 6A]
That's the King! Charge!
Take this head, I dare you!
[BI] Thanks to Lord Piao, the
force pursuing us was weakened.
[BI] Yes! Now we can get
past the enemy force!
[BI]
He broke through! Men!
The King is safe! Keep going!
[TROOPS]
Huzzah!
[BI] I was so sure that
Lord Piao was safe
and that we'd meet again here...
Such a bitter mischance...
Hey Zheng, there's just
one thing I want to ask.
I'm simple-minded so,
explain it in definite terms.
[ZHENG]
What's that?
If I get you back
safely onto your throne,
what will you do
for me in return?
Since you're the King,
will you grant me
anything I desire?
My wish is to become a general.
Will you grant me
this one wish, then?
What suddenly brought this?
I always knew, Piao was special.
Seeing Bi, my man here,
talk about him
as if he was a hero
just reaffirms it.
[XIN] He always knew
since we were kids...
He knew what it took
to win the prize.
[XIN]
But I didn't know anything.
He knew it all,
so I always thought
I could just stick with him.
But Piao's not here
anymore, as you know.
Nothing makes sense to me now.
So why not just
explain it to me?
In definite terms,
how can someone like me
become a general?
[MU TA]
Poison darts are dangerous,
so I'll give you sleeping darts.
[DIAO]
That's a little disappointing,
but what can you do?
[DIAO] Mountain tribesman He
Liao Diao: combat power rising!
[MU TA]
For keeping this hush-hush,
I am going to give you
a piece of advice.
Going with that
young King won't lead
to anything good at all.
From what I understand,
he has only one ally:
that old grizzle-beard.
[DIAO]
At the moment.
But I hear he's got a powerful
ally named Lü Buwei.
Apparently he's away
campaigning, though.
[MU TA] Unfortunately,
you are very badly mistaken.
[DIAO]
Huh?
[ZHENG] This kingdom now works
on a system based on merit.
The era of nobles and
warriors being generals
by virtue of being born
into a caste is now over.
Whoever goes to the battlefield
and accomplishes greater deeds
will rise to the
rank of general.
Piao used to say the
same thing, so I know that.
I want you to
explain the specifics!
Unfortunately for you,
it's impossible.
Say what?! What
exactly do you mean?
The army as it is, is mainly
made up with a group
of regulars of the
noble or warrior caste
and levies recruited
from the common folk.
But at present, you cannot
join the regulars,
or even the levies.
Eh?
[LORD CHANGWEN] You really
don't know anything, do you?
The levies are raised
from registered households
and only from
those houses owning
a minimum level of wealth.
But for you, without a
home to live in,
it's not a matter
of skill at arms.
You can't even step
onto the battlefield.
Don't be so disheartened.
General isn't a rank that
even a warrior or a noble
can easily set his sights on.
[XIN]
Uh-huh. I get it.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
You understand?
Uh-huh. I get it.
So we get Zheng
back to the Palace,
and after we take down his
brother, what's-his-name,
and this minister,
what's-his-name,
I just need to be given land,
have a house built for me,
and gain some wealth!
That is the situation.
That's an agreement!
We are agreed.
Hey, now things have
gotten interesting!
[ZHENG] In return, you'll work
ten times harder for me.
[XIN]
Are you kidding? 100 times!
Zheng! Is it true what I heard?
That Lü's army won't return
until you've been killed?
[SOLDIER 6J]
Minister Lü, a rider has come
from the capital...
Again with news of
Jie Shi's revolt.
[LÜ BUWEI]
Cut his head off.
[SOLDIER 6J]
Sir?
[LÜ BUWEI] It's a ploy
by the army of Wei,
seeking to free itself from
my army's encirclement.
Cut off the messenger's head.
[BI] Lü won't return? Even
knowing of Jie Shi's uprising?
That's outrageous!
Lü would suffer more
than anyone else
at the loss of His Highness!
Well, Bi, you do
not yet understand
the true fearsomeness that
Minister Lü possesses.
[XIN] What on earth
does this mean, Zheng?
Lü is waiting for
me to be slain,
and for Cheng Jiao to
ascend to the throne.
Lü would seize the
opportunity to loudly decry
the tyranny of Cheng Jiao
and Jie Shi,
and storm Xianyang
magnificently,
leading 200,000 troops.
The royal family
may lose their lives
in the chaos of the
battleground in Xianyang.
[ZHENG] With the whole
royal family eliminated,
who do you think the people
would raise up as their King?
Lü Buwei?!
What did you say?!
You're kidding me!
Lü Buwei isn't your ally
like I thought?
This means, you've got nothing
but enemies in the Court!
That's why I told you...
I am a, powerless king walking
in the cruel wilderness of war.
B-But there's some
way to do this, right?
C'mon, Lord Changwen!
It's regrettable,
but with our present
level of strength,
we cannot even manage
getting near the capital.
We can only watch
Lü's and Jie Shi's moves
and seek an opportunity
to regain power.
[ZHENG]
No, Lord Changwen.
I will return to the capital
as soon as possible.
But, Your Highness--!
[ZHENG]
Whether I'm alive or dead,
once Jie Shi is prepared for
all-out war with Lü Buwei,
he'll force Cheng Jiao
onto the throne.
Lü and Jie Shi's struggle
would be of a scale to
split the kingdom in two.
Before they spark a civil war,
I must attain the Jeweled Throne
and restore normalcy
to the capital.
It... It's impossible,
Your Highness!
Our strength is quite feeble.
What's more, there's now
no force in Qin
not bound to Lü or to
Jie Shi that would even
consider aiding us!
Do you think so, Xin?
Can you suggest some
way to do this, Zheng?
Hey, that blowgun! That's
that old guy's, right?
[DIAO] What about it?
He gave it to me!
[XIN]
Let me see it!
[DIAO grunts]
No! It's mine!
[XIN] I won't take it.
I said let me see!
[DIAO]
No! He gave it to me!
[LORD CHANGWEN]
There is...
My lord, did you say something?
There is one large
force that is not bound
to either Lü or to Jie Shi.
I have been thinking
of that ever since
we first arrived here.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
But 400 years ago,
the connection with them was...
[ZHENG]
The likelihood is small.
We can only go to meet them...
[ZHENG]
The mountain folk...
[ZHENG] ...and the
mountain king who rules them.
[BI]
I see.
You don't know the tale of
the "Horse &amp; Liquor Force".
[NARRATOR] Xin and his
companions shudder in fear.
Is it those berserk folk,
creeping through the
unfathomable dark?
Next time: The Fearsome
Folk of the Mountains