[NARRATOR] When Qin got
offensive in the war with Zhao
via Xin's efforts as leader
of the Fei Xin Force,
Wang Yi placed all armies
under Meng Wu's command
and went straight for the
conquest of enemy headquarters.
First Army, move out!
[LONG GUO]
Second Army, into battle!
[LIN FANG]
Third Army, let's go!
[TONG JIN]
Fifth Army, charge!
Qin's main army, as well?
They have changed
their strategy!
[GAN YANG]
Fourth Army, here we go!
[NARRATOR] However,
just as Xin and the others
were on the verge of striking,
the situation abruptly
and drastically changed.
[XIN] What?! What is going on?
[XIN] Zhao seems
to be retreating?!
[DIAO] What's going on?
The mountain of Zhao's
headquarters went all quiet!
[MENG YI]
Zhao's central force is...
[DIAO] Whoa whoa,
what's gotten into them?
[DIAO] They left their
headquarters totally exposed!
Could they be--
[LI MU] Oh!
[LI MU]
It looks like Zhao's armies
are already
going into hiding!
[KAINE] My lord,
there are people already here.
[LI MU] Hm?
Hi! I'm Li Mu, and this is
my gorgeous bodyguard Kaine!
[chuckles softly]
[NARRATOR] The time:
The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
The place: Qin.
Xin, a nameless boy,
met Zheng, a young King,
distinguished himself in battle,
and rose to the rank
of squadron commander.
In the midst of this,
the neighboring
kingdom of Zhao invaded,
and Qin faced
unprecedented crisis.
What manner of
battle will Wang Yi wage
as commanding general?
And what growth
will Xin accomplish?
[SOLDIER]
Take down Zhao's flag!
Put up ours!
[MAO] We took their
headquarters, didn't we?
So we won?!
[TIAN YONG] Moron!
They've just moved
their headquarters
somewhere else, it seems,
to keep their numbers up.
So then, do we
chase them again?
Of course we do!
We're not letting 'em
get away now!
[XIN] Dammit, what are the
combat commanders waiting for?!
If we drag our feet,
the enemy will regroup!
[LONG GUO] So they've
taken the battlefield
into the mountains...
[TONG JIN] We won't be able
to tell where they are now.
[LONG GUO] No, the
steepness of the mountains
limits the number of places
they can station troops.
From our higher vantage point,
we'll spot them.
But it is safe to assume
they've already considered that.
Do you think we should
pursue them, Long Guo?
Don't ask that, Gan Yang!
You heard what my lord said
in last night's war council.
[WANG YI] We can gain
control of Zhao's mountain,
but I'm sure their headquarters
itself will retreat.
Whether we should pursue them
will depend on
the circumstances.
I'll leave that decision to
the general on the ground.
And that means you, Meng Wu.
Mountain warfare carries danger
because it's difficult
for allies to act in concert.
[WANG YI] I advise you
to think calmly.
We will pursue!
[MENG WU'S SUBORDINATES]
Yes, Sir!
[LONG GUO]
Allow me to confirm:
You do remember the promise
with General Wang Yi last night,
I trust?
However, if you do
attack the fleeing enemy
you must promise one thing.
[WANG YI] And that is scope!
You may only attack Zhao
within seeing distance
of their former headquarters.
Under no circumstances
can you break this promise.
I know that.
They seem to be
moving out, my lord.
[growling]
Oh my goodness!
We came all the way here,
and now everybody's
disappeared behind the mountain!
[LI MU] Now all
we can see from here
is Qin's headquarters
facing away.
Well, I suppose that's still
worth the walk on its own,
wouldn't you agree?
[DIAO] H-Hey!
Quit ignoring us already!
[DIAO] Who the heck
are you people?!
Nobody invited you up here!
Both of you,
put down your swords!
[NARRATOR] At Qin headquarters,
preparations to move
were complete.
[NARRATOR] Zhao's mountain
had been thoroughly conquered
and there was no sign of
the enemy between them and it.
Circumstances were good for Qin
to switch its headquarters in.
And yet Wang Yi, who had been
quick to act up until now,
was uncharacteristically silent.
An indefinable sense
that something was off
held him in place.
[WANG YI] I sense
a carefully laid strategy
behind this sudden
retreat on Zhao's part.
Meaning these four days
of Zhao losing were deliberate,
but that hardly seems
conceivable at all to me.
[WANG YI] Something smells
a wee bit strange here.
Teng.
Sir?
Do they have any other
tacticians remaining
besides Zhao Zhuang?
No, they should not
have any, Sir.
[WANG YI] Well, why not?
We'll move headquarters, Teng.
[TENG] Yes, Sir.
[WANG YI] After all, either way
I still have to go and smoke out
that commanding general
of theirs
who hasn't shown his face.
[LI MU] Now Qin's headquarters
is on the move, too!
[DIAO] Huh?!
[LI MU] They're transferring
to that mountain
because it'll be easier to
maintain command from there.
I can figure that out myself!
Don't talk down!
But you know this will
bring those two generals
closer together!
Hohohoho, how very exciting!
Now, then.
Let's get going, everyone!
We won't be able to
see the battle from here.
[DIAO] Just hold on a second!
Why are you giving the
orders all of a sudden?!
[LI MU] Uh, why not?
We're all spectators, aren't we?
The more of us the merrier,
wouldn't you say?!
Would you mind giving
us two a ride in your carriage?
Our horses are a bit
far away right now.
Of all the nerve
in the Kingdom!
We're not just gonna--
[LI MU] The thing is, there's
another abandoned castle
up ahead just perfect
for viewing from!
[DIAO] There is?!
Very well.
But I have just
one request in return.
[LI MU] What is that?
[MENG YI] Will you let us take
charge over all of your swords
if we do?
I am so wary of traveling with
strangers in a place like this.
Put yourself in my place.
Understand?
[LI MU] Okay then. Have them.
[KAINE] What?!
[MENG YI] Thank you very much.
[KAINE]
You're not getting my swords!
Let's leave while
we still have daylight.
[KAINE] My lord!
[NARRATOR]
While Qin's forces set up tents
at their new headquarters,
Wang Yi put the
infantry on standby
in the mountain's
rear foothills
in case of changes in the war.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Long Guo joined Meng Wu's army
and led the way to enemy camp.
The other armies
advanced with them
in their original positions
around Meng Wu.
[NARRATOR] But they had not
encountered the enemy as of yet.
[WANG YI] Any reports
at all on Pang Nuan?
[SOLDIER 30A] No, Sir.
Each army's commander
has reported in,
with no sightings of him.
[WANG YI] You certainly like
to try my patience, Pang Nuan.
[WANG YI] Has what
happened nine years ago
perhaps made you more cautious?
[WANG YI chuckles]
[WANG YI] But you have
no hope of taking my head
if all you do is hide.
[WEI PING] If things
keep going like this,
we may get home sooner
than we thought, huh?
Yep.
And then, we'll
be village heroes!
[laughs]
[YOU YI] Imagine the look
on their faces
when we tell 'em
we took down a general!
When I get home, I'm gonna
go and marry Dong Mei!
[YOU YI]
Nobody asked for that update.
[MAO] Don't say that.
Because you are not actually
engaged, or are you?
[WEI PING growls]
[WEI PING] I said I'm gonna,
and I'm gonna!
[SOLDIERS laugh]
That's right, you go for it.
Dao here has kept
his woman waiting forever
because he says
he can't get married
before his big brother
does so first!
Hey, hey,
Qing, stop sayin--
[WEI PING] What?!
Is that true, Dao?!
I'm sorry! Please give me
just a little longer!
[laughing]
[XIE CI] Ze Gui, so how old is
your kid again... around five?
[ZE GUI]
Just turned six, actually.
Huh, so the same age
as mine! A boy?
[ZE GUI] Yes, a boy.
[XIE CI]
Yeah, sons are the best, right?!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 30A] Moron...
daughters are so much cuter!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 30B]
Nah, boys are the best.
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 30A]
Girls, idiot!
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 30C]
Is your baby big, Long Chuan?
Must be, right?
[LONG CHUAN]
No, normal size...
Hi! The war council is over!
[XIN] What's wrong?
[QIANG LEI] Nothing.
[QIANG LEI] It's just...
They all have a home
to go back to.
Y-You--
Just forget it!
Do not read into that.
Everyone gets to have
different things.
I have something, too:
A goal that I'm living for.
[XIN] Revenge is important.
But you know, Qiang Lei,
that isn't the end whatsoever.
After you get your revenge,
you're alive, and you'll
still have a future.
Deep down, you've already
figured that out, haven't you?
[QIANG LEI] Huh?
"Huh"? Don't you "huh" me!
You took a break from revenge
to come and join the war
with us here!
Of your own free will!
[XIN] Which means...
You've got a perfectly
good home, too!
The Fei Xin Force!
Don't you forget that now!
[QIANG LEI]
Don't decide that solo.
[XIN] Come on. I'm gonna tell
everyone about the meeting.
Or are you saying
you don't like it here?
[QIANG LEI]
No, I'm not.
Then it is settled!
[QIANG LEI] It's not
that I don't like it here.
[QIANG LEI] No. In fact,
it's not half bad.
[QIANG LEI] I think that must
be why I feel a little lost.
[QIANG LEI]
What...
...is this presence I feel?
[QIN SOLDIER 30A]
Hey, you! Who are you?
[QIN SOLDIER 30B]
A Zhao soldier?
What are you doing there?
What unit are you with?!
Halt! State your affiliation!
[WEI DAO]
Is something wrong, Xin?
Xin!
[QIANG LEI] What I'm sensing,
is it a Chi You?!
No... it's different...
Similar, but
different somehow...
[QIANG LEI]
Don't tell me it's...
[QIN SOLDIER 30E]
E-Enemy attack!
It's an enemy attack!
[XIN] Darn, I knew it!
[XIN]
Hey! Which unit went down?
How many hostiles?!
[QIN SOLDIER 30F]
The one over that hill!
Sounds like the
watch team got wiped out
before they could even signal!
[XIN] What?!
[SOLDIERS muttering quietly]
[XIN] There's no enemy army?
[XIN] That whole unit
of guardsmen is dead, but...
...where did the enemy go?!
Did they run because
the rest of us came?
[QIANG LEI]
No. They're still here.
The commotion made me
lose track of them,
but they're still somewhere
in this campground.
[QIANG LEI] Where?
Maybe someone hit the
warning gong by mistake, no?
I'll go and take a look.
It is totally quiet
down there, though.
[SHAN HE]
Wh-Who the heck are you?!
[SOLDIERS yelling in pain]
[WEI PING] No way...
Shan He and his team...?!
This can't be happening!
[WEI PING] Who is he?!
[CHONG YUAN] Everybody run!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[YUAN]
I have to go help them! Now...
What am I doing?
I'm a lieutenant!
Our men are all dying!
[YUAN] Xin!
[XIN] We were just laughing it
up together a few minutes ago!
This can't be happening!
[LONG YOU] Who exactly is he?
[WEI DAO] Just looking at him...
[WEI PING]
I can't stop shivering!
[PANG NUAN] I'm an act of God,
a natural disaster,
and all of you here...
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[PANG NUAN]
...were simply unlucky.
Run, guys!
You Yi!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[FEI XIN SOLDIER 30E]
Someone help!
[YUAN] Everyone, run in
different directions! Scatter!
I-I can't talk...
I can't move my legs...
Sir!
[YUAN] At this rate,
the Fei Xin Force will die!
What are you idiots doing?!
Stand up!
[ZE GUI] Wei Ping, stand up!
M-My legs won't work now!
Hurry, Brother!
[WEI PING]
Run, you two!
[WEI PING] Xin!
Idiot, how dare you do this!
[XIN] I am not giving you an
easy death, that's for sure!
He's gonna fight...
Of course he is. He's Xin.
But, uh...
Don't do it, Commander!
You can't beat him!
[yelling]
That Xin is just amazing!
Stand.
[XIN]
Don't you look down on me...
X-Xin...
[XIN]
Don't worry at all, guys!
He's gonna be
the one to die!
[XIN] What?
[XIN] A guy that big,
dodging Qiang Lei's sword?!
Oh.
It would seem thou
art the one who called me.
What the heck does he mean?!
[PANG NUAN]
Thou mayst be a child,
but I'll still taketh thy life.
[XIN] What's with all the
crazy talk you keep spewing?!
And who in the world do you
think you are, anyway?!
Our camp's got
over 20,000 men,
and you rush in alone
and start killing everyone...
[XIN] Are you a Zhao soldier?
If you are,
what's this one-man raid
supposed to achieve?!
[XIN] No, wait a minute--
He did say Qiang Lei
called him...
[QIANG LEI] I don't remember
calling for anyone like you.
[PANG NUAN]
Thine existence called to me,
independent of thy will.
The savage god
lurking within me now
will permit no other strong
ones to exist around me.
[QIANG LEI]
Who exactly are you?
I am Pang Nuan, god of war.
[XIN] "God of war"?
What you talked about
before Qiang Lei?
Pang Nuan?
Did he just say Pang Nuan?
Pang Nuan, you say?!
But Pang Nuan,
he is the man...
That's the name of Zhao's
commanding general!
I don't care!
I don't care if he's a god
of war or whatever he says!
[XIN] This guy killed Shan He
and Xie Ci and Fa Jian
and all the others!
He's gotta pay!
Time to take revenge,
Qiang Lei!
Of course.
They have him
on two sides...
They're gonna take him
on together?!
Let's join 'em!
Don't do it!
We'd get in the way.
The only support
we can give them
is to stay here
and watch their fight!
[QU HAI] But can they
really win alone?!
They're up against a monster!
If anyone can, it's Xin
and Qiang Lei! C'mon!
[WEI PING gasps]
No way! Even Qiang Lei?!
[QIANG LEI]
Pum, pa-rum. Pum, pa-rum.
[QIANG LEI] Pum, pa-rum.
Pum, pa-rum.
[XIN] If I start
running away now,
I haven't got
a prayer of being
the world's greatest general!
[NARRATOR] Go for
the split-second opening!
Stab the invincible man
with a hundred blades!
Next Time:
"The Power of Unity."