[LORD CHANGWEN]
Why did you respond
to Lord Changping's summons?
You've strenuously refused to
lead Qin's armies in the past.
What brought you here?
[WANG YI]
This surprised you?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
Of course it did!
What made you want
to fight, Wang Yi?
[WANG YI]
You remember MNyáng?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I see... That's right.
MNyáng is the castle you, I
and Liao once seized from Zhao,
and it is also where Liao fell.
That was a total nightmare.
I'd never believed Liao...
could be beaten.
[LORD CHANGWEN] Pang Nuan...
Who in the world
was that man?
[LORD CHANGWEN] No, let's not
talk about a dead man.
Is that it, you reckon?
You can't let another
kingdom have the land
where Liao's body lies?
[WANG YI]
Yes, something like that.
Lord Changwen,
I plan to bid farewell
to my identity as one
of King Zhao's...
six great generals.
Huh?!
[WANG YI] This battle
shall be at its conclusion.
"Conclusion"?
Then you have finally decided
to move on with the rest of us?
I have high hopes that
I will be able to as well.
[WANG YI chuckles]
[NARRATOR] On March
of the third year,
future Shi Huangdi's reign,
Commanding General
Wang Yi went to war.
Meanwhile, the infantrymen
heading for MNyáng...
[BATTALION COMMANDER 26A] We're
about to form five-man squads!
All corporals gather!
[WEI PING] Crap, they've
started making squads!
[WEI DAO]
But Xin's not here yet!
[WEI PING]
That dumbass brat!
Whoa!
So is everybody here?
[NARRATOR] The time:
The Spring &amp; Autumn
and Warring States periods.
The place: Qin.
Xin, a nameless boy,
met Zheng, a young King,
distinguished himself in battle,
and rose to the rank of
squadron commander.
In the midst of this,
the neighboring kingdom
of Zhao invaded,
and Qin faced
unprecedented crisis.
What manner of battle will Wang
Yi wage as commanding general?
And what growth
will Xin accomplish?
[DIAO] Are you sure
it's okay for us
to go visit the battlefield?
It is fine. I got
permission from my teacher.
We have the high commander's
seal of approval!
[DIAO gasps]
The Qin high
commander's?!
D-Don't tell me that
your teacher is...?!
Yep!
My teacher Lord Changping, is
one of LüBuwei's Four Pillars.
[DIAO screams]
[DIAO] Th-Then he's
with Zheng's enemies...
Oh, don't worry.
I don't really care about
what goes on between
the King and the Minister.
I just want to see the
battlefield and breathe its air,
that is all.
[DIAO]
Hey, Meng Yi.
[DIAO] We will win this war,
right?
There is no telling of
the war until it starts.
But I... hope we do.
[DIAO] Xin...
I'll tell you this right now:
This is no ordinary squadron!
It's a special one!
Sp-Special, he said?!
[XIN] That's right!
General Wang Yi himself told me
we are special forces
under his direct authority
and not under any larger unit!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Now I don't know any more than
you do about what that means,
or what we'll all be doing for
him or what his plan is exactly!
But I can say one thing:
If the general singled us
out from the others,
it's 'cause he'll give us a more
important fight than the others!
He might send us charging into
some really messed-up
fights, you see!
[WEI PING gasps, whimpers]
[XIN]
But that means... Heh!
...you can bet the glory
we score will be really huge!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Most of the men in this squad
are tough veterans who have
survived the She Gan Plain!
If we join forces, we can take
on any enemy that comes our way!
So listen up!
Those foolish Zhao warriors
wanna invade us, don't they?!
Well, we are all
gonna crush them!
And we will score ourselves
some glory bigger than Wei's!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[YUAN]
Xin is very good.
He won the whole unit's hearts
with his first pep talk.
Wow... is that really
the same old Xin?!
What the heck
happened to him?
Xin, you are...
Something has happened to that
brat since we last saw him.
Yes.
Next thing: I got permission
to have two second-in-commands
in our squad here!
The first one is Yuan there!
Good day, all!
[SOLDIERS] Sir!
Which one is the other one?
[XIN] Well, not here yet
it looks like.
[WEI PING] Huh?!
[XIN] But don't you worry!
We are very strong
even on our own!
[NARRATOR]
For Wang Yi's army,
the route from Xianyang to
MNyáng was a fifteen-day ride.
Meanwhile, Xin and
the marching infantry
were now nine days
away from MNyáng.
[snoring]
[WEI DAO] O-Ow...
[WEI DAO] What are
you grinning at,
all alone in the middle
of the night?
I-I'm not grinning.
[WEI DAO laughs]
Don't bother playing dumb.
You must be happy you've made
the squadron commander.
Of course I am.
You're the leader of
a hundred men after all.
Up until a year ago,
you were just Li Dian's servant
and the village
called you an idiot.
Now you command men
from that town.
That's really something,
you know.
The "idiot" part was
uncalled-for!
And Wei Ping was the
village idiot! Not me!
[WEI DAO laughs]
But we are happy,
too, you know.
[WEI DAO sighs]
How could we not be?
We're just mere hicks from
the middle of nowhere.
But one of us made
squadron commander!
My brother is even
bragging to people
in the next town about it!
"My sidekick made squadron
commander," he says.
[XIN laughs]
"Sidekick" my butt,
that dingbat.
You'll get to take the
first step as a leader.
Just don't get too fired up
and go rushing over our heads.
[XIN]
Ah, sure, no problem.
[NARRATOR] As they grew closer
to MNyáng, however,
word of the Zhao army began to
spread among the foot soldiers.
[SOLDIER 26A] Have you
heard about the Zhao?
[SOLDIER 26B] Yeah, they rounded
up everybody in the castle
they took and killed them all.
[SOLDIER 26C] I heard they
killed the old folks, women,
and even the babies.
Not one left alive!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIER 26D] The Zhao army
will go that far?
[SOLDIER 26A] Hey, so are
we headed for a death match
with them now?
[YUAN gasps]
This is bad.
Sir, their morale is dropping.
We can't win a battle like this.
Ah, dammit, what are
they scared about?
Will you listen up,
everybody?!
The Zhao are just
around the corner!
We are all gonna put them
to rout, and set the MNyáng free
from the siege so the castle's
waiting for our help now!
You all got that?!
[SOLDIERS groan, sigh]
These guys...
[low rumbling]
What is that sound?
H-Hey! Hey! Look behind us!
[SOLDIER 26F]
What is it?
[SOLDIER 26E] What?
[WEI PING gasps]
[WANG YI] All troops...
[WANG YI] ...forward!
[SOLDIERS roar]
[XIN] You did this
with one sentence?
Only you, General Wang Yi!
[NARRATOR]
Qin's soldiers' spirits rose
when Wang Yi took the field.
But that night, disquieting
news reached the capital.
[MINISTER 26A]
I have a report!
We've finally discovered who's
commanding Zhao's forces.
[LÜ BUWEI] Hm?
Who is it? Speak now.
[MINISTER 26A]
Yes, his name is Pang Nuan.
[LI SI]
Pang Nuan?
[LORD CHANGPING] I've never
heard of him. Who is he?
[MINISTERS murmur]
[gasping]
[LORD CHANGWEN whimpers]
What is it, Lord Changwen?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
P-Pang Nuan?!
Impossible... That can't be!
But he died!
He was killed...
nine years ago by Wang Yi...
Wang Yi...
[XIN grunting]
Huh...?
[XIN]
Wrapped up your business?
[QIANG LEI] No.
The enemy left Wei for Zhao.
[XIN] So I guess you'll
join the fight again
to get to Zhao, huh?
[QIANG LEI]
I suppose so.
[XIN] Okay! Now my squadron's
truly complete at last.
Looking forward to working
with you, Qiang Lei!
[QIANG LEI]
Lu Sui...
Lu Sui is on edge.
[QIANG LEI]
This will be a harsh battle.
Heh! That suits me fine.
Anyway, now that you've drawn
and shown me all that moves,
the "pum pa-rum" thing you do,
I really wanna learn it!
[QIANG LEI sighs]
[QIANG LEI] You are still
an idiot aren't you, Xin?
What?!
[QIANG LEI] The Chi You turned
the power of its priestesses
to soothe the savage gods
into a battle technique.
In a state of rapture, we dance.
We slash through
the enemies around us.
It's a technique of exorcising
gods via our bodies.
It's not something
anyone can imitate.
Uh, g-gods, huh?
You know, I don't really get it,
but it's kind of unfair
if only your people have
gods on your side...
The Chi You aren't
the only ones.
And there are some even
more fearsome than that...
Those who do not
exorcise savage gods--
Those who carry
gods within them.
Carry gods... within them?
[QIANG LEI] We simply
call them "gods of war."
"Gods of war"...
Pang Nuan killed Liao,
one of the six great generals
[LÜ BUWEI] I was told that Liao
fell victim to an illness.
Is that not right,
Lord Changwen?
[LORD CHANGWEN] The illness was
a story that was fabricated
by Wang Yi and me.
Liao was killed
by Pang Nuan.
That's the truth of it.
[gasping]
[LÜ BUWEI] And what
sort of general is...
this Pang Nuan you speak of?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
He is not a general.
[LÜ BUWEI] He's not?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Truthfully, I
know almost nothing of the man,
but I can say one thing:
He is absolutely not the sort to
lead people as a general does.
[LORD CHANGWEN] He is a man
completely apart.
No, he is more...
He's a terrifying
crystallization...
of pure warfare!
[LORD CHANGWEN] Nine years ago,
he appeared all alone
in the center of a
100,000-man Qin army.
Halt, you there!
These are the
general's quarters!
Stop and state
your name and affiliation!
Men, take aim!
[GUARDS scream]
[screaming continues]
[gasping]
So, all by himself, you say he
broke through the battle array
that was protecting
the commanding general?
[LORD CHANGPING] One man
demolishing an army
is something that
can never happen.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
And yet it did happen.
Pang Nuan single-handedly
demolished it,
then killed Liao when
he tried to stop him.
What happened to
Pang Nuan after?
[WANG YI yells]
[LORD CHANGWEN] He was cut by
Wang Yi who rushed to the scene.
I've never seen Wang Yi
in such a fit of passion,
not before or since.
[LÜ BUWEI] Wang Yi
cut down Pang Nuan...
But then, Pang Nuan lived after
you thought he'd died,
and now those same men are
about to face each other
as opposing generals.
That's too much
of a coincidence.
[LORD CHANGWEN]
I imagine that Wang Yi knew
from the very beginning...
And that's why he really agreed
to be the commanding general.
This battle between them was
carved into their destinies
nine years ago.
[ZHENG] Wang Yi must've
lost many brothers in arms
over the years.
Why did he choose
this time to act?
Because they were
members of the six?
No...
Was Liao... special to Wang Yi
in some way then?
One thing
doesn't make sense.
You say Pang Nuan attacked
Liao's headquarters
nine years ago.
Why would he do that then?
It's a reckless plan
for the Zhao army,
However powerful Pang Nuan
might be in reality.
[LORD CHANGWEN] It had nothing
to do with the Zhao army.
[LI SI] Say what?
What do you mean?
[LORD CHANGWEN] Pang Nuan
was not a Zhao soldier.
He attacked Liao purely for
personal reasons, you see.
[LORD CHANGPING]
A personal grudge?
[LORD CHANGWEN]
No, not a personal grudge.
[LORD CHANGPING]
How can you be so sure?
Because I heard it from
the man himself once.
[PANG NUAN] Soldiers, armies,
Qin, and Zhao:
These are nothing but
trivialities to me.
All that matters is that
at this very moment,
there are two beings
in this land
who cause even the
heavens to feel fear.
There is another here
other than myself.
That I can't let stand.
[PANG NUAN] I am Pang Nuan,
god of war!
Show thyself, mine enemy!
What did you say?
I don't understand!
[LI SI] The man seems to be
beyond the pale!
I agree it was truly insane.
But that is the man
known as Pang Nuan.
Mhm-mhm, he sounds like
a really fascinating man.
But as you said earlier,
Lord Changwen,
he certainly does not
seem like the sort
to lead people when
you are at war.
So why is it he would become
Zhao's commanding general now?
[ZHENG]
Wang Yi...!
Pang Nuan accepted in
order to slay Wang Yi.
It is very possible,
your highness.
[WANG YI chuckles]
Hey, there she is!
Look guys, it's MNyáng!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
We need backup!
Give me your soldiers,
or we will--
[MMYÁNG SOLDIER 26B]
Hey, look!
There! Look at that!
[MMYÁNG SOLDIER 26A] Yes!
Look, it's our reinforcements!
[MMYÁNG SOLDIERS cheer]
[MENG YI]
Hurry, Diao!
[DIAO]
What is this place?!
Oh good, we are on time!
[DIAO] Whoa! We can see the
whole battlefield from here!
[MENG YI] Both armies have begun
making their formations.
All troops...
advance to the right!
[GENERAL 26A]
Advance to the right!
Don't leave any gaps!
Stick tight to the
squads around you!
Form lines abreast now!
[NARRATOR] A calm but fleeting
moment of quiet passes.
The men's feelings interplay
along with their lives.
Right now.
Wang Yi and Pang Nuan...
After nine years, the two
confront each other once more.
What do they feel inside?
Is it hatred? Ambition? Or...?
[NARRATOR]
The fated battle now begins!
[XIN] My squadron will
take on that mission now!
[NARRATOR] They plow straight
ahead, without wavering.
That is their strength.
Next Time:
"The FeiXin Force Is Born."