[DR. GERO YELLS]
Y-You beasts...!
You're worse than dogs!
At least they
obey their masters!
[DR. GERO YELLS]
Curse you!
I gave you both life!
[NARRATOR]
Doctor Gero met
his untimely doom
at the hands of
one of his own offspring!
But even though his
life was snuffed out,
his twisted
brilliance lived on!
Unknown to the world above,
a super computer was
diligently working to realize
the Doctor's dark dream--
to create the ultimate,
indestructible android
killing-machine!
♪ opening song ♪
[CROWD CHATTERS]
[KRILLIN] Hey, will
you guys save my place?
I have to go to the bathroom!
[OOLONG]
Nope! Forget it!
You leave, you go to
the back of the line!
[ROSHI YAWNS]
Boy! Uhh! I'm tired!
Yeah! Well,
my feet hurt!
Maybe this wasn't
such a brilliant idea!
I don't think I can
last three more hours!
We might as
well just go home!
Take it easy
there, big guy!
You're in pole position!
You can't give in now!
Be strong!
No whimp is going to get front
row seats at this pageant!
This is the
best in the world!
Rare beauties from
every corner of the globe...!
[ROSHI LAUGHS]
[ROSHI]
Miss Spain, Miss Russia,
Miss France...! Walkin' in
their underpants...! Heh, Heh...
Australia won't fail ya!
[ROSHI]
Eeh, hee, hee!
Now you've got it!
That's the spirit!
[ROSHI AND OOLONG LAUGH]
Enough...!
Control yourselves, you two!
This is ridiculous!
Let's set a good
example here!
Oh...! Well, uh,
don't worry about me, guys!
Well, some of us are
here for noble reasons!
Eh...?
Noble...?
Oh!
Wife hunting! Yeah!
Well, whatd'ya say?
Do you think I can
score a wife here?
I mean not the winner of course,
it could be just a runner-up!
Or hey I'm not picky it
could be the unlucky one
who comes in dead last!
Dry your tears mademoiselle!
Krillin is here to
take away your pain!
Hey! Just joking...!
I don't need to
go for the losers!
We Martial Artists are
like chick magnets...!
We just stand in one place
and let the hotties come to us!
Oh! Well, stand here then!
We are going to go peek in
the dressing room! Come on!
Don't lose our place
in line, Krillin!
Hey! No way!
Get your own seats!
Uhh! Sorry,
Trunks! Gotta go!
Please, keep our
place in line!
Huh...? Krillin...?
How did I get
stuck with this?
I should have
stayed with Goku!
Shopping couldn't be
this bad, could it?
[SHOPPERS YELL]
[CHICHI] Give me that!
I had it first! Get back!
Check it out!
It looks like
that mud wrestling
I showed you on TV
once, remember?!
Mom says she loves
to shop so much
because it's
a stress reliever!
I wonder if it works?
[CHICHI]
Goku! Stop daydreaming!
[GOKU YELLS]
[CASHIER LAUGHS AND APPLAUDS]
[GOKU BREATHES HEAVILY]
We've got quite
a stack here!
Are we done?
No! Now it's your turn!
It's over Goku!
You can't wear that same
outfit every day of the year!
We're buying you some
brand new clothes!
[GOHAN LAUGHS]
[EXPLOSION]
[CROWD YELLS]
[WOMAN 1]
Oh, my gosh!
Ahhh...!
[MAN RUNNING]
Call an ambulance!
W-W-Wait! Don't hang up! Ahh!
[WOMEN SCREAM]
[CROWD GASPS]
[SIREN WAILS]
[COPS YELL]
[EXPLOSION]
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
[ANDROID 14]
Is that the place?
[ANDROID 15]
I dunno! Let me see!
Yeah! That's the place.
So how'd you guys figure out
that you had the wrong day?
[KRILLIN]
Well,the pageant was supposed
to start in five minutes
and we were the only
ones standing in line!
I can't believe we stood
there for six hours!
Well, we built stamina
for tomorrow!
[CROWD CHATTERS]
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
Stop right there!
Ahhh!!!
[CHICHI]
Some things
never change!
[COUPLE LAUGHS]
[LADY]
Oh! What...?
[PATRONS]
Huh...? Oh!
[PATRONS YELL]
[EXPLOSION]
[GOKU] Gohan! You need
to have more food, son!
You're a growing boy!
You can't eat
enough at your age!
[GOKU SLURPS HIS DRINK]
I don't know, Dad!
If I had any more food,
I think I'd pop!
If you ever
stop training,
your muscle's going
to turn to flab
and you're going to get obese
from all the food that you eat!
[GROUP LAUGHS]
[BELL RINGS]
[EXPLOSION]
[ANDROID 15] No!
Please! Don't get up!
Excuse me! Do you
have free refills here?
[GOKU LAUGHS]
[GOHAN]
Oh, uhh, Dad...?
I don't think we're supposed
to yell like that in here!
Time for the last course!
Let's serve it up good!
[DISHES RATTLE]
[TRUNKS]
Either I've had too much
coffee or the room's shaking!
[WOMAN 1]
Is it an Earthquake?
[MAN 1]
I guess so!
What is it, Dad?
[KRILLIN YELLS IN PAIN]
[CROWD YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
Hold me tight, son!
I'm not used to this!
[CROWD YELLS]
[GOKU THINKING]
What a terrible mess...!
That was no ordinary bomb!
That was an energy blast!
But who's behind it?
I can't sense anything!
[SIREN WAILS]
[GOKU YELLS]
Gohan! Get your mother
out of here right now!
Krillin! Trunks!
Get those people as far away
from here as possible!
Hurry! What are
you waiting for? Go!
[CHICHI] Oh, no!
My new shoes! Go back!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU] Company...!
[GOKU THINKING]
Just as I thought!
It's me they're after!
All right!
Who are you guys?
Red Ribbon, eh...?
Now I know why I can't
sense your life force!
You two aren't organic!
[COMPUTER WHIRRING SOUND]
[GOKU]
I hate to say it,
but the quality has really gone
down since the last models! Man!
Gero must
be getting old!
[COMPUTER WHIRRING SOUND]
[COMPUTERIZED BEEP]
Heh...
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GOKU] Huh...?
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[WORKERS YELL]
Ah...!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU YELLS]
[ANDROID 15]
Who blasted my blast?!
Get away from him!
Trunks! Stay back!
[GOKU YELLS]
[TRUNKS] Huh...?
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
Hey! Goku!
It's no good down here!
At this rate,
we'll bring the whole city down!
Let's book it before this
thing gets out of hand!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GOKU]
Got it! Let's go!
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
[KRILLIN]
What are those guys?
[GOHAN]
They're evil! That's what...!
We can't just stand here,
Krillin! We've gotta help!
Yeah, but how...?
We wouldn't last two
seconds against guys like that!
Face it! We're outclassed!
So what...?
That doesn't mean that we can't
find some way to help out!
Right...? I'm going...!
[CHICHI]
Hold it right there!
[KRILLIN]
Uh, ohh...!
Have you forgotten what
tomorrow is, young man?
It's your first day
of summer school!
Mother...!
Don't you
"but mother" me!
You promised that you'd
spend the summer studying!
Now, what's more
important to you Mom?
My studies or the
life of your husband?!
[CHICHI GASPS]
[CHICHI]
Gohan! No! Wait...!
Don't you dare leave
while I'm talking to you!
You get back here this instant!
[CHICHI YELLS]
Gohan...?
You know what...?
He's right! I'm behind
Gohan one hundred percent!
Then what are
you waiting for?!
[OOLONG YELLS]
Get your cowardly butt
up there and help him!
One hundred percent...!
I'll give you one
hundred percent!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
Krillin!
Be careful, buddy!
Hmm...!
Its just fate...!
Let's face it, Krillin!
You're destined
to die all alone!
[COMPUTER WHIRRING SOUND]
[COMPUTER]
Number Thirteen!
You are now complete!
Awake! Awake my son!
I am Doctor Gero!
[ANDROID 13]
Goku...
[GOKU] If it's me you want, then
that's what you're going to get!
Let's go!
You two don't know what
you're getting yourselves into!
[ANDROID 15]
Oh we don't, huh?
Heh, heh, heh...!
[COMPUTER WHIRRING SOUND]
I know you're Trunks!
[ANDROID 15 LAUGHS]
[GOKU] Trunks!
Are you all right?!
[GOKU YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[ANDROID 15]
I think he's had enough!
Huh...?
No! Goku!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13]
Now, I can't believe
that the great Goku
is catchin' a whoopin'
from those boys!
If he can't even
handle the Indians,
why bring out the Chief?
Huh...?
You're an Android too?
Aw man! How many of you
did Doctor Gero create?
Well not that it's any
of your business, city boy,
but the good doctor met
his end some time ago!
We were created by
Doctor Gero's computer!
Now his computer
is trying to kill me?
[ANDROID 13]
That's right!
This particular computer
has been programmed
to think that it
is Doctor Gero!
It's down there
scheming and planning--
trying to realize its
number one ambition
which is to see you dead!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
I know! I know!
We should all just let
bygones be bygones
but that's aint
the way it's gonna be!
I was programmed
to kill you, boy...
...and that's exactly what
I'm gonna do! You hear?
You're just a slave!
A pawn with no free will
of it's own! Is that it?
Free will...!
Pitiful humans...!
War! Segregation! Hatred...!
Is that what you've done
with your free will, boy?
Don't you lecture me with
your thirty-dollar haircut!
Goku dies!
We'll see,
you Red Ribbon red-neck!
Hmm, hmm, hmm...!
Yes, we will!
We sure will!
Go get 'im, boys!
Krillin...?
Let's get 'em!
Right!
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[KRILLIN]
Man. I don't know
about this, Gohan.
What...?
What's the matter?
We wouldn't last ten
seconds in fight like that!
I think we'd
better wait!
Number Thirteen...!
That's your unlucky number!
And I ain't talkin' about no
silly superstition, city boy!
I'm talkin' about
yours truly--Big Thirteen.
I don't care
what you're called,
taking other peoples'
lives is wrong...
...and I won't stand for it!
[GOKU YELLS]
[GOKU GRUNTS]
Father! No...!
Gohan...! Wait...!
There's nothing we
can do about it right now!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
[LOUD THUD]
[KRILLIN] Ow...
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
Ah...!
[TRUNKS YELLS]
This is not good!
Yeah...!
Huh...?
[ANDROID 13]
Well, I'll be...!
[GOKU YELLS]
Dang it boy, shoot...
How did a scrawny
little guy like you
withstand a
blast like that?
[GOKU YELLS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[ANDROID 14] Let's go!
[ANDROID 15]
Shut up and give me a hand!
[WIND BLOWS HEAVILY]
Huh...?!
Ah...!
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS GASPS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 14]
Little boys shouldn't
play with knives.
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
Huh...?
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS GASPS]
[GOKU YELLS]
Huh...?
Look out, Dad...!
Wait...!
No not again!
[KRILLIN GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13]
He's plum loco if he's meaning
to catch that with
his bare hands!
That boy's been out in the sun
without his hat on
for way too long!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU YELLS]
[ANDROID 15]
Say man! Check it out!
[ANDROID 14]
Yeah...!
Ah...! Vegeta...!
Dad! It's you...!
[VEGETA] Let me
make one thing clear!
I didn't come here out of
the goodness of my heart!
I will helped you
because I want you alive!
So I can have my shot
at destroying you!
And no junkyard robot trash
is going to take that
chance away from me!
Hmm...! We're not
programmed to kill you,
but we'll be glad to oblige!
Hey, Fifteen...!
Take care of this guy!
[COMPUTER]
Identity confirmed!
Analysis complete!
[COMPUTER WHIRRING SOUND]
Hmm...?! Heh-heh-heh...
[ANDROID 15 GRUNTS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[ANDROID 13] Time for an
old fashioned butt whoppin'.
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[OMPUTER] Kill...!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13]
Yeeehaa...!
Mmm...!
[ANDROID 13]
I know you ain't ready to
start pushin' up daisies yet!
Come on, son! I was
just now getting warmed up!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13 GRUNTS]
[GOKU] You still don't
know what you're up against!
You're on a path leading
to your own destruction!
Hmm...
[ANDROID 14 GRUNTS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[ANDROID 15] Huh?
Hey! Where'd that
grin go? Little man...?
[VEGETA YELLS]
[VEGETA SCREAMS]
[ANDROID 15 SCREAMS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[GOKU YELLS]
[LOUD CRASH]
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13]
What's the matter, boy?
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh!
Not a thing...!
[GOKU YELLS]
Check it out, Krillin!
Incredible...! Look! It's a
Super Saiyan triune, Gohan!
[COMPUTER]
Analyzing power increase!
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[ANDROID 15]
Okay! Let's dance.
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[COMPUTER]
Analyzing...!
Check it out...!
Yeah...! Goku...!
Huh...? Aaaah...!
[KRILLIN YELLS FRANTICALLY]
Ah... Soothing... Ah...
Hold on, Dad...!
Gohan! No! Don't...!
[GOHAN GRUNTS]
Wait...!
Don't do it, Gohan!
[GOHAN YELLS]
Uhh...
Gohan...! No!
[GOHAN GRUNTS]
Thanks, Piccolo!
Huh...? Piccolo's here?
[GOHAN] Yeah!
I'm pretty sure it's him!
[GOKU] Piccolo...!
Hey! What's up?
I was right! Look, Krillin!
Piccolo...!
[ANDROID 13 YELLS]
Glad you could
make it! Thanks!
[PICCOLO]
Don't sweat it, Goku!
Just so happens I was
in the neighborhood.
[ANDROID 13]
Hey, mean green!
It's Goku we want!
So if you want to live,
just high tail it
outta here right now!
Same old,
unhealthy obsession...!
Same old foul,
one-track programming...!
[VEGETA YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
Hmm, hmm, hmm...!
Haaa...!
[VEGETA YELLS]
[VEGETA GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 15 LAUGHS]
Heh... Heh... Heh...
[BUZZING]
[EXPLOSION]
[ANDROID 14 YELLS]
[ANDROID 13]
Huh...?
[VEGETA LAUGHS]
Inferior craftsmanship
to say the least!
Fourteen and Fifteen
have been destroyed?!
Mmm...!
[ANDROID 13 LAUGHS SLOWLY]
[ANDROID 13]
How sweet it is!
Ha, ha, ha!
[ANDROID 13 GRUNTS]
[ANDROID 13 LAUGHS]
[ANDROID 13]
I feel great!
[VEGETA YELLS]
Vegeta! No!
I've got him, Kakarot!
He's all mine!
[VEGETA GRUNTS]
What the...?!
[VEGETA STAMMERS]
[SUPER 13]
Going down anyone?!
Hold on, father!
[VEGETA YELLS]
Vegeta!
Why do these things
always happen to me?
This is messed up!
Oh, man...!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU YELLS]
Help me!
Daddy! Lookout...!
[GOKU SCREAMS IN THE DISTANCE]
Don't die, Kakarot!
You're mine!
[GOKU SCREAMS]
[GOKU YELLS]
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU LAUGHS]
[SUPER 13 YELLS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
Father...!
[GOHAN]
He'll drown!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
[KRILLIN YELLS FRANTICALLY]
Darn mosquitoes...!
[KRILLIN YELLS WORRIEDLY]
[GOHAN] No!!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
Leave him alone!
Mmmm...!
[GOKU THINKING]
I can't...
Please! Lend me
your energy! I beg you!
[BIRDS CHIRP]
Huh...? Oh...!
Hmm...
Uh... Ah...
[SUPER 13 LAUGHS SLOWLY]
[SUPER 13]
You're very brave little one!
Too bad you have to die!
[GOHAN]
Stay away from me!
[SUPER 13]
Hmm, hmm, hmm...!
Huh...?
[GOHAN]
Father...!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[SUPER 13 GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[GOHAN]
Look out, Dad!
[GOHAN YELLS]
Mountains...!
Great oceans and seas...!
Vast lands of the Earth...!
Please, lend me... your energy!
[SUPER 13]
Hmm...?
Oh, you Android freak...!
Don't even think about it!
Kakarot's mine! Back off!
[VEGETA SCREAMS]
That's it! Keep it coming!
It's working!
[TRUNKS]
Goku! The Spirit Bomb...!
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS SCREAMS]
[COMPUTER]
Danger! Danger!
Huh...?
[SUPER 13]
I know all about your
Spirit Bomb, Goku!
You need more time, which is
something you don't have!
[SUPER 13 YELLS]
[SUPER 13]
Let go of me! Aaaaah!
[PICCOLO YELLS]
[GOKU YELLS]
Huh...? Whatd'ya know?!
He transformed!
That means he's pure!
Even as a Super Saiyan!
[GOKU YELLS]
[GOKU SCREAMS]
[SUPER 13]
What are you doing?
[SUPER 13 GRUNTS]
[SUPER 13 YELLS]
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[GOKU YELLS]
[SUPER 13] You must die!
Goku... must... die!
[GOKU GRUNTS]
[COMPUTER] Goku must die!
Goku... must... die!
Uhh... Huh...?
[GOHAN LAUGHS]
What's up, Dad?
Me...!
[GOHAN AND GOKU LAUGH]
Well, we would have been
if it haven't been for Goku!
That was so awesome!
He was brighter than the sun
when he absorbed
all that energy!
It was incredible!
I didn't think his body
would hold it! Did you...?
As a matter of fact,
no I didn't.
Hey, Krillin!
You got a good shot in!
[KRILLIN] Heh heh! Yeah,
I-I guess I did! Didn't I?
What'd you do?
Kick him in the can
and then run...?
Why you...!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
[EVERYONE LAUGHS]
Gohan...!
As soon as you're well,
it's time for summer school!
Uhh... Uh-Uh...
Ow! My leg hurts!
[EVERYONE LAUGHS]
[GOHAN] Krillin! Don't mention
Senzu Beans whatever you do!
[KRILLIN] Don't worry!
I want to be hurt!
I think the nurse
is kind of cute!
Is it over...?
Not 'til the
fish jumps...!
It's over...
♪ closing song ♪