That's the Koro alarm!
Who knew something like this
was hidden within the Church?
The tricky part now is that it
can only be used one time...
Take down the castle!
Concentrate on the keep!
Why didn't we see them coming?
How could we, sir? It's as if
they appeared out of thin air.
What could they be after?
The keep!
We're lucky,
if not for the race,
we might've all been killed...
You have my thanks, Kenshi.
You're welcome?
We have some
Sacred Mechanoids
in the Forest
practice grounds...
That should buy us
the time we need
for the civilians to escape.
All right, let's move out...!
No casualties, understood?!
Yes, sir!
Burn it all to the ground!
Nothing walks out
of there alive!
We've had enough
of your games!
You Mest bastard!
King Shurifon?!
Curse you!
How did you escape?!
Aw, what's wrong?!
I'll show you!
Evacuations are at sixty
percent in the east district!
Seventy-five percent
for the north and south!
I think I should help.
Please don't...
We simply cannot allow a
guest to be put in harm's way.
Among Mechamasters, my
father is one of the best...
so there is no need
for you to worry.
Come on, boy...!
Is that all you've got? !
No, not at all...
Take this!
You can't defeat me
in a test of might.
It can't be...
A Black Sacred Mechanoid.
Doll...
He's all yours!
Be careful!
That one is different
from the others!
I've never seen
anything like this!
And you won't again.
Father!
Quickly, Kenshi...
Save him!
The shock from that hit
paralyzed its nerve system.
It's Kenshi!
Right on time!
It's him. It's, so...
so... beautiful.
Make a run for it!
Good luck!
Doll.
I've gotta do something
about that shield.
Dagmyer...
We've wiped out most of
the city's infrastructure...
Shurifon is finished.
Well...
That was easy.
All that's left is
to finish him off!
Doll, try to keep
him pinned down!
That's what you
get for butting in!
You idiot...
Get out of my way!
Her shield's so strong...
If that trick didn't work, I
don't think anything's going to!
What an incredible attack...
Even if my shield
can withstand it,
there's no way
my frame will!
Here we go!
This is bad.
Kenshi...!
Pull back!
Princess Aura?
We've evacuated everything.
My father and the other Sacred
Mechamasters are all safe.
On my way!
Doll... Go after him
right now...! Move it!
I see.
A black Sacred Mechanoid
is unable to use the Shield
of Gaia to its fullest.
It's my fault, I'm
sorry I wasn't stronger.
Don't take it all on yourself.
We're safe in this
forest for now.
Yeah, but-
Kenshi, you fought
valiantly back there...
I would be honored if you
would marry my daughter.
In battle, you demonstrated
what your true quality is...
You're a fine man...
In every respect I find
you worthy to be my heir.
What wonderful news.
Kenshi belongs to us, King...
As such, it would be safe to
assume this entire country
will be ours as
well, correct?
Um... I'm
a bit confused.
Surely I'm not meant to take
her statement seriously?
Sorry to disappoint
you, but yeah.
When it comes to money, Empress
Lashara is never joking around.
Well... In that case,
all the repairs of the city
will be your
responsibility...
It's only fair. Babalun is
your Prime Minister, right?
What?!
You give us Kenshi, and we
give you the city as is...
Does that sound like
a reasonable trade?
Uh... We'll have to give
that some more thought.
Your Highness!
What's the matter?!
The Church and Havoniwa
have just been attacked!
This is a disaster!
We are currently disposing
of the teleportation ports
in all of the churches,
Your Eminence...
Unfortunately... some
of them are short on staff.
Give the world
leaders a full account
of what has transpired...
We need their aid!
But if we do that, we'll-
Gaia's already on the move!
If doubt about us begins to
fester it would be disastrous!
That last attack turned
Shtrayu and Shurifon
into shields for
the Holy Land...
If something were
to happen to Havoniwa,
executing our plans
would be nearly impossible.
It doesn't make sense.
How did Lord Babalun come
by all this information...?
Even if he does descend
from a long line
of Sacred Mechamechanics,
he knows far too much!
However disconcerting,
it does not change our plan.
Because this Mechamaster
intervened and suppressed Gaia,
there were no casualties...
from the King down
to the civilians.
No, wait...
Considering their
current location,
it would take them far too long
to rendezvous with the team.
Since he did stand toe-to-toe
with Gaia, as far as the enemy
is concerned, Gaia is the
only weapon they have
that can oppose the White
Sacred Mechanoid.
So we use him as a decoy?
Then we should send an
intelligence officer
to visit Lashara immediately!
This is awful!
Moments ago,
Havoniwa was attacked
by one of Babalun's lackeys!
A black
Sacred Mechanoid teleported
into an abandoned church...
It completely destroyed Havoniwa
Castle before disappearing!
This is a disaster...
We can never take
the Holy Land now.
Are we under attack?
What was that?
Switch the image to
display our headquarters!
That's where we keep
the supply transport.
Gaia has returned.
I assume you'll be leaving
with Empress Lashara.
Of course...
Lord Babalun needs
to be stopped immediately...
He has devastated
our capital...
Shurifon's answer
must be firm.
Or is it that you'd rather
spend time with your groom...
perhaps?
What...? No!
I can't tell you enough
how much I approve.
He's a great
reason to go...
Besides. You've got quite
a bit of competition.
Follow your heart
wherever it takes you.
Do you mean that?
Just don't lose.
Yes, sir.
Strength and
courage be with you!
Kenshi...!
Take care
of our Princess!
Now then... Let's prepare
for a counter attack!
Right!
So... What's the situation at
the Church's headquarters?
Well...
The good news is,
the Pope wasn't hurt in the
attack... And they were able
to maintain minimal
operability over their system.
But still...
Our usual sources
of intelligence
have no information.
All right. Then we
will stop in Havoniwa
on our way to
the Barrier Workshop.
But do you really
think that's wise?
Well, in the event that
we just so happen to get
into a big fight
with Lord Babalun,
we can do so without worrying
about disturbing other nations!
Can we really wage a war
in Princess Maria's land?
Yes... As a way
of paying homage,
we will have to leave
a flower by her grave.
You do realize you
don't actually know
if she's dead
yet, right?
It's a Church ship.
We can see right
through that camouflage.
What are those
idiots thinking?
Judging by their course...
I would guess they're planning
a rendezvous with the SWAN.
Um... Why don't we take
advantage of that?
Good idea...
Do it.
Leave them be.
Hey, how 'bout you
give it a rest, Dolly!
Don't lose sight
of that ship!
Lady Rea! Those are Lord
Babalun's Mechanoids!
I thought
they might show up.
Take out
the power reactor...
Just try to minimize the
damage when seizing the ship!
I'm all over it!
The engine has been hit...!
Power is starting to shut down!
Fire a distress signal, now!
It's a distress signal...
That Church ship needs help!
Chiaia...!
Kenshi!
Hurry...! Seize that ship
before they get here!
You've done well.
Surrender
as soon as I eject.
Yes, ma'am.
Heads up, you guys!
It's an escape pod!
Shoot it...
Take it down, now!!
No luck!
It's way too fast!
You idiots...
Now they know
what your plan is.
The ship is yours,
we surrender...!
Please cease-fire!
Kill them...
Kill them all.
We surrender.
The ship belongs to you!
They'd already surrendered!
Please, it's not like we
could take it with us.
Chiaia, I think something's
moving in our direction.
Whoa, what was that?
An escape pod!
... Hey, wait!
What is she doing?
That was close.
Kenshi...
Is anyone hurt?
No, she's just passed out.
Oh... Good.
Chiaia!
We confirmed
that there was an explosion
near the distress signal...
I need your help!
Got it...
I'm on my way...!
Kenshi, can you handle taking
her to the SWAN yourself?
Yeah...
No problem!
How are you feeling,
are you okay?
This place.
Is it the SWAN?
Lashara's ship?
It is.
I thought so.
Hey, maybe you
should lie down.
Ow...! No, please
stop...! No, really...
Well, I'm glad to know
that this isn't a dream.
I guess you're
feeling better then?
I'm perfectly fine...
I just passed out from shock.
I appreciate you
saving my skin...
Fainting was not
part of my plan.
My name's Rea Second, and I've
been sent here by the Church
to speak with
Empress Lashara.
I think we can arrange that...
But first could you maybe,
uh, let Kenshi go?
Oh... So sorry.
Also... Do you know what
happened to the ship I was on?
By the time we got there
it was already destroyed...
We were too late.
I understand.
Why does that
lady hate me?
This doesn't make sense.
Can you explain to us
why they want him now...?
We understand that
you were attacked...
But the Church hasn't lost
its ability to function, has it?
No, but that wasn't
Babalun's intention either...
If he had wanted to,
he could've taken us out...
The Church's Headquarters
and all our operational systems
were completely vulnerable
during the attack.
Babalun had other motives.
The attacks on Havoniwa,
Shurifon and the Church
were meant to send a message
to the other nations.
He's proved they can no longer
remain peaceful bystanders...
Not anymore, at least.
Yes.
Even if we destroy all of the
Church's teleportation units,
he's just going
to try something else.
If all the other nations
are using military forces
to defend their lands, they
won't have enough fighters
to launch a
successful invasion.
With the Holy Land's
three bordering nations
being used as a shield...
it would require an even
larger force than before.
Babalun's army may be small,
but it's extremely deadly...
Because he still has Gaia.
Gaia's the only weapon Babalun
has that can stand up to Kenshi,
but we can't let them
fight one-on-one...
Well, not yet.
Yes...
I am fully aware.
Sir Kenshi, or rather
his Sacred Mechanoid,
is not up to the task.
I think it's time for you to pay
a visit to the Barrier Workshop.
Have we received a report
from the liaison?
Unfortunately we have
not yet heard back
from anyone
we have sent.
I see...
And what of our
transmissions?
Both our headquarters
and broadcast systems
are inoperable...
If only SWAN
had a marker.
Well... Too bad...
We've no choice but
to continue with the plan.
No, we can't.
There simply isn't time
to debate this any further...
If we don't act now,
things could get much worse.
Do you have a second?
Sorry to interrupt...
but I'm just so happy,
I couldn't help myself...
You know...
We can't talk with you all
the way over there, can we?
No... Miss Second.
You can call me Rea
if you like.
Uh... Okay.
If it makes you
feel uncomfortable,
you don't have to.
Oh no... That's
not it exactly...
It's just... The thing is,
that's my mom's name too,
so it's kinda weird.
Is that so?
Nothin' against you,
or your name, I swear.
I understand... I would love
to hear about your mom sometime.
Okay.
Families have always
interested me...
Parents are our
link to the past,
and we're their
link to the future.
What about your dad? I bet
he was a pretty neat guy.
He's just a weird
old man, really.
I don't get it.
Do you and your father not
get along or something?
No, I love him...!
He's a funny guy.
Funny, huh...?
That's sweet.
Hey, if this conversation's
getting you down,
we can talk about
something else.
No, I'm all right...
I'm just a little
jealous, that's all.
Oh... sure.
Look what we have here.
Do you care to tell us
what you ladies are doing
hiding behind that tree?
Nothing.
Sure doesn't look like
nothing... It's not nice to spy.
And besides, Kenshi's only
trying to get some info.
Yeah, well, maybe that's
all we're trying to do, too.
Besides, how do you know
she's not here to kidnap him?
Oh, please...
a Male Sacred Mechamaster
is completely capable
of protecting himself.
That's exactly why we can't
let her get too close to him.
It's great that
our business with him
is prospering like this!
But what if the Church were
to take him away from you?
What would you do then?
Wait, what?
Generally speaking,
the summoner owns anyone they
bring from another world,
but in Kenshi's case
there is no summoner...
The long and short of it is...
it's up to Kenshi to decide
who he'll side with.
You see them, right?
I wonder what they're up to?
Beats me.
I'm very pleased you
could make it today.
Depending on your performance,
I will consider
making you ranking officers
in Shtrayu's army.
I'm expecting a lot
from all of you.
Keep your eyes
and ears open!
Are you sure
about this...?
The majority of them
are second-rate ronin
and money-hungry
bandits.
You got a problem
with bandits, girlie?
Because we're way better
than a twit like you,
that's for sure.
Bandits have
seen more combat,
and at the moment, that's
what I'm looking for...
But if I were you, I wouldn't
forget your place, Lan.
Yeah, yeah. You're
gonna use us like pawns...
But don't worry, I guarantee
you'll get your money's worth.
I can't thank you enough...
It was a big help...
I hear you did a
number on Havoniwa.
So does it feel
good being done
with that council
of idiots, Uncle?
Hey, watch
your mouth...
Or you're not gonna get the
gift I'm about to give you...
I've got some information
about a Male Sacred Mechamaster
who fled
from the Holy Land...
I can tell you
exactly where he is...
His name though...
I forget.
Ceres?
Yeah, that's it...
How did you know that?
Well, well. Looks like
luck's finally coming my way.
Havoniwa's
border's up ahead.
Let's all cross
our fingers
and hope they haven't
hijacked METEOR FALL.
What's METEOR FALL?
It's a defensive weapon that
protects the Havoniwa border.
Any bad guys who try to break
through will have to deal
with METEOR first...
If they cross the border
on a ship like so...
it drops a big boulder on them
from way up in the sky like BAM,
"Take that, bad guys!"
That's really
all it does?
Primitive. But its destructive
powers are tremendous...
Making the border quite
hard to penetrate.
That must be why the
Black Sacred Mechanoid
chose to teleport inside instead
of trying a frontal attack...
Going head-to-head with
METEOR FALL is way too risky.
Are there any ways around it?
This is the only
path large ships like ours
can pass through...
It's easier to keep an
eye on things that way.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Stupid old Maria, she is
about as smart as a Koro...!
The audacity of the
incompetent moron
to protect her country's border
with such a silly trap...
She is incomprehensible!
Empress...!
METEOR FALL is missing!
No...!
That can't be!
This is where METEOR
would normally stand.
Do you think
they destroyed it?
No way, there's
no debris at all.
At least we don't have to worry
about passing through, now.
Still. I should scout
out the area first.
Good idea... Kenshi, you
should go along with Aura!
Sure thing!
This is weird. I don't
see anything out here.
You're right...
I do not foresee any issues.
Look...
Over there!
Yet another place
has been destroyed.
Judging by this...
we doubt she is still alive.
Rest in peace,
cousin...
We will take your
country for ourselves
and rule it
in your place.
Slow down... We're not even
sure if Maria is dead yet.
Kenshi... I know that
old bag was fond of you.
I hope you're not
taking this too hard.
Flora might still
be alive, too.
Seriously, think about it:
How do we know Queen Flora
didn't flee this place
with Princess Maria?
Because our aunt is
extremely stupid...
She would not have
the sense to flee.
Right.
We've never been
here before...
It's kind of unusual...
The city doesn't seem
very residential, does it?
That's because civilians
didn't live in this area.
This was a government
district...
It used to be the heart and
soul of Havoniwa politics.
Oh, wow.
Increase speed now!
Not good.
They have got us cornered.
Uh-oh... Guys, look!
What's that?
That is METEOR FALL.
All right...
Let her rip, boys!
Our escape route
is blocked.
The SWAN will be
in big trouble
if we sustain
a direct hit from them.
Hey, but what about
all my buried crystals?!
Are you kidding
me right now?
Crystals...?
They'll be destroyed,
along with all of the SWAN.
I'll stop the
boulder dropper!
METEOR FALL is kept in the air
by the suspension systems
located on each
of the four legs.
So then there's a chance we
can escape if we destroy
at least one leg...!
Concentrate your attack!
No luck.
The stone
is far too thick...
In order to damage it,
we need to move in closer.
We can't... Any closer
and the Ena gets thin,
preventing our output
from working properly!
Plus, my Mechaworker
isn't supposed to be
up this high at all!
Do they really think I'll
let them destroy this...?
Give 'em a shot
across the bow!
You got it!
Chiaia...!
Look out!
If we don't do something,
the SWAN is done.
Yes, but what can we do?
Nearing target.
I'll be there soon.
Oh wow, this is the most
pathetic thing I've ever seen.
Come on, let's go
ahead and finish them.
METEOR FALL...
It's moving towards us!
Well...
this is unfortunate.
Whaddaya think,
Wahan? Ideas?
I sure wish I did...
But I don't.
Get closer... But how am
I supposed to do that?
Take 'em out, now!
Boss...! There's
something headed our way!
What...? Hurry up
and show it to me!
A Sacred Mechanoid?
Who's that?
I've reached my
operational limit.
You guys... The reactor
output's down...!
Let's go!
All right!
Is he going to compress
the entire boulder?
But we're
outside the draft!
Oh no!
At least we'll get
the SWAN. Oh no.
Hey, you saved
our lives...!
Thanks a lot.
Did they hurt you?
Yukine!
Where'd you come from?
I thought I recognized
your frame...
We're glad to see you.
Oh, thank goodness...
You're safe.
Good timing.
You just barely made it.
Dagmyer!
Wait, when did this happen...?
What happened to Cordyline?
No word yet... We lost
all contact with them.
You screwed up,
Mom... Way to go.
Oh, wow.
Welcome to Havoniwa's
underground city.
I'm so thrilled to see you
all here safe and sound.
You've had
quite a journey!
Great! We wasted a whole
bouquet of flowers over you...!
We'll be submitting an invoice
for that expense presently!
If it weren't for Yukine, those
flowers would've been for you,
and don't forget it!
Oh how nice. It really is great
to see them back together.
Yeah, and at least I don't have
to worry about her anymore.
Kenshi!
There you are, darling!
Long time no see, Flora.
Oh, that's right...
My apologies.
I have to call you Sir Kenshi
from now on, don't I?
I'll admit, never
in my wildest dreams
did I think you were
a Sacred Mechamaster.
Yeah...
Sorry for not
telling you earlier.
Please, I forgive you...
But only if you marry me.
Aunt Flora...! We need to
speak with you right now!
Maria!
Mother?
From this moment forward,
you're officially in command.
Me?
One day the fate of our country
will rest on your shoulders.
Get some practice.
Really?
Now. Where were we...?
Whaddaya say we leave the hard
stuff to these girls here.
And we go rekindle
that old flame! Let's go!
I see... The rumors
about this family are true.
Oh, good grief...!
Will someone stop her?!
The situation in the area
surrounding the Holy Land
is bad to say the least.
Yes, it is.
This is certainly
unfortunate news to receive.
Since the Church cannot be
relied upon to form an alliance,
we have no other choice
but to act ourselves.
Havoniwa
is no different
than any other nation
you've mentioned.
First and foremost, we must
protect our own borders.
The capital has already
been decimated...
And there's no guarantee
Babalun won't attack us again.
We-
We must determine how many
of our forces we can dedicate
to an offensive strike.
Defending our
borders matters...
But we can't sit by
and ignore this threat.
We should also evacuate
vulnerable areas...
And move those civilians
to a safer place.
If we do, we can dedicate
all our Sacred Mechanoids
to the cause.
The farms in the highlands are
a great place for the refugees.
Martial law has already been
declared in acceptable areas...
On your order we could begin
relocating them tomorrow.
Let's change the timetable for
the railway to the highlands.
If you're willing to give
the order, we could open up
our supply base as well.
Our opinion of Havoniwa
just improved quite a bit!
It's very different from where
you're from, that's for sure!
Yes, indeed, we're
not so selfish here...
We don't think only
of our own interests,
and flee for safety
after being attacked!
Now that is enough!
You have already reached
a resolution, haven't you...?
You set this whole
farce up just to gloat.
This is about more than
rubbing it in your face...
Before a resolution
is reached...
...there is much more
to be discussed...
The issue is
ownership of Kenshi.
No...! What?!
Of course... It all
makes perfect sense.
Indeed.
No way.
Kenshi is vital to
a Holy Land strike...
Depending on him, our military
strategy and line of authority
could change dramatically.
It is unclear who is allowed
to give him orders in combat.
At Shurifon, this
was left ambiguous.
But we must reach
a decision now.
Empress?
Everyone.
I'm sure Sir Kenshi needs
some time to think...
And we will
grant him that...
We will hear your
decision tomorrow morning.
Is that acceptable...?
Sir Kenshi?
Uh... Yeah,
all right.
Poor Lashara...
I hope she's okay.
Oh... Don't worry about her,
she's gonna be just fine.
Still... If Kenshi ends up
going a different way,
it has the real potential
to completely devastate her.
Getting Kenshi was like
striking gold, but now,
all of a sudden, she's on
the brink of losing everything.
Please, Empress...
Could you at least
eat one bowl of soup?
Maybe she's asleep?
Let's give her space and
leave her be for a while.
Can I talk to you?
Okay.
At any rate, there's no
point standing in the hall
like a bunch of morons.
Let's go.
Yeah, you're right...
This isn't something you can
decide at the drop of a hat,
it's a big decision.
But. I can tell by
the look on your face
that you still
don't have a clue...
You've got friends,
so go ask them. Who knows?
Maybe they can help.
You're wavering?
This is the type
of decision
that you must
make for yourself...
Just know wherever you choose
to go, I will be right there.
You should do whatever
makes you the happiest.
Follow your heart
and you can't go wrong!
Do whatever you want to,
we just want you to be happy,
that's all...
Right...?
Yukine?
Or... Follow
your instincts
and do what gives
you the most pleasure.
By that I mean, pick me!
Mother, stop!
You're not being helpful,
not even a tiny bit!
Kenshi...
What's important now is not
to ask, "What should I do?"...
That's nothing...
Instead, just ask,
"What do I want?"
You should have said
that to begin with,
then maybe everyone wouldn't
call you the Horny Queen.
They do?
What do I want? Huh.
Hey, there she is.
Empress Lashara!
Oh, you big idiot!
You realize this is exactly why
Lithia calls you a wild animal.
What are you doing
out here so late?
Looking at...
the moon.
That's amazing...
Actually, it reminds me of
another full moon I saw once.
It's gorgeous. Sometimes
life gets so crazy,
it's easy to forget how
beautiful this world really is.
So, have you made
up your mind?
I'm getting close, but
I haven't had the chance
to hear you out yet.
You should decide
for yourself...
Isn't that what
everybody else told you.
Well, yeah...
That is sorta how it went.
We have nothing
to say to you then...
No!
Nothing at all.
Even though we're
still very young,
childhood never
really happened for us.
To become royalty, childish
things were sacrificed...
And for what?
We didn't do anything
to earn what we are today.
Nothing...
We did not choose or ask
to be born into this life...
Like a flower
forced to bloom,
but having no clue
how to survive.
Please don't leave.
We're begging you not to go.
When I first came to
this world... I was alone.
But then you took me in and
you gave me a real home...
and I'm so
grateful for that.
Oh! There's something
else I wanna ask you.
Well...
What is it?
Would you be willing
to sell me the SWAN?
Say wha?
Like I said, I'd like
to purchase the SWAN.
But the thing is,
I don't have any money,
so I'd have to pay
you for it later.
Are you... stupid?
Here's the deal!
I officially have
no intention of allying
with any nation or becoming
anyone's property.
So the SWAN will
become my kingdom!
And I'll fly my ship
anywhere I want!
But I'm gonna need help.
Mainly a crew
of individuals
willing to make sure
the thing doesn't crash!
Who here wants to sign up to
be a part of something great?!
Uh...
Show of hands...?
Anyone?
Oh, man... Yes.
So I take it the Church
has no objection to this?
Not at all.
Well... In that case,
we are coming along!
Me too!
I wouldn't miss
it for the world!
Neither would I.
If you go, Yukine,
I could be convinced.
Hey...!
Don't forget me!
I'm sorry,
but you can't go!
No... Please!
Why can't I go?!
This is for
your own good!
What a relief...
I don't think my new country
would make it with her there.
Now that you've declared
your independence,
and since you were nice enough
to allow us to join you,
it's only fitting we hold
the first emergency session
of the National Congress.
Sounds good...
What's on the agenda?
Just one thing...
I propose we make crystal
excavation on the SWAN illegal.
This is a terribly
important proposal.
It sure is.
And it's one that must go
into effect immediately.
I do feel for you...
But it just cannot be helped.
Then let's put it to a vote!
Uh... Wait, not yet!
Raise your hand
if you agree.
Well then... It looks
like the motion carries!
No way, I object...
Besides, this is my country!
Oh, shut up...!
We can't let you destroy the
only country you currently own,
you big moron!
No fair!
Quit your whining, we got
a barrier workshop to visit,
so let's get
a move on, everyone!
I think I've made
a huge mistake!
I guess nobody
told you, did they...?
It's not easy being King.
Kenshi...
All of our questions
should be answered here...
Including why you
came to our world...
Next time on
Tenchi Muyo! War on Geminar:
"Barrier Workshop"...
We'll make a fortune
if we can figure out
how to summon beings
from other worlds!