Huh?
I got a bite!
Look at that!
It must be huge!
This is a pretty
impressive pile of food
I've got for myself here.
Now, I just need
to preserve all of it...
According to the report...
Lord Babalun has been
appointed Prime Minister
of the Supreme Parliament,
as you predicted.
So, Babalun finally
has unquestioned power
over Shtrayu...
Meaning that little
assassination incident...
may actually not have
been his doing after all.
That would have
been quite foolhardy
before his new appointment.
This wouldn't be happening
if the belated king
were still alive...
Babalun is attempting
to seize Shtrayu
through his own
natural resources...
We wish to obtain our
country with our two hands
rather than merely inherit
it from our parents.
Are you not afraid you're
placing too much faith
in one boy, Empress?
Work in the dorms?
Correct...
You are still our attendant to
some extent, make no mistake...
However, we cannot pay you
out of our national budget.
Hey, no offense,
Empress Lashara...
But are you broke?
Not in the least!
If we paid you through
the national budget,
we would be forced to expose
your true identity!.
Is that what you want?!
Basically, if you wanna eat,
you're gonna have to work.
I think that's reasonable
though, don't you?
Yeah, but if this is just about
food, I don't need money...
I can find stuff
in the forest.
Well...
Yeah, I guess that's
true; you could.
Do not encourage
him, Chiaia!
Listen, Kenshi!
Do you think you're
some sort of wild animal
because we don't
recall owning any pets!
But I don't understand
why I need money here.
I don't get the point?
Then tell us
what you would do
if you finally found
a way back home...
But... it was only
available to you at a price?
I... don't know.
On top of that
bit of reason,
the dorms house
high-ranking students
from several countries...
Would it not be
in your best interest
to get to know
those students
because you might
want information
or have to ask one
of them for a favor?
Think about it, Kenshi.
Good point...
Well yeah, okay!
I'll do it!
Good-we have already spoken with
the academy on your behalf...
Now, you must
speak with them
in order to learn more
about your new job.
Pardon the intrusion, Empress,
but I'm afraid it's time.
Very well.
Bye!
Take care, Empress.
It is about time for you
to head out as well.
Sure!
Do you know where you'll
be going, my dear?
I'll be fine...!
See ya later!
Good morning.
Hey! Good morning!
This is just like home!
But with, like,
way more girls.
Hey, Kenshi!
Hi!
Oh...
Him again!
Isn't that Empress
Lashara's attendant?
Meow!
Oh, no!
He ran away again!
Doesn't he look
like a Koro!
He's so cute!
Try not to scare him off,
all right, ladies?
Miss Mexiah, you seem like
you're pretty close to him.
Is that true?
Are you?
Curious?
Well, too bad...!
I only answer questions
about school!
Toodles!
Wow... That was
kinda weird...
Having that many girls all
grouped together in one place
is a little intimidating.
It's open.
Excuse me.
Wait...
You're the principal.
I thought this was the
Dormitory Director's room.
In this academy, we all
have more than one job...
So, yes, this is also the
Dormitory Director's room.
Oh.
I think we're going to start you
off with a few different jobs
to see where
your talents lie.
Sound good?
Sure!
That's excellent...
Now, you won't be paid
on a fixed rate...
Instead you'll
receive points
based on how much
work you finish...
Regardless of the hours
you put in working,
you will actually
be compensated
for how many
points you earn.
So if I do a lot of tough jobs
in a short amount of time,
I'll be able to
earn more money?
Yes, precisely.
That's awesome!
The dorms are split
into four sections...
the independent dorms where
high nobles and royalty
like Empress Lashara live...
the boys' dorms, the
upperclass dorms,
and the underclass dorms.
But it's important
to note the independent,
as well as
the boys' dorms,
have their own equerries
and personal staff...
while the underclassmen
all take care of themselves,
for the most part.
So, it won't
come as a surprise
that you will primarily work in
the upperclassmen's dormitory.
The upperclassmen
don't have to work?
What's that all about?
Upperclassmen have been
officially knighted
as Sacred Mechamasters...
They've earned the right
to have their own attendants.
But... The Holy Land
is meant for training...
Aside from royalty
and high nobles,
students are not allowed
to bring their own attendants.
All the upperclassmen are
upperclassgirls, though,
isn't that right?.
Should I be working
in their dorms?
You're alright...
As long as you don't
pass the aptitude test,
we'll make sure to
keep you out of places
where you have to worry
about things like that.
Oh good; I was kinda worried!
But if something
should happen,
you are required
to report it immediately.
A few girls might try
to drag you into their lair,
and they have a way of ignoring
your efforts to avoid it.
Oh.
Hannah!
I would like you
to meet Kenshi.
What am I supposed
to do with him?.
Seriously,
he's just a kid.
You're hardly in a position
to be picky, my friend.
Yeah, you got me there.
Then I will leave
him in your hands.
Work hard, Kenshi.
Right!
Wow! This is
like a factory.
I didn't even know all
this stuff was down here.
The Holy Land is full
of privileged royalty
as well as Sacred
Mechamasters...
So anything unsightly is
hidden under the ground...
We're like feet
hidden by swans.
Okay...
But doesn't the energy
needed to move all this stuff
around give
people aho sickness?
The power is generated
deep underground
and carried
through cables,
so there's really
nothing to worry about.
Try to learn fast
and on your feet...
We may be understaffed,
but that won't stop me
from firing you Okay...
But why are you
understaffed to begin with?
Doesn't the academy
cater to the super rich?.
Do you just not have enough
money to pay a full staff?
I suppose that's one
way to interpret it!
The problem comes
from the graduates
taking their favorite
staff members with them.
Oh, really?
Yeah, we're used to it
happening every year...
but this past one was
ridiculously bad...
Honestly,
it's infuriating.
We spend time and money
perfecting our staff only
to have them leave us.
They're bribed
away of course.
Is this part not
underground, too?
It is. This is
our supply dock...
It also serves as a parking lot
for students' personal ships.
Why's it so bright, though?
It's almost like we're
standing outside.
Meh, a lot of ships have
their own gardens...
Some even have a couple of
house attendants on them.
Even though
it's underground,
we have the lights on the
same cycle as the outside.
Jozzy!
I told you about Kenshi
here yesterday...
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd show him the ropes.
Seriously?
I already said exactly
what you're thinking.
But you'd hire a Koro,
so give him a shot.
Yeah, whatever.
This is important.
You're gonna wanna make sure
to give it a clean corner
like this, okay?
You got that?
Yes, ma'am!
Why don't you try doing
the bed in the next room?
Nice... Yeah, you're
pretty good at that...
Well, moving on...
Dirty laundry.
You pick it up in this...
Leave the door to the hallway
open so the room can air out,
and that's it.
The beds are all the same,
but the extra bedspreads
and blankets
belong to them,
so you wanna make sure
to put them in the right bag.
And no matter what, you're
only allowed in the bedroom...
Seriously...
And no touching anything
or breaking anything...
Ya got it?
Got it!
Okay, then I'll just
leave this floor to you...
I'll come back
and help you
as soon as I finish
doing my floor...
Boy.
Hey, Jozzy!
What're you doing here...?
Did you screw up already?
No. I'm all done,
so I came to help you.
No way you're done...
No way... I'm not
even halfway through yet.
You better not have
done a crappy job!
Um... I can redo them
for you if I did them wrong.
No, you did good.
Finally...
I got a good one!
Everyone's
in total awe!
Hey, now! Why did you
all stop working?!
You better get on top of it so
this newbie doesn't show you up!
Anyway, I'm a
hundred percent sure
they're supposed
to be identical.
I guess we'll just
have to be careful
and match up
all the pieces.
Hey, Chiaia!
Rumor has it Kenshi started
working at the dorms.
Wow, that traveled fast.
Yeah, a friend of mine on the
staff told me all about it...
He also said Kenshi's
pretty popular.
And... people have been
saying that Kenshi is
Miss Mexiah's newest
little plaything...
Is that true?.
Do you know?
Good grief...
No, of course
it's not true...
I can't believe you're
even asking me that.
Well, besides her...
He's also 'popular' Empress
Lashara's newest attendant...
And he has a habit of running
around the Holy Land
looking super cute,
like a sexy little Koro.
So he's kind
of asking for it.
Hey, Princess Aura!
Where are you off to?
I think classes have
already started...
You aren't feeling
sick today, are you?
I'm alright...
I just always head out
this time of day...
I suppose you could think
of it as a kind of custom...
I do apologize
if I worried you.
But tell me Kenshi, what is it
that brings you out here today?
Oh, I just started
working for the Holy Land.
You're working...?
I thought you were acting as
the Empress's attendant, though.
She wanted me to take
advantage of being here
in the Holy Land and try
to meet some new people.
I see...
Then you have
impeccable timing;
I was just about to fetch
a member of the staff
to assist me
with something.
Did the wind blow
it over the edge?
Bullies did.
Bullies, huh?
Students from many
countries gather here.
Some are Sacred
Mechamaster candidates,
and some aren't...
The reasons vary, from
differences in rank to customs.
It's out of the Draft right now,
so we can't use an aircraft.
Honestly, I'm shocked
they threw it down there.
Please don't
worry about it...
It's gone now...
Thank you, though,
Princess Aura.
But that handkerchief
is precious.
Didn't you tell me that
your mother gave it to you?
We'll get it back...
We just need to find
a little rope first...
Kenshi... You can be
in charge of the rope.
Kenshi!
Done!
Here!
For you!
Oh no, it got a
little dirty...
One second!
I'll wash it for you!
No, that's okay!
I think I can
manage it myself.
Kenshi...
That was very dangerous.
Not really. The vine
was pretty strong,
and there were enough
spots for me to hold on to,
so I was perfectly
safe. Trust me.
You were not
at all safe!
Either way...
I really appreciate it...
Thank you, Kenshi.
You too, Princess.
I'm very glad you got your
handkerchief back, Lapis.
Are you ready?.
We should head
back to class now.
Yeah, I've gotta run, too!
Oh, that boy...
He's always
in such a rush!
Man, Kenshi sure
did surprise me!
And this is just
his first day!.
We'll have to see
if any bad habits show.
No way...
That kid has got this
line of work down.
In fact... he's got a weird
gift for it or something.
With a little training, he
could become one of our best.
Well, I sincerely
doubt he's good enough
to replace all the people
we lost this past year...
Although that isn't to say
we won't take him, of course.
Oh, you have got
to be kidding me...!
Your piddling little staff
hardly requires that much skill,
and you know it!
You take the next new one.
You always get
preferential treatment
when it comes
to new workers--
Now, now... Whether
we like it or not,
we're going to have to work
together to make ends meet
until we get some
new staff in here.
In the meantime Mister Masaki
will help all departments.
Remember, the poor child
only has one body...
You must coordinate
with each other
to make sure you
don't overwork him.
Hey, kid!
Be careful!
Okay!
I think he'll be fine.
The underclassmen servers
should be here soon...
Get a move on!
We have a lot of
delivery orders today,
but that doesn't mean
you can get sloppy...!
Treat each order
with love and care!
Uh, excuse me...
Am I doing this
right... sir?
Oh!
Your presentation has a very
unique style, Mister Masaki...!
Who did you
study under, son?
I've just always
helped my sister.
What is that?
Those are sliced
bamboo leaves.
I've heard only royal chefs
use this kind of technique...
Yes, it's very impressive...
Now, I need
you to go ahead
and deliver two servings
of this yourself.
But I'm not done
in the kitchen.
Well apparently you were
asked for specifically.
I was?
Hello!
I'm here with a delivery
from the kitchen!
Excuse me, ladies.
Your lunch has arrived.
Come in.
Sorry to intrude.
Oh...
Princess Aura...
Hi. Thank you for bringing
our food to us, Kenshi.
So...
This is the boy you
were talking about.
Here, let me
introduce you...
This is the current
Pope's granddaughter,
the honorable Lady
Lithia Po Cheena.
I'm Kenshi Masaki.
So nice to meet you, Kenshi.
To be honest, you look
absolutely nothing like
what I expected you to...
Instead...
You're more
like a wild dog.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
I'm sure!
Lithia, remember
your manners...!
Kenshi is not a wild dog...
If that boy is anything,
he is a proud wolf.
Still doesn't change the
fact that he's a wild animal.
Shame on you.
I am sorry.
I know she can be
somewhat harsh at times.
She is straightforward,
that's for sure.
I suppose.
Now if you ladies
will excuse me.
It was nice meeting
you, Kenshi.
I guess
I'll see you later.
He provided a service
to us, Lithia...
The least you could have done
was to thank him, you know.
Oh please; I was merely
stating an opinion.
Found him!
You're Empress Lashara's
attendant, aren't you?
Yeah, um...
Then I would love to talk
to you about something.
Yeah, but I've got a
question for you first!
Tell me about
Empress Lashara!
Hey...
Why don't we go to a more
private place to talk?
No. Don't try
hogging him, Bwoole!
Yeah, that's cheating...!
He should be able to talk
to whoever he wants
to, which is me!
Cool! So Kenshi
is doing well?
That is good to know.
Yeah, and the male workers
won't stop raving about him.
I hear those stupid rumors
about him and my sister
all over the place.
Well, at least everyone's
getting a little excitement.
Get out of my way!
What...
the heck was that?
I knew this would happen!
Nice... He's grown
rather popular...
That's wonderful!
Hey, Kenshi!
Wait!
Wait up!
That's Empress
Lashara's attendant!
We should go
after him, too!
Over here! Swing
around to the right!
He's so fast!
Don't let him get away!
He went over there!
Let's surround him, everyone!
We've got to catch that boy!
I'm going left!
I'm going right!
Honestly, could they
make more noise?
What in the world is going on?
A ton of upperclassmen have
decided to chase Kenshi around
for some reason.
Well, then, they certainly
have bizarre taste.
And supposedly, they want
to use him to get close
to Miss Mexiah
or the Empress.
That's hilarious...
I guess we should go.
I might feel bad about
myself if he ended up
becoming some idiot's plaything,
and I could've helped...
Yes... But miss...
Why me?!
Oh!. I knew
he was a wild beast!
Um... Lady Lithia...?
No one can get
anywhere close to him.
The girls are
dropping like flies.
Did they just chase
him into the forest?!
They did.
I'll let Shurifon's
guards know immediately.
Yes, please do.
Lithia, what
is going on here?
They chased the wild
beast into the forest,
accidentally
over- exerted themselves,
and needed some help...
Since you were busy
with an extended lecture,
I couldn't interrupt you.
So I'm afraid I had to ask your
subordinates for assistance.
Very well.
Wait... Where
is Kenshi, now?
Is he still somewhere
in the forest?
Oh... Maybe?
All right...
I shall join
the search team.
Kenshi?!
Oh, hi, Princess!
Lady Lithia...
Those two were the last
of the ones out there.
Okay, thank you.
You're very welcome.
Now, if you ladies will
excuse me, I have more work...
And Princess Aura...
I'll see you tomorrow.
You did a great job.
Hold on... he was
on the search team as well?
Oh yeah.
I'm back!
Don't track all
that dirt in here!
Pay attention, Kenshi!
I'm sorry!
Very impressive!
He works even harder
than we expected.
To what...
do we owe the pleasure
of your company?
Come now, I'm your
sister, not a teacher.
Now say, 'ah'!
Kenshi...
How has work been treating
you this past month...?
All is well?
All's great!
Everyone is really nice.
I've heard...
You're pretty popular
with the other workers.
They say you're
one of the best!
Perfect...
That is wonderful news.
Ow! Ow, that hurts!
Ears are for
hearing not pulling!
And that other thing?.
How is it proceeding?
I've already
obtained approval...
The main issue was
Kenshi's work ethic,
but no one's worried
about that now.
We see.
So I take it you approve?
Considering how these new
recruits are working out,
how could I not?
It's settled...
They're all going to be
tickled pink... I'm sure.
Now I need to know: This will in
no way interfere with your work,
will it Hannah?
Not at all.
Thanks to him, we were able
to handle a lot of repairs
and odd jobs
we needed to do...
We should be
fine sharing him
on shifts until
more workers come in.
In that case, I'll let
you be the one to draft
a detailed shift plan...
Have Kenshi Masaki come
to my office, please.
Tell me, you must've been
raised in a family
of very hard workers,
Mister Masaki...
Not only did they teach you
the importance of cleaning,
but they also gave you
rather specialized skills...
like construction.
Well, my father did
work in construction,
and my sisters were really
good at demolishing.
Is that so?
One of my sisters
is amazing at cleaning,
so I watched
her work a lot.
And... I have another sister
who might just be the worst
cleaner in history...
So I guess
getting to see
both of those extremes
helped me learn.
I imagine so...
At this time, I would like to
assign you some different work,
if you think
you're up to it.
Sure!
Big Sis Mexiah?
Who said you could
call me that...?
Kenshi Masaki...
I'm Miss Mexiah,
baby boy.
Baby boy?
I've heard some cultures from
other worlds have their teachers
dress in costumes and refer
to their students as babies.
Where did she
hear that from?
Do you object to it?
No, no objection
from me at all.
So, what kinda job is it?
A significant number
of upperclassmen
have submitted
requests for you
to become their personal
estheticians, baby boy.
Esthe-what?
Someone who helps them wash
up before getting into a bath.
To put it simply,
baby boy will be washing
the Sacred Mechamasters'
hair and bodies.
Oh no, I forgot
I have to go...
This is a very
exclusive job, baby boy.
Yeah, I bet it is...
He accepts!
What?
I accept?
Kenshi... It is quite
the honor for them to ask you.
You cannot refuse them;
that would be rude.
It's too embarrassing...
I, couldn't...
You accept!
You should.
It's very sacred work.
But I've never done
anything like that before.
Well, we all have to start
out somewhere, don't we...?
And besides, Kenshi...
For them to have requested
you specifically means
that the Sacred Mechamasters
are starting to take more
of an interest in you.
And try not to forget...
Connections like these
could increase your chances
of going home, so maybe take
advantage of this opportunity.
I understand your
point, but...
There's no
need to worry...
I can give you
thorough instructions
since this is your
first time, baby boy.
Wait!
Big Sis Mexiah, please!
It's Miss Mexiah,
remember?
Are you implying I'm not good
enough for you, baby boy?
No, I am not.
I see...
In that case,
I think it's imperative
I teach you every single thing
there is to know about me.
That way you can make a much
better informed decision.
But I never said you weren't
good enough, I swear!
I didn't even think it!
Get ready!
I'm taking you to a land
of ecstasy, baby boy!
Does she seem far more excited
about this than she should be?
Apparently, he's popular
with all the older girls...
And, yes.
The Holy Land is significantly
lacking in men...
Especially fun ones.
Plus, there are
a whole lotta people
who would like something
to connect them to you.
Well, we don't care
about the reason;
we're just happy they're
all so interested in him!
Let's get started,
baby boy!...
We feel as though
we should stop them.
No, he's just being a baby.
She's only teaching him
how to bathe someone.
Wake up, Kenshi!
Get a grip,
you loser! Come on!
Oh Mexiah...
Could you tell me why Kenshi
looks like he's about to die?
On the other hand, you
yourself seem very lustrous.
I know, right...?
It felt so amazing, too!
What in the world
did you do to him?
He was just such
a quick learner,
I couldn't help
but get carried away...
So, good!
Please tell us you did
not teach him anything
that could prove to be
problematic later...
Kenshi is still
underage, you know.
Oh, no. There's no need
to worry, Empress...
I made sure to teach
him just when to stop.
He'll be perfect, I swear.
Meaning?
I told him...
"Now, Kenshi, don't ever take it
this far when you are working."
You didn't?!
Something tells us we should
probably stop asking questions.
For shame!
At this point, Mexiah,
is it safe for us to say
that Kenshi's bathing
lesson is over?
It is!
Although, I could only
teach him the basics.
Oh great.
What does that mean?
He's still lacking
actual experience.
We need more guinea pigs,
or rather, more subjects
for him to practice
what he's learned on.
Kenshi Masaki,
clean Chiaia!
Don't you dare!
Why do your eyes
look like that?
No! Bad Kenshi!
Nothing you say
can stop him now...
He's trained to immediately
obey any order I give him.
He's essentially
a massaging machine,
and you're
his next victim.
We see...
You input your orders
while his mind was
trying to escape reality,
so he's basically in what they
call "berserker mode," right?
Exactly.
He won't listen to anything
but what I tell him.
Why would you do
something so idiotic?
Kenshi, you need to focus
and pull yourself together!
Oh, no!
Hey!
Put me down!.
Kenshi!.
Let me go!
That's far enough.
Stop it, Kenshi...! Hey!
I am never going to
forgive either of you!
I hate you both so much!.
You're the worst!
He is a massage machine...
We could make a
fortune with his touch.
Then I think we should
probably spread the word
by letting him practice on some
of the other girls we know.
Borrow Yukine?
It's important, baby girl.
What do you need me for?
You are forbidden
to use Kenshi Masaki...!
Miss Lashara!
Why?! Everyone
enjoyed him so much
they couldn't
even move afterwards!
That's exactly the
problem, my dear.
Are you sure you
should be up, Yukine?
Does that look erotic,
or is it just me?
It's not just you.
Princess!
Are you all right
in there?
Princess!
Would you please
stop that banging?!
I cannot believe
what he did to me!
I told them
he was wild!
Stupid jerks!
I'll teach them!
I'm gonna test my
new weapon on him.
People have issued complaints
and are reporting after effects.
Some are even making
strange requests
to undergo the experience before
their marriage ceremonies.
This is unacceptable,
especially for an Empress!
So he got a little
carried away.
Who cares...?
This guarantees there
will be a flock of applicants
when we make
the big announcement!
Very nice...
You all did well.
Now, fill it with warm water
and welcome the Sacred
Mechamasters inside.
Um. I thought I was done
after the tubs were full.
Unfortunately, two of our best
estheticians hurt their backs
after carrying your massage
victims to their rooms...
I imagine you would rather
call them your test subjects,
but still... We're a bit
short on staff now.
And besides,
the Sacred Mechamasters
have started fanatically
requesting your services...
I'd prefer
not to do this...
but I received permission for
you to wash only their backs.
They're on their way.
Now let's get going;
it's time to greet them.
Hey, it's Kenshi!
Wait, Kenshi's here?
Really?
Does this mean you're
going to wash our backs,
because that
would be so awesome!
I guess so.
Yay!
Oh no; I'm sorry...
I didn't hurt you, did I?
No...
You feel like a Koro walking
up and down my naked back.
Hey, uh, Kenshi...?
Could you wash
me here, too?
I'm sorry, no...
I mean, you can
reach those yourself.
I know, but that's
not the point.
I want you to do it.
There are other people
waiting, so why don't you try
using a little self-control
for once, Yeliss!
That's right!.
Kenshi, I'm next!
I'm after that!
But I was
in line after her!
I clearly had a foot
in front of you!
I'm not done
with him yet!
So, Cliff Cleese...
What do you think?
Do you think I'm
being too ideological?
I don't...
Reality will never change
if one does not have ideals.
I offer you
my full support...
Dagmyer Mesut.
Thank you, my friend.
I'm so tired.
Hey!. Kenshi!
Oh, hi, Mister Ulyte...
Heard you've been busy...
That must be fun for you...
Touching all
those cute girls.
It's a tough job...
But, you know what
they say, don't you?
About how some unlucky soul
has to be the one to do it?
There's just so many of 'em.
I don't really have
time to enjoy myself.
I'm sure you
will eventually.
Well I'm not...
I don't think I can keep
up with all those girls.
We are in Holy Land, so those
sentiments are understandable.
Don't you think it's
a little weird, though?
It probably feels
that way to you,
but remember you're
from the highlands...
You do have
to keep in mind,
it's something we're
accustomed to around here.
Yeah...
I guess you're right.
In fact,
there is one theory
that someone
from another world
came here and deliberately
spread a few of our customs
across the land...
Those from other
worlds always make
for superb
Sacred Mechamasters.
There's never
been an exception.
So, naturally they obtain high
ranks and become influential...
It wouldn't surprise me
if some of their interests
got forced onto us.
I see...
So they, like, did
whatever they wanted?
Yes!. They, like,
did whatever they wanted!
Oh...! When I was washing the
Sacred Mechamasters' backs...
I noticed this, uh,
sort of emblem-like thing
near their waists.
Right...
That's a contraceptive shield;
all the girls have them...
They have a duty to fulfill,
so precautions are taken.
Oh, I get it.
Which means...
If a girl you like
makes a move on you,
feel free to go
for it, kid.
Is it just me or do those
two look perfect together?
Yeah, absolutely amazing!
Kenshi!
Oh my-- wow!
What's wrong,
Miss Sister...
B-Big...
Miss Mexiah Sister?
No questions!
Just drop everything
and run away with me!
Did she just say what
I thought she said?
She really did!
Yes, she did!
They're really
gonna do it...!
They're gonna elope!
Please know I'd be happy
to suffer through anything
as long as I could
still be with you!
Would I be right in assuming
that this has to do with that?
I found 'im!
You're not getting
away this time!
I swear upon my pride you
will pay for humiliating me!
You and that wild beast will
pay for what you've done!
You'll both
stand as witnesses
while Lashara coughs up a
fortune in compensation to us!
No...
Please don't!
Why?. You should
be compensated.
No, I don't like it
when... it's rough.
Yes, I understand,
perfectly...
Kenshi Masaki!
Take responsibility for
getting rough with Yukine
and defiling her!
No... blood...
spilt... please!
There was blood...?!
Oh, say it isn't so, Yukine!
Oh, what a monster!
Kenshi, it would seem
I made a grave mistake
that day I saved you...
I shall correct
that error.
No, blood, please!
We understand,
Yukine.
You're not alone...
I'm right here.
Please stop!
Well I, for one,
don't really care!
You're freakin' heavy,
so why don't you get off me
so I can annihilate
these perverts
with my fancy
new weapon?!
Where are they?
Wahan...
Over there!
I'm willing to die
as long as I'm with you!
I don't think this is the
time to be joking like that!
I'm sure you
must be relieved
that Master Cliff
agreed with you, sir...
Now you are another step
closer to your goal.
Master Cliff is a smart man...
I was very confident he would
understand my point of view.?
What is that?!
You won't get
away from me!
What are you doing?
Well, that
was uncalled for!
I do apologize, sir...
Were you injured?
No, not at all...
I'm alright...!
More importantly, isn't
that the "Mechaworker" Wahanly
has been working on recently?
Supposedly it doesn't
use an aho reactor.
Impressive
maneuverability.
Really!
Who do they think
is going to fix
all the damage
they're causing!
Aren't you worried the academy
will make you be the one to pay
for all the stuff that's
getting obliterated back there?
I don't see why they
would, baby boy.
I'm just sitting here...
But just in case,
let's run into the forest
so they can't
destroy anything else.
Why do you keep
calling me baby boy?!
Because I like doing it!
How can he still move like
that while carrying Miss Mexiah?
He's a beast.
That's how!
If they go
into the forest,
then I can really
let this baby rip!
Goodness.
They are not joking
around, are they?
Nor am I,
Miss Lashara...
Believe you me.
Yes, we can agree that no
one is joking right now.
Have everyone involved
come to my office once
this ridiculous
fight is over...
Naturally,
that includes you.
Understood.
I have no intention of
lecturing you on normal ethics,
so let me be
as blunt as possible.
No one standing
before me right now
should come to
school tomorrow.
Are we suspended?
Not quite...
As you are well aware,
the academy is
extremely understaffed,
so we're going to put
all of you to work.
You will be responsible
for repairing every facility
you destroyed today.
None of you
will return to school
until those
repairs are done.
I don't understand...
we aren't exactly
trained in construction.
A few new workers will
arrive tomorrow afternoon.
Kenshi Masaki,
you will instruct them
on how to fix
the damages until then...
Can you do that?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Absolutely.
You can count on me.
What an exhausting day...
What the-?
Kenshi, it's about time we
headed back to the dorm...
How long are you
planning to stay in here?
What do you think
you're doing, you idiot?!
Pardon me, sir.
I hate to intrude,
but I just received word
that the 'packages'
are in transit.
Understood.
Is everything
all right, sir...?
Are you concerned about
that machine we saw earlier?
The aho reactor, if it
really doesn't need one...
then it could be used for
battle outside the Draft
without using a cable...
Which means...
It would be rather useful
in seizing the castle.
That's true.
Uh, good morning,
everyone.
I'm excited to work
with you all.
If you could just
follow my instructions
to get the repairs all done,
that'd be great!
How dare a lowly attendant
tell us what to do!
It can't be helped...
We are less than amateurs when
it comes to this type of work...
Let's just do
whatever he tells us.
Yes. Someone kill me.
Reconstruction is fun...
I bet I can get some sweet
data out of all this stuff.
We have to admit,
we're rather jealous
a certain country bumpkin
is so accustomed to such work...
We have personally never had
to lift anything heavier
than a teacup.
Surprising...
One would figure by now your
greed would have forced you
to grab any bag of money,
no matter the weight.
Excuse us?!
I will not!
I'm starting to think
this might go faster
if I just did it myself.
Wow, you brought a lot
of options this time!
Yeah...
We got an odd last minute
flood of applicants
from out of nowhere...
They seem fairly capable, too,
so I'm sure more than one
will be a nice contribution.
I hope so... I do hate putting
them all to work so soon...
But could
you try to send
about ten more experienced
construction workers
over to me first...?
I wish I could let them rest,
but I just don't have a choice.
That's fine...
They came here to work,
so we might as well let them.
Can we get ten here?!
Wake up already, Kenshi!
You've got to smack
into an upperclassmen,
resulting in a
hilarious chain of events!
Next time on Tenchi Muyo!
War on Geminar:
Pendant...
A romantic comedy is
about to get under way!