Nice!
You can totally tell
future Sacred Mechamaster
lords and ladies
hang out here.
Talk about fancy.
It's not only Sacred
Mechamasters...
Royalty and nobility
attend school here as well.
You need to be...
Lan... Be careful
not to draw
any attention
to yourself, at all...
We cannot afford
to have you jeopardizing
Sir Dagmyer's plans;
do you understand?
Sure... Whatever
you say, Lady Emera!
Ugh...
We're dying from boredom now
that summer vacation is over...
There has to be something
fun to do! Doesn't there?
Have anything
particular in mind?
Oh, we dunno...
make some quick and
easy money in a way
that doesn't require us
to put up any capital?
Yeah, right.
Don't get your hopes up.
Things like that
don't just happen.
I totally see what
you're saying.
Is something
the matter?
It's ridiculous.
This is way too easy.
I don't think we could
if we tried
Excuse me;
did you drop this?
Sorry?
Oh, yeah.
That is my watch...
How weird; I thought
it was in my pouch.
It must have
fallen out then.
Gone!
When did he
take it from me?
I know him.
Lan...! What exactly were you
thinking running off like that,
and what are
you doing here?
I just went on a walk...
Hey... What about him...?
What is that guy's story?
Who in the world is he?
Thank you so much!
Yeah, that was so crazy!
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm still amazed
how easy it was to sneak
into the Holy Land.
Yeah, well I'm still amazed
how much they let us just
screw around all day.
This is the best
job I've ever had.
Seriously! And how crazy
is the power they give away
to those Sacred Mechamasters...?
Well, at least one of
'em is keeping the boss
in a good mood, though.
Whaddaya wanna bet she's in
the middle of a really good mood
right now?
Once she's pregnant,
she'll be as privileged
as the nobles they got
prancin' around here.
Think her kid'll wind up being
a Sacred Mechamaster, too?
Be great to have some of
that luck rub off on me.
With that face?
Keep dreamin', sister.
Sorry... I would
rather not be forced
to confine
you to my ship,
but... there is a significant
chance you'd be recognized,
and that's simply not a risk
I am willing to take.
I don't mind...
Everyone else is enjoying
themselves anyway,
so it's not a big deal.
Tell me...
Is the plan
moving along okay?
Yes...
It's all right
on schedule.
Good...
When you first explained
the gig to me in Havoniwa,
I wondered what this young,
naïve lord was talking about...
I only half believed
you were serious
when I accepted
your offer.
To be honest...
I still find it hard to
believe you actually got us
inside the Holy Land.
I don't know why...
I thought I told you that
I am not like other men.
And I thought I told you I'll
give you all I've got to give.
And I'll take it all.
Well, look
what we have here.
Word has it you're
Lashara's servant...
So, what did ya do before
you started working for her?
I... I was...
in the highlands...
And uh...
Don't lie to me.
I'm not...
It's the truth.
Yeah, I'm not buying it.
We're used to the
same line of work...
You don't have
to hide it from me.
It's not like I'm
gonna tell anyone.
In fact, I have a pretty
juicy gig coming up...
Want in on the action?
Oh I get it, now.
Come on, you should have a
little fun working with me.
Unlike your lame job
being a servant,
it'll put your
talents to use.
You shouldn't do stuff
like that anymore.
Bye!
Well... Guess that's what
I get for trying to help...
The dumb guy's
been domesticated.
C'mon, your retreat
pattern's too simple!
Well done, Alan!
You should put more
thought into your patterns.
Yeah, I know.
They appear to be coming
along quite nicely.
They're ready for combat.
Trust me...
how are things proceeding
on your end, Uncle?
All that's left is
a final confirmation...
And after that,
we'll be ready to go.
And how much longer do you
think that will take you?
I suppose that answer would
depend on whether or not
you're willing to help
me out with something.
Say the word.
What do you need?
A competitive
sports tournament?
Yes... It gives us
the opportunity
to test the results
of our training
and promotes friendship
among Mechamasters
from different lands.
But if I'm going to
be honest with you...
The tournament's
real purpose...
is to prevent those
dorm room humdrums,
also known as boredom.
How interesting...
The main event...
is a long-distance
obstacle race...
That sounds like fun.
Thank you...
I figured we could hold
preliminaries during class,
so it shouldn't be
too demanding.
Good job...
And we think we know
how to get the students excited
about who will win the race.
Gambling...? And I
suppose you also think
you should be the bookie?
Well naturally!
That's hardly necessary;
based on the size of the event;
the council's monthly
budget should cover it
without taking bets.
Yes, but do you really
think the council should pay
to keep students
from getting bored?
Expose anyone who would cheat
and try to maintain order...
Do that, and I will
give my approval.
Understood.
All right, then...
It doesn't appear
a vote will be necessary...
but just in case, does
anyone oppose this event?
Ladies and Gentlemen,
the motion is approved;
we're going
to have a tournament.
Uncle... the vote
has just been passed.
That's wonderful...
You have done rather well.
I expect you to keep
your promise to me now.
You must be talking about
allowing you to be in charge
of the front lines...
I can do that.
However...
I will still need
to have some assurance
my needs are getting
met, as well.
You always were
the one to worry.
Only because I realize
trust is born from one's
track record, nephew.
Yes, I am well
aware of that...!
Excuse me.
Do you think those thugs
Dagmyer brought in
are going
to become a problem?
At the moment, they are keeping
quiet and staying low...
But that girl, Lan, is more
than a little mischievous.
Well, either way...
The hardest part
is still to come...
We don't have
a choice here...
Failure is simply
not an option.
Talk about
a piece-a-cake.
What in the world
is wrong with you...?
I thought I specifically told
you not to attract attention!
Will you relax? No one
even knew I was there.
Now, whaddaya plan
on doing with that?
I will not allow you to cause
problems for Sir Dagmyer.
Sure... Okay...
Hey, Dagmyer!
Aw, no...
You don't know
how weak you are.
What's going on here?
Ya know, just makin' sure
I don't lose my touch.
Forgive us, sir.
Why would you waste time
with such tasteless appetizers
when the main dish
is coming up?
I grabbed them
while doing recon...
Besides, you can use
this to help get
to that main dish faster...
Maybe start a few
fights or something fun.
We'll be pushing the
plan forward soon...
So try not to attract
any attention.
Fine...
I just don't like to let all
this easy prey go to waste.
Yes, thank you!
I can't help it...
I like rich stuff...
So, how's mom doing?
She good...? Are you
taking care of her?
You know that isn't any
of your business, Lan.
Yeah, true enough!
How are those dividend
rates coming along?
Good. We'll be done
with them shortly.
We can't help ourselves!
We're so excited!
I don't see why you need to get
ready for this thing so early.
Well, why would we not...?
We're planning to start
accepting bets tomorrow morning.
You mean you're taking
bets on the prelims?
Is it not truly exciting...?
We want to make certain
we're thoroughly
enjoying this experience.
Is everything all right?
We're going to
have a festival...
I think you ladies are all going
to enjoy the change of pace.
Hey... did you hear
about the tournament?
Of course I did!
The preliminaries are
supposed to start today!
I don't care what it is.
I just really wanna make
the cut in something!
If we do well, the student
council might notice us, right?!
I'm looking forward
to the tournament...
as well as our other little
bit of "fun" with it.
Yeah, the judges are supposedly
screening the contestants
right now.
So, whaddaya think?
Are you gonna try
and win a fortune, too?
You better believe it; they're
accepting prelim bets now.
Yeah, good luck to
both of you guys,
but until you win that fortune,
you still work for me.
So try to stay
focused, okay?
Only until I'm rich.
Oh yay...!
I'm moving on!
Oh no!
I didn't make it!
Well, I don't know about you,
but I'd say things
have been running fairly
smoothly so far.
Yeah, too smooth
in my opinion...
Most of this
tournament is boring...
The event to watch will be the
long-distance obstacle race.
It appears to duplicate
Shurifon's traditional race...
The contestants will include
Princess Aura and Kenshi...
Oh, and it looks like Dagmyer
will be running, as well.
Things are about to
get exciting, Mexiah.
That's a good job
on you, Sir Dagmyer.
Everyone's going crazy
over your little tournament.
Well, if you ask me, it's
a complete waste of time...
We should have been
doing something.
There's no need for
any of us to rush.
Our time will
come soon enough.
Our time should be now; we
have our pride to defend here...
If you ask me, we need to
focus on proving ourselves.
And we will.
All right!.
Bring them down!
We're all
hooked up now, Miss!
This is overwhelmingly awful.
The life of a councilwoman
certainly isn't an easy one.
I don't think I've ever
felt this exhausted.
Again, only those
who actually worked
should be talking like that.
This is really dirty.
That's because it doesn't
get cleaned much...
They only shine it up for big
events, like the tournament.
But isn't it supposed to
be, like, a really big deal?
Well, yeah; it's
a way big deal...!
I mean, we're talkin' about
the only one in the world.
Wait...
There's just one?
Yep... This is the only
fully intact Sacred Mechalord
that has been excavated from
a prehistoric civilization...
So, the church is, like,
super protective of it,
for obvious reasons.
Empress Lashara was only allowed
to use it in her coronation
because Shtrayu originally
owned the excavation site.
Also known as,
the Holy Land.
Oh, wow.
In Shtrayu...
the Sacred Mechalord is
revered as a symbol of power.
This is just a
symbol of power?
It's not like anyone
can pilot it... ya know?
To me, it just seems
like a massive piece
of weird decoration.
Are we all done yet?
This is proving to be much more
profitable than we expected.
We have particularly high
hopes for the main event!.
Speaking of, how are
the preparations going?
We are almost
ready, Empress.
Almost is not good enough;
we must be ready...!
Then the fun can begin...
Remember: sell, sell,
sell, and sell some more!
It should be reassuring
to see her like this--
enthusiastic
about her job...
Yet it worries me.
Me too...
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Get your winning
predictions right here...!
You could get rich quick, so
don't let this chance slip by!.
Winning predictions,
right here!
Goodness me; this place
sure is packed wall-to-wall.
Yes, Miss Mexiah!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but Empress Lashara is the
head bookmaker, isn't she?
Yeah. Success
smells so good!
What is this crap?
Kenshi's name is the
only one on here!
Yeah...
He's very popular.
It's true. He's
everyone's favorite.
You guys! Can't you
bet on anyone else?
Do you not understand
how real gambling works!
Yeah, we don't
really care, though.
We just want to
see Kenshi win!
Yeah!
That's so rude!
This looks
like my chance!
I see...
and I agree.
You have my permission to
take care of this situation.
Thanks, Lithia.
Hello!
Wait, please!
You have some
dirt on you.
Thank you.
I didn't even notice.
It's not a problem,
but I should be
the one thanking you...
You have my gratitude
for saving Sir Dagmyer
in Havoniwa... Thank you.
No, uh, I-I didn't
really do anything.
That was all Queen Flora!
I was told you were
immensely helpful as well.
I mean...
no, not really.
If possible, I don't want
to become enemies with you.
Nothing.
I've been looking
for you everywhere
I need to warn you
about something.
Excuse me.
What were the two of you just
talking about back there?
What?.
Why do you ask?
It's fine...
Never mind.
Kenshi!
I'm really confused.
Give Empress
Lashara a message.
I will be taking care of Kenshi
until the day of the tournament,
to make sure
he stays safe.
I even have the Student Council
President's letter of consent.
Let's go!
No!. She did what?!
She beat us to him...
How did Mexiah know
what we were planning?
Planning...? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Chiaia...
What's up?
Apparently, Kenshi is by
far the crowd favorite.
Pretty much every
student and teacher
is betting on him to win.
The way the upperclassmen used
to chase him around all the time
probably has something
to do with it...
But that's
just my opinion.
And you know the bookie is
Empress Lashara, right...?
I bet Mexiah is making sure
Kenshi doesn't get hurt
before the games
even start.
Talk about a traitor!.
We will get you for
this Kenshi Masaki!
No one crosses us
and gets away with it!
And, she's already
losing it...
Whatcha think
we should do?
It's probably best
to ignore her...
Unless you really want
to get lost in crazy land.
But you guys!
What if she does something
to Kenshi, and he gets hurt.
Trust me, you don't
need to worry about him.
Oh yeah. If anybody's
gonna be okay, it's Kenshi.
No, not with her,
he won't!
He'll be in seclusion with
Miss Mexiah... Think about it!
That means he'll be alone with
her until the tournament starts!
Uh... Could I-?
Could you what?
I was just wondering
if it would be cool
if I went
to the restroom.
Sure, let's go!
No, I can go by myself...!
But, I would appreciate it
if you'd take off this chain.
No way. Until
the tournament starts...
Or I guess, more precisely,
until the long-distance
obstacle race begins...
You and I are going to get
to go everywhere together!
But!. How come?
Oh, Kenshi, why does
it even matter...
I mean, we have already seen
each other naked, haven't we?
Um... I don't remember
that ever happening.
And also,
I'm a student now...
Like officially... And I don't
think it's very appropriate,
or a good idea,
for a student and a teacher
to be sleeping in
the same bed together.
Why's that?
Well, because it's kinda frowned
on in my world, er, country--
wherever
it is I'm from.
Oh...?
How very unusual.
Unusual?.
What do you mean?
I mean, who teaches you about
the opposite sex that way?
Your mother...?
Or your sisters, maybe?
Not them... You just kinda
pick it up from books,
and like, your friends
and that stuff...
But, we do figure it out.
That's horrible!
No one teaches you what
everyone has the right to know?
How are you ever gonna find
out what's fundamental,
applicable,
or abnormal, even...?
What if you learned
something crazy on your own
and thought it was normal, but
only later found out the truth?
Please tell me you don't plan
on spending your entire life
in the dark about women...
This is serious!
The adults in your life are
ignoring their responsibilities!
I'm offering
you a chance...
I can teach you an entire
world of things, Kenshi.
I don't like that
look in your eyes...
Um... Am I just
imagining things,
or are you about to teach
me what's fundamental,
applicable
or abnormal, even?
Yes.
Crap! I gotta
get outta here!
I have sister-in-laws,
aunts, and grandmas
who get that same
look in their eyes,
and I don't
like it at all!
Now isn't that
interesting, baby boy.
As Student Council
President...
It is by the authority
of my office...
That I hereby commence
the Competitive Tournament!
This is bad.
It's pretty obvious who
will win each game...
If Kenshi wins, we're gonna
be in the red big time.
Most of the wagers
are for him.
I think 'in the red big time'
is putting it mildly.
Then, clearly, we need
to do something about Kenshi.
You can't
really be serious.
Oh, Empress Lashara,
you wouldn't!
We do what we must when we
don't have any other options.
How is everything running?
Great...!
All the games are proceeding
according to schedule.
How are
the preparations
for the long-distance
obstacle race coming?
Oh... Let me
check real quick.
Why did I get stuck wearing
this wacky costume, too?
Basically, because I knew
while everyone was occupied...
you were planning to go on
a little stealing spree.
The checkpoints
are all set,
so the main event
is ready to go.
Good...
And, in that case...
Let's get ready
to start the race!
Here's the
instruction manual
for the long-distance
obstacle race...
Please read it carefully
before the race starts.
Thanks.
It looks like they're
starting the race now!
What's she up to...?
Oh, Lan.
So, it's
about to begin.
Ready...
Go!
Nineteen, twenty...
What the-?!
Twenty-one,
twenty-two,
twenty-three,
twenty-four,
twenty-five.
Twenty-six,
twenty-seven,
twenty-eight,..
Excuse me,
Wild Beast, but...
what exactly
are you doing?
You're in a race.
But the rules said I had
to count to ten thousand
before I could
start to run.
The rules say
no such thing...
Now, start running!
Okay... I'm going!
Why do you have that
attached to you?
Because... I'm supposed
to have a handicap. I thought?
How does
that make sense?!
Are you an idiot on top
of being a wild beast...?
Take it off immediately!
Yeah, right!
Seriously?!. Will someone
sever this chain, please?!
Thank you very much!
Save the thanking
for later...
Get a move on!
Mew!
You know...
Kenshi has a tendency
to make that strange sound
when he gets really scared...
I wonder what
that's all about.
I have no clue.
But I'd guess it probably
comes from being raised
by wild animals.
Hm...
He finally
started running.
What do you think
the problem was, sir?
Oh, I have a couple
of theories on that.
Right.
Curse Lithia...
Why did she have
to get in our way...
But luckily,
we have got a plan B.
Kenshi, wait!
Sorry, but the course got
changed at the last minute.
So go this way, okay?
Okay, yeah,
thanks a lot!
And with that we've got
plenty of leeway...! Go me!
Poor girl; the pressure must
really be getting to her.
Kenshi's gone off course...
I'm not sure why!
You have got
to kidding me...!
Do everything you can
to get him back on track now!
Yes, miss!
The target seems to have
abandoned course, sir.
This has got to be
Empress Lashara's doing...
Kenshi was the overwhelming
favorite before the race,
after all.
That's the truth...
To be honest, I bet
on him myself, sir.
Yeah, my money's
on him, too.
Which only serves
to further my point.
As the bookmaker, her earnings
would take a decent hit
if Kenshi were to win.
I swear... when
it comes to money,
Empress Lashara sounds
exactly like her mother.
I will agree with that.
Oh good; it worked.
He's back on course!
I only know of one
who could even imagine
doing something like this.
How dare
that royal brat!
The bookmaker is supposed
to expose cheaters,
not be the cheater!
Empress Lashara,
Kenshi has somehow
found his way
back on course.
Are you kidding us?.
Already...?
We've barely been able to slow
that jerk down at all!
All right...
We've got another plan.
Good luck, Kenshi...!
You can do it!
Come on...!
Go Kenshi!
He almost made it to the lead;
the kid's gonna win!
Stupid Kenshi...!
We're going to break
his legs for this!
That kid
is something else.
Dagmyer!
Thanks, Chiaia.
What am I?
You're currently
in third place.
Behind Princess Aura...
and Kenshi.
Yes, but Princess
Aura is a Dark Elf...
and Kenshi
didn't actually enter
any of the other
tournament games.
Thank you for trying
to cheer me up...
Sadly...
I don't think I'll make that
next checkpoint in time,
as much as I might like to.
Then, you're stopping?
I am afraid I must retire.
However, as a man...
I certainly did make a
good show of it, didn't I?
He's finally catching up.
I expected it to come
down to these two.
Dagmyer has retired now...
All other contestants
are out of the race.
Well... I wonder
who's going to win, then.
He's keeping up
with my pace...
Impressive.
I guess it's time
to take this seriously.
We're receiving feedback.
Conduct a data check
and reexamine it.
Right...!
The data is accurate.
Please send all acquired
data to our motherland.
Yes, sir.
Looks as though we
finally found it!
Honestly... how much
stamina do those two have?
What should we do?
They've run the course
three times now.
All right...
Decrease time limits
between checkpoints...
If that doesn't work, we'll
go with the last checkpoint...
Whoever crosses it before
the other one will be
declared the winner.
Right.
This is actually starting
to get challenging.
Man... I can't believe I fell
for that weird list of rules...
I'm getting the idea something
bad might happen if I won.
What is he doing?!
Chiaia?
I've gotta be careful about
this so no one catches on.
Kenshi!
Chiaia?
If you back off, I'll take away
every crystal you're hiding...!
So pick up the pace!
Don't stop like an idiot.
Get out there and run...!
Boy, I'm sorry!
Oh, yeah, and you
better win this!
He is such a handful.
You guys are like
brother and sister.
Princess Aura!
Are you okay...? You still
have some time to make it...
What do you wanna do?
I just can't do it...
I think I'm going
to have to give up.
I've lost the main event.
Princess Aura is out!
She just retired at
Checkpoint Number Nine.
That makes it official.
The Wild Beast has
finally won the race.
Goodness.
You seem happy... Why?
Because I um...
I bet that Kenshi
would be the winner.
Oh.
Me too! We won!
What a stupid,
stupid head!
This is the first time
we've cursed our ability
to recognize talent.
It's like
losing your key
and being forced
to break into your house...
But then you end up falling
for one of the booby traps
you set yourself for
your own protection.
Congratulations, Kenshi!
Kenshi?
The wild beast
isn't stopping...
Why not?
I have no idea, he did
cross the finish line...
But what's more, he isn't
even slowing down, yet.
Can't lose!
Can't lose! Can't lose!
Can't lose! Can't--
Maybe he was actually a monster
instead of a wild beast?
I'd love an explanation
from his owner.
Chiaia must have threatened
Kenshi with something bad...
We imagine that is the reason
he's running like a mad man.
She threatened him?
It's fine; We're sure
he will stop eventually.
He must stop now.
I need him...!
The award ceremony's
about to start.
How would it look if
he didn't show up?
Oh yes, we know!
Meaning you have a plan?
No, but when do you think
he'll stop...? Wanna bet?
Kenshi, you
can stop running!
The race is over!
I don't think he can
hear us from back here...
This reminds me of the time
Miss Mexiah hypnotized him...
He's kinda acting
the same way.
It is possible.
Well, we might as well
resort to using force, then!
I've been waiting to
test this sucker out!
No... You can't!
Yes... Please don't!
Too late!
Take this!
And this!
And this! And this!
No way! How's my awesome machine
slower than some silly kid?
Uh-oh... He's
coming this way!
His eyes look as though
they're glazed over.
I guess he really is in
berserker mode, huh...?
Hey, Chiaia...
Why did Kenshi stop
all of a sudden
toward the end
of the race?
How should I know?
Because...
you were acting like
his sister at the time.
Oh yeah!
Hey, Kenshi!
Snap out of it,
or I will take away
every crystal you have!
Huh... It worked.
On it!
Maybe asking for Wahan's
help wasn't too smart...
You know how
intense she can get.
Kenshi!.
Kenshi,
where are you?!
Kenshi!
Look who's
finally awake.
Princess Aura.
What happened...
Where am I?
The forest?
Don't tell me I collapsed
from exhaustion
during the race
or something.
Actually, that's
not the case...
Well, I'm sure
I must have lost...
I was pushing
myself a little bit.
Are you listening
to me, Kenshi?
Wow... sorry
if I bothered you.
Will you please
listen to me?!
You're the winner
of the race, okay...
For whatever reason,
you kept running afterwards
like you didn't know.
What...?
I really did?
Yes.
That's pretty weird.
It is strange...
But you should know
how amazing you are...
Until you, I only ever
lost a race to my father.
Thanks a lot...
But you're the amazing
one, Princess...!
I've never seen anyone
run as fast as you.
I mean, other than my
sisters, of course.
Why thank you.
So... Kenshi?
What's up?
I think...
Well, I think that I...
I think I like you!
So, do--...
Do you--...
Do you want to be...
There you are!
Oh...
Hey, Chiaia!
I found him, guys!
He's over here!
Are you okay...?
All good?
Yeah...
I'm just fine.
Oh... and thank you
for your help, Princess...
I'm really sorry
if we were annoying.
You're fine.
Chiaia!
What?!
If we hurry, Kenshi can still
make it to the award ceremony!
You wanna come too,
Princess?
Thank you, Kenshi.
I hear you
found it, Uncle.
Yes...
Indeed I did.
Then it only makes
sense we get rid
of our biggest
obstacle first...
Right?
The event is almost here...
I think it would be wise for
us to avoid doing anything
that might arouse suspicion.
Huh?
Uncle, the job you came
to do here is done.
Feel free to shut up
and watch me work.
No, Sir Dagmyer,
you must not...!
Please, the students
aren't the only ones.
The faculty
adores that boy,
and the staff can't
say enough about him.
His death will
be investigated.
Silence!
You dare to order me...?
When did I say you could speak?!
Yes, yes.
But she's... so right...
Besides, Kenshi
is far too strong.
He's already done a number
on Lan and her friends,
or have you forgotten?
Whatever, this time we know
not to attack him head on.
You have made no real assessment
of his skills, though...
Let me help;
he will massacre you.
He's hardly an
issue right now...
And don't you have
something more important
than a servant
to worry about...?
On top of that,
Kenshi is the one
who helped us
out the most...
Couldn't we let him enjoy
his simple, peaceful life
just a tiny bit longer?
Oh, pretty please?
Very well, Uncle...
I shall defer to you on
the matter, this time.
Mark my words...
She'll try something.
She is a clever girl...
But could you look
after her for me anyway?
Done.
It's all falling
into place...
isn't it.
The real challenges
are yet to come.
I have a feeling I'm gonna
dig up a big one tonight!
Hey, there!
I recognize you!
Wow... This girl
is strong...
She's like,
"Chiaia good."
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I don't know what's goin' on, so
don't take this the wrong way...
but it seems crazy to waste
your own life like that.
So, thank you
for saving us.
I was only trying
to protect the girl...
Although, it appears
that wasn't necessary.
Well, technically, you did
throw a rope down, so...
There's that.
A storm is coming soon...
Be careful.
Consider that a "thank you"
for not hurting the girl.
A storm, but--...
What do you mean?
Hey...
That hole is dangerous...
would you mind taking
care of it for me...?
A Koro's
about to fall in.
Wait...!
Don't move!
Good...
That was close!.
Aw, that lady got
away because of you.
A storm, huh...?
I wonder
what that means.
Good morning!
What's wrong,
you guys?
Um...
What is that?
We knew this was our fate,
but we never thought things
would turn out the way
they have so far...
Next time on
Tenchi Muyo! War on Geminar...
Invasion...
We swear on our lives
that we will return!
You had better
prepare yourselves!