Blocks and guard shifts
for all countries in
attendance confirmed.
Yet another job well done!
Thanks. I was afraid I'd end up
breaking my operational limit.
Can you imagine
if word got out
I dirtied my cockpit
during the main event?
There'd go any luck I'd
have with any guy, ever.
I'm glad you didn't.
You know, it's funny...
I realize they're here for
Princess Lashara's coronation,
but...
I've never seen
so many ships before.
With Sir Dagmyer in front!
Even the male
Sacred Mechamasters
are in the guard shift.
Maybe I'll take a little
break and go say "hi" to him.
Well, if you get
the chance, good luck!
It's appreciated.
Oh... and don't forget to take
the bypath on your way back.
We don't want those
aho energy waves
from your Sacred Mechanoid
hurting anyone down there.
Will do!
Outta my way people,
coming through!
All these nobles
from all these countries
make quite the spectacle,
don't they...?
I suppose it's befitting
the honorable Shtrayu Empire,
though...
Or, rather...
befitting Lord Babalun.
Perhaps.
With the King's death, Lord
Babalun has assumed control
of the country.
Although she may be young,
she is the daughter of the
Empress and the belated Emperor!
I doubt she'll go
down without a fight.
This should be
quite the show...
I take it you came to evaluate
the situation for yourself,
as well?
That...
is our target.
You mean...
the little girl?
That is correct.
And remember:
You don't have
the luxury of options.
It's here!
Do it... Now!
Come on, you can do this...
I don't have a choice!
I wanna go home!
Little Empress Lashara...
Your pathetically short
reign has come to an end.
I knew it...
The Sacred Mechalord...
The Sacred Mechanoids
just can't compare...
It's magnificent.
Think so?
Yes, it has an air of dignity
and power impenetrable by most.
We thought it décor
immovable by most.
My Empress...
Even though it was only
for your coronation,
Shtrayu is the sole nation
allowed to borrow it
from the church.
You should show
more respect.
It's so big
and heavy, though.
We still think
it's stupid.
The Koro alarm?!
What's going on?!
We've just been
attacked, Empress...!
An enemy
Sacred Mechanoid!
My, my...
Some people are
so impatient...
We had not
anticipated attacks
until after training
in the Holy Land.
How strange... The Koro
did not notice this adversary
until it was practically
on top of us.
I wonder who it could be...
This is not a good sign!
Chiaia...
what is it?
It's a white
Sacred Mechanoid!
A what?!
Not good...
Go to the helm and have them
take us as low as possible
while maintaining
current speed...
Take care of her.
The Empress
is in your hands.
You are the Captain...
so whatever you wish.
Chiaia, wait!
We have much
to ask this girl...
so give her a proper
welcome, won't you?
Would you like
for me to contact
the Pilgrimage
Route Guard?
No, we mustn't insult
Chiaia's honor...
On top of that, we hate
asking Aura for help.
This is no time for ego.
As you command.
Do you encourage her?
Not at all...
A white Sacred Mechanoid
is unprecedented.
We have no way to identify
the Mechamaster behind it.
We shall find out
once we capture her.
Are you aware this ship belongs
to Her Majesty Lashara Earth
of the Shtrayu Empire?
If you refuse to answer,
I have no problem
forcing one out of you.
She's good.
And strong.
Knowing Dame Chiaia, I'm sure
she will be perfectly fine.
If she's up against only one.
We have not seen a foe
such as this, after all.
You're mine!
How'd she dodge me?!
Mahya, no...!
Sir Ulyte!
Who are you?.
And who ordered you
to attack us...?
Yes... My father's new
contraption works well...
Prepare to die!
Who was that?
The Sacred Mechalord...
What happened?!
There was only supposed to be
one Sacred Mechanoid on SWAN!
Oh, yeah!
I just rescued Empress
Lashara like a pro!
Points totally
scored for me!
Curse her!
No! The Empress?!
He's worthless.
Freeze, fool...!
Wait up!!!
How dare you
try to stop me!
You're an idiot
to challenge me
with those pathetic
fighting skills.
Come, on...
You're about to be the guinea
pig for my new weapon...
Lucky you.
You're finished!
Yeah, okay...
How's this?!
No...!
This girl's a decoy.
Move it!
What was that?
Oh, yeah...!
Way to go me!
Impressive...
So that's what Wahanly's
rumored "gunpowder" can do.
This damage is bad.
I have no choice
but to retreat.
You're not goin'
anywhere, buddy!
Whoa!
Where did that
thing come from?
Wait, now there's a
black Sacred Mechanoid?!
What's this?
You're falling apart.
Silence!
Stop jabbering and take me
to a safe location immediately!
Is that any way to talk to
the lady who just saved you?
Wait right there!
I still have a buncha stuff
I wanna test out on you!
Hurry!
Tell me what you
think of this!
Oopsie!
Come on!
You're right...
I'd rather not
get hit, after all
Oh, wow...
That hurts...
I feel bad for her...
but not bad
enough to stop!
Why do you keep
trying to leave?!
It's just you and me now!
Useless imbecile!.
We failed because you
couldn't hold them at bay...!
I have to retreat, but you
must take responsibility
for your error and kill
Lashara yourself...!
If you succeed...
I shall keep my promise
and return you to your home.
She's fast, and that
fighting stance is powerful.
But I still see
fear in her blade.
Her tail?!
I don't think so!
There's another one.
Hey there, looks like
somebody needs a little help!
You're supposed
to be in the workshop.
What are you doing here?
Rude! I'm the one
who saved the Empress!!
I don't have time
for your gadgets.
I'm a little busy
at the moment.
You were supposed to capture
her, not kill her, right?
So I was...
It's two to one now...!
We totally have the upper hand!
Don't let your guard down!
Her fighting stance
is unusual, at best!
Cool! It's tailed...
Looks pretty strong, too.
No... They
won't stop me...
I... Will...
Get back home!!!
What?!. She removed her
reactor's limiter!
What is that thing,
a monster?
She's amazing.
I wonder who she is.
Hit her!
Come on;
hit her already!!!
She has no limiter;
how's she okay?!
I don't know; she should
have passed out by now!
I'm out of ammo!
Oh great...
I've so gotta pee now.
What is going on now?!
She just hit her
operational limit!
Stop it!
I told you to stop!
The reactor is
over-accelerating!
Lashara...
Go now!
No!
Listen to me, Wahanly...
Oh please, not now!
You certainly put
on quite the show...
Sacred Mechamaster...
You...
You're not a girl?
I'm not.
Well, then...
We would not mind getting
killed by a Sacred Mechamaster
as strong as you.
Let's go...
I'm taking you with me.
Oh...? Are you saying you
wish to elope with us...?
Not that it isn't an
ever-so-tempting proposal...
But you appear
to be suffering
from a nasty case
of aho sickness...
Unfortunately, you are hardly
up to whisking us away.
Although, we must admit,
it is rather impressive
you can still move
after all you've done.
Why you-
It seems you still have
some fight left in you.
Hold on...
He's a guy?!
Stop!
Not only did he attack and
try to kill you, Empress,
he managed to break into
your chambers by himself.
You know only one man
is allowed in here.
It's fine.
But if people started
to doubt your purity,
it would damage the empire.
Which is not a problem if
people do not find out...
But primarily,
he is a precious witness
to the planning of
tonight's incident.
Male Sacred Mechamasters
are so rare;
it's difficult
to believe someone
would waste him
as an assassin.
We doubt he is even
a true assassin.
If he were serious...
he would have killed us when
he walked through the door.
True enough.
Whoever is behind this
has decided to use him
as a sacrificial pawn,
so who is to say we cannot
take him for ourselves.
But why?!
Think about it-he is
a young, powerful,
male Sacred Mechamaster...
We think he would sell for
a high price-do you not agree?
So... Lord Babalun has
finally made his move...
Who do you think will win?
How can you be so blasé?!
That man is dangerous!
It will merely
be a civil war
if no one contacts
the other countries...
This is hardly uncommon when
there's a shift in power...
More importantly...
He is correct.
In truth, our priority
at this time
should lie with the Sacred
Mechalord, above all else.
Centuries have passed
since we excavated it.
Why does it move now?
Your role has become...
exceedingly grave.
Look who's awake.
Ew...! Gross!
How many days in a row
did you wear those...?
They were filthy, so I went
ahead and washed them for you.
Now then, let's not
waste any more time.
I have a few questions
I need to ask you.
First I'm supposed
to say if you cooperate,
we will treat you well.
And please don't tell me you
think your nasty little friends
are planning
to come rescue you.
It's not gonna happen...
You're nothing more
than an expendable pawn.
Fine...
Just stay here forever
for all I care... Bye.
Oh, one more thing...
and you might want
to pay attention
because this
is very important.
You should probably
not tell anyone
you entered Empress
Lashara's bedroom,
because if you do, we will
execute you immediately.
Ooh, I can see him!
See who?
What are you
looking at?
It's him!
Oh, him! The boy
Dame Chiaia captured.
I can't believe
he's so young...
Is it just me,
or does he kinda look like
a little Koro in there?
Spying on our detainee
is unacceptable.
Lady Mahya!
I suppose
that's the boy?
Does something
about him upset you?
No... Nothing at all.
But Dame Wahanly does
have work to do...
Once you finish
checking for damages,
please deliver your report
to me straight away.
Yes, ma'am!
Empress Lashara,
why did you not report
what happened last night
to the nation?.
It is rather obvious who
these vicious attackers were.
Because they are the
most dangerous nation.
Lord Babalun.
But he's a good man.
That's true...
Good but...
Ambitious
above all else.
That man has nothing at all
to gain by assassinating us...
We also fail to understand
why he chose last night,
in particular, to resort
to such ugly methods.
You believe other
powers might be at work?
We are still attempting
to find that out...
Not to mention, letting
others beat up on us
is so not our style.
Find out how...?
We can barely even protect
the SWAN right now as it is.
Not true;
we have two Mechas.
So does that mean you're
planning to hire Wahanly?
She can quit the
Barrier Workshop now...
We could definitely
use her help
with repairing the SWAN...
not to mention your
damaged Sacred Mechanoid.
I suppose...
Her saving us was
too good to be true...
Right?
Right...
Right!
And there are some
not-so-great rumors about her.
Your majesty...
It may not sit well with you,
but the Pilgrimage Route Guard
should really be informed.
Then, you must hasten
back to the Holy Land.
But that would make
the enemy pull back...
If we do not get something
good on them quite soon...
even the Holy Land
won't be safe.
Come in!
Good morning,
Empress!
I'm glad you came...
You were marvelous
last night.
Nah...
It was nothing-I would
do anything for you.
Thank you...
What is that
you have there?
Just research materials
from the Barrier Workshop.
I can totally explain
all of them to you
if you have
a few minutes.
Wow...
First last night's
heroics and now this-
you certainly
are prepared.
Actually, last night was just
like a weird coincidence!
I had a couple of weapons I can
only test in the Holy Land,
but I wanted to show
them to you first.
You mean you fought with
that thing before testing it?!
'Tis fine...
We found the weapon
to be most impressive.
Does this container of yours
hold similar weaponry,
by chance?
Yep, by chance it does.
How very exciting...
Incidentally,
do you have any idea
who the attacker
might have been?
No... I'm sorry;
I don't.
Oh, Chiaia; I forgot to ask-Did
that intruder you found down
by the forest provide you
with any information of use?
He hasn't said a thing.
Rumor has it
he's just a boy.
What if he was the pilot
for that Sacred Mechanoid?
Oh yeah, like
that could happen!.
Who ever heard of a male Sacred
Mechamaster assassin before?!
Seriously.
One more thing, did
you find anything out
about the White
Sacred Mechanoid?
I did; she used a basic model
supplied by the Church...
That Mecha wasn't altered
at all, like even a little.
Meaning... All that power
belonged to the pilot.
Yeah, I hope she doesn't come
back; she was really strong.
How long will
the repairs take?
Well, mine'll be
done in no time...
But yours're gonna
take a bit; so sorry.
So, basically, we're down
to one Sacred Mechanoid?
Don't worry...!
I am all over it...!
I kinda had a feeling
this would happen.
Empress Lashara!
She's here!
Wait... my sister?
Now we have
two Mechanoids...
At least until
yours is fixed.
Oh, Lashara!
You've grown so much since
the last time I saw you!
Sister! Her Majesty Lashara
is the Empress of Shtrayu, now!
I missed your
coronation, too.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, Mexiah, why
did you come here?
Your loving sister flew
all night to get to you,
and this is how you act?
Stop! That seriously hurt!
Teachers from the Holy Land
are supposed to be prohibited
from aiding specific
countries in any way.
That rule doesn't
matter if I'm trying
to protect a
student though...
You know it's true.
Plus, we're borrowing the Sacred
Mechalord from the church,
so she's fine.
We're right?.
Right?
Exactly right,
Empress.
Now then, you can
focus on the repairs...
Chiaia... you fill Mexiah
in on what's happened.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Now we just
have to wait...
Let's hope the fish decides
to take our tasty bait.
A black and a white
Sacred Mechanoid...
How strange...
Where are their pilots?
They all got away.
But you did catch
that boy wandering
around by the forest...
Did he tell you
anything useful?
Nothing yet...
He won't talk.
It's probably those
scary eyes of your,
they frighten
all the boys.
I don't frighten boys!
Poor thing.
Don't you feel bad leaving
him out there like that?.
You should at least put
him somewhere warmer.
That defeats the point
of torturing him!
Help yourself...
You're hungry,
aren't you?
Rumor has it you
refuse to speak...
I hope that's not true because I
would love to know your name...
I'm Ulyte, by the way.
I'm...
Kenshi...
Masaki.
Masaki...
That's a rather
unusual name.
Are you
by chance from...
No... of course you're not;
how silly of me.
Well...
Enjoy, Kenshi!
Well done,
Sir Ulyte...!
You got him
to reveal his name.
No fair;
I wanted to do that!
"Kenshi," huh...?
Call me crazy,
but he doesn't seem
like he would be part
of an assassination attempt.
Either way,
I do feel bad leaving
him out there in the cold.
Still, you have to admit he's
kinda cute when he shivers.
It is not easy to witness,
but we follow procedures
in case he is an ally to those
who attacked the Empress...
These things must be done.
You are all making it sound
as if we were an evil monster.
We refuse to let even a prisoner
believe we are a monster...
We would never damage
our precious merchandise.
Merchandise?
We mean precious witness...
It would be a
loss if you died.
A loss?
Anyway, stay right here
and try to be good.
And be sure not to tell Chiaia
we brought this to you.
She is...
inflexible...
She's the one who has a somewhat
hostile look all the time...
Don't let her get
to you though;
she just has an
odd personality.
What...?!
Oh no...!
Chiaia!
Hi! We didn't
see you there!
You'll have to excuse
this viciously hostile
look on my face;
I can't help it-
I just have one of those
odd personalities.
We only said
'somewhat' hostile.
Please,
big brother...
Big sister...
Big sis...
The Koro seem to really
like you; it's fascinating.
Um! Who are you?
You have,
a big sister...?
She's not here, but I'd be happy
to take her place if you want.
What is it now?
Mexiah... what in the crap
are you doing in there?!
What?
He looked cold.
Why are you naked?!
Obviously,
I'm warming him up.
I've heard this is the best
way to get the job done.
He's not that cold.
No one is!
I swear; you are
so ridiculous.
Aw, I couldn't help myself;
the little guy was freezing!
Who cares?
That didn't mean you had
to get naked with him!
See you later, Kenshi!
You messed up,
Kenshi.
Doll!
Ready?
Nice...
She took the bait.
Dark Elves on the
Pilgrimage Route Guard...
There is an uninvited
guest in your airspace.
Dame Chiaia!
What is it?
That boy...
he escaped somehow!
Why isn't the Koro
alarm going off?
Chiaia?!
We have to admit, we are
a little eager to see
what we catch this evening.
Chiaia, you can't...! Your
knight frame has to be sent
to the Church for final
repairs; it's still broken!
Fine. Then I'll borrow yours.
Okay, but try to be careful!
Mine still hasn't been
fully restored, either.
That's weird.
Where did Mexiah's
knight frame go?
It's supposed to be
right over there.
Why have you not
finished Lashara off?!
How tragic.
You're from another world,
but this is all you've got.
Search him!
Yes sir!
He's wearing an aho magic
transmission circle!
I suspected as much.
Well, that was
surprisingly fast...
But it was certainly enough
for some valuable insight.
You're up, Chiaia.
How did the princess
win you over?.
Did she...
tell you she'd give you
whatever you wanted?
No... No.
Playing dumb?
I didn't say...
anything...
Either way...
It is no matter...
I had planned for you to die
here from the very beginning.
We had a deal.
Do you mean how I would send
you back to your world...?
We only needed you
to kill Lashara.
You're a pawn, and an
expendable one at that.
You're nothing more
than an expendable pawn.
Besides, we don't exactly have
the means to send you back.
You lied to me.
Goodbye.
What are you
waiting for?.
Kill him already!
I want him dead!
Go!.
Get him!
Why are you laughing...?
You should be
finishing him off!
You want me
to kill Kenshi...?
With my hands...?
Surely you jest.
How dare you?!
Registry: unknown...
It's just
as we were told...
Yes.
You dare humiliate me?!
You owe me for everything
I've done for you.
Interesting...
Oh no...
You've gotten sick,
haven't you?
I don't like the idea
of him dying here...
How will you act,
Aura Shurifon.
Dissention
in the ranks?
What's going on?
What is Aura doing here?
I should have thought
about this first.
I wonder who's inside
that Mechanoid.
I can't even attack, let
alone move quickly...
I should bring him inside.
No, a Sacred
Mechanoid's aho waves
are dangerous to commoners...
What do I do?
Is that...
Gunfire...?
The boy!
Fine; I'll kill both of you!
I need help.
I'm pleased
you rescued him.
Let me help.
Who was that?
Chiaia Flan!
If it isn't Aura Shurifon!
It's the boy!
You go on ahead.
I'll take care of this.
Gladly.
This might be more obstacles
than I can handle...
I need to retreat.
Please, Princess Shurifon,
you can't go in!
As we are on a pilgrimage,
the SWAN has special rights...
My apologies,
but you cannot enter.
But as a member of the
Pilgrimage Route Guard,
I cannot let this go...
I will need some answers.
I'll certainly explain
the situation...
However, first I would like
you to surrender him to me.
This boy is my
exclusive witness...
Meaning I won't simply
hand him over...
And I would prefer to
hear your explanation
from Empress
Lashara herself.
I only informed HQ that I
saw something suspicious...
As long as the situation
is reasonable,
I won't need
to report it.
Stay back.
'Tis fine.
She has our
permission to board.
Empress Lashara Earth...
Please pardon my demeanor
during this crisis.
Of course...
It would be highly inappropriate
to discuss these matters here...
Would you care
to talk over tea?.
Chiaia.
As the one who just
saved this boy's life...
I will keep him until
I understand the situation.
I heard Kenshi's back!
Mexiah...?
Where have you been?!
Miss Mexiah!
What are you doing here?
Oh no...
I'm sorry... but it's likely
aho sickness from my Mechanoid.
It's worse...
Look at that rash!
It's Rodeshiatore...
The altitude sickness.
Rodeshia-what?
He's gotta be
from somewhere
that has a really
high altitude...
Rodeshiatore is an illness
specifically from the Ena Ocean.
So you've had it, too?
Oh, no way; I'm fine...
But I've already had
the vaccination for it...
If this boy's got it,
he could die.
We've gotta do something;
he's burning up.
Honestly, I'm surprised
you tried killing him...
Reckless behavior.
It's too dangerous
to let him live!
Jealous of someone
better than you?
If we allow him to live,
he'll reveal who we are.
We're dealing with
the princess...
I'm assuming she
already knows.
That's all the more
reason to destroy
whatever evidence
is left out there!
Focus on killing Lashara
before she enters the Holy Land.
Yes, sir.
Prepare to launch
the Sacred Mechanoid...!
And move the ship before
the Pilgrimage Route Guard
gets here!
At this rate, he has about
six hours before he falls
into a coma and suffers
heart failure.
I know...! I've heard
if the shot isn't good enough,
and you get sick anyway,
a natural antidote
is the Triam herb!
Oh...
Triam is rarely
used as medicine,
so we don't normally
carry any on board.
Then I shall go
and find some.
I'll go with you!
We leave the SWAN in your
more than capable hands.
Triam grows in the shallows
of rivers and lakes,
but we may have
difficulty finding
any since the herb
is not in season.
There's not much time...
Let's split up, shall we?
Agreed...
So he is from another world,
just as I suspected...
How, I wonder, did
they summon him here?
It is of no matter...
at the moment we must
focus on keeping him alive.
Your pacing is
making me nervous.
Quit worrying about
me and get that done!
They could come back and
strike at any moment!
Oh crap! I wasn't ready
for them to show up...
This sucks...!
What're we gonna do?!
I'm not done with it, yet!
Guess I'll just have
to go with skill.
Well, well... Someone's
overly confident, huh?
There are three enemy
Sacred Mechanoids...!
Change course
above the Draft!
Moving above the Draft.
Attack!
Looks like the number one
Reactor Ring is hit, sir!
We can't increase the power!
They managed to damage
our large Barrier Reactor.
Those aren't normal
Sacred Mechanoids.
One of them is missing...
Three-to-one is
hardly even a fight!
No... I can't
win against three...
What if I used his
fighting style...?
She's gone!
That's so rough on
the knight frame...
I can't believe he managed
to fight like this!
Crazy...
I just don't have the power!
What's wrong?
Dead already?
Who's that?!
Impressed?
Triam should be
somewhere around here.
I know it.
Who's there?!
Shocking dodge.
Well played.
A Black Mechanoid?
You're done!
What?!
If you had that, why
did you wait to use it?!
Watch your tone;
remember, I'm the one
who just saved
your big ol' butt!
And, so you know, this bad boy
takes a little time to activate.
You're certainly
a tough one...
But you'll be reaching
your limit, soon.
Where is Miss Mexiah?
I need her help...
Focus... We have to get
the Triam to that boy!
Not now...
My operational limits.
I can't move...!
Was that her
Dark Elf Field...?
No... I've lost.
I can't believe I had
to activate my field.
That was pathetic, Aura...
It doesn't matter
how strong a weapon is
if you can't hit the target.
I'm still here, sir
If you can still move,
retrieve the other knight
and retreat immediately!
But... sir!
I can handle this
on my own...
Don't leave
any evidence... Go!
Right.
What is that...?!
Are you kidding me?.
Your reaction time is awful!
Wow... That stupid
jerk is fast...!
Crap!
I'm out of ammo!
Without any bullets, you're
fighting with a mere toy.
Not good!
Oh...
What is that?
Aura...
are you okay?
A black Sacred
Mechanoid appeared.
What?
And you faced it alone?
Why didn't you let me know?
It doesn't matter;
did you find the herb?
Yes...
This is Triam, isn't it?
Yes, it is...
Let's head back, quickly.
Why's she so weak?
She must have
activated her field.
We have to go.
I swear, Aura, you
are beyond stubborn.
Try not to push
it too hard...
You still haven't been
baptized, you know.
Yes, I'm aware.
A Sacred Mechanoid
of unknown alliance
and a black Sacred
Mechanoid...
What in the world
is going on?
What now?
Hello.
You fool!
We got him!
What?!
Oops...!
I guess I missed!
Your aim is the worst!
I know...!
Quit reminding me!
Curse you!
What the?!
Mexiah!
I knew it...
Doll screwed this
up completely!
I'm done here.
I've seen that stance and
fighting style before...
Don't tell me it's
who I think it is.
You're back!
I heard Lashara and the others
entered the Holy Land territory.
I need you to lend
Doll to me again.
Doll shall remain asleep
until the time is right.
Concentrate on
personal duties, now...
Unfortunately, we've no time
to waste on the princess...
Understood, sir.
Wonderful!.
You're finally awake!
Your fever is gone.
It's surprising.
The herbs are good, but you're
still recovering swiftly.
I hope you appreciate
all of this.
And don't worry
about paying us back;
you can just
do it whenever.
Will you shut up?
Um... Thank you so much.
Come here!
Oh!
Back off, crazy.
He's recovering!
Now get some rest.
Go back to sleep
until morning.
We suppose we could all
stand to take that advice.
Beautiful...
Behold, Kenshi...!
That is the academy
for Sacred Mechamasters!
Isn't it fun how so much stuff
happens as soon as we get there?
Next, on Tenchi Muyo!
War on Geminar:
To the Holy Land!
I guess it's time
for your glorious debut!