I've never seen anything
like this before...
After they lost contact
with the Church,
the countries took up
defensive positions
'cause they're all scared of
the Black Sacred Mechanoid.
We have to take down
the SWAN no matter what!
Once we've beaten them,
Shurifon, Havoniwa, Shtrayu
and the Holy Land will have to
bow down and follow Babalun...
Then we'll get the money and
respect we've got coming to us.
RONIN can officially
join the army
and earn the name
Sacred Mechamaster.
And you're positive you
can deliver on that?
If the three nations
and the Holy Land merge,
we have a real shot at
conquering the continent.
Keep your eye on the prize.
Are you sure it's a good idea
to let her take the lead?
Oh, I'm fine with it...
It's not like Dagmyer can
be of any use to us now.
She's a loose cannon and
I don't trust her judgment...
Something has to be
done about it at once.
She's partially responsible for
us losing the barrier reactor,
but so what...?
It's not like we've
been able to figure out
how to use it anyway.
You two can stay here
and get some R &amp; R...
It would suck
if something happened
to our Male Sacred
Mechamasters.
Just calm down,
Chiaia...
Doll, or... Mexiah,
we guess we should say,
clearly didn't come here
just to do harm
to your father.
Yes but still-!
Do we have any information on
what exactly this Neizai stole?
She took a device that
deletes Core Crystal data.
The thing is, if the
Central Core Crystal inside
an artificial
being can be reset,
then there's no one to pilot
the Sacred Mechalord.
As far as I know, it's the
only sure-fire way to defeat it.
I see, but what
happens if we do that?
If we go that route,
Mexiah would be gone forever.
You guys...
We can't.
Hey, this wasn't an easy
decision for Naua either.
That's horrible.
They needed two
Sacred Mechalords
to defeat Gaia
the last time!
And those two were the
most advanced machines
the previous civilization
ever created...
Even as powerful
as Kenshi is-
As things stand now,
he can't win.
No luck. We tried
to use Kenshi's bullets,
but they're insufficient
as an energy source.
Surely the issue isn't that
they aren't strong enough?
It's just the
opposite, actually.
We're unable to mount them...
They're too strong...
In fact, we can't
even scratch them.
Yeah... that's my bad,
I'm sorry about that.
I think I got it!
She's right.
Kenshi can use his compression
abilities to make a weapon.
Even though they were replicas,
his compression bullets
blasted through those shields
like they were nothing.
We might be able to use
that power against Gaia!
It could really work.
The issue is finding
the materials we need.
Couldn't he gather up
a whole bunch of boulders,
rocks and debris that
are lying around unused?
No, that won't work, the
weapon'll be too brittle...
What we're gonna need
is one massive rock.
Do you mean like
a metal ingot?
Exactly like that...
One that's
as huge as the SWAN!
How...? Something that
big doesn't exist.
Yes it does, and we're all
flying on it right now.
No... No way!
The SWAN's my country!
The fate of the entire
world rests on this, Kenshi!
Could you at least wait till
I dig up all the crystals?
You idiot! That would
tear the SWAN apart!
I don't wanna!
The SWAN might be on
the small side actually.
Really?
Well... Then how big
does it need to be?
If we use stone, hundreds
of times larger than the SWAN.
What...? Where are we supposed
to find something like that?
I know.
Yukine...?
Are you sure?
The SWAN changed course.
Any idea what that's about?
Very peculiar.
It doesn't appear that
they're going to hook up
with the Havoniwan army.
Oh, who cares...? Wherever
they go, I'll follow 'em there.
We're gonna finish them off
this time for sure!
I promise!
That's correct! If it's not a
horrible inconvenience to you,
I would like to use that
facility as a meeting point.
Naturally, we wouldn't
cause any problems at all...
And the Pope's already
given us permission.
I'm very surprised
you gave approval.
I didn't have a choice.
Considering the situation
we find ourselves in,
the priority of the Church
must be recovering
our functionality.
If she calls this an extension
of student council affairs,
you must give your
approval then too, yes?
That sounds like an...
Yes, that's true.
I have to ask you, who is this
Kenshi Masaki to push Lithia
to such great lengths?
He's had the same effect
on all the students here,
as a matter of fact.
Hang tight,
almost there!
Done and done.
Well, I'm so glad
to hear that.
He's a good boy,
that's all.
I am so terribly sorry
to put you out like this,
but I just-
Lithia...!
Lady Lithia!!!
What is wrong with you?
I'm standing right here!
What's the matter...?
Why are you yelling at me?
Uh...
Hello there.
Hey Lapis, isn't she the old
student council president...?
That is her, right?
Yeah... Her name
is Dame Morga.
You two... Please stop your
gossiping and get back to work!
Yes, ma'am.
Now...
Lady Lithia...
Would you care
to explain exactly
why you never bothered
to contact me?
Because you're serving
as the Trible Royal Court's
Sacred Mechamaster.
I just assumed you had more
important things to do.
Well, there's no point
fretting over one country
when the entire world is
on the verge of destruction.
Besides, I consider it a
high honor to gather arms
under a Sacred Mechamaster
from another world!
Wait, how do you
know about that?
Even though
I'm just an alumni...
I still keep tabs on my
precious alma mater...
No matter what the danger,
I will always...
This sorta reminds me of the
'not so good old days.'
Yeah, me too.
Oh, calm down...
Just leave this to me, okay?
I can handle
everything from here!
No, I will not!
Great...!
I have to go prepare...
I'll see you soon!
Morga, stop...
Hold on!
Lapis?
Yes, ma'am?
Send the transmission to King
Trible right away, please.
Yes, ma'am.
At the very least,
that should help buy us
a little more time...
I'm in for it...
That woman may
have some talent,
but she never did quite learn
how to play well with others.
Wow, it's so big...
Just unbelievable.
Here in Yukine's hometown,
it's worshipped as
their guardian deity.
Occasionally, they conduct
rituals, ceremonies,
and important summits here.
So that's gonna
be our weapon?
Over my dead body!
This structure is sacred.
We won't sit back and
watch you destroy it!
But we have to!
Yukine...
you're from a long
line of priestesses
who swore to protect
this place...
We won't let this ruffian
desecrate our shrine
and use it in
someone else's war!
Please sir, you
must see reason...
If we don't do something,
this world is doomed forever!
Princess Maria, not you too...!
Oh, this is a nightmare...!
Your mother would
never even consider
such a deplorable measure!
Oh, she would
do it all right,
she just wouldn't
tell you first.
Would you let me
ask the goddess?
Ask her...?
Yukine.
Impossible...!
Have you already forgotten
that you were unable
to enter the barrier?
You can't... No one's been
able to for fifteen years now...
Not since your
grandmother passed away...
Not a single soul
has done... What?!
Hey, you! You're not
allowed to go in there!
Uh... I'm sorry!
What are you doing...?
Are you trying
to embarrass us?
What... in
the heck was that?!
I swear... The kids these
days have no respect.
Uh...
Do you see that?
They treat this place
like it's nothing
but a tourist attraction.
Please, look.
You... I am so disappointed,
you should know better!
Please look.
Little brat...! I told you
not to go in there...!
You come right back
here this minute!
Don't you know what
forbidden means...?
You crossed the barrier!
Well, he seems to have
finally caught on.
A miracle!
Um... what?
What are they doing
in a place like that?
Well, go on.
This new Mechanoid can move in
bursts, even with a low output.
And its operational limit
has been upgraded big time.
I wish I had enough ready
for everyone right now,
but don't worry, they'll be
done in time for our siege
on the Holy Land...
At any rate, one
goes to Kenshi...
and we can all take turns
using the other two.
Sounds good!
Kenshi... Don't compress it more
than twenty 'm' in one go...
Otherwise your powers
will fry the knight frame.
Now...
Let's do this!
I'm all over it.
All right...
Here's to hoping
no enemies show up
until we've finished
compressing that monolith.
A sword...?
What do you mean?
Lan, look!
No way...
What's that?
Amazing... He did
it in one try.
What the-?
Incredible!
Kenshi... This anti-gravity ring
will indicate when you're done.
Did you see that? What in
the world are they up to?
It seems to me as though
they're compressing
that monolith in
an attempt to make a sword.
That big rock?
The battle at
the Barrier Workshop
should have been
documented for reference...
especially with regard to
Kenshi's compressed bullets.
Oh, that.
Is something the matter?
It looks like he's
taking a little break...
He just swapped out
with the other two.
That's weird...
He's leaving.
I think they're
holding it up for him.
I can't begin to imagine
how heavy a stone structure
of that size must be...
If they try to set it down,
even for a moment,
it will sink
into the surface.
Say, uh... If we let them turn
that thing into a sword,
that's bad news
for us, yeah?
Do you really think you stand
a chance against Kenshi?
Who do I look like,
Dagmyer...?
Just 'cause he's weak,
doesn't mean I am, too.
No, not again.
Oh, come on,
get up...
If you're going to sleep,
please do so in your room!
No, thank you...
I'll just stay here.
We never cease
to be amazed by him.
I think it's best we leave
Kenshi alone, Empress Lashara.
Why's that?
Wait, what are
you talking about?
I've heard in the previous war,
Sacred Mechamasters slept
on the ground upon reaching
their operational limit...
According to legend, it helped
them recover more quickly.
We've never heard
that story before.
It was an emergency measure
used only on the front lines...
Back then, the rotations
of the Sacred Mechamasters
were far worse than what
they are up against today.
All right...
Fine then...
This seems as good a place
as any to set up camp.
As you wish, Empress.
Hey... What's the
game plan, Lan?
It's simple enough.
We wait for
the perfect moment.
Looks like
they're struggling.
The rock is definitely
getting smaller,
but the weight is going
to stay the same.
Even though they're taking
turns, they must be exhausted.
You should go and
get some more rest.
No, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You need sleep.
Just focus
on compressing it.
But you're exhausted.
I'm okay... Can we hurry
it up though, please?
Looking good...
This was well
worth the wait...!
All right, guys,
let's move out!
They're much too slow.
This is no good.
Oh no!
Should we attack the ship?
No way, we're gonna get
an even bigger reward
if we can manage to take
that sword of theirs away!
Enemy crafts
approaching rapidly!
Kenshi!
Yukine! That's just a regular
Sacred Mechanoid, so be careful!
All right, boys,
let's do this!
Guys...!
Watch your backs!
Look out!
No!
Like I thought... it takes
all the energy they've got
just to support the rock!
We're almost there!
Come on... Drop it
already, you jerks!?
It's Yukine!
Keep going...!
I'll take care of them!
No, you can't...
You're in no condition
to fight all on your own!
Wait, where are
the rest of them?!
On the way!
Great,
Sacred Mechanoids!
Don't waste time on her...!
Make them drop the boulder!
The Ena is thin!
Oh, you're just useless,
that's why you're a lowly RONIN!
Don't come near them!
Well, this should
be interesting.
I'm okay!
Yukine!
Kenshi...!
Hurry up!
They won't be able to
hold out for much longer!
We have to power
through this,
if they don't compress
it right now,
we won't get
another chance!
Yukine...
Just hang in there.
There are too many of them,
there's nothing I can do!
Reached your
operational limit?
Yukine! No!
I'm fine...! Don't stop,
we need that sword!
Attack!
You guys...!
Hang on!
Yukine?
This girl
doesn't give up.
It's no use!
Not at this rate!
Keep pushing on!
We can't.
Yes...
We need this sword...
Keep going!
We have to...
To defeat Gaia.
Yukine!
Finish them!
Go ahead and get it over
with, you wild beast!
Who's that?!
This can't be...!
Who are they?!
Awesome.
Amazing...
It's going to work.
Yes!
I was so close,
I could taste it.
Yukine...
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm all right...
I'm glad we made it.
All right, Kenshi!
Oh... Hey, you guys!
Long time
no see, Kenshi!
No, no, Gryno...
You call him Sir Kenshi now.
I'm glad to see
everyone is all right.
Principal!
These ladies insisted on
being there by your side
to fight with you.
Lady Lithia... Lapis.
If you'll let us, we will
follow wherever you go...
Sir Kenshi Masaki.
Why did you
come here, Uncle?
Is it to laugh at me?
Oh no... I imagine that you've
had your fill of that...
But in the end, you still want
to be a Sacred Mechamaster,
don't you?
Ends don't justify
the means...
In matters such as these,
the process will always
outweigh the outcome.
Yes, but-
I wanted to beat him
so badly... That's all.
But I have failed.
Don't worry, the Sacred
Mechalord will revive
soon enough.
Be proud...
Your original mission to buy us
time was a resounding success.
I see, so you're done with
me now, is that about right?
I have prepared the Sacred
Mechanoid I made for Doll...
Oh... I suppose I should
say I prepared a frame
that utilizes
Mechaworker technology.
I understand...
After all this, you want me
to go down with him, don't you?
Come on, don't you think
it's about time you got to do
what you wanted, my nephew?
Are you serious?
Wow.
I've never seen anything like
this before, it's amazing.
So hey, Wahanly...
Even though it's compressed,
the mass of the rock
is still the same, isn't it?
Yeah, of course it is!
That's awesome!
I can't believe that ring
can support its weight...
Even Hazuki
can get near it,
so obviously, the ring must
have a low output reactor.
Master Naua gave us a special
ring he found in the ruins.
If this was a normal one,
it would snap right in two.
Wait, that's the
original ring...?
I'm surprised he's letting
us use something like that.
Yeah, me too. Must be
a sign of the times.
Sorry for the wait...
So tell me,
what can I do for you?
Oh...! The walk-in
refrigerator's temperature
is going up.
Oh. How terrible.
My, my...
We've become quite
the party, haven't we?
Thank you for all your
help back there, Lapis...
You saved us.
Oh, well...
I didn't do much, but that's
very nice of you to say.
Without your help, we
wouldn't have succeeded.
It was an excellent battle...
And it showed great
leadership on your part.
Wow, Kenshi, you really are
full of surprises, aren't you?
First a Sacred Mechamaster and
now you're King of the SWAN!
We think you're
incredible!
It's true.
And now all of us get to work
together one more time.
I never dreamed
this would happen.
Yeah, don't you get it,
you're the reason everyone
has gathered here!
Hail, King Kenshi!
Uh.
Kenshi,
are you all right?
Yeah...
I'm fine...
It's really nothing.
We love you,
King Kenshi!
Sacred Mechamasters
from around the world
are coming to serve
Empress Lashara and Kenshi.
Although, I wasn't sure
if you were right...
you certainly called it.
His physique and mannerisms
are rather unique.
We may have just borne witness
to an historical moment, ladies.
I have no idea how you knew,
but I'm impressed.
Yes, I am too.
Are you sure you're
all right, Kenshi?
You really don't
look so good.
Yeah... I'm okay.
Yes, we understand...
Use the compressed bullets
to cross the highlands...
But still.
Only three of our knight
frames will be able
to make that trip...
If Doll shows her face,
Kenshi will have no choice
but to fight her...
And that will leave us only
two frames to ward off
the rest of the enemy's
main forces...
With odds like that, there's
no guarantee we can prevent
the Sacred
Mechalord's revival.
Our odds will increase
if we take them by surprise.
But Rea...
No...
Neizai can see
right through us...
Don't discount her yet.
She's still a major problem.
Even so, of all our options,
this one seems
most likely to succeed.
The question now is how
quickly can our main forces
break through
the enemy's defenses,
complete their mission,
and regroup with us.
Oh yeah...
There's that.
What's the matter,
Empress?
Is there something
bothering you?
Oh my goodness!
King Kenshi! Are you okay?
What's going
on down there?!
Is that Kenshi?!
It's a fever,
he's burning up!
I wouldn't worry, it's probably
brought on by exhaustion...
He just needs to rest.
Poor guy.
It's hardly surprising.
Since we fled the Holy Land,
he's not had a moment's rest.
Then to top everything off,
he had to compress that
huge monolith all by himself.
Weird...
I feel like I've been
in this position before.
Wipe that creepy smile off
your face and get some sleep!
Oh no, the fever's
made him delusional!
Ladies, please
try to keep it down
when you're sitting
by a sick boy's bed.
We're not
kidding around...
You need to rest.
Time to go, Yukine.
Keep an eye on him and let
us know if you need anything.
I will.
That Ulyte jerk is a
slave driver, isn't he?!
It is what it is, so stop
complaining and keep working!
We failed our mission.
We deserve it!
You'll get another chance...
We're transferring to
the front line of defense.
Ulyte. I take it
everything is in order.
Yes, brother,
of course it is.
The bandits
used Mechaworkers
to tear apart Havoniwa's
railway system...
Their route to the
highlands is now cut off.
My concern at this
point is the ability
of their Sacred Mechanoids to
function outside of Ena's draft.
Right. There's good
news on that front.
Compressed bullets are their
current energy source,
and even if they had a whole
arsenal of Mechanoids,
they would barely
have enough power
to successfully send three
of them across the border.
Although...
It would be enough energy
to send Kenshi's White
Sacred Mechanoid through.
And?
Both its operational
time and capabilities
outside of the Ena Ocean
have improved significantly...
With the Black Sacred
Mechalord inoperable,
he has the power
to obliterate us.
Then all I need to do
is turn their ray of hope
into fear and despair.
I'm really worried
about Kenshi.
I hope he
gets better soon.
Yeah, me too.
Looks like
your fever's down.
How did you manage
to get in here...?
Did anybody
see you come in?
Habits don't usually change
and they're no exception.
Sneaking in was even easier
than I thought it would be.
So what, have you
come back for good?
No... But I have something
I would like to tell you.
Okay, but you'd
better hurry.
Of course...
I went to the Barrier
Workshop to learn something...
Something only my father
would be able to confirm.
And I was right...
Everything I thought was true.
Tell me, Father.
During the age of the
ancient civilization,
the artificial beings created
to defeat the Sacred Mechalord
possessed such
advanced faux bodies
that they were fully capable of
procreating with actual beings.
Naturally...
This wasn't exclusive
to beings from our world.
There was a possibility that if
one bred with an other worlder,
the child of mixed blood
would end up stronger
than both parents...
Though unions such as these
never actually happened,
and these mixed
children didn't exist.
The Gaias were fierce...
And they attacked
other worlds...
Any beings that could
pilot a Sacred Mechanoid
were always the
primary targets.
The timeframe for summoning
did not fall in that dark era...
As a result, they were unable
to summon more other worlders.
But... Inversely,
they did have the ability
to send their own kind
to other worlds...
As such, the only
safe option
was to send an artificial
being in their place...
The being would procreate
and then after some time
had gone by, they would
summon the child back.
And so you were created and
sent here from another world.
No... that can't be true.
The way the Sacred
Mechanoid reacted to you...
The incredible
powers you possess...
The simple fact that,
even now, I am still unable
to attack you is all
the proof you need, Kenshi.
But how come you
can't attack me?
An artificial being's unique
biowaves cannot be bred out...
We have no choice
in the matter.
Don't you see...?
We are programmed
not to attack anyone
who emits those waves...
That's not all...
This fever and the
fatigue you're feeling.
It doesn't have anything
to do with me...
And it has nothing to do with
your resistance to harming me.
Yes... You and I
are the same...
In this whole world, there's
no one else like you and me.
Strange, isn't it?
It's Babalun!
Wait, what are you doing?
I'll admit, I was
concerned about you...
But once you're
properly disposed of,
there'll be no one
left to defy me.
Slave...
Accept my orders or die!
So... What are
we gonna do now?
Wait, what are
you talking about?
She means, if the
worst comes to pass,
how are we
going to fight them
without the Wild
Beast in our corner?
We're not fighting!
Well, we can't
just do nothing... Can we?
Oh Aura, not you, too.
He is from another world.
In the end, the outcome of
this war is our burden to bear
and no one else's,
especially his.
She's right...
This is something the
citizens of our planet
should fight to resolve.
We can't just
rely on Kenshi...
But one fact still remains.
He is the only chance we have.
It sure is
pathetic, isn't it?
Mother, it's you!
And my father, too?
We weren't so foolish
as to think you two
would not show up...
But we did not
expect you so soon.
And I'm happy to see
you as well, Lashara...
I just got word that my future
son declared his independence.
No... He isn't
your future son,
he is my daughter's
future step-father.
Mother, will you stop?
Your radical notion
has left that
daughter of yours speechless...
Although, it's really
not an awful idea.
But, Father!
Well, well.
Now they both seem
to be in complete
and utter bewilderment,
don't they?!
If they're thinking what we're
fairly certain they're thinking,
any reasonable being
would be in shock.
So that's why you're here...
To poke fun and mock
us to our faces.
On the contrary,
we'd like to demonstrate
how mature we both can be.
I'll never obey you!
There's simply no point in
you resisting any further...
You were made to
follow orders...
It's the only
reason you exist...
Give in to your true
nature and bow down...
Become what you
were destined to be!
Shut up!
I don't care
why I'm here...
or why I exist...
I'm me...
And I have a will
that's my own...!
I'll die before I follow
your orders, understand?!
'A will', you say?
Even when that 'will' is nothing
more than a fabrication...?
Does a newborn
babe have free will...?
One's opinion changes
depending on the expectations
set before them...
By opposing me, you are only
meeting Lashara's expectations,
are you not?
But there were others
who planted the expectation
of 'submission'
deep in your heart...
And that, Slave, will
turn you into my doll.
There's nothing you can do
in a battle against your fate!
Yes. There is!
Even if someone planned
this whole thing out...
Every choice I made, every
action I took in my life...
Those things were done
'cause I chose to do them!
You wretched doll.
I am not your doll...!
I'm Kenshi...!
And I don't
believe in fate!
Impossible...!
You cannot defy me!
You little brat!
Doll...!
Destroy the SWAN!
I'll check on him!
I must say, I'm constantly
impressed by the stunts
you're able
to pull off...
Yet...
Hey, what happened?!
Mexiah!
Chiaia,
is something wrong?!
Your sister.
Bye.
Chiaia, wait!
What is going on?!
There's an abnormal
mass inside the hangar!
Wait, what do you
mean 'abnormal?'
The Tenchi sword!
Its anti-gravity
ring's broken!
Oh no!
That is not good...
You know what
this means, right?
Oh, please tell me
this isn't happening.
No, don't go!
Empress!
We're crashing!
The weight of the
sword is just too much!
We're going down, fast!
Maximize our output now!
If we don't do something
about the Tenchi sword quick,
the SWAN's doomed!
Yukine, I want
you to help her!
Right!
Where's Lapis...
Is she okay?
Yes... We had just
put her to bed.
What about you...? Are you
sure you're all right, Kenshi?
Yeah... I think most of
the numbness is gone now.
I'm good to go!
What's taking
Wahan so long?!
No use!
We're falling!
It's over!
Something stopped it.
Why didn't we crash?
Excellent catch.
This is the awesome power
of his new knight frame!
It's so incredible...!
We should be calling
it a Sacred Mechalord!
Curse you...! How dare
you not submit...?!
Very well...
Then I have no choice but to
crush you with my own two hands!
You'll see, the real
Sacred Mechalord
will awaken soon enough!
Now then...
Let's stick to the plan.
Right.
We're all counting
on you, my dear Kenshi.
Don't worry, son.
You'll do fine.
Thank you.
Well, goodbye for now.
I'll see you soon.
Please be careful...
And keep an eye on her, Yukine.
I'm happy to.
Father...
Best of luck.
Remain true
to your husband.
I will.
Let's go.
Right!
Havoniwa and
Shurifon's armies
are gathering around the
checkpoint as we speak...
Our time has come.
Indeed.
At last it's time
for the final battle!
We take it you are ready!
Next time on
Tenchi Muyo! War on Geminar:
"Gaia."
If we win this war,
there is bound
to be a flood of girls
dying to marry you.
You ready for that?!
We sure do hope so!