Huh... Tonight's just
as quiet as last night.
Hey, are we positive those
guys are headed our way?
We sure are...
They have to.
Havoniwa's
railway is down,
so this is the only
entrance to the Holy Land.
Do you think our forces
will be enough to stop them
when they get here, though?
What, are you
scared, princess...?
This was originally
a fortress...
We have buried
defensive capabilities.
Yeah...
Not to mention the underground
barrier reactors here
makes the whole
joint Ena free.
Their Sacred Mechanoids won't
be able to get close to us.
That's a good point, and with
the formation we're using,
I guess we only have to worry
about the highlands.
Those long cords
all over the place
will keep their cabled Sacred
Mechanoids from attacking.
And their Mechaworkers
got nothing on us.
As long as we've got our
Shield of Gaia replicas
there's no way
they can beat us.
I'm looking forward to it.
They're weak little babies,
and they don't even know it.
Yeah, but... what about
that white one...?
He can move outside
the Draft, can't he?
Well, the white
one won't come...
Don't worry about him.
Even if he did show up,
we'll still be able to win
as long as we can hold out until
the Sacred Mechalord revives.
If Babalun conquers the world,
we'll get rewarded big time.
So, I'm counting
on you guys
to make sure this
goes down as planned.
No mistakes, got it?
Yeah...
we got it.
Woah... What the...
We're under attack!
Move it, now...!
Activate the Mechas!
And so it begins...
All units,
commence fire!
Shoot all you want--
there's no way
you're taking this checkpoint
down with a frontal assault.
Make sure you
don't get too close.
Concentrate fire
on the gate's cannons!
Would you like me
to deploy my unit, now?
Hey, Lan!. Havoniwa
sent out cabled Mechanoids!
Don't panic.
They can't get close
with those cables attached.
Just like the
battery-operated ones.
Oh, no!
You didn't expect
those landmines, did ya?
You know, it's almost too
easy with that white one gone.
What the...?
What was that?
What's going on out there?
Changing the screen, now!
What the heck are those?
They look like
moving armors.
And they're using
steam reactors!
Take that!
I think I got 'em!
Why are RONIN so stupid?
Every highland Sacred
Mechanoid we've got is down!
They also severed
the battery line!
Try to keep it together.
They haven't broken
through, yet!
Get the Mechaworkers out there
and reconnect those lines!
And in the meantime, deploy
all remaining Mechanoids!
We've still got this!
First line of defense:
Damage at forty percent!
The checkpoint itself remains
largely undamaged, sir...
but the majority
of Mechanoids are inoperable.
Let's have Lan continue
to hold down the fort...
But more importantly,
is the SWAN present?
Not as of yet, sir.
How peculiar...
The SWAN should be
participating in the attack
on the checkpoint...
This is BABEL's team
from the Top Observatory!.
We've finally
located the SWAN!
Believe it or not, she's
traveling through the highlands.
What? You're kidding me!
How can the SWAN manage that?
Hooray for Aunt Flora not
being a complete idiot!
She had holes dug
throughout the highlands
for Aho barrier reactors,
and then used the reactors
to supply the tracks with Ena.
Whatever gaps are
in the tracks are, like,
at the most a few hundred
meters apart, which is awesome!
The reactor can totally
make up for the difference
since it's set to use
Kenshi's compressed bullets.
I must admit, it was
a good strategy...
But do not praise her too much.
It'll go straight to her head.
We are not praising
her at all.
We are merely stating
she is not as dumb
as we originally thought.
We are on target to reach the
designated point momentarily.
And so, Lashara,
I hope we will meet again
if you happen to survive.
We refuse to die
until after we've gone
to your poorly
attended funeral!
Funny, I was about
to say the same thing.
An armored locomotive
is approaching
from the opposite direction.
All cannons target
the warship BABEL!
Cannons,
commence fire!
Commence
counter-fire, now.
Ooh, Maria is going all out!
We like it!.
'Tis our time
to descend as well.
Let's go! Everyone
prepare for impact!
We can turn around here and
try to attack the checkpoint
from behind!
Sounds good. We're
counting on you, Lithia.
Oh, don't worry,
Empress...
We've got everything
under control.
That's right, we do...!
We're ready to fight...!
Anything for King Kenshi!
Cool, yeah, thanks...
'Kay, be careful.
That is so like
Queen Flora...
She has always been one
who enjoys a good stunt.
Curse that woman...!
We've no time for this.
I've almost resurrected
the Sacred Mechalord!
Would you like me
to send Doll out?
If you're willing
to allow it... I'll go.
Very well.
This is it...
Show me what you can do.
Yes, sir!
Good luck, sir.
I don't need luck.
Bastards...
They're making fun of us!
At this rate,
we're totally screwed!
It's not like we owe
Babalun anything.
If we stay, we're all gonna
get killed. Let's go!
No one's going anywhere...!
If we play our cards right,
we can score an entire country
instead of one measly ship!
We'll get money and jewels.
Anything we want!
Do you understand that?
All we have to do
is defend this fort!.
As long as they don't
sneak in from behind,
we've already won!
Lan, we have something
approaching us.
What are those?
These are new weapons
invented by my son-in-law!
Now, go!
What is that?!
Oh Lithia, how dare you
try to leave me behind?
I wouldn't miss out on a battle
like this for the world.
But I'll wait
to deal with you
until after I take care
of these minor obstacles.
This is bad.
They came in from behind.
How did this happen?
Die! Die,
you fiends, die!
Remind the other pilot that no
matter what happens around her,
she must stay still while Dame
Morga is in berserker mode...
Anything that
moves is a threat.
Send in the
reinforcements already!
That's why we have a
rear guard, isn't it?!
First line of defense,
reporting in...!
We need help!
Second line of defense!.
We're requesting
immediate reinforcements!
Second line of defense,
please respond!
are you there?!
Third line
of defense, respond!
Hello? Hello!
I did as you ordered
and had the second and
third lines of defense
pull out of the
battle immediately...
They are scheduled to rendezvous
with our main forces
when they
cross the ravine.
Are you sure about this?.
You will be sacrificing
the first line.
Let them die.
They are nothing more
than money-hungry thugs.
They might have become
a threat later, anyway.
Are you seeing
what I'm seeing?
What is it?
Probably the unit strengthening
defenses in the ravine.
It seems they
intend to rendezvous
with the main forces
in the Holy Land.
I don't think so.
Team One and Team Two!
Enter your frames...!
Team Three on down!
Prepare for mobilization!
Now then, ladies...
You can win, provided you remain
calm and do as you were trained.
Who are they?
Enemy Sacred Mechanoids?
Where did
they come from?
Here we go!.
Are you ready, Lapis?
I'm ready,
Lady Lithia!
We're ready
to fight, too!
Yeah!
Wait, what are students
from the Holy Land doing here?
Well, that's a surprise!
Who would have imagined
we'd run into our very own
Student Council President here?
You think we should...
go help 'em out?
I have no intention of
fighting my classmates.
And besides that...
we should make sure we see
this with our own eyes.
You know, where our ideals
will ultimately take us
and everything.
We will arrive
at the Holy Land soon.
We hope you are prepared.
No matter what,
we cannot allow them
to resurrect
the Sacred Mechalord.
Babalun must not succeed.
Princess Lashara, there's a
Sacred Mechanoid in front of us.
Who is that?!
It's Dagmyer...
What's he doing?
Kenshi Masaki, I challenge
you to a one-on-one duel!
A duel, huh?
We shall fight him...
Kenshi, you should go and deal
with the Sacred Mechalord!
Listen to Princess Aura.
Ignore that jerk!
What is that?.
Wait, hold on...
He's holding a Mechalord's
barrier reactor!
We won't be able
to get near him.
Will he self-destruct
if you don't accept?
Kenshi, we don't
have time for this!
I don't know
if it'll work...
but try compressing
his Sacred Mechanoid!
I've gotta accept
his challenge.
What?
We don't have
that kind of time!.
Kenshi!
Chiaia...! Let Kenshi
do as he chooses.
But why?!
Because he is probably
trying to show his respect
for Dagmyer's resolve
in some weird way.
Again, we don't
have time for that!
He is a Sacred
Mechamaster.
A genuine one.
I am glad you accepted.
Although, I will admit
the ultimatum
was somewhat cowardly
on my part.
"If only you
weren't around."...
I've thought
that many times...
I should've seen you
for what you were...
My own personal challenge.
And now...
I will finally crush you!
Now come at me!
All right.
How dare you?!
I simply can't deny
his skill anymore.
You did well... Dagmyer.
What are those waves?
Oh no!
Behold the Sacred
Mechalord's resurrection!
No...
The Sacred Mechalord.
We're too late.
Don't worry, ladies, we were
prepared for this the second
they tried to buy
more time...!
Kenshi!
Oh, come on.
Kenshi,...
We shall confirm the true
reason you came to this world...
Now that we are in
our time of need.
Wow... he's incredible.
His fighting is on par
with the Sacred Mechalord.
Yes, and we expected
no less from him.
I am honestly surprised he
is able to stand his ground...
In that case...
What is he doing?
Sacred Mechamaster
from another world...
Prepare to experience
Gaia's true form!
I am the perfect
form of Gaia.
No...!
Prime Minister Babalun!
Target the Sacred Mechalord!
Concentrate all fire on Gaia!
Help Kenshi!
You fools.
Princess Maria!
Watch out!
Disconnect command car!
Die!
Oh, thank you, Kenshi!
It's too dangerous...!
Get back!
We shall retreat as well.
The last thing we need
to do right now
is get in Kenshi's way!
Right behind you.
It cannot be helped.
Let's go.
Kenshi...
I'm counting
on you, Kenshi.
This is all Rea's doing...
And it pains my heart to have
to thrust this burden upon you.
I hope it's not too late for us
to provide him assistance...
My time is almost up...
More little baby
chicks to kill!
Not this time!
Oh, you're finished, now!
Lapis!
If it weren't for my operational
limit, they'd be dead!
Number two! Number four!
Number six! Swap out!
Well... that'd be us!
Let's go teach those
jerks a lesson!
Just in time.
I'm at my limit!
Thanks, ladies...
Have fun!
You ready for this?
They've sent out new pilots!
You're not calling
us cowards, are you?.
Because I'm pretty sure
you were the ones
who attacked us en masse!
Huh. They're
barely even a match.
What matters most
is who can last...
Our girls may be
professional,
but even their odds
won't be good
if they're forced to keep
fighting fresh pilots.
So power and quantity beat
experience and expertise...
This is most educational.
Plus, it would seem
their most recent backup
is rather experienced
themselves.
Tides have
changed... huh?
Seems so.
It looks like we've subdued
them for the most part...
I think it's best now to
proceed through the ravine
and eliminate
any remaining units
that may be on our way
to fight at the checkpoint.
Empress Lashara!
We're in.
The checkpoint's gates
have been forced open!
I see...
So we were unable to stop the
Sacred Mechalord's resurrection.
I know we would've
made it in time
if it weren't
for Dagmyer's stupid duel.
Of course!.
As a Sacred Mechamaster,
that was only natural for him!.
He has such
ardent courage!.
I keep liking
my son-in-law all the more!
Unfortunately,
the Sacred Mechalord
has already surpassed
our worst fears!
Babalun somehow merged
with the Shield of Gaia
and became one being
with the Sacred Mechalord.
He became Gaia!
Is that so?
If it is, Babalun
has succeeded.
Before the fusion, Kenshi
and the Sacred Mechalord
seemed like
they were equals.
But now I'm afraid
he's at a disadvantage.
He's fighting out
there right now...
He's all by himself...
And he's doing it for us.
Well, come on...
Let's go help Kenshi, then!
In that case...
I wanna go, too!
You can stay!.
Bad girl! Bad Aunt Flora!
What? But I want
to go help him!
Don't be mean!
Let me go to Kenshi!..
You be careful
out there, okay?
Tell Kenshi we're
thinking about him.
Yeah! Let go!.
No! Stop!
Don't you lose!
That's an order, Chiaia!
Okay!
I'm a little surprised you
didn't want to go with them.
We thought
we'd help make sure
they had somewhere
to come home to.
This is total devastation.
And this is what Kenshi
has been up against.
Oh, Kenshi...
Yeah, I figured its head
would be its toughest section.
Obstinate wretch!
Okay... How's this?!
So strong.
Yes, but the difference in their
frames' power is too great...
It has incredible
defensive capabilities.
Fool! The outcome
will always be the same!
Fool! Oh, Kenshi...
If he keeps it up, Kenshi
will hit his limit sooner
rather than later...
And if that happens...
Is there anything that we
can do to help? Anything at all?
How can he survive?
Do you not understand
this is futile?
Wahan...! Look...!
Down there!
Oh, heck yeah!
Well...?
Is it usable?
Totally!
But we'll have
to make sure it's charged
before we'll be able
to activate anything.
A Mechalord's barrier
reactor emits killer waves!
Kenshi!
Do you copy?!
Huh...? Wahan?
Is that you?
We're going
to overcharge that
Sacred Mechalord's
Aho barrier reactor...!
Hit Gaia with it!
No! That's
too dangerous!
You're the one in danger...
We're trying
to help you this time!
We are at forty...
Climbing to forty-five...
We are at fifty!
No, please don't...!
I can take care of him!
Fifty-five...
Sixty...
We are at sixty-five...
We...
We are at seventy...
I said no!
We can't stop, now...
Not after we've come so far!
Seventy-five...
Eighty.
Eighty-five...
We're...
up to ninety.
Ninety-one...
Ninety-two...
Enough already!
Everybody, get out of here!
Ninety-five...
I said get out of here...!
That's an order from your king!
Shut up and quit
being stupid!
Listen to me. If you keep
whining like a little baby,
I'm going to take away every
last crystal you've been hiding!
Okay, fine...!
I'll do what you guys want.
Finally!
Curse you!
Look out!
Aura, no!
Die!
Chiaia!
Don't worry about me!
Now's your chance, Kenshi!
Ninety-eight...
Ninety-nine!
Critical!
Now, Kenshi! Go!
Chiaia, get down!
Did it work?
No, not yet.
Okay, how did
that not work?!
Die!
Chiaia...
Get everybody
out of here!
But Kenshi, wait!
It's amazing.
He still hasn't given up.
Kenshi...
Is that Doll...?
And Mexiah, too?
It can't be...
Kenshi...
Please, save me!
What?! How dare you
disobey my orders?!
I will not tolerate defiance!
You will pay!
Nothing can damage
the Shield of Gaia!
What is that?
The massive amount of Ena
that got trapped inside
when he compressed the sword
is emitting feedback!
You cannot pierce through me!
I shall not die by your hands!
You are a fool!
Hey! What's
keeping you?!
Will someone please cut off
that thing's creepy head?!
Come on!.
You've almost got him!
Go!
Hurry!
Quit screwing around!
Hurry up and kill him
so we can save my sister...!
If you do it right now,
I'll let you dig up
all the SWAN's crystals!
Consider it done...!
You're going down, Gaia!
What?!
No...
what did you do?!
He... He did it.
Amazing...
Mexiah... Mexiah!.
Please wake up!
Come on...
Wake up, Big Sis Mexiah!
Hi, Kenshi.
Does this mean
that you saved me?
So... I have to know...
Which body of mine
did you prefer:
This one or
my busty adult form?
I don't really know...
Well, I mean...
usually at the end
of stories like this one,
the hero and the
princess he valiantly...
...rescued are supposed
to kiss, isn't that right?
I don't see a princess!
Chiaia...! Have
your kicks grown soft
in the short time
we've been apart?
Will you shut up!
He's alive!
Mister Ulyte?
Ulyte. There's not much time!
Hurry and give me your body!
So that must be
Gaia's true form?
What's going on?
This ends now,
my brother.
Mister Ulyte!
You're... burning up...
Are you sick?
No... My body...
is leaving me...
but not before
I fulfilled my goals...
And now...
I can go in peace.
No, you can't go!
Calm down...
It isn't as though
I'm going to die, Kenshi.
What. It's Rea?
I mean,
it's Neizai?!
Neizai?!
I see...
So it was you...
The one they planted in
you back then was Neizai.
No... How dare
they plot against me!
My father planted
a Core Crystal
inside of my older brother
and me when I was just a boy.
It gradually
eroded my flesh,
but fortunately I was
still a child...
My actual tissues
adapted to the crystal.
My body changed
to match Ulyte or Neizai,
depending on whose
awareness was stronger.
Ulyte had practically
reached his physical limit...
but he was able
to hang on until today...
all because of the drink
you gave him, Kenshi...
You have our gratitude.
Like from
when he was sick?
Gaia's core ate away
at my father...
and then...
it took my older brother...
I was just a child...
so there was no way
for me to stop him...
let alone... find a way
to defeat him by myself...
All I could really do...
Well... was hide the fact that
I was Neizai and bide my time,
and, that's about it.
Now, you mustn't continue
to keep everyone waiting.
Sacred Mechamaster
from another world...
Quickly! This way!
Um... Hi, guys!
Well, it looks like someone
just stole the 'princess
in need of protection'
position.
So let me get
this straight:
Mister Ulyte
is really you, Neizai?
Simply put, we are the same,
yet we're not the same.
That's not simple at all.
You know, your mother
is the one responsible
for this little
predicament.
I don't like this!
We already settled the
problem regarding ownership
over Kenshi, lady!
Well, I wasn't part
of that decision.
I can't believe her...
She pulls the same kinds
of stunts as Miss Mexiah.
It's deplorable at best.
She will not...
That hussy will
never be my sister!
You know, since we've taken care
of this whole Babalun problem,
we might as well
revisit the whole
"who owns Kenshi"
thing now, right? !
Wahanly! Please do not tell us
that you want him as well?
No!
Kenshi has already sworn to
marry into the Shurifon family.
I'm sorry, but it's
only natural for Kenshi
to take Yukine's hand
in marriage!
Aura and Maria...
We can't believe
you're doing this, too!
I know! Since this
is becoming a big mess,
why doesn't Sir Kenshi
hook up with me instead?
Certainly not!
What is going
on in that tiny...
Um... Pardon
my interruption...
Yeah...?
What do you want?
I wish to confirm the
Student Council's reward
for our consistent assistance
throughout this incident.
We don't know why
you're asking us.
We thought Shtrayu was supposed
to become a subordinate state
to cover
all those costs.
Yes, we are not
necessarily interested
in anything like that.
Well, what
do you want, then?
Are you kidding us?
I am now speaking
on everyone's behalf...
We would like to reserve the
right to marry Kenshi Masaki.
For the record, all the
female students present
have given their consent.
The order of marriage is first
come, first served, right...?!
Last one there
is a rotten egg!
Morga!
That's cheating!
I won't lose!
Where do you think
you are all going?
He still belongs to us!
Which of the forests do
you want to get married in?
Don't you wanna help me do
tests on my new Mechaworker!
Yukine, hurry up
and steal Kenshi away!
Oh yeah.
Baby boy...
Come to sister!
Oh my!
Kenshi is just so cute!
Ugh, I don't know how much
more of this crap I can take.
Back off, Kenshi
belongs to us!
They're all so scary.
Mob mentality
at its worst.
Sorry, ladies!
What?. He left!
What are you waiting for?
After him!
And there they go again...
Ah, well, I suppose this
must be our big, fancy finale.
No matter
where I go in this world,
I'll be screwed if I don't have
some sort of peace offering.