Oh... It must be
time for the next shift.
Thank you for coming.
We've been expecting you.
We're in... Target one
is under our control.
Good.
That wasn't as tough
as I thought it'd be.
And they call themselves
defenders of the Holy Land.
They're not defenders...
They usually have
pretty good intel,
but I guess this time
we caught them off guard.
Mainly they just keep
an eye on other nations
and slap their wrists
when they're outta line.
Whatever they are,
apparently they're weak
when attacked
from the inside.
Yeah, normally, getting in
would be the hardest part.
Huh...
Sir, we've taken out targets
two and three, as well.
Why don't we just keep on
pressing them with an attack
and overrun all
the guard posts?
Because we only have so
many Sacred Mechamasters
in our possession...
There's no point in stretching
ourselves too thin, is there?
Besides, the last thing we want
is for Shurifon to catch on...
They're independent
and we do not want
them getting involved...
On another note,
where did Emera go?
Beats me. If you're
asking my opinion,
I think that girl's a
complete waste of space
and we're better
off without her.
Who's there?
I hope I didn't
inconvenience you.
But she was needed.
No! Don't...!
If you ever borrow
one of my subordinates
without my
permission again...
I will have
to punish you.
My sincerest
apologies, sir...
But it couldn't
be helped.
Sir... we've suppressed
targets four, five and six.
Well, since you're already
here, you should stay
and watch the show.
I'm grateful I could
see this day come...
We've been preparing for
this moment for a long time.
Ideals only matter
when put into action.
When they're only talk,
they mean nothing...
But in practice,
they shine.
The actions that we
take here today...
will guide each and every one of
us to never before seen heights.
So get out there
and do your job.
The main forces will
arrive any minute now.
Good morning!
What's wrong,
you guys?
Let's go...!
For this morning
we shall all be victors!
Oh no!
The guard post!
It's here!
I need to get as many
merit points as I can...!
Come on, let's crush
them all, one by one!
Time to show them our
true strength, gentlemen!
Right!
You'll have to do
better than that!
What are you doing...?!
It'll revert back to a cocoon
if you leave the draft.
Oh, right.
What could
that noise be?
Yukine?
But that's impossible.
What is it?
There's lots
of black smoke.
The guard post...
It must be on fire.
But how can that be...?
If we're under attack,
why hasn't the alarm sounded?
Seventy percent of the
posts have been destroyed!
Well done...
Almost there.
Don't you move!
What do you think you're
doing here, Dagmyer?!
What exactly
is this about?
Well... It would appear
that the Holy Land
has fallen under
my control.
No, you can't...!
That's Shtrayu's
flagship fortress!
I'm demanding a complete,
unconditional surrender...
The battle
is already over.
Stupid old bag!
Let her go.
The Shurifon Mechanoids
have arrived!
Huh... It looks like
they've kept two hidden...
I'm going in...
You can handle
things here!
I'm telling you...!
Those bandits have overrun
the central control room...
Dagmyer's the one
calling the shots!
All right.
You got it.
I'm on my way now.
Poor hotheaded baby
thinks he's in control.
Well, we'll
see about that.
That lady said a storm
was coming our way...
Maybe this
is what she meant.
This is more of a
typhoon than a storm...
Curse you,
Lord Babalun...
We do not understand,
how in the world
did they manage to get
through that narrow ravine?
Empress Lashara, the
Principal would like a word.
Could you please explain to us
just what is going on out there?
We suppose this means
you have heard
about our current
predicament in Shtrayu...
Please, you have
to believe us!
We had nothing
to do with this!
No, of course you didn't...
However, given the current
situation, I believe
we have no other choice
but to evacuate the campus...
But we won't be able
to do it without you!
Whatever you need!
Principal!
Go...! Get the SWAN ready
for takeoff immediately...!
Kenshi!
You have to fight them
off and keep us safe...
You're the only
one who can do it!
Do you think I could
maybe get a little help?
The Holy Land Instructors
have started evacuating
the students...
But every second
that passes,
those bad guys get
closer and closer...
And if we don't do something
to stop them soon,
we will be in
an awful situation!
"We" or "you?"...
My family motto is, "one must
clean up their own messes,"
and I think those
are wise words!
Perhaps you should
consider this then...
If you don't
help us out,
everyone who's
looked after you here
is going to
be in grave danger!
Right...!
On my way!
You are going to hear
more from us later on...!
Chiaia, go and join
Kenshi, please.
No, I can't.
We understand this must
be very hard for you...
Dagmyer's involvement
in all of this.
He wouldn't do that.
Empress Lashara,
please hurry!
Chiaia...
If your heart is telling you
to join him, go ahead and go.
First up...
Evacuations!
Target seven's silent.
It looks like-
I don't know why, but
we've lost control!
Who cares, we've
done our part...
Have you looked outside?
It's complete chaos out there!
We should go earn some
pocket money then.
Hey...! Wahanly...!
You okay?
Yeah,
you bet I am...!
But I'll be doing
a whole lot better
once I get this
thing in the air!
Are you close?
I'm almost done!
Just gotta finish
attaching the weapons!
No, I like it like this...
If you weigh it down with
stuff it won't maneuver well.
According to Lan's info,
this is a Sacred
Mechamechanic's workshop...
If we find anything
valuable, we take it.
Great work...! It's like a
totally different mechanoid!
Thank you... Hey,
aren't those two guys
part of the gang of bandits
that attacked us at the resort?
Think so...
You handle them!
Kenshi, hold on...!
Wait! Don't go yet!
The way is blocked.
Well, well, this sure
is a sight to see...
The Elf Princess
is scared.
Sad.
Please don't hurt me.
Oh, don't you worry.
There's nothin'
to be afraid of...
I promise
we'll be gentle!
Don't touch me!
What's that?
You again!
No!
Ah...! No...!
That punk!
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?!
Stop...!
I'm gonna fall!
Oh, you are so dead!
Almost there!
I'm very sorry,
Kenshi...
Unfortunately, it seems you
always catch me at my worst.
I'm just glad you
didn't get hurt.
They're my least favorite
parts of the day.
You should've held onto
him a little bit longer.
Perhaps this was
your big chance.
Go confirm if there
are still students
who haven't made
it to safety yet!
Right... Good idea,
I didn't even think of that.
Will do...! Sir Kenshi!
Please look after our
Princess, won't you?
Princess...
You should
make your move!
I'm going to have to dock
their pay for this!
Oh no.
Something tells me
I'm gonna like this
combat thing after all!
Those cowards!
No!
That's what she gets
for messing with us!
How dare you?!
Come and get me!
These dark fields
can be a hassle.
Finish her off!
Is this equipped
with weapons or no?
No.
You're finished!
I failed you,
Princess... I'm sorry.
What is going on now?!
They turned on the
defense system!
Now let's try to
secure the way
for the students
fleeing to safety.
Yeah, good idea!
We're taking hits
from the outside...
but the damage is minimal!
The enemy stronghold
is increasing!
Well, well...
Considering it's Dagmyer,
it could've been much worse.
Launch all Sacred
Mechanoids at once!
Nothing will stand
in BABEL's way!
Prime Minister...!
We have received a transmission
from Queen Flora of Havoniwa.
Lord Babalun.
What is going on?
What is the meaning of this
attack on the Holy Land?
A silly question...
You know as well as I do
what's happening, Queen Flora,
so don't play
the fool with me.
Just be warned...
we won't stop till
we've achieved our goal.
Well, I have to admit...
I figured as much.
After all, when someone
wages war in the Holy Land,
it must be for some
greater purpose, right?
Lord Babalun...!
A massive object is coming
straight towards us!
What's that?
All canons are ready...
waiting on your command!
Commence attack please.
I will make
her pay for this.
Principal...
I haven't spoken
to you in ages.
Yet another
grand entrance.
You know me...
I'm happy to take as many
of the students and faculty
as I can hold...
Open the tracks
when you're ready.
Thanks so much...
It means a lot.
Hurry up... Everyone keep
moving and make for the train!
Whatever you do,
just keep going!
Watch out for the
Sacred Mechanoids!
Don't worry,
you're almost there!
Well,
this is fun!
Wait!
Miss, what are you doing?!
It's too dangerous...!
Please, don't do this!
I have to...! I can shield
them while they run for cover!
There are too many,
you could be killed!
Hey, it looks like the Student
Council President's gonna get
in a mechanoid!
How about that?
Lady Lithia wants in
on the action, too!
Careful
what you wish for!
Are you
all right, Miss?
You big coward! You should be
ashamed of yourself!
I'm gonna make you regret
ever calling me that!
Lapis! You can't!
Yes, I can...!
I'm protecting you.
Stand back!
Ha!
Serves you right!
Look...
What's that?
It's that kid!
That guy...?
Wait, isn't he
Lashara's attendant?
You're not hurt,
are you?
I'm okay, I'm just
a little shaken up...
Lapis, why are you crying?
What's wrong?
Oh... I'm fine, I'm just glad
you're okay, Lady Lithia.
Can you stand up...?
Quick... We have to move,
it's not safe here!
Okay.
It's horrible.
Don't cry, you'll be fine...
I'm gonna take care of this.
Princess Aura... I'm leaving
this Mechaworker to you!
Where exactly do you
think you're going?!
Kenshi, wait!
The kid's making
a run for it!
Calm down...
Everyone, please.
The coliseum's built to
withstand attacks like this.
You're safe.
It's impossible
for the Mechanoids
to pass through
Ena's draft.
Let's get a headcount and
figure out who we're missing.
Once that's done,
classes one through four
go to the
Church's battleship
using Underground
Passage sixteen.
Classes five through eight,
use passage twenty-nine to
reach Princess Lashara's SWAN.
The rest of you go to Queen
Flora's armored train
through passage seven...
and make sure to stick to
your evacuation routes.
Yes, ma'am!
Line up according to
your seating number...
Come on you guys, I'm counting
on you so let's move out!
Oh Dagmyer...
Tell me this
is all a big lie.
I knew this would
happen eventually.
Sis... Where
have you been?
You're Empress Lashara's
personal bodyguard...
He belongs to the Mesuts.
Yes, I know that...
and I always have.
Miss Mexiah!
Everybody's here
and we're ready to go!
One by one, all the
classes are escaping
through the three
different passageways!
Great, thank you for
keeping me informed...
You should go and join the
rest of your classmates.
Yes ma'am!
Hey...
Is that Kenshi?
Kenshi, no!
What in the world
is that idiot doing?!
If you ask me,
all the attention
he's been getting
went to his head.
He's just an attendant...
He's not a real Sacred
Mechamaster like we are!
Stop him!
Move it!
Die!
All right...! That's
what I'm talking about!
It appears that everyone from
this block managed to escape.
Yes. I can't
believe Mother...
A shoot out between a battleship
and an armored train
in the Holy Land
has never happened before.
Yukine, what's the matter?
Dagmyer!
Wait a second...
That's Kenshi!
What could he be doing?
Be careful!
It's too late!
That little brat!
It's Kenshi!
That jerk.
Oh... Wow.
A total of one thousand,
one hundred forty-nine students
and faculty have taken
refuge in the SWAN.
So far, everyone
is holding up well.
The majority of the injuries
sustained were minor.
Unbelievable...
We've never seen anything
like this before in our lives,
that's for sure.
Queen Flora has some
fight in her yet.
What's going on?!
Would you care
to explain?!
Wait!
Explain what?!
Him...! Him!
Oh my! That's Kenshi...!
But it can't be!
I think I'm gonna be sick!
Can it be...?
Is he really a light-type?
What's a light-type?
The sacred texts of
the Church tell us,
"He who is garbed in light shall
be the savior of the world...
While he who dons the robes
of darkness shall be bent
on its destruction."
Darkness...
And light?
Both of these forces
are interconnected.
Light can take the
shape of darkness,
and darkness can take
the shape of light.
A real white
Sacred Mechanoid.
Wow.
I'm not surprised,
I always knew Kenshi
was made to pilot
that Sacred Mechanoid!
Amazing.
Kenshi's
a Sacred Mechamaster?
Oh no... Quick,
defend yourselves!
Don't kill me...!
Please don't kill me!
Coward!
Will you get back here?
No...!
You can't stop me...!
Be gone!
Sir Dagmyer!
Oh no!
Wahan...! Help him!
Sorry, but my hands are
a little full right now!
That idiot, he fell
for it...! Finish him!
Kenshi, no...!
It was a trap!
It doesn't matter
how strong he is!
He's got
a big disadvantage!
He's completely outnumbered!
They've got him cornered in
there like a poor little Koro.
What'll he do?
Hey.
Where'd Mexiah go?
With all these pillars
so close together,
he'll have
zero maneuverability.
Found him.
No way!
No!
Squeeze him
from both sides!
He's gone?!
Cordyline!
Be careful!
That's good,
come this way...
Just a little closer.
I'm gonna
treat you real nice!
No!
Curse him...
The brat!
Oh wow.
Unbelievable.
Who's piloting that thing?
I've never heard of a pure
white Sacred Mechanoid.
Oh...? I guess you
don't know then?
It's Kenshi Masaki,
he's the one responsible
for fighting the bad
guys and saving the day!
What...?
Like, for real?!
You mean Empress
Lashara's attendant...?
It's that Kenshi?
I saw him enter the cocoon
with my own two eyes!
Isn't that nuts?
Kenshi's piloting
the White Mechanoid!
Is it really Kenshi?
Oh yeah, it is definitely him!
That's Kenshi down there!
Kenshi...
He's our hero!
That is so amazing!
They are enclosed
by the Draft
as they fight
around those pillars...
It is terrifically
difficult.
Oh... Well, it doesn't really
look all that hard to me.
What an idiot.
Mexiah?
Many great Sacred Mechamasters
who were hailed as 'experts'
have fought right here
on this hallowed ground,
but not a single
one of them
was able to use
moves like he just did.
The boy exceeds all
our expectations.
Dagmyer...
We should retreat
while we still can!
Coward...
There's no way I'll show
my back to that wretch!
We're not done!
Where are you?!
Cliff, no!
Come on!
The little jerk knew
exactly what he was doing.
He lured us right into
his hunting grounds!
Mother!
Yukine,
I owe you big time...
Thank you for bringing my
baby back to me in one piece.
Yes, ma'am.
This day certainly has
been full of surprises.
Can you believe he's
a Sacred Mechamaster?
Amazing!
It's hard to imagine someone
wielding that amount of power...
One of these days,
I'll make that niece of mine
give me the inside scoop.
Thanks to Kenshi,
the majority of the enemy Sacred
Mechanoids are inoperable...
If we keep
pushing forward
we should be able
to make them retreat.
I wouldn't be so certain.
Babalun's still got
something up his sleeve.
Don't count him out yet.
We're here.
BABEL has reached its target
location, adjusting for errors.
I have just confirmed the
barrier, Prime Minister...!
Commencing scans.
Constructing the
anti-barrier circle!
What in the world
is he up to?
Don't tell me Babalun
is after that!
Why?
This can't be!
Dagmyer!
Time to get outta here!
We can't...
She's still out there!
Cordyline will be all right,
she knows what she's doing!
There isn't anything I can do
against a monster like this!
Mexiah...!
What is wrong with you?!
Say something...!
Can't you hear my voice?!
Please...!
Will you just answer me?!
Mexiah!
It has been quite
a while, Chiaia.
What is going on...?
Tell me, what have you
done to my sister?
You'll find out
soon enough.
Stand back.
The Sacred
Mechalord Pedestal!
Something isn't right.
Mexiah.
Barrier
analysis complete.
Synching now.
What's going on?
It can't be!
That's right...
Come to life!
Let her go!
Hear me, Chiaia...
It's time you learned
Mexiah is not your sister.
Your father excavated her
body from the same ruins
where he discovered
the Sacred Mechalord...
Your 'big sister' was made
by the ancient civilization.
That's impossible.
See for yourself then.
Miss Mexiah!
Is that... Doll?
It can't be real...
There's no way.
Put me on a direct
line with the Pope!
No, this can't
be happening.
I don't know how things
could possibly get worse!
The ways of old
are resurrected!
Sister!
I'd hurry and get those
kids out of here...
Unless of course,
you want them to die.
No, wait...!
You don't have to do this!
Mexiah, don't go...!
Please stop!!
I hate pillars.
Don't touch them!
He's strong...
Especially for a mere
Sacred Mechanoid.
Its not safe here...
Get inside!
I'll follow
right behind you,
as soon as I do one
last head count!
We're not leaving
without you!
Thank you, but I can't abandon
that idiot and my sister!
Whatever you do,
just get out safely.
It would appear
this is the end.
What are you doing?
Take your shot!
I don't get it, why
can't I attack him...?
Is it Mexiah's personality?
Or something else?
But no... I have orders
and I have to follow them!
The deterioration
of the frame is worse
than I originally
anticipated.
Chiaia!
All the students are safe.
There are no more stragglers!
I think it's about time
we sought refuge ourselves!
Not yet, Kenshi
is still out there!
I'm sorry...
but there's nothing
we can do.
What if we create some
kind of diversion?
If we're unable to retreat
at the right moment
we could be killed...
And besides...
It's very likely we would end
up getting in Kenshi's way.
We need
to get moving...
I know Kenshi can
take care of himself.
Kenshi...
please...
save her.
Please, snap out of it,
Big Sis Mexiah!
No use wasting your breath.
Mexiah and I have
merged into one being.
Her experiences
are mine now...
I remember all the times
we've spent together.
I remember all
sorts of things.
Not sure
if it's possible,
but if you could forget some
of that stuff, that'd be great.
I really did enjoy
my time here...
And I'm sorry,
but I can't stay.
But if you wanted...
you could come with me.
I really wish I could,
but my place was
never on that side...
But what if you came with us
instead of going with them...?
I could make a nice home
for you here if you'd let me.
I can't do that.
I'm 'Doll,' remember...?
Fighting is my only
reason for existing.
It's how I was created,
and how I'll always be.
Are you okay with that?
This is my destiny, Kenshi...
I've no choice.
Principal,
I've confirmed
that all students
have made it out safely!
That's excellent news...
Prepare to launch immediately!
Yes, ma'am!
Thank goodness,
you're safe!
Damage report.
Thanks to Kenshi, we were able
to rescue all of our team!
Good...
Then let's prepare
to launch at once!
Queen Flora... We've
been able to accommodate
all of the refugees
who fled this way.
There were some
minor injuries,
but all two hundred
and twenty-one students
made it safe and sound.
Excellent.
Stand by...
Arm the cannon!
Mother! No...!
Kenshi's still out there,
you could hurt him!
Oh, don't worry, something
tells me he'll be fine.
Right... Yukine?
The main cannon
is ready to fire.
Waiting on your
command, Queen Flora!
All right then... let's
retreat to a safe distance.
After firing
the main cannon
have the front
cars self-destruct.
With any luck we can cut off
anyone trying to track us!
Put me through now... Kenshi!
It can't end like this.
Kenshi!
Wait, Princess Maria?
My mother is about to do
something incredibly stupid...
so look out!
Aw man,
this sucks!
There he is!
Hey, are you okay?!
Mexiah.
For now, that is
the best we can do.
We are simply too weak.
They'll be overtaken
soon, though.
Fine, but we should go back
to the barrier workshop!
It's a
one-in-a-million chance
the Sacred Mechalord
is ever activated.
And in that event...
Naua said we should
definitely go and see him.
My dad said that?
Well, all right then...
Wait a second, Wahan,
this means you're finally going
to tell us everything you know,
doesn't it?
It does.
But hold on... Look.
Kenshi...!
Take them out!
Right!
The frame
is breaking down...!
I guess Kenshi's power
was too much for it!
It can fight though,
can't it?
No, it won't even morph!
This is not good.
It's time the bad guys
went... bye-bye.
We are going
to kill you, Aunt Flora!
The nerve of that
stupid old bag!
She doesn't ever think!
What if we had been caught
in the middle of all that?!
Relax, at least we get
a happy ending, right...?
This day could have
been so much worse.
Oh no!
Kenshi...?
What's wrong?
I left behind
all my crystals!
Aw man!
Aw... I worked
so hard for those.
Kenshi!
Look at me.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I seem to remember
you telling me
you weren't going to
dig up crystals anymore.
So tell me about this...
in greater detail,
you little twerp!
Mew, mew, mew, mew.
Come back here!
I'll make you
pay for this!
Yep.
Moron!
Glad to see some
things never change.
Yeah!
Hey, Dagmyer...
There's no reason
to be down in the dumps...
Your plan was
a complete success.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Promise you won't
do anything crazy...
'Cause who knows...?
Next time I might not
be there to help you out.
Well, how did
everything turn out?
She snuck right in,
no one saw her.
Everything's on schedule,
just as planned.
Excellent.
Stupid us!
Here we were thinking the
only thing we had to worry
about was Babalun...!
Okay... First let's head
to Aura's country...!
Next on
Tenchi Muyo! War on Geminar:
"Expectations"...
This time we'll return her to
her old self, no matter what!