Yes, very good...
A little farther!
At this rate, we'll finish
by the end of the day.
I can't believe how much
we have accomplished.
"We've accomplished?"
Pardon me, but I think only
those who actually worked
should talk like that.
They insisted we leave
because we were in the way...
'Tis not our fault.
Yes, knowing when
to gracefully retire
is the most
important job of all.
With all due respect, laziness
is not something to brag about.
You are in no
position to criticize.
You were so invaluable they
gave you the earth-shaking task
of setting the table!
Apparently,
the 'ever-so-competent'
Student Council President is not
all she's cracked up to be.
I'd say it's hardly my fault
I have a gift for table décor.
All done!
A hot bath after
a hard day's work...
It doesn't get much
better than this.
Oh, come now...
You don't really believe
you did work today, do you?
We suppose we could
ask you the same thing.
There's nothing more relaxing
than a big bathtub, though.
All things considered,
I'm still amazed
at how quickly
we got done.
Well, personally...
this incident has taught me
to have a newfound respect
for how hard all the staff must
work to maintain the dorms...
It was an excellent
experience.
I'm happy I was finally able
to shed most of the useless data
off my Mechaworker.
Lithia! What is
the matter...?
You seem like you
are rather upset.
Dame Chiaia
and Dame Yukine.
It's rude
to isolate yourself.
Join us at once!
I find your lack of
modesty exasperating.
The wild beast that caused
such a catastrophe the other day
is right there!
How can you sit out in the open
with your whole body exposed?!
Please, he's harmless.
You need to relax.
Besides, he's been working
here for several days now
and is earning
a good reputation.
That's right...
Kenshi's a hard worker,
and his technique
is totally flawless!
I shouldn't have to
remind you that we're here
to have a meeting about the
completion of the repairs...
We do not need
someone to bathe us...
So do us
all a favor,
and tell that wild
animal to leave at once!
I agree...
Dressed the way we are,
even allowing him to
innocently wash our backs
could be a
risky proposition.
I guess you're
right about that...
Kenshi...
Sorry, but we don't need
help bathing anymore.
That's okay by me...
If it's cool,
I'll be going now.
Wait.
Considering this meeting
involves you directly,
it's probably a good idea
if you stick around...
Come on now, why don't
you take off those
constricting clothes
and strip down.
Uh... I can't,
this is the girl's bath.
Oh please, stop worrying
and get comfortable.
We give you our
permission, Kenshi.
The rest of us
don't mind either.
After working with him on
several projects, I admit...
I admire his skill.
I cannot believe the words
I'm hearing right now!
Now that I think of it,
we owe Kenshi big time
for those massages.?
Excellent point.
In that case, I would
like to officially retract
my previous objections.
Great...! So shall
we give it a go?!
Okay!
Since that's out of the way we
can get the meeting started...
Well.
We received word
from the Principal.
Starting first thing tomorrow,
school will resume.
And that's all.
Are you kidding me?
I put up with all this
just to hear that crap?!
Next time, just tell me,
instead of stripping my clothes
off like a buncha lunatics!
Yes. To make it up,
you could take my clothes off.
Too bad for you I'm only
wearing this one layer.
I can't win, can I?
Oh, this is
so relaxing.
I'm glad
I thought of it.
Oh, shut up.
You've got scrapes and
bruises all over your hands.
What gives...?
How in the world did
that happen to you?
Oh... Well,
I got banged up when I was
cleaning all the rubble...
Don't worry
though, I'm okay.
Oh my...
You're hurt.
I'll be all right.
What exactly were you
looking at pervert?
So the SWAN is
covered with holes?
What about all the Koros
who live around here,
maybe they're the
ones responsible?
No, the holes are
far too big for that.
Are they occurring
with more frequency?
All we can say for sure is
that there were no indications
of any traps...
As far as we know, the
appearance of these holes
is nothing but
random coincidence,
though it's hard to imagine
why this would happen.
Oh, who knows?
Perhaps someone is
searching for something.
It might be best to consult
with the Holy Land's security.
Hey, wait just a second!
What's wrong,
you have an objection
to bringing this
matter to the authorities?
We don't need security
to trap one measly Koro.
And that would mean...?
You're quite the
cautious one, aren't you?
We need to be extra careful
so he doesn't spot us.
Otherwise we won't be able
to catch him in the act.
That little-
The rat even used camouflage.
That moron!
I guess it was a
Koro, after all!
Awesome.
Someone's a big fan of
stones, aren't they?
It's not a stone;
it's a crystal.
That isn't the point,
you imbecile...
Tell us right now, why you're
filling a SWAN with holes...?
If we hadn't intervened,
you could've compromised
its external strength!
No way...
I made sure that every
hole I made was blocked,
to keep the SWAN safe.
Just keep your mouth
shut, Captain Koro!
It's so pretty...
This is the first time
we've seen a raw gemstone...
Just be honest, there
must be some reason
you're so obsessed with them.
Why don't you tell us
what this is about.
Well, back when I
was a little kid...
My big sister had a
spaceship made out of crystal
and she used to take off in it
from my brother's house...
And I'd watch it lift
up out of the pond.
It was really cool.
I'll never forget
how the crystal sparkled
when the sun set.
You're right;
'tis a beautiful thing
at which to look.
Wait a second!
Did you just say your big
sister's spaceship...?
Let us get this straight:
You're saying you
actually have a sibling
who owns a craft
that can fly in space?
Yeah, that's right.
Empress Lashara,
what is it?
Kenshi... Tell us:
is it really normal
for other beings
where you come from to have
their own personal spaceships?
No, don't be ridiculous,
of course it's not normal...
Besides, our ships are
just over-sized rockets;
they're really not
that big of a deal.
Why in the world does my
family have a spaceship?
What... exactly
are you getting at?
According to
reports from those
who have
explored the galaxy...
Even the most sophisticated
civilizations,
with the most
advanced sciences
can barely send their
own to nearby moons,
much less travel
freely through space.
Ships like that...
simply do not exist.
Hold on, I still don't get it.
Are you saying Kenshi
must've come from the future?
Sometimes children's
memories can mix up dreams
with reality...
Are you absolutely positive
this story you told us happened?
Yeah, I'm sure of it...
I even remember riding
inside of it a couple times.
And that never struck
you as curious or odd
until just a moment ago...?
What about everyone else;
how did they react to it?
Well, obviously I didn't
tell anybody about it...
My sis... She made me promise
her I'd always keep it a secret.
That mad scientist...!
Damn, her!
Is that how she kept it
a secret from everyone,
by hypnotizing you?
That could also explain why
you succumbed so easily
to Mexiah's hypnosis.
At any rate,
it seems you come
from a very complex
family life, as well.
That's all
beside the point!
And let's not forget
about the crystal!
You even had the nerve
to make yourself a pendant!
I did not...! My sister
gave that to me as a gift.
It's part of her ship!
Oh no.
Uh...
My fault...
I did not mean
for that to happen.
Hey... Come on,
it's not worth crying over.
Don't worry about it.
I promise I'll fix it.
Are you sure...?
You're pretty much the clumsiest
person that I've ever met.
Relax, I'll find someone
who's able to take
care of the repairs.
Oh, would you
quit crying already,
If the story he just
told us is true...
Then perhaps he wasn't
summoned here after all?
Could he actually
be from the future?
Unfortunately,
I am afraid there's nothing
I can do for you at this point.
In order to fix this, you
will need to send it home
and enlist the aid of one
of Empress Lashara's jewelers.
Well, that's too bad.
If the matter
is pressing...
You could talk to a jeweler
in the Holy Land...
I suppose it's possible they
would be able to assist you.
So how does it look?
I'm sorry, but this
is beyond me...
There was a guy who specialized
in this kind of stuff,
but he retired
last year.
Well, that's too bad.
Sorry I couldn't
help you, miss.
What should I do?
It's hard to say...
You're only shred of hope
would be to ask a jeweler
who serves a
Sacred Mechamaster.
Where am I supposed
to find a jeweler
who serves a
Sacred Mechamaster...?
I might as well
just give up now.
Chiaia...!
Hello, there!
Is everything all right?
You seem frustrated today.
Of course!
Well...
How does it look?
I've never seen workmanship this
intricate in my whole life...
At this point, I'm not even
certain what it's made out of.
Unfortunately, fixing it
is going to take some time.
I can't exactly say I'm
surprised, I've often heard
the highlands use different
techniques than we do...
But whatever the case,
I'll give it my best shot.
This is indeed one
incredibly unique crystal.
Dame Chiaia...
The only sensible
solution is for someone
from Kenshi's
homeland to fix it.
Yeah... That might be
my only option.
If you need
something in a hurry,
maybe replacing
it's a better option.
Why don't you fashion
him a braided cord?
Like from Havoniwa?
Yes, why not?
The cords from our country
hold different meaning
depending on their style,
color, and design...
The most common
way they're used,
though, is a charm to
tell someone how you feel.
I can't think of a better
way to convey your remorse
over breaking his chain.
Yeah but I
wouldn't even know
how to begin making
something like that...
and besides...
I'm too clumsy.
No reason to fret over not
knowing how, we'll teach you...
Isn't that right, Yukine?
Yes.
I can't.
All right, fine...!
I'll do everything I can!
Uh...
Mr. lyte?
Is something wrong?
Regarding the 'packages'
you inquired about?
They have
all arrived, sir.
I'm much more concerned
with the status
of the other arrangements.
Right... I will
handle it, sir.
Kenshi!
Somebody's in a
good mood today!
Good luck
with all your work!
Thanks!
See you later!
Oh, what an eyesore.
He went to bed
like a good boy.
Oh wow,
that was perfect,
who knew there was
another entrance nearby?
It doesn't get any luckier
than that, does it?!
Who are you?
Whoa, you're a woman.
Hey, wait...!
That lady was just a decoy.
I gotcha.
There are ruffians out
in the street tonight.
I know... I'm chasing someone;
did they just run by here?
Yes... They went that way.
Thank you very much.
Wait, what're you doing?!
He's an animal,
that one.
Well, did you get it?
Yes, here it is, sir.
Good.
Found her!
Man... It's
just the decoy...
But there's no point
goin' back now!
In that case!
Tell me... Are you
from another world?
Why do you ask that?
I'm not... uh...
I'm from the highlands,
why are you-
Come back!
He's chasing me...
I can't believe it!
She vanished...
What gives?
Well, well...
What are you doing
out at this hour?
I could ask you
the same thing.
I received word a burglar was
out and look who I find...
So then are you the culprit?
No way...!
I was chasing
the burglar and then-
Oh, just calm down...
I was taking a bath...
This is the girl's
dorm, you know.
Yeah, well, guys happen
to work here, too.
It was an emergency; there
was no time for clothes!
Come on, the robber might
be hiding somewhere nearby.
Kenshi,
don't be so shy...
Why don't we take a
bath together later?
Dagmyer really
retrieved that?
Yes... He seemed acutely
proud of himself.
Naua's pupil,
hunh...?
Certainly seems like
the work of a highlander,
wouldn't you agree...?
If they were practical, they
could be extremely useful
when we seize castles
outside of the draft.
Unfortunately, though,
they're not practical.
I'm amazed he created such a
stir over something like this.
He is your heir after all,
and if you take
that into consideration,
it makes sense he might
want to use it one day.
Even if he will need it,
there are other ways
to go about these things...
Make sure he fully
understands that.
He's still very
young, my Lord...
But as a male
Sacred Mechamaster,
he's extremely talented.
Ridiculous child...
He wants to succeed my
lordship more than anything.
But he cares nothing for
cultivating his talents.
That's very true...
Especially since Lashara is just
about ready to give up on us...
Ah well, such is the way
of our world, I'm afraid.
That's very disconcerting.
Are you positive
nothing was stolen?
Yep... They definitely rummaged
through my research data,
but everything is accounted for,
so it doesn't look like it...
Luckily, none of it was highly
classified information,
so we are
in good shape.
Wonderful.
Given the circumstances
I think it's definitely best
we handle the investigation
for breaking and entering...
Any issues with that?
That will be fine.
Sorry... I'm totally
running late.
Oh, that's perfectly fine.
I admit, I'm curious as to why
Lashara isn't more concerned
about potential threats.
Well, obviously,
it was a huge mistake
to leave it so vulnerable in
the academy's locked barrier.
To tell ya the truth,
I had no idea
someone would be interested
in something like that.
I'd be very interested
But Princess Maria, nothing of
any consequence was stolen,
so really, there's no
reason to be concerned...
Don't worry.
Tell me then...
Could you make the Mechaworker
fit for practical use?
Thanks to Empress Lashara,
I got some in-combat data...
I- I think I can
drastically increase
its operational efficiency...
But if you wanted
it to fight
wired Sacred Mechanoids
outside the Draft...
You're gonna run into
issues with its power,
as well as duration
of operability.
We are currently seeking
out a Sacred Mechamaster
who has the skill to create
quality-compressed bullets.
One of this year's new
students would be preferable.
That's a good idea,
since they get tails once
they become upperclassmen...
You know, like Chiaia
and Aura both did.
Don't forget...
You did too.
To be honest, I'd prefer
if you'd leave me out of this.
The maneuverability
would suffer,
but I'm thinking about
making a Mechaworker
that co-functions
as a charger.
Oh boy...
Those two Sacred Mechanoids
were like beyond incredible...!
I wish I had
some like that.
You are referring
to the Sacred Mechanoids
that attacked
Empress Lashara?
Right.
Honestly, I have doubts about
what they really were...
I'm not convinced they
were Sacred Mechanoids.
Well, of course they were!
What kind of Sacred Mechamaster
could've done that to you...?
I, for one, have never
seen anything like it.
I bet she's a monster,
twice the size of a normal woman
and twice as strong, too.
She may very well be.
I wonder why someone would want
to break into the vault.
It's impossible
for us to say.
These things just
happen sometimes.
While we're
on the subject...
Wanna tell me what you were
doing by the girl's dorm
last night?
Walking.
By the way, Chiaia what's
going on with my pendant...?
Did you fix it yet?
Hey, I'm doing
the best I can...
Why don't you
just take it easy?!
I told you I would
fix it, you jerk!
Hi, Kenshi!
You seem to be
feeling better
since you started taking
Kenshi's medicine.
To tell you the truth,
I still can't believe it
He truly is a mysterious boy.
Little by little...
A ring of supporters has
started to form around him.
But if we are to stand on
equal terms with him,
that won't be enough.
You are correct...
In that case,
maybe it's time
I put him somewhere
out in the open,
where he'll
stand out even more.
Oh, my God look at that.
Keep up the
good work, Kenshi!
Yeah, you're doing great!
Thanks!
Thank you for
coming, Empress.
I have some questions for you,
regarding Master Masaki.
Wait, this
is about Kenshi?
That's correct...
I heard a rumor that
has me quite concerned.
Supposedly, the boy
has not completed
his compulsory
education.
Although
I am very aware
the highlands have
completely different
educational standards...
Since he resides
in the Holy Land,
I cannot allow
this to slide.
Of course not...
We've given this exact issue
some serious thought ourselves.
I see...
One more thing...
I understand that in order for
him to take care of himself,
you're to pay him for
the work he's doing...
Perhaps then,
you can explain to me
why he has yet to receive any of
the funds paid to him thus far?
He told us...
"Don't worry, I'm fine,
they've been feeding me
and for everything else I can
fend for myself in the forest."
You can imagine my surprise when
he laughed the whole thing off,
without a hint
of resentment.
We can picture it now.
So... All joking aside,
for the record,
do you care
to explain to me
why your attendant is forced
to pay for his own food?
The thing about that is...
We know... He's
saving for tuition.
Because after all,
he can't go to school
while he's
in the Holy Land.
I see...
In that case,
why doesn't
he just enroll here?
What...?!
Wait, but this is -
True... Aside from Sacred
Mechamaster candidates,
only royalty and
nobility may enroll...
But we do make exceptions
if the Church approves.
All of the instructors
who have seen him work
at the dorms have offered
recommendations.
I doubt there would be
any objection
should he try to enroll.
Perhaps, but-
And as for the tuition...
we'll allow him to pay for it
after he graduates.
Although...
Considering the amount
of work he's willing to do,
he could enroll and work
off his tuition in the dorms
within one year.
But, he's not smart enough
to go to this school.
Actually, we just gave him a
test to gauge his abilities...
The results indicate he'll
perform well above average.
When did you do that?
His knowledge of history
leaves something to be desired,
and he lacks basic
reasoning skills...
Of course that is to be expected
being from the highlands...
Well then...
Do you give permission?
Yes, very well.
Yeah but.
Do you think it's
smart to throw him
into the academy
like this?
We don't know,
but all the instructors
gave him glowing
recommendations.
It's the source of the
rumors I'm worried about.
Yes, and we can already guess
what many of the rumors will be.
As long as no one discovers
he's a Sacred Mechamaster,
everything
should be fine.
All you ever do is cause
the rest of us problems,
do you realize that?
Yeah, but I just-
At the academy, there'll
be even more opportunities
to talk to individuals
from other countries...
So you'll have to be
extra careful, got it?
Got it!
Perfect.
I can't help but think the
timing of this whole ordeal
is a bit suspicious.
Now I simply have to
hope that nothing happens
until everyone
accepts Kenshi as mine.
...Would you please relax?!
We forgot to ask you,
what class are you in?
Let's see...
I'm in beginner's class two.
That's Maria's class...!
No, there must
be some mistake!
Look... Your little
'thing' for Yukine...
it doesn't mean you get to
let Maria win you over, okay?
You're forbidden
to talk to her...
Only ignore her
If she does attempt to engage
you in conversation,
just walk away.
We did not say
you could go...!
We are not done
speaking with you!
Come back here!
There he is!
That's him, right?
Huh... Wasn't expecting
him to look so normal.
Wanna know what I heard from
some of the upperclassmen?
You've gotta be kidding!
That's crazy!
I just don't think enrolling
him is a good idea...
Have you considered
this moron might do something
really stupid and damage
your reputation?
Come now, you can't actually
think we're concerned
with such trifles as that?
Fine...
Your call.
Pardon me, Empress.
Kenshi, I hope
it's all right,
but I've been ordered to give
you a tour of the school...
Remember me?
I'm Lapis.
A tour...?
Why yes, of course.
Wait...
Aren't you-?
Well then,
let's get going...
You ready?
Are we seeing things,
or does he know her?
It sure seems
that way to me.
Come on, Chiaia!
We're going to follow them!
What...?
Like right now?
Yes, we can't let him
run free, after all.
I think it's sweet
you remember me.
Thank you for that.
Yeah. Have you
had any more...
you know, problems...
with um... uh-
Oh... that happens
all the time here.
But no need to worry,
I'm okay now.
Well, they seem pretty
close, don't they?
Yes... He is surprisingly
quick with the ladies.
So, see that building
right up ahead?
That's for
the upperclassmen.
But the courtyard
just across the way?
The underclassmen
get to use that area.
Aw, cool!
Hey! Aren't you
two underclassman?!
You don't have any
business being here.
This area's off limits.
Uh... Yes,
I know that...
Sorry, I was assigned to give
our new student a tour.
Oh...! Kenshi,
it's you!
Good morning.
Oh... If we'd known you
were friends with Kenshi,
then we wouldn't
have bothered you.
Welcome! I'm really excited
to see the rumors
about you coming
to school here are true.
I'm looking
forward to it.
Hi!
Keep up
the good work!
Excellent sneaking,
no one saw us creep in.
Wait a second, isn't that
Empress Lashara up there?
Yeah but this is where
you're supposed to pretend
you don't see anything.
The upperclassmen
were so nice.
I'm surprised
they were friendly.
I was expecting them
to be upset with us.
And why is that?
Well, for one thing,
the upperclassmen
have all been knighted
as Sacred Mechamasters...
That puts them in a
different social standing
than the underclassmen.
Although, I guess that
doesn't really apply
to male underclassmen,
since they're already
Sacred Mechamasters.
Oh.
That goes for
you too, Kenshi.
For me...?
Yeah, but I'm not
a Sacred Mechamaster.
Well, then you're absolutely
the exception to the rule...
The attitude of the
upperclassmen says it all:
You're very special.
Uh, you sure...?
Chiaia doesn't think that, she
says I'm no better than a Koro.
A Koro?
Well, she may be
kinda right...
You're as cute as a Koro.
I can see that much.
Going by this, there
shouldn't be any problems.
No way, this is where
all the problems begin.
Are you sure?
Classes are gonna start soon.
We are not going!
Shame on you,
Empress.
Miss! We can explain!
I heard there was a
suspicious duo lurking about
and look who I found.
As his master, we were
simply making sure
he did not do
anything weird.
Yes and as your teacher
I'm simply making sure
you don't do anything
weird, understand?
What are you doing?!
Let us go!
Let us go right now!
You'll pay for
doing this to us!
Hey, did you hear?
All the scary upperclassmen?
They're nice to him;
they treat him like
he's royalty or something.
A couple of
the upperclassmen
I know have been excited about
him coming here for days.
Quiet down,
everyone...!
We have a
brand new student
who'll be joining
our class today...
His name
is Kenshi Masaki.
Hi, everybody...
I'm glad to be here.
Now... I hate to disappoint you,
but the test is still on.
Those who need
to prepare...
Go ahead
and move out.
And Kenshi...
You can just stay put,
you'll be studying in here
with all the other boys.
Right.
Now then.
Hold on.
Listen up...!
After your teacher
announces you to the class,
give male
students, royalty,
and high nobility
a personal introduction.
It's a pleasure to study
with you, Princess.
Oh... The pleasure's
all mine, Kenshi...
I look forward
to this year.
Unfortunately, it's past time
I headed out to prepare...
Let's meet up
again very soon.
I'm Kenshi Masaki...
It is a pleasure
to meet you guys.
So... You're Empress
Lashara's attendant...
Lucky for you.
Let's see, where
was my desk again?
Are we getting a break?
Kenshi!
He's one...
big... jerk!
My name's Ceres Taito.
How're you?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Noble Lord.
Hey, knock it off...
Boys here don't
address each other
with fancy
titles like that,
and you don't have
to either, so relax.
Oh yeah. Try not to let those
jerks get to you, okay...?
That's just how they
are, they all suck.
So where is everybody
headed off to...?
The teacher
mentioned a test?
This academy has special
classes for wife training,
such as tea ceremonies,
flower arranging,
and various
types of dancing.
Aw, man...
I got bad news; I'm not
equipped for that type of thing.
No, no, all we have
to do is watch.
What do you mean?
I mean, we get
to sit back and judge...
Having taste in the
arts is part of our job
as Male Sacred Mechamasters.
Riiight.
Aw, man...
This is crazy!
You're pretty much the
clumsiest person I've ever met.
Ah, forget about him,
I can do this!
What are you working
on so fervently?
Oh, hello, Dagmyer.
Well...
That is unusual.
Quite a project.
Uh... No, there's
a reason I'm doing this!
It's Kenshi's, I had to!
Kenshi...?
You'd go to such trouble
for a mere attendant?
Oh... Well...
It's just this is
a special thing.
Umm...
I don't mean that Kenshi
is special or anything, but-
Dagmyer.
Sorry, but... he would like
to borrow you for a minute.
I see...
Well, goodbye for now.
Okay.
Since this is your
first time, Kenshi...
don't fret over
what score you give.
Okay.
Yes, I agree.
He's working out
better than expected.
Tell me, what do you think
of this new crop of students?
They're about the same as
they are every other year...
Well, except for
Kenshi Masaki, that is.
Honestly, I was
quite surprised...
The kid may be brand new, but
his marks are as good as ours.
That's quite impressive
for his first day.
Indeed...
His numbers are, by far, the
most accurate we have ever seen.
But still...
I don't think
it's wise to ignore
the possibility
this is nothing but
a simple anomaly...
He did just arrive here,
so time will be the judge.
Take as much time
as you'd like.
In my humble opinion,
he's our top male student.
Trust me Principal,
you can look forward
to great things from him.
Now Kenshi...
Since this is your
first day with us...
I'd like to get a sense
of your skill level.
Sure thing,
Ms. exiah.
Oh... How
very intriguing.
Is something going
on over here? ...
Is that... .?
L ooks like he's managed
to snake his way in here.
He truly is
a wild creature.
It's just what I thought.
I'm ready whenever you are.
All you have to do is block
my attacks, understand?
Amazing.
I thought as much.
So annoying.
Have you studied
swordsmanship under someone?
My grandpa.
Is he a skilled
martial arts master?
No way...
He's just an old man who
lives in the country.
Very well then.
I want you to observe
the rest of the class.
Okay.
Excuse me?
Since our class is still
at the beginner's level...
Could he start
studying with us?
Oh, don't you worry.
I'll give him a private
lesson later on.
Oh my!
I'm surprised a low
class guy like him
knows anything
at all about fighting.
This one thinks he's
something special.
I think it's time we give
him a lesson in humility.
Ceres,
come over here!
Pardon me,
Ms. exiah.
I'm curious to know
why you're not letting
Kenshi participate in class.
Because...
He uses a rather
unusual style...
It's clear he's
a master at it.
A master, but how?
Oh, I have no idea...
But if I actually
fought him, I'd lose.
Is he really that skilled?
The gap of ability between him
and the others is immense...
It wouldn't be safe to let
him spar with any of them.
I understand...
You're doing the right thing
for the safety of the children.
Right.
Miss, come quick!
Since Miss Mexiah gave
up on instructing you.
We've decided,
as your classmates,
to do the right thing
and teach you a lesson
you'll never forget.
Although...
I should probably warn you,
our teaching style's
a bit aggressive.
Oh, is that right...?
Lemme see.
Well, you're pretty good at
running away, aren't you...?
Hey!
You really think you can
dodge all our strikes?
Kenshi, no!
Don't interfere yet!
Let's see
how he handles this.
Don't get in my way!
Sorry about that...
but I've had it.
I can't go on!
Yeah... me neither.
You guys
are so pathetic!
I don't know about you,
but I feel pretty warmed up.
Whaddaya wanna do next?
I suppose it's about time
I put a stop to this.
Kenshi Masaki...
Who do you think
he really is?
According to reports, a bandit
was behind the recent attack
against Empress Lashara.
The white
Sacred Mechanoid...
He's the pilot.
An interesting theory...
I'll admit that would
certainly make the most sense.
But how could there be
a male Sacred Mechamaster
who we've never even heard
of or seen before...?
The only other possible
explanation
doesn't fit time-wise.
You've taken a liking
to him, haven't you?
I have.
Should we steal him then?
Yes.
He is too special to waste
on Empress Lashara,
don't you agree?
Yukine,
come over here.
Hey... what do you think they're
gonna have on today's menu?
Let's just hurry!
They hate it...
Lunchtime.
Oh no!
Hey...!
Kenshi, wait up!
That guy...
I just don't get how
he's so full of energy.
Be quiet... I'm trying
to rest my brain here.
Sorry!!...!
I'm late.
Relax, Kenshi, didn't you
start school today...?
Don't worry; you don't have
to help with lunch anymore.
Huh...?
I guess I came
outta habit...
But I'll help out
since I'm here.
Hey, you're alright...
Thanks a lot, kid.
Next we're cooking for
the underclassmen...
Hey kid, quit working
and get back to your
school day right away!
Yeah, okay!
Let me help ya.
Oh, no...
It's okay,
you really don't
have to do that.
But I always
do stuff like this.
Hey, Yukine.
Are you taking lunch
to Princess Maria?
I am...
I'm bringing it
to the classroom.
That's where she said
she wanted to eat today.
Then how 'bout
we go together?
Sure.
Look at them...
I bet they've got
something going on.
Have you heard any good
gossip about it, Lapis?
Not really...
Kenshi is Empress
Lashara's assistant.
It makes sense he and Yukine
would get to know each other.
Hey Ceres, can I eat
lunch with you today?
Oh... Yes,
of course...
Please. Kenshi.
You care to join
us for lunch?
I'd love to.
But sorry...
I asked Ceres.
Perfect... Then Ceres
will dine as well.
No...
I-I couldn't...
I...
I'm just a-
Of course, I see...
Well, since
everybody is here,
why don't we all
dine together today?
After we graduate,
we'll each have our own
unique stations in life.
But right now, we all study
in the same classroom...
So while we're
in the Holy Land,
let's ignore the social barriers
that will ultimately oppress us.
Yeah...
You are so right.
Yeah.
So, tell me, how was
your first day at school?
Oh, I had a really
awesome time.
Kenshi!
I'm sorry...
Really.
About what?
Earlier today...
I was so scared of them...
I froze up.
I'm sorry.
I'm just glad you were around
to explain everything to me.
Kenshi!
A little bird told us
you got rather friendly
with Maria at lunch today.
Huh...?
Wait, whaddaya mean?
You're our attendant and
nothing will change that...!
Do we make ourselves
perfectly clear...?
Stupid!
I'll see you
guys tomorrow!
Here... For you.
Whoa!
You won't be able to
repair the chain properly
until you return
to your homeland...
In the meantime,
you can use that.
It's a very
pretty cord...
Thanks...!
I love it!
I'm impressed you
were able to fix it.
Yeah, you and me both.
Lookie!
Ah...
A red cord...
I see.
Is red bad?
No...
It's a supposed tradition
from another world...
Between partners, red cords
are an expression of love,
a symbol of two bodies
forever intertwined.
Oh my...
Love is in the air.
Kenshi, give that
back right now!
How come?
Don't argue with
me about this,
I'll just give you
a different one...
Just give it back!
Yeah but, I really
like this one!
Too bad! Hand over the cord,
you little freak!
Come on, can't I keep it?
Red is my favorite color!
I don't care what your
favorite color...
Oh, goodness gracious.
No way!
Tell me...
How did our
wild beast do?
Good... He will definitely
meet the criteria.
Well, well.
They finally decided to put
you on the student council,
Kenshi...
Your big social
debut is almost here!
Next time on Tenchi Muyo:
"War on Geminar:
To be Chased and Pursued."
That vile Maria...!
What in the world
could she be up to?