Watch those lunges. Your point
needs to strike home. Here.
Finally!
[HITOMI] Congratulations, you
improved your form just enough
to distract yourself
into getting skewered.
Well done. Bravo.
Gee, thanks...
So encouraging.
Encouraging is for
sissies, don't ya think?
Now get up... Rei.
[HITOMI] He's Lost.
This shouldn't be possible.
An eye for an eye... Tooth for
a tooth. And evil for evil.
You're full of surprises,
aren't you? Just look at you.
Determined to beat me
whatever the cost. Well...
[SAKURA] Ogami!
[HITOMI] It pains me to do this,
but I'm not letting you win.
[HITOMI] What?!
He absorbed his power?!
How'd he do that?
Try absorbing this,
you bastard!
[TOKI] Oh, no!
[HITOMI] Your flame can't deal
with this much electricity...
You'll have to take the
whole thing at once!
No, Hitomi!
Die!
Sakura!
Hey, freak! Get the hell
out of there already!
Damn it, Number One...
Stop it!
Oh, my god...
He absorbed
the whole thing.
Exquisitely done. Bravo,
Number Six... Magnificent.
[SAKURA] What's going on?
I don't understand.
Those eyes... He's not
himself anymore!
Oh, no... This isn't over!
No one stands in my way!
Hitomi!
I will fulfill my vision.
Don't do it!
You cannot stop me!
This world will be changed!
Incredible.
He's become a god.
Burn to nothing.
[KANDA] Hitomi!
[HACHIOJI] No, please!
God. Is he dead?
[SAKURA] Ogami!
[YUKI] Number six!
[HEIKE] Well done, my friend.
You've reached the
pinnacle of your art.
[KANDA]
Hitomi. Look at me!
[HITOMI] Kanda...
[SAKURA]
Wake up! Come on!
Don't you even think
about doing this to me!
[HITOMI] So I screwed up, huh?
Wait! You shouldn't
be moving!
[HITOMI] Get away from me.
[SAKURA] Hey!
What's happening?!
Ah... We have
arrived at Code End.
[TOKI] Wha--? He's there?!
[KANDA] Oh, no...
[HACHIOJI] Hitomi...
Heh...
So you knew...
about Code End...
all this time, huh?
Oh, man...
His powers have
turned on him.
[HITOMI] Safe to say I don't
have long. I've pretty much been
on borrowed time since Eden
had me in the crosshairs...
I was so scared.
Not so much of dying, but of
being all alone when I went...
And I knew... that our
brothers felt the same terror;
that it filled their
last moments on earth.
Listen to me rant...
It's not like I can expect
you all to understand...
And it's my fault you don't.
I wish I could've changed
things for you guys;
found a way to reform Eden...
But when I realized
my Code End was just around
the corner, I panicked.
I couldn't... I couldn't focus.
And I hated Eden so much...
All... All I wanted...
was to carve out a better world
for people like us, without...
This fear... This horrible
feeling that life just marches
on without you... I didn't
want this to be our destiny.
We deserved better.
Anyone would.
[HITOMI]
But it all fell apart.
[HITOMI] No...
I have one last card to play.
This isn't over... Just yet.
Enough already! Please!
I can see to it
the Prime Minister
pays for what he's done!
It's all over, Hitomi.
The man must atone for the
deaths of my fallen brothers...
It's justice! As long as
I breathe... evil must...
Stop! It's over--!
He deserves to die
and you know it!
Who's gonna do it if not us?!
And what did all those
people deserve?!
Are we worth it?
Is payback worth it?!
You don't care who dies,
do you? Is that justice?!
What happened to
protecting the helpless?
How is it okay to just use
them to make a point...?!
I believed in you...!
I wanted to be like you!
[OGAMI] You bastard!
You were our compass,
don't you understand?!
We followed you to make
sense of ourselves!
I had to... I had no choice.
I owed it to you as your leader.
He took this burden on
himself for their sakes...
Like they were all...
[SAKURA] ...his children.
[OGAMI] No!
[HITOMI] Kanda isn't the
only one whose job it is
to keep us in check. Other Code
Breakers watch from the wings.
[HITOMI] I didn't want to
involve you in my plan,
because if I so much as
contacted you... There was
a chance Eden would blame
you too. I had to do it alone.
[HACHIOJI] Hitomi!
Oh, god...!
Hang on!
[HITOMI] How 'bout that...
Loyal to the end,
even when I try to keep you at
bay... Even after all this...
[TOKI] Tell us what to do.
[HITOMI] Just like
old times, huh...?
Hey, Yuki... Always the first
one to come running at any sign
of trouble, aren't you? You
sure set a good example, kid.
Number one...
[HITOMI] Toki... I'm glad you
protected Kanda from me...
I was wrong to do what I did.
It was heartless.
It's okay.
I'm so sorry... Kanda...
[HITOMI] Hachioji... I'm amazed
you fought Yukihina and lived...
And I'm glad...
But it's too bad
we couldn't get the
children out in time...
[HACHIOJI] I didn't...
[HITOMI] No, it's okay;
it wasn't your fault.
Heike... I want
you to know that
I trusted you every
step of the way.
Hell, even when you were acting
suspicious, I figured you still
had my best interests at heart,
so I just went with it...
The time we spent
together as Code Breakers
were some of the happiest
moments of my life.
Had to go and give you the
transmit point, didn't I...?
Everything seemed so tightly
wrapped up till then...
But you got me.
[HITOMI] I just wish I could've
met all of you sooner.
We could've worked together
to improve our lot.
God knows I couldn't
do it on my own.
Ogami... your powers
are astonishing.
But... your point
didn't strike home.
You gotta watch
those lunges, kiddo...
Don't get distracted
by your own power.
It's about follow-through.
Finish what you started.
Don't talk to me... What the
hell is wrong with you?!
You think I care about you
after what you've done?!
I didn't fight you out of
respect! You understand?!
I beat your ass because
you betrayed us!
And look at you now!
Lying there like a broken animal
begging for death...
Screw you! You're the Ace!
You were supposed to have
our back no matter what!
I didn't want to do this!
I wanted you to be right!
How is anything supposed to
change for us with you dead?!
I don't know... But
I saw this through
as far as I could, and that's
something, at least...
If that's as good a deal
as I get, I'll take it.
Maybe it's up to you...
Maybe you ought to be the one...
I mean... you're
the hero here...
If anyone can bring
us into the light...
it's the guy who saved
the world from me.
You and Toki... Yuki...
Heike... and Hachioji...
Why not join hands and step
into the light together?
It would be beautiful...
Do that...
Take your place in the world
proudly... For me... For them.
That won't be possible.
Take it from me, my friend:
ten years from now,
no one will remember your
name... You're just small-time.
Come forward now
and all they'll do
is turn the code breakers
into boogeymen.
So, yes. I think we're
finished here, are we not?
[SAKURA] How can
you say such a thing?!
All of this could have been
avoided if you'd only listened
to him! He came to you in
confidence as their leader!
What he wanted for them
was what you should want
for the people you're
supposed to lead!
Don't get all high-handed,
love. I'm not obligated
to let a freak of nature bombard
me with his existential dilemma.
But, you... You groomed him
into his role. You chose him...
And now I regret having done
so. If I'd had any inkling
it would pan out like this,
I'd have had him put down.
But, live and learn... I'll be
far more cautious in future.
With the next batch.
You... monster!!
Oh, no.
Stop this!
I'm finished watching
you destroy innocent lives,
you twisted son of
a bitch! I'm done!
You will pay! You...
...will pay!!
It's alright...
Just let it go.
You've done enough... Let us
handle it from here on...
No more... No more
blood on your hands.
I don't want to see you go
out like that... Please.
Trust us. You've taught
us well. And we're here.
You're not alone... Your death
will not have been for nothing.
You're right. Thank you, Ogami.
I'm so damn proud of you.
It's been an honor to
watch you grow up.
You have fulfilled
your role admirably...
We are in your debt... Ace.
[PRIME MINISTER]
I thought he'd never go...
A black sheep to
the very end, eh?
Shut the hell up!
[SAKURA] Surely he didn't
have to end up like this.
[OGAMI] How else should a man
end up who does what he did...?
He had this coming.
[SAKURA] Shut up!
He was scared; he wasn't
in his right mind!
It doesn't matter anymore!
He's dead. End of story.
Oh, Ogami...
I hear the crazy son of a
bitch took a slug to the head.
Justice is served.
[WOMAN 13A] Well,
it just goes to show you
that we're all in
very good hands.
[CHILD 13A] Police do not get
enough credit. Seriously.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Outstanding work, m'boy.
I had a job to do
and I did it.
Don't be so modest...
Come now...
Your supposed betrayal
was a fulcrum point.
You played the poor
man like a fiddle.
[HEIKE] If you insist.
[PRIME MINISTER]
You used Hachioji and Yuki
to marvelous effect as well.
The children were kept
in our hands; this country's
illustrious Prime Minister
was spared-- all in all,
a good day's work.
Hm. Oh, don't worry...
I'd be a fool to think
you didn't have ulterior
motives behind all this.
The extent of Six's power
could only manifest
when his back
was against a wall.
If Hitomi had succeeded
in bringing Ogami
to his cause, we'd have
been in quite a pickle.
But you made sure
they were at odds.
Now one is no longer a problem
and the other is, well...
[PRIME MINISTER] Kudos,
Heike... I'm impressed.
You are too kind.
[PRIME MINISTER] Your
skirmish with Hitomi
was a particularly
brilliant piece of theatre.
I don't know if I'd
call it that, sir.
So... Number Six... What do
you think of his power?
Is it mature enough yet to make
a play against the Seekee?
[SEEKEE] Really? Hitomi is gone?
Nothing stopping them from
making the girl a collar around
his neck anymore, then.
[SEEKEE] Lucky her.
Rei's power made a good
show its first time out,
but we'd be the
epitome of naive
to presume we
can maintain control.
[PRIME MINISTER] Bah. We've got
the rarebreed under our thumb,
lest you forget.
She's our secret weapon
should his fire ever
need extinguishing.
I see... How pragmatic
of you, sir.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Our plan owes everything
to the juxtaposition
of those two.
They are the reason Hitomi was
given the opportunity to become
a Code Breaker, let alone
lead them, in the first place.
His powers drew Ogami's out;
Sakura's kept them in check.
In the end, it unfolded like
an elegant game of chess.
Exactly as planned.
Congratulations.
Indeed...! Now our pawns are
lined up against the Seekee...
Fire shall be fought
with fire... Yes? Heh.
Heh... Yes, sir.
Still, all bets are off...
Hitomi did come
uncomfortably close
there for a bit...
When push comes to shove...
The Seekee might prevail...
There's just never
a moment's peace.
That's right, never a
moment's peace...
Says the man who
egged Hitomi on.
I was well protected,
right...? Come...
Why shouldn't I take
risks when I have
someone of your caliber in
my pocket? Nothing ven--
[DRIVER 13A] What happened?!
Guess I spoke too soon...
Sneaky bastard...
[HEIKE] Hitomi...
Where is he?
[puppy whimpers]
[YUKI] I know.
Kinda sucks, right?
[SAKURA] What are you doing?
He's gone... I'm sorry.
[YUKI] Cheer up, though--
I'm still around.
If you're, like, ever in
trouble or something...
All you gotta do is call.
Uh... Thanks,
I appreciate that.
[YUKI] Later!
[HACHIOJI] Yeah, the cat boy's
never been strong on goodbyes.
[SAKURA] What do you mean?
[HACHIOJI] The gig's over.
They only pulled us together
for the Hitomi thing...
Now that it's put to bed,
we're back to working solo.
That's how it goes.
So yeah, anyway...
Thank you. For everything...
Your mom can cook.
Well...
You're always welcome.
Hey there; look at that...
So you do smile.
Wow... Now that I see it,
your smile is really beautiful.
Shut the hell up!
Uh... I mean,
see you 'round!
Y'know, I think I like her.
So I suppose... everyone will
go their separate ways now.
[SAKURA] Don't give me that...
Good riddance, I say.
[SAKURA] Nothing but trouble...
[TOKI] Whoa. Somebody looks
like they need a pick-me-up.
[SAKURA] There... There was
something in my eye!
Least they said
goodbye, ya know?
So, does this mean
you're not leaving?
Oh, no... You and I
have unfinished bus--
Knock it off...
You're an ass.
That was uncalled for...
I was gonna tell you
where you might find Ogami,
but I guess you don't care.
Out with it, now...!
Please, I have to know...!
He and I left too much
hanging between us...
I can't just let him
go off on his own!
[TOKI] Damn...
Guy's got all the luck.
Really? He's already
back in the field?
Yeah... Can't believe
I'm the first one
you're hearing this from...
Such a douche.
What, he's just gonna leave you
to wonder if he's even okay...?
I mean, give me
a break... Ugh...
How hard is it to say
goodbye? Seriously.
[TOKI] Whoa... What the...?
What are you doing?
Driver! Stop the bus, please!
I need to get off this instant!
Bye, Sakura...
Best of luck.
Mom...! Look up!
Ogami.
Snooze, ya lose!
[GIRL 13B] Whatever!
In your dreams!
Wow! This is so neat!
Well done...
[SAKURA] Ogami...
Code Breakers go unnoticed
by the bulk of
humanity, yes, but...
You leave no less a
mark because of it...
You've made a
difference in my life...
In some secret way, you thrive
in all of us... You exist...
No matter how well you keep
to the shadows or walk between
the raindrops, none of you is a
ghost; none of you is alone...
Even Hitomi, and the fallen
comrades he mourned,
live in the hearts of
those you've saved.
And we thank you.
An eye for an eye...
tooth for a tooth...
And evil for evil.