♪
Earlier this morning...
a fire claimed the life
of one of the country's
most notable politicians...
Emergency responders were called
to the private residence of
Shigeru Tabata to combat
a four alarm fire, only to
find that he'd succumbed.
It's a staggering loss...
The man and I have
worked closely for years;
he was a tireless ally and
a trusted friend of mine.
[MALE REPORTER]
Investigators say the fire
may have been started
by cigarette ash.
Can you tell us if you knew
Dr. Tabata to be a smoker?
I've known him to light up
from time to time,
I must admit...
If there's a link I'll
be greatly saddened.
[buzz]
[ADVISOR A] Prime Minister,
sir, Toki is here to see you.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Excellent... Send him in.
Ah! Toki...! Welcome!
Splendid work last night.
Oh, where are
my manners... Please.
My how time flies.
We haven't broken bread
together like this in ages.
Children, huh...?
Rats were a little too close
to home for you
I suppose... is that it?
Bah. Now let's not
start in with that...
Come, dear boy...
Let's enjoy our repast.
[PRIME MINISTER] Fine.
I'm a bastard.
My thinking was, Toki,
that if I could defer even a
small part of your burden,
then to hell with the cost.
I am painfully aware of
the emotional strain
your responsibilities present.
Code Breakers carry a
weight unimaginable to most.
As your father, I'm compelled
to do whatever I can to try--
[TOKI] Father?
Give me a break...
I'd have to exist to have
one of those, wouldn't I?
Son... about Nenene...
I am sorry...
It was never my intention
to put her in this position...
I simply had no
choice in the matter.
[TOKI] Don't even
say her name...
You promised to leave
her out of this mess.
That's why I became your dog...
You and me had an understanding.
That was the deal.
Of course...
Doesn't help when you visit
her in secret, though...
How is she,
by the way...? Happy?
Miserable son of a bitch.
[SAKURA] Absolute power
corrupts absolutely.
[SAKURA]
The Code Breakers answer
to the government's whim,
do they not...?
You're black ops errand boys...
The public is
completely oblivious.
[motorcycle honks]
[SAKURA] Who's that?
Ogami?
This a friend
of yours?
Hey... You mind
doin' me a solid, honey?
Um... No?
[HACHIOJI]
Give us a little space.
We need a few minutes.
[HACHIOJI] Eden's pissed.
You shouldn't have let
your friend tag along
on the Tabata mission:
bad enough she's
in on the whole thing without
you exposing her to danger.
[OGAMI] Since when is
Eden worried about her safety?
Hey, I'm just relaying
the message...
Thing is... That girl's
your problem now.
What about Hitomi...?
I'm not a babysitter.
When you're given
an order you make time...!
You got her into all this;
she's your mess...!
Understood?
Look...
I know you're not Eden's biggest
fan and I don't blame you.
I don't exactly
love them either...
But when you cop this
whole bad boy attitude...
It makes it hard on all of us.
I gotta go,
but someday I want
to talk to your little pet...
Rarebreed or not,
I can't get my head around
why Eden's worried
enough about her
to give the girl
a security detail.
Relax. I'm just curious.
Hey.
Listen. Ease up.
Don't work too hard...
Burning the candle at
both ends ain't good...
You'll get Lost.
Makes an impression,
doesn't she...?
So, I assume she's a
Code Breaker as well...?
First there was Toki...
Now this woman...
Interesting...
You have more friends
than your average
lone wolf, don't you?
[OGAMI] They're not friends...
I'm a Code Breaker;
a non-entity.
[SAKURA] Then they're
colleagues at least... Yep.
Sorry, Ogami, they humanize
you whether you like it or not.
[SAKURA] Don't get me wrong.
It's comforting to know you're
not entirely alone out there,
sure, but I definitely
think you need
to expand your
friend-pool a bit...
The more the
merrier, right?.
That's not
really my thing.
I have enough
responsibilities...
Besides, it's not
like anyone here
can contribute to my objective.
Think about what I do.
Friends would just tie me down.
They're a needless complication.
Heh...
The Code Breakers aren't
a chess club, Sakura.
Like you said, we're
colleagues. That's all.
Good morning everyone!
Uh, hi there...!
What's up?
What's going on?
Errr... We're, just
passing the time, right?
Yeah! You know
how it is...
Just trying to
keep busy and all.
[students whispering]
[MALE STUDENT 1] Dude! What's
all this crap on my desk...?
I mean jeez, come on!
[MALE STUDENT 2] My bad. Heh.
[MALE STUDENT 3]
Bell's about to ring, you guys.
[TEACHER]
Okay, pop quiz...
Take one, then pass it back.
[TEACHER]
Eyes front, Sakurakoji!
Come on!
Right...! Yes!
Sorry. Blanking out.
[SAKURA] You're black
ops errand boys.
The public is
completely oblivious.
[OGAMI] If she's decided
to broadcast my secret
to everyone in this school...
people are gonna die.
Damn her.
[HEIKE] "Crawling
through the darkness,
the young man held his
breath, his heart racing...
Shoring up his nerve,
he stole into the attic
above his love's bedroom,
eager to have done
with rumor and vile hearsay."
"Squeak... Squeak...
The boudoir
floorboards creak..."
"The young man avails
himself of a small gap
in the planks
and peers down..."
"Oh cursed sight!
His love lays
supine upon the bed.
Above her, coiled
as if to strike,
heavy rope in hand, a woman..."
"The schoolmistress...!
Her eyes gleaming,
she intones..."
[KANDA] That's enough.
Ah... Hello,
Miss Kanda.
I would appreciate
it if you didn't
recite this lurid trash right
in the middle of the hallway!
[HEIKE] I grant you the
prose is a touch lavender,
but calling it trash
seems a bit harsh.
It's... inappropriate
subject matter!
Please forgive
my enthusiasm.
I'm simply struck dumb
by the author's deft hand
at writing characters stuck
in the quagmire of Eros.
Oh, Ogami... Caution...
You're perilously
close to the Dead Zone.
[OGAMI] Excuse me...
I'd like to get my bag now
if there's no objections.
[SAKURA] Um now is
not really a good time.
What the hell's
going on in there?
Something of
vital importance?
Trust me,
you don't want to know.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1] Crazy, right?
[AOBA] I know! So exciting!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
Keep it on the DL, girls.
Is this about me...?
I want the truth.
[MALE STUDENT 1]
Crap, he's right outside!
Everyone, shut up!
You're not
going in yet!
[SAKURA] No, no, no!
You're going to ruin the--
Somebody start talking!
[STUDENTS] Hey, Ogami...!
Surprise...!
Welcome to our school!
[AOBA] Sorry.
Better late than
never, though, right?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
We had to put it off 'cause
of all the club
projects, you know?
[FEMALE STUDENT 1] Yeah. But we
finally got our crap together.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2] Here!
All guests of honor have
to wear the party hat!
[AOBA] Bit of a rush job,
so it's not the Ritz -but mad
festive, if I do say so myself.
[MALE STUDENT 1] Here.
We made you a lil' somethin'.
[MALE STUDENT 1] So you
can get all our names down.
Why would
you do all this?
[MALE STUDENT 3]
Dude, come on.
What kind of question is that?
We're stuck together
for this whole year--
might as well make the
best of it and be friends.
Am I right?
[FEMALE STUDENT 1] Yeah, I mean
you're always polite and stuff
but it's like the
only person you
wanna hang out with is Sakura.
We thought maybe it's our fault
for not making more
of an effort, ya know?
[MALE STUDENT 1] We want ya
to feel like one of the gang!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
So, yeah: Welcome!
[MALE STUDENT 3]
Welcome!
[MALE STUDENT 4]
[SAKURA] I only found
out about it this morning...
They went to a lot of trouble...
I got the job of keeping
you out of the room
while they set everything up.
[OGAMI] Mitta...
Yagi... Yusa... Watanabe...
It wouldn't kill you
to be friendlier
with them, you know...
Everyone in the class is
actually very fond of you.
[OGAMI] Pointless.
[flame ignites]
What is wrong with you?!
Seriously...! Ugh...!
Heartless jerk!
[OGAMI] Keepsakes tie you down.
Just more crap
the people you leave
behind have to deal with...
I prefer no traces of
me exist when I'm gone.
So, Takeshi:.
He's the gamer...
Then there's Aoyma:
Into rock Climbing...
The blonde Bombshell:
Ijuin... And Uesugi:
He's taking up ESL..."
I don't need flashcards.
It's all up here...
They'd probably get all
emo on me if it wasn't.
What if you...
[OGAMI] I won't forget.
Trust me.
What do you know...?
Sounds like you're
making friends to me...
The lone wolf act is
starting to fall apart.
[OGAMI]
Whatever...
I'm not getting
buddy-buddy with anyone.
[SAKURA] Ugh!
You are some piece of work!
You'd think I was asking you
to run for class president!
[TOKI] Okay...
This sucks.
[TOKI struggles]
[TOKI] No...
Goddamnit... Not now!
[ADVISOR A]
Following target confirmation,
Kamura's report
abruptly cuts off.
Which is worrying
for obvious reasons.
He would be the 43rd agent
to go missing, sir...
That we're aware of, anyway.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Hitomi is a former Code Breaker.
Quite a piece of work.
[ADVISOR A] Worthy of
the Code One designation,
without a doubt.
Indeed...
Contemplating his
next move is a thrill.
[HITOMI]
Ah. Just the man. G'morning.
[YUKIHINA] Pretty
impressive roundup, bro.
Whacha gonna
use 'em for?
They are the opening
act to Earth 2.0.
Do you think Ogami
really liked his surprise party?
Yeah, I dunno...
He's always such a
difficult guy to read.
No joke, right...?
He and Sakura...
You gotta wonder how
they make it work.
The two of 'em need all
the alone time they can get...
Thankfully I'm
stage-managing it for them.
Good call...
Roof's a good spot.
They are so gettin'
it on right now.
That'd be the idea.
I swear to you, Ogami...!
You damn well better make
Sakura the happiest girl alive,
or you'll answer to
every dude in this school!
This may sound silly,
but I think they'd love it
if you showed them
that you've already
memorized everyone's names...
plus we need to help... clean--
[JANITOR] Hold on just a minute!
What are you all doing here?
You can't just
come in here without--
[SAKURA] What is this?
What's going on?
Oh crap... Not good.
[SAKURA] No, Ogami,
please! No more killing!
Stop...! You
can't help them.
They're already dead.
What do you mean?
See...?
They're basically
just puppets.
And I know who's
pulling their strings.
[SAKURA] Are you okay?!
[HEIKE] Tsk tsk...
This is what comes of burning
the candle at both ends.
What's wrong...?
Talk to me!
[OGAMI] Damn it, why now?
Oh no! Ogami!
I've got you.
[footsteps]
[SAKURA] Whoa!
Wh-who are you?!
[SAKURA] Miss Kanda?!
[KANDA] Hitomi... Has to be.
Please explain to me
what's going on!
Not yet... First
we make our exit.
Ah hell...
Not the kids!
[SAKURA] What...?! We have
to get them out of there!
[SAKURA] What are you doing?
[OGAMI] Kanda! Stay with Sakura.
Wait, what?!
Sir, no!
Alright!
Cross the boundary--And
you get incinerated!
An eye for an eye!
Tooth for a tooth!
And evil for evil!
Oh, Ogami.
[SAKURA] If we survive this,
you and I are going
to have a nice, long chat
about your colleagues.
Ogami!
Master!
[SAKURA] No!!!
[YUKI] Hang in there,
Number Six!
Help is on the way!
Yuki... Hey.
Another one?
[HEIKE] Caught between
a rock and a hard place.
Points off for
sloppiness of form, Ogami.
[SAKURA] Heike!
[HEIKE] And you, cat boy...
You've impeccable
timing, as always...
But low marks
for your performance.
[YUKI] Huh?
Whoa...! You
wanna go?!
Stand down.
You're in the Dead Zone.
An eye for an eye...
Blah blah... And eternal
rest... for the dead.
Damn... Light energy...
Lucky bastard.
[SAKURA] Exactly how
many Code Breakers
are there hiding in plain sight?
Ogami!
[SAKURA] No...
Stay with me...
Don't you dare do this!
Look at me!
[SAKURA] Please. You can't...
Not like--Come back!
[HEIKE] He's Lost.
No he isn't.
[HEIKE] Accept it.
If needs must,
madam... blame fate...
Every Code Breaker
succumbs to this in time...
I'm sorry.
♪
[SAKURA] I refuse to let
Fate have the final word...
Not today. Not ever.
Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 7,
"Sakura, In the Light."
Come back to me,
Ogami! We need you!