[car horns honk]
[SAKURA] I need to bring the
little guy something to eat.
Stop!
Hmm? There's a scheduled
stop a few blocks up.
I'll stop then.
People are
on fire back there!
We need to call the paramedics!
[bicycle bell dings]
[SAKURA] Wait! Please, officer!
Come with me!
These folks were
burning alive...?
Uh-huh...
'fraid we didn't get here
in time to keep the blaze
from destroying all the
evidence along with 'em.
How high are you right now?
[SAKURA] I'm not...!
I know what I saw.
[POLICEMAN A] Look,
I'm seein' scorch marks--
but they're clearly from
some homeless guy's campfire.
A what?
[siren blares]
[school bell rings]
[cheering]
Full point. Excellent.
Um... it's an...
[SAKURA and SUZUKI]
...honor to spar with you!
[TEAM CAPTAIN A]
Sato, you're next.
[SATO] Honor guide our hands!
Honor guide our hands.
Haaa!
[SAKURA] What did I see?
[SAKURA] Was I imagining things?
Arrgh!
[TEAM CAPTAIN A]
Full point! Break!
[gasps]
So hot!
[TEAM CAPTAIN A]
Thank you for paying
our little club a visit today,
Miss Sakurakoji.
Means a lot to us.
[SAKURA] Oh...
Thank you, sensei but the
pleasure was all mine...
Your students here do you proud.
[FEMALE STUDENT A] Is she
not the most totally amazing
person you've ever seen?
[FEMALE STUDENT B] Seriously!
Spars with the whole martial
arts club all morning,
and still manages to
look like a million bucks.
[MALE STUDENT A] You know
she's a genius, too, right?
Her grades are, like, perfect.
[MALE STUDENT B]
If that girl had eyes for me
I wouldn't give a damn
about anything else.
Hey-hey...!
Fair warning, I'm coming at'cha!
Oh, good morning, Aoba...
How are you?
[AOBA] Uh-oh. I know that face.
Not good.
S'wrong with my face...?
There's nothing bothering me,
if that's what you're implying.
Hmm...
Better not be
holding back...
Hey! Miss Kanda!
What's the haps?!
Ah... A very pleasant
morning to you, ladies.
Who's the mystery man?
Oh, yes... our newest
addition to the student body;
a transfer from across town...
[OGAMI] Ogami Rei... I'm very
pleased to meet you all.
O.M.G...! He's a total
10...! Lemme at him!
Normally I don't
fall for that
whole "mysterious" act, but
I'd take some'a that drama!
Okay, settle
down, class...
Mr. Ogami is going to be a
permanent feature around here;
his parents travel on business a
great deal, so he's on his own--
and I expect every one of
you to make him feel at home.
[SAKURA] This isn't
coincidence. It can't be...!
The guy last night...
It was him!
[school bell]
[MALE STUDENT C] Overseas?!
Dude, I bet you got crazy game!
Nothing to write
home about...
[MALE STUDENT C]
Where all have you lived?
[OGAMI] Europe mostly.
For the past few years anyway.
I know, right...?
Cray cray...
You best make a move soon
though, if you're gonna.
That isn't why
I'm staring.
[SAKURA] Excuse me.
Oh, uh, it's
Sakura, right?
We need to have
a word in private...
Can we talk outside, please?
Yeah. Sure.
[yelling]
It's the end of
the world, man!
Sakura's in love...!
She's gonna ask out the new guy!
What?!
[MALE STUDENT C]
This cannot be happening!
[MALE STUDENT D]
Life is so unfair!
[MALE STUDENT B] I've waited
years just for her to notice me!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
She's doing the asking? Strong.
[FEMALE STUDENT B] Look at 'em.
Their babies are totally
going to rule the world!
So, what did you wanna
get off your chest?
[SAKURA] Let's cut
to the chase, huh?
Last night: Tell me exactly
what you were doing.
I was on the late shift.
Oh sure... 'kay, fine...
What's with the
glove...? Come on.
We both know it's
covering up burns...
Burns you received
while in the act
of murdering innocent people!
Speak up, girl...!
Nobody can hear you!
[SAKURA] If I'm wrong,
take it off and prove it;
otherwise I've got you--
But you were there...!
[OGAMI] I like to keep
this ring to myself.
A personal reminder
of the damage
this hand can do if
I strike out in anger...
See, I learned the hard way
about the
importance of restraint.
A friend gave this to me.
You're telling the truth...
[OGAMI] No reason not to.
But, last night...!
[OGAMI] We done?
[SAKURA] Uh, yes! We're done!
I apologize for taking up
so much of your time!
No worries...
I'm glad I could help you out...
Tell you what, though...
How 'bout you and I...
Try being friends.
If you're game.
O.M.G... Start
spillin' sister...
Is he into you?!
Well, he...
...did mention that he'd
like for us to be friends.
Whoa...!
You're kidding me!
He turned you down?!
[MALE STUDENT A] Unreal! He
gave Sakura the friends line?!
[MALE STUDENT B]
That arrogant son of a bitch!
[MALE STUDENT C] Seriously! Way
to blow your chance, dumb ass!
[MALE STUDENT B]
Rei Ogami,
every guy in this
school hates you!
Ugh! Damn it all!
I know there's something
weird about that new guy!
I get it, honey bear.
It's always the ones that
get away that drive you cray.
[SAKURA] I will find
out who he really is
if it's the last thing I do!
Umm, don't take this
the wrong way, but...
if you wanna turn his head,
maybe watch how you eat...?
[chattering]
[MALE STUDENT C]
Like hell, dude!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
That's it.
I am now officially
ruined for all other men.
[AOBA]
Uh oh.
Somebody's being
a lil' stalker.
Whatever...
He's dangerous...
I'm gonna have to
watch him like a hawk.
Mm-Hm. I'm feelin'
your pain...
Heh... Hey,
he's eye-candy...
You're not
made of stone.
Um, sure.
Damn...
Not letting you get
away that easily.
[SAKURA] They say a
murderer is always drawn
to the scene of the crime.
[children laugh]
[GIRL A] Wait for me!
C'mon, slow down!
[SAKURA] Am I sure
I didn't imagine things...?
I mean... It was all so vivid...
[SAKURA] Here.
Take the whole thing.
You probably need it since
I couldn't come yesterday.
See, I'm trustworthy...
Not that I'm trying to
replace your previous--
Paranoid mutt!
Why won't you like me?!
Ogami!
Interesting...
So, turns out you don't reserve
the attitude just for me, huh?
Uhh...
[OGAMI] A little awkward,
sure, but I like it.
Means you're a fighter.
Huh...
You trying to say
I have a bad attitude?
Not at all...
You're just confident.
And I don't think there's
anything wrong with that.
Ah... I guess that's
all right, then.
It's not every day...
My family's a little
on the weird side so- I--
Oh...
He's a bit timid, so don't take
it personally if he's scared.
C'mere, you.
Wow, you...
Poor thing.
Not many people have done
right by you, have they?
Ha, ha. Easy on
the kisses, champ!
[OGAMI laughs]
Hey, he's eye-candy,
right...? I get it.
[OGAMI] ...try being friends...
If you're game.
C'mon, knock it off.
[SAKURA] I suppose
he's not all bad.
[OGAMI]
By the way, he's a she.
You know her name?
Just "Dog."
[OGAMI laughs lightly]
[OGAMI] Gets to
the point, I suppose.
She a stray?
[SAKURA]
Her master died recently...
An old homeless man...
So she's more of an orphan.
A gang of street thugs
was responsible...
You'd know them
from their tattoos;
they call themselves G-Falcon...
The crime bosses of
this city cover for them
so that the bastards literally
get away with murder...
That's what my dad says, anyway.
That a fact?
Their connections put
them above the law...
So even the police...
turn a blind eye.
[OGAMI] Would you like to see
them get what they deserve?
Such men are in
need of punishment.
Is that what you'd like
to see happen to them?
No thank you!
I don't want revenge...
I just feel for that old man...
He lived and died
without leaving a trace
of himself in anyone's heart...
Mine breaks thinking about it.
[children laugh]
He's not without
his mourners...
You're living proof of that.
The world may brush
his memory aside,
but you don't.
And though I may not
have known the man...
I'll follow your
example... Forever.
[OGAMI] Unfortunately...
As a rule, justice
is only as effective
as the people charged
with doling it out.
An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth...
And evil for evil.
So, Hammurabi's
Code, huh...?
Kudos on the reference,
but that last part you
plucked out of thin air.
[OGAMI] Look at that.
You do smile.
I was starting to worry
it was something about me.
You have my
sincere apology...
Perhaps I'm not the
best judge of character.
[PRIME MINISTER]
And Ogami Rei? What of him?
[ADVISOR A] Fully
infiltrated and awaiting
our instructions,
Prime Minister, sir.
[PRIME MINISTER]
Good. Very good...
Then our plan can proceed.
[SAKURA] Assuming it wasn't him,
what exactly did I see...?
I must be losing my mind.
[AOBA] Hey, Ogami!
You like karaoke?
Sakura's gonna be there.
Actually I've got a lot
of stuff to do tonight.
Huh?!
I'm not doing this
for the vocal practice!
Ugh...! Put it together!
Thanks for
the offer...
But I'm kinda
busy tonight, too.
Well boo.
I see...
So you got stuck with the
late shift again, did you?
Trash collectors...
We live the high life.
[SAKURA] Ah. Noble profession.
[cell phone rings]
See...? Probably wondering
where I am already.
What the hell
is this...?!
When did you two start
getting all buddy buddy?!
[SAKURA] We're not buddy buddy.
We're just... I don't know...
[AOBA] If you're
gonna work that fast,
let a gal know, huh?
What've we got?
[KANDA] You ready to
do some cleaning up?
What kind of
question is that...
Just give me the specs.
[KANDA] What about
the Sakura problem...?
Have you decided?
There was never really
any choice, was there...?
I'm proceeding as planned.
She'll have to be neutralized.
That's right: scarf
down the goods
and blow me off! Mongrel!
[SAKURA] Sorry.
[HOMELESS MAN A]
Ahhh! Somebody help me!
Whoa. What in the...?!
Let's go over this again...
We haven't been able to
get ahold of our friends
for the past couple nights
and we wanna know
what you've seen...
You tapeworms have
the run of this place;
figure you had to
have seen something.
Am I right?
I told ya I haven't seen
a goddamn thing, I swear!
[G-FALCON A] Hey! Don't backtalk
you useless piece of shit!
Somebody please--
[SAKURA] Leave him alone!
I have the police
on the way...!
If you're smart, you'll all
clear out while you still can!
Police...? Oh no!
Anything but that!
[SAKURA] It's them... G-Falcon.
[SAKURA] These monsters killed
the old man in cold blood.
[G-FALCON C] Word of advice...
Don't go pokin' that pretty nose
where it ain't got
no business bein'...
Why don't you get out of here?
We're just trying to find out
about some friends of ours.
Wait, you...
You don't mean...
Sounds like
you know something...
Best spit it
out, girlie.
[SAKURA] It's been two nights
since anyone's
seen them, hasn't it?
[murmuring]
I think we got some
questions for you.
[G-FALCON C] Tell me
everything you know. Now.
I really did see it...
Those men...
They -they were
all burned alive.
Hey! In English.
We don't speak bitch!
You want a
helpless little girl,
you're gonna have to
look someplace else...!
You thugs have gotten everything
you're gonna get out of me!
[G-FALCON E] You are so dead...!
I demand you turn
yourselves in--
[Dog whimpers]
We're not done playin'
with you yet, little girl,
so why don't you stay put!
[SAKURA] I- I'm paralyzed...!
Let's tie 'er up...!
Stupid bitch...
You just had to come runnin'
when you heard the
parasite scream...
Well take a wild
guess what happens
to good Samaritans on our watch!
[G-FALCON A yells]
The hell'd you come from?!
No, don't!
[G-FALCON A] Get off!
[G-FALCON A] Seriously?!
You're not gonna get me!
Leave her alone!
[G-FALCON D]
Pass 'er over, I'm open!
[G-FALCON A] Heads up!
[G-FALCON B] And it's gooooood!
[G-FALCON E]
Where're you goin'--
You bastards...!
She has nothing
to do with anything!
Face me like men!
If that's what
you really want...
We can be all kinds
of manly for ya...
Hang on...!
I'll get you to a
vet as soon as I--
[G-FALCON C] Two stupid bitches.
If you're so set on
gettin' yourself killed
we can help you out, sweetheart.
Right after you tell me
what happened to my boys.
[OGAMI] Are you in pain?
[G-FALCONS] Huh?
[G-FALCON A] Who the hell?!
No! What are
you doing here?!
[OGAMI] I'm sorry, girl.
There's nothing do
be done for you.
Not anymore...
Frankly I'm surprised
you're still breathing.
[Dog whines]
[OGAMI] You fought justly and
valiantly to protect a life...
Now it's time for you to rest.
[G-FALCON A] Hey, kid...!
This ain't a goddamn pet store!
[SAKURA] Ogami!
Please: get out of here
and find her a vet!
Just please... go now!
[OGAMI] Little one...
Allow me to do you the honor.
[SAKURA] Ogami?
No... Please, no...
How could you?!
[G-FALCON A] Holy crap...
Somebody does it
hardcore... Oh well...
Looks like we're
just gonna have to take
our frustrations out
on the dog whisperer.
[OGAMI] An eye for an eye...
...a tooth for a tooth.
And evil... for evil.
[G-FALCON A] Why you
people gotta mumble--
Burn to nothing.
[G-FALCON A screams]
And here we go.
It's about time...
Let's do this.
Wha... What in
the hell are you?!
Who me...?
I'm just the guy who
takes out the trash.
Pay close attention...
This is the part where
I give you all the chance
to face the judgment
of your world
or be consumed by
the flames of mine...
So what do you say?
[G-FALCON B] Screw this!
I say you're a dead man!
Very well...
Die... as you have
chosen to live.
An eye for an eye...
...a tooth for a tooth...
And evil for evil.
That's what I saw before!
[OGAMI] It's only
fair to tell you...
...when I suggested
we be friends...
I was lying.
[SAKURA screams]
[OGAMI] Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 2...
"The Spiral Blue Flower,
Blossoming in Flame."
I will burn
everything to nothing.
Until the end.