[OGAMI] Explosions?
What the hell?
[KANDA] I don't have
all the details yet...
All we know for sure
is that they're IEDs;
apparently half a dozen have
detonated all over the city.
[KANDA] Sir?
Go on.
[KANDA] There's only
one person this could be.
I know.
[KANDA] So...?
I'm gonna take the bastard
out myself. Understood?
[KANDA] Yes, sir.
You've gone too far, Hitomi...
We end this tonight... Be ready.
[FEMALE ANCHOR A] Officials
are putting the death toll
at twelve, with
twenty-four injured
and at least four
reported missing.
Emergency responders are
still working tirelessly
to combat the blaze and
locate any survivors...
The bombing took place at the
height of rush hour traffic,
so as I'm sure our viewers
at home can imagine,
the scene here is a chaotic one.
We'll keep you updated
on this terrible tragedy
as developments unfold.
[HITOMI] Terrible indeed.
No... How can you support what
he's doing to these people?!
The misfortune of others
seems to weigh on you heavily,
doesn't it...?
A rather amusing trait.
[door opens]
Are we having fun...?
I'm glad you're getting along.
Oh, I was merely commenting
on our guest's talent
for empathizing.
Huh. "Our" guest? I'm surprised
you even brought her here.
Ask and ye shall receive,
my embattled fellow traveler...
Haven't I always been your
greatest champion?
You've been a person of
interest for quite some time.
Why is that?
Don't be naive... Come on,
this isn't your first clue;
the only reason Ogami
transferred to your school
in the first place was
to keep tabs on you.
That's not true!
Well, to be fair, Ogami didn't
know what he was signing on for.
But don't take my word for it.
See, doll... The powers that
be have spared no expense
trying to foil yours truly,
in money or human lives.
What are you... What are
you talking about?
What exactly do you
intend to do with me?
Don't be so dark. Not much
I can do with a rarebreed.
Look, I'm just
keeping you here
to make sure you
stay out of the way...
You won't come to any harm...
Think of it like this...
You've got a front row seat
to the best show in town.
You're sick!
This is terrorism!
Yes, it is.
You're a madman!
People are dying!
And what if I told you
to bear with me...
Just for a bit... That this
was for the better good?
[KANDA] He's not in
this for the carnage.
Can't be. It'd go
against his nature.
Hitomi...
[beeping noises]
[KANDA] It's me, sir.
I've just received
an anonymous tip
regarding his whereabouts;
I think it's worth following
up on. What? You, too?
[HEIKE] Be straight with me,
Ace. The pyrotechnics
on the city's outskirts
were just a warm-up, yes?
Just a taste of
what's yet to come?
[HITOMI] Easy, tiger.
Nobody likes a busybody,
especially in my position.
Ya got it?
[HEIKE] You make it sound
as though I've been
rifling through
your sock drawer...
Enough. If I trusted you
with the bigger picture,
you'd have it by now.
[HEIKE] Ah.
[HITOMI] I might be persuaded
to open up a little more if,
for example, you fessed up
on just how you found me.
It's like you knew
what'd I do before
I had a clear notion
of it myself...
[HEIKE] My recon network
had these charming digs
flagged months ago...
Come now...
A desperate man isn't
very hard to anticipate.
I don't suppose he is.
[HEIKE] I ask your plans only
as a courtesy. Truth is, I know.
And my sole aim is to
keep them from being foiled...
You and I are in this
together. What other reason
would I have had for
delivering the rarebreed?
Or for that matter reducing
Hachoji to a bloody pulp?
[SAKURA] You didn't!
[HITOMI] Now, why would you,
who cares more than anything
for his comrades-in-arms,
turn against... Hachioji?
Why...? Because
I understand...
You and I share the
same bitter grief.
You bastard...!
You wouldn't dare!
Shut up! Don't
presume to know
what a man who doesn't
exist would dare!
[HEIKE] I'm no fool, Ace.
In your position,
I wouldn't believe me either.
But there you have it.
Do as you please... But...
Try anything cute... You die.
[HEIKE] I will endeavor
to earn your hospitality.
[HITOMI] Speaking of which...
Kanda's here, which means
Ogami won't be far behind.
Crossing swords is looking
more and more inevitable.
[HITOMI] Short
notice, I know,
but how'd you feel
about doing me a favor?
[KANDA] He's up there.
I can feel it.
[OGAMI] I'm gonna take the
bastard out myself. Understood?
[KANDA] I'm sorry,
master. Forgive me.
[KANDA] Heike?!
But how...? Wait...
[HEIKE] My dear...
I've wanted to see you
in binds since
the day we met.
[phone ringing]
[OGAMI] Say that again?!
[MOTHER YUKI] Sakura hasn't come
home yet. I'm worried sick.
Please tell me she's with you.
Oh, no--she's not, is she?
She's not answering her phone,
she hasn't left a word,
with all these
bombs going off--
She's gonna be fine...
I think have a good idea
where she might be...
I'll call you when
I know for sure.
[YUKI] Six!
Number Two
has changed sides.
[YUKI] Wait!
[HEIKE] Oh, good...
You've brought the cat.
What have you done
with Number Five?
[HEIKE] Why, what could you
possibly mean by that?
[YUKI] Give it up, dude! I was
there: I saw you attack her.
Interesting. Yet you
inquire after her fate.
Explain yourself...
Right now.
What's there to explain...?
Are you that... thick?!
This is precisely
what it seems.
[YUKI] Yeah? Well, this is
what I think of traitors!
[HEIKE] Not bad. Not bad at all.
Of course, sound does have the
advantage of invisibility.
A shame its trajectory is
so predictable, though.
Ugh! You're such a dick!
[YUKI] Running away?
We call these
evasive maneuvers.
[HEIKE] Aha!
Uh... Uh-oh.
[HEIKE] Kudos on
the mercilessness.
Well, you know me...
Mercy is for bystanders!
Solid policy... Intend to
stick to it, do you?
[OGAMI] What?
Hey, Six! Heads up!
[YUKI] It's okay,
I've got your back. Go on.
[YUKI] I'll take
care of Number Two.
Think so? Ha... I may have
a bone to pick with that.
Kanda? What the hell
are you doing here?
[OGAMI] Damn you, Hitomi.
[HITOMI] Probably.
[OGAMI] You--Sakura!
[SAKURA] Ogami!
It's not Miss Kanda's fault!
She's being controlled!
He's made her a prisoner
in her own body!
[OGAMI] I know. He's disrupted
her central nervous system
with electromagnetic pulses.
[HITOMI] Very easy to
get the hang of, actually.
Living tissue's a better
conductor than dead.
Bastard.
[KANDA] Stay back. Please...
He'll... make me...
[KANDA] Run!
Get out of here, now!
I'm begging you!
Sir, please.
No! Stop!
[OGAMI] Keep firing.
I'll deflect every
round you've got...
Just empty the damn clip.
[HITOMI] Wow, kid. Respect...
I'm bummed I've
got to deal you out,
but you know--
it is what it is.
Your Gal Friday has
specific instructions
to unload the final slug into
her pretty little temple.
It's all on you, my friend.
Keep playing Man of Steel
and her ammo gets whittled
down to the coup de grace.
Take one for the team,
though, and I'll let go.
She'll walk out of here
minus a job, sure,
but she'll walk out of here
alive. What's it gonna be?
Hitomi...
[KANDA] Please, sir...
You hardcore enough to
watch her kill herself?
[SAKURA] Coward! Look at
what you're doing...!
They don't deserve this!
[HITOMI] Aren't you
adorable? Poor girl.
[SAKURA] These people
were your friends once.
You fought alongside each other!
How could you do this to them?!
Don't let him win,
whatever you do!
Don't give him the satisfaction!
This ends now. You won't
die by your own hand.
What are you...? Oh, no.
That's our Rei; he can
always be counted on to
eliminate a threat without
hesitation, no matter the cost.
He's a warrior, and a good one.
Course... could just be a pose.
Ogami... I'm sorry...
So sorry.
No. Don't! You can't kill her...
Please don't do this!
Ogami, please stop!!
No way!
[OGAMI] What did you do?
[SAKURA] I... I don't know.
Heh... You sneaky
little bastard.
[KANDA] What happened?
[SAKURA] Oh, thank heavens!
I don't understand,
are you okay?
[SAKURA] I'm fine! All that
matters is that you're okay.
Good work.
[SAKURA] I think it
was all her, actually.
She cares for you so much that
Hitomi's spell was broken--
[HITOMI] Don't be so modest.
You're a rarebreed...
Interfering is what you do best.
Oh, so now you intend to take
my dog hostage, is that it?!
Come clean... Tell me
what this is all about.
What happened to you...?
Why are you doing this...?
The Hitomi we
knew and followed
would never resort
to--To terrorism.
[HITOMI] How can you
see all the clocks
on this wall and
not have a clue?
I didn't notice it
before... but... they...
They're all stopped
at different times.
[HITOMI] Each one commemorates
a Code Breaker's time of death.
[HITOMI] 6:23 am--Former
Code Three is killed
while overseeing a
routine escort mission.
10:47 pm--Ogami's successor dies
in a sudden accident
while on cleanup duty.
[HITOMI] Each of
them lost their lives
without ever having the
chance to live them.
These are their headstones.
Each of them killed in
a battle their superiors
never spilled blood for.
This wall their only memorial.
That is truly awful.
[HITOMI] Don't patronize.
You can't imagine.
[SAKURA] He's insane with grief.
This whole thing is like
some kind of warped eulogy.
[HITOMI] Their orders came from
the Prime Minister... In effect,
he signed their death warrants;
and for that, he must pay.
That's absurd...!
What would his death prove?!
Are you listening to yourself?
This won't bring
your friends back!
Sweetheart.
It isn't about that...
I'm giving him the chance
to fulfill his supreme duty.
He gets to die
serving his country.
[SAKURA] You can't be serious.
I arrived on the scene of
this tragedy moments ago...
And I'm coming to you live...
[HITOMI] It's a shame so many
people have to die before him,
but... we need the country
in a state of panic.
It's the only way to whet
everyone's appetite
for the Main Event: the Prime
Minister's public execution
will open the eyes
of all of Tokyo.
You're psychotic!
[OGAMI] Shut up!
You sit there and act like
this is a noble cause...
What is this really about?
I want the truth.
I want people to see us...
For Code Breakers
to step into the light and
take our place in the world.
We've suffered in silence far
too long... This is what happens
when the ignorant take
their protectors for granted.
[HITOMI] None of them has earned
the peace they feel entitled to;
the illusion of tranquility
we've spilled blood to maintain.
It won't last... The storm'll
break soon enough.
[FATHER] Somebody, help!
My little girl's hurt!
I need an ambulance!
[HITOMI] Only when they tremble
in fear for their lives--
their way of life--when the
veneer is peeled away...
Only when it's perfectly
clear they've been living
on borrowed time
all this while...
Only then will they embrace
what we do and how we do it.
So, yes... It's about
power, sure.
The power to live as the
people we protect live
and the power to die without
being devoured by shadows.
You just want to be
accepted... But...!
[OGAMI] So let me
get this straight.
Once the smoke's cleared,
you're steppin' out on the town,
confident the survivors
will greet you
as a champion of justice?
More or less.
Yeah, well, that's a lot better
than the deal Eden gives us.
You don't mean that...
[OGAMI] Sounds like membership
has its privileges...
Hell, maybe you're right.
Maybe this is our only
way out of the dark.
Now you're gettin' it...
Join the cause.
[OGAMI] Tempting, but...
For all your talk,
has it ever occurred to you
that we belong in the dark?!
Code Breakers are killers...!
We don't get a place in the sun!
You don't understand...
Not even a little.
What is there to
understand about evil?
You and I are qualified
to judge it...
'cause we're cut
from the same cloth.
Look at you...!
For all your talk,
the only thing you want is
to see the world in flames!
[HEIKE] Come on, Yuki...
Make this interesting...
Give me a challenge!
[YUKI] Bite me, jerkwad!
[YUKI] Gotta hand it to him,
though. He's good.
[HITOMI] The more things
change, eh, old friend?
But this is the
point of no return.
From here on, Code
Breakers will be granted
full citizenship to the world!
Gone will be the era of secrets
and lies; gone the days
when we died in obscurity...!
We will exist! Our brothers
will not have died in vain...!
I burn Tokyo...
to liberate us all from Eden!
Here I am!
[HITOMI] Damn it, Yukihina!
[YUKIHINA] I figured something
must be up for you to be taking
this long. Clock's tickin',
boss--now's not the time.
You could've gone ahead
without me, you know.
Yeah, right... If I leave,
you'll be doing this all night.
Fair enough; let's get
a move on, then.
[SAKURA] What was that?!
I hope you're not
stupid enough to think
you can melt my ice
with your flame.
He'll figure it out. Meet you
there, or are you coming with?
Hitomi!
Wait! This isn't--
[OGAMI] Sakura, look out!
I'm coming with.
[OGAMI] Sakura!!!
You're a really pitiful
bodyguard, man...
The whole point is to keep
Sakura out of danger.
[SAKURA] Toki!
[TOKI] You're welcome,
by the way...
Sorry I couldn't be here
sooner, but, you know...
It's always cooler
when the hero makes
his entrance at the last
possible second, right?
Hey! Stop right there!
Drop the politician!
Just so you guys know...
There's a truckload
of explosives set to blow this
place up... You might wanna
think about putting some
distance between you.
Seriously?
Come back! Don't you care
that that's his father?!
Don't be an idiot!
[TOKI] Sakura, no!
He's dangerous!
Not ideal. I propose we
revisit this down the road.
Huh?! No you-- Damn it!
Wow... I didn't
think you were game
for what's about to go down.
You won't get away with this...
I promise you that right now...
No one else is
dying on my watch!
[SAKURA] Look at him.
He doesn't even care.
[SAKURA] What could've driven
him to be this kind of person?
[OGAMI] I'll always remember
the night we met; the smell
of death and gun smoke. The
haunted look on your face.
[OGAMI] Next time,
"Code: Breaker" episode 10,
"The World People See."