[PRIME MINISTER] It's my
pleasure to inform you
that the Eden Council
unanimously supports
your inauguration
into our little family.
I can't thank you enough.
Welcome, Code Six.
We expect great things.
[HITOMI] An eye for an eye;
a tooth for a tooth...
And the hammer of
judgment for all evil.
[TARGET 10A]
Screw you, punk!
[PREVIOUS PRIME MINISTER]
I'm very happy with
the new recruit's performance.
He seems to be moving
along at a nice pace.
[PRIME MINISTER] Quite.
I believe a promotion
is in order, sir.
[PREVIOUS PRIME MINISTER]
You thinking of making him
king of the hill someday?
[PRIME MINISTER] Perhaps.
Hey... It's gonna
be alright.
Ha! Too slow!
[GIRL 10A] You are so dead!
[HEIKE] Practicing your
thousand-yard stare?
Tell me you're
not moved by this.
When I see kids doin'
their thing, laughing it up,
it's like seeing a perfect
world in miniature.
We have a shot at
making that world real...
That's what this is about.
I like that... Makes
what we do sound noble.
Hey... You know I couldn't
do it without you.
Target is proceeding
west on foot
through the intersection
of 3rd and Beacon...
I'm almost on top of them.
[HARUYA] Copy that, Six.
Standing by on 4th.
Oh, shit! It's a trap!
[Haruya screams]
What the hell...?!
Come in, Five!
[HEIKE] It's a shame.
Haruya was a good man.
Moving on. As of today,
you are promoted to Code Five...
I am sure you'll do your
predecessor proud.
Come and get me, loser!
[BOY 10C] Aww! Hey,
that's cheating! No fair!
[HITOMI] Focus on the end game.
[ORIGINAL 01] Stay alert.
Three and Five will be
sweeping in from the right.
Understood.
[ORIGINAL 01] These guys
aren't your usual suspects.
They're defectors from Eden;
meaning they'll give
as good as they get.
According to our man on
the inside, we're looking
at a potential large-scale
terrorist coup.
You are to terminate
with extreme prejudice.
[HITOMI] Where is
everyone...? Damn it!
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL]
The dog barks!
[HITOMI] Please. No...
Code One!
You are a dead
son of a bitch!
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL] Well,
well! I've heard about you!
Hell of a rep you got
to live up to, kid.
Take out my guys, you leave
me with expectations.
Let's see what you got...
Put your friend down
and die like a man!
They're all dead.
How can they all be dead?!
Well, you made it through
without a scratch;
so there's that... Their leader
evaded capture, yes, but...
The terrorist cell as a
whole is neutralized...
At the end of the day we
achieved our mission objectives.
[HITOMI] Too many of us had to
die... It's a hollow victory.
[HEIKE] Off the record,
I don't disagree...
Four of the six most formidable
operatives in the world
have been wiped out
in one fell swoop.
The prospect of rebuilding
the team is not a happy one.
Heike. How
much does Eden
actually know about
our abilities?
[HEIKE] In what sense?
[HITOMI] Code Six wasn't
killed by the target.
I saw it: Her power
somehow turned on her...
The column of water she was
trying to control engulfed her.
She drowned. The enemy
hadn't even reared its head.
I don't care for that.
It bears rather too close
a resemblance to Code
Four's untimely death.
[HITOMI] Exactly.
Look into it... I wanna know
what the hell's going on.
Consider it done... Ace.
What?
[HEIKE] As of today, you are
promoted to Code One...
Congratulations.
If that's the way
things are... Okay...
I'll find us some
new recruits...
From now on...
Nobody dies.
♪
[PRIME MINISTER]
Work hard, my children... Heh.
This is not my day!
An eye for an eye... Tooth for
a tooth... and evil for evil.
Burn away.
[HITOMI] He's got talent...
A little rough around
the edges, but hey...
[KANDA] I agree. His
scores are astronomical,
even by Eden's standards.
[HITOMI] True, but...
[KANDA] Sir?
[HITOMI] His take on what
we do is too severe.
A trap?
[TOKI] Way to look
'fore you leap, dude.
If you wanna stay
Code Six forever...
you are rockin'...
Don't change a thing.
[OGAMI] Screw you.
[TOKI] Screw you!
It's called teamwork...
And that's a real
nice attitude to throw
at the guy who just
saved your dumb ass...
"I was so in over my
head, Toki. Thanks!"
You are welcome.
[gunshot]
[HITOMI] Trade quips when
the job is done, fellas.
Getting to it!
[HITOMI] I know you
like to focus on
taking out the bad
guys, Number Six,
but our first and foremost
concern was to rescue the child.
Word of advice: Don't get so
caught up in fighting "evil"
that you give
yourself tunnel vision.
Hey... It's okay.
[BOY 10E] You gotta
be faster than that!
[GIRL 10B] Yeah, yeah!
[HITOMI] Do you even
have a clear notion
of why you became
a Code Breaker?
[OGAMI] To abolish
the evil in the world.
'Kay... How 'bout this...
Say death comes
knockin' at your door.
You've got moments left...
How do you spend the time?
Keep my fire lit...
See to it evil suffers
till my very last breath.
[HITOMI] You are
a piece of work.
[HITOMI] Me?
Believe I'd like to go
knowing I was helping someone.
[OGAMI] Six of one, half a
dozen of the other, right?
I don't think you understand
what I'm getting at.
Rei, listen... Yes, we
punish the wicked, but...
That's not the end of it... Our
job is to protect the powerless
as much as it is to
destroy the lawless.
That's the first
obligation of power:
to help those without it...
The gifts we've been given
are not a right;
they're a privilege...
Don't ever forget it.
So I should accept
dying for someone else
who's weaker than me?
Death is what binds us;
powerful and helpless alike...
'Sides...
[HITOMI] The off
chance that the memory
of what I've done for
them gives someone
the strength the fight
their own battles
is more than enough for me.
That'd be beautiful.
What if they die
in that fight?
[HITOMI] Not gonna happen...
I'll die making sure of it.
[OGAMI] Hitomi!
[Hitomi snores]
Ah, hell.
[HITOMI] It's him.
Yes... I've familiarized
myself with the file...
That's the crazy son of
a bitch who went rogue
and nearly drove the Code
Breakers to extinction...
Looks like he's resurfaced.
Are you ready to
face him again?
Hell, yes, I am.
[HITOMI] Go time.
Let's do this, people.
Understood.
[TOKI] Just look both ways 'fore
crossing the street, Ogami.
[HITOMI] There are targets
in every room on this floor;
it's vital we synchronize.
You're in the
Dead Zone... Sorry.
[HITOMI] Show yourself... Now.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL] Someone
knows how to make an entrance.
[HITOMI] I'm not
trying to impress you.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL]
Well! It's Eden's lapdog!
[HITOMI] Good, you remember
me... Saves some time.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL]
You've come to avenge
your piss-ant lil' clubhouse
pals from back when?
What are you gonna do, right?
Eden's got you by the balls...
[OGAMI] Code One!
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL] Ah.
Rounded up some new ones, I see.
How 'bout this
time you spare 'em
and all of you hop
over to my side?
[HACHIOJI] Do what?
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL]
Let me break this down for ya:
Work for Eden and what's
there to show for it...?
Join me and it's a
whole other ball game.
Money. Freedom.
Hell, take out bad guys if
you want. It's up to you.
You're a moron... Heh.
Huh?
Dude, you hearin' yourself...?
Only reason you're offering
is 'cause your back's
against the wall...
We answer to something
larger than ourselves.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL] Really?
[TOKI] Yeah... It's called
having a purpose in life.
[HITOMI] That purpose is to
combat evil. Vermin like you...
Understand something right
here and now, my friend...
If we wanted to use the powers
given to us for personal gain...
There's no one who could stop us
from taking over the world...
But... That'd make us no
better than scum like you.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL]
To hell with all of you!
Ha! So... Who's next...?
I'll burn every last one of you!
[HITOMI] You might be
overestimating yourself a bit.
You're a formidable foe...
But... Your time has come.
[ROGUE SUPERNATURAL] Screw you!
What the... My body... I...
[HITOMI] Thanks for
making it easy;
the slightest touch
was all I needed
to transmit the necessary
electrical signals
to your nervous system.
The rest, I'll let you handle.
Maybe take this opportunity
to reevaluate your choices.
Not that it'll do any good.
[TOKI] Man, that was
a job and half, huh?
You okay...?
Is anyone hurt?
Uh... Kinda looks like your
hand's seen better days, chief.
What, this...? Eh, better me
than one of you guys.
[HACHIOJI] Here.
At least wash it off...
It'll get infected.
Ah... Thank you.
[YUKI] Okay, I'm just gonna say
what we're all thinkin'...
It was totally awesome
how you took that guy out.
Hey, whaddya want...?
It's my job.
[YUKI] Well, yeah...
Technically, I guess...
[HITOMI] Technically, it's what
we're all supposed to do...
Which means you're gonna
need to step up your game.
[YUKI] I don't think I
could be that badass.
[HITOMI] I recommend
taking a page from Six...
Where you going?
Something wrong...?
I thought we were done.
Good work, kid...
I'm proud of ya.
[HITOMI] This. Right here.
It's the ultimate team.
I won't ever have to watch
any of them die. Ever.
Rest, my brothers.
We've got it figured out.
[BOY 10F] Bring it on! Come on,
you can run faster than that!
[BOY 10G] Watch me!
[OGAMI] You're laughing.
What's that all about?
[HITOMI] I'm in a good mood.
C'mon, Rei.
Don't you get it?
I hardly ever know
what you're thinking.
I don't see why this
should be any different...
Oh... And would you stop
calling me by my first name?
No one else does.
[HITOMI] Sorry, kid:
till you can best me,
you'll just have to deal
with it. Sucks to be you.
[HITOMI] What am I looking at?
[HEIKE] I have to confess I
didn't think the prognosis
would be so grim...
It appears as though
a widening gap
between Lost periods
deprives us of the time
needed to recharge,
resulting ultimately in...
well, what we've seen.
We're kept in the dark, but...
this happens enough for
Eden to have a name for it.
What is "Code: End"?
[HEIKE] The higher ups are
nothing if not succinct.
And they... They've
known this was a risk
virtually from the beginning?
Seems so, yes.
So, all this time...
they lied...
[HITOMI] This can't be real...
I've worked too goddamn
hard for this to be real.
The whole point was
to save lives... But...
Whatever I do...
We die like animals
in service to people who
think we're expendable!
My team... My friends...
I can't let them do this!
[OGAMI] Hey. Why all the
cloak and dagger stuff?
What's going on?
This doesn't
seem like you.
[HITOMI] They'll finish it soon.
[OGAMI] What, the Sky Tower?
Sure, I guess.
[HITOMI] Imagine all the people
who'll look out from the top
once they open it to tourists.
Families. Couples.
[OGAMI] Yeah.
Okay, so while I'm
trying to imagine that...
You'll wanna take a look
at these, I think...
The specs about tomorrow's job.
Always on the clock, huh?
[HITOMI] Ogami... what if...
[OGAMI] What?
What if we...
disappeared?
[HITOMI] Forget it.
Talking out of my ass.
[HITOMI] Please... Like
he could extricate himself...
Code Breakers are
his whole world...
Even if he did run,
Eden would find him...
Besides, what am I supposed to
do? Tell him about Code End?
That'd be cruel--like handing
him a death sentence.
[HITOMI] Maybe the
illusion of a normal life
is the best it'll get.
It's not like they'll
get a better offer.
As far as the world's concerned,
they're less than ghosts.
Bad enough they die unsung;
no reason they have
to live in fear.
[HITOMI] This isn't
a choice for them;
but it is for the
people in charge.
Sorry to be all weird...
Thanks for coming.
[OGAMI] And I came because...?
Have to be prepared...
I had to know
you were ready for tomorrow.
'Kay...
[HITOMI] I am Code One.
The pack leader. The Ace.
I have to do it.
They need me.
[OGAMI] Talk to me.
[KANDA] Sir!
It's Hitomi...
I don't even know
how to say this--
[OGAMI] What's wrong?
[KANDA] Last night... Hitomi
attacked the Prime Minister...
He killed the entire
security detail and fled...
No one knows where he is.
[ADVISOR 1A] This is
most unfortunate...
His Excellency is
uninjured, at least...
But the situation is
a very grave one...
Very grave indeed...
Code Breaker One...
is hereby divested
of the title, and his
commission is rescinded...
Men... Hitomi is now
considered an extreme threat.
[OGAMI] You lied
to me, you bastard...
You promised you'd
be there for us.
How could you do this?
[SAKURA] Why does he
hate the Prime Minister...?
It doesn't make any sense...
They were on the same side...
What really happened...?
I have to know.
Alrighty, folks... Let's get
this coming out party under way!
Biting the hand that feeds
him... How very like him.
[HITOMI] Hello, citizens of
Japan. Thanks for tuning in.
As you can probably surmise
from the countdown
there on the big screen,
your illustrious Prime Minster
has less than an hour to live.
Matter of fact, same goes
for a sizable chunk of you.
Soon, fifty thousand people
will be under smoldering rubble.
There is nowhere
you can run.
Hitomi!
[SAKURA] Disaster strikes.
Panic spreads. Death draws near.
Next time, "Code: Breaker"
episode 11, "50,000 Hostages."
A showdown of epic
proportions is about to unfold.