[NYANMARU]
Stop right there, crook!
Never fear,
for Nyanmaru's here!
And I'll protect you!
Nyanmaru.
♪
♪ [YUKI] Nyan-Nyan-Nyanmaru,
everybody's cat... ♪
He's not in
mortal danger, is he?
He'll be fine.
♪ No kitty's too
fat or furry... ♪
♪ He'll protect
them in a hurry... ♪
[KANDA] If a Code Breaker over
uses their special ability...
The power temporarily
leaves them...
and their bodies get
thrown out of whack.
[SAKURA] So he's 'Lost.'
He's been pushing
it to the limit
and using his power
so much lately I knew
it was only a matter of
time before this happened.
♪ ...to fight evil
from the moment of... ♪
No need to fret...
It'll take him a
little while to recover,
but trust me, he'll be
better before you know it.
What a relief...! Great...
That's wonderful news!
I have to say, with Heike's
big talk of destiny and fate,
I wasn't too sure that he
could come back from this.
I can't tell you
what a relief it is
to know the situation
isn't as bleak as I thought.
I can't believe
you're a Code Breaker...!
I don't think I ever
would've guessed that,
not in a million years...
And... I certainly never thought
you'd be a part of
their agency, too...
Oh... and I nearly forgot...
So is Yuki.
[KANDA] I work as
an agent of Eden...
My job is simple:
to provide Code
Breakers with support.
[SAKURA] Support?
[HEIKE] Ogami is
Code Number Six.
Because he was the last to join,
that makes him the
lowest ranking member.
As such...
He has a support staff agent
assigned to him exclusively.
That makes sense...
Although... It's strange.
I'm so sorry,
its just I never would have
figured him to be the
lowest ranking one.
Yuki here is
Code Breaker Number Three...
He uses special
sonic abilities...
And although he's
not with us today,
Toki is Code Number Four.
I'm afraid that
putting a Nyanmaru sticker
on Ogami isn't going to
help him recover any faster.
So what...?
I like Nyanmaru.
[YUKI] Being Lost is
no fun, Number Six...
I hope you're back
to your old self soon.
I'm sure
you've noticed,
he's a character.
Uh... Yeah...
I suppose every
person expresses grief
in their own way,
don't they...?
Oh... That's right,
I almost forgot to ask,
what number are
you, Heike?
[HEIKE] I am
Code Breaker Number Two.
I perform all the standard
duties, but in addition,
I judge the others and
help them to improve.
[HEIKE] Points off for
sloppiness of form, Ogami.
I see... So there
are more, then...
There have to be a Number One
and Number Five that
I haven't met yet, right?
Actually no,
as a matter of fact,
you have met Code Number Five.
Wait...
Do you mean the
woman on the bike?
[SAKURA] I thought so...!
So who is Number One?
Well... Anyway...
If we're attacked again,
we'll be in big trouble...
We should probably relocate him
to be on the safe side.
Oh, right...
But where to?
You're not saying it,
but I know you think
he's behind this,
who else could it be?
All I know is,
whoever it is,
they have to know about
Ogami's apartment...
We can't take him there,
it won't be safe.
[SAKURA] Well, there's
always my place...
[BOTH]
No!
[KANDA] That's out
of the question!
Listen...
I know you're in charge here,
but you have to
trust me on this.
My house is as safe
as it's gonna get.
[MEN]
Welcome home, Miss Sakura!
We're at your service!
Thank you...
It's good to see all of you!
[KANDA] The Kizakura
clan is the strongest
and most preeminent 'good fella'
organization in all of Japan.
The only daughter
of the clan's chief,
Gotoku Sakarukoji...
...is none other than our
darling little Sakura.
Oh, wow.
[DAISUKE]
Miss Sakura...
Tell me, who are
your guests?
Oh...
They're some friends
of mine from school,
I told them they'd
be welcome here,
so I hope you
guys don't mind.
We're friends?
Are you boys being nice
to my darling little girl?!
[MEN] Yes, ma'am!
And I hope you're being
nice to our guests too!
[MEN] Yes, sir!
Oh my goodness,
what happened to him?
He'll be all right...
He was brave and he fought
for our whole school,
but he got hurt.
He needs rest,
so I'd like to look after him
here till he's recovered.
Well a friend of yours
is a friend of ours...
So of course...
We'll just put him
up in the guest room.
Thanks so much,
you guys...
You're the best!
[NYANMARU] A true hero
fights for those in need...
Don't you see?
Nyanmaru?
[MOTHER YUKI] By the way...!
A friend of yours came
by to see you just now!
[SAKURA] What?
[MOTHER YUKI] I asked him
to wait for you in here.
[MOTHER YUKI] Guess what?!
Sakura is home...!
Where'd he go?
[SAKURA] Mother,
what friend...?
What was his name?
[MOTHER YUKI] Let's see now,
I believe he said it was Toki.
[TOKI] What's the
hell's going on?
Yuki and Heike are here too?
You idiot...! Stop!
If you don't let go of
me right now I swear--!
Look, I found
Number Four.
[SAKURA] Is that... Toki?
How come he looks so mini?
I'm afraid
he's gone Lost.
Oh... So it
makes him shrink?
Reactions to being Lost
vary from person to person...
In the case of Toki,
unfortunately,
he reverts to being a small boy.
[MOTHER YUKI] What in
the name of everything holy
are you people talking about?
[SAKURA stammers]
Oh...!
We're just kidding around;
a little inside joke between
school chums, you know.
Don't worry about it.
[MOTHER YUKI hmmms]
[MOTHER YUKI] Okay...
I'll leave you alone, then.
[SAKURA sighs]
[SAKURA gasps]
[MOTHER YUKI] I forgot,
dinner'll be served
in the banquet hall
in just a bit.
[SAKURA] Uh...
That sounds perfect...
Thank you!
[yawn]
So...
I got word from Eden
that Ogami was Lost...
And the moment I heard
I came running here
so I could give
him some back up.
[HEIKE] That's very brave,
and very stupid considering
you're Lost, too...
So, has Eden been made
aware of your condition...?
Have you told them yet?
Well...
From the look
on your face,
it's clear you've decided
not to tell them, you fool!
Hey!
Who said you could put
stickers on me, dumbass?!
[YUKI] Don't be a jerk.
It'll help you get better.
[TOKI] What's wrong with you?!
You two sure do seem
to get along well.
[MOTHER YUKI] So...
I hope you brought
your appetites,
because boy do we have
a feast prepared tonight!
[KIZAKURA] Let's eat...!
We thank you for this food!
[laughter and chatting]
Are you all right...?
Is something the matter?
No... I'm fine.
Forgive me for asking,
but why did you become
a Code Breaker?
I see...
That's what you're
wondering about.
Tell me, what is
Ogami's take on it?
He thinks he has
to wipe out evil.
Is that a fact?
Burn to nothing.
But I know it's not
good for him...
Not at all.
Hey, Sakura...!
Do you want a drink?
[SAKURA] Toki,
what are you doing?
Underage drinking
is illegal!
S'not booze, dork face...
Ugh... Gimme a break!
[SAKURA] You're
clearly drunk!
Yeah...
It happens when I get Lost...
I just can't hold my juice.
[SAKURA]
Wait, juice?
Toki...
You lose points
for this, big time.
Oh yeah?
I'm not scared of you...!
And you know why?
'Cause you don't
have any eyebrows!
Seriously, who could
be scared of that?!
[HEIKE] Look...
If you insist on acting
like a wayward infant
I'm going to discipline
you like a wayward infant.
[TOKI] Unless you
want to get peed on,
back the hell off!
[YUKI] Thanks for
bringing Number Six here,
it was really nice of you.
No, it's my
pleasure, really...
After everything
he's done
for my classmates and me
it's the least I can do...
Plus...
These stubborn idiots
need help now more than ever...
I couldn't turn my back on them.
[NYANMARU] The others are
too worn out to fight...!
So Nyanmaru will fight for them!
Nyanmaru?
[TOKI screams]
Let go, doo-doo face!
I mean it, get me down
from here right this minute!
Oh damn it, I think
I just peed my pants, again!
[KANDA] I can't
thank you enough
for letting
everyone stay here...
You saved the day.
Please...
I just wish there
was more I could do...
I'm happy that
I could help.
Nyanmaru...
I will protect you.
[HEIKE] What a haunting sky...
Not ideal for my reading.
[TOKI] Out here keeping
everyone safe, are we?
[HEIKE] Yes well,
it's a dirty job
but somebody has to do it.
[TOKI scoffs]
Toki...
I've spent time
thinking about it...
And I believe I know
what they were up to today.
From my vantage point,
it seemed clear they were
split into two groups.
One team that
focused on Ogami...
And another team that
went after Miss Sakurakoji.
Did you ever stop
to wonder why
Hitomi would set up an
operation like that?
[TOKI] Are you suggesting
Sakura was the target?
The girl is a rarebreed,
is she not...?
It doesn't seem surprising
to me that he'd show
interest in her... But.
If his primary objective
was to kidnap her,
it seems to me there
are far easier ways
to go about it...
I can't fathom why he would try
to take her with Ogami
standing right by her side...
It just doesn't make sense
for him to divide
his forces like that...
Why not hold off and
grab her when she's alone?
Yeah...
The only good
thing that came of it
is that idiot was
forced to go Lost.
[HEIKE] You're absolutely
right... That's true.
[HEIKE] Could there have been
another motive I'm not seeing?
Where am I?
[KANDA] I'm glad
to see you awake.
[OGAMI] Kanda...
Is this Sakura's house?
[KANDA] Yes...
It is.
[KANDA] I am so sorry, sir...
If there was anything
I could've done
to stop those men
from attacking you...
Please don't apologize...
It's my fault,
I was careless.
[KANDA] Sir...
Those men, they
were definitely
the agents that
went missing on us...
And more than that...
Yeah...
I know, they were controlled
by special powers.
You really
think it's him?
No question...
We're dealing with the
former Code Breaker...
Code Number One... Hitomi.
[phone rings]
What's up?
[MAN] Code Number Five...
Head to Sakura Sakurakoji's
house immediately.
Why...? I don't understand,
I thought Yuki and
Toki were already there?
[MAN] Toki is Lost
and Number Three
can't manage on
his own... Acknowledge.
Copy that.
[HACHIOJI] What the
hell are those guys doing?
Either I missed a
meeting or something's up.
[GOTOKU]
Beautiful blade, isn't it?
[GOTOKU] You certainly look like
you're feeling better now...
I'm glad to see it.
Your interest in
this isn't casual, is it?
[GOTOKU] My guess...
You've seen your share of death.
It's there in your eyes...
Your dark past
and the bad things
you've witnessed.
You've lost the anxiety
and dread that comes
from taking another
person's life...
And I'm guessing
you've also lost sight
of what it means to be alive.
[GOTOKU] Sakura's the
light of my life...
If anything were
to happen to her...
It'd come at a great
cost... You understand?
[GOTOKU] My men!
It's you!
No! Sakura!
I'll protect you, Nyanmaru!
Be more careful please...
You wouldn't wanna hurt
the young lady,
now would you...?
Also...
Please tell me that's
not the best you can do.
You shut up!
Oh well...
Night night, kitty cat
Yuki!
[HITOMI] You walked
right into going Lost...
As your mentor, I must say,
I'm very disappointed.
Ogami!
[KANDA] Stop...! Right now...
Let her go...! I mean it!
Do you seriously
think you can stop me?
Hitomi... Please.
[HITOMI] I'm impressed.
Your swordsmanship's
gotten much stronger...
As your teacher,
I feel proud... But...
You're still
no match for me...
so back off... If you obey...?
Then you'll live.
[HEIKE] You wanna dance?
Wow... Well, well...
The gang's back together again.
What do you know about that,
it's almost like old times!
Hey...! You're still
recovering, man...
Keep back.
No way, this kill
is all mine.
Why are you
doing this, Hitomi?
What do you hope to gain?
Just revenge.
That's all.
Revenge against Eden.
[OGAMI] You've changed...
You hated the idea of revenge...
You called it a
tool of darkness.
[SAKURA] Are he
and Ogami friends?
[OGAMI] But since you
chose the path of evil...
I have no choice but this!
[HITOMI] It's sad to see
you've turned into
a dog for Eden...
Such a tragedy.
[OGAMI] It's not about Eden!
I'm doing this for myself
and for no other reason!
[HITOMI] Dogs like you don't get
to make their own choices!
Oh no!
Now it's my turn, asshole!
[TOKI] What, you're not
gonna take your hands
out of your pockets, douche?!
I'll take them out
when I have a good reason to.
Ah.
Ogami.
[HITOMI] How fun...
I take it your Lost
period is up then.
Look...
I don't know what kinda grudge
you've got against Eden
and I don't care...
But whatever it is you're
up to, I won't let it happen.
You haven't
changed a bit...
You and your extremes...
So silly.
[OGAMI] An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
And evil for evil!
[HITOMI] Nice try...
But your powers
just don't measure up.
[SAKURA] Ogami...! Toki!
Now, then.
[HITOMI] Surely you don't think
you can actually beat me.
Well, I suppose there's
only one way to find out.
[footsteps]
[HEIKE] Don't you move...
This is over, Code Number One...
Now...
There's no way
we're gonna let you
walk away with the girl.
[HITOMI] Ah, there's a
name that takes me back...
Code Number One.
There's a reason
I held that rank.
I think it's about time
I showed you why.
[HACHIOJI] Whoa...
When did he get that strong?!
Those who
stand against me...
Meet death.
Bye, bye now...
Code Breakers.
[SAKURA] He can't!
[SAKURA] No!
I won't let you!
Sakura, no!
Oh, my darling.
[SAKURA screams]
What happened?
[HITOMI]
Excellent job, young lady!
Better than I hoped.
Oh, Sakura.
[SAKURA] What...?!
I don't even know what
you're talking about...!
Why are you doing this...?!
Uh...! Hey...!
[OGAMI] How can you
be so reckless...?
Please just stay back!
[HITOMI] Fortunately
for you, I'm running late...
We'll pick up where we
left off another time...
It's been fun, my friends.
[OGAMI] We're not done!
[HITOMI] Yes we are, actually;
I've already gotten
what I need from you today.
[HITOMI] See my success
was pretty much guaranteed
the moment you
all convened here...
In the same place,
at the same time.
[HEIKE] What are
you talking about...?
Oh no!
[MAN] Code Number Two!
The Prime Minister
has been kidnapped
by someone
with special abilities.
I'm in pursuit of the culprit.
But I'm going to
need back up, ASAP!
[HITOMI] Until next time...
Night, night. Code Breakers.
Damn him!
He took the Prime Minister?
[OGAMI] Hitomi!
[HEIKE] Kidnapping
the Prime Minister...
There's no coming
back from that...
Code Number One.
♪
[YUKI] This is not good...
I can't believe I let
Number One make me go Lost.
Well I guess the
cat's out of the bag.
[OGAMI] Next time...
Code Breaker, Episode eight...
King and soldier...
Child and house...
I don't care who you are...
If you choose
the path of evil...
Friend or not...
It's my job to destroy you.