♪
[SAKURA] He took
the Prime Minister!
Damn it...
We walked right
into Hitomi's trap.
He got us all
in the same place...
And then used that opening
to move on the Prime Minister.
This attack was
carefully planned...
Even if we tried to intervene
now we'd be too late.
No need to
save him...
The dude can
manage on his own.
Of course we're
gonna rescue him!
The Prime Minister
is your father, Toki...
You might show a little
bit of concern over this.
That's his Dad?
All the more reason
to go after him, right?
You guys do
whatever you want.
Hold on,
where're you going?
[TOKI] On a date...
Later on, suckers!
A date...?
You mean in the
middle of the night?
Seriously, what in the
world can he be thinking?
Everyone expresses
grief in their own
unique way and this
is his, apparently...
But don't you worry...
Give him time,
he'll be all right.
[HEIKE] What we
need to be focused on
at the moment is what our
next move is going to be.
[HACHIOJI]
Do you mean about Hitomi?
Yes, indeed.
[YUKI] He's always
been stand-offish,
never did share
anything with any of us.
Did that
cat just talk?!
Ah...
Well, now you
know what happens
to Yuki when
he goes Lost.
[SAKURA] You're
kidding me!
So that's what happens to you
Yuki, you turn into a kitty cat?
[YUKI] Yep. 'fraid so.
It's a real pain.
Seems we all learned
something new today...
You can withstand
a powerful attack
from Hitomi and be
none the worse for wear.
Uh... Yeah...
That was pretty nifty, huh?
More than nifty.
You idiot...
Why in the hell did you expose
yourself to him like that?
Hey... Don't
call me an idiot!
You're lucky the blast
didn't kill you, you know.
I'm sorry, okay...?!
I did it 'cause I didn't want
anybody else to get hurt.
You're such
a child sometimes...
This isn't a fairy tale.
I won't allow it!
I don't care
if it's childish...
I won't let anyone die.
Hang in there,
boys, you'll be alright.
[KIZAKURA 1] Don't
you worry, Boss!
It'll take a hell of
a lot more than this
to take down the Kizakura!
That's right,
we're gonna be fine!
Damn skippy!
Thank you, men.
I gotta admit,
that long haired kid...
I don't know what kinda
technique he was using...
But it sure was crazy effective.
[HEIKE] Hitomi's
special ability allows him
to use electric shockwaves...
He utilized it to
create that corpse army
that ambushed our school.
Apply a little
voltage, and voila:
dance of the marionettes.
His power sets him apart
even among Code Breakers;
hence his rank.
Three years ago,
he dropped off
the face of the earth,
only to resurface recently.
Hold on, the
Prime Minister
is his former
superior, isn't he...?
Why would he want
to kidnap him?
For revenge.
He said himself
that that's his goal...
Question is,
revenge for what?
[HEIKE] Supposing
Hitomi does in fact
hold some grudge against
the Prime Minister.
If he wanted to
exact that revenge
he would kill him,
not kidnap him...
So why go to all the trouble?
[HACHIOJI] There's
something else he wants.
[HEIKE] Exactly.
Yes, but what could it be...?
For him to go this far,
it must be very important.
I have no idea...
Whatever his end
game might be,
this is just the beginning,
and knowing him,
he'll make his
next move quickly,
so we'd better figure
something out soon.
If we don't, we're guaranteed
the results will
be catastrophic.
[HACHIOJI] Damn it!
I can't believe the
son of a bitch turned on us!
This must
be so difficult.
[YUKI] Man...
The old him
would never have done
something like this...
Whatever happened, the
Hitomi we knew is gone.
I'm sorry...
I can see you all
cared about him.
He was our leader...
The best and
brightest of us all...
Respected and admired
by the whole group.
[OGAMI] Well, I don't
care who he was.
It's my duty to
destroy evil,
no matter what shape it takes...
It doesn't matter
if he was my friend,
I'll do what has to be done!
Nenene!
Nobody is here today.
Sissy.
I'm glad you're safe.
[NENENE]
Don't worry, I'm fine... Toki.
You came because you were
worried about me...
That's very thoughtful.
[TOKI] No way...?
You know who I am?
Wait, what were we saying...?
I'm sorry, who are you,
and what are you doing here?
[NENENE] I have to get going.
I'm supposed to go
shopping with my Dad today!
It's gonna be lots of fun!
I promise you I will
make everything better.
[NENENE] Uh, what
are you talking about?
I'm just
thinking out loud.
I don't care
if it's childish...
I won't let anyone die.
[OGAMI] Why is she so stubborn?
[MOTHER YUKI] Do you
suppose it could be fate?
[GOTOKU] Yes...
I'm afraid it's turning
out just as we feared.
But still-
Don't worry, my dear...
No matter what happens,
Sakura will always be
our little girl, I promise.
[footsteps]
[KIZAKURA 5] Boss...!
The doctor just got here!
[GOTOKU] Well...!
It's about time...
Let's put him to work, then.
What is that?
[SAKURA] Dad!
It's the doctor...
He's uh-Ogami...?
What are you doing in here?
Oh...
You got a hold of our
old photo albums, huh...?
I'd forgotten about these.
[OGAMI] What are you doing here?
It's finger lacing.
It's not
finger hooking?
Kind of, only it's a bit
more intimate I guess...
I can't believe you've
never heard of it before.
You do this, and by
dovetailing your fingers,
you make a shape that's
supposed to reflect
your sense of kinship and
respect for each other.
I learned it
when I was little...
I was crazy about it,
used to do it with everyone--
my dad, mom, the guys;
basically everyone I saw...
You could say it's
a family tradition.
[OGAMI] I see...
I can tell you care for
your family a great deal...
And your parents...
I bet they're
the same way too.
No baby pictures...
That's a bit on the weird
side, don't you think...?
Too rambunctious, I bet...
Your folks couldn't get you
to stay still could they?
Oh...
No, I was adopted...
So the pictures start
after my parents found me.
[GOTOKU] Ogami?
Do you have a minute?
To talk?
[GOTOKU] We raised Sakura...
But she's not our
biological daughter.
[GOTOKU] Years ago...
We found her lying
on our doorstep...
It was a pitiful sight; there
was blood all over her.
[OGAMI] Blood?
[GOTOKU] That's right...
Luckily though, she wasn't hurt.
Though from the amount
of blood splattered
everywhere you wouldn't have
thought so at first glance.
She endured
something that night...
It was clear the
poor child experienced
something unspeakably bad...
I think it shaped who she is...
It was the trigger that
compelled Sakura
to fear the death of others
as strongly as she does.
[GOTOKU] We've been dreading
this day since the beginning.
We knew the time would come
when Sakura would
face tragedy again...
And now it's here...
the poor thing...
We only wanted
to make her happy...
But I suppose that kind of
life isn't possible for her.
The truth is that I
don't understand
the kind of powers you people
have and I don't care to...
The only thing I care
about is Sakura...
Promise me you
will do everything
in your power to keep
her safe...! Please!
[YUKI] Something on
your mind, Number Five?
Ah, you know, I was
just thinking about Hitomi.
[YUKI] Right, you two were
always pretty close, huh?
We all were.
[YUKI] He always left me alone
and told me to do
whatever I wanted.
[HACHIOJI]
Don't you think that's
because he trusted
your judgment, Yuki?
[YUKI] I don't know. Maybe.
With him you
never knew...
He kept things to
himself so much...
He was hard to read.
[YUKI] Yeah,
that's for sure...
Did he ever, like,
open up to you?
Yeah, once...
When I was much younger...
I lost my family in an accident.
Being the only
member of my line
to survive was
pretty hard on me...
I went through a
bit of a wild stage...
When I met Hitomi he said
something to me
I'll never forget.
[YUKI] Oh yeah?
"If you've got the
time to run wild,
then you should do
something else... Sleep."
[YUKI] Why sleep?
Apparently he'd been
working himself
so hard that he hadn't had a
chance to rest in a while...
So when he heard my behavior
was cutting into my sleep...
He just couldn't let it stand.
That sure woke me up...
Hitmoi made me realize I was
letting my grief destroy me.
Yeah, that sounds
like oh one, all right.
[YUKI] It's almost hard to
believe how much he's changed.
[HACHIOJI] Yeah, I know.
Uh-oh... I didn't mean
to fall asleep.
[SAKURA] I hate that
I've caused so much trouble.
My house is as safe
as it's gonna get.
[SAKURA] I'm such an idiot...!
There had to be a
better way than this!
Please stop it...
You're just killing
your brain cells.
Eavesdropping?
You're supposed
to be this 'rarebreed',
it's disappointing to see
you bent out of shape
like a normal person.
Well... I am a
normal person.
It's ridiculous...
You feeling guilty
over this mess...
The whole thing started
after I went Lost...
It's bad enough I feel
like an idiot because of it.
But now I have to
sit back and watch you
beat yourself up
over nothing, too?
Please...
Just mind your own business.
If you let yourself
get discouraged by this...
You're gonna make all the
people who believe in you
feel like they've been
backing the wrong horse.
[KIZAKURA 1] Kid knows
what he's talking about;
you should listen to him.
Yeah, don't worry.
We may look rough right now but
we've been through a lot worse!
Don't ever feel guilty
for bringing your
friends home...
Especially when they're
being chased by bad guys;
that's what we're here for!
You guys...
If that bastard
ever shows up here again,
he'll regret it!
Forgive us...
We're the ones who should
be apologizing, Sakura,
we failed to protect you when
you needed our help the most.
We're just relieved things
didn't turn out worse for you.
[SAKURA] Ugh!
I can't let them
see how upset I am.
It'll just make
them worry about me!
Guys...!
I'm just mad that I let
him get the better of me...!
He's just a
scrawny little nobody
and somehow he managed
to beat me anyway...!
Daisuke...! We need to
get back to our training!
Sounds good to me!
[YUKI] We used to be
like that once, remember?
I sure do...
And I remember Hitomi
at the center of it.
[YUKI] Wish we could
all be together...
like we were
in the old days.
Who says that
we won't?
What are you saying, Hachioji,
you haven't given
up on Hitomi yet?
I just can't...
There must be a reason
he's acting like this.
[YUKI] Yeah...
Oh one is behaving
like a completely
different person now...
But he was a good
Breaker once.
I think you're right.
[TOKI] Oh, what
a big load of crap!
Personally,
I couldn't give a damn
why the guy's being such a dick.
[KANDA] There you are.
[TOKI] I'm pissed...
And I'm not gonna
stop till I've decked
that bastard right
upside his face...
If something did
happen to the jackass
maybe a good ole kick
to the head will undo it!
Right now, we've
all got work to do...
I think the best plan
is for us to split up
and search for
the Prime Minister...
Get out there and do
some good Code Breakers!
[YUKI] Yeah!
[SAKURA]
Wow, this place is empty.
[OGAMI] Yeah,
Eden usually takes care
of anything that's
been left behind.
Honestly...
I don't think anything
was left here to begin with.
[phone rings]
What is it, Yuki?
I see...
There's no leads here either...
Yeah, alright. Thanks.
Be honest...
You must have some idea why
he abducted the Prime Minister.
You knew him
better than anyone...
Surely some kind of
motivation comes to mind.
Damn it, Ogami...
It's obvious that the
two of you were close--
[OGAMI] Sorry, but that's
none of your business.
[SAKURA] Ogami!
Where did he go?
Let's go...!
Strike him out!
Step up, batter!
[knock]
[MALE TEACHER] Come in.
[MALE TEACHER] Welcome...
Sit down, Miss Kanda.
[MALE TEACHER]
So you're saying...
the rarebreed's power is
greater than we ever imagined.
I'd like to know why
you didn't inform
me of this sooner...
Miss Sakura being a rarebreed
is something
I should've known about.
We had to take into
account that you used
to work for Hitomi ...
Unfortunately,
we couldn't run the risk
of the info being leaked.
[MALE TEACHER]
Fact is, we weren't sure
who could be trusted...
Our contacts were giving
us bad information.
We were told that Ogami
was attempting to
neutralize Sakura...
But we didn't really feel
the need to intervene...
There's no chance
Ogami could've hurt her...
Since she's a
rarebreed we backed off
and let everything
play itself out.
[KANDA] You suspected me, that's
what you're saying, isn't it?
Yes, part of our mandate was
to supervise your
activities, Kanda...
To ensure you weren't
communicating with Hitomi.
We thought he might try
to make contact with
you at some point...
apparently that
was a miscalculation.
[KANDA] So we're clear...
I'm Rei Ogami's agent
and that's all I am...
I am not involved with Hitomi!
Then you shouldn't have
any problem getting rid of him.
Trust me...
When we find him,
he'll be dealt with.
[HEIKE] There are two
versions of the world...
The Prime Minister's
and Hitomi's.
So that's it then.
[HEIKE] I think
I understand... Ace.
[HEIKE] Have you come up
with any promising
leads on Hitmoi?
[HACHIOJI] It's no use.
I don't think
we'll find anything.
[HEIKE] Looks like
killing the police chief
and that yakuza bunch is working
against us now, doesn't it?
[HACHIOJI] Yeah, maybe so...
Are you investigating at
the Prime Minister's house?
Yes, of course I am.
Heike.
All things considered,
you were pretty negligent,
don't you think?
[HEIKE] How do you mean?
[HACHIOJI] You had
to know that by getting
all the Code Breakers
together in one place,
you'd be leaving the area around
the Prime Minister shorthanded.
[HEIKE] Well, I wasn't
the one who ordered you
to go there, after all.
[HACHIOJI] I'm not
so sure about that.
But even so, you're definitely
the one who called in Yuki.
If you have something
to say I wish you'd say it.
I'm impressed...
But then again, you always have
been the sharp one, haven't you?
Well, it has been
a pleasure... but...
You bastard!
Well, well.
Looks like
it's finally begun.
What?
Hitomi's made his next move...
The plan's underway.
[YUKI] Oh no! This is bad!
[HEIKE] Truly magnificent.
The shadow special ability.
A dark and all-powerful
guardian angel...
The only one among us who can
defend against so many attacks!
Such a rarity.
What is this,
Heike...?! Tell me!
[HEIKE] But I already did...
Hitomi's master plan
is finally underway...
And with that, dear Hachioji...
I'm overdue in bidding
you a fond farewell.
Stop this!
You may have a
special gift for protection,
my dear, but
nothing in the world
is powerful enough to
deflect my own specialty!
[YUKI] Five!!!
[sirens]
Is that... a fire?
Where are you...?
Like it or not,
I do worry about you.
[SAKURA] What are
you doing here?
[HEIKE] Ogami needs you...
He asked me to help him
track you down, Sakura.
Really? Thank goodness!
He's extremely worried,
now that we know
Hitomi's after you.
Please... I think it'd
be best if you follow me.
[SAKURA] He's really in here?
[HEIKE] Yes, this
is a secret base.
[SAKURA] Oh, wow,
I'm in some kinda secret
Code Breaker hideout...?
Not to nerd-out,
but this is really cool!
Sure is a bit
dark, though...
Are there any lights
we can turn on, maybe?
It's the Prime Minister!
What in the world's
going on here, Heike?!
[HEIKE] I brought the
rarebreed, as promised.
No need to thank me, Ace.
All I ask is that you
hold up your end
of the bargain, as discussed.
Heike, this is crazy!
Tell me you're not dealing
with this maniac...!
What is this?!
Oh, I've decided
the Code Breakers
really aren't right for me...
We call that
shifting loyalties...
Delivering you here was
the price of my admission.
Be a good little hostage
and you wont get hurt...
Do I make myself clear?
[SAKURA] The desperation
of anger... a cold light...
And the darkest of
resolutions laid bare...
Next time, Code
Breaker episode nine...
'Stopped time'...
A blue flame lights
the darkness of betrayal.