It happened on what seemed
like an ordinary day,
on a quiet,
residential street...
Well, I better get going.
'Kay... See ya!
I wanna suck your blood.
At first I
was totally like,
"cut it out, creep!"
That's when the guy
jumped out and grabbed me.
I thought, "Oh crap!
He must be a molester!"
There have been all these
unexplained deaths lately-
maybe it was him.
Then all of a sudden I
was bitten by something.
I didn't even have
time to defend myself.
I guess I must've
passed out after that...
All I know is that
when I woke up,
everything around me had
been completely torn up!
Would you mind showing
us the bite marks, miss?
Luckily for Ms. A,
these were the only
injuries she received.
Unfortunately, these
types of assaults
have been on
the rise lately.
In fact, the city has
seen seven murders
in the last three months.
The victims,
all young women,
were left with puncture
marks on their necks
that look very similar
to those of Ms. A.
This startling information
has fueled a rumor
about the attacker
that has forced
the people of Japan
to ask themselves...
Could these brutal attacks
have been the
work of a vampire?
Would a vampire be
able to go undetected
in modern day Japan?
Is it possible that the
attacks in Suginami
are the work of a creature
that, until now, has thrived
only in novels and movies?!
We'll find out when
the facts are weighed
by the scales
of the goddess.
Our question tonight:
Do vampires really exist?
Let's put it
in the balance!
And the judgment is...
False! Vampires do not exist!
Welcome, everyone, to
the Scales of Astrea...
You know the drill...
Here we weigh the facts
and find the truth!
We break down mysteries and
legends live from our studio!
After the suspicious
attacks in Suginami
we decided that tonight's
debate should be...
Whether or not vampires
really exist...
I can't wait to see
the final judgment!
Well, our first
judgment was false...
But as you know
that could change
over the course of the show.
Okay... How about we check in
with our panel of judges...?
We've got an eclectic
bunch tonight....
That's true...
Our first guest... is a
world-renowned historian...
Professor Isao Ebikawa!
Tell us what you think.
Vampires do not exist...
but... if you
can prove me wrong
then I would certainly
love to meet one of them.
Our next guest is a
famous comedienne...
Her film, "Go Home,
Forty-Something",
is in theaters now...
Ms Hiroe Ubayama.
Hi, everybody...!
I'm thrilled to be here!
So you don't think
they exist either?
I hope not!
They're so scary!
I mean, I can handle
ghosts and goblins,
but the vampires really
scare the crap outta me...
I'm anemic... I need
all the blood I've got.
Our next judge is
a real beauty...
And many of you may
recognize her as Miss July...
Please welcome, Yumi!
This is awesome...!
I totally love vampire
movies and manga and stuff!
So is that why
you voted 'true'?
Dracula and the
other vamps...
They're all just
so freakin' sexy!
Well, I've got a treat for
you vampire manga lovers...!
Sitting next
to you is the...
I know! I love Bloody Waltz!
And I'm so excited to meet
the man who's behind it.
He's a famous
manga artist...
who's best known for his
Bloody Waltz manga series...
Let's hear it for
Nozomu Tamaki!
In my opinion,
they don't exist...
Vampires are fiction...
That's why I write
manga about them.
Aw... man.
Well, we do have
another judge
who voted with you, Yumi...
You got it...! He believes
vampires really do exist.
I'll give you an
eternal kiss...
my love.
The ladies are excited
about our next guest...!
In the new
Bloody Waltz film...
He plays Ryo Hibuse...
the sexy vampire prince.
Give a warm welcome
to Seiichi Hirai.
I'm afraid I have to
disagree with Mr. Tamaki...
Playing a vampire has
lead me to believe
it's possible that
they could exist...
A vampire...
is the embodiment
of darkness.
Oh wow...! He's so hot!
Come and get it, baby!
So far...
The Scales of Astrea
have weighed in 3 to 2...
What'll be the
final verdict?
We've got compelling
evidence for both sides...
and exciting guests
who'll weigh in!
Oh, now I'm intrigued.
You should be...
Today's show is
going to be great!
Well, I can't wait to
see how it turns out.
Be sure to stay with us...
I'm your host for
the evening...
Yukinobu Tokita.
And I'm...
Mr. Tokita's co-host...
My name... is Akane Sasanuma.
All right then...
For the final judgment,
we'll have everyone weigh in;
our panel of judges,
our studio audience,
the viewers at home and even
the people on the street!
Nella's at Shibuya Station.
You there, Nella?
Yes, sir!
Everyone watching
us in Shibuya
is going to have a chance
to cast their vote as well.
Those votes will
then be tallied
and will become part
of our final verdict.
What will the goddess say...?
Do vampires exist,
or are they fiction...?
Let's put it in the balance!
This program is
brought to you by
Lorenzo Chemical Industries:
striving for a
better tomorrow...
And Wolf Pack
Total Security...
Also, the new
"Bloody Waltz" movie,
in theaters now.
I guess it's time to
get the ball rolling...
Let's bring out our first
proposer of the evening!
My name is Nero Tanaka...
Thank you for having me.
I was just wondering...
Would you all
mind telling me
what you know
about vampires?
Ooh, me! They suck blood!
Yes, that's true.
Anyone else?
Me! Me! I've got one!
Um... They are weak against
crosses and garlic!
It's fascinating
that vampires have
such an extensive
list of weaknesses.
There're just so many...
They can't come in contact
with water or sunlight...
They can't cast a shadow
and they don't
have reflections.
It's amazing we find
them frightening at all.
But that vulnerability
is why women love them.
Now tell me Mr. Tamaki...
How do you handle
these flaws?
I don't want my
characters to seem weak,
so I throw most of them out...
I have kept the sunlight turning
them into ash bit, though.
I don't know if
you're aware...
But documented
vampire-related assaults
are happening at an increasing
rate throughout the world...
These attacks have been
happening everywhere lately!
Oh no! Don't tell me that...!
I'm gonna have to start buying
stock in iron pills now!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to
scare anyone...
But while incidents like
the Suginami cases are rare-
they seem to be happening
more frequently now...
We have been seeing more and
more witnesses come forward.
It's probably because
of the bad economy.
You think?
He's right...
There's a theory
that vampires are popular
in bad economic times,
while Frankenstein is
popular in good times.
Huh, but I thought Japan's
economy wasn't hit as hard...
Yeah, we're okay...
But even so... last
year's "dollar crisis"...
sent the global economy
into a tail spin,
and we have yet to work
our way out of it.
When people
feel downtrodden
they start to look outside
the box for anything
that'll make their
lives more exciting.
Change your mind, Yumi?
Well, Professor Ebikawa
is, like, way smart.
For example, this bizarre
Suginami attacks
have caused all this hype in
the media... That means...
What does that have to
do with the economy?
A failing economy tends to
leave people wanting more:
whether it's in their careers,
their home lives,
or what have you.
Vampires offer people
this mysterious, exciting,
and enticing world...
It's the break
from reality
they so desperately need.
I see...
It's so enticing that
some find themselves
at the point of obsession...
The attacks were likely
caused by someone
who's acting out
something they've read
in their favorite manga
or that they saw
in an anime...
They're escaping into
a world of fiction
rather than living in our
world of harsh reality.
They've lost their
minds, completely...
Of course, that's
just my opinion.
I really don't think
it's fair for you
to blame the attacks on
manga and anime, Professor.
I'm not blaming
anime and manga
any more than I would
blame any other form
of popular culture
involving vampires...
Let's be realistic,
even if they did exist...
they simply have
too many weaknesses
to survive in our world.
Well... It looks like our debate
is starting to get heated...
Why don't we hear what the
members of our audience
have to say on
the subject...
Who've you got
there, Akane?
Are you awake,
little girl?
It's pretty late
for you to be up.
You must be sleepy, huh?
I'm just bored 'cause
I don't know much about
pop culture here.
And why is that...?
Are you from
another country?
I'm from Romania.
You're from the
land of vampires...
So, tell me...
How do you feel about them;
do you think they exist?
Would you tell us why?
I'm sorry... but can I ask you
about something first...?
Have you ever met
a vampire before?
I've never met one,
but I'd assume
they're very much like
what you read
about in books.
But I don't understand...
I thought those were
just made-up stories...
You really think those ladies
were attacked by... vampires?
I'm not sure...
Then how can you
say without a doubt
that they don't exist...?
Obviously, you still
have a suspicion
that the attacker could
have been a vampire...
-Am I right?
-Um, well...
She has a point and being
that she's from Romania
she's probably more
knowledgeable on the subject.
But this debate
isn't over yet!
We've got
compelling evidence
that could change your vote!
As mentioned, the young
lady we're calling Ms. A
was the latest victim of
the Suginami attacks...
She claims that when she
regained consciousness
after the attack,
everything had been destroyed.
We scoured the
area for witnesses,
but to no avail...
until we received a
mysterious call...
You know somethin'
about the attacks?
Yes, it was one
of our agents
who stepped in and
saved the girl's life...
Unfortunately, we were unable
to apprehend the suspect.
However, I promise
when we do,
we'll take care
of the matter.
But I don't understand...
why did you get involved?
We were ordered to do
so by the princess...
She's been deeply troubled
by this rogue vampire's
antics for some time now.
So she gave out an
order for his capture.
The "princess"?
Yes, the ruler of
the vampire race.
Part of the
"true blood" lineage
that has existed
for centuries.
And then we were
contacted by a woman
claiming to serve the
ruler of all vampires...!
Sensing our skepticism,
she asked us to meet with
her at a secret location.
Hello and welcome...
to the princess's mansion.
Now let's bring out our
very special guest...
Welcome Ms. Veratos!
This is impossible...
I don't believe it...
That's a great set of titties.
She's definitely
got me beat.
Professor Ebikawa...
It looks like you have
something you'd like to say.
Not really...
I simply find this
very hard to believe...
Servant of the "ruler
of the vampires"...?
I mean... it's laughable.
You may be a
great actress,
but it'll take more
than that to sway me.
I'm sure I'll be able
to convince you all.
I dunno...
Cause I'm not buying it.
I understand that
"seeing is believing"...
So I've brought along
some evidence...
I have no doubt it will sway
your judgment in my favor.
Yes...! Wait until
you see it...!
The lovely Ms. eratos...
is about to
blow your mind!
This significant
piece of evidence
was recovered at the scene of
Ms. A's attack in Suginami...
It's the vampire's arm!
Ms. Veratos...
You said this was
actual evidence
from the scene of the crime?
That's correct...
The severed arm
of the vampire...
who was foolish enough to
attack Ms. A in broad daylight.
Why does it look frozen?
That's because it's been
encased in a special polymer
that will prevent
it from decaying
or breaking down
in direct sunlight.
Made by... our sponsor,
Lorenzo Pharmaceuticals.
Yes, sir... I was told that
the cellular tissue inside
is still alive.
That's so gross!
This is bullshit...
Have you done any
biochemical testing...?
What does the DNA say?
If you expect
me to believe
that this is actually
the arm of a vampire,
then I need to see some
sort of scientific proof.
Let me ask you something,
Professor Ebikawa...
You seem utterly determined
to disprove the
existence of vampires...
-Are you frightened by us?
-Absolutely not!
Good. I'm glad...
There's no reason
to fear us-
we're not going
to harm you...
We're discerning predators-
we don't attack
unless agitated.
Let's say that is the
severed arm of a vampire...
What the hell are you doing
showing it off in public?
If it was real, surely
you'd want to keep it hidden.
That's not
necessarily true.
Did you have some
input, little girl?
Ms. Veratos said one of her
mistress's agents failed
to apprehend and kill
the monster, right?
And we know the arm
is still alive...
What's your point?
It's kind of like that
old Japanese folk tale.
You know, the one where
the ogre loses his arm
and then he comes
back for it later.
The Ogre of Rashomon...?
But I don't get
the connection.
Maybe... the ruler
of the vampires
thought that if the arm was
presented on television...
its owner would come out
of hiding to repossess it...
Get it?!
Well, things are certainly
getting intense here
in the studio...
Let's hear what our viewers in
Shibuya Station have to say.
-Take it away, Nella!
-Right...!
Excuse me, may I
ask you a question?
No, it can't be...
I'm sorry...
Did you want something?
You okay, Nella?
Yeah, I'm good...!
So, uh, do you think it's
possible that vampires exist?
What...? That's a
stupid question...
No, they don't exist.
Sorry to burst your
bubble, little girl,
but there aren't many
believers out there...
So is that it...?
I assume we've reached
our verdict, am I right?
Not just yet...
I won't give up that
easily, Professor...
I can prove
the arm is real
by subjecting it
to direct sunlight.
As soon as the light
hits it, it'll turn...
This is ridiculous!
There's no direct
sunlight in the studio...
You can just drop your
little act, okay...?
It's obvious that you ladies
are actors hired on by the show!
How sad...
I thought you'd
be convinced ...
I swear I've been
completely honest with you
this entire time.
Is that so...?
And you really
expect us to believe
that you work for
the ruler of vampires?
You're a good
actress and all
but I can see
through that lie.
I'm sorry but I don't
believe a word of it...
So I'm changing
my vote right now.
Looks like you've lost
the argument, ladies...
Vampires are nothing
more than fiction...
They simply do not exist...
They're no different than
Santa Claus or the Tooth Fairy.
I don't blame you for
not believing me...
We've remained
secretive...
For centuries, we've
hidden in the background
of mankind's history.
Over the years, we've purposely
leaked false information
about our race...
hoping to further
fictionalize our existence.
Meanwhile, we've been
working behind the scenes;
manipulating your wars,
your economies
and even your religions.
If that's true...
then why would you reveal
yourselves here...?
I'd think you'd want a better
outlet than a crappy TV show.
Oh, it wasn't our plan
to reveal ourselves
to you at this time...
That is, until this renegade
vampire went on a rampage.
We knew we had to stop
him at any cost...
Even if it meant revealing
ourselves to you.
The royal family forbids
that vampires kill recklessly
or feed upon the innocent.
Only a lowlife would
disobey that order
and be so shamefully
indiscreet about it.
So you have your
own society,
including a ruling family?
That's correct...
Those of royal blood
are our leaders...
and the three clans
and their bloodlines
follow closely behind.
Blood relation
grows thinner
as you go farther
down the bloodline...
As a result,
lower-ranking vampires
are required to obey
the higher-ranked.
That is the law
of the vampire.
It's what holds our
society together.
We are attempting to lure
out the lowest of the low...
One I hesitate to
call a true vampire...
He's a low-ranking traitor
who obviously has no
pride in his race.
Despicable, don't
you think...?
Mr. Movie Vampire?
Well, I, uh...
Surely you have
an opinion...?
The owner of this arm
must be a lowlife...
to kill against order.
Shut up, you bitch...!
I've heard...
enough from you!
May I ask you a question,
Mr. Manga Artist?
On which hand does the
character of Ryo Hibuse
wear a glove
in your manga?
On his left hand,
of cour...
Fine! It's me...!
I am the noble king
of the night!
I refuse to obey...!
I make my own rules!
I was hoping we'd
be reunited...
I've missed you.
You're a vampire?
What?!
Let me give you
an eternal kiss...
my love.
She's so delicious!
No... you've gotta
be kidding...
Vampires really do exist?!
How dare you call
me a lowlife...!
Die!
Nelly! Nero!
Beowulfs!
Damn you all!
What the hell?!
Why are you still filming?!
We can't miss this!
It's ratings gold...!
Go after him with
portable camera #4!
Yukinobu, go with him!
You, up there!
After him!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Stop this broadcast
immediately!
-Don't worry about them, Vera.
-But Princess...
The situation has escalated
beyond what we expected.
We'll simply
accelerate our plans.
Are you sure?
-Where's the portable camera?
-On the roof, sir!
Get us connected!
We're coming to you live from
the roof of the TVC building!
This is unbelievable!
Vampires really do exist!
They're right here
in front of us!
The agent I sent failed
to fulfill his duty...
You were to be killed
for your disobedience...
This time... I will do it.
Not just yet, Wolf.
Princess!
I will handle the traitor.
-Is that understood?
-Yes, ma'am.
You can tell me what's
happened to Akira afterwards.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, I knew the prospect of
appearing on a television show
would lure you
out of hiding...
However, I didn't expect
you to be quite so bold.
It seems this world is
full of surprises...
Wouldn't you agree
with me...?
You scum.
I find your true
form hideous...
I'm not surprised;
our true forms are but a
reflection of our hearts.
So this is the embodiment
of what a black heart
and an arrogant ego
looks like...
How unfortunate.
Shut up!
What in the hell...
How were you
able to stop me?!
My name is Mina Tepes.
Blood descendant
of Vlad Tepes,
known as Vlad the Impaler.
I am the ruler of
the vampire race.
You have brought
shame to our people...
For that you must die.
I beg you...
spare me...
please!
I have a message for
all of you humans...
Remember what
you've seen today...
This is the power
of the vampire race.
Excuse me, miss...
Are you really the
ruler of the vampires?
You dare to doubt me...?
Oh, dear...
Must I... suck your blood?
Our bloodlines are
tied to the darkness...
For centuries we
have hidden...
in the dark of night, in the
shadows of human history.
That is... until
today, anyway.
W-why reveal yourself now?
That bund over there...
Tokyo Landfill #0...
That place... will become
something special.
On that land
I will establish
the kingdom of
the vampire race.
It will be known
hence as...
The vampire bund.
Now then...
come dance with me.
[Music]
Dance with the vampire maids!
Part one!
There he is! The
target's been located!
-Nero, you take the right!
-Okay!
And Nella, you
attack from the left!
Got it!
I saw you on that
"Scales of Astrea" show!
Why're you attacking me?!
Sorry, but we can't
allow you to be here.
What? But why not?
Gotcha! You can do it, Nelly!
One good hit
to the noggin'
and we'll make you
lose your memory!
Yeah, and knock
me unconscious!