Here she comes.
Everybody, run!
Holy crap...!
That chick's insane.
Where'd you come from?
At the request of the
three noble lords...
And as required by the ancient
pact of the royal family...
I have been sent to
perform a purity inquiry.
Hold it right there!
The next inquiry isn't
for another 3 years...
Why are you doing this?
It's okay... Vera...
I had a suspicion...
I knew these scoundrels would
try something like this.
You may proceed.
[Music]
So you're telling
me everything
those guys from
the Three Clans
were saying about being
her future husband...
I'm afraid it's all true.
The princess is obligated
to marry and bear the
child of one of those men
in order to preserve the
royal family's blood line.
Aw, come on, kid...
You didn't seriously think
you were gonna be with
her forever, did you?
I just figured...
Are you kidding me?
It's not gonna happen...
You and the princess come
from two different worlds.
Your time together's
almost up.
Do you know what she's
doing right now?
She's fighting back the
only way she can...
It's probably
happening as we speak.
A purity inquiry!
That's correct...
It's a physical
exam to determine
whether or not her
body is pure enough
to be the royal mother.
How could they do that!
It's an inquiry
in name only.
In reality, it's a
display of power.
What they're doing is
essentially reminding the
princess of who's in charge.
That her body belongs
to the Three Clans.
It's the Stigma spray...
I'll put the top up.
I don't understand...
What reason do they have
for making the princess
go through all this?
Are you sure that
you wanna know?
Yes, tell me!
A long time ago,
there was a civil war
within vampire society.
Rozenmann, Li and
Ivanovic's clans
revolted against
the royal family.
They were able to overthrow
and completely absorb
the other clans
leaving them as the
last 3 standing.
Then they invaded
Tepes territory...
They burned the royal castle
and harassed the people...
Our ruler at the time,
Queen Lucrezia,
was driven from her land
and she died at their hands.
What!
But they knew our race would
face the prospect of extinction
if they ended the
true-blood lineage...
So they let
Princess Mina live
but merely as a
vessel of royal blood.
In exchange for her life,
she would have to undergo a
purity inquiry every decade.
A long time has
passed since then
and the development of the
artificial blood known as Stigma
has freed us
from our fate.
We no longer have to feed
on humans to survive
and as a result we are
living beside them.
The darkness
and the light
which were once so separate
have started to blend...
We dwell in more
of a twilight now.
This intermixing has
caused some confusion,
which has bred radical
groups like Telomere,
which are comprised of
both vampires and humans.
On the bright side,
this new relationship we
have with the human race
has allowed the princess
to build the vampire bund.
However, I worry that she
will forever be constrained
by the Three Clans...
With each inquiry it's
as if they're saying,
You may be our ruler,
but one day your
body will be ours.
They've attempted to
capture her spirit as well
but thankfully
she's fought hard
to keep that from happening.
Princess...
I'm sorry you had to
witness the inquiry...
Forgive me...
But now you know
what it means
to be ruler of
the vampires...
This is horrible!
I can't even imagine what
you're going through!
You have to tell
Akira about...
No...! I don't want
him to see me...
not when I'm so weak...
I can't see him...
not like this...
But I bet he could help get
you out of this situation!
Don't be ridiculous.
Akira could never solve
this problem for me...
You're wrong!
Princess...
He cares more about you...
than anybody else
in this world.
What?
I was just thinking
about the first time
I ever met Akira...
Are you talking about...
seven years... ago?
No, it was ten
years before that.
The first time I met him
was just a few hours
after he was born.
I had just been subjected to
an inquiry back then, too...
I couldn't help but feel
that he was my salvation.
No longer would I feel
so utterly alone...
Akira...
Where are you...
Please hurry back...
I need you to save me...
So let me get
this straight,
whoever kills me wins
the bet. Is that it?
Yeah, and nobody's
gonna come help you.
That's fine by me.
If scheming,
hate and madness
are the chains holding
the princess down...
I'll cut through every
last one of them.
Just be careful
out there, kid.
You're starting to sound
like someone from Telomere.
I don't suppose
you remember
what you saw on that
mission a year ago
I guess that's the last
little piece of your memory
that hasn't made it
back to you quite yet.
How can you be so sure?
Because I don't think you would
be acting like this right now
if you had your memory
back completely.
I might side with
the Three Clans
depending on how you react
when you get that piece back.
But for now,
I'm on your side.
Just take care of
yourself, alright?
So it's safe
for me to assume
you're not going
to be an enemy...
at least for
the time being?
Yeah.
Do me a favor and give a
message to the princess...
Tell her that
I won't die...
and I promise to come
back to her alive...
And please, remind
her to stay strong.
I'll pass that along.
I will come back, Princess!
Okay, here I go...!
One...!
Two...!
Three...!
Four!
Shh!
Shhh...
Seven...!
Eight...!
Nine...!
Ten! You guys ready!
I'm ready!
Hello Princess...
I see things haven't
changed since the old days.
There's no sense
in moping around
feeling sorry
for yourself...
Don't forget there's
someone out there
who's risking his very
life to set you free.
Alphonse, did
you see Akira?
Yes, and he asked me to
deliver a message for him...
He said to tell
you he won't die;
he promises to come
back to you alive...
And he wants you
to stay strong.
But how can he promise that?
I mean, considering
what he's up against!
He's determined to defeat
each of the assassins
that have been
sent after him.
He's out there on his own,
fighting three extremely
skilled hired killers
with nothing but his wits.
Anyone else would
run for their life
but he's determined to fight...
and it's all for
you, Princess.
So he wants me...
to be strong for him.
He wants me to fight...
Then I'll gladly do so!
Yuki, bring Vera to me!
Right!
Thank you, Alphonse.
Don't die on me, kid.
Sir Alphonse.
Go ahead and laugh...
I'm a child's messenger.
Telomere?
Yes, it seems
the organization...
has secretly placed their
pawns in this game as well.
Pardon... Could you
please say that again?
I said that I would
like to participate
in your little game
with a wager of my own...
I bet you gentlemen
that Akira will survive
your assassin's attacks
and come back here alive...
And... if I lose
I shall give you my body,
my future and my entirety.
Well, this is
quite a surprise!
It would appear that
the odds are stacked
against you, Princess.
Yes, but I thought that was
the definition of gambling...
To risk something...
Akira is out there
fighting all alone...
The least I can do is put my
own life on the line as well.
Now when you say you'll
give us your entirety,
is that also including your
true-blood legacy Ivanovic!
Well, Princess...
Are you prepared to
surrender that as well?
The true-blood legacy...
What is he talking about?
Answer me now!
That's exactly what
entirety means...
You don't doubt me, do you?
That's all I need to know.
The stakes to
our little wager
have been raised
exponentially.
Our assassins have
spun a lethal web
to catch that wolf
pup of yours...
Let's see if he can
chew his way out...
I highly doubt it.
Damn it...!
I can't even get
close to her!
Here goes nothin'...
No... why!
What the hell
was I thinking?
How could I be so stupid?
Let's make a deal,
Akira Kaburagi...
I will let you survive if
you'll be honest with me.
One year ago,
you went to the ruins
of the Tepes royal castle
on a secret mission
led by your father,
Wolfgang Regendorf.
It's said that you
discovered a grave secret
about the legacy of the
true-bloods that day.
What did you see
in the castle?
Akira Kaburagi...
Tell me, what did you see!
I swear, you can be
such a numbskull, Akira.
Mei Ren...
But you know... it's one of
the things I love about you.
Vampires are tough, huh?
I was worried about
you for a second there.
Mei Ren, I...
I didn't know you...
One assassin down
and one to go.
May I have your attention
This is an important message
from the Special
Zone Government.
Hostile clan operatives
have infiltrated the bund.
They aim to capture and
kill Akira Kaburagi,
a devoted servant
of Princess Mina's.
They are likely locked
in combat at this moment.
We ask that all
citizens please refrain
from going outside until the
situation has been resolved.
I had no idea that
you're a beast-person...
just like me.
Sorry I never told you...
I'm the sole
survivor of a race
that was destroyed during the
civil war between the clans.
So what's the
matter, Akira...
Why did you allow yourself
to be so badly wounded?
You should have transformed.
I tried to but
I couldn't...
Damn...! I don't
know what's wrong.
It must've been a
real shock to you...
being betrayed by the
princess like that.
What are you talking about?
I can only assume
that's how you felt...
You didn't know
that she was engaged
to someone else, did you?
Shock like that can throw
off your whole system...
You know, as beast-people
we're not able to transform
unless our bodies allow it.
Take this sedative...
But be careful;
it's kinda strong.
But I don't...
I don't feel betrayed
by the princess...!
She's fighting for her life
against the Three Clans...!
Despite the humiliation
they've put her through!
Because that's her duty...
As the ruler of the vampires
she has no choice...
Hey, you gotta stop...
Just give it up...
Don't you remember what I
said the last time we met...
No matter how much
he may desire it...
the butterfly can never
be with the flower...
Can you feel it...
That's my heart
beating in my chest...
Don't you see,
we're different from them.
Because we both have
a beating heart.
Humans... and vampires...
Neither race
would accept us
if they knew what
we really are.
I am the only one who
understands you...
what you're
going through...
And only I can love you.
No!
Akira...
You're coming with me!
Akira!
Where is she?
Oh, Akira...
How could you?
Damn it, why
won't you die!
I don't understand...
Why are you being so hateful to
me all of a sudden...
I've been so
worried about you...
That evil Princess Mina
hasn't gotten to you, has she?
Please Akira...
Tell me what you
saw that day.
What was it that you saw
at the Tepes castle
that made you lose
your memory...
Tell me, and I'll let you do
whatever you want to my body.
I've had enough...
You monster...
How dare you defile Yuki!
I was trying to
be nice to you...
but it's too late...
I'll just make
you tell me!
Why won't you tell me!
It's the least
you could do...
After you toyed with
my heart and dumped me!
I'm done playing games...
You better tell me what
you saw that day?
I...
Akira...
Princess...
You're safe now...
I'm here for you.
And you can tell
me anything.
Okay?
Please, Akira...
Tell me...
I want to know
what you saw...
Don't call my name...
with that voice...
Wha... What is the matter
with you, Akira...!
Don't you recognize
your beloved Mina!
Don't call my name...
with that voice...
and in that form!
Please, Akira...
Don't you die on me...
Though Akira had regained
most of his memory...
There was still one
important piece of the puzzle
that was eluding him.
Neither Princess Mina
nor I had
any way of knowing
what it was...
It was a secret hidden deep
within his subconscious.
We felt completely helpless.
All we could do was
pray for his safety...
and wait for the distant
dawn to end the night.
[Music]
Dance With the
Vampire Maids...!
The Revenge Chapter!
The Princess is finally
going to be ours!
Whoa, spicy!
Oh, I'm sorry is that
not to your liking?
What the hell are you doing!
Just styling your hair
like you asked me to.
You look dirty!
Let's give you a bath!
Stop this nonsense!
How dare you patronize
the Three Clans!
What do you ladies
think you're doing!
Help us, Vera!
Just give them a good
punch to the gut, like this!
Yes, ma'am!
The Tepes household is scary...