Someone...
Please...
Help us fight...
Save my friends...
Hang in there, everyone.
I'm coming!
What are you up to, kid?
It's not safe for you to be
wandering around out here alone.
Who the hell are you?
We've met once before;
it was last year, right after
you lost your memory...
But I guess you don't
remember that, huh?
You were one of
the investigators
looking into my accident...
Yeah, that was a lie.
My name is
Alphonse Medici Borgiani.
I'm a marquis, a protector
of the royal family...
When you get right down to it,
kind of like Dermaille,
only not quite
so old-fashioned.
I specialize in odd
jobs for the Princess.
Basically, anything that
needs to be kept under wraps.
So you're the one!
You kidnapped
that little boy!
That's right...
Though I take it
from your expression,
you're not a fan
of that mission.
Just so you know,
I was the one who
suggested the plan...
So don't blame
the Princess.
But she agreed to it,
though, didn't she...?
She's just as guilty!
The princess is simply
following her duties
as a policymaker.
And besides, it's not
like you're without fault.
First you ditch
the princess
even though it's your
duty to serve her...
And then you go and
abandon your friends
who you should
be protecting.
What do you mean?
Lord Alphonse,
elevator 13 is ready.
We had a team that was
monitoring the church,
but they've been attacked...
The enemy has since
infiltrated the building
and we're uncertain of what's
happened to the students inside.
Come with me and
I'll fill you in.
I know you're a
man of your word,
but you're not gonna make
it back to the church in time
to save them.
Watch me!
Well... Judging by
his stubbornness
I'd say it's obvious
that he's your son, Wolf.
Father?
Listen, Akira.
When you failed your
mission a year ago,
and subsequently
lost your memory,
you became completely
useless to us.
As a result, I was then faced
with a difficult decision;
whether or not I
should kill you.
And just to set the
record straight,
I was all for killing you...
It seemed like the most
humane option considering
what you must've
seen that day...
But in the end,
I decided to let you live.
To protect the princess
we had to lie to her.
We told her that
you had gone missing
during the operation.
Don't make me regret
my decision, Akira!
When we told her
you were gone...
She was a mess;
that's how important
you are to the princess.
I'm not really sure she's
that important to you, though...
If you go, there will
be no turning back...
You will have to face the
enemy as well as the princess.
Are you prepared
to do that?
Yes!
Just know... I'm not doing this
to prove anything to you two...
This is between me
and the princess.
No!
Yeah!
No! Don't touch me!
There's no use
praying, Sister.
You see, real vampires
aren't bothered by prayers
or silly crucifixes...
They don't have any
effect on us whatsoever...
There's no need
to be afraid.
It may be painful at first,
but you'll feel euphoric
once you awaken
as a vampire.
You monster...
You have to understand,
it may seem violent,
but the act of blood- sucking
is actually a source of
extreme pleasure for a vampire.
Even sex pales
in comparison.
Sister Laura...
It's such a shame
that you've chosen to
live a life of abstinence,
your body hidden
under religious garb.
I can't wait for you to
experience this pleasure!
No!
Here you go, boys!
I know you've been dying to
get your hands on Sister Laura.
No!
Sorry... you guys...
This is my fault.
Now how shall
I handle you?
Poor Nanami here hasn't
had a single drop of blood
since she became
a vampire.
You'll be the one to
quench her thirst.
I'm sorry, Yuki...
But I can't
take it anymore.
No... don't!
I can't control myself...
Once you've
become one of us,
I'll give you your
first mission.
You will take on
that dog, Akira...
And kill him with
this silver sword.
I can't wait!
No...
No!
Akira!
You have no right to call
for my servant like that,
you foolish girl!
It all started
going downhill
when our numbers
started growing.
Unfortunately,
so did the attacks.
Some vampires started
attacking humans
without leaving
behind any clues...
It was almost as if they were
trying to flaunt their power.
We tried to stay
hidden in the shadows,
but eventually we were
forced to come out...
We realized that we didn't
have much of a choice...
Whether or not we chose
to reveal ourselves,
the truth was going
to be exposed.
Mankind would have deemed
us their archenemy.
You saw the reaction
your classmates had
when confronted
with vampires...
Now imagine the chaos we
would have caused
had that same reaction happened
throughout the world.
So in order to avoid that
worst-case scenario...
We chose to reveal
ourselves in a way
that would show the humans
that we are a regulated society.
And that we would stay...
On the vampire bund.
Whoever was manipulating
Mizoguchi...
The vampire infiltration
at the school...
The terrorist attack at
the press conference...
The attack on the princess
when she went
looking for you...
Even that idiot
who went berserk on the
"Scales of Astrea" show...
It all stems
from one thing.
We were made
aware of a plot
attempting to destroy
the millennia- old order
between humans and vampires.
If this plan was
ever carried out,
then the entire world would
be plunged into chaos.
The princess was
determined to fight back,
so she came up with a plan
to lure out our enemies
in the hopes of destroying
the conspirators.
She was prepared to do
whatever it took to stop them
and keep her
people protected...
Even if it meant
deceiving her allies
or sacrificing her life...
Princess...
Her plan was successful;
it wasn't long before
we had lured them out
and their identity
became clear.
Who are they?!
Tell me!
They go by the name...
Telomere.
I'm surprised.
I never would
have suspected
that you were the head
of this organization...
Monseiur Jean Marais Dermaille.
I am honored that you not
only know my humble name,
but that of my
organization's, as well...
Please understand...
this truly is nothing
personal, my Princess.
Tell me, Jean...
Is your father,
the marquis,
in any way involved
with Telomere?
No, my father is an
old-fashioned fogey.
He is merely
another obstacle
that will someday
need to be destroyed.
You're just an
impudent boy
from a distinguished family
who's playing with fire...
So, you tried to
manipulate Mizoguchi
and flooded the school
with vampires...
Just what are you up to...?
And what, exactly,
do you want?
I want everything.
Oh?
Vampires and humans
cannot coexist...
It's only a
matter of time...
before everything
implodes in on itself
and we have to
start from scratch.
Your power as the ruler of
the vampires is limited...
Everything has
to be approved
by those three
detestable clans...
And in the human world it
means absolutely nothing.
But we can give
you power...
Our organization
needs to be rebuilt
with a new perspective
and a new ruler...!
And that ruler that
will lead Telomere
into the glorious, new
world order should be you!
I ask that you please
join us, Princess.
Let's show this world
what the vampire race
is truly capable of!
What we're
capable of, huh?
Interesting.
Princess?!
You can't fathom the
damage you've caused.
Did you really think this would
persuade me to join you...?
You're such a fool.
How could you...?
I never wanted harm to
come to any of them...
Because of you, they will no
longer be able to trust me!
Princess...
I was only trying
to please you...
I thought you were building
the bund to gain more power!
Silence, you imbecile!
You have no right to say
a word about my kingdom,
am I understood?
You're pathetic, Jean;
your ignorance will
be your downfall.
You should know that
we can never be the
rulers of this world!
But why not?
We cannot survive
without humans...
In fact, our very existence
is dependent upon them.
We are merely travelers
in this world.
The purpose of the bund
is solely to give
those travelers
a place to rest their
wings for a short while.
That is also why I
created the school.
I never wanted to
conquer the world.
It was quite
the opposite...
I wanted to be
like the humans
I had watched for so long...
I wanted to see
what it was like...
to be just a normal
girl for once...
Oh... Princess...
However...
we all know how
that's turned out...
I neglected my duties and
as a result this happened.
I will make you pay
for what you have done!
Wait, Princess!
If you refuse to join us,
then at least give us
the chance to join you!
-Please, let...
-Silence!
You insolent boy!
I would never allow an
insect like yourself
to join my ranks?
So you decided
to transform?
Your true form is foul...
Fitting for a despicable
creature like you.
Stop now!
Good...
You are a child
of Dermaille
and as such you are forbidden
to disobey my orders...
Go ahead and try.
That a vile
creature like you
has a blood line even close
to mine makes me sick.
Please forgive me,
Princess... Please!
It's too late.
Prin... cess!
Let go of me!
Well, it looks as though
this fight is settled.
We will change the world,
and we will use your
power to do so, Princess.
I'm sorry...
but you must die, vampire!
No!
Yuki!
Damn you!
I've been beaten
by a lowly dog...
I had heard that Telomere
had a human sympathizer...
But I never imagined
it would be you...
How could you, Saijo?
The master's dead!
Hurry! Give everyone who's
been bitten the vaccine!
There's still time
to prevent them
from turning into vampires.
Princess...
Hi, Akira...
Princess, no...
Come on, let's go...
It's over, right?
I'm afraid it isn't
over just yet.
No, it's not.
What do you mean...? Why?!
I'm sorry, you wouldn't
understand, Yuki...
Let's just say that
I have my intentions
and he has his...
Once a sword is drawn
it cannot be put away without
first crossing blades...
Isn't that right...
Akira?
Yes.
One day, a young
boy asked a question
to the great ruler
of monsters...
He asked, "Why do you
always look so unhappy?
You aren't always going to
be sad like this, are you?"
I'm sorry, I can't help
but question you...
And myself,
for that matter...
I feel bad for you...
You've had to fight on
your own for so long...
I don't need sympathy!
The ruler replied,
"If you will promise
to grant my wish,
then I promise to you that
I will stop being sad.
But I should warn you,
if you ever break the
promise you've made to me..."
You don't understand, Akira.
I want things to be
the way they were...
I want you by my
side again,...
But I know that
will never happen...
So I have to stop
living in the past!"...
Then I may devour you."
Deep down I knew...
I knew that everything
had changed...
We could never be together
the way we were...
all those years ago...
And if we can never
go back to that...
But he was bothered...
Then I might as
well kill you!
She's transforming?!
One day, the boy
mustered up the courage
to open the door to the
ruler's room in the tower...
He was shocked by
what he saw inside...
It's her!
So beautiful...
Akira...! Your hand...
I never wanted you to find
out about my secret, Yuki...
But...
Now you know why I've
been so distant...
I didn't wanna put you
in any kind of danger.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me...
But I have to go back
to where I belong.
Akira...
No, you don't have to!
You've grown so
much stronger...
I can hardly
see any traces
of the boy you once were.
Everyone changes...
They evolve...
That is, everyone but me...
I remain constant...
I thought I could
handle that fact, but...
Princess...
I am the ruler of
the vampire race.
I control the
world of darkness;
even death itself fears
crossing my path.
But all of that means
nothing to me...
I didn't ask for
any of this...
All I wanted was
something simpler...
I would forgo this life of
blood, scheming and violence
if only I could
be with you...
The promise that we
made to one another
was all that ever
mattered to me...
The words you said to me
that day gave me strength...
Suddenly I had a reason
to continue fighting...
Without you, I never would
have made it this far.
Soon I will have
my own kingdom,
a place that my people
can finally call home.
And so what?
What does it matter?
What I wanted more than
anything has been lost...
I've watched it slip
through my hands...
I know it's
sentimental nonsense;
go ahead and laugh...
I feel so utterly alone...
Be careful, Akira...
"But I should warn you,
if you ever break the
promise you've made to me...
then I may devour you."
"Will you still promise,
despite that?"
No!
"Yes, I promise"...
said the boy with a nod.
"In that case...
my wish is..."
Everything's back to
the way it should be...
Why'd you do
something so stupid?!
I'll be fine...
My body will
heal itself...
Shush...! Don't
waste your energy.
Don't worry about me...
Because I've already died
and come back to
life, Princess.
And now we've
been reunited.
Do you wanna
know what it was
that brought me
back to you...?
It was the sight
of you crying...
and the promise we made...
Akira...
I promise to you now ...
I will never
forget again...
I'll always be
by your side...
I promise.
Akira...
The Special Zone
Establishment bill
is hereby passed
by majority vote!
Akira Kaburagi Regendorf...
I bestow upon thee the
honor of knighthood.
You are now ranked amongst
my greatest warriors.
[Music]
Vera told me
you returned the
Prime Minister's grandson to him
and that you gave
him a vaccine
to prevent him from
becoming a vampire...
you also gave it to the
students who were attacked...
I appreciate it.
That may be true, but it
doesn't change the fact
that I used that poor
child to get my way
or that I caused your
classmates mental anguish.
Be honest with me...
Do you have any
regrets, Akira?
Not a one...
As I've told you before.
I will always
be by your side.
Children of darkness,
we have been liberated...!
We've been given
our own nation
to do with as we please!
I hereby declare
the establishment
of the vampire bund!
Theirs was the story
of a promise...
It was a tale of the
great ruler of monsters
and the boy who gave
his all to her...
This was the story
of their love.
Dance with the Vampire Maids!
Why do you refuse to recognize
Akira as one of my knights?
I'm sorry, Princess,
but I just don't think
that he's worthy.
How can you say that?!
He was impaled
trying to protect me!
I would impale myself,
if it meant I could
save you, Princess.
But if you did that,
then you'd turn to ash!
I would do anything to keep
you safe, my beloved Mina!
Oh, my, Nelly;
I had no idea.
Excuse me! Would
one of you ladies
do something about the
giant hole in my chest?
Here ya go!
Don't pass it through me!