'Scuse me?
Hey...
What's wrong?
Does your tummy hurt?
It is time.
Theirs was the story
of a promise...
A tale of the great
ruler of monsters
and the boy who
gave his all to her.
Looking back,
I can't help but think
that this was the day
everything started
to fall apart.
He's best known for destroying
the Byzantine Empire,
and despite resistance from the
lords of the Balkan Peninsula,
It's Dracula, right?!
Well, yes...
That's true.
So as you can see,
Vlad Tepes of Romania
is an example of...
Dude... He's real?!
So Dracula was
a true story?
Yeah, I thought
everybody knew that.
That vampire princess
is named Tepes!
Everyone, please...
Calm down.
There's no
reason to worry.
The real Vlad Tepes
was different...
He was nothing
like Dracula...
Sister Laura?
Yes, Akira?
Sorry to interrupt...
but I really gotta pee.
Um, sure...
Please go ahead.
That was a good
one, dumbass.
Way to freak everyone out.
Vampires became the popular
topic of conversation
on campus...
I don't know why,
but every time the
subject came up
he seemed to get upset.
Even at this point,
I still had no idea...
Of course, how
could I have known
when he had forgotten
what happened himself...
Damn it... Why?
Why do I feel so uneasy?
Their story began a
long, long time ago...
Long before I'd had the pleasure
of meeting Akira Kaburagi...
Before he lived
within my thoughts...
[Music]
The chief cabinet secretary's
announcement confirms
that self-proclaimed "ruler
of the vampires", Mina Tepes,
has legally purchased
Tokyo Landfill #0...
As a result, the government
is facing public scrutiny.
Whoa, they seriously
bought the whole thing?!
Those vampires
must be loaded!
Don't tell me you actually
believe in vampires.
I saw them myself on last
week's "Scales of Astrea".
That was the real deal!
Well, if you
believe in vampires
then what about all the
other monsters, huh...?
Do you think
werewolves exist, too?
Yeah, and what
about Frankenstein?
Oh, hey Yuki.
I have a lunch
delivery for you.
Thanks.
Caught ya.
Did you see anything?
You saw.
No, I didn't.
You liar...!
I know you saw!
I swear I didn't
see anything, Yuki!
Okay, you got me...
I caught a quick glimpse;
sorry about that...
It wasn't a bad view if
it makes ya feel better.
Don't be creepy, Akira.
Geez, what do you
want me to say?!
I don't know...
I just figured that...
Maybe you'd be a little more
interested in what you saw...
What was that?
You say something?
Thanks a lot, Yuki.
It's nice to have
someone worry about me...
Sorry I did that.
Sorry about that.
I know. I shouldn't have
left in the middle of class.
You idiot.
You had me worried.
Do you have a minute, Yuki...?
I have a few
questions for you
about the student council
financial report...
It'll only take
just a second.
Yeah, sure thing, Nanami.
Don't be such a wuss, man.
Ryohei, you think I
should have made a move?
She'd probably beat the crap
out of you if you tried.
I think you're right.
That Yuki is pretty
cute, though.
Yeah.
I don't get it, dude.
Why don't you try harder?
Try harder at what?
I don't know. Everything.
I don't know how
to explain it...
But I just feel like
things are fine
the way they are, you know?
I don't know what's
gotten into you lately...
You used to be so
much cooler before.
Well... I guess...
nothing you can do.
Sorry.
Dude! We've been looking
all over for you, Ryohei.
So you're a... member of the
student council, right...?
Do you think you could
do us a favor?
Let me guess, you want
the AV room again.
What for?
Princess Mina is gonna have
another press conference!
And we want to see
it on the big screen.
Man, you guys
are pathetic...
You really believe that
vampire crap...?
Go watch it at home 'cause
you're not seein' it here.
Would you talk some sense
into your friend here, Akira?
You wanna see Mina,
too, don't you?
Who's this Mina person?
How can you not
know who she is?
Yeah, the whole school's been
talking about her nonstop;
she's the ruler
of the vampires!
Oh yeah...
Quit playing dumb;
you know what
we're talking about.
You were interviewed on
that "Scales of Astrea" show!
Sorry but vampires just
don't interest me...
And I'm not really
big on TV or the news.
Hey, we're not done
talking to you!
I can't seem to get away
from all this vampire talk...
Why does it make
me feel like this?
Is there something
I can help you with?
-Hey, you!
-Stay away!
Akira?!
Are you sure you're
gonna be okay?
Yeah...
I'll be fine...
Sorry for worrying you.
It's okay but you gave me
a good scare this time.
I don't know
what happened...
It kinda scared me too.
That head injury you had
last year was pretty hardcore.
Maybe what happened
today is somehow related.
I think you need
to go to the doctor
and double check everything.
Just to be safe.
Alright, Dr. Yuki.
Cut it out; I'm serious...!
I want you to promise me
that you'll go to the doctor
and get yourself checked out.
I'm gonna go...
I just can't today.
So I need to
try harder, huh?
Truth number one:
I drink the blood
of human beings!
Truth two:
I'm dedicated to the karma
of the immortal!
Truth three:
I have been chosen
to govern...
The world of the dead!
Mina Tepes?
The one and only.
Are you... for real?
What do you mean by
that... dear sir...?
Are you asking me if I'm
really... a vampire?
Or are you asking me whether
or not I'm truly Mina Tepes?
I guess it doesn't
matter either way...
the answer is the same...
You see, I am the
ruler of the vam...
Hey, wait...!
Come back here!
Damn it...! I hate
these dumb clothes...!
I can't move at all!
Please do not assume that
I am always this helpless.
Why have you been
following me around?
And why were you
crying last time?
You don't remember...
You really have lost
all your memories.
Princess!
What the hell...?!
What do those bastards
think they're doing?
You saved me...
What's going on...?
Are they after you?
An attack?
Does that mean it's begun?
No, those aren't our men.
Must be somebody else.
Yeah...
I'm sure that
many of our kind
have been waiting for an
opportunity like this.
May I have your attention:
due to unforeseen
circumstances,
service has temporarily
been halted.
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
Who are those guys
who're after you?
It's hard to say...
There are many who would
love to see me dead...
Both human and
nonhuman alike.
And they just attack you
out of nowhere like that?!
You start to get used
to it after a while...
They'll try just
about anything
because they know it's
not easy to kill me.
Well, that is
until now anyway.
I'm afraid my shade gel
is beginning to wear off.
What the hell
is shade gel?
It's a drug that when
applied topically
can prevent our cells from
being destroyed by sunlight...
I have about
a minute left.
What happens when
your time's up?
The sunlight will
turn me into ash.
How can you be so
flippant about it?!
Whatever shall I do?
This is quite
a predicament.
I have shade gel with me,
but I cannot put
it on myself.
Damn it.
How did I get
dragged into this?
What do you mean?
I don't get why I
have to help you...
I mean, don't you
have servants?
Hurry up. This dress isn't
going to come off by itself.
I may have the
body of a child...
But don't worry, I'm actually
hundreds of years old.
So there's no reason for me to
feel weird about this, right?
So not true...
Still creepy.
Just hurry and put it on...
I can't do it by myself.
You want me to
put it on you?
No way.
Is that a problem...?
I told you, I may
look like a child
but I'm much
older than you.
I know... But it's
still freakin' creepy!
So, uh... Tell me...
Do you always have people
trying to kill you like that?
Unfortunately, yes.
Then why were you walking
around in broad daylight
without a bodyguard?
That seems pretty careless.
It was your pinky...
It called out to me.
That's why I
risked it all...
to come and find you...
but it seems...
I was wrong in doing so.
Who's there?!
It's the police!
There was a terrorist
bombing down the street...
We are looking for
possible witnesses...
Do you mind if we ask
you a few questions?
Liar!
Impressive talent,
young man...
Tell me: How did you
know they were assassins?
It sounds weird but...
I could smell it.
My... What do
we have here...?
Now I'm being
attacked by humans...?
Well... Do you want to tell
me who you work for...?
Or shall I just force you to
talk with a bite on the neck?
Behold!
This is the power
of the vampire.
This is who we truly are.
I swear I saw
Akira back there...
I'll be safe once I
make it to the bund...
Thank you very much...
You saved my life.
Honestly...
I still can't believe
you're really a vampire.
I don't know why after
everything you've seen today.
Let me ask you something,
why did you suddenly
reveal yourself
and announce you
were building a bund?
This is my way of
preparing for battle...
Now let me ask
you something...
Do you feel happy...?
The way you are now?
It's tough to say
since I've lost my memory.
I was in an
accident last year
and I woke up with amnesia...
Isn't that crazy?
16 years gone in
the blink of an eye.
But...
I have friends
that stuck by me,
even though I couldn't
remember them...
And a sweet girl who's
always worried about me...
So I guess...
I'm happy.
I must be going.
Until we meet again...
Akira...
The reason I was crying
was because I was
so happy to see you.
I don't get it;
how do you know my name?
I've been expecting
you, Princess.
Someone very important
would like to meet with you...
So I have been sent as
your personal guide.
Is that so...?
Where will you take me?
To our organization.
Oh... So I have
another enemy?
Why you, hey...!
Stay back...!
This is the realm
of the night!
As one who lives
in the daylight,
you have no business
getting involved!
Princess!
You're coming with me!
Let go!
You won't get
away from me.
Who are you...?
Which clan are you from?
Damn it!
She warned you not
to get involved!
Stop it...!
He has nothing
to do with this!
Are you crying?
Is he really that
important to you?
You're not talking, huh...?
Fine then.
Akira!
Why do you cry for me?
Why are you crying?
Does your tummy hurt?
Princess...
There's no
reason to cry...
I'll always be
by your side...
I promise that
I'll protect you.
I'll always be
there for you.
I promise...
Princess...
Don't cry...
Please.
Akira!
What a landing...
That was the end of him.
What the hell...
He can't be...
This is...
my true form.
He's a member of
the Earth clan!
Oh, Akira!
Theirs was the story
of a promise...
Akira...!
A tale of the great
ruler of monsters
and the boy who gave
his all to her...
It was a tale of
loyalty and devotion...
and the fleeting love
that they shared.
[Music]
Dance with the vampire maids!
Part 2!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
How dare you put
your grubby hands
on our princess,
you pervert...!
For that you must die!
This might sting
a little at first,
but it'll be over quickly.
I'm not some perv
who's attracted to
flat-chested preteens!
Who are you calling
flat-chested, Akira?
Who wants to watch
me fillet a werewolf?
I do!
Don't worry. I'll
try to make it fast!