Hello, Akira.
What're you up to?
Nothing much. What about you?
Nothing, I just wanted
to hear your voice...
I hope that's okay...
I don't want you to think
of me as a nuisance.
No, not at all...
Hey princess,
let me ask you something...
I can trust you, right?
Of course.
You can trust me.
I'm gonna go.
Okay...
When I was a little girl,
I always thought that falling in
love would be a happy thing...
I honestly believed
the love you felt
for one another
was all that mattered....
But as I've gotten older,
I've realized that's
not always the case...
Even now, Akira and I felt
lost in the twilight...
wondering if the clarity of
the morning would ever come...
My innocent childhood
but a memory...
What happened...?
At the Prime Minister's home?
Are you positive?
Princess, we should go.
It's time to finish this.
[Music]
Mei Ren...
Happy to see me?
Not really.
Why're you here?
Tell me something,
why didn't you put
the moves on her?
'Cause the princess
wouldn't have liked it?
I don't get what
the big deal is.
If you had your
way with her,
maybe you'd forget
about your troubles.
Don't talk about
her that way!
You don't even know her...
Yuki isn't like that!
Gee whiz, you're such
a nice guy, Akira...
But you know,
that's only gonna make things
harder for you in the long run.
What the hell are
you up to...?!
Who are you?
I'm a servant of
the royal family
who's been sworn to protect
the "true blood'
lineage of vampires.
The princess has never
said anything about you...
Sorry, I'm not buying it.
Oh yeah?
And what do you
know, Akira?
She's got you fooled.
Remember that first day
you two were together?
All of that chaos was
actually part of her plan.
She was attempting to
lure out the people
who're trying to kill her.
She mobilized an entire
battalion of troops
just to make sure that the
two of you were protected...
Crazy, huh...?
I thought it was sweet
how you fought so desperately
to keep her safe,
thinking that you were
the only one there
who could protect
her from harm.
Sorry, kiddo but you
don't know anything...
not about the
vampire bund...
or about your
beloved princess.
She isn't the sweet,
innocent girl
that you think
she is, Akira...
What do you mean by that?
I've already
said too much...
Why don't you ask the
princess yourself?
Wait! Hey! Wait!
My grandson was
attacked by vampires!
He was bitten
by one of them!
Oh my, how horrible.
That's unfortunate
for you.
How dare you act so
flippant with me!
It's obvious you're
the one who sent them!
I'm sorry...
It would appear that this
regrettable incident
was the result of a lack
of supervision on my part.
I suppose this will
ruin my plans
for the vampire bund...
I'll just have to
contact the assembly...
and withdraw my
approval request.
Goodbye.
And just where the hell
do you think you're going?!
To go get your
grandson, of course.
This is quite a conundrum.
As you've said before,
you want the
approval decision
to be based on
public opinion.
The humans would never
approve this bill,
which means we'll be forced
to leave the country.
I'm truly sorry to hear
that your grandson was
bitten by a vampire...
You do realize that
makes him one of us now.
There goes your spot
in Japanese history...
I almost pity you.
Shinya...
I'm sorry, but I can't
let you see her...
She's refusing visitors.
The princess is very tired
and needs her rest...
I can't allow
anyone inside ...
not even you, Akira.
I have to talk to her!
Please, it's
really important!
I'm sorry, but you
have to leave now.
She isn't the sweet,
innocent girl
that you think
she is, Akira...
How's the little boy
in the guest suite?
Well, he's been
crying non-stop.
So sad...
Little boy?
I don't understand,
what would the princess
want with a child?
She must have
some kind of plan.
Exactly...
And I think we're better
off not knowing...
Why don't you ask the
princess yourself?
What's the matter?
A strange lady took me
and brought me here.
Can you tell me
what your name is?
Shinya Mizoguchi.
Mizoguchi?
My dad is Koichi Mizoguchi...
and my grandpa is
Katsuichi Mizoguchi.
The prime minister?!
My neck hurts bad...
Would it be okay if
I took a look at it?
I wanna go home...
After he made his promise
to the ruler of
the monsters...
the boy remained
by her side...
even when he worried
that she might be wrong.
The people
began to gossip.
They claimed that he
had been possessed
and surely he would
be eaten next.
The boy refused to let
the gossip affect him.
He didn't want to
believe any of it.
But he was bothered
by the time she spent
alone in the tower.
Sometimes the ruler
would hole up there...
refusing to see the boy.
One day, the boy
mustered up the courage
to open the door to the
ruler's room in the tower...
He was shocked by
what he saw inside...
I have made the
arrangements.
Tomorrow morning, your grandson
will wake up in his own bed
without any recollection
of what happened.
I can't thank
you enough...
However, before I
let your grandson go,
there's something that
I need you to tell me...
Yes?
It's simple really...
I need the name of
the mastermind...
whoever it is that's been
funding your operation...
I want to know
who ordered you
to crush the
Special Zone bill.
Yuki!
Hey, is it true that you
were attacked by vampires?!
How did you know?
So it's true?!
How scary!
We heard that a
bunch of vampires
have snuck into the school!
Um... Who told you that?!
Who?
Cut it out, Hiko!
You can't just go around
spreading lies like that!
I'm not lying; I'm
being completely honest.
It's only a matter of time
before they take over
the whole school.
But you never know, huh...?
There could be a vampire
standing right next to you.
You better cut the crap or
I'm gonna kick your ass.
You don't wanna get
beat again, do ya?!
What's so funny, huh?
You better let go...
Or I'll have to hurt you!
Whoa...! Just
calm down, Hiko!
Please don't hurt us;
we're friends of yours!
No... I am not friends
with you anymore.
I've had enough...
I won't be bullied by you
pathetic little humans!
Oh, no!
This is more fun than I
thought it would be...!
I finally get
to be the bully
instead of always
being the victim...
Sorry, but you guys don't
have any power over me now.
I've chosen to
become a vampire;
I'm a child of the darkness...
now I'm more powerful
than all of you!
-Hiko!
-A vampire...
Wow, Yuki...
You've got some guts,
don't you...?
My brethren told you not
to come back here......
but you... didn't
heed their warning!
Yuki!
No... Hiko!
You should let
go, Akira...
I really don't wanna
have to hurt you...
You've always been
so nice to me...
Damn...! Why did
you do this, Hiko?!
Don't you realize what it
means to become a vampire?!
It means I'm more
powerful than you!
My fang...
I lost my fang!
Why, Hiko?
Why did you
become a vampire?!
Akira...
I know you've had a hard
time with bullies,
so I can understand why
you wanted power...
But still...
this wasn't the
way to go about it!
Who turned you into
a vampire, Hiko?
It's very important
that you tell me.
Who is your master?!
Master...? Uh...
Sorry!
Hiko!
You sure seem happy.
Akira!
Good news...!
We finally struck a deal
with the Prime Minister...
We're going to be making the
announcement later tonight!
Well, good for you.
Is there something wrong...?
You seem awfully
cranky today.
There are vampires
at the school!
They were able to
sneak in somehow
and now they're feeding
on the human students!
Did you know about this?!
Of course you did...
So...
then you know what
happened to Nanami, too?
Well, I received a
report about it...
I suppose I should have
been on top of the matter,
but I had pressing
business matters
that needed to
be attended to.
You had pressing business
matters, huh...?
You mean like using a kid to
blackmail the entire country?!
How do you know
about that?
Because I met him.
The future of the
bund is in jeopardy
because of Mizoguchi.
I have to use any
means necessary.
But he's just a kid...!
Don't you think you're taking
this too far, Princess?!
How dare you
question my motives?!
You wouldn't
understand, Akira!
The fate of the vampire
kingdom rests on my shoulders...
I will use whatever
tactics I see fit
to achieve my goal...
That is the duty
of a policymaker.
You're a child
unable to understand the
intricacies of politics.
So stay out of it!
Princess.
At least tell
me one thing...
That day...
The day you came to the
school to find me...
It wasn't because you
wanted to see me, was it?
Why should I answer?
You won't believe
me anyway.
You are a kid...
You're an entitled brat.
I'll bet that
promise we made
doesn't mean a
thing to you...
I should have known.
I'm finished talking
to you, Akira...
Would you please leave?
I can't trust her...
I wanted to believe
you, Princess!
Prime Minister Mizoguchi,
the leading opponent of the
Special Zone Establishment bill,
surprised the nation as he
announced his retirement today.
The Prime Minister
had threatened
to dissolve the assembly
to keep the Special Zone
bill from passing.
Now that Mizoguchi has
announced his early retirement,
the bill is expected to pass.
Following his startling
announcement,
an emergency meeting was called
requesting the attendance
of all assembly members.
It seems that today's
announcement
has affected the stock
market in a positive way.
Overseas investors are
seizing the opportunity-
I saw this guy...
and her...
There's so many...
And this kid had a freak
out like Hiko earlier today.
Man, this is
unbelievable...
Everything's changed
since the "vampire princess"
first showed up...
All of a sudden...
we have to worry about
vampire attacks...
even in our own school.
Damn it...
We have to stop them.
Akira...
What do you want?!
I need you to help me.
Help you do what?
Find and get rid
of every vampire
who's hiding out
in our school!
Before she went missing,
Nanami wanted to make sure
that the students
of our school
were able to
protect themselves.
That's why we've gathered
here this afternoon.
We'd like to thank you
for your help with this...
Sister Laura.
It's my duty to
protect you...
Not only as your
instructor,
but also... as a
servant of our Lord.
Okay, so here's the plan.
Our first step
is figuring out
which students at the school
have become vampires.
We can't fight until we
know who we're up against.
But how are we going to be
able to tell who's a vampire?
Yeah, it's not like you can
just tell by looking at them.
There is one
way to find out.
Tomorrow we're gonna hold
a school-wide assembly
outside on the lawn...
As most of you know,
vampires and
sunlight don't mix.
So anyone who's a vampire
won't be able to come
to the assembly.
But isn't there some kinda
lotion they can put on?
We've already got
that covered... Akira.
The Shade Gel they use to
protect themselves from the sun
loses its effect after 15
minutes of direct sunlight.
So in this case,
it won't help them.
He hangs out with
Princess Mina!
Can we trust him?
Akira came to us asking for
help to fight the vampires.
He's on our side...
Don't worry.
Vampire's blood has
a distinct scent
and I have a fierce
sense of smell.
I can pick them
out easily.
And there you have it...
While we're on
the subject,
you don't smell any
vampires in here, do ya?
No, we're all clear...
I think...
we should stay
here tonight.
But why?
The vampires are smart...
I'm sure they've caught
on to what we're doing.
If we split up, I'm afraid
we'll be attacked one by one.
Sister... We should
be safe here, right?
Well, the church
windows have shutters...
and there's an
emergency generator...
Yes, I think so.
So anyone who doesn't show
up tomorrow is a vampire...
Once we've identified them,
we'll take action.
We won't let these vampires
take over our school!
-You with me!
-Yeah!
I hate to bug
you, Akira...
But I have a favor to ask.
Sure, what is it?
We're gonna need weapons
to fight off the vampires.
It's dangerous
enough tonight,
but we really don't know
what to expect tomorrow.
Right now we're helpless
if they come after us.
Do you know where we
could find anything?
I might be able to find some
stuff in the Special Zone...
Could you go check it out?
Do it for us.
I guess...
We've decided to
trust you, Akira...
Show us that we've
made the right choice.
Alright.
Akira...
Yuki...
Are you sure about this?
I have to confront
my feelings...
I don't have any choice.
So I...
I have to fight
the princess.
Can I ask you about
something...?
What happened to the
ring I gave you?
I'm sorry...
I should've told
you I lost it.
Did you give it
to someone else?
I would never do that...!
That ring is special to me...
It represents the promise
we made to each other.
I finally remember
the truth...
You gave this to me...
right, Yuki...?
So then... does that mean...
that we're...?
No, it's not like that.
It's just a symbol of
the promise we made...
That we would always be
friends no matter what.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I should've told
you the truth,
that we were boyfriend
and girlfriend.
You only lied because you
were trying to protect me
and you stayed by
my side anyway.
I don't know what I would've
done without your help.
After losing my memory,
I didn't have anyone.
I would've been completely
lost without you there.
Akira... that means...
so much to me...
thank you...
for telling me...
No, thank you... Yuki...
I promise, I will
keep you safe!
Okay.
As soon as I leave,
I want you to shut all
of the doors and windows
and keep them locked!
Do not open them,
no matter what!
Vampires can be clever...!
They'll play tricks
with your mind!
Let your guard
down and it's over!
Goodbye...
So, what's up?
Junior high let out
about an hour ago.
And the high school
should let out...
Are you sure that it's
gonna be sunny tomorrow?
Well, that's what the
forecast predicted.
It seems like...
We're doing this
the slow way...
Wouldn't you say?
From what I understand,
vampire society
is like a pyramid
with the ruler
sitting at the top...
If we could do something
about Princess Mina...
Then everything else would
probably just fix itself.
But... That's out
of the question.
What happened?!
A blackout?!
Please... try to stay
calm, everyone...
I'll go and turn
on the generator...
You don't think...
it could be them?
You guys...
Let me in...
Uh... Who's there?!
It's me...
Please let me in...!
I need help.
Is that...?
It sounds like Nanami!
No way...!
I... I thought
she was dead!
I escaped from the vampires,
but I'm injured.
Please, let me in.
I need to see a doctor.
What should we do?!
We have no choice.
Hold on! We're
opening the doors!
No, don't do it...!
Akira told us not
to open them!
But it's Nanami out there,
and she could be in danger!
Yeah, if she's hurt,
then we have to help her!
No...! Please don't!
No!
It's... you...
Hello there, Yuki...
I'm so sorry...
[Music]
Dance with the
Three Stupid Maids!
Who're you calling stupid?!
Geez, that kid
won't stop crying.
Look, Shinya, I'm Dracula!
Aren't my fangs
cool lookin'?!
What the hell
are you doing?!
I thought that all children
loved scary monsters!
You are such an
idiot, Nero...!
Kids like giant
robots like this!
I don't know,
I think that's scarier.
How so? Robots don't
even suck blood!
What are you doing, Nella?!
I thought kids liked
stuff like this.
-No, no, no!
You're gonna piss
off all the parents!
This is such a
pain in the ass.