Tango Team is locked
in combat on B3!
I can't see! What the hell?!
Retreat! Retreat!
Come in, Tango Team!
Are you there?!
What happened...?
Is it just me now?!
Your mission is to seize
control of the facility
below the castle without
causing any damage whatsoever.
As per the ancient pact
made with the Tepes family,
you will become Princess
Mina's devoted servant
and protector when you
turn 17 next year.
You will never
leave her side.
This mission will act as
a litmus test to determine
whether or not
you're ready...
Do your best, my son.
What is this place?
Princess...?!
Don't tell me...
these are all...
I'm so sorry you had to
see this, you poor boy.
I'm going to kill you...
I'm going to kill you!
They've been destroyed.
Now that just
leaves me and her...
It sounds like he's
hurtin' pretty bad.
Does he have an ouchie?
Don't worry,
he'll be fine.
He must be having
a nightmare.
I'm going after him...
Princess.
[Music]
Thanks for saving me...
They were so excited...
Kept saying that I
had to fix you
because you're the
princess' knight.
My mommy's a nurse...! She'll
make your ouchies go away!
I work at a Special Zone
government healthcare clinic
here on the bund.
We have some
werewolves who come in
so I knew how to
treat your wounds.
Hey... could you promise...?
Please save her...
You have to...!
She's counting on
you, mister!
I've only got
three hours...
until it's dawn...
Princess...
What does it all mean?
I don't suppose you
remember what you saw
on that mission a year ago?
You discovered a
grave secret
about the legacy of
the true-bloods...
You okay, mister?
I'd better go...
It's almost dawn.
This way!
What's going on?
Everyone here... is a
fangless vampire...
We live together in this
geofront beneath the bund.
Take this with you...
Don't want ya gettin'
hungry out there.
Please be careful, okay?
Whatever you do,
don't die on us!
The princess is
very special to us;
she's the only leader
who's ever given us hope.
Go get those bastards!
You gotta get
through this, okay?
For the princess' sake!
By removing our fangs and
refusing to feed off
of humans we have chosen
a life of isolation.
We had resigned
ourselves to believe...
that was simply
our lot in life
and we would never belong to
human or vampire society.
But when the princess
built the bund
she created a place
especially for us.
She gathered fangless
vampires living in isolation
all over the world
and we formed a family.
She has brought so
much joy to our lives.
We would be lost...
if it wasn't for
our Princess Mina.
You okay, mister?
I promise you...
I will not be defeated...
I will make it back alive!
This is the utopia
the princess
has created for
the fangless...
This is what she was
fighting to protect...
I'm ready... I can do this!
You won't be able
to transform
because the cellular
transformation blockers
haven't worn off yet.
So please be careful.
So tell me...
What is this
"true-blood legacy"
that Ivanovic is talking about?
Don't play dumb with me!
Please do not
take offense.
We have refrained from
telling you about it...
because we do not
fully know the details
ourselves, Princess.
Wolf, stop!
I'm sorry but I
don't see the point
in being secretive
any longer.
So... You wanna tell me why?
Cellular transformation
blockers...
They're drugs used to
temporarily suppress
cellular activity when
a beast-person
is undergoing surgery.
They take about 3
hours to take effect.
How do I know this?
Because the only thing I
ate before this game of tag...
was one of your
pieces of hard candy!
Why Mei Ren?
Why did you do it?
Why did you set me
up like that?!
I've been waiting for this
moment for a very long time...
Three clans
and Mina Tepes,
the leaders of
the vampire world,
are finally together
in the same room.
Now I can turn them all
into ash at one time.
That's what I must do for the
person who is dear to me...
And just so you know,
I'm not talking about Rozenmann.
Let me guess, it's the
girl I saw in that castle
who looks like
the princess.
Well, it seems like you've
finally remembered everything.
During the mission we
conducted one year ago,
Akira stumbled upon the
"true-blood legacy"...
Although he was badly
injured when we found him,
I suspect his memory
loss was self-induced.
We still have no idea
what he saw down there...
It was that
traumatic for him...?
What is this "legacy"?!
I'm afraid only Akira
would know the answer to that.
All we know is
whatever it is,
it was left behind by
the true-blood lineage.
I highly doubt Rozenmann
and the others know
any more than we do.
It is said that the
legacy involves the blood
of the true-bloods, Princess.
But what does that mean?
Time is essentially at a
standstill for the vampire race
We have been cut off from
the evolutionary cycle
and eventually we'll all
be turned to ash.
Supposedly, with the
"true-blood legacy",
we are able to move forward.
Thus providing
for us a future.
So it was you...
You're the one I saw with
her at the castle that day.
Tell me... Who
the hell is she?
She's the one who's given
me a reason to live...
She's been treated cruelly
and has had her existence
erased just like me.
Even so, she
continues to fight.
She is my princess...
Mei Ren... Come with me.
That's the name I
have given you...
Don't you think it's cute?
She gave me
everything-- my name,
my freedom, a
reason for being...
My people, the Forest
Clan, were endangered
and I was being kept as a
pet when she rescued me.
She has done
so much for me
that I long to
return the favor.
I will do whatever it
takes to make sure
the door to the new
world order is opened!
Then we will crown my princess
as our rightful queen.
Vampires and humans alike
will have no choice
but to bow before her.
What...?!
Mei Ren...! You're with...
Telomere?!
So you were involved
from the very beginning?
Well, come on,
think about it...
We can't let you find the
"true-blood legacy."
This "legacy" you
keep mentioning...
does it have anything to do
with all those clones I saw?
Or is it that blood
looking stuff
she poured on top of them?
I guess you could say
it's a little of both.
The vampire race would not
have a future without them...
We could not survive...
without both...
The blood of
true-bloods...
and either your
princess...
or mine.
Aren't you the least
bit worried...?
I mean, after seeing
all of those clones...
What if your princess...
isn't the real Mina Tepes?!
That's a joke!
You must be kidding me.
Countess Elizabeth
Bathory, Gilgamesh,
Emperor Qin Shi Huang...
That those with power ultimately
end up on a treasure hunt
hoping to find an elixir
that might extend
their lifespan...
I guess the Tepes
aren't exempt.
Princess?
I don't care to
discuss this anymore...
Forgive me but I have much
more important things
to worry about.
I have faith in Akira...
Whatever this "true-blood
legacy" may be...
The promise he made
to me means that
it will never fall
into the wrong hands.
Remember what
you told me...?
You said that we
were the only ones
who can truly
understand each other.
So I'm sure you
know what I mean...
when I say that
in my book...
the princess I made
a promise to...
is the only
princess there is!
Yeah, I know...
And I also feel the
same way about mine...
She's the only one
who matters to me.
We've let them take
over our lives...
We're both crazy.
We're butterflies in
love with flowers...
willing to sacrifice mind,
body, and every drop of blood
without any regret!
This is "Agni's Blood"
that's been modified
for beast-people...
Wanna try to take it out?
Mei Ren...!
Don't worry, I'm
not gonna die alone.
Because your
beloved princess
will be right beside
me when I detonate it!
Now... How about one
last dance, Akira?
Only one can be
the true ruler.
The question is...
will it be your
princess...
Or mine.
It's a shame that things
have to end this way...
I actually liked you.
It's almost daybreak...
Akira?!
Akira!
So those two are the
only ones still alive?!
My word!
This show is incredibly
entertaining...
Wouldn't you agree...
Princess?
No!
It's all over...
Akira.
Damn it, she got him.
Akira...
No...
Princess... Please!
Don't look away!
Akira said...
he would live...!
He made a promise that
he would return to me!
And I know that he
keeps his promises...
even to the death!
Don't give up! You have to
keep fighting, Akira...!
Your Mina is
waiting for you!
I'm coming, Princess...
I'm so sorry...
I made you...
cry again...
Just hang on...
I will come back to you...
I was thinking, Akira...
I know why our princesses
loved us so much.
Because we kept them
from being all alone.
You...
win...
But I must admit
I'm happy...
I never thought
that I would die...
with someone...
holding me...
Oh, Akira...
My word!
The show's over,
gentlemen.
That's ridiculous...!
He must've cheated;
I want a rematch!
A bet is a bet...!
The three of you
are true-blood nobles
and as such I suggest that you
proceed with honor and decorum.
You dare to scold us...
lowly vermin?!
Wolf...! Show yourself.
I told them we shouldn't
have trusted you...
You deceived us,
you little brat!
Dear Princess...
Did you really think
such a small army...
would frighten the noble
leaders of the Three Clans?
She was hit with sunlight!
Where did it come from?!
The interior
of this castle
is fitted with a special
optical fiber...
It captures sunlight
from the exterior...
which we can then emit
inside the building.
Just the touch
of a button...
And we can flood this
entire room with sunlight
if we so choose.
I know that you're
bluffing...!
Because if you
were to do that
you'd kill your own
master as well!
I rule half the world...
that of the darkness...
Which means you should
live by my word.
I was raised to
rule over you...
I have fought to
keep my title...
I will not let
it go so easily.
If you refuse
to honor me
and continue to insist
that I kneel before you...
I shall turn us all
into ash here and now!
So choose!
Either die with me and
our race is wiped out...
or honor your ruler
and bow before me.
You have served as my
guardians for so very long...
You have my gratitude.
Now I would like for you
to return to your domains
and focus on your
domestic affairs.
[Music]
You came back!
Akira...!
Akira!
Please smile...
Do it for me...
Princess.
There ya go...
beautiful... smile...
That's why I...
It's why... I...
Men...
Three howls for
the warrior!
Thank you...
You've done so
much for me.
I hope you have
pleasant dreams...
Mei Ren...
So your friend served
someone who looked just like me
but she never told you
any more than that?
I wonder who she is...
Why? Does it worry you?
Only because it
means that someday
she and I will be forced
to come face-to-face...
And nothing good
can come of that...
I'm sure there will be
much blood shed on that day.
Akira... Is your
arm feeling better?
Yeah, I'm just really glad
they were able to reattach it.
There's almost
no pain now.
That's good.
I'm glad...
I have to tell
you Princess,
it's pretty shocking
to find out
that there's something like
this beneath the bund.
I call it the Cradle...
I think of it as a place
for eternal napping;
far away from the hustle
and bustle of everyone
and everything living
life up above.
A butterfly.
Akira...
So... on that day
seven years ago...
You gave me my wish...
a promise that
remains unbroken.
I think that it's my turn
to hear your wish now.
I want you to be by
my side, Princess.
All I want is for you
to be with me until...
my final moments.
Are you sure...?
I may not be the only
Mina Tepes, out there...
What if I'm not
the real one?
Well, you're the only
princess that matters to me.
In that case...
I swear to you
here and now...
I promise I will
always be with you...
until either you or I
move on from this life...
We are bound together...
by the promise we've made.
Though it may seem
like a fleeting moment
in the finality
of eternity...
our promise will
endure forever.
The boy promised
the ruler of monsters
that they would be
together forever.
And she in turn,
swore to him
that she would always
be by his side.
Would you care to
dance with me... Akira?
Of course.
And the promise
that the boy made
to the ruler of monsters...
Would remain unbroken...
for the rest of
their story...
Theirs was the story
of a promise...
A tale of the great
ruler of monsters
and the boy who gave
his all to her...
and the eternal bond
that they shared.
I can't find it anywhere.
Where could that dumb
werewolf have dropped it?
Lighten up on him...
he saved our
beloved Princess.
Okay fine, but
only a little bit.
Look! I found it!
Where was it?
Yeah, it looks like
it's been through hell.
I took it from a rat
that was gnawing on it.
Gross, it's all nasty now.
Don't worry! We can just blow
it off and it'll be fine!
It's not like it's a
piece of candy we dropped!
I'm so glad
the doctors were able to
reattach your arm, Akira.
Yeah, it seems
to be A-OK now.
Well, you have the
maids to thank for that.
When they heard
what happened
they went looking
for your arm.
Oh really...?
I guess they're not
so bad after all.
Are you guys ready?!
Hurry Nero! It's time!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Okay, okay, okay!
Ready... go!
Dance with the
Vampire Maids!
Is now over!
So bye-bye everybody!
Okay, ready?!
Rock... paper... scis...
Would you two knock
that off, already?!