Oh, yeah...
It's affected my work...
Now that we all
know they're real...
it's a lot harder to
write vampire manga.
But I hear your
past works...
are selling better
than they ever have!
And now they're on TV...
So you must really
be raking it in!
I guess so...
Yeah... sure!
Vampire mania has
gotten so wild,
some people even
idolize them!
Yumi, you've actually
been bitten by a vampire,
can you tell us about that?
I was given the vaccine
right after it happened...
And as you can see,
I wasn't turned...
But let me tell you, when
I was bitten it felt so good!
Wha...? Nanami...
Yuzuru...
No, wait!
Nanami, come back!
[Music]
That night...
under the light of
the pale moon...
I experienced
an end to love.
It had been a month since
the chapel was taken over...
and it seemed like
some kind of peace
had finally returned
to the school...
But that was only
on the surface...
deep scars still
remained...
And I began to feel
the distance growing
between Akira and me
with each passing day...
Werewolves...
The Earth Clan.
The destiny that awaited
some side of him I didn't know.
But it was so much
deeper than that...
She was in his heart...
And she had
always been there.
According to a
government survey...
when asked the question,
"Would you want to
become a vampire?"
Thirty percent of
the under twenty-five
demographic answered "yes."
And it appears... eternal life
was the most popular reason.
Well, at least our plans
are finally starting
to come together.
Yes... but there is still
one troubling rumor.
Supposedly a number of
vampires broke out of the bund
and are now roaming
the city at night.
I thought I'd
made it clear
the bund was to
be sealed off...
Breakouts cannot
be tolerated
if we wish to maintain any
semblance of security.
I want you to
investigate...
Determine if it's true.
I brought a draft of the student
council officer invitation...
I'm sorry...
but it looks like
they're not planning to
come back after all.
I see.
We have a counselor
who specializes in
vampire-related PTSD...
Maybe the former
student council members
could use some counseling?
No, we can't force them to do
something they don't want to.
It's almost like there's
two different Minas...
One shows concern and has
compassion for the weak...
While the other
finds cruel delight
in punishing her followers...
and fights for keeps,
like she did with Akira...
But which one is
the real Mina?
Yuki... Why are you
staring at me like that?
I know my beauty
can be shocking...
But you have a lovely face
that's worth
staring at as well.
You're teasing
me the same way
you tease Akira, aren't you?
When we first reunited
he grew flustered with
every little comment.
But he has this calm
about him lately,
it's almost bizarre...
If he were here, he would
be saying to me,
"Yeah, yeah, you're
cute Princess"...
something like that.
That's a great impression!
Well, I am always
watching him...
It's the one thing I
never grow tired of.
Yeah, so... anyway, if you
could just take a look at this;
it's a draft I wrote...
I'm sorry, I brought the wrong
notebook along with me...!
I'll be right back!
You sunbathing?
Hang around
vampires too long
and you start to
go all nocturnal...
You start to miss
the sun, don't ya?
That seat belongs
to someone else.
Aw, your beloved
princess...?
Well I'm not moving,
so you'll have to make me...
If you dare.
Nice try!
What is that...
around your neck?
You mean this...?
It's very
precious to me...
It's just a replica,
but the person most
important to me
has one just like it.
By the way, Akira...
Yeah?
How long you gonna
keep coppin' a feel?
Oh, baby!
Are you okay?
What was all that noise?
Akira!
Yuki...! I, uh... it's
not what you think!
I was just taking a nap
and I fell out of my chair,
'cause I'm an idiot!
Let me guess, you're
waiting for the princess?
You got it...
So, is she finished
up with her work yet?
Not quite, I think she
might be a little bit longer.
I really shouldn't
spend all this time
by the princess' side...
Even if it means I have to
quit the student council...
Seeing them together is
just too painful for me.
What're you doing?!
That's...!
I must say this is
rather unexpected.
I didn't realize that
you're an aspiring novelist.
But... Princess...
That's so mean!
It was rude of me to read
it without asking you...
but once I started I honestly
couldn't put it down.
Your narrative skills
are captivating, Yuki...
I was swept up
by the story.
You're lying...
And why would
I do that...?
I've read everything from
Ulysses to Oliver Twist,
so you can trust
my opinion...
I'm never wrong.
Now, granted, it's not
quite at the level of
Byron or Rimbaud...
But your writing exudes
a unique tenderness
and a youthful spirit.
And that... has to
come from your heart...
It's a quality that
cannot be taught.
Yeah right...
You're just saying
that to me to be nice.
You shouldn't sell
yourself short...
You have an inner
warmth to you...
I've seen it with
my own eyes, Yuki...
You even shed
tears for me
after I intimidated you
and told you to be gone.
No, Akira!
That's not necessarily...
The truth is...
there are now two things
for which I owe
you an apology.
Two things?
I lied to you
about this ring.
Akira didn't
give it to me.
Please, I beg your
forgiveness...
I was envious of you...
Because your
connection with him...
was not born out of
servitude or fate...
but instead it was out
of honest camaraderie.
Oh, Princess...
Yuki?
There's nothing for
you to apologize for.
You and I...
We're kinda the same...
We both love Akira...
and I think we'd
make great allies!
You would consider me...
your friend?
You're kind and brave
and compassionate...
I always hoped if
I ever made a friend
it would be with
someone like you.
Wait...! Does being friends
with me upset you?!
No, I... I don't
deserve your friendship!
I thought... you were
a horrible person...
and I was so
jealous of you!
Then the two of us
should work together...
Let us help each other
where the other is lacking...
We might even make a
surprisingly good team!
"Tomorrow is
always fresh...
with no mistakes in it."
That's "Anne of Green Gables,"
right...?
I'm afraid I lack Anne's
red hair and freckles...
but do you think you
can accept me anyway?
With pleasure!
By the way, may I
ask you something?
Yeah sure, what is it?
Occasionally in your novel
I came across terms that
I wasn't familiar with...
"Aggressive top", "seductive
bottom", and "BDSM"...
So what are these things...?
Are they codes for something
from Japanese literature?
Is something wrong?
Uh...! Everything's
just fine...!
Right, Princess?!
Akira doesn't know
about my writing yet...
Please don't say
anything to him.
I won't, Yuki.
What's going on...?
If the princess is being
mean to you just say so.
Akira! I was not
being mean to her...!
How could you say that
about a pretty girl like me?
Yeah, yeah, you're
cute Princess.
Okay, this is seriously
weirding me out...
I thought you two
were fighting.
Of course we're not!
Right, Princess?
We're confidantes now.
I don't get it...
Nice, isn't it...?
Finding a friend with whom
to share common feelings?
Finally... I had rediscovered
my ability to smile.
But I should have realized
that it wouldn't
last very long...
Because little
did we know...
another series of tragic,
horrifying events
had already begun...
Hey! Kid...!
What're you doin'
out so late?
Hi, Officer...
I'm just looking
for someone...
I'm going...
to the vampire bund.
That right...? So you wanna
meet a vampire, huh, kid...?
Then let me
help ya find one!
Do not bare your
fangs in public...
Show some couth.
Apparently the rumors
about vampires
sneaking out of the
bund to feed are true.
He self-destructed?
Excuse me, are you
a vampire, too?
I'm looking for someone
who might be on the bund...
Is there any way
you can take me?
I'm sorry, but I can't...
Humans are not allowed
access to the bund...
You will find no one
but vampires there.
But... the person
I'm looking for...
My neighbor...
she is a vampire!
Your neighbor...?
So she's not family?
No, but we're very close.
She looked after me ever
since I was little...
And what would this
girl's name be?
Her name is Nanami...
Nanami Shinonome.
My, my, aren't you a
daring little girl...?
And you look so innocent,
too, don't you!
Nicely done,
my little piglet.
Now come here.
Nanami Shinonome?
You mean the student
council president?!
All of the students who
were attacked at the church...
were given the
vaccine afterward.
But it seems
Miss Shinonome
has been a vampire
for some time now...
so the vaccine
was useless.
There is a record of her
entering the special zone...
However, there have
been no signs of her
at her assigned residence.
So then what does that mean
about the other students
who were sent
there with her?
We can't find them...
There are dozens of vampires
who were sent to the island,
but have since
gone missing.
As far as we know they're not
even in the special zone...
It's shocking to think
that somehow we've lost
vampires from the bund
without even knowing it...
Whoever is behind this had
a well-thought out plan.
Do you think that...
it's Telomere?
Possibly...
But they're too proud
to keep quiet for long.
If it was them,
they'll reveal themselves.
But Nanami doesn't
have a master now...
'cause Jean Marais's dead.
Well, if she isn't
roaming free...
then she may be serving
a new master now.
Do you think she
would do that?
At this point, I wouldn't
put anything past her.
She isn't heartless...
she's plagued with
worry and delusions
we cannot begin
to imagine...
someone may be using
that against her.
Delusions?
Do not worry...
For I will be Nanami
Shinonome's savior.
Yuki, I want you to wait
here and look after Yuzuru...
Let's go, Akira.
Yuzuru...
What do you want with him?
Is it your intention
to try and turn him?
Princess Mina...
It seems you've
abandoned your morals
since the last
time I saw you.
As per the blood pact,
thou shalt obey thy ruler...
Nanami Shinonome!
You must return to the vampire
bund with me this instant.
What's this...?
You refuse to
obey my order?
So someone else has
gotten to her...!
Akira!
I'm okay!
Damn you!
Princess...!
Heads up, Vera...!
It's an ambush,
I can smell it!
Nest One to Fang Leader...
Requesting backup.
Copy! Fang Leader out!
Where's the Princess?!
I'm right behind her!
Okay, I'm on my way!
Cease your
running, Nanami.
I will do whatever I must.
Please allow
me to save you.
Wow Princess,
you're so generous!
The ruler of all the
creatures of the night...
Feeling indebted to a
helpless young vampire
of the lowest
social order...
Disappointing,
to say the least.
Let me introduce myself...
You may call
me Hysterica...
A pleasure.
I take it you're Nanami's
new master, then...
'Hysterica' was it...?
What is your scheme,
gathering vampires like this?
Stay behind me, Princess.
So, you're the wolf boy
I've heard so much about...
A knight in furry armor.
I wonder if you
can handle...
fighting my entire army.
Hiko?!
Hear me now...!
Surely some
among you...
were never given a choice
in becoming vampires.
I'm giving you one now...
Come join me!
Do so and I swear to
nurture and protect you
to my utmost ability.
I had no idea that you
were such a fool, Princess!
And you call yourself
"ruler of the vampires"?!
The throne is mine by right
of the noble true-blood
that flows
within my veins...
But your true
nature is showing.
Watch what you say, or you
might give yourself away.
Destroy them!
We eight are the elite
Beowulf Soldiers...
We have been sent by
Sir Wolfgang Regendorf
to serve and protect our
beloved Princess Mina.
Give us your
orders, ma'am.
Leave Hysterica and
the girl unharmed.
As for the others,
you may return them all
to the dust of the earth!
-Right!
Go now and prove thy
allegiance to me!
Show them your power,
Wolf Boys!
Draw your weapons!
As I'd expect from the
princess's guard dogs...
You guys mean business.
Die!
Now reveal your scheme
to me, Hysterica.
Nanami!
Stop being so
reckless, Princess!
Don't go, Nanami!
Are you so worried about
her that you'd ignore me...?
I will not be mocked!
Vera!
Allow me to handle her.
Very well.
Well, doesn't this bring
back some fond memories?
Hey, Veratos...!
When was the last time
we saw each other...
Nineteen Hundred?
No, I think it was
Nineteen-Eighteen in Paris,
Francesca.
I'm afraid she
doesn't exist anymore.
I go by "Hysterica"
these days.
So you've changed
your name again...?
Am I correct in assuming
you change masters with
the same reckless abandon?
I don't feel the need
to blindly worship
a single master like
you do, Veratos.
So what now...?
Are you serving
Telomere?
What's with the
ridiculous get-up?
You've fallen far since
the days of high society
when you were Veratos
the Black Ruby.
You're pathetic...
You should have come
with me back then...
You could've had everything
you ever wanted.
You still don't
get it, do you...?
I do not want for
anything now...
And the princess' trust
is all that I need.
Why do you insist
on being loyal
to that silly little girl?
She'll ruin everything
trying to turn the world
into her playground...
Her self-made reign
means nothing!
Enough! Do not disparage
my princess any further...
Or I will show no mercy!
I've been waiting
for this moment.
Let's finish what we
started ninety years ago!
Yuzuru... no...
Where did she go?!
What's wrong? Your mom
didn't come get ya?
She's absorbed in her
day-trading, like always...
How does she think you're
supposed to get home?
Come with me...
I'm kinda on my own, too.
I'll make us some food...
We can have
dinner together!
So are you as
lonely as I am?
No, I'm not lonely...
'Cause I have you, silly!
Nanami!
Don't go...! Don't
leave me, Nanami!
Please don't go!
Nanami... I take it
that you resent me.
Yes I do...
I resent you, but not
because of what you made me!
I don't care
about that...!
I tried to act like
it was nothing...
I tried so hard
to fight it!
You mean how you
feel about the boy?
Don't say it!
My god...
If Yuzuru ever found out
I had such shameful
feelings for him...
But... I'm obsessed...
I just can't help myself!
Even as we speak,
I want him so bad
it feels like my
heart is gonna burst!
Kill me...! Do it now!
Kill me before I'm
forced to defile him!
Nanami...
Do it...!
Kill me, before I make
him hate me...! Please!
Nanami!
Yuzuru!
No...! Don't look...!
Don't look at me like this!
Nanami!
Stay away from me!
She said stay
away little boy!
Yuzuru!
Please... stop!
Vera!
Princess... I apologize...
I underestimated her.
Just my luck,
I step away for a moment
and things finally
start to get interesting!
I think it's about time
for me to get going;
we've had enough fun
for one evening.
You'll find out about
my "scheme" soon enough.
Hysterica...! What
are you planning?!
A magnificent event...
to teach all the cowardly
humans a lesson...
about the true
terror of vampires...
Come back here!
Persistent little
wolf cub, aren't you?
Outta the way!
Take cover!
Princess!
I'm okay, Vera...
Akira was able
to protect me.
Self-destructions...
Damn you, Telomere...
As if stuffing yourselves
full of explosives
wasn't bad enough...
You had to come up
with something worse.
[Music]
Dance with the
Vampire Maids!
Part... um,
what are we on again?
Here's the creator
of the manga!
Hey! Thank you!
So why haven't we been
in the show much lately?
It's not my fault.
There's nothing for any
of you to do right now.
Whoa! Controversial remarks!
Don't blame me.
Mr. Yoshino handles
the series structure.
But... Aren't you the writer?!
What? Do you think
manga creators
have any control over
what happens in the anime?
Uh... They don't?
Yeah, I thought that
was common knowledge...
Nelly...
Hey, I didn't know
that either...