Somehow, the princess snuck out
of the executive building
without an escort.
She's likely headed for the
residential block of the bund;
where the developers live.
Go find her!
Geez...
Mailman, Mailman
Do your duty.
Send this letter
To my cutie.
Don't you stop
And don't you delay.
It has to get to her
Right away.
How many days is
it gonna take?
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
You can do it...!
Six...
Seven....
You're not very good
at jumping rope.
I just need a little
more practice!
I'll show you!
The next time I
jump I swear to you
that I will cross the
10 jump threshold!
But you can't
even make it to 8!
I guess you've
got a point...
Then I'll make it to 10.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
[Music]
Since revealing herself
to the human race,
Princess Mina Tepes,
the supposed vampire ruler,
has repeatedly given
the same statement
each time she's
been questioned.
The only exception being
her sworn testimony
before parliament.
She's just announced
that she will be holding
a press conference
to set the record straight.
As you ordered,
all evidence of the attack
has been cleared...
And Nanami Shinonome is being
treated as an absentee.
Does Akira know the truth?
No ma'am, we've completely
covered our tracks.
Well done.
Hey Princess,
sorry to interrupt,
but Nelly asked me to
bring you a fresh towel.
Thank you, Akira...
You can leave
it on the chair.
This doesn't make
you uncomfortable?
Not in the least.
I've come to realize
you're just messing with me.
Well, I think...
If the special
zone is established
it would be an unprecedented
event and a story
any journalist
would die for.
Tell us what you think
about Princess Mina Tepes,
the vampire ruler.
I'll refrain,
but at this time,
I will say that
my opinion may change
depending upon the outcome
of the press conference.
I don't know about this...
You sure it's a good idea?
Well...
look who's suddenly concerned
about my well-being.
Please don't do that.
You know how much I hate the
smell of that damn shade gel.
You're so mean...
We're doing our utmost
to ensure security.
All members of the press
coming onto the bund
are being checked thoroughly.
Their personal effects
are being inspected
for foreign objects,
and they're undergoing
physical examinations.
We're testing...
to ensure that
they're all human.
Hello?
Princess.
I was wondering when
you'd show up, old fox.
Your timing is impeccable.
It's been a long time...
dear Juneau.
Dear Princess...
Please know that I, Juneau
the Marquis of Dermaille...
am pleased to look upon your
lovely visage once again.
I see you haven't given up
your tongue twisting
manner of speech...
Tell me... what brings you
all this way, old friend?
May we speak privately...?
This is not a discussion
I would care for your
guard dogs to overhear.
The Earth clan are
dignified knights...
They have been protecting the
royal family for centuries...
You should not
speak of them
in such a disrespectful
manner.
So... the princess has
resorted to guard dogs
and a henchwoman
of lowly blood!
You heard what he said.
I came here to assist the
princess, not to bicker.
My soldiers will protect
her from this point forward.
I suggest you call off
your dogs, my lady.
And why don't you go
back to the forest...?
Return to whence you came
from and find a new master!
Who the hell is
that old man?
Juneau, the Marquis
of Dermaille...
He's the head of a
line of nobles...
ones who serve the
Tepes royal family.
I hope you'll forgive
me, Sir Wolf...
I never should've given
in to his provocations.
I know that's
what he wanted.
He must have felt the
development of the bund...
was simply too important an
event to be overlooked...
I assume he's come here to
secure his own interests...
which puts us in an
advantageous position.
Yes, that's true.
And if that's the case...
we need only do what is
expected, nothing more...
Lady Vera.
Not to interfere,
but have you and Sir Wolf had
an opportunity to talk yet?
No, we haven't...
I was told he's my father,
but I don't have
any memory of him.
I gotta say...
this whole thing's
caught me off guard.
How?
I didn't think vampire society
would be so complicated.
It's really not too
difficult to understand...
You see, the royal family
has absolute authority...
Therefore, we have
constant battles
between lineages that hope
to gain that power.
The princess ardently desires
to develop this bund...
I will not allow anyone to take
advantage of the situation
or prevent that
from happening.
I will do whatever
it takes...
to make it happen...
Anything at all.
Can I ask you something?
Why are you so
devoted to Mina?
Well, because she
means everything to me.
Now let me ask you
something, Akira.
Do you think you're worthy
of being a servant
to the princess?
Do you think you'll be able to
live up to her expectations?
I'm just going to do
all I can for right now.
I don't know if I'm
worthy or not...
I don't...
But I made a promise
to her a long time.
Those are property of
the Marquis of Dermaille.
So they're
already arriving.
Geez, they just
keep coming...
I know and this is
just the beginning.
There's just so many...
The scoundrel who
attacked the princess
in front of you
the other day.
He was a vampire... correct?
Yeah...
The thought of a vampire
threatening her life
is completely inconceivable.
Why? Because she has
absolute authority?
No, it's more
complicated than that.
Why has the princess
chosen this place...?
She doesn't belong in the
far reaches of Asia...
It's unthinkable...!
I cannot allow it!
My lord!
What?!
C4...?!
Do we know who?!
Well, what do you mean
"more complicated"?
The death of the princess
would be catastrophic for us...
It... would mean the end
of the vampire race.
Interesting ...
The wind's starting
to pick up.
We're coming to you live
from the Central Management
Center on Tokyo Landfill #0.
An unprecedented press
conference with Mina Tepes
is being held here today.
Everyone is waiting
with anticipation
to hear the message of
the ruler of the vampires
and the owner
of this island.
I'd like to take
this opportunity
to thank each of you for
accepting my invitation.
I promise to answer
all of your questions
to the best of my ability.
So you may ask to
your hearts' content.
The conference
has begun...
This blunder of
theirs is a disgrace.
We'd better get
going, Vera...
We've gotta go
clean up their mess.
It has been discovered
that one of the agents
I brought along with me
has gone missing...
We are attempting to locate
his whereabouts now.
And you think this
man is responsible
for stealing the bomb?
Yes... That is my suspicion...
He was a newly
recruited agent
who joined shortly
before our departure.
Therefore, I am unfamiliar
with his background.
So you're saying, you
have no idea who he is?
Yes, ma'am...
I'm truly sorry,
but your announcement
of the press conference
caught me by surprise.
If I had been
told in advance,
I would have had the time
to conduct a more
thorough screening
of our new agents.
A deadly weapon
has gone missing...
The princess is at
risk because of you!
Silence, wench...!
Although his background
is unknown...
at least we know that
the person suspected
of stealing the
bomb is a vampire.
You can deny it
all you want,
but the reality is that
there are vampires out there
who would harm
our mistress.
I realize the severity
of the situation.
The princess is in danger
and I am partially at fault...
However, simply knowing that
the suspect is a vampire
will help us to keep
her protected.
Your logic doesn't
make any sense!
I've heard enough.
The press conference will
go on as scheduled...
Dermaille, you will remain
in charge of security
as I have ordered.
Yes, ma'am.
Princess...
Damn it... I can't
believe she trusts him.
So... any word on the bomb?
We've been searching,
but we haven't
had any luck.
It's gonna be
difficult to find him.
There are so many
places to hide,
since nobody's really
moved here yet.
He has to come out
sooner or later.
Judging by the
timing of the theft,
I think it's safe to assume
that he intends
to use the bomb
during the press
conference.
The question is:
where is he hiding?
No way...
First of all, on behalf
of all of us here,
I would like to thank you for
answering our questions today.
I was wondering if you
could tell us about
establishing the
Special Zone.
How are you able to
get the government...
Uh, Princess?
My apologies...
I had imagined the
first question
would be something
more fundamental.
I was expecting "Are
you really a vampire?"
Something like that.
I assume after the
"Scales of Astrea" show
there's no need for me to
answer such questions.
It seems that program
turned many into believers.
However, I'd guess that
there are probably more
skeptics here today.
But that's to be expected.
As journalists, you
forsake sensationalism
and deliver the hard facts.
I assume what you'd
really like to know
is how a little girl
from a foreign country
plans to negotiate
to obtain this bund
from the Japanese
government...
So, shall I start there?
Exactly!
That's the question
we've all been asking.
She must be running
some kind of scheme.
What does she
mean by "bund"?
Like the one in Shanghai.
The answer to that
is one word...
Money.
This government's failed
economic policies
have caused the national
deficit to skyrocket
to one quadrillion yen.
I am prepared to assume
the entire amount
as soon as the
Special Zone is approved.
As I'm sure you're aware,
this country's economy
has been on the
rise recently...
And do you know why?
Just prior to
this upswing,
we transferred many of your
failing corporations
into our control.
We are also responsible
for many of your large scale,
public works projects,
including Landfill #0.
We did this for you to
lay the groundwork...
You see, by helping
you grow stronger,
we thereby improved
our chances
of getting you to
help us in return.
Let me put this bluntly,
if the Special Zone
is not approved...
I'll have no choice but to
withdraw our financial support.
That's blackmail!
Why should we continue
to give to someone
who refuses to
return the favor?
I'm sorry, but we did
not come to this country
to be charitable.
I would like to take
this opportunity
to clarify what this means
and what I'm asking of
the Japanese government
and its citizens.
I currently have ownership
of Landfill #0...
Meaning we have exclusive
land and building
rights on the bund...
However, I would
like this land...
to be recognized as leased
territory belonging to us.
I demand that there be no
term limit on the lease.
The vampire bund will
belong to us indefinitely.
It will be a settlement
much like Hong Kong
and Shanghai once were.
Land that exists
within a country,
but is actually a separate
nation entirely.
We will not be Japanese,
but a chaotic mixture
of different cultures.
That is my desire...
I want to create a
kingdom of vampires,
by vampires, for vampires...!
On the vampire bund!
What do you want at
a time like this?
-Old man!
-Old man...?
Who is this?
The members of
the press...
did you check them as
they came in today?
Don't be ridiculous, boy...!
Of course we checked them...
Each person was
physically searched
and their
equipment examined.
Are you sure
they're all human?!
Did you test them at the
door to the interview
to make sure there're
no vampires?
That's not necessary.
We tested everyone
coming onto the island.
What is it, Akira...!
What's going on?
We have to hurry...
I smelled shade gel on
one of the reporters
who walked past us.
But we ran tests
to ensure that everyone
who arrived was human.
Someone must've changed.
You don't mean...
That's the only
explanation...
One of those
reporters was human
when they got to the island,
but they somehow became
a vampire while here.
Why would anyone do that?!
Because a vampire
can hide a bomb...
Get it...?
Remove a few organs and it'd
be easy to smuggle inside.
Lady Vera...
We found a large amount of
blood in the hotel room
of one of the reporters
at the conference.
We've also come across
internal organs
that our suspect has
recently removed.
Who is it?
CNN newscaster...
Nicole Edelman.
Miss Tepes,
may I ask how you were able to
afford the astronomical sum of
one quadrillion yen?
My ancestors have
quietly been amassing
an unparalleled fortune
for centuries...
We were already wealthy
when your people were
working with stone tools...
So splurging on
something like this...
would hardly even make
a dent in our finances.
The thought of that much
money is incomprehensible.
And how can you expect
us to believe you?
After all, this is
based on the premise
that you're
actually a vampire.
I knew we would reach this
point sooner or later.
I'm at a loss right now...
I simply have no way to
prove to you all
that I am indeed a vampire...
Surely you don't expect me to
expose myself to sunlight...
I could drive a stake
through my heart,
but that'd only prove
my own mortality.
I know... I could always just
suck the blood of one of you
to prove my point.
My, my...
I never would've imagined
that I'd actually have a taker.
Are you really who
you claim to be...?
Are you the ruler
of the vampires...
I don't need to
suck your blood...
Because it's obvious
that someone has
already beat me to it.
Vera!
Rip her open!
There's no time!
It's already
been activated!
Hurry and disarm
it, Akira!
One of the first things young
Beowulf soldiers are taught is
how to disarm a bomb.
But I don't remember
any of that stuff!
We must leave, Princess...
It's too dangerous!
Calm down, fools!
Quiet!
Are you there, Wolf?
-Can you hear me?
-Yes, ma'am.
-You know what to do.
-Right...
Akira...! Go to elevator 3!
We have temporarily
disabled the car.
I want you to throw the
bomb down the shaft!
It will be fine
down there...
Do it!
Open... the doors!
It exploded and that's it...?
Hey, Vera...?
What the hell's down there?
You'll find out
soon enough.
Surely that was enough to
prove to all of you skeptics
that vampires do exist.
What you have seen...
and what you have heard...
spread it throughout
the world!
Tell everyone what
happened here today.
This is our world,
the world of darkness...
Where blood and death
rule above all else.
But there is no need
for any of you to worry.
For as long as you remain
good neighbors to us...
I promise that we will
never be a threat to you
or to your loved ones.
But if you ever
disappoint me,
the story will be different...
That is all I have to
say to you for now...
I bid you goodnight.
You may return
to your world.
Prime Minister...
The bipartisan coalition
has just submitted
the Special Zone
Establishment Bill!
Sorry Princess,
but I'm not so sure about
that old Marquis guy...
Shouldn't you
have fired him,
or at least demoted him?
Don't worry
about Dermaille.
Killing me and
ending our race
wouldn't benefit
him in any way.
Besides, he would never
have the courage to do so.
Your success on this
mission means that
Juneau can no longer
disparage you...
Keep up the good
work, my friend.
Hold on...
You mean you meant
for this to happen?
I can't tell you how
much it meant to me,
seeing you out there
fighting for me,
without any regard for
your own well-being.
That's the Akira Kaburagi...
that I've come
to know so well.
I guess that means Dermaille
wasn't the only one being
tested today, was he?
I am fully aware
that you've had considerable
doubts about me...
Consider us even.
Seems like the more
time I spend with you...
the more confused I get.
One minute you're blackmailing
an entire nation...
and the next
you're pouting,
because you can't jump rope.
Hold on...
How do you know that?!
I saw everything;
even your promise to
"make it all the way to 10."
What...?
The only reason I even
played that ridiculous game
is because those children
insisted upon it!
You know...
It was nice to see you...
like that.
I mean, watching
you play jump rope
with those human children...
It was almost
like you were...
Those children aren't human,
they're fangless vampires.
They're members
of our race
who have chosen to
remove their fangs
and who have
rejected the act
of sucking the
blood of humans.
In fact, there are many
"fangless" among the volunteers
who are working hard to
help establish the bund.
Although they have
become vampires,
they don't want to lose
touch with their humanity.
Unfortunately, because of
the way they've chosen
to live their lives,
they are persecuted by both
humans and vampires alike.
But once the bund
is established...
they will have a place
that they can call home...
Finally.
Is that why you're
building the bund?
For these "fangless" vampires?
Sadly, no.
I wish it were.
Suddenly, the existence of
vampires became a reality...
Some chose to dismiss
it as a strange incident
in a far-off corner
of the Orient.
Others scoffed,
claiming the attack at
the press conference
was nothing more
than fiction
created by a
television show.
Although outwardly they
seemed skeptical, deep inside,
everyone was now
forced to believe.
Little did we know then,
but the ripples caused
by this quiet shock
were silently and steadily
closing in on Akira and I...
And there was nothing
we could do...
to prepare ourselves
for what would happen.
[Music]
Dance with the vampire maids!
Part 4!
So what's troubling
you, young man?
I have amnesia and it's
causing problems for me.
I don't even recognize
my own father!
I'm just not sure I can
keep up with everyone.
I'm lost without
my memories-
Don't let them get to you...!
So you have amnesia...
big deal!
That's a part of what
makes you who you are!
Maybe it'll get
you out of work!
If I were you, I'd milk
it as long as you can.
Uh...
Okay, take care!
Next patient!
Our coworker isn't taking
her work seriously.
What do you think
we should do?
I think you should
tell your coworker...
We're talking about you, dummy!