[Music]
What the hell...
He can't be...
He's one... of
the Earth Clan.
Oh, Akira!
Man, that was a
crazy dream...
Where am I?
Wait a minute...
so that wasn't
a dream...?
Akira...
This isn't a dream...
is it?
Tell me, Akira...
What is my name?
You are... Princess Mina.
Good and what is
your full name?
Akira Kaburagi Regendorf.
Now tell me who you are.
I'm a werewolf...
of the Earth Clan.
Excellent!
We bid you good
morning, Your Highness!
Although technically...
it's not morning anymore!
Who are you people?
These girls
are my maids...
Good morning Nelly,
Nero and Nella...
Now get to work!
Your wish is our command!
Move your hands...
They're just going
to get in the way.
No it's fine, I can
manage on my own!
Are you refusing to
let me do my job?
Princess, please!
Would you call off the
scary maid lady...?!
What the heck is
going on here?!
What do you
think...? Is it 'me'?
That outfit you're
wearing...!
Pretty sharp, don't you think?
She was like a
summer thunderstorm
that strikes
without warning...
bringing chaos to
a quiet afternoon.
Hello, my name
is Mina Tepes...
I've recently arrived
in your country...
I am so pleased to make
all of your acquaintances.
This isn't gonna
end well...
That was the day
everything changed...
The day our peaceful school
suddenly became a stage...
for the dazzling
rondo of the vampires.
[Music]
Teen Wolf Is
that really her?!
[Music]
What's she doing here?!
Check it out!
What?!
Princess... You can go ahead
and pick your seat now.
A word, Sister Laura?
Uh... Yes?!
You don't have to worry...
I promise that I'm
not going to bite you.
Well, it just so
happens that one of my
royal servants is a
student in this class...
If you have no objections,
I would like to be
seated next to him.
Your royal... servant?
Correct...
Akira Kaburagi.
What?! No way!
Seriously?!
Sister... My apologies,
I intended today only
as a greeting...
I'll stop interrupting
your class.
Akira... I want
you to come
to the Chairwoman's
Office after class...
Understood?
Yeah, got it...
Oh...
Okay, what the hell?!
When'd you become that
vampire's servant?!
Yeah, man, what did the
princess mean by that?!
You told us you didn't
give a crap about vampires!
Butt out guys, I got this!
Hey, I think we have a
right to know... Ryohei!
Yeah, tell us!
What's she want with you?!
Whoa!
Toilet.
-Nice, what was that?
-He ran away!
Akira! Wait!
That is so not fair!
Spill it, Yuki...
Did you know about
this...? He trusts you.
May I have your
attention please...
Addressing all student
council members;
an emergency council meeting
will be commencing shortly...
All executives and class
officers, please report
to the student council
office immediately.
Yuki, wait!
I repeat... Addressing all
student council members...
Damn, guys!
Get off my back!
I could use an explanation
for all of this, too.
I've gotten some of
my memory back...
but nowhere
near all of it!
Next year...
on your seventeenth
birthday,...
In accordance with
our ancestral vows...
you will be remanded to
the princess' service...
where you will
remain at her side.
This assignment...
will serve as a litmus
test to gauge your ability
to handle responsibility.
Do your best.
I know, Dad.
And I will.
It must've been
after that when I--
Damn it...!
That's where it's
still all fuzzy...
I thought that I might
find you up here.
Yeah... Hey...!
With the exception
of the administration
and the instructors...
everything at this academy
is run by the
students themselves!
Our esteemed chairwoman
founded the school
on this very principle...!
And to simply
ignore precedent
and allow vampires to enroll
without student approval...
Is unthinkable!
I'm taking this
directly to her
and putting an end to it!
Wait, directly to who?
So you're saying...
the chairwoman
is actually here?!
They say she hasn't
even shown her face
since the day she
opened the school!
Don't question her.
I'm sure the President's
thought this out.
You have a good
reason for doing this?
Or are you just
that scared...
Do not be afraid, people!
As we speak, the
rest of the world
is being overrun by
these bloodsuckers!
As the student council
it's our duty to make sure
the same thing doesn't
happen to our beloved school!
Oh... So you're not?
Not me...
I swear I'm not
a vampire, Yuki.
But then...
How are you the
princess's servant?
Well, it's like a
family obligation...
I don't know. It's
kinda hard to explain.
What, you mean like an
arranged marriage or something?
It's not like that...! My
dad ordered me to do it...
Not that I really
have any idea
what the point of it all is...
So, your memory...
is it starting
to come back?
Yeah ...
It's still just bits
and pieces, though...
But...
At least now...
I guess I'm finally
beginning to remember
who I really am.
Or what I am...
Anyway, forget I
said anything...
I'm sorry I've had you
worried all this time.
It's okay...
I'm glad for you...
Really.
Thank you.
Well, I, uh, better
get a move on...
I've made her wait
long enough...
See ya later, Yuki!
Where is he?
I would imagine that he's
still quite confused
at the moment...
All of this happened to
him so quickly, after all.
Yeah, you're right...
Guess it's to be expected.
What do you people
think you're doing...?!
You can't just barge in!
It's my understanding that
the chairwoman is in there!
What should we do?
It's okay...
Let her in.
We beg your pardon.
Miss Chairwoman...
Why have you
permitted a vampire
to enroll in this school?!
I'm sorry,
but I didn't catch
your name, young lady.
Student Council President
Nanami Shinonome...
So tell me... Is this monster
blackmailing you or something?!
Is that the question you
marched down here to ask?
Yes... I want to know...
I understand...
And your concern
is duly noted.
You heard the
young lady...
Anything to say on the
matter, Madam Chairwoman?
Obviously, I can't
blackmail myself...
Nor would I, as
attending this academy
was the reason I built
it in the first place.
I am the founder and
also the chairwoman
of this
prestigious academy...
I am Mina Tepes.
No way!
Yeah, very funny!
You can't be
the chairwoman,
I mean, you're just a kid!
Have you already
forgotten what I am...?
I have lived decades longer
than the three of
you have combined.
-C'mon! You've gotta be
-That's enough!
Of course...
It all makes sense now.
I knew there was something
strange about this school...
How all the windows are
made of polarized glass...
and the gym was
built underground...
It's all because...
You're a clever girl.
I have only recently
arrived on campus,
but I am happy to see
the school has grown
into a valued
place of learning.
The students are cheerful
and self-reliance
fills the halls...
I can't thank you
enough for your efforts.
Because of you, this will
be the perfect school
for our children
when the vampire bund
is finally established.
You can't be serious!
We didn't fight
tooth and nail
for the betterment
of this school,
just so you could turn it
into a den for you people!
For vampires!
I hear you want to be
a lawyer one day,
Miss Shinonome...
Is that correct?
We have no privacy,
either...?!
Serve out your student
council term without incident,
and I'll
provide a scholarship
and recommendation to the
university of your choice.
You're horrible!
All right, Miss
Shinonome...
Are you finished
with your questions?
I am not.
Then I'll have to ask you
to come back another time...
The chairwoman has a
very busy schedule...
Damn you.
Hey... Sorry I'm late, uh--
I guess I've caught
you at a bad time...
Akira...! One moment!
So I take it you really want
me gone from this school?
Yes!
In that case, how
about a small wager?
You gave this to
me, right Yuki?
So then...
does that mean...
that we're...?
This is Student Council
President
Nanami Shinonome.
By this time, I'm sure you've
all heard that Mina Tepes,
the self-proclaimed
ruler of the vampires,
has transferred to
our academy.
The Student Council is adamantly
opposed to this outrage!
And so, in direct
response...
I use my council authority
to announce a boycott
on afternoon classes!
Furthermore,
after negotiating
with the school's
administration...
We've reached an
agreement and succeeded
in winning a major concession.
If we can catch
her servant...
second-year student,
Akira Kaburagi...
the princess will withdraw
her transfer to our school.
My fellow students...!
Allowing vampires into our
school is reckless...!
It must not be permitted!
You all know what
you have to do...!
Capture Akira Kaburagi...!
Protect the sanctity
of this institution...!
And protect our
peaceful academy!
Also...
Whoever catches
him will be rewarded
by the student council.
We will give the
winner's class,
or designated
club, extra funding!
Hell yeah!
Damn it, Saijo...!
By doing that,
we're just stooping
to the vampire's level.
People need something
tangible to fight for.
Well, I suppose
you're right....
Let's get started.
Yuzuru.
Please give me the strength
to get through this.
For cryin' out loud...
Talk about fuel
for the fire,
this is like pourin'
oil on hot embers...
You can do it, Akira.
And you can bite
me, Princess.
You're not coming
down with a cold,
are you Princess?
No... We aren't susceptible
to the common cold.
I wish I was so fortunate.
As for this meeting, I
believe it should prove
to be a watershed moment
in trying to pass the
Special Zone
Establishment Bill...
I must admit to you,
I have high hopes!
Well... It's time to set
foot on the battlefield.
Akira Kaburagi's been
spotted in Building Number Two!
Got it!...
I'm on my way!
Seriously? Wanted signs...?
When did anyone have
time to make these,
much less
put 'em up?
My cell phone!
Uh... hi!
Later!
I found him!
Hey, Akira! Over here!
For Princess
Mina's sake...!
Don't let 'em getcha, dude!
You can do it!
Thanks, I owe ya one!
Wow, you student council
executive officers
are really good at your
jobs, aren't you?
Found you!
Oh, come on!
There is only one thing I
want from you gentlemen today.
And that is the
ratification of the
Special Zone
Establishment Bill,
which the esteemed Mr. surugi's
faction has submitted...
It's that simple.
If only your politicians had
the spines to be so decisive...
Japan would not be in the
dire financial straits
it is today.
Vera. Show them what I mean.
Ma'am.
I would like you gentlemen
to take a look at this first...
Then we can discuss
the matter further.
Impossible!
That's preposterous!
Is this accurate?!
I assure you, it is...
So what are your
thoughts, gentlemen?
This is insane...!
Why won't they just
let up for a second?!
My club needs funding!
Damn it...! It's
always about the money!
Of course it is!
I can assure you, gentlemen,
that I am not bluffing...
Approve the
bund's creation,
or I'll withdraw
these corporations.
I'll find out what
you're up to...
I swear it!
We can't allow that...!
We would be ruined!
Well, that was the plan...
Those companies were
strategically chosen
to do the most damage.
I'm sorry, Princess, we're
not able to give you
a definitive answer
right away...
Give us some time to look
over these documents
and we'll get back to you.
So naïve...
You're all so
incredibly naïve!
You're certainly
welcome to waste time
and avoid the situation,
but it will not
turn in your favor.
In fact, you will only drive
yourselves into a corner,
as the clock
ticks away,
and you run out of
places to try and hide!
There's no escape now!
You, gentlemen, are
this nation's elite...
You, few, determine
the fate of the land
in accordance to the
will of the people!
You should just
give it up already!
Will you grant
our proposal?
Or will you turn us
away and make things
more difficult for yourselves?
It's your decision.
Where'd he go?
I think I lost 'em...
That was
impressive, Akira.
You... you saw all that?
I guess it's true, you
really have lost your memory.
Wow... That flustered look is
really doing something for me.
You're the princess's
servant, huh?
Do you also "serve"
her in the nighttime?
You kiddin' me?!
Then explain this.
I added my contact info...
That way you can
get a hold of me.
Mei Ren?
I am beat!
You did have a
workout... of sorts.
You can say that again...
So... how was your
meeting today?
It was a joke...
I think the student
council might have
more backbone than the
politicians of this country.
So... How are you feeling...?
Has the rest of your
memory filled back in yet?
Nope, it's still
full of holes.
I feel like there's...
so much I don't remember.
Even... the promise you made
to me seven years ago?
I made a promise...?
Doesn't ring any bells...
Oh, I see...
Well, I guess it's
to be expected...
Your memory has only
started to come back to you...
But if you just
give it some time...
I'm sure you'll
begin to remember
everything more clearly...
You've always been
light-hearted and carefree-
You dare... to fool me!
Take this!
Ow! Okay,
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Cut it out!
I'm glad to have
you back,...
Akira.
Me too.
Thanks, Princess.
Man, Nanami's been workin'
herself to the bone.
I appreciate you
walking me home.
Not a problem...
I wouldn't wanna leave you
all by yourself out here...
So, it must've
been quite a shock
to find out about
Akira today...
There's something I think
about to this very day...
Back then, I was so
focused on Akira
it never even
occurred to me...
I honestly
didn't have time
to worry about
anything else...
I can't help but wonder
what would've happened
if I had waited for Nanami...
I wonder if things would
have turned out differently...
I managed all
right today...
but I can only imagine...
that things are gonna
get tougher from here.
Never fear... I have a plan.
So... tell me...
Why did you go out of your
way to visit the school
while there's so much
other chaos going on?
What are you
up to exactly?
I'm sorry, Akira...
But that's none
of your concern.
No!
[Music]
"Dance with the Vampire Maids"
Part Three!
Must! Have! Extra! Funding!
C'mon guys! I
can't believe you!
Unleashing the flood!
Now I'll attack with
Strawberry Poison Frog Arrows!
That's kinda lame.
Okay, Strawberry
Poison Frog Blow Darts!
Really? Frogs...?
How 'bout
something flashier?
Super Earth
Destruction Bomb!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Now you ask?!
Seriously!
Oh, for crying out loud!