I promise that
I'll protect you.
Princess!
No... way...
I'm going to kill you...
'The hell?
Did you have
another nightmare?
I guess...
What're you doing here?!
I've been so busy
lately we haven't had
an opportunity to
spend time together...
so I decided to come
by and see you now.
But you had the
nerve to be asleep
when I snuck into
your room...
So instead of waking you
I decided to sit here
and admire you
while you slept.
You were watching me
sleep? That's creepy.
Well... I like it.
Don't get me wrong, you've
grown into a handsome man...
but when you're sleeping,
you look just like
the little boy
that I met so
many years ago.
Hey I was wondering...
What are those
weird flowers
that are blooming in
the greenhouse?
They're cleomes.
I used to have a
little hiding place...
and I had a beautiful
flower garden there...
In fact, all of the
flowers in the greenhouse
were transplanted
from that garden.
Cleomes...
So tell me, Akira...
Are you going to be
available this weekend?
Yeah, why?
Well, I thought...
Since establishment of the bund
is finally underway and all...
I thought maybe...
I thought maybe I could
take a few days off
to spend with you.
Want to go look at
flowers with me?
I would love to...
Oh no...! I'm sorry, but
I have plans this weekend.
What?!
But I'm totally free
next weekend...!
We can go wherever
you want to!
Do you promise me?
Yeah.
[Music]
It happened on a
peaceful afternoon
after the terrorism turmoil
had seemingly ended...
Everything appeared to be
calm within the bund...
This place is
beautiful, isn't it?
It is... But are you
sure that it's okay...
for us to join you?
Of course it is.
Though you are a servant
to the princess,
when you're not on duty,
you are considered
a friend...
You're welcome here.
Nanami was now living with
Yuzuru in the vampire bund.
Princess Mina had taken
her in as one of her maids,
and she was also allowed
to return to school.
Are you becoming
accustomed to it?
Yeah... It takes some
getting used to at first,
but I'd do anything
to be with Nanami...
I can't thank you
and Akira enough.
That is so
incredibly sweet...
You two are precious.
We started to believe
that our lives
were finally peaceful...
It felt like all was
well with the world...
So where is Akira, anyway?
I don't know.
I invited him to come,
but he declined...
He told me that he had to
take care of some business.
But suddenly our tale
took a cruel, new turn...
Oh well, he's missing out!
We can have plenty
of fun without him!
Yeah!
The events that unfolded
between that moment
and the following morning
scarred each of us forever;
me... Princess Mina...
and Akira...
The memory of that day
would haunt all of us
for years to come...
I'm surprised...
When I called you,
I honestly didn't think
you were going to meet me.
You're such an
obedient werewolf.
Well, it's not like I
had much of a choice.
You've helped me
out in the past
so I kind of owed you one.
Are you saying that you
feel indebted to me?
'Indebted' is such
a strong word...
Anyway, I've got
some questions
that only you can
answer for me.
From the top...
I'm thirty-two...
twenty-three...
thirty-three.
Uh...
And just so you
know, I'm a virgin.
You don't believe
me...? I'm not lying...
However, you
could be my first?
What is wrong
with you...?!
We're in public in
the middle of the day!
So you only do it
at night...? Pervert.
Just who are you
calling a pervert, huh?!
Do you like it?
Why, you!
Catch me if you can!
Damn it!
This water feels great...!
You should come and
join me, Akira!
Lunatic.
Looks like I won our
little game of tag.
Yeah, whatever.
-Mei Ren, your shirt-
-What...?
Uh-oh...
I can't believe you...
Why aren't you wearing
a bra or something...?!
You can see right through.
I guess you caught me.
C'mon, let's
get outta here.
Geez, don't you
have any modesty?
Did you seriously think I was
gonna be cool with that?
Well, I certainly didn't
expect to get yelled at
for giving you a peek!
Are you jealous?
You don't want any other
guys seeing the goods, huh?
Alright, I think you've had
enough fun at my expense...
Can we get down
to business now?
Looks like someone can't
handle being teased.
You're no fun, Akira.
Just leave me
alone, would ya?
Those flowers...
I've seen 'em before.
They're cleomes.
They're different
from other flowers...
because they only
bloom at night.
They bloom at night?
They go by another
name as well...
Go ahead and take a
closer look at them...
Do they remind
you of anything?
They kind of look like...
flowers with
butterflies on them.
Exactly...
They're Butterfly Flowers.
You know, there's a
heartbreaking legend about 'em.
It's said that there
once was a butterfly
that was searching for love.
One day he came upon
another beautiful butterfly
and it was love
at first sight.
But the butterfly
soon realized
that his love remained perfectly
still on top of a flower,
his beloved never moved
a single inch...
Even so, he continued to
woo his love day and night,
while his life slowly
slipped away from him...
The butterfly eventually
ran out of strength
and fell to the ground...
Meanwhile, his love's
wings fluttered in the wind...
Although his beloved
looked like another butterfly,
turns out it was,
in fact, a flower.
A cleome that
simply stood there
with its petal swaying
in the breeze.
A Butterfly Flower...
That reminds me of...
Are you having
a good time?
Yeah! I know that it's
not possible but...
it would be even nicer...
if we could be
out in the sun.
Well, we can make
that happen...
Believe it or not,
this castle was built
with a special function
that allows sunlight
in with just the
touch of a button.
You're so mean!
Don't tease me like that!
Cut it out!
You know... I thought
vampires were...
supposed to be more
stylish than humans.
Are you making a snide
remark about my swim suit?
No, it's just not what
I expected...!
I don't know...
when you transformed
you just looked so-
I asked you to never speak of
what you saw that day, Yuki.
I've been in this immature
form for quite a while now.
As a result, most people
treat me like a child...
so I've taken to
dressing like one...
even though I find
it embarrassing
and totally out of character.
I find... even Akira
treats me like a child,
though he knows better.
But... Why don't you
like the other form?
Oh, I do...
I wish I could stay
that way forever...
I dream of someday being a
size that matches Akira...
then we'll finally...
be able to embrace.
Although I may complain
about my childish appearance,
I am truly grateful
for this body...
It's kept me from doing
the unthinkable...
And it gives Akira...
a reason to
stay by my side.
That makes sense...
What?!
Princess...! A message
from the Port Authority!
Three ships - the
Abokyu, the Kremlin,
and the Sanssouci
-are currently
approaching the bund!
I learned a lot today.
You really know
your flowers, huh?
No... it's just that cleomes
were the favorite flower
of someone who was
important to me.
I gotta tell you,
I'm surprised that you
weren't able to recognize
those flowers yourself...
It's obvious that your memory
isn't completely back yet.
The main reason I asked you
to meet me here today, Akira,
was so that I could
assess your memory loss,
see how much of
it has returned.
Why is that?
I'm sorry, but I
can't tell you.
All I'll say is that
when you do remember,
blood will flow.
Just who are you, Mei Ren?
I've already
told you that.
Well I don't believe you.
That doesn't
really matter...
Just know that you're not
all alone in this world...
I understand you
more than anyone.
More than any human...
more than any vampire...
I'm the only one who
truly understands you.
What do you mean?
Very soon you'll be
faced with a dilemma
the likes of which you've
never experienced before.
I'm on your side...
I wanna see you
survive, if possible.
Akira...
The Three Clans?
That's correct.
They are the three living
"true blood" lineages...
Long ago, hundreds of
vampire clans ruled
various territories
throughout the world.
We prospered far and wide.
Unfortunately, only
three of those clans
have been able to survive...
Li, Ivanovic
and Rozenmann...
They are my subjects
and my blood relatives.
They're also... my nemeses...
Nemeses?
There is an internal
feud of sorts
that's been going on
for centuries now.
Because we live for
eternity our quarrels...
are quite lengthy and
not easily abated.
So what do you think
of my fighting outfit?
Fighting outfit?
There's no need
to worry...
It won't get physical...
Causing harm to me would
mean the end of our race...
they don't have the
nerve to touch me.
They have no
power over me...
They've reduced
themselves...
to plotting, intimidation,
and deception.
In their minds...
another word for
ruler is "trickster".
Princess...
Shouldn't you wait
until Akira comes back?
I can't!
This is my problem...
I cannot allow him
to get involved.
But why not...? He
can protect you!
I've spared him from
this aspect of my life
and I shall continue
to do so...
There are some things even
he doesn't need to know.
Don't worry, Yuki...
I will not lose to them...
I promise.
Good luck, Princess...
What?!
She told me not to
say anything to you,
but I thought you
should know...
Is this what you
were talking about?
'Fraid so... You're
gonna go anyway...
-aren't you?
-Yeah.
Tell me...
Why are you so fixated
on the Princess?
Because I made a promise.
Is that all?
No...
I knew it...
Don't forget.
No matter how much the
butterfly may wish for it...
He can never be
with the flower.
How good of you gentlemen
to pay a visit to my new home.
I hope you can forgive us for
stopping by unannounced.
We waited to be invited
to the housewarming
with baited breath...
but our impatience
got the best of us.
Shall I assume the invitation
was lost in the mail?
My sincerest
apologies, gentlemen...
I'm afraid it's been one
troublesome incident
after another around here.
You mean Telomere?
The world around us is
continually changing
despite the fact that you
sit in your castles...
simply glaring
at one another.
I find it quite
amusing you're using
the Telomere as an
excuse, Princess.
It's become quite obvious
that you've chosen to ignore us,
your guardians, as
you continue to push
your own plans forward.
Sorry, are you implying
that I should
ask the three of you
for permission
whenever I want
to do something?
Though we are blood relatives
I am still your master.
I kindly ask that you do not
interfere with my matters.
I've had enough
of your impudence!
Let's be honest,
though we belong to a
"true blood" lineage,
the royal family's power...
means very little anymore.
Your "ruler of
the vampires"
act can no longer
go on without us.
It is you three who
mean little now.
Let me ask you this...
You allowed this to become
the Tepes royal castle,
did you not?
Have you not permitted me
to live here as ruler,
all of this time,
without question?
You three have continually
tried to constrain me...
You have stood in my way
and reprimanded me
for my actions.
And yet, this castle was
built on my behalf...
Was it not?!
I am still here!
That, more than anything,
is proof of my rule
over not only you,
but all vampires.
Don't you see,
gentlemen...?
There is no one who
can rule over me!
You've become quite the
spitfire recently, haven't you?
I see your point...
And perhaps
you're right...
that there is no one among the
vampires who can control you.
However, even if
that is the case...
you still cannot defy the
principles of our lineage.
You haven't forgotten
about that, have you?
Of course you haven't,
my bride-to-be.
What do you mean I can't?!
Sorry, but it's
a direct order
from the princess herself...
Akira Kaburagi is not
allowed on the island.
Aw, man... This is ridiculous!
I'll just have
to call someone-
Hey, Vera...?
What does he mean by that?
As you know, you have
a responsibility
to the vampire race...
As the head of the
royal family,
you are entrusted with--
Believe me, I am
well aware of my duty.
I must partner with
another noble of the
"true blood" lineage...
and produce an heir that
will keep the lineage intact.
That's correct.
We four are the
only vampires left
who carry the bloodline
of the ancient clans.
And the only one among us who
can carry a child is you...
my dear, Princess Mina.
You will be forced
to marry one of us
and then bear that
man's child...
That is our lineage's
responsibility
to the vampire race...
It is our fate.
And I would never dare
to question fate...
You do realize
that this puts me
in quite a predicament...
If only there was a way
for this immature female body
to bear a child...
Then I would be happy
to go forth with my duty
and marry one
of you gentlemen.
Yes, so you have
continually said.
All the while, we three have
continued to circle around you,
patiently waiting
in a holding pattern.
We've grown weary
of playing that game,
Princess...
So we decided to make
things more interesting
by placing a little wager.
What kind of wager?
Well, we have heard there
is an Earth Clan pup
who's been stuck to
your side as of late.
Rumor has it the two of you
are quite fond of one another.
Akira has nothing
to do with this!
I'm told the dog is
currently in corridor
Put us through ...
I know that
you're watching.
Can you hear me, werewolf?
Upon our arrival
to the bund...
each of us released a deadly
assassin from our clan...
They've been ordered
to hunt you down.
We've chosen our strongest
and most vicious subordinates
to stand off against you.
None of their targets have
ever survived an attack.
Those voices!
The Three Clans?!
In case you hadn't already
noticed you are their target...
The beloved wolf pup
of Princess Mina.
The master of the assassin
who slays you by dawn...
Will be the winner
of our wager...
and shall marry
Princess Mina.
You should feel honored
to have been chosen
to take on such an
important role.
Now die.
Damn it!
Well... Let the dog
hunt begin, yes?
Stop it! Call off your
assassins at once!
I don't understand
why you're upset...
The boy is just
a lowly servant.
No, that's not true...!
Akira means much more to me-
Because he's
your beloved...?
You can't fool me, Princess.
He is nothing but
a lowly werewolf...
You cannot be with him...
It simply can't happen...
The two of you are separated
by lineage and lifespan...
It's impossible for you
to make a life together...
He is of the other world.
Princess, you
need to realize...
whether you like it or not,
you only have three options.
If you choose him over
us then you'll be turning
your back on the
entire vampire race.
But, the choice
is yours...
Akira...
No matter how much the
butterfly may wish for it...
He can never be
with the flower.
Don't let their
words get to you!
I'm gonna make it
through this...
I promise...
Princess!
If you gentlemen are
finished with your business...
you may retire
to the salon.
We're not finished.
No...
At the request of the
three noble lords...
And as required by the ancient
pact of the royal family...
I have been sent to
perform a purity inquiry.
[Music]
Dance with the
Vampire Maids!
Part 10!
Put your arm into it!
You can't shine
silverware like that!
Um... Okay.
Say "sir" before
and after you reply!
Sir! Yes, sir!
Tell me about yourself!
I'm a cute girl
with glasses!
You can do
better than that!
I'm a cute girl with
glasses and big boobs!
How old is your boyfriend?!
I said how old?!
Uh, way too young!
And what's his name?
-It's Yuzuru...
-Louder!
We're really
whipping her into shape!
The Maid Squad is
gonna be unstoppable!