- Rinmei: LUO CHANG'S BECOME
A CHARNEL HOUSE.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE WERE JUST HERE OURSELVES
NOT ALL THAT LONG AGO.
- FEELS LIKE A TRAP.
- YEAH THIS PLACE IS
WAY TOO QUIET.
- SOMETHING'S DEFINITELY POISED
TO CATCH US OFF GUARD.
TROUBLE OF THE WORST KIND
IS ALWAYS AFOOT
WHEN THE HAIRS ON THE BACK
OF MY NECK BRISTLE.
- ( growling )
- Koyo: WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
- ( theme song playing )
- Rinmei: THE SHEER NUMBER
OF THEM!
- DAMN IT! YOU'D THINK
MY INSTINCTS
WOULD LEAD ME ASTRAY
ONCE IN A WHILE.
- EVERY LAST ONE OF THESE POOR
SOULS CALLED THIS THEIR HOME.
- POOR SOULS.
LIKE LADY KOEI.
- HOSEI, I'M SORRY.
- MOWED DOWN OUT OF SPITE.
THEIR CORPSES BENT LIKE A REED
TO THAT BASTARD'S WHIM!
NO ONE DESERVES THAT.
NOT THE WORST OF US.
- THE ODDS ARE DECIDEDLY NOT IN
OUR FAVOR AGAINST SUCH A HORDE.
- TO HELL WITH ODDS. THEIR
DEFILEMENT ENDS RIGHT NOW.
EVERY ONE OF THEM
WILL REST IN PEACE!
- I FOR ONE SHARE IN
HOSEI'S NOBLE SENTIMENT.
- WE CAN'T LET THEM SUFFER.
WE HAVE TO AVENGE THEM
AND SET THEM FREE.
- CAI FEI PALACE IS UP AHEAD.
IN THE DEAD CENTER OF TOWN.
- LET'S DO THIS! FOLLOW ME!
- ( all yelling )
- LADY CHOKA.
- ALKAID MOVES TOWARD
THE INNER SANCTUM.
- TAITO. I SEE. SO HE
COULDN'T BE STOPPED.
- TELL ME, WOULD YOU KILL
A LOVED ONE AT KEIRO'S BEHEST?
OR DOES YOUR OWN LIFE NOT HOLD
A CANDLE TO FRIENDSHIP?
- I WILL NOT BE PERSUADED.
DUBHE, NO.
KEIRO'S BLOODY INDULGENCE IS
NOT A CHARGE I WILL KEEP!
- YOUR SCRUPLES ARE FICKLE.
- YOU MOCK ME.
KEIRO'S AMBITIONS DREW ME IN
BECAUSE I HAD NOT THE WIT
TO SEE THEM FOR WHAT THEY WERE.
BUT I WILL ATONE YET.
- ATONEMENT? SO YOU ARE EAGER
TO LAY DOWN YOUR LIFE.
WELL, THEN YOUR SCRUPLES
WILL BE ACCOMMODATED.
- ( screams )
- ALAS! THE END COMES.
I MUST DEPLOY THE MOMENTS
ALLOTTED ME WELL AND QUICKLY.
- Rinmei: THE ZHU KEH GATE!
- Koyo: THE FINAL BULWARK
BETWIXT US AND LORD KEIRO!
- Choka: NOT QUITE!
- Taito: YOU!
- WHATEVER GARB IT
CONDESCENDS TO WEAR,
MUTINY IS AT LAST
JUST THE COUNTENANCE OF
COWARDS AND VERMIN!
- Koyo: STAND ASIDE, WITCH!
OR DO YOU INTEND
TO TAKE US ON YOURSELF?
- OH, NO. I WAS MERELY
CORRECTING YOUR MISAPPREHENSION.
- MOVE!
- NO WAY!
RYUKO! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DON'T! YOU MUST
ALL GET BACK.
- THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- TAITO!
- YOU ROTTEN SON OF A--
- NO, WAIT. HOLD ON.
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT.
HE CAN'T HELP IT!
- Choka: PRECISELY.
ONCE A FIGURATIVE PAWN,
NOW A PAWN IN FACT.
- STOP HIM!
HE'S GONNA KILL TAITO!
RYUKO OR NOT, WE CAN'T
JUST STAND HERE!
- THE ONLY REMEDY
FOR HIM IS DEATH.
- BUT WE CAN'T DO THAT.
- I KNOW. WE HAVE TO LET
TAITO HANDLE THIS.
- RYUKO.
- LOOK AT ME. I AM NOT GONNA
FIGHT YOU, YOU UNDERSTAND?
GO RIGHT AHEAD. I WON'T!
- THE LOYALTY OF A FOOL.
HOW SAD. NOW FERRY THE ALTRUIST
TO HIS REWARD!
- ( screams in frustration )
- FIGHT IT.
YOU'RE ABOVE THEIR TRICKS.
- NO, I'M NOT.
- STRIKE ME DOWN.
- WHAT!
- FOR THE WRONGS I'VE DONE.
FOR THE WRONGS
I WILL PERPETRATE YET.
KILL ME
BEFORE I SPILL YOUR BLOOD!
- YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
I SAID I'M NOT GONNA KILL YOU!
- WHY DO YOU HESITATE?
SLAY ALKAID!
-TAITO, PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU.
KILL ME NOW!
IT'S THE ONLY WAY!
MY LIFE IS MEANINGLESS.
ONLY YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO END KEIRO'S TYRANNY.
IF YOU FALL BY MY HAND, THE
MONSTER WILL REIGN UNCHALLENGED!
- AND IF YOU FALL BY MINE?
STOP AND THINK ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE ASKING ME.
NEITHER ONE OF US
SHOULD HAVE TO DIE.
PEOPLE STILL CARE ABOUT YOU,
WARTS AND ALL.
PEOPLE LIKE RINMEI.
PEOPLE LIKE HOSEI AND LAILA.
HELL, ALL OF US!
REMEMBER THE CLIFF?
WE'RE BOTH SEEING THIS THROUGH.
YOU HEAR ME?
I'M NOT GONNA KILL A FRIEND.
- ARE YOU INSANE?
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE
YOU STILL CALL ME... AH!
- YOU FOOL! ANY ATTEMPTS TO
RESIST KEIRO'S HOLD ARE FUTILE!
- THAT MAY BE SO.
BUT THE CHOICE BEFORE ME,
BETWEEN MY LIFE AND
THAT OF A FRIEND.
BEHOLD MY ANSWER!
- NO, YOU MUSTN'T! PLEASE!
- FORGIVE ME.
- NO!
- WHAT THE...
- RYUKO!
- SHOKAKU! WHAT IS
THE MEANING OF THIS?
- KEIRO'S MADNESS
SHALL BE HIS OWN RUIN.
RYUKO SHALL BE FREE.
- VERY WELL! KEIRO HAS NO NEED
OF FEEBLE SYCOPHANTS!
- DOES HE BEAR A SIGIL?
- ( blood splatters )
- DAMN YOUR EYES!
- INDEED. WHAT NEED HAS HIS
LORDSHIP FOR FEEBLE SYCOPHANTS?
- HOLD ON, RYUKO!
KEEP FIGHTING IT!
- Taito: WHAT THE HELL'S
HAPPENING TO HIM?
- MIZAR AND THE DARK MAGIC
OF THE WAN XIANG SHI MING
ARE WARRING WITHIN HIM
TO THE DEATH.
- SO, HOW DO WE
GET THEM TO STOP?
- THE TEMPEST IN HIM IS MIGHTY.
- IF WE CANNOT STAUNCH
ITS RAGE, HE'LL DIE.
- WHAT!
- HE WILL NOT DIE.
NOT AS I DRAW BREATH.
- Taito: WHAT THE HELL'S
HAPPENING TO HIM?
- MIZAR AND THE DARK MAGIC
OF THE WAN XIANG SHI MING
ARE WARRING WITHIN HIM
TO THE DEATH.
- SO, HOW DO WE
GET THEM TO STOP?
- THE TEMPEST IN HIM IS MIGHTY.
IF WE CANNOT STAUNCH
ITS RAGE, HE'LL DIE.
- WHAT!
- HE WILL NOT DIE.
NOT AS I DRAW BREATH.
ENDURE IT JUST
A BIT LONGER, FRIEND.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- I WILL DRAW
THE DARK MAGIC FROM HIM
AS ONE DRAWS WATER FROM A WELL.
- YEAH, BUT HOW ARE YOU
GONNA DO THAT?
- BY RYUKO'S IRONCLAD WILL.
HIS BODY REJECTS
THE EVIL WITHIN ITSELF.
IT DWELLS NOW ON THE SURFACE
WHERE IT CAN BE SIPHONED OUT.
- ( screams in pain )
- ( thinking ) THE DARKNESS
IS STRONG. CAN I OUTSTRIP IT?
- OUR STAR SIGILS
ARE RESONATING.
- I'M RIGHT HERE.
- WHAT THE HELL'S IT
DOING TO YOU?
- IT'S NO MATTER.
DEATH HAS LONG BEEN MY SHADOW.
MY LIFE HAS RUN ITS COURSE.
I BROUGHT THIS UPON
US, MY FRIEND.
BUT YOU HAVE THE POWER TO
SET THINGS ARIGHT IN MY STEAD.
- ALIOTH. THE SAGE MAKES FIVE
AT THE HEEL OF ALKAID.
IT IS OF LITTLE MOMENT.
- RYUKO.
- RINMEI.
- THANK THE STARS.
- HE'S OKAY!
- OH, WOW! HE REALLY HAD US
WORRIED FOR A SECOND THERE.
- COME ON, MAN.
ON YOUR FEET.
- NO. I AM UNFIT
TO TAKE YOUR HAND.
- NO YOU'RE NOT!
- ( bang )
- Ryuko: SHOKAKU!
- I AM MAIMED.
FORGIVE ME, MY LORD.
ALKAID DRAWS EVER
NEARER AS I SPEAK.
HE WILL STAND
WHERE NOW I KNEEL.
WITH SHOKAKU'S DEFECTION,
ALL FIVE ARE NOW AGAINST YOU.
- THESE THINGS I KNOW.
- I AM THE ONLY ONE
ON WHOM YOU MAY RELY.
WE ARE ONCE AGAIN BUT TWO AS IN
THE DAYS WHEN FIRST WE MET.
I BESEECH YOU! USE MY CORPSE
AS YOU SEE FIT!
LET ME BE OF USE
TO YOU IN DEATH!
- YOU SHALL.
- OF ALL PEOPLE, WHY LAY DOWN
YOUR LIFE FOR ME?
- IT WAS ON MY ACCOUNT
THAT YOU STRAYED SO FAR AFIELD
FROM THE PATH OF LIGHT.
THE EMPIRE WAS MY CHIEF CONCERN.
I WOULD SEE PEACE AT ANY COST.
IT MATTERED NOT
WHO SAT ATOP THE THRONE.
I CARED NOT WHICH
WARRIOR GOD PREVAILED,
SO LONG AS THIS LAND
INHERITED THEIR TRIUMPH.
COULD KNOW PROSPERITY.
BUT KEIRO SLIGHTED FATE.
RUNNING AFOUL OF HIS STAR.
AND FOR IT, THE LAND SUFFERS.
FOR ME IT IS TOO LATE.
OTHERS MUST REAP WHAT
MY ARROGANCE HAS SOWN.
BUT YOU, YOU CAN BE
AN INSTRUMENT OF HOPE.
- NO, I RAN AFOUL OF MY STAR.
KEIRO AND I ARE
ONE AND THE SAME.
- THERE'S TIME ENOUGH FOR YOU
TO WEND YOUR FOOTFALLS
BACK TO THE PATH.
BETTER STILL, YOUR FRIENDS
ARE CONTENT TO WAIT FOR YOU.
PLEASE, RYUKO.
FIND YOUR TRUE WAY.
BE AS THE DAWN.
- SHOKAKU! SHOKAKU!
- FROM THE VERY BEGINNING
THIS MAN WAS PREPARED TO
LAY HIS LIFE DOWN FOR YOU.
- THEN IN ATONEMENT,
ALLOW ME THE HONOR OF
FIGHTING ALONGSIDE YOU
ONCE MORE.
- OF COURSE, NO NEED TO GET ALL
FORMAL ON ME ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
THING ABOUT MISTAKES IS
WE CAN ALWAYS CORRECT THEM.
AS LONG AS WE CAN STILL SEE
WHERE WE WENT WRONG,
WE HAVEN'T GONE
ALL THAT FAR OFF TRACK.
- I, I AM HUMBLED.
- HE'S RIGHT YOU KNOW.
AND WITH ALL OF IN TOW,
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE TO FIND
YOUR WAY BACK ALONE.
- I'M GRATEFUL.
KEIRO WILL BE STOPPED.
AND PEACE RESTORED
TO THE EMPIRE BY US.
TO HONOR THE MEMORY OF SHOKAKU.
- PLACE LOOKS DESERTED, HUH?
- HE LAYS COILED IN THE
THRONE ROOM. LET'S HURRY.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT THE...
- THE FIVE OF YOU GO ON AHEAD.
YOU HAVEN'T THE TIME TO SPARE
PLAYING KEIRO'S GAMES.
I'LL HOLD THEM OFF WHILE
YOU GAIN THE THRONE ROOM.
- GOOD PLAN.
- SO, LADIES,
AT LAST WE'RE ALONE.
WHAT!
- ( growling )
- SORRY, MY DEARS,
I RATHER PREFERRED
YOU ALL AS WOMEN.
- PITIFUL, MISLED YOUTH.
OH, HOW YOU CLING TO HOPE
WHEN HORRORS ARE IMMINENT.
- CHOKA!
- I'LL HANDLE THIS!
- WAIT, RINMEI!
- JUST GO! YOU HAVE MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO ATTEND TO!
- COME ON!
- EVEN AS WOUNDED AS YOU ARE,
YOU'RE STILL COMPELLED TO FIGHT.
IS THIS WHAT FEALTY
TO KEIRO BEGETS?
- I COMMEND YOU.
PLUNGING HEADLONG INTO
HARM'S WAY FOR YOUR BELOVED.
BUT YOURS IS NOTHING COMPARED
TO THE SACRIFICE I'VE MADE!
MY VERY SOUL IS KEIRO'S!
- RINMEI!
- GONNA GIVE HER A HAND?
- NO! I MUST FULFILL MY SACRED
DUTIES AS A DIVINE WARRIOR!
- OH, WAKE UP!
TO HELL WITH ALL THAT,
THE WOMAN YOU LOVE
NEEDS YOU NOW!
- I MEAN COME ON, RIGHT?
WHAT KIND OF GUY LET'S
HIS OLD LADY FIGHT ALONE?
- FOLLOW YOUR HEART, RYUKO.
- GO ON, THEN.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU.
- THERE'S NO END
TO THESE HARPIES.
SO YOU FEAST ON YOUR
OWN WOUNDED, HUH?
NOT THE FRIENDLIEST
OF GESTURES, I'D SAY.
NO WONDER
YOU'VE GOT SUCH PLUCK.
- IS THIS THE STRENGTH OF MERAK?
HOW WILL YOU SUBDUE KEIRO WHEN
EVEN HIS MINIONS OVER TOP YOU?
HE COURSES THROUGH ME.
MY TRUE LIFE'S BLOOD.
HIS WILL ENLIVENS EVERY FIBER.
- YOU WOULD PRAISE HIM.
THAT USES YOU IN DEATH?
- IN DEATH WE ARE ONE.
BUT YOU'LL DIE, ALONE!
- RYUKO?
- NOW YOU DEAL WITH ME.
- CURSE YOU! CURSE YOUR MEDDLING
AND YOUR SLIPSHOD LOYALTIES!
THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS ARE
THE VERY ESSENCE OF PERFIDY!
- I DO NOT FACE YOU AS MY STAR.
NOR AS A TRAITOR.
MY PURPOSE IS STRAIGHTFORWARD.
I'VE COME TO PROTECT
THE ONE I LOVE!
- RYUKO!
- WHAT DO YOU, ANY OF YOU
KNOW OF LOVE?
- CHOKA, AS ONE WHO KNOWS
SOMETHING ABOUT LOSING HIS WAY,
I ASK WHAT ILL WIND COULD
POSSIBLY HAVE DRIVEN
SO FINE A VESSEL
SO FAR FROM THE LIGHT?
WHY ANCHOR YOURSELF
TO A DESPOT?
- DESPOT?
( laughs ) ONLY THE FALSE
CALL GREAT MEN DESPOTS.
LORD KEIRO IS MY STAR!
HIS IS THE FIRE
THAT PURIFIES ALL.
YEAH, THE FIRE THAT SCOURS CLEAN
AS BONE THE NIGHT!
WITHOUT HIM, ALL IS
DARKNESS AND MISERY.
I SERVE HIM AS A LOVER OF LIGHT.
AS ONE, HAPPY TO DIE!
- I'M SURE HE'D BE HAPPY
TO INDULGE YOU.
- SILENCE!
- THE JIG IS UP, MUSTACHE.
LET'S END THIS!
- YOU'VE FINALLY
ARRIVED, ALKAID.
A MOMENT WE'VE BOTH
YEARNED FOR. BUT ALAS,
YOU'VE COME TOO LATE
TO VANQUISH ME.
- OH, YEAH?
- BEHOLD!
( in hoarse voice) I HAVE
SURPASSED HUMANITY!
- ( theme song playing)
- Ryuko: THE FINAL BATTLE
BETWEEN TAITO AND KEIRO BEGINS.
- Taito: WHEN YOU LOSE COUNT OF
ALL THE CORPSES YOU'VE HAD TO
WALK OVER ON THAT ROAD,
I DON'T CALL IT DESTINY!
- Keiro: WALLOW IN IT, ALKAID!
DROWN IN THE BITTER
TIDE OF DEFEAT!
- Taito: COME ON! AND WHILE
WE'RE AT IT, THAT'S NOT MY NAME!
- Laila: TAITO!
- Ryuko: AT LAST
THE PENDULOUS SKY BURSTS OPEN.
IN HERO TALES: FINAL CHAPTER -
"THE END OF THE TALE."
- ON THE WINGS OF MY TRIUMPH.
SOARS THE ANNIHILATION OF ALL!