- Keiro: TAKI.
- YES, FATHER?
- DO NOT WORRY, MY CHILD.
YOUR FATHER IS HERE.
- MY LORD, THE EMPEROR
HAS ARRIVED AND MAKES HIS WAY
TO THE GREAT HALL.
- THAT LOOK SUITS YOU WELL.
- THANK YOU, FATHER.
- ( theme song playing )
- Enki: WE WILL REMAIN HERE
WITH THE DOU YA.
PLEASE TAKE GREAT CARE.
- AW, THIS PLACE IS PRETTY SAFE.
WE SHOULD BE FINE.
- THIS LAND IS VERY NEAR
TO THE LIAN TONG TEMPLE.
AND THUS UNDER THE EVER VIGILANT
EYE OF THE QING LONG PLATOON.
- YEAH, WEREN'T YOU TELLING ME
THAT'S THE GROUP THAT YOU
AND TAITO'S OLD MAN
RUNS TO TRY TO KEEP
THE PEACE AROUND THESE PARTS?
- THAT'S THE ONE.
I HOPE IT'S BEEN QUIET.
- WELL, LET'S GET A MOVE ON
AND WE CAN ASK HIM OVER DINNER.
- SOUNDS GOOD!
- ( men shouting indistinctly )
- WE SHALL RETURN!
- Taito: WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED HERE?
- Laila: THIS IS HORRIBLE.
IT WASN'T LIKE THIS BEFORE.
WHEN WE CAME THROUGH EARLIER,
EVERYTHING WAS FINE.
- WHOEVER DID THIS
TOOK ALL OF THE FOOD AS WELL.
- THE WORK OF ROVING BANDITS.
STILL FRESH.
MAYBE ONE OR TWO DAYS AGO.
THREE AT THE MOST.
- WHERE ARE ALL THE PEOPLE?
AWFUL.
- ISN'T THE QING LONG PLATOON
SUPPOSED TO STOP
THINGS LIKE THIS?
CUT IT OUT.
- BUT WHY?
- IT'S NOT HIS FAULT, DEAR.
I'M SURE IT JUST HAPPENED
TOO FAST FOR THEM TO GET HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, TAIGA!
YOU PROMISED ME THAT
YOU'D CLEAN UP THE EMPIRE
AND YOU'D BETTER NOT FORGET!
YOU HEAR ME?
- I AM HONORED TO HAVE
SO MANY DISTINGUISHED GUESTS
GATHERED TO BID MY DAUGHTER
THEIR BLESSINGS ON HER BIRTHDAY.
MOST NOTABLY THE SON OF HEAVEN,
HIS LORDSHIP EMPEROR TAIGA.
I HOPE THAT ALL OF YOU
WILL SHARE IN OUR GOOD CHEER
ON THIS MOST JOYOUS OCCASION.
- Taiga: HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
LADY TAKI.
- MY LORD?
- WHAT? IS IT NOT?
ARE YOU UNHAPPY?
- YOUR LORDSHIP IS BY HER SIDE.
SURELY, ALL IS WELL
WITH MY LADY.
- CHOKA. IT IS NOT YOUR PLACE
TO ANSWER FOR HER.
- EXCUSE THE INTERRUPTION
BUT PERHAPS THE MAGNITUDE
OF YOUR IMPENDING ANNOUNCEMENT
IS WEIGHING HEAVILY
ON HER MIND.
- PLEASE FORGIVE MY TARDINESS.
- OF COURSE.
- YOU'VE ARRIVED!
- HMM.
LADY TAKI. I HOPE THIS SPECIAL
DAY FINDS YOU IN GOOD SPIRITS.
- IT DOES, SIR. THANK YOU.
- YOU HAVE
QUITE AN AUDIENCE ASSEMBLED.
OFFICIALS OF EVERY STRIPE
CONGREGATED TO OBSERVE
YOUR BIRTHDAY.
SUCH SPECTACLE.
YOUR FATHER'S INFLUENCE
IS CERTAINLY A THING TO BEHOLD
IN AND OF ITSELF.
- WHAT'S MORE. I MYSELF HAVE
A MATTER OF GREAT IMPORTANCE
THAT I WOULD LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
TO OUR GUESTS.
- Shokaku: MY CURIOSITY
IS PIQUED.
- THE TIME WOULD SEEM RIPE.
- YES.
HEAR, HEAR.
I HAVE A DECLARATION
THAT WELL WARRANTS THE ATTENTION
OF SO AUGUST AN ASSEMBLY. LADY.
- Shokaku: HE TAKES THE PATH
OF LESSER RESISTANCE,
BUT GREATER BOND.
- Man: GENERAL TOKAKU!
I BEAR AN URGENT MESSAGE!
- I AM NOT TO BE BOTHERED TODAY.
I HAVE TAKEN ILL
AND WISH TO BE IN SECLUSION
UNTIL SUNUP TOMORROW.
- YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF THIS MATTER
IS PARAMOUNT.
- IT REGARDS, THE EMPEROR.
- HMM.
- THE GRAND GENERAL WISHES
TO SPEAK, MY LADY.
- GRAND GENERAL TOKAKU
HAS ARRIVED?
WELL THEN, MAKE HASTE.
- GENERAL TOKAKU. TO WHAT
DO WE OWE THE SUDDEN PLEASURE
OF YOUR COMPANY?
HAS YOUR HEALTH RETURNED?
- I APPRECIATE YOUR CONCERN,
MY LORD.
HOWEVER, I CANNOT SIMPLY REST
WHILE THE FATE OF THE EMPIRE
IS THROWN INTO PERIL.
- OF WHAT PERIL DO YOU SPEAK?
- YOUR HIGHNESS,
I RECEIVED THIS JUST NOW.
WORD THAT YOU HAVE ANNOUNCED
YOUR UPCOMING UNION
WITH THIS YOUNG LADY.
- IN FACT I HAVE.
- YOU MUST HALT THIS AT ONCE!
- ( all gasping )
- THE EMPIRE IS A SACRED THING.
ITS FUTURE MUST NOT BE LEFT
TO WAYWARDNESS AND WHIM.
NEITHER TO THAT MAN'S DAUGHTER!
THERE IS STILL TIME
TO RECONSIDER, MY LORD.
- WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE
YOUR OBJECTION TO MY HAPPINESS?
SPEAK NOW!
- THE ESTEEMED GENERAL TOKAKU
IS CLEARLY TROUBLED
BY MY ATTENDANCE HERE MY LORD.
I WILL RESPECTFULLY
TAKE MY LEAVE.
GENTLEMEN, GRANT THEM
THEIR PRIVACY!
- IS IT WISE TO LEAVE HIM THERE?
- I HAVE NO DOUBT LADY CHOKA'S
SHARP-EDGED TONGUE
WILL DISPOSE OF HIM.
- INDEED, SIR. TAKI...
- TOKAKU, I IMPLORE YOU
TO EXPLAIN.
- MY LIEGE, FORGIVE MY CANDOR
BUT CLEARLY YOU ARE REMISS.
THIS WILL BIND GENERAL KEIRO
UNEQUIVOCALLY TO THE THRONE
AS A MEMBER OF THE ROYAL FAMILY.
- WHAT'S THE PERIL IN THAT?
- YOUR HIGHNESS. WE MUST NOT LET
THAT MAN WITHIN ARM'S REACH
OF SUCH GREAT POWER.
- PERHAPS THE GENERAL FEARS
HIS OWN REACH OF THE THRONE
WILL BE OBSTRUCTED BY KEIRO.
- CHOKA.
- SILENCE! MY CONCERNS
ON BEHALF OF THE EMPIRE
WILL NOT BE DISPARAGED
BY THE LIKES OF YOU!
- IT IS SURELY NOT
MERE COINCIDENCE
THAT HE OBJECTS TO A MOVE
THAT MAY RAISE THE PROFILE
OF HIS RIVAL.
PERHAPS THIS BILE WAS THE CAUSE
OF HIS EARLIER INFIRMITY.
- MY LIEGE, I ASK YOU
HAVE THIS LOWLY SERVANT
BITE HER TONGUE!
STOP INFECTING HIS EARS
WITH YOUR DAMNED LIES!
- ( laughing ) HOW FRIGHTENING.
THE GENERAL SEEMS EAGER
TO PORTRAY THE ROLE
OF SPURNED MISTRESS
TO THE COURT!
YOU DESPERATELY ATTEMPT
TO SEW SEEDS OF DOUBT
IN OUR DIVINE RULER'S MIND
AND CAST ASPERSIONS
ON THE INTENTIONS
OF A TRUSTED SERVANT
TO HIS HIGHNESS.
THESE ARE ACTIONS FITTING A MAN
WHO FEARS LOSING THE COMFORT
OF HIS POSITION.
- YOU TREACHEROUS WENCH!
- GENERAL.
- LORD.
- HEAR MY WORDS, LADY TAKI
IS NOT A POLITICAL OBJECT!
SHE IS THE WOMAN
WHOM I TRULY ADORE.
I WOULD MOST APPRECIATE
YOUR BLESSING.
I MUST RESTORE
THIS LAND OF OURS.
MY LOVE FOR THE EMPIRE,
IS AS BOUNDLESS AND UNWAVERING
AS THE SUN THAT SHINES
IN THE HEAVENS ABOVE US.
BUT I CANNOT STEWARD IT ALONE.
TOKAKU, LEND ME YOUR STRENGTH.
SHARE IN OUR JOY.
- MY SUPPORT
IS BUT YOURS TO ASK.
- I THANK YOU FOR THAT.
- I AM YOUR HUMBLE SUBJECT,
MY LIEGE.
- QUITE UNEXPECTED FROM THE LAD.
PERHAPS AN INDICATION
OF THE FIRE HE HOLDS WITHIN?
ALAS.
ALL FOR NAUGHT WITHOUT
THE POWER OF ALKAID
TO STOKE IT INTO
AN INFERNO'S PROPORTIONS.
AND, WHAT'S MORE...
IN ORDER TO ENSURE
THIS LOVELY CATACLYSM.
ALKAID AND DUBHE
MUST CLASH.
- I SWEAR. I WILL SHINE
THE LIGHT OF PEACE
UPON THIS EMPIRE ONCE AGAIN.
TO HONOR MY LOVE FOR TAKI.
AND, TO HONOR MY WORD TO TAITO.
- MY PATIENCE WEARS THIN.
WHEREFORE THIS HESITATION?
COME ALKAID.
- ( sneezing )
- YOU CATCHIN' A COLD THERE?
- NO, I'M FINE.
- THAT'S RIGHT. DON'T WORRY
ABOUT HIM, HE'S SO BACKWARDS,
HE CAN'T EVEN CATCH A COLD!
- Both: OH, IS THAT SO?
- DON'T ENCOURAGE HER, YOU TWO.
- HEY, UH, IS THAT REALLY TRUE?
- DON'T ASK ME. I'M NO DOCTOR.
WHO'S THERE?
- ( laughing )
PRETTY GOOD MOVE AVOIDING MY
ASTOUNDINGLY SKILLFUL ATTACK.
BUT...
PRETTY BAD MOVE
STEPPING RIGHT INTO THE HEART
OF BA GANG TERRITORY.
- YOUR TERRITORY?
SO YOU'RE THE BASTARDS
THAT DESTROYED THIS VILLAGE?
- IT WASN'T OUR FAULT, RUNT.
YEAH. THEY COULD HAVE PREVENTED
THE WHOLE DAMN THING
- IF THEY JUST DID
LIKE WE ASKED THEM TO.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- ( laughing )
NOT READY FOR THAT?
- WHAT ARE THEY, TWINS?
- Bashi: NOT JUST TWINS, WOMAN!
- WHAT?
- THERE'S FIVE.
- BAEI!
- BABEI!
- BASHI!
- BADEI!
- BAI!
- All: WE ARE THE BA BROTHERS!
BEHOLD WE FIVE!
- YEAH, THAT'S TELLING 'EM
WHO YOU ARE, BOSSES!
- YOU'RE SCARED NOW, RIGHT?
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
THE SHEER POWER OF OUR LEADERS
AND THAT THERE'S FIVE OF 'EM,
CAN YOU?
- Man: BEG ALL YOU WANT,
YOUR LIVES END HERE!
- THEY'RE SO UGLY.
- SHE CLEARLY CANNOT APPRECIATE
THE FACT THAT WE ARE
THE TRUE EMBODIMENT OF POWER!
- All: AT HER OWN FOOLISH PERIL!
- AND THEY'RE STUPID, TOO.
- All: MMM-HMM.
- WHAT? SHE DARES TO MOCK US?
- WHAT NOW?
WELL, WE CAN'T JUST GO ALL
CRAZY ON THESE GUYS.
I THINK WE SHOULD START
WITH THE ONES IN FRONT.
- RESTRAIN YOUR URGE
TO USE CHANNELING.
WE DON'T WANT A BLOODY MESS
ON OUR HANDS.
- AS MUCH AS I
HATE USING SWORDS,
I GUESS YOU HAVE A POINT.
ALL RIGHT THEN. COME ON.
- WELL, BROTHER?
- I KNOW.
BASH IN THEIR HEADS!
- ( men shouting )
- IF PART OF MY BURDEN AS ALKAID
MEANS I HAVE TO WIPE OUT
SCUM LIKE THIS, SO BE IT.
AND, I TOLD HIM I WOULD DO
WHAT I CAN TO SAVE THE EMPIRE
FROM OUTSIDE THE CAPITAL WALLS.
- LADY.
- I'M HONORED TO TRAVEL
WITH YOU, MY LORD.
- IGNORE THE NAYSAYERS.
I WILL HAVE YOUR HAND
BEFORE TOO LONG.
- YES.
- ( gurgling )
- LORD KEIRO.
I GIVE YOU ALL I HAVE,
MY ONLY CHILD,
IN HOPES SHE CAN
SERVE YOU IN YOUR GOAL.
- IT'S FOR THE BEST. FOR HER.
- Taiga: KEIRO IS NOT HERE
WITH HIS BLESSING?
- MY LORD, GENERAL KEIRO
SENDS HIS BLESSING
BUT THOUGHT IT BEST
THAT YOU ANNOUNCE
THE GOOD NEWS
OF YOUR ENGAGEMENT
WITHOUT THE FATHER OF THE BRIDE
OVER YOUR SHOULDER,
THUS HE REMAINS INSIDE.
- I SEE.
I ADMIRE HIS THOUGHTFULNESS.
- HE'S NOT HERE.
- IN THE GENERAL'S STEAD,
I AM HONORED TO OFFER
MY SERVICES AS YOUR GUARDIAN.
- YES. AND YOU ARE
WITH THE XUAN LANG PLATOON?
- I AM. MY NAME IS KOCHO,
MY LORD.
- DO WELL
TO KEEP US SAFE, KOCHO.
- I WILL DEFEND YOUR LIVES
WITH MY OWN. I SWEAR.
- Tokaku: HIS MAJESTY
DOES APPEAR EMBOLDENED.
- Ryusho: BUT, KEIRO BECOMING
PART OF THE ROYAL FAMILY
DOES NOT BODE WELL
FOR THE EMPIRE.
- OUR HAND MAY BE FORCED
TO BECKON HIM TO RETURN
FROM LIAN TONG.
TO HOLD TIGHT THE REINS
ON KEIRO'S AMBITIOUS LUST.
- DOES HE LIVE BY OUR WHIM?
BANISHED SO MANY YEARS AGO
BY THE SAME ONES WHO WOULD NOW
BEG HIM RETURN?
- HE WAS REMOVED
FROM THE CAPITAL IN THE INTEREST
OF PRESERVING HIS VERY LIFE!
- I AM WELL AWARE OF THAT FACT.
BUT HIS RETURN WOULD
INCREASE THE SCHISM
NOW PRESENT
IN THE COURT.
WHAT'S MORE...
IT ENSURES THE CLASH
BETWEEN THE STARS.
- RIDICULOUS.
THE CELESTIAL DEITIES NEVER
INHABIT THE EARTH
CONTEMPORANEOUSLY.
- DUBHE'S VESSEL IS AMONG US.
IT'S GENERAL KEIRO.
- KEIRO? THIS CANNOT BE.
- KEIRO'S DESIGNS ON POWER
ARE THE MANIFESTATIONS
OF DUBHE'S BLOODY KARMA.
- ( cymbals clashing )
- SURELY GENERAL TOKAKU
SEES THE FOLLY
IN CHALLENGING YOUR WISHES.
YOUR DESIRES WILL INDEED
BE MADE FLESH.
CONTROL OF THE EMPIRE IS YOURS.
- WHAT OF ALKAID?
HE STILL HIDES, YES?
- THE SEARCH FOR ALKAID'S VESSEL
IS STILL AFOOT, MY LORD,
BUT HE HAS NOT BEEN LOCATED.
MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES.
- SEIZING CONTROL
OF THIS EMPIRE IS BUT MERELY
ONE STEP IN MY PLAN.
IT IS NOT THE TERMINUS
FOR MY AMBITION.
- YES, MY LORD.
- IS THERE SOMETHING
TROUBLING YOU, YOUR LORDSHIP?
- NOTHING.
IT IS OF NO MATTER.
- ( laughing )
WERE YOU HOPING TO FIND
TAITO IN THE CROWD?
- MY DEAR BELOVED CERTAINLY
DOES KNOW WELL MY HEART.
I FEEL MY MEETING WITH TAITO
THAT DAY HAS LEFT ME
A MAN TRANSFORMED.
FOR THAT SERVICE,
I OWE HIM MY GRATITUDE.
YOU FIND THAT ODD?
- NO. IF YOU FEEL THIS WAY
YOU SHOULD BY ALL MEANS
SHARE IT WITH HIM.
- I THOUGHT
I MIGHT FIND YOU HERE.
- AH, SO YOU'VE RETURNED.
HAS THE BANQUET CONCLUDED?
- IT HAS AND QUITE
ABRUPTLY IN FACT.
I WAS NOT COMPELLED
TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE SUBSEQUENT SPECTACLE.
- WHAT SPECTACLE?
- THE CAVALCADE CELEBRATING
OUR DIVINE EMPEROR'S
UPCOMING MARRIAGE
TO KEIRO'S DAUGHTER TAKI.
IT WAS JUST NOW ANNOUNCED.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD ENJOY
THE WARM SUN OUTSIDE.
- HEY LOOK!
- THE SUN IS BEING SWALLOWED UP.
- THE END IS UPON US!
- ( all screaming )
- TAKI!
ARE YOU INJURED, MY LADY?
- NO, I'M FINE.
- MY LORD, LADY TAKI,
ARE EITHER OF YOU HARMED?
- WE ARE SHAKEN BUT UNINJURED.
WHAT IS THIS?
- ( laughing )
EVEN HEAVEN HAS BENT TO MY WILL!
ALKAID, YOUR LIGHT TOO
SHALL FALL VICTIM TO MY SHADOW!
- WHAT ON EARTH IS HAPPENING?
- MY PEOPLE BE CALM!
DO NOT FEAR!
WE MUST NOT BE AFRAID.
WE MUST SHOW RESOLVE AND
CONFIDENCE IN TIMES OF DANGER,
NOT PANIC AND CONFUSION.
THE SKIES MAY DARKEN AND
THE HEAVENS MAY FALL UPON US,
BUT YOUR EMPEROR IS HERE
TO BE YOUR SHEPHERD.
WHATEVER WICKEDNESS MAY COME,
I WILL PROTECT MY PEOPLE!
- ( gasping )
- IT'S HIM.
- BEHOLD! THE SUN'S LIGHT
HAS BEEN RESTORED!
SO TOO SHALL THE GLORIOUS LIGHT
OF THE XIAN EMPIRE
BE RESTORED ANEW!
WE SHALL EMERGE
FROM THE DARKNESS
AND SHINE WITH THE BRILLIANCE
OF A THOUSAND SUNS!
- ( crowd cheering )
- Man 1: LONG LIVE
THE PRINCE OF HEAVEN!
- Man 2: HEAR, HEAR!
LONG LIVE EMPEROR TAIGA!
- THIS IS THE FIRST
YOU'VE LAID EYES ON HIM.
THE FIRST TIME YOU'VE BEEN IN
THE PRESENCE OF EMPEROR TAIGA,
DIVINE RULER OF THE XIAN EMPIRE.
- THE EMPEROR, TAIGA.
THE RESEMBLANCE IS UNCANNY.
BUT WHAT CAN THIS MEAN?
- Laila: OH MY GOSH,
THAT WAS SO SCARY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN IT
GET DARK LIKE THAT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY.
I THOUGHT THE WORLD
WAS COMING TO AN END.
- SURELY IT'S AN OMEN
OF SOME KIND.
A SIGN OF A MAJOR CHANGE
ON THE HORIZON.
- Both: NOTHING SEEMS
TO BE HAPPENING SO FAR.
- ( grunting )
- ONE HUNDRED AND TWENTY-SEVEN
MERCILESS KILLERS
DEFEATED BY
THESE FIVE INSECTS?
- OH. WOW, ARE YOU GUYS
STILL HERE?
- YEAH, I PRETTY MUCH FORGOT
ABOUT THOSE GUYS.
- PERHAPS WE NEED
TO REMIND YOU WHO WE ARE!
- All: BUT THIS MEMORY
WILL SURELY BE YOUR LAST.
- ( grunting )
- I CAN HANDLE THESE CLOWNS.
- ( screaming )
- BABEI, BADEI, BASHI, BAI!
- FROM FIVE DOWN TO ONE!
I'LL SPARE YOUR LIFE
IF YOU PROMISE YOU'LL CHANGE
YOUR WAYS FROM HERE ON OUT!
- ( grunting )
YOU MAY HAVE BESTED
MY YOUNGER BROTHERS.
THEY MATCHED MY HANDSOME LOOKS
BUT NOT MY SKILL IN BATTLE!
( grunting )
WHAT? HOW COULD YOU STOP
MY UNRIVALED AND FLAWLESS ATTACK
WITH JUST ONE SWORD?
- JUST WORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENS NEXT!
- NICE TRY, KID!
( laughing )
BUT I WIN!
- OH YEAH?
- YOUR SWORD'S GONE. I WIN!
- I DON'T NEED TO USE
A SWORD OR CHANNELING!
- ( groaning in pain )
- I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
A WORK-WITH-MY-HANDS
KIND OF GUY!
- ARE YOU SOME KIND OF MONSTER?
- YOU WANT TO FIND OUT?
- NO! NO, SIR!
- VERY WELL DONE, MY FRIEND!
- Laila: THAT WAS GREAT!
- OH HEY, THANKS.
- ( Baei grunting )
- OH MAN, ARE THERE
MORE OF THEM?
- I'LL GO LOOK.
- DON'T JUST RUN OFF, TAITO!
- WE'VE GOT COMPANY!
- THESE GUYS SEEM GOOD.
- NOTHING LIKE THAT
BAND OF MISFITS
WE DISPATCHED
WITH EARLIER.
- ( gasping )
- THAT FLAG.
- SO YOU'RE BACK.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- FATHER!
( crying )
- ARE YOU WELL, DAUGHTER?
- I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
- SO THAT BADASS OVER THERE
IS YOU GUYS' OLD MAN?
- HE IS A GREAT MAN.
LEADER OF THE QING LONG.
- AND GOOD FATHER.
- HEY THERE.
- MASTER.
- Soei: TAITO.
- I'M BACK.
- YES.
- YOU SURE HAVE GROWN, TAITO.
- ( laughing ) YEAH?
- ( Japanese song playing )
- Koyo: THE FRESH AIR
OF TAI SHAN IS A BALM
TO THE SOUL.
ABATING THE PAIN, AND SADNESS.
- Taito: THIS WHOLE
THING HAS BEEN LIKE
SOME CRAZY DREAM I HAD.
TO GO FROM THE CAPITAL
TO BEING BACK HERE AT HOME
WITH YOU.
- Laila: WHAT GREAT NEWS.
ISN'T IT AMAZING?
- Taito: THIS IS MORE LIKE IT.
YOU AND ME
WALKING THE BEAT AGAIN,
MAKING SURE
THAT THERE'S NO TROUBLE.
- TAITO. I FEARED THAT THIS DAY
WOULD EVENTUALLY COME TO PASS.
- Koyo: A LIFELONG CLOUD
OF SECRECY IS DISSIPATED.
IN HERO TALES,
"CHAPTER SEVENTEEN,
THE FATHER-SON BOND."
- Laila: IS HE EVER GOING
TO GROW UP AND STOP
BEING SO STUPID?