- RYUKO.
- Laila: NO! STOP!
COME ON, EVEN YOU SHOULD KNOW
YOU CAN'T EAT THAT PLANT.
STUPID IDIOT.
- KEIRO?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( door opens )
- STAND DOWN!
THAT'S AN ORDER!
- GRAND GENERAL TOKAKU, YOU ARE
HEREBY UNDER ARREST FOR TREASON
AGAINST THE XIAN EMPIRE.
- TREASON? ABSURD!
- YOU CAN PRESENT YOUR ARGUMENT
IN DUE TIME.
FOR NOW, YOU MUST COME WITH ME.
- IT SEEMS THE COURT HAS
FALLEN UNDER HIS SHADOW
SOONER THAN I EXPECTED.
- HE'S BEEN ARRESTED?
- IT SEEMS HIS WAS
THE UNSEEN HAND
FANNING THE FLAMES OF REVOLT
AMONG THE PEOPLE.
GENERAL KEIRO'S MEN
HAVE HIM IN CUSTODY.
- I CAN'T...
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- HE HAD DESIGNS ON
TAKING YOUR LIFE AS WELL.
TO BE BETRAYED BY
SUCH A TRUSTED ADVISOR,
YOU HAVE MY
DEEPEST SYMPATHIES, HIGHNESS.
BUT THE SEVERITY OF
THE CRIME REQUIRES
SEVERE PUNISHMENT
BE METED OUT, AND SWIFTLY.
- AS HE'S BEEN MY
TRUSTED ADVISOR,
I WILL WITHHOLD SENTENCING
UNTIL I HAVE OCCASION TO
DISCUSS THIS MATTER WITH HIM.
MEANWHILE, HE'S TO
REMAIN IN CUSTODY.
- MY LORD! SURELY WE DO NOT WANT
TO MEET SUCH A DESPICABLE ACT
WITH WEAKNESS.
THE PRICE OF TREASON
IS ONE'S HEAD!
- DO NOT DARE
CHALLENGE MY ORDER!
GENERAL TOKAKU
WILL BE DEALT WITH
WHEN AND IN THE MANNER
THAT I DEEM FIT!
HE IS NOT TO BE HARMED!
- YES. AS YOU WISH, MY LORD.
- SHOW YOURSELF.
- AND I THOUGHT I HAD THOROUGHLY
CONCEALED MY PRESENCE.
- YOU STINK OF DEATH.
WHEREVER YOU PROWL,
A FETID CLOUD OF ROT
BETRAYS YOUR HIDING PLACE.
THE GRAVE HAS FOREVER
CLAIMED YOU AS ITS OWN.
- IS THAT SO?
UNTIL NOW I WAS UNAWARE.
- NOW WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- A "PALTRY THING," AS IT WERE.
THE SWORD OF RULE,
IN MY HAND, AS IN YOURS,
AN UNREMARKABLE ITEM.
HOWEVER, WHEN GRASPED BY THE
HAND IT DEEMS FIT TO WIELD IT,
THAT'S A DIFFERENT
STORY ALTOGETHER.
YES, QUITE.
A SHAME WE COULD NOT
BEAR WITNESS TO SUCH
A DIVINE PAIRING. AT PRESENT
THE EMPIRE ALLOWS
A MERE PRETENDER TO SIT
ATOP THE THRONE.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE, MY LORD?
- I ASKED WHAT YOU WANTED.
- AND SO COMMANDING
A VOICE WAS HEARD,
BUT I FIND THIS LAISSEZ FAIRE
APPROACH TO OUR PROBLEM
DREADFULLY BORING.
I'D LIKE TO LIVEN IT UP A BIT.
- YOU MAY.
- I WAS HOPING TO GARNER
YOUR BLESSING, MY LORD.
AND, WHO KNOWS,
WE MAY YET FIND A MEANS
BY WHICH TO BREATHE NEW LIFE
INTO THIS RUSTY OLD ARTIFACT,
AFTER ALL.
( laughing diabolically )
- Taito: YEAH, THIS'LL BE GREAT!
- IT'S THE PERFECT SPOT
FOR A LITTLE HIDEAWAY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- I GOTTA SAY I ADMIRE THE
BIRD'S EYE VIEW OF THE CAPITAL.
- IT'S MAGNIFICENT,
PERHAPS THE MAIN WE REASON
WE CHOSE THIS PARTICULAR CAVERN
TO BE OUR DEN WHEN
THE FATEFUL HOUR DREW NEAR.
- WHAT FATEFUL HOUR'S THAT?
- ( smirks )
COME NOW. THE HOUR
WE SLAY KEIRO, OF COURSE.
- UGH, COME ON, GUYS, GEEZ!
- LIGHTEN UP! WE'RE WORKING
ON OUR STRATEGERY.
- YOU NEED TO HELP ME!
- ALL RIGHT! I'LL DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT!
- HEY, WHATCHA GOT THERE, LAILA?
- OH, ENKI SAID I COULD
HANG THIS OUTSIDE THE ENTRANCE
TO OUR NEW HEADQUARTERS.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WELL, MAYBE IF YOU GUYS
PULLED YOUR WEIGHT AROUND HERE,
YOU'D HAVE A SAY IN IT. HMPH!
- SO WE'RE KILLING KEIRO.
- WHAT'S WRONG, ARE YOU
HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS?
- HELL NO! IT'S JUST THAT...
- IT'S RYUKO, ISN'T IT?
- DO YOU GUYS THINK THAT
RYUKO REALLY BELIEVES
ALL THAT STUFF HE WAS SAYING
ABOUT KEIRO WANTING PEACE?
- I CAN'T SAY
WHAT HE BELIEVES IN,
BUT SOMETHIN' ABOUT IT
JUST DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT TO ME.
- WHAT?
- IT'S...
I DUNNO, THIS WHOLE THING
DOESN'T SEEM VERY
"RYUKO-LIKE" AT ALL.
- WELL, I SURE DON'T GET IT.
- I'M JUST NOT CONVINCED
THAT'S WHO HE REALLY IS, Y'KNOW?
- ( sobs )
- OH, ARE YOU OKAY, RINMEI?
- I'M FINE.
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
( thinking ) RYUKO
WAS A FOUNDLING.
MASTER RYUSHO TOLD ME
WHEN HE WAS DISCOVERED,
THIS DAGGER WAS ALL HE HAD.
HE'S CARRIED IT EVER SINCE.
I WONDER, DID HE KNOW
OF ITS MESSAGE?
AND IF SO...
- SOMETHING TROUBLING YOU?
- IT'S NOTHING.
- I HAD DOZED OFF FOR A BIT,
BUT WAS AWOKEN BY THE SOUND
OF HURRIED FOOTSTEPS
OUT OF THE CAVE.
- OH?
- I FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE
THE WO JIN SQUAD IS DRY-DOCKED
FOR THE TIME BEING, AT LEAST.
GUESS MY MEN WILL HAVE TO GET
THEIR LAND LEGS BACK, HUH?
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME I HAVE TO
MAKE MYSELF LOOK BUSY,
LEST I INCUR ENKI'S WRATH.
- WAIT.
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU.
- SURE. ANYTHING
YOU WISH TO KNOW.
- A SWORD, IS IT COMMON
TO HAVE A NAME ENGRAVED?
- A NAME?
WELL, QUITE A FEW CRAFTSMEN HAVE
BEEN KNOWN TO MARK THEIR BLADES
WITH A NAME PARTICULAR
TO THAT WEAPON.
IT'S NOT TYPICALLY
A PERSON'S NAME, HOWEVER.
BUT, IT'S NOT UNHEARD OF.
IN SOME FAMILIES OF
HIGH SOCIAL STANDING,
THE PATRIARCH WILL BESTOW
A WEAPON ENGRAVED WITH HIS NAME
AS AN HEIRLOOM TO
HIS FIRST BORN SON.
HIS SUCCESSOR, IF YOU WILL.
AN ARCHAIC TRADITION,
BUT STILL DONE SOMETIMES.
IS THERE A SPECIFIC REASON
FOR YOUR QUERY?
- NO, THERE'S NOT.
- I'M QUITE SURPRISED.
I'D THOUGHT HIM INCAPABLE
OF MAKING SUCH A DECREE.
- I COULD NOT DISSUADE HIM,
MY LORD.
- OUR PLANS WILL HAVE TO BE
ALTERED YET AGAIN I SUPPOSE.
THE OLD FOOL WILL SIMPLY BE
PUT ASIDE BY SOME OTHER MEANS.
MY ASCENSION WILL NOT
BE HINDERED.
- LORD KEIRO.
TOKAKU IS NOW UNDER
IMPERIAL CUSTODY, MY LIEGE.
- EXCELLENT WORK.
- WHAT WILL YOU HAVE ME
DO WITH HIM, SIR?
- IT MATTERS NOT.
A GENERAL STRIPPED OF HIS RANK
IS NO MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANY COMMONER.
SHALL I IMPRISON HIM?
- NO, ALTHOUGH HIS POSITION
IN THE COURT IS TENUOUS,
FINAL JUDGMENT REMAINS.
ACTING RASHLY MAY CAUSE A STIR.
- SO WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
- I WOULD PREFER TO HANDLE
THIS MATTER MYSELF.
THAT IS, IF IT
PLEASES YOU, MY LORD.
- VERY WELL, THEN.
- MY GRATITUDE.
RYUKO, REPORT TO MY QUARTERS
AT YOUR EARLIEST CONVENIENCE.
- YES, SIR.
- ONE MOMENT.
NEWS HAS TRAVELED UPWARD,
I'VE HEARD TALES OF
YOUR PERFORMANCE
AND LEADERSHIP IN XUAN LONG.
- WELL, SIR. IT'S MY DUTY.
- DON'T BE SO MODEST
AS TO STAGNATE YOUR RANK.
- ( whispers ) YES, FATHER.
- Koyo: WHAT? GENERAL TOKAKU?
YOU'RE CERTAIN OF THIS?
- MY SOURCES HAVE VERIFIED IT.
- I WASN'T EXPECTING KEIRO TO
MAKE HIS MOVE IN SUCH HASTE.
- SO WHO IS THIS TOKAKU GUY?
- LATELY HE'S BEEN THE MOST
PROMINENT VOICE OF OPPOSITION
IN THE IMPERIAL COURT
TO KEIRO'S INCREASING
THIRST FOR POWER.
AND THOUGH STEADFAST, HE'S NOT
THE TYPE TO PLOT ANYTHING
THAT WOULD UNDERMINE THE EMPIRE.
- AND IF HE'S BEEN OUSTED
FROM HIS POSITION, THAT MEANS...
- THAT MEANS THERE IS
NO VIABLE OPPOSITION
TO KEIRO SEIZING POWER.
- DAMN IT ALL! WE MAY ALREADY
BE TOO LATE TO STOP HIM!
- WE SHOULD TAKE A PAGE FROM OUR
ENEMY AND MAKE HASTE AS WELL.
- IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
THE TIME ISN'T RIGHT!
- THE TIME IS GONNA BE
A HELL OF A LOT LESS RIGHT
ONCE THAT MURDERING
BASTARD HAS CONTROL OF
THE WHOLE DAMN EMPIRE!
- DON'T YOU THINK I KNOW THAT?
IF WE MOVE TOO QUICKLY
WE MAY ONLY SUCCEED
IN JOINING COUNTLESS
OTHERS IN THE GRAVE!
BUT WHAT CAN WE DO?
WITH TOKAKU AND HIS MILITARY
OPPOSITION BROUGHT TO HEEL,
THE THRONE IS WELL WITHIN
KEIRO'S RAVENOUS GRASP.
THE EMPIRE WILL BE SHROUDED
IN A VEIL SO HEAVY
THE LIGHT OF THE STARS WILL BE
RENDERED BUT A MEMORY.
BUT STILL, WE MUST DO SOMETHING.
- HEY, IS KOYO EVEN
TALKING TO US ANYMORE?
- UH...
- THE CAPTAIN IS SIMPLY
DISCUSSING POSSIBLE STRATEGIES
WITH HIMSELF. HE NEEDS
SOME TIME TO ORGANIZE
HIS THOUGHTS WITHOUT
FURTHER DISTRACTION,
SO LET'S LEAVE HIM BE FOR NOW.
- THERE IS ACTUALLY
ANOTHER ITEM TO REPORT.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THERE'S BEEN SOME TALK
ABOUT THAT RYUKO GUY.
- RYUKO?
- WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT HIM?
- WELL, THAT HE'S RECENTLY
RISEN UP IN THE RANKS
AND HAS USED HIS POSITION
IN THE XUAN LONG PLATOON
TO CLEAN HOUSE IN THE CABINET.
HE'S ARRESTED A LOT OF OFFICIALS
FOR CORRUPTION.
- GAH! THAT BASTARD!
- WELL, AT LEAST HE HASN'T
COMPLETELY CHANGED, HAS HE?
- GUESS NOT.
- ACCORDING TO MY SOURCES,
RYUKO WAS ALSO THE ONE
WHO LED THE SQUAD
THAT ARRESTED
GENERAL TOKAKU AS WELL.
- SERIOUSLY?
- DO YOU THINK THAT RYUKO
STILL ARRESTED HIM
EVEN THOUGH HE KNEW
TOKAKU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG?
- RYUKO IS A SMART GUY. HE KNOWS
EXACTLY WHAT HE'S DOING.
- SO HE'S COMPLETELY GONE OVER
TO KEIRO'S SIDE, HAS HE?
- Koyo: YES. THAT'S IT.
FOR NOW IT'S BEST THAT WE LET
THE CHIPS FALL WHERE THEY MAY,
AND GENERAL TOKAKU
ALONG WITH THEM.
- TOKAKU, SIR, YOU ARE HEREBY
ORDERED TO REMAIN WITHIN
THE WALLS OF TONG YO,
TO AWAIT THE VERDICT
FROM HIS MAJESTY.
- I UNDERSTAND. A FITTING PLACE
TO ENGAGE IN CONTEMPLATION.
- YES, WELL, THE EMPEROR
WILL ARRIVE IN DUE TIME
TO DISCUSS THE
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST YOU.
UNTIL THEN, I WILL KEEP WATCH.
- I SEE. I'M SURE THAT I WILL BE
QUITE STIMULATED HERE.
I HAVE AN OLD FRIEND
WITH WHOM TO PASS THE TIME.
- TAKE HIM IN.
- ( soldiers grunt )
- Ryusho: WELL, MY BOY.
- FATHER.
- SO THIS IS THE PATH
YOU'VE CHOSEN?
( sighs )
THEN I'VE NOTHING TO SAY.
- Koyo: THE PLAN IS THIS.
WE HAVE TOKAKU EMBRACE
HIS ALLEGED ROLE OF INSTIGATOR
AND START THE REBELLION
IN EARNEST.
WHILE THE CAPITAL IS GRIPPED
IN THE THROES OF CHAOS,
WE CARRY OUT OUR PLAN TO
ENTER THE CITY WALLS,
AND FINALLY CUT KEIRO DOWN.
- HOW DO WE DO THAT?
- I'LL TRY TO EXPLAIN THIS
IN THE SIMPLEST TERMS.
ALTHOUGH LARGE FIRES
OF REBELLION HAVE BEEN QUELLED,
MANY EMBERS STILL REMAIN
BURNING WITH THE DESIRE
FOR REVOLT AND CHANGE.
IF WE CAN COMBINE THESE EMBERS
BY ADDING OUR OWN FUEL,
THE RESULTS
COULD BE SPECTACULAR.
- COMBINING THEM?
BUT IS THAT REALLY POSSIBLE?
- OF COURSE IT IS!
THE IMPETUS FOR RISING UP
TOGETHER IS ALREADY THERE!
- I JUST DON'T THINK
I'M FOLLOWING YOU, BROTHER.
- THIS WILL BE OUR CRY!
GOOD PEOPLE, KEIRO HAS
CAST A SHADOW UPON THIS LAND
BLACK AS DEATH ITSELF.
BUT TOKAKU CAN GIVE US MEANS
TO DISPEL THAT PALL
AND ILLUMINATE A PATH TO VICTORY
WITH THE FIRES OF REVOLT!
RISE UP!
- HMM. UM-HMM. I GET IT.
- YEAH, I'M SURE YOU DO.
- KOYO, DON'T YOU THINK BY
CASTING TOKAKU IN THIS ROLE,
WE'LL ESSENTIALLY BE
GIVING HIM THE DEATH SENTENCE?
- EXECUTION IS
CURRENTLY HIS FATE.
SO, IN FACT, WE ARE GIVING HIM
TWO CHOICES OF LEGACY.
YIELD AND DIE, OR FIGHT AND DIE.
- ( whispers) KOYO'S A
LITTLE HARSH, ISN'T HE?
- HE HAS TO BE, Y'KNOW?
- UM-HMM.
- OUR NEXT STEP IS TO SIMPLY
PRESENT OUR PLAN
TO THE GENERAL HIMSELF
AND CONVINCE HIM
TO FOLLOW ALONG.
- LUCKILY, THE GENERAL IS
NOT IMPRISONED BUT MERELY
UNDER HOUSE ARREST.
HE'S CURRENTLY BEING HELD
AT TONG YO TEMPLE.
- I SHALL SEND SOMEONE THERE
RIGHT AWAY.
- VERY GOOD. I'LL WRITE
MY THOUGHTS IN A LETTER
TO HAND THE GENERAL
WITH THE HOPES
WE CAN STOKE THE FIRES
OF REBELLION WITHIN HIM.
- Rinmei: WAIT!
- ( both gasp )
- I'LL GO. I SHOULD BE THE ONE.
AFTER ALL, I'M THE MOST FAMILIAR
WITH TONG YO TEMPLE.
- YES, THAT'S TRUE.
BUT TAKE A MAN WITH YOU.
- I'LL GO WITH HER, CAPTAIN.
- ENKI, SURELY YOU DON'T
NEED TO GO WITH HER.
- AS A SISTER MEMBER OF THE "MEN
ARE HOPELESS LEAGUE," YES, I DO!
- Ryuko: YOU'RE TO CONDUCT
ALL PATROLS IN PAIRS.
ANY SUSPICIOUS PERSON YOU
ENCOUNTER SHOULD BE TAKEN IN
FOR QUESTIONING IMMEDIATELY.
- Soldiers: SIR!
- Choka: SHOKAKU'S
PLAN OF KEEPING TOKAKU
LOCKED AWAY AT TONG YO
ALLOWS US TO KEEP WATCH
OVER THIS UPSTART RYUKO AS WELL.
SOMETHING TROUBLES ME, HOWEVER.
HIS FATHER IS HERE.
CAN HE BE TRUSTED TO PREVENT
THAT MONK FROM CAUSING
MORE DISRUPTION?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT AT THIS HOUR?
- Woman: PLEASE!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THERE'S A WOMAN AT THE GATE.
- A WOMAN?
- Woman: PLEASE OPEN UP!
HE'LL KILL ME IF HE CATCHES ME!
HE NEVER WORKS AND HE JUST
STAYS DRUNK ALL THE TIME
AND ALWAYS HANGING OUT WITH
HIS DISGUSTING FRIENDS.
- WHAT NOW?
- EH, SHE'S JUST HAVIN' A LITTLE
TROUBLE WITH HER HUSBAND.
- LET'S LET HER IN.
- Woman: LET ME IN!
- ALL RIGHT, LADY,
JUST CALM DOWN, OKAY?
- WHAT THE HELL?
( groans )
- WELL, THAT WAS EASY, THANKS TO
YOUR CONVINCING PERFORMANCE.
- IT HELPS IF THERE'S
A LITTLE BIT OF TRUTH TO IT.
YOU KNOW WHERE
THEY MAY BE KEEPING TOKAKU?
- IF I HAD TO GUESS, HE'S MOST
LIKELY IN THAT CHAMBER THERE.
IT CAN BE LOCKED
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
- ( door opens )
- GRAND GENERAL TOKAKU
I PRESUME?
- OF COURSE. AND YOU ARE?
- YES, FORGIVE ME, SIR. I AM
ENKI WITH THE WO JIN SQUAD.
- WO JIN? WHAT DO YOU
WATER BANDITS WANT WITH ME?
- TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
WE NEED YOUR HELP, GENERAL.
WE BELIEVE YOU CAN BE
OF ASSISTANCE TO US
IN OUR PLAN TO ELIMINATE KEIRO.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
- UNTIL WE CAME BACK
HERE TONIGHT,
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW MUCH
I'VE MISSED THIS PLACE.
THAT WAS ONCE RYUKO'S CHAMBER.
- YOUNG LADY, YOUR GROUP
WISHES ME TO AID IN YOUR REVOLT?
- I'M AFRAID IT'S
MORE THAN THAT, SIR.
WE ASK THAT YOU TAKE ON
THE ROLE OF ITS INSTIGATOR
AND ACCEPT ANY AND
ALL CONSEQUENCES
SUCH A ROLE MAY BRING.
- SO, THEN, YOU'RE ASKING ME
TO MARTYR MYSELF?
- IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO
PROTECT THE EMPEROR.
THE LAST HOPE TO SAVE HIS LIFE.
- TO SAVE HIS LIFE THEN.
YES, I SEE.
IF I MUST FORFEIT MY OWN LIFE
TO ENSURE HIS, SO BE IT.
I WILL GLADLY DIE.
- WE WILL HONOR YOU NAME,
GRAND GENERAL, SIR.
WHERE IS SHE? RINMEI.
- Choka: WHAT A SURPRISE.
I KNEW SOME SORT OF PREY
HAD SKULKED ITS WAY INSIDE.
BUT NOT A DIVINE WARRIOR.
THAT IS QUITE THE PRIZED CATCH.
SURROUND HER!
- ( Laila exclaims )
-WHAT IN THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
- RELIGHT THE FIRE!
- ( clinking )
- HEY, UH, WHERE DID TAITO GO?
- OH, NOT THIS PLACE AGAIN.
- NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN, LAD.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT,
YOU BASTARD? TELL ME!
- I'VE COME TO INQUIRE ABOUT
YOUR FINAL DECISION, ALKAID.
- ON WHAT?
- HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
THE EMPIRE IS YOURS
IF YOU DESIRE IT, MY BOY.
THE DECISION RESTS
IN YOUR HANDS.
- ( grunting )
- THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE!
SURELY YOU CAN DISPOSE OF ONE
WOMAN, DIVINE WARRIOR OR NOT!
- ( swords clanging )
- RINMEI!
- ( gasping )
( groans )
- A RATHER INOPPORTUNE TIME
TO LET DOWN YOUR GUARD.
OR RATHER THE PERFECT TIME FOR
YOU TO PROVIDE A DISTRACTION.
I THANK YOU.
- HOLD ON, RYUKO!
( gasping )
- ( sniffling )
- ( sobbing )
- TAKE HER AWAY.
- THIS IS BAD.
- Shimei: THE SWORD CHOSE YOU,
THE ONLY ONE IT SEES FIT TO SIT
ATOP THE EMPEROR'S THRONE!
IT IS QUITE AN HONOR!
- I DON'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT SITTING ON THAT THRONE.
- BUT DON'T YOU WISH
TO DEFEAT KEIRO?
- WHAT?
- YOU CAN END HIS LIFE AND TRULY
BEGIN YOUR OWN AS EMPEROR.
OR WOULD YOU RATHER CONTINUE
SPOUTING THIS CHILDISH DRIVEL
ABOUT ENGAGING HIM
WITH YOUR BARE HANDS ALONE?
ABSOLUTE POWER IS IN YOUR GRASP!
THE WORLD WILL REST IN YOUR
HANDS IF YOU TAKE THE SWORD
AND RULE AS A GOD ON EARTH!
A WARRIOR GOD!
- DEPOSE TAIGA!
IT CAN WORK!
- I SEE, THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
THE PROBLEM ALL ALONG.
I UNDERSTAND NOW.
- YOU DO?
- I FINALLY UNDERSTAND WHY
ALL THAT CRAP RYUKO WAS SAYING
ABOUT KEIRO WANTING PEACE
DIDN'T SOUND LIKE HIM.
IT WAS BECAUSE
HE WAS TRYING TO MAKE
ME BELIEVE YOUR WORDS.
YOU WANT AN ANSWER? I'LL GIVE
IT TO YOU AS PLAIN AS DAY!
( yelling )
NOW, IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T UNDERSTAND,
I REFUSE TO PLAY YOUR GAME
AND BE THE EMPEROR!
- ( air whooshing )
- ( roars )
- ( chuckling )
- ( neck cricks )
- IT MATTERS NOT. AS I SAID,
THE DECISION WAS YOURS
TO MAKE, MY BOY.
I'LL HAVE PLENTY TO
KEEP ME OCCUPIED.
- HOLD ON!
- LORD KEIRO! IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER, SIR?
( gasps ) YOU'VE DRAWN IT!
THE SWORD OF RULE!
IT'S YOURS, MY LORD!
- AT LONG LAST
THE SHAWN GHEE LAN WU
CHOOSES ME AS ITS TRUE MASTER!
YES!
WITH THE POWER I NOW HOLD,
THE VERY HEAVENS SHALL
SUBMIT TO MY WILL!
( laughing diabolically )
- ( theme song playing )
- Koyo: WHAT HE TRULY DESIRED,
WAS PEACE.
- Keiro: IT WAS NOT THE BRANCHES
OF THE EMPIRE THAT WERE ROTTEN,
IT WAS DISEASED FROM
THE ROOTS UPWARD.
- Shimei: OH, HOW THEY
FLAIL AND STRUGGLE.
LABORING UNDER THE SELF-CENTERED
DELUSION OF FREE WILL,
FIGHTING AGAINST FATE.
- Taito: THAT'S
THE SWORD OF RULE.
- Keiro: AND THUS I AM TASKED
WITH RESTORING ORDER BY FORCE.
- Koyo: WHEN A STAR'S
TRAGIC PAST IS REVEALED,
WILL THE CONFLICT
CONTINUE UNABATED?
IN HERO TALES:
CHAPTER TWENTY-ONE.
"A COMMONER INFURIATED."
- WHAT HAD LAIN DORMANT
WAS AT ONCE AWOKEN,
MY KARMA AS DUBHE.