- ( panting )
- ( metal clanging )
- KANYO. JUST TRY
TO HOLD ON, PLEASE.
- IS THAT YOU, TAITO?
YEAH, IT'S ME.
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
HOW MANY ATTACKERS ARE THERE?
- JUST, JUST ONE.
- SERIOUSLY?
- ( screams )
- AT LAST XIAN JIA LAN WU,
THE SWORD OF RULE,
SHALL BE CLASPED
BY A HAND FIT TO WIELD IT.
- ( grunts )
- HMM?
BASTARD! MOWING INNOCENT PEOPLE
DOWN LIKE THEY WERE NOTHING.
WHY SHOULD I LET YOU
DRAW ONE MORE BREATH?
IF I WERE YOU, I'D RUN!
( grunts )
- THEY WHO STAND IN THE WAY
OF DESTINY SHALL FALL.
FANCY MOVE.
GUESS I CAN SEE HOW YOU STORMED
THE TEMPLE SINGLE HANDEDLY.
- MY PRIZE IS THE SWORD OF RULE,
BLADE OF CONQUERORS.
IT IS ACQUIRED EITHER
BY ONE'S METTLE ALONE
OR NOT AT ALL.
- STOP YAMMERING AND FIGHT.
THE ONLY THING YOU ARE
ACQUIRING TONIGHT, MOUSTACHE,
IS THE HONOR OF BEING
CONQUERED BY ME.
( grunts )
- TOO SLOW.
( grunting continues )
- YOU GOADED ME INTO USING
MY RIGHT ARM. VERY IMPRESSIVE.
- ( exclaims )
- DO NOT TOUCH THAT SWORD!
- ( groaning )
- DAMN YOU.
- UNHAND THE BLADE AT ONCE
AND I WILL FORGIVE
YOUR LACK OF DECORUM.
- HA! IN YOUR
DREAMS, MOUSTACHE.
OH, NOW, YOU'RE
REALLY IN FOR IT.
I'M NOT A GUY
YOU WANNA MESS WITH.
- FOOLISH BOY.
YOU GRIP THE HILT OF A WEAPON
FAR BEYOND THE POWER OF AN
INSECT LIKE YOU TO UNSHEATHE.
- SHUT YOUR FACE.
( grunting )
- NO, IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( screams )
- WHAT IN THE HELL WAS THAT?
- XIAN JIA LAN WU
CHOOSES ALKAID OVER ME?
( screams ) NO!
THE HEAVENS WILL SEE
OUR FINAL RECKONING THIS NIGHT.
- WHAT? WHY DOES EVERYTHING
YOU SAY SOUND CRAZY?
- I WILL VANQUISH YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- THEN WALK THE WALK, MOUSTACHE.
WHAT WAS THAT SHOCKWAVE
ALL ABOUT JUST NOW?
DON'T TELL ME THIS GUY'S
BEEN HOLDING OUT.
- ( yelling )
- DIE!
- YOU'VE ONLY POWER ENOUGH
TO DRAW THE SWORD.
EVEN THOUGH ALKAID,
YOU ARE STILL LITTLE
MORE THAN A CHILD. WHAT?
- I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET.
MY FALLEN BROTHERS
WILL BE AVENGED.
- WILL YOU NEVER LEARN?
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
( gasps )
- ( screaming in pain )
- ( exclaims )
- ALKAID!
- HAIL LORD KEIRO!
DID YOU SUCCEED?
THERE, BEHOLD, MEN.
YOUR LORD AND MASTER CLUTCHES
THE FABLED SWORD OF RULE,
AND WITH IT, THE VERY FORTUNES
OF THIS WORLD.
- ( crowd cheering )
- ( theme song playing )
- Sonnei: THE HEAVENLY SPHERE
PIVOTS ON THE FORTUNES
OF THE GREAT DIPPER,
A CELESTIAL RETINUE COMPOSED
OF SEVEN BRILLIANT STARS
UPON WHOSE DEEDS THE PRINCIPLE
OF KARMA IS SAID TO REST.
BUT, JUST AS HERE
IN THE EARTHLY PLANE
YIN AND YANG HOLD SWAY,
SO, TOO, DO CONTRARY POLES
DEFINE THE GREAT DIPPER'S FORM,
DUBHE AND ALKAID,
THE WILD WARRIOR GODS OF OLD.
FOREVER CLASHING,
FOREVER CALLING UPON THE PEOPLE
TO CHOOSE SIDES
AND TAKE UP ARMS.
- ( panting )
( gasps ) THERE YOU ARE.
HOLD ON, TAITO, I'M COMING.
- ( knocking on door )
- MASTER SONNEI. SENIOR SOEI.
- NO NEED TO BE FORMAL. WE'RE
SORRY TO HAVE KEPT YOU WAITING.
THE PAST FEW DAYS
HAVE CLAIMED MORE
THAN THEIR SHARE
OF OLD FRIENDS.
- AND IF NOT FOR YOU, RYUKO,
MY SON MIGHT BE AMONG THEM.
OUR THANKS.
- PLEASE, WE REALLY
ONLY HAVE DUMB LUCK TO THANK.
WELL, THAT, I SUPPOSE,
AND MY TRULY DEPLORABLE
SENSE OF DIRECTION.
- NO. YOUR STUMBLING
ACROSS TAITO WAS FATE.
- AS ARE ALL THINGS, MASTER.
- FOOLS ARE A HEARTY LOT,
THEIR CARETAKERS LESS SO.
- AND I AM GRATEFUL
FOR ONE LESS KIN TO MOURN.
- PLEASE FORGIVE MY INDOLENCE.
- I ONLY WISH I MIGHT HAVE
ARRIVED HERE A BIT EARLIER.
- DON'T START HAUNTING
YOURSELF WITH "WHAT IFS".
I'M GUILTY ENOUGH
FOR HAVING GONE TO EMEI SHAN.
- AND I INVITED YOU
TO THE MOON VIEWING.
- PERHAPS THERE'S NOTHING
WE COULD'VE DONE.
I MEAN, THE QING LONG PLATOON
AND THE PRIESTS OF LIAN TONG,
ALL OVERWHELMED BY A SINGLE MAN.
IT BEGGARS BELIEF.
- EVEN ALKAID WAS HELPLESS
AGAINST HIM.
- MASTER SONNEI, YOU MEAN...
- Laila: TAITO. TAITO.
HEY, TAI... OH, SORRY.
HI, MASTER SONNEI.
- ( laughs ) YOU'RE
IN HIGH SPIRITS TODAY, LAILA.
- WELL, I WOULD BE
IF MY STUPID BROTHER
WASN'T BEING SUCH A PAIN.
( laughs ) IS...
- HE'S OUT OF THE WOODS NOW.
HIS WOUNDS HAVE HEALED NICELY.
- REALLY? WELL, THEN, SOMEONE
NEEDS TO GET UP, DON'T THEY?
- ( groaning )
- RISE AND SHINE, SLEEPY HEAD.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- YOU'RE GONNA GIVE ME
A PERCUSSION, GENIUS.
- YOU MEAN CONCUSSION.
- SHUT UP.
I KNOW WHAT I MEANT.
- ( screams )
RUN FOR YOUR LIVES. THERE'S
AN ANGRY IDIOT ON THE LOOSE.
- YOU'D BETTER RUN AWAY.
DAMN IT.
- I TAKE IT THEY KNOW
EACH OTHER?
- MY DEAR SWEET DAUGHTER.
HIS LOVING SISTER.
- ( laughing loudly )
- OH, WHEN I GET MY HANDS
ON YOU, YOU'RE GONNA BE SORRY.
- AW, AND WHAT'S GRUMPY
GONNA DO?
UH, TAITO, WHAT ARE YOU
STARING AT?
- ( people chattering )
- KANYO...
LIAN TONG TEMPLE WAS MY HOME,
TAI SHAN MY GARDEN.
THE PRIESTS AND THE BRAVE
WARRIORS OF QUING LONG PLATOON,
SOME OF MY CLOSEST FRIENDS.
- ( breathing heavily )
- DAMN IT!
- HOLD ON!
- ( grunting angrily )
- TAITO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP!
- ( rumbling )
- ( Laila screaming )
- WHAT KIND OF A MORON ARE YOU?
LASHING OUT LIKE THAT?
- YOU OUGHT TO BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY PERSON
WHO MISSES THEM, YOU KNOW.
THEY WERE ALL MY FRIENDS, TOO.
WE'RE THE LUCKY ONES HERE, TAI.
LOOK, THOSE PEOPLE
THERE HAD EVERYTHING
TAKEN AWAY FROM THEM.
WE STILL HAVE OUR LIVES.
WE STILL HAVE EACH OTHER.
AND WE STILL HAVE OUR MEMORIES
OF THEM TO KEEP THEM ALIVE.
- ( grunts )
I'M STRONG, RIGHT?
I'M A FIGHTER
THEN, WHY COULDN'T I BEAT HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
( exclaims ) HERE.
- WAIT. LAILA...
- WHY ARE MEN SO STUPID
AND USELESS?
WINNING AND LOSING ARE THE ONLY
THINGS THEY EVER CARE ABOUT.
TAITO, YOU'RE A HEARTLESS IDIOT!
- ( grunting )
WHY AM I UNABLE TO DRAW IT?
THE ALKAID BOY,
HE MUST STILL BE ALIVE.
SO BE IT.
IF THE SWORD WILL NOT DEIGN
TO CHOOSE ME,
I WILL TAKE
THE LAND BY FORCE.
SHIMEI, EMERGE.
- EVER THE WARY EYE
HAS MY LORD KEIRO.
- EVEN THE DEAD FIND
NO QUARTER IN WHICH TO HIDE.
- DO IT.
- WITH PLEASURE, YOUR GRACE.
REST ASSURED.
- ALKAID MUST PERISH, AS WILL
ALL WHO STAND IN MY WAY.
- Ryuko: INCREDIBLE.
THE BLADE OF CONQUERORS?
THE SHINING SYMBOL
OF THE XIAN EMPIRE'S DESTINY?
- INDEED. THE VERY SAME.
HE WHO UNSHEATHES IT REIGNS,
ACCORDING TO THEIR FATE.
- BUT I THOUGHT EMPEROR TAIGA
POSSESSED THE SWORD OF RULE?
- HIS IS A RUSE.
THE REAL ONE HAS BEEN HIDDEN
IN THE LIAN TONG TEMPLE
FOR YEARS.
- WHY SHOULD THE EMPEROR
NEED A RUSE?
- BECAUSE, MY BOY,
HE COULD NOT DRAW THE BLADE.
- HE'S A FRAUD?
- HIS POSITION CERTAINLY
IS A PRECARIOUS ONE.
HE'D PREFER NOT TO
ANNOUNCE THE FACT.
THE EMPIRE STANDS ON THE BRINK
OF RUIN AND DISSOLUTION
AS IT IS.
- ( grunts ) WE'VE KEPT UP
THE MASQUERADE,
AND THIS IS
WHERE IT'S GOTTEN US.
- SO, THE BANDIT'S INTENTION
WAS TO STEAL XIAN JIA LAN WU.
ANY IDEA WHO HE WAS?
- A FACTION OF TROOPS
WERE SEEN IN THE MOUNTAINS.
THEY BORE FLAGS EMBLAZONED
WITH THE SIGN OF THE WOLF.
- THEY WHAT? SUCH FLAGS
ARE BORNE ONLY BY THE ELITE.
- Soei: OF THE IMPERIAL ARMY,
YES.
- SUCH FOOLISHNESS.
THEIR GAMBIT IS FOLLY.
- ONLY THE SWORD ITSELF
MAY CHOOSE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HE WHO WOULD FORCE
THE HAND OF FATE
HAS LEFT THE PATH OF WISDOM.
SUCH A WEAPON CANNOT
BE UNSHEATHED
BY CUNNING
OR BRUTE STRENGTH.
IT ALONE DECREES IT'S MASTER.
- YOU BASTARD. I'LL MAKE YOU PAY
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
- MAYBE I WAS A LITTLE HARSH.
POOR GUY.
( inhales ) OKAY.
HEY, TAITO.
- ( exclaiming )
ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I COULD'VE PLUNDERED
TO MY DEATH.
- I THINK YOU MEAN PLUMMETED.
- SHUT YOUR FACE.
I KNOW WHAT I MEANT!
- OH, COME ON. DON'T BE MAD.
YOUR ADORABLE SISTER
WANTS TO SEE YOU SMILE.
- OKAY, YOU'RE ACTING WEIRD.
- I'M ACTING WEIRD?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
TRADED THE CAREFREE TAITO
WE ALL KNOW AND LOVE
FOR THIS GLOOMY GUY.
- HEY, UH, THANKS
FOR PICKING THOSE HERBS.
- YEAH, WELL, I'M JUST
GLAD THERE'S NO HERB
FOR CURING STUPIDITY.
I'D BE PICKING THAT ONE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- STOP MAKING FUN OF ME.
YOU KNOW I AM STILL YOUR
OLDER BROTHER,
EVEN IF WE'RE
NOT RELATED BY BLOOD.
- I KNOW, YOU'D BE SMARTER
IF WE WERE.
- ( chuckles )
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'D BETTER RUN.
- OH, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
HE DOES HAVE SOME SKILL,
ALAS, NOT ENOUGH
TO BE A THREAT.
ALKAID WOULD HAVE SENSED ME
LONG BEFORE NOW.
SO, WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
AN EXCELLENT IDEA.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( martial art cries )
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I JUST FINISHED DOING
THE LAUNDRY.
- Shimei: GOOD AFTERNOON,
YOUNG LADY.
- ( gasps )
- SORRY TO STARTLE YOU.
MY MASTER'S DISPATCHED ME
ON A VERY IMPORTANT ERRAND.
- IMPORTANT TO HIM, AT
LEAST, HOWEVER...
- WHAT'S YOUR BUSINESS WITH ME?
- I'VE COME TO SEE WHAT ALKAID
IS CAPABLE OF, DEAR HEART.
- DID YOU JUST SAY "ALKAID"?
- IF I FIND HIS POWERS WANTING,
I AM TO DESTROY HIM.
THAT'S THE GIST OF IT, ANYWAY.
- ( exclaims )
( Laila screaming )
- I KNOW THAT SCREAM.
SIS, I'M COMING.
LAILA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU OKAY?
- STAY AWAY FROM ME.
JUST GO.
- WHY'D YOU YELL? SOMETHING...
( groaning )
- HEY, WHAT GIVES?
- TAI. I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT THE ONE DOING IT.
- PRETTY USEFUL TRICK, EH?
I HAVE TO SAY, THE GIRL MAKES
AN EXQUISITE MARIONETTE.
- YOU SON OF A...
- NOW, NOW...
- DON'T WASTE THAT PRECIOUS
ANGER ON WORDS.
I CAME TO SEE
ALKAID IN ACTION.
- WAIT. THAT NAME,
I'VE HEARD IT BEFORE.
- HAVE YOU NO IDEA WHAT YOU ARE?
- PLEASE, STOP THIS.
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE'S
BEEN KEPT IN THE DARK.
ALKAID IS A WARRIOR GOD,
A WRATHFUL STAR
DESTINED TO PLUNGE THE
EARTHLY PLANE INTO CHAOS
AS HE SLAKES HIS UNQUENCHABLE
THIRST FOR DESTRUCTION.
- WHAT?
- YOU, I'M AFRAID, GET THE
BALANCE OF HIS KARMIC DEBT.
THE MARK UPON YOUR BODY
LEAVES NO ROOM FOR DOUBT.
MY MASTER, LORD KEIRO,
BEARS THE MARK OF
ALKAID'S OPPOSITE, DUBHE,
WITH WHOM YOU'RE FATED
TO SCRAPE SHIELDS.
- WAIT A MINUTE. YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU'RE MOUSTACHE'S LACKEY?
( screaming )
YOU BASTARD!
- ( laughing )
OH MY. THIS IS TOO EASY.
TRUE, I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO BE MUCH OF A CHALLENGE,
BUT THIS IS PATHETIC!
- ( grunting )
- TAITO.
- YOU'VE GOT QUITE A LONG WAY
TO GO BEFORE YOU CAN LIVE UP
TO YOUR STAR'S EXAMPLE.
YOU LACK AMBITION,
RESOLVE, CUNNING,
AND OF COURSE HATRED.
- UGH! WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU, YOU PERV?
- QUITE THE FEISTY LITTLE
CHERRY BLOSSOM, EH?
JUST THE SORT OF GIRL
I CAN'T RESIST.
- NO. LAILA...
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HER.
- ( Laila gasps )
- CERTAIN PEOPLE ARE
VERY SLOW TO ANGER.
THEY'RE MUCH LIKELIER
TO BE PROVOKED
WHEN THE LIFE OF A LOVED ONE
HANGS IN THE BALANCE.
NOW LET'S SEE,
WHERE IS THE HEART?
- STOP IT, DAMN YOU! STOP IT!
- OH, DOES THIS BORE YOU?
HOW ABOUT THIS?
- ( Laila screaming )
- LAILA! WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
- I'VE TAKEN THE LIBERTY
OF MAKING THINGS MORE EXCITING.
WATCHING A LOVELY YOUNG THING
STRANGLE HERSELF
IS SUCH
RARE PLEASURE.
- ( laughing )
- ( choking )
- JUST LOOK AT THOSE EYES
BULGING OUT OF HER HEAD.
- BASTARD, YOU'RE DEAD,
YOU HEAR ME?
- SUCH SAD, EMPTY LITTLE NOISES
YOU BOTH MAKE.
AM I SUPPOSED
TO FEEL THREATENED?
- ( whimpers ) TAITO...
- WHERE'S THAT STRENGTH?
POOR CHILD, IS THERE
NOTHING YOU CAN DO?
YOU FAILED TO SAVE
YOUR FRIENDS, AND NOW,
YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO LIE THERE SNIVELING
WHILE YOUR LITTLE SISTER
DIES LIKE AN ANIMAL.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( explosion )
- NO.
- I FEEL IT. A DREADFUL POWER
HAS AWAKENED.
- TAITO...
- SO, THERE'S A LITTLE FIGHT
IN THE BOY AFTER ALL.
OH, THE CATASTROPHIC DEEDS
THAT HATRED WILL SPUR YOU
TO COMMIT. WELCOME BACK, ALKAID.
IT'S BEEN SO MANY CENTURIES
SINCE YOU AND DUBHE
HAVE CLASHED IN
THE EARTHLY REALM.
WHAT A FIGHT IT'LL BE!
- ( yelling )
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryuko: A STAR ROUSED FROM
THE SLEEP OF EONS LASHES OUT.
TAITO'S REACTING
TO MY OWN MARK, SIR.
- Laila: MY FATHER DIDN'T WANT
TAITO TO LEARN THE TRUTH.
HE WANTED HIM TO KNOW
A NORMAL LIFE. A PEACEFUL LIFE.
GUESS DESTINY CAUGHT US
OFF GUARD.
- Ryuko: IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE IT KILLS YOU.
- Shimei: WE LIVE IN
INTERESTING TIMES, DON'T WE?
- Ryuko: NEXT, ON HERO TALES.
THE PATHS OF THE ETERNAL
CHAMPIONS BEGIN TO CONVERGE
IN "CHAPTER TWO,
THE KARMA OF MIZAR".
WHY IS MY STAR SIGIL RESONATING?