- Taito: WELL, THIS IS SCENIC.
WHY IS IT I GET THE FEELING
EVERY TIME WE LISTEN TO YOU,
WE'LL WIND UP
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- AH, QUIT CRYING, YOU BIG BABY.
A REAL MAN WOULD SUCK IT UP AND
KEEP HIS EYES ON THE ROAD AHEAD.
- A REAL MAN WOULD'VE GOTTEN US
TO THE CAPITAL BY NOW.
YOU KNOW, TEN WHOLE DAYS EARLIER
THAN THE NORMAL ROUTE
LIKE YOU SAID
YOU WERE GONNA DO?
- MY FRIEND, YOU HAVE REALLY
GOTTA LEARN TO LIGHTEN UP.
LAST THING THE LADIES
WANNA DEAL WITH IS A WHINER.
RIGHT, LAILA, SWEETHEART?
- COULD WE ALL JUST
KEEP MOVING ALONG, PLEASE?
- NOW YOU SEE THERE?
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
- HOSEI. REMIND ME,
EXACTLY HOW MUCH FURTHER?
- OH, YOU KNOW.
ABOUT AN HOUR OR SO, I'D SAY.
( chuckles )
IF WE'RE LUCKY.
- THAT BEING THE CASE I'D REALLY
LIKE TO TURN BACK NOW.
- Hosei: ( chuckling ) AW,
LOVE-CAKES. YOU'RE SO SCARED!
IT'S SO CUTE!
- Taito: THAT'S IT!
I'M THROWING YOU
OFF THIS MOUNTAIN!
- ( theme song playing )
- Taito: A SHORTCUT
TO THE CAPITAL. RIGHT.
- Hosei: HEY,
WILL YOU TRUST ME ALREADY?
I KNOW THESE PARTS
BETTER THAN ANYBODY.
THERE'S NOT A BACK ROAD
AROUND HERE
THAT HASN'T SEEN MY BOOT HEELS.
THE WAY I'LL TAKE YOU
WILL GET US THERE
TEN DAYS QUICKER.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THEN LET'S DO IT!
- TALK ABOUT A ONE-TRACK MIND.
"YOU'VE GOTTA GET ME
TO THE CAPITAL NOW."
"I WANNA GO TO THE CAPITAL."
IT'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE,
YOU KNOW.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF TIME.
( laughs )
LAILA, SPEAKING OF MINDS,
HAVE YOU CHANGED YOURS
ABOUT ME YET?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- EVERYTHING ABOUT THE ATTITUDE
YOU'RE GIVING OFF IS CUTE.
- OKAY, SO ANYWAY,
IF YOU CAN GET US
TO THE CAPITAL THAT QUICKLY,
I'M ALL FOR IT.
THE SOONER MOUSTACHE AND ME ARE
LOOKING EACH OTHER EYE TO EYE,
THE BETTER FOR EVERYONE.
- ALL RIGHT.
JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME!
- FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
EVERYTHING OUT OF
YOUR MOUTH HAS BEEN A LIE.
YOU'VE BEEN LEADING US
TO YOUR MASTER'S PLACE
THIS WHOLE TIME
AND I WAS DUMB ENOUGH
TO FALL FOR IT
'CAUSE THE ONLY WAY THAT I...
( shouts )
- HEY, I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO!
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU GUYS
WOULD'VE COME ALONG
IF I'D TOLD YOU
WHERE WE WERE REALLY GOING.
I MEAN, GIVE ME A BREAK.
I COULDN'T BEAR PARTING WAYS
WITH MY DEAR, SWEET LAILA
SO SOON!
- REMIND ME
WHY I SHOULD GIVE A DAMN!
- LOWER YOUR VOICE, TAITO.
HE'S ACQUIRED THE WEAPON
MEANT FOR HIM AS INSTRUCTED.
SO, HE'S OBLIGED TO REPORT BACK
TO HIS MASTER.
- GOOD FOR HIM!
IS HE ALSO OBLIGED TO
MAKE SURE WE ALL TAG ALONG?
- SO, UH, HOSEI, YOU TOLD US
THIS MASTER OF YOURS
WAS PRETTY MEAN.
WAS THAT A FIB TOO
OR IS OUR GOING
A WHOLE "SAFETY IN NUMBERS"
KIND OF THING?
- IT'S TRUE. MEAN DOESN'T EVEN
BEGIN TO DESCRIBE HER.
SHE'S A BEAST!
- REALLY, HOSEI!
THAT IS NO WAY TO SPEAK
ABOUT YOUR MASTER!
- OH, SURE, THAT'S EASY
FOR YOU TO SAY, MAN.
YOU'VE GOT NO IDEA
WHAT SHE'S LIKE!
( panicked cry )
SHE'D TAKE BEING CALLED A BEAST
A COMPLIMENT!
IF SHE THOUGHT
I'D FOUND THE SHUANG CHAN BOW
AND GONE TO THE CAPITAL
WITHOUT TELLING HER FIRST,
YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO KNOW
WHAT SHE'D DO TO ME.
- Demon Koei: HOSEI!
WHY DID YOU NOT RETURN
TO ME DIRECTLY
AFTER OBTAINING THE BOW,
YOU VILE LITTLE WORM?
- ( Hosei screams )
I'M SORRY, BENEVOLENT MASTER!
PLEASE HAVE MERCY!
- YOU DARE BEG FOR MERCY?
( roars angrily )
- ( screams )
AND THAT'S HER IN A GOOD MOOD,
BELIEVE ME.
- DON'T BE SILLY! COME ON.
- MOCK MY PAIN, BUT YOU'LL SEE
FOR YOURSELVES SOON ENOUGH!
WHENEVER SHE STOMPS HER FEET,
THERE'S AN EARTHQUAKE.
WHEN SHE RAISES HER VOICE,
BIRDS FALL OUT OF THE SKY.
SHE CAN CUT DOWN A WHOLE FOREST
WITH HER BARE HANDS.
SHE EMPTIES A BOTTLE OF SAKE
EVERY SINGLE NIGHT.
HER MAKEUP IS THICK,
AND SHE SNORES LIKE A MAN.
- YEAH, YOU PROBABLY SHOULD'VE
STARTED THAT LIST IN REVERSE.
- RETURNING TO HER IS THE LAST
THING IN THE WORLD I WANT TO DO,
BUT WHAT CHOICE DOES A POOR
YOUNG LAD LIKE ME REALLY HAVE?
OH, LAILA!
- ( Taito cries in fear )
- IF ONLY YOU AND I COULD
SOMEHOW RUN AWAY TOGETHER.
BUT SHE WOULD TRACK US DOWN.
WE WOULD BE
CRUELLY RIPPED APART...
- HEY! JERK,
GET YOUR FILTHY PAWS OFF HER!
- IDIOT. WE'RE HAVING
A TENDER MOMENT!
- IF YOU CALL ME THAT
ONE MORE TIME...
- WATCH IT.
FINE! HOW ABOUT
I JUST CALL YOU MORON?
SHUT UP! YOU GOT SOMETHING
TO SAY TO ME, TOUGH GUY,
YOU SAY IT TO MY FACE!
- WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
THAT'S WHAT HE JUST DID.
( arguing )
- THIS MUST BE THE PLACE.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
REMEMBER, YOU SWORE AN OATH.
PAY ATTENTION. WE'RE ABOUT
TO HAVE STORIES TO LAST US
THE REST OF OUR JOURNEY.
ASSUMING I SURVIVE
INTRODUCING YOU.
- WOW. THE POOR GUY'S REALLY
PETRIFIED OF HER, ISN'T HE?
I'M ACTUALLY STARTING TO FEEL
A LITTLE NERVOUS MYSELF.
- ME, TOO.
- Hosei: MASTER, I'VE RETURNED!
- YOU'RE BACK!
- ( all gasp )
- OH, I'VE BEEN SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU!
I CAN'T IMAGINE
HOW EXHAUSTED YOU MUST BE.
YOU DIDN'T GET HURT, DID YOU?
MY, YOU'VE GROWN!
I'LL BET YOU'RE STARVING. RIGHT?
- MASTER! STOP IT, PLEASE!
- SORRY, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
LET ME GUSH FOR A LITTLE BIT.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
MY FAVORITE PUPIL RETURNS
FROM A DANGEROUS MISSION.
YOU ARE EVEN MORE ADORABLE
THAN WHEN YOU LEFT!
- MASTER, THERE'S SOME PEOPLE
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET.
- WAIT, WHAT?
OH, DEAR!
( giggles )
WELCOME TO MY HOME.
- THIS IS HER? TOTALLY NOT
WHAT I WAS EXPECTING.
- I THINK HE MIGHT'VE BEEN...
- COMPLETELY FULL OF CRAP?
- PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
JUST CALL ME KOEI, IF YOU LIKE.
YOU MUST BE LAILA AND TAITO FROM
THE LIAN TONG TEMPLE, CORRECT?
AND THAT MAKES YOU RYUKO
FROM THE TONG YO TEMPLE.
- NO OFFENSE, MA'AM, BUT HOW
DO YOU KNOW WHO WE ARE?
- AH, WELL, I HEARD WORD OF
MASTER SONNEI SUMMONING RYUKO.
AND THAT THE THREE OF YOU
SET OUT TOGETHER
ON A JOURNEY
TOWARDS THE CAPITAL.
CONSIDERING HOW THE STARS
HAVE BEEN MOVING AS OF LATE,
IT WAS REALLY ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOUR PATHS CROSSED
WITH THAT OF MY BELOVED HOSEI.
- Both: OH.
- YOU ARE KNOWN AS
YIYANG'S FOUNT OF KNOWLEDGE.
ONE CAN SEE THE NAME IS JUST.
I AM AT YOUR SERVICE, MY LADY.
- OH, MY!
FLATTERY WILL
GET YOU EVERYWHERE!
HOSEI, DARLING,
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO HAVE MADE ME OUT
TO BE SOME KIND OF CRAZY,
SADISTIC DEMON WOMAN
TO YOUR NEW FRIENDS,
NOW WOULD YOU?
- I MAY HAVE PAINTED
A SOMEWHAT VIVID PICTURE,
BUT IT WAS TRUE TO LIFE.
I MEAN, IT WAS ONLY FAIR
THAT I PREPARE THEM
FOR MEETING THE HAG BEAST!
- WHY, YOU VILE BOY!
THAT YOU WOULD EVEN ASSOCIATE
SUCH A HORRIBLE IMAGE
WITH A DELICATE
YOUNG FLOWER LIKE ME!
- DELICATE AND YOUNG, HUH?
EVERYONE KNOWS
YOU'RE TURNING 39 THIS YEAR!
- KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN!
- HOW MANY LAYERS OF MAKEUP
DO YOU THINK IT'LL TAKE
TO LOOK 38?
- "HOW MANY"?
YOU BED-WETTING LITTLE BRAT!
ONE MORE WORD AND I...
I WILL MAKE YOU CUT FIREWOOD
WITH YOUR TEETH!
- HEY, THE REAL YOU
IS COMING UP FOR SOME AIR.
BETTER PEEL BACK A FACE OR TWO
SO THE OLD GAL CAN ACTUALLY
BREAK THE SURFACE.
- YOU HAVE TILL THE COUNT OF
THREE TO TAKE BACK
WHAT YOU JUST SAID!
- KINDA HARD TO BUY THEM
AS MASTER AND PUPIL, HUH?
- IF YOU ASK ME, THEY'RE MORE
LIKE BROTHER AND SISTER.
- ( Taito and Laila sigh )
- Koei: HONESTLY, YOU'D THINK
I'D ASKED HIM TO RID THE WORLD
OF PESTILENCE
OR BRING ME THE HEAD OF
A DRAGON OR SOMETHING.
I'D FIGURED YOU'D RUN OFF.
- YEAH, WELL, EXCUSE ME
FOR TAKING SO LONG,
BUT A CLUE MIGHT'VE HELPED SOME.
- ♪ I CAN'T MAKE OUT
A WORD YOU'RE SAYING ♪
- YOU KNEW WHERE THE BOW WAS?
BUT WHY MAKE HOSEI
SEARCH EVERYWHERE FOR IT
WHEN YOU COULD'VE
JUST DRAWN HIM A MAP?
- ♪ I CAN'T UNDERSTAND YOU
EITHER WHY DO YOU KIDS MUMBLE? ♪
- BELIEVE ME, SHE'S SPENT
A LONG LIFETIME ON THIS MOUNTAIN
SQUIRRELING AWAY EVERY SCRAP
OF INFORMATION SHE HEARS.
GUESS WHEN YOU GET
RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
THERE ISN'T MUCH
SHE DOESN'T KNOW.
- EXACTLY. ME TO KNOW
AND YOU TO FIND OUT.
THERE'D BE NO FUN IN MY JUST
LAYING THINGS OUT FOR PEOPLE
ALL THE TIME.
- YEAH, WHY MAKE ME
JUMP THROUGH ONE HOOP
WHEN YOU COULD MAKE ME JUMP
THROUGH 1,000, RIGHT?
- ♪ BLAH BLAH BLAH
HOSEI'S MUMBLING, BLAH ♪
- FORGIVE MY SAYING SO,
LADY KOEI,
BUT THIS WHIMSICAL
SENSE OF HUMOR
IS A BIT SURPRISING
IN SOMEONE SO WISE.
- WHIMSICAL, EH?
WOULD IT BE PRESUMPTUOUS
OF ME TO HEAR THAT
AS YOUR WAY OF SAYING THAT
I ACT LIKE A CHILD?
- NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I...
THERE'S NO HIDDEN MEANING TO IT.
PLEASE EXCUSE MY RUDENESS.
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
THIS AWKWARDNESS
IS A BIT SURPRISING COMING FROM
SOMEONE SO WORLDLY,
ESPECIALLY ONE OF
THE DIPPER BEARERS.
- THE WHOLE THING'S AWKWARD!
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO MAKE OF ALL THIS STUFF!
ONE MINUTE I'M JUST NORMAL
EVERYDAY TAITO
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
SUDDENLY EVERYONE'S SPOUTING OFF
TO ME ABOUT BEING ALKAID.
I MEAN, GIVE A GUY
A REST, RIGHT?
ALL I WANNA DO IS GIVE MOUSTACHE
WHAT HE'S GOT COMING TO HIM!
- AND MOUSTACHE IS?
- LORD KEIRO,
AN IMPERIAL GENERAL
AND THE INCARNATION OF DUBHE.
- OH, HOW INTERESTING.
DESTINY DOES FOLLOW
THE PATH OF LEAST RESISTANCE.
THE STARS SHAPE OUR FORTUNES
WHATEVER MEN DO.
AS OFTEN AS NOT, WE SET
FATE IN MOTION BY OUR DENIAL.
PHECDA IS CAREFREE.
WHILE MIZAR IS THE WORRIER,
IS HE NOT?
- WELL, YES, BUT...
- AND YOU... ALKAID IS EVER
THE MOST TEMPESTUOUS OF STARS.
BUT WITHOUT CHANNELING,
HE HAS NO HOPE AGAINST DUBHE.
- ( swallows hard )
( chokes )
- YOU CAN REALLY TELL THAT?
- YES. IT'S RATHER EASY TO SPOT
IF YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR, ACTUALLY.
CHANNELERS GIVE OFF
A VERY UNIQUE SORT OF ENERGY.
- FOOLS, BEWARE!
THE HAG BEAST SEES ALL!
- LUCKY FOR YOU,
FATE BROUGHT YOU TO MY DOORSTEP.
SEE, I JUST HAPPEN TO BE
AN EXPERT IN SCHOOLING WARRIORS
LIKE YOURSELF
IN THE WAYS OF CHANNELING.
- YEAH? YOU COULD TEACH ME?
- THIS IS
AN AWESOME OPPORTUNITY, TAITO!
SURE SHE'S VICIOUS
AND IT'S KINDA HARD
TO LOOK AT HER,
BUT MY MASTER'S
THE BEST TEACHER EVER!
- THE JAB AT MY LOOKS
WAS A LITTLE UNNECESSARY.
- THIS IS WONDERFUL. IT'S
AN EXTREMELY GENEROUS OFFER.
YOU SHOULD ACCEPT.
- BUT KEEP IN MIND, WHAT I HAVE
TO TEACH YOU DOESN'T GUARANTEE
VICTORY OVER KEIRO.
- I'M READY TO KNOW.
SHOW ME THE WAY.
- VERY WELL. YOUR TRAINING
REGIMEN BEGINS AT DUSK.
AND IF I WERE YOU,
I'D MAKE SURE TO REST UP WELL
BETWEEN NOW AND THEN.
- ( birds chirping )
- Taiga: SUCH LOVELY FLOWERS.
- THANK YOU, YOUR HIGHNESS.
THEY'RE MOTH ORCHIDS.
- HMM. MOTH ORCHIDS.
- Man: THERE YOU ARE,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- SHOKAKU.
- LORD KEIRO HAS RETURNED,
YOUR MAJESTY.
HE SEEKS AN AUDIENCE.
- WHAT NEWS BRINGS HE
OF THE REBELLION?
- BY YOUR ORDERS HE HAS ROUTED
VIRTUALLY EVERY ENEMY
OF THE THRONE, MY LIEGE.
- BY MY ORDERS?
I NEVER GAVE...
- THIS IS A PROUD MOMENT
FOR YOUR FATHER, LADY TAKI.
IT WOULD BE ALL THE PROUDER
FOR YOUR PRESENCE ALONGSIDE HIM.
- YES, OF COURSE.
- Choka: THEY'VE GROWN SO CLOSE.
A BOY EMPEROR AND
THE DAUGHTER
OF AN ILLUSTRIOUS
IMPERIAL GENERAL
AT THE HEIGHT OF HIS FAME.
THEIR PAIRING
BALANCES QUITE NICELY.
- INDEED IT DOES, MY LADY.
NO DOUBT YOU LABORED TIRELESSLY
TO SEE TO IT THAT BALANCE
WAS STRUCK. WELL DONE.
- ( birds chirping )
- Koei: ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU READY?
- Taito: YOU BET I AM.
- YOU'RE COCKY NOW, BUT LET'S
SEE YOU PICK THAT ATTITUDE
OFF THE GROUND
AFTER SHE'S SMACKED YOU ONE.
- FIRST OF ALL,
ALLOW YOUR ENERGY TO GATHER
AS YOU NORMALLY WOULD.
STAY CALM AND FOCUS.
- RIGHT.
AH, DAMN IT.
- YOU SEE?
HE LACKS PROPER CONTROL.
- OH, MAN. TAITO, OLD BUDDY,
GET READY FOR THE BEATING
OF YOUR LIFE.
- LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN NOW,
SHALL WE?
- ( gasps )
- I SENSE AN INNER RESERVOIR.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THIS TIME,
LET'S TRY IT
WITHOUT A WEAPON PER SE.
- ( Ryuko gasps )
LADY KOEI,
IT'S FAR TOO DANGEROUS!
WITHOUT SOMETHING TO ACT
AS A CONDUIT,
HIS BODY MAY NOT WITHSTAND
THAT KIND OF ENERGY!
- JUST WAIT AND SEE.
NOW THE OBJECT HERE, TAITO,
IS TO TRY
NOT BREAKING THE ARMBAND.
- RIGHT, WELL, I'LL TRY.
( guttural groan )
- TAKE IT EASY, LAD.
CHANNELING'S ALL ABOUT FOCUS,
NOT STRENGTH.
LOOSEN UP A BIT.
GOOD, NOW CLOSE YOUR EYES.
TRY TO VISUALIZE YOUR ARM
AS A KIND OF SOFT TUBE.
- A SOFT TUBE, YOU GOT IT.
- ( both gasp )
- ( gasps )
- I DON'T INTEND
TO HOLD BACK, TAITO.
( yells )
THAT WAS EXCELLENTLY DONE!
LOOK AT YOUR ARM!
- I... I DIDN'T BREAK THE BAND.
AND I THREW THAT PUNCH
WITH EVERYTHING I HAD, TOO.
YOU SEE NOW THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN ENERGY AND STRENGTH?
WHEN CHANNELED PROPERLY,
ENERGY IS INEXHAUSTIBLE.
- BUT, LADY KOEI,
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
- IT'S QUITE
STRAIGHTFORWARD, REALLY.
YOU SEE, OUR YOUNG FRIEND HERE
POSSESSES WHAT THE ANCIENTS
CALLED AN INNER RESERVOIR.
- AN INNER WHAT?
- AND DOES THIS INNER RESERVOIR
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE EIGHTH STYLE
LONG BELIEVED TO BE LOST?
- YES. THE STRICTLY WEAPON-BASED
STYLES YOU AND HOSEI ADOPT
UTILIZE OUTER RESERVOIRS.
YOU CAN'T CHANNEL WITHOUT
AN OBJECT, IN OTHER WORDS,
BUT TAITO IS CAPABLE OF USING
HIS BODY AS YOU DO YOUR STAFF.
IT'S QUITE A TALENT TO HAVE,
BELIEVE YOU ME.
AND IT WILL TAKE A GREAT DEAL
OF TRAINING TO MASTER.
BUT IF YOU CAN CALL TO MEMORY
HOW IT FELT TO DO THIS ONCE,
YOU WILL GET THERE EVENTUALLY.
- THANK YOU
FOR SHOWING ME, KOEI.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
YOU BEAT ME TO A PULP
IF I SO MUCH AS BAT AN EYE
BUT YOU'RE SOFT ON THIS CLOD?
- WORDS ABSOLUTELY FAIL
TO GRASP THE DEPTHS OF
YOUR INSIGHT, LADY KOEI.
YOU ARE WITHOUT A DOUBT
ONE OF THE FINEST TEACHERS
I'VE SEEN.
- YOU REALLY ARE IN A LEAGUE
ALL BY YOURSELF!
- OH, STOP IT!
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME!
( giggles )
- HEY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
I'M THE ONE WHO
DID ALL THE WORK HERE!
- TAITO. YOU HAVE TO
MAKE A SOLEMN PROMISE.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND, CHANNELING
FROM AN INNER RESERVOIR IS AS
HAZARDOUS AS IT IS BENEFICIAL.
ONE'S MIND MUST BE CALM
AND TRANQUIL AND ONE'S SPIRIT
ABSOLUTELY DISPASSIONATE
BEFORE YOU DARE PUT IT TO USE.
NEVER, EVER,
EVEN AS A LAST RESORT,
VENTURE TO CHANNEL WHILE
IN THE THROES OF ANGER.
PROMISE YOU WON'T.
- UH... OKAY.
- WOW, TAITO.
I'VE NEVER HEARD YOU AGREE
TO ANYTHING SO FAST.
I DON'T THINK I KNOW
THIS SIDE OF YOU!
- SHE ASKED ME TO PROMISE!
YOU GOT AN ISSUE WITH THAT?
- IT IS SOMEWHAT BIZARRE.
- SO, WHAT? I CAN'T AGREE
TO SOMETHING IF I FEEL LIKE IT?
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS CRAP.
- Ryuko, Taito and Laila:
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL!
- MAN, THAT WAS GOOD GRUB!
I SWEAR, THERE MUST BE NOTHING
YOU CAN'T DO!
- I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
- YOU ARE SO LUCKY TO GET TO EAT
LIKE THIS ALL THE TIME!
IF YOU'D TOLD US SHE COULD COOK,
WE WOULD'VE RACED YOU HERE!
- YEAH. SHE FEEDS ME WELL.
EXCUSE ME FOR A MINUTE
WHILE I STEP OUT FOR SOME AIR.
- Taito: THERE'S AIR
IN THE HOUSE.
- PARDON HIS MANNERS.
HE DOES TEND TO SULK.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- IT'S BECAUSE I PRAISED
YOUR BROTHER EARLIER.
HE'S LIKELY UPSET
I WASN'T MORE HARSH WITH HIM.
SEE, IN HOSEI'S CASE,
I WAS STRICT FROM THE BEGINNING.
ONE HAS TO BE WITH CHILDREN.
I WAS OBLIGED TO
TAME A WILD BEAST, AS IT WERE.
OTHERWISE HE WOULD NEVER
HAVE LEARNED SELF-DISCIPLINE.
POOR BOY'S SO SENSITIVE, THOUGH.
- SO DOES THAT MEAN...
- YES. HE'S AN ORPHAN.
WHATEVER YOU MAY THINK OF HIM,
KNOW THAT CAVALIER EXTERIOR
HIDES A HEART OF GOLD.
HE CAN BE A HANDFUL, NATURALLY.
BUT I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU LOOKED OUT FOR HIM.
- HEY, WHENEVER HE NEEDS US,
WE'LL BE THERE.
- Laila: ISN'T SHE
JUST MARVELOUS?
I MEAN, SURE, MAYBE SHE'S
A LITTLE STRICT WITH HOSEI
AND THAT'S WHY HE TOLD US
ALL THAT STUFF,
BUT I THINK ON THE WHOLE
SHE MIGHT JUST BE
THE NEATEST PERSON
I'VE EVER MET.
DO YOU THINK IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT OUR MOTHERS MIGHT HAVE BEEN
ANYTHING LIKE HER?
- DAMN IT. WHAT GIVES?
I KEEP BREAKING THEM.
SHE SAID ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS THINK OF WHAT IT WAS LIKE
WHEN I WAS DOING IT RIGHT.
- I BET IF KOEI WAS WATCHING
YOU PRACTICE,
SHE'D TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
- LOT OF GOOD I'LL BE
IF I ALWAYS NEED HER HELP.
WHATEVER OUR MOTHERS
MIGHT HAVE BEEN LIKE,
IF THEY'D BEEN AS SWEET AS HER,
CHANCES ARE WE WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ABANDONED.
- THAT'S NOT NICE.
- COME ON.
HEY, I'M GLAD THEY WEREN'T.
'CAUSE OTHERWISE
I WOULDN'T KNOW YOU,
OR DAD, OR ANYBODY
FROM TAI SHAN. GOOD NIGHT.
- YOU STILL BENT OUT OF SHAPE?
- I'M NOT BENT OUT OF SHAPE.
- YOU CAN BE
SO THICK-SKULLED SOMETIMES.
YOU KNOW THAT DIFFERENT PEOPLE
REQUIRE DIFFERENT METHODS
OF TRAINING.
JUST LIKE FIGHTING,
YOU HAVE TO TAILOR YOUR METHODS
TO FIT THE SITUATION.
- YOU NEVER CHANGE
THE WAY YOU TRAIN ME.
STOP TRYING TO SPARE
MY FEELINGS.
YOU'D RATHER TAITO
WAS YOUR PUPIL.
- GOODNESS. NOW WHY ON EARTH
WOULD I PREFER TAITO OVER
MY CUTE, DARLING LITTLE HOSEI?
- WELL, BECAUSE... HE'S ALKAID
AND I'M JUST MEASLY OLD
PHECDA THE ARCHER.
- IS THAT WHAT THIS IS?
FINE, YES. ALKAID GETS PRIDE OF
PLACE AMONG THE DIPPER BEARERS,
I GRANT YOU.
BUT SO WHAT? WHY SHOULD THAT
MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
TO SOMEONE LIKE ME?
THIS CHANGES NOTHING
BETWEEN YOU AND I.
I WAS THE ONE WHO TOOK YOU IN.
I RAISED YOU, KICKED YOU,
BEAT YOU, SCOLDED YOU, FED YOU
AND EVENTUALLY TAUGHT YOU,
ALL BY CHOICE.
THE LEGENDS HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH MY REASON WHY.
- OF COURSE THE LEGENDS
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
BECAUSE IN THE GRAND SCHEME
OF THINGS, I'M JUST A DUMB KID.
- NEVER SAY THAT ABOUT YOURSELF!
- I CAN SEE THROUGH YOUR GAME!
YOU THINK TAITO'S BETTER THAN ME
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT!
- STUPID HAG BEAST!
- HEY, DON'T YOU RUN AWAY
FROM ME!
EVER THE WOUNDED BOY.
YOU REALLY NEED TO BE
MORE THICK-SKINNED THAN THIS.
THE STARS
ARE IN A FOUL HUMOR TONIGHT.
- THIS IS A BUNCH OF CRAP!
WHAT'S IT GONNA TAKE WITH HER?
GIVE ME A BREAK!
ALL I WANT
IS A LITTLE ENCOURAGEMENT
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN.
IS THAT TOO DAMN MUCH TO ASK?
BANDITS? WHAT THE...
HERE? NO WAY.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, ALL OF YOU!
NOW SAY HELLO
TO KOEI'S NUMBER ONE PUPIL!
THIS MOUNTAIN'S DEFENDER, HOSEI!
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
SHE'LL ACKNOWLEDGE ME!
I'VE EARNED IT.
- WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO
BY YOURSELF AT SUCH A LATE HOUR,
MY LADY?
- TO TRY AND TALK
SOME SENSE INTO HOSEI.
HE THREW ONE OF HIS
LITTLE TANTRUMS EARLIER
AND CHARGED OFF INTO THE WOODS.
- PLEASE ALLOW ME THE HONOR
OF ACCOMPANYING YOU.
IT ISN'T SAFE TO TRAVEL ALONE
AT NIGHT.
- OH, I'LL BE FINE.
I KNOW THIS MOUNTAIN
LIKE THE BACK OF MY HAND.
BESIDES, IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING
YOU'RE MORE LIKELY TO GET LOST
THAN TO BE OF ANY HELP TO ME.
- SO YOU'VE HEARD THAT ABOUT ME,
HAVE YOU?
- I'M SURE I'LL BE BACK BEFORE
TOO LONG. HE'S A DIFFICULT BOY.
IF I DON'T TRACK HIM DOWN SOON,
WHO KNOWS WHAT
HE'LL GET HIMSELF INTO.
OH, AND A WORD OF ADVICE...
- YES?
- IT'S IMPORTANT IN LIFE TO
FOLLOW A PATH YOU BELIEVE IN,
BUT NOT SO IMPORTANT AS SEEING
A WAY TO BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
- EXCELLENT ADVICE INDEED.
YOUR SENSE OF DIRECTION
ISN'T HALF AS BAD AS
YOU'VE CONVINCED YOURSELF IT IS.
- ( Hosei yells )
- ( grunts )
- HA! ONE DOWN, NINE MORE TO GO!
WHICH ONE OF YOU UGLY BASTARDS
IS NEXT IN LINE, HUH?
WHAT?
YEAH? TRY GETTIN' BACK UP
FROM THIS!
THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- Shimei: DEAR, OH DEAR. PHECDA
ALL BY HIS LONESOME AGAINST
A HORDE OF GROTESQUES.
HOW TRAGIC.
- WHO ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE?
- MY FRIENDS CALL ME SHIMEI.
- THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
- SUCH A SPITFIRE.
I BELIEVE USING YOU
WILL BE QUITE THE ROMP.
- ( screams )
- AS THE GREAT SAGE ONCE SAID,
"HELL IS WHERE YOU FIND
YOUR TRUE ALLIES."
- ( laughs )
- ( theme song playing )
- Hosei: MASTER?
WOULD YOU...
WOULD YOU BE UPSET IF I WENT
WITH LAILA AND THE GUYS
TO THE CAPITAL?
- Koei: WHY IN THE WORLD WOULD
I BE UPSET WITH YOU FOR THAT?
YOU STILL HAVE SO MUCH TO LEARN.
THE BEST REMEDY FOR THAT
IS EXPERIENCE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HOSEI, PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL TAKE CARE
OF TAITO AND THE OTHERS.
- Ryuko: NEXT ON HERO TALES,
"CHAPTER SEVEN:
SORROWFUL PHECDA."
- Hosei: I'M PROUD
YOU'RE MY MASTER.