- ( guttural groan )
- LORD KEIRO!
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER, SIR?
YOU'VE DRAWN IT!
THE SWORD OF RULE!
IT'S YOURS, MY LORD!
- AT LONG LAST, THE XIAN JIA LAN
WU CHOOSES ME
AS ITS TRUE MASTER!
- ( thunderclap )
- LORD KEIRO HAS UNSHEATHED
THE SWORD OF RULE?
- INDEED. WHAT HAD ONCE ELUDED
HIM, HE'S NOW ACCOMPLISHED.
BUT FOR WHAT REASON?
THE HEAVENS HAVE PLACED DUBHE
AT THE VERY AXIS OF THE EMPIRE.
WAS THIS DECREED BY FATE?
OR HAS KEIRO MADE FATE
ITSELF BEND TO HIS WILL?
- MY FATHER IS EMPEROR?
- ( thunderclap )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( yelling )
- ( chuckles )
- DAMN IT! THAT BASTARD!
I TOLD HIM IDON'T WANT
TO BE THE EMPEROR SO
WHY WON'T HE JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE?
I GUESS IF I REALLY
WANT THE ANSWER,
I'M JUST GONNA HAVE
TO BEAT IT OUT OF HIM!
YOU HEAR ME?
- TAITO! YOU'RE JUST DOING
WHAT HE WANTS YOU TO DO!
- DON'T BE A FOOL, MAN!
COME BACK! TAITO!
- THIS LACKADAISICAL APPROACH
THE BOY IS TAKING
WILL NOT WORK AT ALL.
FATE HAS CHOSEN THEM
TO PORTRAY ADVERSARIES
IN THIS COSMIC DRAMA.
SO I AM SIMPLY MAKING SURE
THEY HIT THEIR MARKS.
- I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU! SHIMEI!
- THOSE VESTMENTS.
- MY LORD, PLEASE FORGIVE ME
IF I'M SPEAKING OUT OF TURN.
BUT THE THRONE OF THE EMPIRE
AWAITS YOUR ASCENSION
TO MAKE SUCH A JOURNEY TONIGHT.
ARE YOU QUITE CERTAIN IT'S WISE?
- THE THRONE CAN WAIT.
HOWEVER, MY ENGAGEMENT THIS
EVENING CANNOT BE POSTPONED.
- BUT, SIR...
- THERE IS NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO DISSUADE ME.
- I SEE. IN THAT CASE I IMPLORE
YOU TO LET US BE YOUR ESCORT.
- IF YOU MUST.
- YES, MY LORD.
RYUKO, WE MUSTN'T TARRY.
- OF COURSE, SIR.
- ( panting )
- WAIT HERE.
- OF COURSE, MY LORD.
THE FOG HANGS THICK.
- ENSIGN KOCHO.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I CAN INFER KEIRO'S GARMENTS
HOLD SOME SIGNIFICANCE,
BUT WHAT?
- ANOTHER YEAR
HAS PASSED, CHOUSA.
ONE MORE SINCE OUR PARTING.
NEARLY A SCORE SINCE
I LAST GAZED UPON YOU.
- SHIMEI! STOP HIDING
AND FACE ME LIKE A MAN!
- THAT VOICE.
- SHIMEI!
MUSTACHE! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- ALKAID.
- LOOKS LIKE I'M
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
WE'VE GOTTA SETTLE THE SCORE
RIGHT HERE AND NOW!
( yelling )
- NO BLOOD SHALL BE SPILLED
ON THESE GROUNDS.
- WHAT? WHY THE HELL NOT?
HEY, WHY'RE YOU EVEN OUT HERE
DRESSED IN THOSE PRAYER ROBES?
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHOSE GRAVE IS THIS?
- IT IS MY LATE WIFE'S.
SHE WAS TAKEN FROM ME.
MURDERED BY THE FORCES
OF OUR SACRED EMPIRE.
- THAT CANNOT BE.
LORD KEIRO'S WIFE WAS MURDERED?
- YES. A VERY TRAGIC
AND PAINFUL CHAPTER
IN HIS EXCELLENCY'S LIFE
WAS WRITTEN ON THIS DAY
MANY YEARS AGO.
HE COMES HERE EVERY YEAR
TO PAY HIS RESPECTS.
GOING ALONE INTO THIS FOREST,
TO PRAY FOR HER SOUL IN PEACE.
IT IS A SOLEMN DAY INDEED.
- MY MOTHER'S GRAVE
IS IN THIS FOREST?
- RYUKO.
- YES, SIR.
- YOU HAVE QUICKLY BECOME
A TRUSTED ALLY OF LORD KEIRO,
BUT THERE'S STILL MUCH YOU
DO NOT KNOW ABOUT HIM.
IT'S TIME YOU LEARNED
OF HIS PAST.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING
THOSE IMPERIAL ARMY BASTARDS
KILLED YOUR FAMILY TOO?
DAMN IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
I FINALLY CORNER THE GUY
WHOSE ASS I WANNA KICK
MORE THAN ANYBODY
ELSE'S IN THE WORLD
AND I CAN'T BECAUSE HE'S PRAYING
AT HIS DEAD WIFE'S GRAVE.
EVEN I KNOW
THAT WOULDN'T BE RIGHT.
JUST EXPLAIN ONE THING TO ME.
WHY DID YOU ATTACK
LIAN TONG TEMPLE AGAIN?
WHY THE HELL
DID YOU KILL MY FATHER?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- DON'T LIE! YOU KNOW!
HE'S DEAD!
YOUR GOONS BURNED DOWN LIAN TONG
AND THEY MURDERED MY FATHER!
- I SEE. I GAVE THEM
NO SUCH ORDERS.
- WHAT?
- SO THE LEADER OF THE QING
LONG PLATOON HAS FALLEN.
I'D HEARD OF HIS REPUTATION FOR
GREAT STRENGTH AND INTEGRITY.
BUT NOT HIS DEATH.
- WHAT? YOU MEAN
YOU HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT?
- ALKAID, MUCH LIKE
YOUR LATE FATHER,
I TOO ONCE TOOK UP THE BANNER
OF THE WEAK AND DOWNTRODDEN,
TO SHEPHERD THEM FROM
THE EMPIRE'S UNENDING TYRANNY.
- WHAT?
- IT WOULD SEEM FATE IS NOT
WITHOUT A SENSE OF IRONY.
US MEETING HERE TONIGHT.
IT WAS A TIME BEFORE OUR CURRENT
FIGUREHEAD HELD THE THRONE.
OVER TWENTY YEARS AGO,
DURING THE REIGN OF MIYO.
- Kocho: LORD KEIRO HAILS
FROM LING FAWN,
A REMOTE REGION ON THE OUTSKIRTS
OF THE EMPIRE.
HE WAS THE SON OF KEITO.
A WISE AND VIRTUOUS LEADER,
WHO CHERISHED THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVED UNDER HIS FIEFDOM,
AND PASSED THESE NOBLE TRAITS
ONTO HIS SON.
IN TURN, BOTH MEN WERE BELOVED
AND RESPECTED BY THEIR SUBJECTS.
- AH, WISE LORD KEIRO!
- HOWEVER, THIS PEACE
WOULD NOT LAST.
A GOVERNOR GENERAL OF THE EMPIRE
DESIRED THIS FRUITFUL LAND,
AND SEIZED UPON IT
WITH UNIMAGINABLE SAVAGERY.
- KEIRO, MY SON.
THE TIME HAS COME
TO USE YOUR POWER.
DRAW UPON YOUR INNER RESERVOIR.
- FATHER, PLEASE!
- TO PROTECT OUR DEAR VILLAGERS,
YOU MUST...
KILL THAT MAN!
- ( yelling )
- NO. SPARE ME.
PLEASE, SPARE MY LIFE.
- YOU TOOK THE LIVES
OF EVERYONE IN MY VILLAGE,
MY FAMILY!
WHY SHOULD I SPARE YOURS?
- ( both yell )
- WHAT THE HELL? KILLING A MAN
LIKE THAT WOULD MAKE YOU
AN ENEMY OF THE EMPIRE,
NOT A MAJOR GENERAL.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
FOR MANY YEARS I WORE MY OUTLAW
STATUS AS A BADGE OF HONOR
WHILE FIGHTING THE EMPIRE
AS A REBEL.
- Kocho: KEIRO TRAVELED ALONE,
FAR AND WIDE ACROSS THE LAND
UNTIL ONE DAY...
- ( yelling )
- ( groaning )
- ( people chattering )
- Kocho: THAT WAS THE DAY
HE ENCOUNTERED CHOUSA.
OVER TIME, SHE WAS
ABLE TO FILL THE VOID
IN HIS EXCELLENCY'S HEART
TO EASE HIS TROUBLED SOUL,
AND FOR THAT, HE TREASURED HER.
DURING THE COURSE
OF HIS TRAVELS,
HE SPARED MANY LIVES FROM
THE BLOODY ACTS OF MEN
SEEKING DOMINION AND POWER.
MANY OF THOSE HE SAVED
PLEDGED THEIR FEALTY TO HIM
AND FOLLOWED HIM
WHEREVER HE ROAMED.
TOGETHER THEY CARVED OUT
A MOUNTAIN PASS
AND MADE THEIR HOME UNDER
ITS AND LORD KEIRO'S PROTECTION.
IT WAS AT THIS TIME
HE TRAINED THE VILLAGERS
IN THE WAYS OF BATTLE,
AND ESTABLISHED THE SCHWAN LONG
PLATOON TO KEEP A VIGIL
AGAINST THE EMPIRE'S
ENCROACHMENT.
- SO YOU GAVE THEM A SAFE PLACE?
THAT'S WHAT FATHER
DID WITH TAI SHAN!
- Keiro: OUR LIVES
WERE FILLED WITH PEACE
AND OUT OF THAT PEACE,
A CHILD WAS BORN.
- ( baby cooing )
- MY SON!
I SHALL CALL YOU KEIKO, CHILD!
I WILL RAISE YOU TO BE STRONG
AND HONORABLE. I SWEAR!
- THAT CHILD WAS ME.
- FILLED WITH
A NEWFOUND SENSE OF PURPOSE,
LORD KEIRO SET OUT TO PURGE
THE NEARBY LANDS
OF CORRUPT OFFICIALS
AND DESPOTS.
- A PURGE?
- TO RESTORE HEALTH
TO THE EMPIRE,
HE SAW IT NECESSARY TO LOP OFF
ITS ROTTEN BRANCHES, AS IT WERE.
HE DID THIS SELFLESSLY AND
WITHOUT ANY DESIRE FOR POWER.
THE EMPIRE VIEWED THIS PURGE
AS AN ACT OF TREASON,
AND METED OUT
PUNISHMENT ACCORDINGLY.
- ( thunderclap )
- Keiro: THIS HOLOCAUST
WAS THE EMPIRE'S DOING.
IT WAS AT THAT MOMENT
THAT I REALIZED I HAD BEEN
COMPLETELY WRONG IN MY THINKING.
IT WAS NOT THE BRANCHES OF
THE EMPIRE THAT WERE ROTTEN.
IT WAS DISEASED
FROM THE ROOTS UPWARD.
CHOUSA! KEIKO! CHOUSA!
CHOUSA.
CHOUSA! SPEAK TO ME!
( gasps )
NO! CHOUSA, PLEASE,
YOU CAN'T DIE!
I CURSED NOT ONLY THE EMPIRE
AND ITS UNYIELDING BRUTALITY,
BUT MY OWN INABILITY TO PROTECT
THOSE CLOSEST TO ME FROM IT.
MY RAGE BURNED
LIKE A THOUSAND SUNS.
WHAT HAD LAIN DORMANT WAS AT
ONCE AWOKEN. MY KARMA AS DUBHE.
- ( thunderclap )
- Kocho: IN TIMES
OF GREAT TURMOIL,
THE DIPPER BEARERS ARE GIVEN
THE TASK TO ACT AS BEACONS,
GUIDING THE PEOPLE
OUT OF DARKNESS.
OF THESE STARS, DUBHE'S FATE IS
TO RESTORE ORDER THROUGH FORCE.
LORD KEIRO
HAS BEEN HANDED THIS FATE.
THE HEAVENS THEMSELVES
HAVE DECREED THAT HE SHOULDER
THIS INCONCEIVABLE BURDEN.
THAT HE ALONE SHALL
BRING THE WORLD TO RIGHTS
BY THE SHEER FORCE OF HIS WILL.
( sighs )
ALL I KNOW ABOUT HIM IS WHAT
I'VE SHARED WITH YOU TONIGHT.
- THANK YOU, KOCHO.
QUITE A STORY.
- TELL ME. IF ALL
THAT STUFF IS TRUE ABOUT
WHAT THE EMPIRE DID TO YOU,
WHY ARE YOU WORKING
FOR THEM NOW?
- AFTER I BURIED CHOUSA,
I SURRENDERED TO
THE IMPERIAL FORCES
AND SWORE UNCONDITIONAL LOYALTY.
- YOU LET THEM WIN?
- YOU SEE, I KNEW IF I WOUND
MY WAY THROUGH THE RANKS,
I COULD TAKE CONTROL
FROM THE INSIDE.
REBELLIONS ARE ULTIMATELY
MEANINGLESS ACTIONS BOTH BORN
OF AND BEGETTING DESPERATION.
I WILL CONQUER THE SHAWN EMPIRE
BY USING THE POWER GRANTED
TO ITS MILITARY AS A FULCRUM
WITH WHICH TO TOPPLE IT
AND SEIZE IT FOR MY OWN.
THE HEAVENS HAVE CHOSEN
TO BESTOW THIS FATE UPON DUBHE,
AND THUS I AM TASKED
WITH RESTORING ORDER BY FORCE.
- YOU MEAN BY BLOODSHED.
- ( wind whooshing )
- I CAN UNDERSTAND YOUR REASONS
FOR DOING WHAT YOU DID
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU AND YOUR FAMILY.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT
BY CAUSING MORE SUFFERING!
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU,
I'LL MAKE SURE TO SETTLE THE
SCORE ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- WAIT.
- FOR WHAT? WE'RE DONE HERE.
( gasps )
NO. THAT'S THE SWORD OF RULE.
- ( guttural groan )
THE SWORD HAS CHOSEN ME
AS ITS MASTER!
SO KNOW THAT NEXT TIME OUR PATHS
DO CROSS, YOU WILL ADDRESS ME
AS SON OF HEAVEN, EMPEROR KEIRO!
- IF I MAY ASK, SIR,
DO YOU HAPPEN TO
KNOW WHATEVER BECAME
OF HIS EXCELLENCY'S SON, KEIKO?
- I'M TOLD THAT
HE WAS ABANDONED.
- BUT WHY?
- THE PATH TO THE THRONE
IS A BLOOD-SOAKED ONE.
I CAN IMAGINE MY LORD
DID NOT WISH HIS ONLY SON
TO BE WASHED AWAY IN IT.
- BUT WHAT OF HIS DAUGHTER?
WHAT OF TAKI?
- THE TRUTH OF IT, LADY TAKI
IS THE CHILD OF ANOTHER MAN.
- WHAT?
- PERHAPS IT IS NOT THE WILL
OF THE HEAVENS
THAT THE TWO WARRIOR GODS
OF OLD ENGAGE EACH OTHER
IN BLOODY CONFLICT AFTER ALL.
- WHAT? I DIDN'T DRAG ALKAID ALL
THE WAY OUT HERE FOR DISCUSSION.
HOW VERY DISAPPOINTING.
- Choka: LIGHT THE TORCHES!
- THAT LIGHT.
- I'LL GO INVESTIGATE, SIR.
- THAT'S FIRE. FOR WHAT REASON?
- Keiro: ON MY ORDERS.
- LORD KEIRO!
- NOW THAT I'VE DRAWN
THE SHAWN GHEE LAN WU,
ALKAID IS NO LONGER
OF ANY USE TO ME.
- KEIRO!
- YOU RAT! ONE OF THE FIVE?
- INDEED!
- HEY! YOU KEEP THESE CLOWNS
BUSY WHILE I GO HELP TAITO!
- AYE-AYE!
- ( yelling )
WHAT THE HELL? BARE-HANDED?
- TIME NOW TO DIE, ALKAID.
- I GET IT. YOU CAN'T KILL
UNLESS YOU GET ONE OF YOUR GOONS
TO DO IT FOR YOU.
NICE TRY,
BUT YOU STILL WON'T WIN!
I WON'T DIE!
( guttural groan )
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT THE HELL?
- I'LL BE DAMNED. WELL, NOW,
TAITO, YOU DON'T NEED ME.
BYE.
- RAT! DAMN YOU!
- Ryuko: SO, HE'S LEARNED
TO HARNESS ALKAID'S FURY.
COULD THIS NEWFOUND CONTROL
LEAD TO POWER EQUALING
THAT OF FATHER'S?
- THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME.
THE GRAVE BECKONS.
- ( Shimei chuckles )
OH, HOW THEY FLAIL AND STRUGGLE,
LABORING UNDER THE SELF-CENTERED
DELUSION OF FREE WILL,
FIGHTING AGAINST FATE.
THE LIFE OF MORTALS
IS BRIEF AND BRUTAL.
BUT HOW I RELISH IN THE
SPECTACLE
THEIR EMPTY GESTURES CREATE.
- ( theme song playing )
- Koyo: WILL THE SWORD OF RULE
CLEAVE IN TWO
THE VERY EMPIRE ITSELF?
- THE XIAN EMPIRE IS
BUT MERE PAGEANTRY!
FOUNDED ON LIES
AND ANCHORED IN DECEIT!
- Ryuko: I SPEAK AS ONE
ALLIED TO THE EMPEROR!
KEIRO HAS BEEN DECREED
THIS LAND'S SALVE.
- Taito: IF KEIRO'S TAKEN
THE THRONE ALL OF A SUDDEN,
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO TAIGA?
- Koyo: IF HE GIVES IT UP
WITHOUT A FIGHT, HE MAY LIVE.
- BEHOLD! THE WILL
OF THE HEAVENS!
- Koyo: VIOLENT UPHEAVAL
ROCKS THE EMPIRE TO ITS CORE
IN HERO TALES, CHAPTER 22,
"THE IMPERIAL CAPITAL
IN CONFUSION."
- Keiro:
THE TRUE SWORD BEFORE YOU,
HAS CHOSEN THE TRUE EMPEROR!