- MASTER SOEI! TAITO!
- LIEN?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( grunts )
- WHY ARE YOU JERKS EVEN HERE?
- WHY? WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO COME AND BURN
LIAN TONG TO THE GROUND?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO KILL
INNOCENT PEOPLE TO GET TO ME?
KEIRO!
- ( theme song playing )
- I'LL KILL HIM.
HEY!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- I'M SORRY.
WE FAILED YOU.
XUAN LANG, THEY, THEY ATTACKED
SO QUICKLY, WE...
- DON'T WASTE YOUR
STRENGTH, IT'S OKAY.
- TAITO! LIEN!
- LAILA! YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, ME AND THE
KIDS ARE OKAY.
SO MANY PEOPLE GAVE
UP THEIR LIVES TO SAVE US.
- IT'S HORRIBLE.
- HE'LL PAY FOR THIS.
- BASTARD!
- STOP. TAITO.
YOU NEED TO USE YOUR
ANGER CONSTRUCTIVELY.
LEAVE THE FIGHTING TO THE OTHERS
AND HELP ME AND YOUR SISTER
TEND TO THE WOUNDED.
- BUT, FATHER!
- HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN THE MOTTO
OF THE QING LONG PLATOON?
- WE SWEAR TO WORK FOR PEACE.
TO HELP OTHERS
AND TO LOVE OUR FELLOW MAN.
- THAT'S RIGHT THE DIVINE
WARRIORS CAN HANDLE
THE IMPERIAL TROOPS.
BUT YOU ARE A PART
OF THE QING LONG PLATOON,
FIRST AND FOREMOST.
- YES, SIR.
- WE CAN HELP TOO.
- Taito: STILL FOR WHAT
YOU'VE DONE TO US TODAY.
I WILL SEE TO IT MYSELF
THAT YOU GO DOWN.
- ( indistinct shouting )
- STOP MOVING, DAMN IT!
COME ON, FIGHT ME LIKE A MAN.
I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND WHY
THE HELL YOU CAME HERE.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT BURNS
INSIDE THESE WALLS?
PRICELESS RELICS ARE TURNING
TO ASH AS WE SPEAK.
SO THAT MEANS...
- THEY'VE COME HERE FOR TAITO.
FOR HIS HEAD AT LEAST.
- A DAMN FOOL'S ERRAND.
BUT STILL IT'S QUITE STRANGE.
I MEAN, WHO WOULD THINK
THAT THIS SORRY LOT,
COULD EVEN DREAM
OF TAKING ON ALKAID
AND THREE DIVINE WARRIORS
AND LIVE TO TAKE THE PRIZE?
WELL, THEIR MISTAKE.
- Man: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS
HANDLE THAT ONE OVER THERE.
- I'LL TAKE THIS ONE.
- HOSEI.
- RINMEI.
- WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO
DISPOSE OF QUITE A FEW
OF THE IMPERIAL TROOPS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
THINGS UNDER CONTROL HERE.
- I'M NOT SO SURE HOW
"UNDER CONTROL" IT IS!
I WAS FIGHTING ONE OF
THOSE GIRL NINJAS
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT,
SHE COMPLETELY
DISAPPEARED SOMEWHERE.
- I WONDER.
WAS ALL THIS CARNAGE
JUST TO CREATE
SOME KIND OF DISTRACTION?
BUT FROM WHAT?
- WHERE'S KOYO?
- BEATS ME. I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
- UGH, I TOLD HIM TO COME HERE
TO HELP WITH THE FIRES,
BUT I GUESS HE CHOSE
NOT TO LISTEN TO ME.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW
YOU THAT MEN ARE, HOPELESS!
OH, I MEAN, UH...
( chuckles )
- IF YOUR AIM IS TO KILL
A HELPLESS OLD MAN,
AT LEAST GIVE ME THE
PLEASURE OF A LOOK.
- I KNOW MY TARGET BETTER
THAN YOU THINK.
THE NAME SONNEI OF LIAN
TONG TEMPLE CARRIES WITH IT
QUITE A CACHET
THROUGHOUT THE EMPIRE.
- ( laughs ) MY DEAR,
YOU CERTAINLY DO FLATTER ME.
BUT PUTTING ALL MODESTY ASIDE,
THIS SMALL BAND OF GIRLS IS
NOT ENOUGH TO TAKE ME DOWN.
- ( gasps )
- YOU ARE A LIVELY ONE,
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
- YES, WELL, YOU REALLY
SHOULD'VE SEEN ME
WHEN I WAS STILL IN MY PRIME.
- ( indistinct chattering )
- Boy: HEY,
HE'S GOING TO BE FINE.
- THERE, THAT SHOULD
DO THE TRICK.
- I APPRECIATE ALL YOUR
HELP, YOUNG MASTER.
- ANYBODY ELSE NEED PATCHING
UP AROUND HERE, POP?
- WELL, I THINK WE'RE
GETTING A HANDLE ON IT.
TAITO, I'M EXTREMELY
PROUD OF YOU.
- I'M, UH, JUST DOING
WHAT YOU TOLD ME TO.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
BEFORE, YOU WOULD HAVE
JUST RUN OFF TO FIGHT
WITHOUT LISTENING
TO A WORD I SAID.
YOU'VE REALLY GROWN UP.
- THANK YOU, POP.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE? GET DOWN FROM THERE.
- GRANDPA!
- SONNEI!
- HARK, ALKAID.
IF YOU VALUE THE LIFE
OF THIS DECREPIT WARRIOR,
YOU'LL COME HERE ALONE AT ONCE!
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- SO THAT'S IT. THEY WERE
TRYING TO GET MASTER SONNEI.
THIS WHOLE TIME.
- THAT ISN'T FAIR.
HE'S JUST AN OLD MAN.
THOSE GIRLS SHOULD BE
TAUGHT LESSON IN RESPECT.
- ALL YOU "DIVINE" WARRIORS
NEED TO STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
IF ANY ONE OF YOU
TAKES ONE STEP CLOSER,
THEN THE OLD MAN DIES.
- DAMN YOU, YOU HAG!
OH, YOU'VE ASKED FOR IT NOW.
I CANNOT WAIT TO GET UP
THERE. WELL, POP?
- HIS LIFE IS IN
YOUR HANDS, SON.
- YES, SIR.
- TAITO, PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- HEY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
WELL...
- I'M SCARED, DAD.
- DON'T BE.
HAVE FAITH IN YOUR BROTHER.
- YEAH.
- ( soldiers laughing )
GOOD THINGS DO COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
LOOKS LIKE WE JUST MISSED
RUNNING INTO THAT ALKAID BRAT.
- LEAVE US ALONE.
- KNOCKING OFF THE
HEAD OF QING LONG?
SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD
CAREER MOVE TO ME.
WE COULD BE EATING BREAKFAST
IN THE OFFICERS' TENT TOMORROW.
- ( laughing )
- I ADMIRE YOUR AMBITION,
SON. BUT I'VE GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
BY THEN. YOU'LL BE IN HELL.
- OH, YEAH?
- ( all shouting )
- ( yawns ) IT'S SAD.
YOU HAVE TO STAND HERE
STILL AS STATUES
AT THE TOP OF THIS TOWER,
SWORDS AT THE READY TO SLASH
AN OLD MAN'S WRINKLED THROAT.
MAKES YOU WONDER WHERE THINGS
WENT WRONG, DOES IT NOT?
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH OR I'LL
SHUT IT FOR YOU.
- ( laughing )
- I HAVE TO ADMIT, I'M NOT
AS QUICK TO UNDERSTAND
MY SITUATION THESE DAYS.
BUT SINCE WE FIND
OURSELVES TOGETHER,
MAY I ASK IF YOU TWO ARE
BEING COURTED BACK HOME?
- I TOLD YOU TO SHUT UP!
- DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
- ( laughing )
- YOU'RE JUST DARLING
WHEN YOU'RE ANGRY!
AS HE IS NOW, I HAVE NO
DOUBT TAITO IS CAPABLE
OF CONTROLLING THIS MESS IN
WHICH WE FIND OURSELVES.
IT SEEMS DUBHE HAS UNDER
ESTIMATED HIS ADVERSARY.
TAITO. PLEASE SAVE ME. THESE
GIRLS ARE BORING. POOR DEARS.
- HOLD ON, GRANDPA. I'M COMING.
- ALAS, CHOKA IS AS
MISGUIDED AS EVER.
SO MUCH WORK WITH
SO VERY LITTLE INSIGHT.
SHE DOESN'T SUBSCRIBE
TO THE "KNOW THY ENEMY"
SCHOOL OF THOUGHT.
THIS FOOLISH PLOT TO
HOLD THE OLD MAN
HOSTAGE WILL HAVE NO
LASTING EFFECT WHATSOEVER.
WHAT A SHAME.
IF SHE'D ONLY CHOSEN A
DIFFERENT BARGAINING CHIP
HER TROPHY COULD
HAVE BEEN CLAIMED.
- ALL RIGHT, WHO'S NEXT?
- YOU BASTARD.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE HIS STRENGTH.
I THOUGHT THE QING LONG PLATOON
AVOIDED FIGHTING AT ALL COST.
- ( both screaming )
- LIEN, NO!
- ALL RIGHT, SOEI!
COME AT ME AND I'LL KILL HIM.
- HELP, FATHER!
- ANOTHER HOSTAGE,
YOU IMPERIAL BASTARDS,
CERTAINLY DO LOVE TO PICK ON
THE WEAK, DON'T YOU? PATHETIC.
- I'M NOT FOOLING AROUND.
I'LL CUT THIS LITTLE BRAT'S
THROAT IN A HEARTBEAT!
( screaming )
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU,
YOU'LL BE IN HELL SOON.
- THAT COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN STRONG ENOUGH
TO PUT A CRACK IN
THE SWORD LIKE THIS.
- SO YOU CAME AFTER ALL, ALKAID.
- I CAME ALONE, JUST
LIKE YOU ASKED ME TO.
NOW STAY TRUE TO YOUR WORD
AND LET MASTER SOEI GO.
- I CAN'T SAY I RECALL STRIKING
THAT BARGAIN, BUT I'LL RELEASE
THE OLD MOSSBACK AFTER
WE DISPOSE OF YOU.
- KEEP YOUR HEAD, TAITO.
ANGER AND RASHNESS ARE
THE GATEKEEPERS OF DISASTER.
( gasps ) I SENSE A FOUL
PRESENCE. COULD IT BE HIM?
THE SOWER OF CHAOS, WAN
SHONG SHI MING IS AMONG US?
BUT HOW? NO!
IT CANNOT BE.
- TAITO!
- GRANDPA!
- LEAVE THIS PLACE AT ONCE.
RETURN TO THE OTHERS.
THEY ARE ALL IN GRAVE DANGER.
HURRY, GO BEFORE
IT IS TOO LATE.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE! RUN!
- BUT I CAN'T JUST
LEAVE YOU HERE!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
YOU MUST TURN BACK!
- PLEASE, TAITO. HURRY!
- GRANDPA!
- OLD MAN! WHAT GAME
ARE YOU PLAYING?
- THERE ARE ELEMENTS A FOOT
THAT ARE FAR BEYOND
THE LIMITS OF YOUR CONTROL.
UNTIE ME AND TAKE HEED
TO FLEE AS WELL.
- I WILL NOT FALL
FOR THIS TRICKERY.
YOUR HEAD WILL HAVE TO SUFFICE
FOR KEIRO'S TRIBUTE, KILL HIM!
( gasps )
- HAVE YOU NO MANNERS? THE OLD
MAN MAY BE A DODDERING FOOL,
BUT THAT IS NO EXCUSE FOR
YOUR RUDE BEHAVIOR.
- ( chuckles )
DODDERING FOOL, AM I?
- QUITE SO, IN FACT.
- HOW DARE YOU!
- YOU WON'T STAY PRETTY IF
YOU SCOWL LIKE THAT. CAREFUL.
- MY LADY, SHOULD
WE GIVE CHASE?
- LET'S COUNT OUR
LOSSES AND GO.
BUT MARK MY WORDS, ALKAID
WILL FALL BY MY HAND.
- I NEVER IMAGINED
YOU AS MY SAVIOR.
- THINK OF IT AS TUITION,
FOR MY BRIEF SCHOOLING HERE.
BUT WHY DID YOU
SEND TAITO AWAY?
- THERE'S A FOUL SPIRIT HERE,
WAN XIANG SHI MING.
- DO YOU MEAN, SHIMEI?
- WHAT A FOOL,
I NEVER CONSIDERED HOW
THIS CELESTIAL FRACAS,
WOULD APPEAL TO SUCH
A LOVER OF DESTRUCTION.
- DAD. LAILA!
- WELL, THAT CERTAINLY
WAS QUICK, TAITO!
- I GUESS GRANDPA'S OKAY?
- HE SAID THAT I SHOULD
COME BACK HERE.
THAT YOU WERE IN TROUBLE.
- WAN XIANG SHI MING
TAKES HUMAN FORM
AND WALKS AMONG US,
BUT HE IS NOT ONE OF US.
HE IS A DEMON. A VILE AND
LOATHSOME CREATURE WHO
THRIVES ON THE SUFFERING
AND SORROW OF MANKIND.
- AND NOW,
HE'S IN LEAGUE WITH KEIRO?
- YES. HE HAS EXISTED
FOR COUNTLESS GENERATIONS
ONLY TO CAUSE TURMOIL
IN THIS WORLD.
TURMOIL WHICH A MAN LIKE KEIRO,
IS ALL TOO EAGER TO SEIZE.
I SUSPECT HE IS NOT SERVING
KEIRO, BUT IS USING
THE MAN'S PROPENSITY
FOR BLOODSHED,
AS A SOURCE OF
GHOULISH AMUSEMENT.
- HE THRIVES ON PEOPLE'S
MISERY, THEIR SORROW.
- NOW, NOW, ALKAID.
MY APPETITE HAS
MERELY BEEN WHETTED.
IT'S HIGH TIME WE GOT
ON TO THE REAL SHOW.
- I TOOK CARE OF ALL
THE "TROUBLE".
NOW WHY HAVEN'T YOU
RETURNED WITH MASTER SONNEI?
- WELL BECAUSE HE SAID...
- BUT HOW? I THOUGHT I'D
ALREADY KILLED THEM.
- I'M SURE YOU DID. BUT THESE
GUYS, THEY DON'T STAY DEAD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU WANT THEM DEAD?
YOU GOTTA HIT THEM HERE.
- RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
- ( growling )
- ( gasps )
- ( gasping )
- ( screaming ) NO!
- DAD, COME ON, PLEASE,
DAD! TALK TO ME!
- FATHER, PLEASE!
- TAITO, MY DEAR SON.
- STAY WITH US.
- DON'T CRY, SON.
LISTEN TO ME ALL MEN MUST DIE.
IT IS AN UNENDING CYCLE.
IT IS OUR FATE.
- BUT WHY? BUT WHY NOW?
- OH, NO!
- MASTER SOEI
- MASTER.
- SONNEI. IS HE, HE'S SAFE?
- I MYSELF RETURNED MASTER
SONNEI HOME SAFELY.
CHOKA AND HER MINIONS
HAVE RETREATED AS WELL.
- THANK YOU,
I'M RELIEVED.
I CAN LEAVE THIS WORLD KNOWING
MY LOVED ONES ARE SAFE.
AND YOU STAYED TRUE TO OUR
CODE. TO FIGHT FOR PEACE,
TO HELP OTHERS,
AND TO LOVE YOUR FELLOW MAN.
NEVER FORGET THAT, NEVER!
- ( both gasping )
- IT'S YOUR FAULT. YOU LET
THIS HAPPEN. YOU WERE THERE.
YOU WERE RIGHT BY HIS
SIDE THE ENTIRE TIME AND
YOU STILL COULDN'T PROTECT
HIM FROM THOSE MONSTERS.
YOU LET HIM DIE.
HOW COULD YOU BE SO USELESS?
- ( laughing )
- YOU'RE DEAD!
- HE THRIVES ON PEOPLE'S SORROW.
- WHAT THE EXPERIENCE, EH?
HAVING YOUR OWN FATHER DYING
IN YOUR HELPLESS ARMS.
OH, THAT IS QUITE THE LOOK.
THE FRUIT OF MY LABORS.
I'VE WORKED VERY HARD TO
CULTIVATE THAT EXPRESSION.
SEEMS KILLING DADDY
FINALLY DID THE TRICK.
( laughing )
- Taito: I'LL KILL YOU FOR THIS!
( grunting )
- THE ALKAID SIGIL IS GLOWING!
-COME ON, "SON." NOW GET ANGRY.
LET YOUR HATRED BURN,
DESTROY EVERYTHING IN SIGHT
AND UNLEASH ALKAID'S
CLEANSING HOLOCAUST!
- ( grunting )
( screaming )
( panting )
- ALKAID'S, CALMED.
- I ALMOST CAN'T BELIEVE IT,
HE WAS ABLE TO KEEP
IT UNDER CONTROL.
EVEN AFTER WHAT JUST HAPPENED,
HE SOME HOW DIDN'T
GO TOTALLY NUTS.
- DAMN THAT BRAT.
HAS HE ACTUALLY FIGURED
OUT HOW TO KEEP
THE REIGNS ON ALKAID'S FURY?
NO FUN, NO FUN AT ALL.
( gasping )
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
ALKAID.
- YOU'RE GOING BACK THEN?
- I AM.
- THE STARS THEMSELVES FORETOLD
OF YOUR DEPARTURE.
THEY ARE ONCE AGAIN TO
CONVERGE UPON THE CAPITAL.
YOU NEEDN'T WORRY ABOUT
SOEI AND THE REST
OF OUR FALLEN BROTHERS.
I'VE TAKEN STEPS TO PROTECT
THEM FROM THAT DEMON'S,
SINISTER MACHINATIONS.
- I APPRECIATE IT, GRANDPA.
BUT THERE ARE STILL
JUST SO MANY THINGS
THAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHO IS SHIMEI? WHY DID KEIRO
BURN DOWN LIAN TONG?
ALL OF THIS
KARMA OF THE STARS STUFF.
IT STILL DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE TO ME YET.
- SINCE MY BROTHER'S STILL GOT
A LOT TO LEARN ABOUT THE WORLD,
I'LL BE GOING WITH HIM.
HONESTLY, I'M PRETTY SURE
FATHER WOULD HAVE
INSISTED ON IT ANYWAY.
- BUT DON'T WORRY,
I'LL KEEP AN EYE ON HER.
- WITH THE RESCUE AND ALL
THAT, THEY HAVE ACCRUED
QUITE A DEBT FOR MY SERVICES.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE THEY
DON'T SKIP ON THE TAB.
- WHILE WE'RE IN THE
CAPITAL WE CAN LOCATE
RYUKO AND THE REMAINING WARRIOR.
I AM CERTAIN WE WILL RETURN TO
LIAN TONG BEARING GOOD NEWS.
- HMM.
- WELL, GUYS, I GUESS WE
SHOULD BE HITTING THE ROAD.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
GRANDPA, OKAY?
- I WILL. AND YOU AS WELL.
IF FATE HAS ORDAINED THAT
TAITO LEAVE HOME YET AGAIN
THEN SO ORDAINED WAS
SOEI'S PASSING.
AS WAS THE SURVIVAL OF
THIS OLD FOOL,
TO BEAR WITNESS TO IT ALL.
I STILL HAVE TO WONDER. WHERE
DOES THE WILL OF THE STARS END,
AND OUR OWN BEGIN?
- ( Japanese song playing )
- Koyo: HOPES FOR A TENDER
REUNION ARE DASHED
BY A HEART HARDENED BY DESPAIR.
- Taito: WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU PLAYING AT HERE?
THIS JUST DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
- Ryuko: GOOD, GENUINE GOOD,
IS A FUNCTION OF POWER.
- SO I TAKE IT
YOU'RE ESSENTIALLY
KEIRO'S GOODWILL AMBASSADOR.
- IF YOU COULD HEAR THE
WORDS YOU'RE SAYING
AS CLEARLY AS WE DO,
YOU'D BE ASHAMED!
- WHY MUST YOU ALWAYS DEAL
ONLY IN BARREN EXTREMES?
- LORD KEIRO IS VITAL
TO THE EMPIRE.
- CONFLICTING ALLIANCES
THREATEN TO THROW
THE CELESTIAL ORDER
INTO DISARRAY.
IN HERO TALES, CHAPTER
NINETEEN, "STARS DIVIDED."
- IF WE DESIRE LASTING PEACE,
WE MUST BE WILLING
TO PAY THE PRICE!