- Shimei: XIAN JIA LAN WU,
ALPHA AND OMEGA
OF MANY A DYNASTY.
KNOWN MORE COMMONLY AS
THE SWORD OF RULE,
FOR ONLY AN EMPEROR'S
HAND MAY DRAW IT.
SOMETHING TELLS ME YOU'RE
THE KIND OF BLEEDING HEART
WHO'D SET THE WORLD TO RIGHTS
GIVEN HALF A CHANCE.
DO I ASSUME CORRECTLY?
- IF SO, THEN WHAT BETTER MEANS
TO ACCOMPLISH IT THAN A THRONE?
- WHAT?
- YOU AND YOU ALONE
DREW THE SWORD OF RULE.
FATE HAS MADE ITS CHOICE.
THE HELM OF THIS
BROKEN LAND IS YOURS.
RISE TO THE OCCASION, BOY.
TAKE THE SWORD.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( metal gonging )
- AS EMPEROR, I ORDER
THE UPRISING IN QIAO YAO
TO BE CRUSHED AT ONCE.
THIS MATTER IS OF
VITAL IMPORTANCE
TO THE PEACE OF THE EMPIRE.
WE CAN BROOK
ABSOLUTELY NO DISSENT.
SHOW THE RABBLE THE MEANING
OF UNITY IN YOUR CONCERTED
EFFORTS TO ROUTE THEM.
- YES, MY LIEGE.
- MAY FORTUNE SMILE UPON
YOUR CAMPAIGN, LORD KEIRO.
- I WAIT NOT ON
FORTUNE'S CAPRICE.
- FORWARD, MARCH!
- ( all yelling )
- FORTUNE, WHAT IS MY STAR?
- WOW! LOOK AT HOW
MANY OF 'EM THERE ARE.
- THERE'S MOUSTACHE!
- CALM YOURSELF, TAITO.
YOU PROMISED ONLY
TO WATCH, REMEMBER?
- YEAH, I KNOW!
- THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
SITTING BACK WHILE YOUR
MORTAL ENEMY PARADES BY.
OF COURSE THE
WALL OF SOLDIERS
IS A PRETTY MAJOR
DETERRENT RIGHT NOW.
- Man: I DON'T ENVY THE MAN.
YOU'D THINK SOMEONE OF
HIS RANK WOULDN'T NEED
TO THROW HIMSELF
INTO THE FRAY.
- HE HARDLY HAS A CHOICE.
WHATEVER THEIR STATUS,
ONE DOESN'T REFUSE
AN ORDER FROM THE EMPEROR.
- OH, I THINK IT'S
MORE THAN THAT.
HIS MAJESTY MUST HAVE
THE BEARING OF A TIGER
TO BRING A WARRIOR LIKE
HIS LORDSHIP KEIRO TO HEEL.
- MOUSTACHE LETS HIMSELF BE
PUSHED AROUND BY THE EMPEROR?
- THAT'S BIZARRE.
I CAN'T ASCERTAIN OUR LITTLE
FRIEND'S WHEREABOUTS.
WHAT KIND OF BASE
TRICKERY IS CONCEALING HIM?
- WOW. THIS CHARM YOU DREW FOR
ALL OF US CERTAINLY IS STRIKING,
MASTER RYUSHO.
YOU SAID JUST CARRYING IT
ON OUR PERSON
IS ENOUGH TO KEEP PEOPLE
FROM DETECTING US, RIGHT?
- PRETTY HANDY WAY OF TOURING
ALL THE HOT SPOTS, I'LL BET.
- AND ITS EFFECTIVENESS
IS BEYOND DISPUTE.
I USED THESE MANY A TIME
TO GET OUT OF TRAINING
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG MAN.
- FATHER.
- ( all laughing )
- OH, LIGHTEN UP, MY BOY!
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
YOU HAVE THE LOOK OF
SOMEONE WHO'S PREOCCUPIED.
- I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU,
ABOUT THE EMPEROR.
IS HE SOME KIND OF BIG
MONSTER OR SOMETHING?
- WHAT ON EARTH GOES ON
IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS?
- YOU CAN'T JUST BLURT OUT THE
LAST THING IN A LONG CHAIN
OF THOUGHT, GENIUS.
SPELL IT OUT FOR US.
- FINE THEN.
EVERYBODY'S BEEN GOING ON
AND ON ABOUT HOW USELESS
THE EMPEROR'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
BUT A BIG BAD GENERAL'S
TAKING ORDERS FROM HIM.
SO, HE CAN'T BE A WEAKLING.
- TAITO.
- I'M BEING SERIOUS!
WHAT KIND OF PERSON WOULD
MOUSTACHE LET HIMSELF
BE BOSSED AROUND BY?
EXPLAIN IT TO ME!
- AS FAR AS I CAN TELL
ABOUT HIM WITHOUT BENEFIT
OF PERSONAL INTERACTION,
HIS MAJESTY'S HEART IS
IN THE RIGHT PLACE AND PERHAPS
COULD MAKE AN EXEMPLARY RULER.
THE ONLY THING HOLDING HIM
BACK IS A BRITTLE CONSTITUTION.
- SO HIS HEART'S IN
THE MIDDLE OF HIS CHEST,
AND HE'S ONLY HELD BACK
BY SOME KINDA BRITTLE BARRIER?
( screams )
WE CAN'T LET THAT
MONSTER BREAK FREE!
- WHAT'D I JUST TELL YOU
ABOUT THINKING OUT LOUD?
- ( laughs ) I'M AFRAID
THAT WORDS CAN'T REALLY DO
JUSTICE TO THE MAN HIMSELF.
AS WITH ANYBODY, I GUESS YOU'D
HAVE TO MEET HIM IN PERSON.
- OF COURSE! I SHOULD JUST
GO MEET THE GUY FACE-TO-FACE.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
- HA, COMMONERS LIKE OURSELVES
ARE LUCKY TO CATCH A FLEETING
GLIMPSE OF HIS MAJESTY.
AND EVEN THAT PERHAPS
ONCE IN A LIFETIME.
- YOU WOULD STAND A BETTER
CHANCE OF SEEING
YOUR OWN ARSEHOLE
ON A MOONLESS NIGHT.
- MASTER. THAT'S DISGUSTING.
- ( all laughing )
- THE IDIOT'S ACTUALLY
GONNA DO IT.
- WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THOSE THE LAST OF THE GOODS
YOU INTEND TO BRING IN TODAY?
- YEAH. THIS IS IT.
-RIGHT. THAT'S ALL.
RAISE 'ER UP.
- ( chuckling )
TAITO, YOU'RE A GENIUS.
MASTER RYUSHO'S CHARM
WILL KEEP ME INVISIBLE.
AND WITH MOUSTACHE OFF PLAYING
WAR HERO, NOTHING CAN STOP ME
FROM SEEING HIS HIGHNESS.
UP WE GO.
NOW, IF I WERE A LOUSY
GOOD FOR NOTHING EMPEROR,
WHERE WOULD I BE?
WHAT THE...
HOW THE HELL DOES ALL THIS
BELONG TO JUST ONE GUY?
I CANNOT WAIT TO GET MY
HANDS ON THIS GREEDY BASTARD.
I AM GONNA TEACH
HIM A LESSON ABOUT
WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE A REAL MAN.
I JUST HOPE FOR HIS SAKE
HE'S A REAL GOOD LISTENER.
OKAY, OKAY, REMEMBER,
THIS THING DOESN'T TURN YOU
LITERALLY INVISIBLE,
IT JUST KINDA HELPS YOU BLEND
IN TO YOUR SURROUNDINGS.
- FAREWELL, LADY TAKI.
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER MIDDAY MEAL.
- INDEED. ENJOY IT,
YOUR MAJESTY.
- ( stomach growling )
- UGH, I'M STARVING.
SO MUCH FOR BEING DONE
WITH ALL THIS CRAP AND BACK
AT THE TEMPLE BY LUNCHTIME.
- KARO'S WARMONGERING WILL RAIN
HAVOC DOWN UPON US BEFORE LONG.
EACH BLOOD BESOT VICTORY
ONLY INCREASES HIS APPETITE
FOR THE BATTLEFIELD.
- WHOA, HE SOUNDS
LIKE AN EMPEROR.
- THERE ARE THOSE WHO
WOULD ARGUE HIS READINESS
TO SACRIFICE LIFE AND LIMB
FOR THE EMPIRE'S SAKE PAINTS
THE MAN IN FAVORABLE HUES.
- A PLOY TO CURRY
THE PUBLIC'S FAVOR!
- INDULGE US.
WHO EXACTLY MAKES
SUCH AN ARGUMENT?
- COME. LADY CHOKA,
NATURALLY. WHO ELSE?
- NATURALLY, INDEED.
BOTH SHE AND KARO HAIL
FROM PLEBIAN STOCK.
WHY HIS MAJESTY
SURROUNDS HIMSELF
WITH LOW BORN UPSTARTS
I'LL NEVER KNOW.
- JUST WHERE IS HIS MAJESTY?
- HE'S IN RESIDENCE AT DAMING
PALACE THIS AFTERNOON, SIR.
- HM, OF COURSE.
DEEPENING HIS NAIVE AFFECTIONS
FOR THE VAPID LITTLE
ORCHID TENDER, NO DOUBT.
THAT IS THE CASE
IS IT NOT, SHOKAKU?
- WELL, WITH ALL
DUE RESPECT, SIR,
BEING A DOCTOR,
MY POLITICS ARE WANTING.
- THAT IS ALL, GENTLEMEN!
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- OKAY, SO THAT WASN'T HIM.
WHERE IS HE, THEN?
I'M STARTING TO WONDER IF
HE'S EVEN REAL AT THIS POINT.
( yells )
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE!
I HAVEN'T EATEN IN HOURS!
OH, MAN! I CAN SMELL LIKE A
THOUSAND KITCHENS MAKING LUNCH
FOR ALL THESE RICH BASTARDS.
( sniffing )
NOW THAT'S THE KIND OF
DELICIOUS SCENT YOU CAN
ONLY CATCH A WHIFF OF
ONCE OR TWICE IN YOUR
ENTIRE LIFE, IF YOU'RE LUCKY.
TOP GRADE MEAT.
ONLY THE EMPEROR WOULD CHOW DOWN
ON FOOD THAT HIGH CLASS
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE AFTERNOON.
OF COURSE.
THIS WORKS OUT GREAT, I'LL DROP
IN ON OLD HIGH N' MIGHTY
AND CATCH A BITE
TO EAT. OH, YEAH.
- IS SOMETHING THE
MATTER, MY LADY?
- IT'S CLOSE!
NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
THE NOSE OF A WARRIOR
WHO HASN'T EATEN
SINCE BREAKFAST.
( exclaims in pain )
( yelling )
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT!
( exclaiming )
- IMPOSSIBLE.
ALKAID IS IN CAI FEI PALACE?
- WHEW. THERE WE GO.
MAN, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- WHO GOES THERE?
- ( gasps )
- WHO'S THERE?
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT'S MY
BURDEN TO ANSWER THAT QUERY.
NOW, WHO ARE YOU AND
HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE?
THIS IS...
WHAT?
YOUR FACE, IT...
- ( knocking on door )
- Woman: ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
MY LIEGE, ARE YOU IN NEED OF US?
- IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S
GOOD FOR YA,
YOU'LL GET WHOEVER
THAT IS OUTTA HERE.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME GET
CAUGHT, I'M BEGGING YOU!
- MAY WE COME IN?
- YES, ENTER.
- ( door opens )
- WERE YOU NOT JUST
SPEAKING TO SOMEONE?
- NO NEED FOR ALARM.
IT SEEMS I MERELY GREW
A BIT TOO ENRAPTURED
BY THE POEM I WAS RECITING.
YOU MAY GO NOW.
- YES.
- ( door closes )
- IS THAT WHAT YOU HAD IN MIND?
- ( growls )
- ( chuckles )
- ( sighs )
THANKS FOR PLAYING ALONG.
SORRY IF I SOUNDED KINDA UGLY
THERE AT THE START.
IT WASN'T ANYTHING PERSONAL.
I SHALL TAKE MIDDAY MEAL
IN THE ARBOR TODAY.
PLEASE SEE THE TABLE
IS SET FOR TWO.
- YES, OF COURSE, YOUR GRACE.
MY PLEASURE.
- AH, WILL LADY TAKI BE
JOINING YOU, YOUR HIGHNESS?
- WHETHER SHE IS OR SHE IS NOT,
WE VALUE OUR PRIVACY.
- ABSOLUTELY, YOUR MAJESTY.
- Laila: HUH?
- Ryuko: HE WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN TAI'S
GONE TO SEE THE EMPEROR?
- WHY ARE YOU MAD?
HOW IS THIS EVEN A
SURPRISE TO YOU?
WE ALL HEARD HIM EARLIER.
HE WAS RARING TO GO.
- AND YOU JUST LET THE BIG DOLT
WALK RIGHT OUT OF HERE
LIKE HE WAS
GOING TO MARKET?
- BUT WHY ARE YOU
BLAMING ME FOR THAT?
- BECAUSE YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT HE'S AN IDIOT, THAT'S WHY!
- UM, RYUKO.
SHOULD WE HAVE EXPECTED THIS
KIND OF BEHAVIOR FROM HIM?
- YES, WE SHOULD HAVE.
WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
WARY AT LUNCH,
WHEN HE DIDN'T BURST IN AT THE
FIRST SCENT OF YOUR COOKING.
HE'S JUST SO IMPULSIVE.
- UGH! I SWEAR MEN ARE
ABSOLUTELY HOPELESS!
- ( chewing noisily )
THIS IS THE BEST
GRUB I'VE EVER HAD!
YOU EAT THIS STUFF EVERY DAY?
YOU MUST BE NEXT IN LINE FOR
THE THRONE OR SOMETHING.
- YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO THESE IF YOU LIKE.
- WOW, DO YOU REALLY MEAN THAT?
YOU'RE THE NICEST GUY I KNOW!
- WELL, YOU SEEM LIKE QUITE
THE AMIABLE FELLOW YOURSELF.
- IF THAT BIG WORD THERE
TOWARD THE END MEANS
"FIERCE DEFENDER OF
THE BROKEN AND DEPRESSED"
THEN YOU HAVE SUMMED
UP TAITO PRETTY WELL.
- SO YOUR NAME IS TAITO, THEN.
WELL, ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MY...
- NOT SO FAST, FANCY DRESS.
JUDGING BY THIS
SET UP YOU GOT HERE,
THE CHANCES OF US SEEING EACH
OTHER AGAIN ARE PRETTY SLIM.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN KNOWING YOUR NAME.
NOT TO BE A JERK, BUT PEOPLE
THAT BATHE BEFORE LUNCH
USUALLY DON'T MIX
WITH PEOPLE LIKE ME.
- ACTUALLY, AS IT SO HAPPENS,
I BATHE A TOTAL OF
THREE TIMES A DAY.
- THREE TIMES A DAY? WHAT,
DO YOU GOT A PERSONAL VERANDA
AGAINST DIRT OR SOMETHING?
- I DON'T BELIEVE THAT'S WHAT
THE WORD HAS COME TO MEAN.
- YOU SOUND LIKE A CROSS
'TWEEN MY FRIEND AND MY SISTER.
- TAITO, EARLIER YOU SAID
YOU SNUCK INTO THE PALACE
ON THE REMOTE CHANCE OF
LAYING EYES ON THE EMPEROR.
- THAT WAS THE PLAN.
- WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
- TO SIZE HIM UP. IF I CAN TELL
BY LOOKING HE'S HALF THE JERK
HE'D HAVE TO BE, WELL THEN,
I'M GONNA BEAT HIM
TO A BLOODY PULP
AND TAKE THE
THRONE FOR MYSELF.
- NOW WHAT ON EARTH DO YOU MEAN
BY "THE JERK HE'D HAVE TO BE?"
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THE COUNTRY'S FALLING
APART BECAUSE OF HIM.
THE ONLY FOLKS WHO GET TO
EAT LIKE I JUST DID ARE EITHER
TOTAL BASTARDS OR
JUST PLAIN LUCKY.
MOST PEOPLE HAVE TO
GET BY WITH JUST SCRAPS,
WHILE BANDITS AND CROOKED
MAGISTRATES EAT LIKE,
WELL, EMPERORS.
AND ALL THE FIGHTING.
IF HIS ROYAL HIGHNESS
GAVE A DAMN,
THINGS WOULD'VE
NEVER HAVE GOTTEN THIS BAD.
BUT, TO BE FAIR, I DON'T
HAVE THE FIRST CLUE
WHAT THE EMPEROR
ACTUALLY DOES,
SO IT'S ANYBODY'S GUESS IF I'D
BE BETTER AT IT THAN HE IS.
HEY, YOU GREW UP HERE.
YOU KNOW HIM, RIGHT?
- I SUPPOSE THAT'S ONE
WAY OF PUTTING IT, YES.
SO THEN, WHAT'S
MR. HIGH N' MIGHTY REALLY LIKE?
- HE WHAT?
HOW COULD ALKAID HAVE
SIMPLY CREPT INTO OUR MIDST?
- HOW ISN'T THE ISSUE.
THAT HE'S OUT OF MY SIGHT
AGAIN IS WHAT GIVES ME PAUSE.
SURELY A ROUTINE SEARCH OF THE
PALACE GROUNDS WOULD UNVEIL HIM.
- THE IMPERIAL GUARDS
ARE TO KILL HIM ON SIGHT.
- YES.
- DAMN YOU, ALKAID.
TO WHAT CONCEIVABLE
PURPOSE HAVE YOU COME?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'VE NOT YET HAD THE
PLEASURE OF MAKING HIS
ESTEEMED ACQUAINTANCE,
HAVE YOU MY LADY?
- AND WHAT IS THAT TO YOU?
- NOTHING. IT'S JUST THAT HIS
VISAGE MAY WELL SURPRISE YOU.
( chuckles )
- ( birds chirping )
- REALLY? THAT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
I DON'T THINK BEING EMPEROR
IS SOMETHING I'M REALLY
TOO KEEN ON AFTER ALL.
ALL THE FORMALITIES AND CRAP,
NOT HAVING ANY SAY SO
IN HIS OWN LIFE.
OR EVEN WHAT GOES ON
IN THE COUNTRY
HE'S SUPPOSED TO
BE RULING OVER.
- IT'S TRUE.
HE'S A FIGUREHEAD, NOTHING MORE.
- SCREW THE THRONE!
IT REALLY SUCKS!
- YOU UNDERSTAND THOUGH, YES?
THE EMPEROR IS ESSENTIALLY
POWERLESS TO CHANGE ANYTHING.
MUCH THOUGH HE MAY DESIRE TO.
- SO WHAT'S ALL THIS FOR, THEN?
WHAT'S THE EMPEROR ACTUALLY DO?
- HE PRAYS.
FOR CONTINUED PEACE AND
THE PROSPERITY OF HIS SUBJECTS.
THAT IS THE SACRED DUTY
ENTRUSTED TO HIM
BY THE STARS ABOVE.
- BUT, CAN'T ANYBODY PRAY?
- TELL ME, IN YOUR
WILDEST DREAMS,
WHAT SETS AN IDEAL COUNTRY APART
FROM THE ONE IN WHICH WE LIVE?
- HMM.
I'M NOT SURE.
BUT IN MY COUNTRY,
EVERYBODY WOULD BE SMILING.
- THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A LOVELY PLACE.
- THE WAY I SEE IT, UNLESS THE
POOREST PERSON CAN SMILE
JUST AS OFTEN AS THE RICHEST,
THE COUNTRY'S JUST NO GOOD.
WAIT.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE EMPEROR REALLY IS TO
BLAME FOR THIS WHOLE MESS.
IF HE CAN'T FIND A WAY TO CLAW
HIMSELF OUT OF THE MURK,
HOW ARE HIS SUBJECTS
SUPPOSED TO HAVE A SHOT?
WHAT THIS COUNTRY
NEEDS IS AN EXAMPLE.
SEEMS TO ME HE'S GOTTEN
COMFORTABLE SULKING
UNDER THE WEIGHT
OF HIS SACRED DUTY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL BET THE REASON
HE'S SO POWERLESS IS BECAUSE
HE LETS HIMSELF BE.
WHAT HE NEEDS IS TO TASTE
A LITTLE BLOOD IN HIS MOUTH,
SO HE KNOWS WHAT
FIGHTING REALLY FEELS LIKE.
- PERHAPS YOU'RE RIGHT.
INEFFECTUAL THOUGH I MAY BE,
THE PEOPLE OF THIS LAND DESERVE
MORE OF ME THAN SELF PITY.
WHAT THEY DESERVE IS
ONE WHO CAN LEAD THEM.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, FANCY DRESS?
IT'S THE EMPEROR'S PROBLEM
TO GET HIS HEAD AROUND,
NOT SOME PAMPERED LITTLE
"I TAKE THREE BATHS A DAY"
RICH KID LIKE YOU!
- ( glass shattering )
- MY EYES DECEIVE ME.
CAN... CAN THERE REALLY BE TWO?
TWO EMPERORS?
- IT'S OKAY, DON'T WORRY.
I KNOW I LOOK SUSPICIOUS,
BUT I'M SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
SEE, I'M ACTUALLY AN OLD PAL
OF THE EMPEROR, SO UH...
( gasps )
THE EMPEROR?
- ( chuckles )
- YEAH. WE DO LOOK KINDA
ALIKE IN A WAY, I GUESS.
- I DON'T SEE HOW THE FACT
COULD HAVE ESCAPED YOU BEFORE.
- WELL, I'M REALLY NOT ALL THAT
FAMILIAR WITH MY OWN FACE.
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF LOOKING
GLASSES WHERE I COME FROM.
- I SEE.
- HMM.
- I NEVER WOULD HAVE
GUESSED YOU WERE YOU.
HOW LONG WERE YOU GONNA LET ME
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF MYSELF
BEFORE YOU TOLD ME?
- WELL I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO
BEAT ME TO A BLOODY PULP.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- HA.
YOU WERE NICE ENOUGH TO HIDE ME
AND FEED ME AN AWESOME LUNCH.
SO FOR TODAY AT LEAST
I GUESS YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
- THANK YOU.
- I UNDERSTAND THE EMPEROR
HAS MORE THAN
HIS FAIR
SHARE OF PROBLEMS.
BUT DON'T THINK I'M GONNA LET
YOUR LITTLE PITY PARTY
GO ON FOREVER, MY FRIEND.
- MY SOLEMN VOW TO YOU, TAITO,
IS THAT I WILL TRY
TO LEAD THIS COUNTRY
AS A GOOD EMPEROR
SHOULD, JUSTLY.
- YOU WORK ON MAKING STUFF
BETTER FROM THE INSIDE.
AND I'LL DO WHATEVER
I CAN ON THE OUTSIDE.
YEAH, AND THANKS AGAIN
FOR THE FOOD, BUDDY.
- AND OFF HE GOES.
WHAT AN ASTONISHING DAY.
- I WONDER WHAT'S
TAKING HIM SO LONG.
- ( yelling )
( grunting )
- AVERT YOUR THOUGHTS FROM THE
RESEMBLANCE HE BEARS
TO HIS MAJESTY AND
RUN HIM THROUGH.
- ( grunting )
- SO THIS IS THE ENEMY.
SHIMEI SPOKE THE TRUTH.
THEY ARE THE VERY IMAGE
OF ONE ANOTHER.
CAN THIS LIKENESS
BE MERE COINCIDENCE?
- DAMN IT, GET OFF MY BACK!
FOR THE RECORD, I HAD NO BEEF
WITH ANY OF YOU FELLAS.
BUT YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE.
( yelling )
- WHAT?
- HE'S RUNNING AWAY!
- GET HIM!
- ( groaning )
WHO IN THE HELL ARE YOU?
- LOOK, BEHIND YOU.
THERE'S YOUR OUT.
- HMM, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR
GAME IS, PAL, BUT I OWE YOU ONE.
- Guard: CONFOUND IT,
HE CAN'T HAVE GOTTEN FAR.
FIND THE VERMIN! FIND HIM.
- IT PROFITS US NOTHING TO LET
ALKAID BE DONE IN SO SOON.
- DAMN THAT BOY!
- PLEASE, TAITO.
- THANK YOU, FRIEND.
- SO THAT WAS THE EMPEROR.
BEST OF LUCK TO HIM.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: A CELESTIAL RETINUE
COMPOSED OF SEVEN
BRILLIANT STARS.
- Taito: BUT THEY'RE THE BEST
FRIENDS A GUY LIKE ME
COULD EVER ASK FOR.
- Hosei: TOGETHER WE CAN TAKE
CARE OF OLD FURRY LIP
WITH NO PROBLEM!
- Ryuko: THE PURPOSE OF
THE DIVINE WARRIORS
IS TO MAINTAIN PEACE AND
ORDER IN THE XIAN EMPIRE.
IT IS OUR DESTINY,
OUR SACRED MANDATE.
WE CANNOT FAIL.
- Taito: WHY WAS I CHOSEN
TO BE ALKAID. WHY ME?
- Keiro: I DO NOT WISH TO
BE DISAPPOINTED, ALKAID.
- Ryuko: NEXT, ON HERO TALES,
AS ABOVE, SO BELOW,
IN CHAPTER ELEVEN,
"THE TALE OF THE BIG DIPPER."
BUT CAN I POSSIBLY
CONVINCE TAITO
THAT HE GIVE UP HIS
QUEST TO DESTROY KEIRO?