- ( thunder rumbles )
- WOW! LOOK UP
INTO THE SKY, MASTER.
- THE HOUR HAS COME.
ONE SMELLS IT IN THE AIR.
DUBHE AND ALKAID WILL CLASH.
- WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO TAI?
- ( theme song playing )
- SO, UH, NOW WHAT?
- HA! SURPASSED, MY FOOT!
WHEN THE HELL WERE YOU
EVER PART OF HUMANITY?
- A TRIFLING STEP ON THE
ROAD TO MY DESTINY.
- ENOUGH OF THIS CRAP! WHEN YOU
LOSE COUNT OF ALL THE CORPSES
YOU'VE HAD TO WALK OVER ON THAT
ROAD, I DON'T CALL IT DESTINY!
I CALL IT THE COWARD'S WAY OUT!
- Laila and Hosei together:
TAITO!
- ( laughing )
- EXCELLENT! THE BODY OF
A GOD SUITS ME WELL.
YOU GRAZE ME LIKE
AN AUTUMN BREEZE,
THOUGH THAT IS, PERHAPS,
AN INSULT TO THE SEASON.
- STOP RUNNING YOUR MOUTH!
YOU DIRTY SON OF A...
HE'S NOT JUST SPOUTING OFF.
HE REALLY IS DIFFERENT.
- CAN YOU STILL NOT PERCEIVE?
YOU AND I NOW OCCUPY TWO VASTLY
DISTINCT LEVELS OF EXISTENCE.
- HE'S TRADED LIFE
FOR SHEER POWER.
- Shimei: AN ASTUTE
OBSERVATION, YOUNG LADY.
- YOU COWARD! COME OUT!
- Shimei: BUT I PRACTICALLY
DANCE AT THE CROOK
OF YOUR SHOULDER.
- ( he laughs )
GHASTLY, ISN'T IT?
PERHAPS TO SAY THAT I DANCE
AT THE CROOK OF YOUR SHOULDER
WAS A WEE BIT MISLEADING.
ONE'S METAPHORS PLAY SOMEWHAT
LOOSE IN THE PRESENCE OF A GOD.
PARTICULARLY GIVEN THE
UNMITIGATED ATROCITY
OF THIS SPECIMEN.
HORROR FEASTS UPON HORROR,
YOU SEE. SOMETIMES LITERALLY.
NOW ALKAID, BEHOLD THE GOD
THAT CONSUMED EVEN ME.
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU
LEAVING HERE ALIVE!
- ( he laughs )
- SO KEIRO'S CONSUMED HIM?
- HE'S INHUMAN!
- THE LANDSCAPE OF
NIGHTMARE MADE FLESH,
THE HARBINGER OF YOUR
DEMISE REALIZED.
OH, MY BOY.
THE FUN WE'LL HAVE.
- ( thunder rumbles )
- DAMN IT! IS THERE NOTHING
WE CAN DO FOR THEM
IN THEIR HOUR OF NEED?
FOR HEAVENS' SAKE, MY
BROTHER'S IN THE THICK OF IT!
- CALM YOURSELF, YOUR MAJESTY.
YOUR ROLE IN THIS WILL BE AS
EMPEROR ONCE THE WAY IS CLEARED.
- ALAS! ONLY TAITO POSSESSES
THE STRENGTH TO PRY
KEIRO'S HOLD FROM THIS LAND.
- ( he grunts )
- TAITO! TAITO!
- DAMN IT, NO!
- YOU'RE A DISGRACE
TO THE INFIRM.
TO THINK YOU BEAR THE MARK
OF A WARRIOR GOD.
YOU WHO WHIMPERS
LIKE A BABE.
IT SEEMS EVEN THE WRETCHED CAN
STIR A TITAN FROM HIS SLUMBER.
YOUR FATE WAS BUT TO STOKE
THE FIRES OF MY WRATH.
GIVE IT LIFE. HAD YOU NEVER
RISEN TO CHALLENGE ME,
I MIGHT'VE REMAINED AS I WAS.
- Hosei: TAITO!
- Laila: TAITO! NO!
- ( Shimei laughs )
- WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
I EXPECTED SO MUCH BETTER
OUT OF YOU, DEAR BOY.
- ENOUGH! I'M PUTTING A STOP
TO THIS NOW.
- THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- NO.
I WON'T LET YOU FIGHT HIM.
YOU'VE GOTTA PROTECT LAILA.
MUSTACHE, BELONGS TO ME.
- TAITO!
- ( whispers ) - RUN AT HIM
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
- LAILA?
- YEAH?
- I CAN'T KEEP MY PROMISE
TO YOU. FORGIVE ME.
- IS ALKAID PRACTICING
HIS GENUFLECTION?
I MUST SAY, THE ATTITUDE
SUITS YOU BETTER
THAN ONE MIGHT FIRST SUSPECT.
- ( he grunts )
- YOU CHARGE TO YOUR DOOM.
- SHIMEI! LOOK AT ME!
- FOOLISHNESS. THE BODY IN WHICH
HE'S SUBSUMED IS INVIOLATE.
YOU'VE MORE OR LESS
LANCED A BOIL.
- Laila: HOSEI!
- HOSEI.
HOSEI!
- LISTEN TO ME. WE HAVE TO SET
A COURSE FOR LUO CHANG.
I KNOW I'M ESSENTIALLY
POWERLESS TO HELP.
BUT I WILL NOT LUXURIATE WHILE
MY BROTHER WAGERS HIS LIFE.
- PLEASE, YOUR HIGHNESS,
BE REASONABLE.
- NO!
WORDS WILL NOT ASSUAGE ME!
- AT YOUR MAJESTY'S
INSISTENCE, WE MUST COMPLY.
- Enki: LIKE HELL WE DO.
- I BEG YOU, FOR THEM!
- MY ORDERS ARE TO ESCORT YOU
AS FAR AWAY FROM
DANGER AS POSSIBLE.
I AM NOT ABOUT TO BREAK RANKS.
WHETHER YOU LIKE THOSE TERMS
OR NOT, YOUR MAJESTY,
THAT IS HOW IT'S GOING TO BE.
- LOOK, MY REIGN WAS THAT
OF A FECKLESS SCAPEGOAT
SCARCELY ABLE TO BLEAT.
IF I ABANDON THIS EMPIRE'S
TRUE HEROES NOW,
NOT A SINGLE THING
WILL HAVE CHANGED.
NOT ONE, AND IT WILL ONLY BE
A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE SOMEONE
FOLLOWS KEIRO'S EXAMPLE.
PERHAPS I HAVE NOT THE
MEANS TO MARSHAL AN ARMY.
PERHAPS I HAVEN'T
THE STRENGTH TO FIGHT.
EVEN SO, AT MY PERIL,
I WILL LEAD THE CHARGE!
- TURN THE SHIP AROUND. SET
A SWIFT COURSE FOR LU CHONG!
WE SAIL FOR THE CAPITAL!
- ( all cheering )
- YOU HAVE MY THANKS, ENKI.
I WILL APOLOGIZE TO
KOYO ON YOUR BEHALF.
- YEAH, GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- ONLY ONE OF THEM LEFT.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
- ( she growls )
- YOU WERE LOVELY ONCE.
BEFORE KEIRO AND CHOKA
SUNK THEIR TALONS INTO WHAT
WAS A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
COME! I'LL RELEASE YOU.
- RINMEI!
- RYUKO!
- HER POWER'S IMMENSE!
- INDEED. RIVALED ONLY
BY HER MADNESS.
- HOW YOU SCUTTLE TO
ONE ANOTHER'S SIDE.
LIKE SCAVENGERS TO THE BAIT
OF FRESH CARRION.
YOURS IT NOT A GENUINE LOVE!
YOU FEAR TOO MUCH THE
OTHER TO DIE.
YOU CHEAT THE TRUE
MEASURE OF DEVOTION!
- YOU'RE WRONG. THE MEASURE
OF OUR DEVOTION IS THAT
WE DESPAIR EACH OTHER
TO BE USED AS BAIT.
A SENTIMENT KEIRO
DOES NOT SHARE.
- ( he screams )
- Rinmei: RYUKO!
- Choka: INSOLENT LITTLE TRAMP!
I AM NO DECOY. KEIRO'S LOVE
FOR ME DEFIES IMAGINATION.
- WHAT THE?
- SHE IS DELUSIONAL.
SHE SUMMONS EVERY SCRAP
OF HER POWER TO SUPPORT THE LIE.
- IT'S SAD, HER STATE. ONE FEELS
PITY FOR SUCH A CREATURE.
WILL YOU HELP ME TO FREE HER?
- YOU FOOL, DO YOU
EVEN HAVE TO ASK?
- DIE!
WHAT IS YOUR ARM
TO HELL'S FURY?
- RINMEI! NOW!
- ( she yells )
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THERE GOES EACH OF US BUT
FOR THE GRACE OF HEAVEN'S WHEEL.
IN ANOTHER LIFE, WE...
- LET'S GO. OUR FRIENDS
ARE ALL COUNTING ON US.
- NOW. STAND, ALKAID.
THAT I MAY KNOCK YOU DOWN.
YOUR MIND HAS NOT YET BEGUN
TO REEL AT MY POWER!
- IN YOUR PLACE, I'D OBEY.
OR ELSE SCURRY TOWARDS THE
SUREST MEANS
OF TAKING MY OWN LIFE.
- ( whimpers )
- Taito: WHY TRY TO STAND?
I'LL ONLY GIVE HIM THE PLEASURE
OF SEEING ME DOUBLE OVER.
HOSEI'S MORE OR LESS DONE
FOR. RYUKO, RINMEI, KOYO...
NONE OF US EVER STOOD A
CHANCE AGAINST THIS GUY.
BUT YOU KNOW. IT'S OKAY.
I'VE DONE MY BEST.
IT'S NOT LIKE ANYBODY'D
BLAME ME FOR STAYING DOWN.
- ACQUAINTED WITH
YOUR LIMITS, ARE WE?
- ( he grunts )
- WALLOW IN IT, ALKAID!
DROWN IN THE
BITTER TIDE OF DEFEAT!
- I GUESS THIS IS IT.
FOR ALL MY CHEST THUMPING,
I'M JUST A PATHETIC,
LOUD-MOUTHED WEAKLING AFTER ALL.
- ON THE WINGS OF MY TRIUMPH.
SOARS THE ANNIHILATION OF ALL!
- Ryuko, Rinmei, Koyo together:
TAITO!
- YOU MADE IT THROUGH!
- ( he chuckles )
- JUST IN TIME.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME. I'VE
A LONG WAY TO GO YET
BEFORE I CAN HOPE TO...
- ( Both groan in pain )
- RYUKO! KOYO!
- YOU STILL THINK TO WIN?
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
RINMEI! GET BACK!
- YOU NEEDN'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I HARBOR NO ILLUSIONS
OF DEFEATING KEIRO.
THAT SAID, I MIGHT BE ABLE TO
BUY YOU A FEW MOMENTS
WITH WHICH TO RECUPERATE,
SUCH AS I CAN.
- BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE WITHOUT YOU,
HOPE WILL FALTER.
YOU ARE A BEACON, TAITO. THE
EMBODIMENT OF THAT INNOCENCE
THIS LAND AND ITS PEOPLE
WOULD SEE RESTORED.
IMMUNE TO DEGRADATION'S GRIP.
IT'S PLAIN TO ALL OF US.
TO SEE YOU THRIVE, WE FIGHT!
- THAT'S IT! COME TO ME!
- WHAT!
- Rinmei: TAITO!
- THIS CANNOT BE!
ALKAID'S POWER IS SPENT!
- THANKS, RINMEI,
I OWE YOU ONE.
I WAS ABOUT TO CALL IT QUITS
FOR A SECOND THERE.
KEIRO PRETTY MUCH HAD ME
BELIEVING HIS WHOLE LINE
ABOUT INVINCIBILITY.
I WAS JUST KNUCKLING UNDER
BY CHOICE.
BUT THERE REALLY IS NO CHOICE.
IF I LET HIM WIN,
EVERYONE SUFFERS.
HEY, SIS, WOULD YOU KNOCK
SOME SENSE INTO ME?
- SHAPE UP, TAI!
GET OVER YOURSELF!
- ( groans in pain )
- THAT'S THE STUFF. THANK YOU.
- Keiro: NO! YOU REJECTED
YOUR FATE, ALKAID.
THE WHEEL OF HEAVEN DOES
NOT RESCIND ITS VERDICT.
- FATE HAS A LOT LESS TO
DO WITH THIS THAN YOU THINK.
NO STAR HOLDS A
CANDLE TO FRIENDS
WILLING TO FIGHT FOR YOU.
THE SKY CAN TURN ALL IT WANTS!
RYUKO, RINMEI,
KOYO, HOSEI, LAILA,
GRANDPA, THE MONKS,
THE QING LONG PLATOON,
LIEN, THE CHILDREN, RYUSHO,
TOKAKU, THE WO JIN SQUAD,
TAKI, MY BROTHER THE EMPEROR,
COUNTLESS KIND HEARTED
STRANGERS ALONG THE WAY.
THOSE OF US WHO FELL.
SHOKAKU, KOEI,
THE MAN I WAS PROUD
TO CALL MY FATHER, SOEI.
I'M NOT IN THIS MESS FOR
MY OWN SAKE, BUT THEIRS.
AND NOT A DAMN THING
YOU'VE GOT COMPARES TO THEM.
- BLASPHEMY! EARTHLY TIES ARE
EPHEMERA BEFORE THE STARS.
YOU AND YOUR LITTLE RAGTAG
ENTOURAGE ARE AS NOTHING!
- HEH. FOR ALL THAT FANCY TALK,
YOU'RE KINDA MISSIN' THE POINT.
HOW MUCH MORE YOU GONNA
RATTLE OFF ABOUT FATE?
- Keiro: WHY DO YOU
PIT YOURSELF AGAINST DESTINY?
- BECAUSE YOU REALLY
PISS ME OFF!
- ( he screams )
- THIS WILL END.
ALL OF IT WILL END.
I SHALL SUNDER YOU, ALKAID!
- COME ON! AND WHILE WE'RE
AT IT, THAT'S NOT MY NAME.
IT'S TAITO!
- TAITO.
- TAITO
- Laila: TAITO!
- WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- THE SWORD OF RULE.
- Tokaku: SWORD OF
RULE INDEED!
- Taito: WE'RE ALL
COUNTING ON YOU.
- Taito: DON'T YOU DARE FORGET
THAT PROMISE.
- I SWEAR I WON'T.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, MY DEAR?
- OH, NOTHING.
I SHALL MAKE THINGS
RIGHT AGAIN.
- ( theme song playing )
- SO, ABOUT WHAT HAPPENS TO US
ONCE MY BROTHER'S BEEN AVENGED.
YOU SEEMED TO STOP JUST
SHORT OF AN ANSWER.
- WHY WAS THAT?
- UH, WELL. YOU SEE, I...
- Ryusho: TAIGA ACCEPTS HIS NEW
ROLE WITH APLOMB, DOES HE NOT?
- Tokaku: QUITE SO. AND STEEPED
IN BEAUTIFUL IRONY, TO BE SURE.
KEIRO'S REIGN OF TERROR ROUSED
IN PRINCE AND PROLE ALIKE
A NEWFOUND ARDOR FOR
THE WORK OF PEACE.
- HEY, I'M SENDING A LETTER TO
LIAN TONG. ANYTHING TO ADD?
- NO, NOTHING INTERESTING.
WELL, PERHAPS TELL THEM
I'LL VISIT ONCE MY HAIR'S
GROWN BACK OF COURSE.
- I LIKE YOU BALD. THINK IT
GIVES YOU CHARACTER.
- Ryuko: REALLY?
- Laila: SHE SAYS THE CAPITAL
IS IN MUCH BETTER SHAPE NOW.
- Hosei: THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
I GUESS TAIGA'S REALLY
TURNED OVER A NEW LEAF.
- Laila: SOUNDS LIKE IT.
- HOSEI, DOES IT EVER FEEL
TO YOU AS IF NONE OF THIS
REALLY HAPPENED?
YOU EVER THINK,
MAYBE TAI WAS WRONG?
I MEAN ABOUT FATE
BEING A SHAM.
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
REALLY ALL THAT CUT AND DRY.
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT THAT SKY!
THE STARS GO ON AND ON.
EVERY PERSON
WHO'S EVER LIVED,
WHO EVER WILL LIVE COULD BE
A PART OF SOME AGE OLD DANCE
GOING ON UP THERE.
- MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF US HAS A STAR.
NOT JUST THE DIPPER BEARERS.
BUT I STILL AGREE WITH
WHAT TAITO SAID ABOUT FATE,
THAT OUR DESTINY IS
UP TO US.
HEY! WHICH STAR DO YOU THINK
BELONGS TO YOU?
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
THE BIG ONE!
- ( Hosei laughs )
- Hosei: WOW! SO MUCH
FOR MODESTY, HUH?
- YEAH, WELL. I SAW IT FIRST,
SO THERE.
- I'D HAVE PICKED THE
SAME ONE FOR YOU.
- YEAH, IT'S A PERFECT MATCH.
YOU DEFINITELY GOT THE
ROUND CRATER FACE THING
GOING ON AT LEAST.
- PLEASE! LIKE YOU'VE GOT
ANY RIGHT TO DISH OUT INSULTS.
I'D SAY HAVE A LOOK AT YOUR
OWN MUG IF I DIDN'T THINK
IT'D SCARE YOU HALF TO DEATH!
- Hosei: SCARES ME JUST SEEIN'
THE THING IN PROFILE.
- Taito: YEAH,
THAT'S IT, LOSERS.
SCRAMBLE TO OVERCONFISCATE LIKE
THE GREEN EYED YEASTS YOU ARE!
- Sonnei: ALKAID TRIUMPHS,
DUBHE FALLS.
AND FOR NOW IT SEEMS
THE WHEEL OF HEAVEN
TURNS A TRANQUIL EYE
TO OUR HUMBLE SPHERE.
BUT 'ROUND AGAIN WILL COME A
TIME WHEN EVIL HARRIES GOOD.
WHEN SOULS MUST RISE
TO HEED THE CALL OF DESTINY
AND BRAVE ANEW
THE RAZOR'S EDGE.
SOULS PERHAPS MUCH
LIKE OUR DEAR TAITO,
FOR WHOM JUSTICE
IS BUT COMPASSION,
STARS BUT FLECKS OF LIGHT,
AND FATE BUT A HERO'S TALE.