- ( theme song playing )
- COULD YOU WALK ANY SLOWER?
I COULD'VE PAVED A ROAD BY NOW.
- CALM DOWN, TAITO.
WHAT'S THE BIG RUSH?
THERE'S NO HARM IN PACING
OURSELVES.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE
CAPITAL'S GOING ANYWHERE.
- WHAT ABOUT MOUSTACHE?
YOU THINK THE BASTARD
IS JUST ROOTED TO THE SPOT?
IF HE'S GONE WHEN WE GET THERE,
I'M HOLDING YOU RESPONSIBLE.
- PLEASE LOWER YOUR VOICE,
WE CAN HEAR YOU. BESIDES,
THE MAN IS A GENERAL.
HARDLY THE TYPE TO TAKE UP
THE MANTLE OF VAGABOND.
- YEAH, WELL, SO HE MAYBE,
HE COULD TAKE UP THE MANTLE
OF SOME OTHER KIND OF BOND.
- AH, DO YOU PRACTICE
BEING A MORON?
- SHUT UP.
NO ONE ASKED YOU.
- WHY, YOU JERK.
- DON'T TROUBLE YOURSELF.
THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR.
WE'LL ARRIVE IN
OUR OWN GOOD TIME.
BELIEVE ME, KEIRO WILL MOST
LIKELY BE WAITING FOR US.
IT'S YOUR DESTINY. THAT SAID,
THE QUESTION YOU SHOULD BE
ASKING IS WHETHER YOU'RE
STRONG ENOUGH
TO FACE HIM.
- FACE HIM? HEY, HOLD ON.
THE ONLY REASON HE BEAT ME
IS 'CAUSE I WAS TIRED
AND HE CAUGHT ME OFF GUARD.
IF IT'D BEEN A FAIR FIGHT HE...
- WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A FAIR FIGHT.
YOU'D BEST LEARN THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME, I SUGGEST
WE TRAVEL AT OUR LEISURE.
BESIDES, THIS IS A GOOD SPOT
TO WASH UP.
- ( humming )
- SO, YOU REALLY THINK
I'VE GOT MY WORK CUT OUT
FOR ME, DON'T YOU?
- LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
YOU DO KNOW THE EIGHT
GREAT STYLES, YES?
- OF COURSE, I WAS RAISED
BY THE PRIESTHOOD.
- VERY WELL. THEN WHAT EXACTLY
ARE THEY? NAME THEM ALL OFF.
- AH. YOU'VE GOT THE FIST,
AND YOU'VE GOT THE STAFF
THEN THE ROPE, THE BOW,
THE SPEAR, THERE'S THE SWORD
THEN THERE'S THE...
- SO, UH, THERE'S ONLY SIX?
- THAT'S KINDA STRANGE, HUH?
YOU'D EXPECT THERE
TO BE EIGHT OF THEM.
- VERY FEW PEOPLE KNOW
THE REMAINING TWO.
THEY BOTH ENCOMPASS
THE TECHNIQUE KNOWN
AS CHANNELING.
- CHANNELING? WHAT'S THAT?
- OF THE TWO, TRAGICALLY,
THE OLDEST STYLE IS NOW LOST
TO US.
LIKELY AS NOT BECAUSE
FEW PEOPLE WERE ABLE
TO MASTER IT.
- AH. WHO CARES?
COME ON, I'M NOT HERE
FOR A STUPID HISTORY LESSON.
WHAT DOES ANY OF THIS HAVE
TO DO WITH ME? HEY, WAIT,
DON'T JUST WALK AWAY.
I WANT TO HEAR WHY YOU THINK
I CAN'T DEFEAT LORD KEIRO.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps ) MY WORD.
- THAT, FRIENDS, IS CHANNELING.
NOT THE BEST EXAMPLE.
CLOTH IS A POOR CONDUIT.
BUT I'M SURE YOU GET
THE BASIC SENSE.
INCIDENTALLY, IT MAY INTEREST
YOU TO KNOW, KEIRO'S REPUTATION
AS A CHANNELER IS UNMATCHED.
TAITO, UNTIL A WARRIOR
LEARNS SELF-CONTROL,
THINGS DO NOT
AUGER WELL FOR HIM.
WE MUST TAKE THAT TO HEART.
IT IS THE ESSENCE OF
CHANNELING. DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- HMM. GIVE ME A BREAK.
HOW HARD COULD THIS BE?
WORK YOU PIECE OF CRAP.
- PATIENCE IS NOT HIS
STRONG POINT.
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles ) THAT THING
IS COLOSSAL.
- THE WO JIN SQUAD. WHAT BRINGS
THEM TO SUCH A RURAL PORT?
- WOW. THIS IS
INCREDIBLE, TAI.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY
BUILDINGS IN ONE PLACE.
LOOK UP THERE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE LIVING
IN THE SHADOW OF THAT THING?
- NOT REALLY. IS IT ME OR
DOES THIS PLACE FEEL WORN OUT?
- YOU KNOW, NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT.
- I'VE HEARD STORIES
ABOUT IMPERIAL MAGISTRATES,
PASSING THROUGH ONE
AFTER ANOTHER.
BLEEDING TOWNS LIKE THESE
OF ALL THEIR WEALTH.
SUCH TRAGEDY IS RIFE THESE DAYS.
- MAGISTRATES? I SEE.
THE GUYS BACK HOME
USED TO TALK.
THEY'D SAY THE SAME THING.
EVER SINCE THE CURRENT EMPEROR
PARKED HIS RUMP IN THE THRONE,
THEY SAY IT'S GOTTEN WORSE.
NOT JUST IN TOWNS LIKE THIS,
BUT EVERYWHERE.
DAMN IT. BETWEEN MOUSTACHE
AND WELL, WHOEVER IS RUNNING
THE SHOW HERE, IT'S A TRAVESTY.
THE EMPIRE IS NOTHING
BUT A BUNCH OF FAT...
- SHUT UP. YOU TRYING
TO GET US ARRESTED?
- TELL YOU WHAT.
SINCE WE'RE HERE,
I'LL GO PROCURE LODGINGS
FOR THE NIGHT.
AND YOU TWO CAN TAKE
A LITTLE TOUR OF THAT BIG SHIP.
- I'M SURE THEY'D WELCOME
THE CURIOUS.
- NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
- HOW DO YOU ALWAYS KNOW
JUST WHAT TO SAY?
- SEE YOU IN A BIT.
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
- CAN'T YOU MAKE AN EXCEPTION
FOR US? COME ON, PLEASE.
WE JUST WANT TO HAVE
A LITTLE PEEK INSIDE.
- THIS IS THE DOU YA, KID.
NOT SOME FLOATING MUSEUM.
THE WO JIN SQUAD
DOESN'T PLAY TOUR GUIDE
TO SNOT-NOSED COMMONERS.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A SNOT-NOSED COMMONER,
YOU ONE-EYED RIVER RAT?
- COME ON, LET US ON BOARD.
- TAITO.
- ( coughs )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
IS IT TOO COLD OUT FOR YOU?
DEAR SISTER, CURSE THIS
INCURABLE DISEASE
LAYING WASTE TO YOU.
- ( coughs ) BROTHER, I HAVE
BUT ONE WISH BEFORE
THE DISEASE CLAIMS
ITS FINAL TOLL.
- SPEAK IT ALOUD, DEAR SISTER.
- WHILE I, WHILE I STILL
POSSESS THE STRENGTH TO STAND,
I WISH TO BOARD THIS SHIP.
- OF COURSE. ANYTHING
AT ALL FOR MY DEAR SISTER.
SURELY, THIS KIND SAILOR'S
HEART CANNOT BE MADE OF STONE.
- WELL THEN, HOW ABOUT IT?
YOU GOING TO LET US ON?
- GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- WHAT A JERK.
YELLING AT A SICK GIRL.
- I'M KINDA SHOCKED, ACTUALLY.
THAT WAS A ONCE IN A LIFETIME
PERFORMANCE.
- AH, THERE YOU ARE.
- HUH?
- I FOUND A PLACE FOR US
TO STAY.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- NOT TO NITPICK,
BUT, UH, THIS PLACE LOOKS
A LITTLE RUN-DOWN.
- THAT IT IS. BUT FOR
OUR HUMBLE PURPOSE,
IT WILL MORE THAN SUFFICE.
- YOU AGAIN? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YES, MA'AM.
THESE TWO ARE MY FRIENDS.
THE ONES I SPOKE TO YOU ABOUT.
WE SEEK SHELTER FOR THE EVENING.
- I SUPPOSE. THE RAIN
WILL BRING A CHILL.
I'LL MUSTER UP SOME EXTRA
BLANKETS FOR YOU. SOMEWHERE.
- WE'RE GRATEFUL TO YOU.
- WELL, UH, SHE SEEMS NICE.
- YEAH, REAL NICE.
- Oen: IMAGINE ME, SHARING
MY TABLE WITH NONE OTHER THAN
KOYO OF THE WO JIN SQUAD.
PRESIDING OVER
A HOLE IN THE GROUND
LIKE THIS DOES HAVE ITS PERKS.
FEW AND FAR BETWEEN AS THEY ARE.
- ( people chattering )
- ( chuckles ) YOU FLATTER ME.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
IF I MAY SPEAK CANDIDLY, SIR,
IF I'D HAVE KNOWN
YOU WERE POISED TO RETURN,
I'D HAVE COME SOONER.
THE CAPITAL'S IN NEED
OF SHREWD MEN LIKE YOURSELF.
- ( chuckles ) WELL PLAYED.
THAT SAME SILVER TONGUE
MUST'VE MANEUVERED YOU
INTO THE POSITION OF CAPTAIN.
- I THINK YOU FLATTER ME.
- NOT ONE BIT, SIR.
- WE LOWLY ENTREPRENEURS MAKE
IT A POINT OF READING THE TIDE.
THAT'S HOW WE STAY AFLOAT.
I HOPE IT'S NOT VULGAR OF ME
TO SAY, BUT WHEN ALL SIGNS
POINT TO A MILITARY COUP,
I'M THE KIND OF MAN
WHO LIKES TO HEDGE HIS BETS.
- ( laughs ) YOU ARE
A PIECE OF WORK.
MORE FOOD AND DRINK
FOR MY GOOD FRIEND,
THE WATER-FARING SOOTHSAYER.
- AS YOU WISH.
- CARE FOR SOME
LIGHT ENTERTAINMENT?
- HUH?
- MY SPECIALTY, ONE OF SEVERAL.
- ( screams )
- ( people cheering )
- FORGIVE ME,
I'M A BIT OUT OF PRACTICE.
- BAH, IT WAS SPLENDID.
- HMM.
- DID YOU SEE, KORIN?
- THE FAMOUS CAPTAIN
OF THE WO JIN SQUAD.
A VERY GOOD SIGN,
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- QUITE. KOYO'S REPUTATION
DOES PRECEDE HIM, SIR.
AND HE SEEMS EAGER
TO BE AT YOUR DISPOSAL.
- WHAT HAVE I ALWAYS TOLD YOU?
POWER FOREVER GRAVITATES
TOWARDS POWER.
- INDEED.
- MY RETURN MUST BE GRAND.
I'LL SPARE ABSOLUTELY
NO EXPENSE.
BID FAREWELL TO OBSCURITY.
AND TAKE WITH ME
WHAT RICHES
THIS STAGNANT
BACKWATER STILL HOLDS.
- ( chuckles )
- TROUBLE SLEEPING?
- ( screams )
- THERE'S A CORNER OF THE
COURTYARD THAT'S RELATIVELY DRY.
IDEAL FOR KEEPING
ONE SELF SHARP.
FEEL FREE TO USE IT.
- OKAY. SHE'S A NICE PERSON.
REMEMBER THAT.
CHANNELING BEGINS WITH BEING
CONSCIOUS OF THE BODY'S
NATURAL FLOW OF ENERGY.
THE TRICK IS TO REDIRECT
THAT FLOW.
THEN, LET YOUR
WEAPON DO THE REST.
( grunts )
COME ON. WHY WON'T THIS WORK?
GEEZ, MAYBE, IT'S THE CLOTH.
( grunts )
DAMN IT.
- Ryuko: REMEMBER, LET
THE OBJECT BE YOUR CONDUIT.
YOU'RE ALLOWING THE ENERGY
TO DAM UP IN YOUR RIGHT ARM.
DON'T TRY TO FORCE THINGS.
LET THE WEAPON RECEIVE IT.
ENERGY FOLLOWS THE PATH
OF LEAST RSISTANCE.
YOU HAVE TO SIMPLY
LEARN TO LET IT FLOW.
- YEAH, YOU SAY THAT
BUT HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO LET IT FLOW INTO THIS?
IT'S JUST A STUPID RAG.
- TO DEFEAT KEIRO,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WORK THAT OUT FOR YOURSELF.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S DO THIS.
- YOU'VE ALREADY USED
CHANNELING ONCE, TAITO.
WHETHER YOU KNOW IT OR NOT.
DO I DARE RISK RE-AWAKENING
ALKAID BY TEACHING YOU
HOW TO USE IT CONSCIOUSLY?
MAY THE STARS GUIDE US.
THEIR WAY IS OUR WAY.
- WOW, LOOK AT ALL
OF THEM.
SOLDIERS AS FAR
AS THE EYE CAN SEE.
WAVE AFTER WAVE. LED BY
THE BIG MAN HIMSELF, NO LESS.
THE ONE WHO IS SITTING PRETTY
WHILE HIS MEN TOUGH IT OUT
HERE IN THE WILDERNESS.
( whimpers ) THESE POUR SOULS.
( chuckles ) LET'S GO SEE
IF I CAN LIGHTEN THEIR LOAD.
- ( snoring )
- TAITO, WAKE UP. WAKE UP
- ( grunts ) I SAID WAKE UP!
- Taito: OW.
- SO, NOW, WE ARE
STRANDED HERE. GREAT.
- THE FLOODING'S BOUND
TO SUBSIDE BEFORE TOO LONG.
THERE'S NOTHING TO DO BUT WAIT.
TRY TO MAKE THE MOST OF IT.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
HEY, AT LEAST THIS GIVES ME
A CHANCE TO GET SOME MORE
TRAINING UNDER MY BELT, RIGHT?
- HA. TRAINING FOR WHAT,
I'D LIKE TO KNOW.
SLEEPING IN ALL DAY?
- THAT'S ABOUT ALL
YOU'VE DONE SO FAR.
- SHUT YOUR FACE!
- HMM.
- EXCUSE ME FOR JUST A MOMENT.
- IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT,
MA'AM?
IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO?
- NO, NO. YOU'RE FINE.
THIS ROOM IS WHERE I HAVE
THE BEST VIEW, THAT'S ALL.
FORGIVE MY POOR MANNERS.
I'LL BET YOU'D LIKE ME TO BRING
IN SOME MORE TEA, WOULDN'T YOU?
- AH. YES PLEASE.
- WE CALL HIM THE SACRED BEAR.
HE IS THE VILLAGE'S
GUARDIAN SPIRIT.
FOR UNTOLD GENERATIONS,
HE HAS PROTECTED US.
WE'VE WORSHIPED HIM
SINCE TIME OUT OF MIND
AND GLADLY, HIS BENEVOLENCE
HAS BEEN OUR BOON.
BUT AS OF LATE, CORRUPT
OFFICIALS LIKE OUR LATEST
BLOCKHEADED LORD MAYOR
FORBID US FROM PAYING HOMAGE
TO ANYTHING BUT WHAT THE EMPIRE
DEEMS APPROPRIATE.
- REALLY?
- POOR AS WE ARE, IN ORDER
TO SURVIVE AT ALL,
WE MUST DO
AS WE'RE TOLD.
WE'VE HAD TO SURRENDER
OUR FAITH.
- THAT'S WRONG. IT'S CRUEL.
YOU GUYS SHOULD ALL BAND
TOGETHER AND KICK THE MAYOR OUT.
STAND UP AND FIGHT.
- Man: OPEN UP.
WE'VE GOT AN EMERGENCY.
- THAT IS UNTHINKABLE.
YOU MEN. PREPOSTEROUS.
THE SACRED BEAR HAS STOOD
FOR CENTURIES.
IT'S NOT GOING TO COME
CRASHING DOWN NOW
ON ACCOUNT OF A LITTLE RAIN.
- THERE'S NO POINT IN DENYING
IT ANYMORE.
THAT ROCK IS
TEETERING ON THE BRINK.
THE TOWN IS IN JEOPARDY.
- WORSE YET, THE ROADS
ARE FLOODED.
WE HAVE NO
OPTION BUT TO STAY HERE.
- PERHAPS, THIS IS NO MORE
THAN WE DESERVE FOR HAVING
ABANDONED OUR GUARDIAN.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- THERE'S NOTHING
TO DO BUT FLEE.
WE'LL TAKE OUR CHANCES.
THIS TOWN'S FATE IS NOT OURS.
- WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
THESE POOR PEOPLE TO BE CRUSHED.
- WE'RE NOT LEAVING THEM.
THEY NEED OUR HELP.
I DON'T GIVE A
DAMN ABOUT FATE.
AH, I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
- IT'S A MATTER OF LIFE
AND DEATH.
- WE BEG YOU.
- I TOLD YOU THE ANSWER IS NO.
I DON'T CARE IF THAT ROCK
SPROUTS LEGS AND WALKS.
THEY'RE NOT SETTING FOOT
ON THIS SHIP AND THAT'S FINAL.
- SCREW YOU.
I DEMAND TO SEE THE CAPTAIN.
- PLEASE, JUST LET US
TALK TO HIM.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M NOT GOING TO PESTER
THE BOSS FOR YOU TWO.
NOW, GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE
BEFORE I START TO GET MAD.
- AH, YOU SON OF A...
- ( grunts )
- YOU LITTLE PUNK.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME TO DEAL
WITH PISSANTS LIKE YOU.
GET YOUR CAPTAIN
OUT HERE RIGHT NOW.
- WHO ARE YOU
TO BARK ORDERS AT US?
- WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
THREE AGAINST ONE STRIKE
YOU FELLAS AS THE BEST WAY
TO REPRESENT THE WO JIN SQUAD?
- THIS KID'S THE ONE
THAT THREW THE FIRST PUNCH.
- DO I HAVE TO SPELL IT OUT?
- SO, I GUESS YOU ARE
THE CAPTAIN OF THIS RIG, HUH?
- NAME'S KOYO. AND YOU ARE?
- MY NAME'S TAITO.
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
THAT BOULDER UP THERE
IS GOING TO FALL ANY MINUTE.
NOW LOOK. THE PEOPLE HAVE
NO WAY OUT.
THEY'LL ALL BE KILLED.
LET THEM ON BOARD.
- PLEASE, SIR.
WE'LL DO ANYTHING.
- Oen: CLEAR A PATH.
SORRY TO MAKE YOU WAIT, CAPTAIN.
- NOT AT ALL, LORD MAYOR.
YOUR APPEARANCE
IS IMPECCABLY TIMED.
- HMM. BELIEVE ME, MY FRIEND,
YOU DON'T KNOW THE HALF OF IT.
THAT TREASURE'S NOT
GOING TO HAUL ITSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
CHOP CHOP, WASTRELS.
- MY GOOD MAN, WE GREATLY
APPRECIATE THE ASSISTANCE.
- DON'T THINK WE WILL FORGET
YOU IN THE DAYS TO COME.
- YOUR GRATITUDE HONORS ME.
THANK YOU, SIR.
- HEY, HOLD ON.
WHAT ABOUT EVERYBODY ELSE?
ISN'T A POOR PERSON'S
GRATITUDE ENOUGH FOR YOU?
- OH, WHAT A WIT. WHO'S THE
RUNT? NOT ONE OF YOURS I HOPE.
- NO, SIR. HE MISTAKES ME
FOR A PHILANTHROPIST
AND EXPECTS MY SHIP
TO HARBOR THE ENTIRE TOWN.
- DON'T BE ABSURD.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M NOT SHARING QUARTERS
WITH PEASANTS.
THE RABBLE WILL JUST
HAVE TO FEND FOR THEMSELVES.
IT'S NONE OF MY CONCERN.
- YOU HEARTLESS MONSTER.
- LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
THEY'VE HELD THE OLD FAITH
SECRETLY ALL THESE YEARS.
MAYBE THEIR GOD
WILL SPARE THEM.
( laughs )
- TAITO, WAIT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- ( laughs )
BEHOLD THE SECRET
KINGS OF MEN.
I'VE SPENT AN AGE BUILDING
THIS LITTLE NEST EGG.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO HEDGES HIS BETS.
- I CAN TELL BUT SURELY
THIS CAN'T BE ALL.
THAT IS, I'D EXPECTED TO SEE
THE JEWEL OF THE SACRED BEAR.
- JEWEL OF THE SACRED BEAR?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, SIR.
ACCORDING TO MY INFORMATION,
THE JEWEL SAID TO HAVE BEEN
BURIED BY YOUR PREDECESSOR,
IS ONE OF THE LARGEST
IN THE REALM.
DON'T TELL ME IT'S NOT HERE.
I ASSUMED YOUR MEN WOULD
HAVE DISCOVERED IT BY NOW.
- HURRY IT UP, CRETINS!
- MY WORD. THAT KOYO
IS WORTH HIS WEIGHT IN GOLD.
- I'LL SAY. A GEM OF THAT
CALIBER HAS BEEN UNDER
OUR FEET THIS WHOLE TIME?
JUST WHAT I NEED TO SECURE
MY FORTUNES.
- THE OLD BEAR IS NOT
GOING TO HOLD MUCH LONGER
IN THIS DOWNPOUR.
HEY, YOU THERE, GIRL.
THE VIEW'S FAR BETTER ON BOARD.
- THIS IS A LOAD OF CRAP.
POOR PEOPLE HAVE TO DIE JUST
SO RICH BASTARDS LIKE HIM,
CAN CLEAR OUT WITH EVERYTHING?
WELL, NOT ON MY WATCH.
TRY TO HOLD ON, OKAY?
JUST A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
GIVE YOUR PEOPLE A CHANCE
TO ESCAPE.
HOLD ON, DAMN IT!
- YOU KNOW, TAITO.
I FEEL FOR YOUR SISTER.
- SHE'S GROWN UP HAVING TO DEAL
WITH THIS KIND OF STUPIDITY.
- RYUKO.
- AS MASTER SONNEI SAYS,
NO ONE FORGES THEIR PATH ALONE.
THOUGH YOU CAN BELIEVE
AS YOU LIKE.
- PUT YOUR BACKS INTO IT, MEN.
WHOEVER FINDS THE JEWEL,
GETS A PROMOTION.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
SO CLOSE I CAN TASTE IT.
( laughs )
- HAVE YOU GOT IT YET OR WHAT?
- DONE. YOU CAN LET GO NOW.
- I DO BELIEVE THAT
WILL HOLD QUITE NICELY.
THEN AGAIN, IF THIS RAIN
SOFTENS THE GROUND ANY MORE,
WHO KNOWS?
- AH.
- RYUKO!
- WHA... WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( grunts )
- LET GO OF ME. THERE IS
NO POINT IN BOTH OF US FALLING.
I'LL BE FINE, TRUST ME.
- YEAH, NICE TRY. I DON'T
CARE HOW STRONG YOU ARE.
A FALL FROM THIS
KIND OF HEIGHT?
PLEASE, THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'D SURVIVE IT.
- TAITO, NEITHER ONE OF US
WILL SURVIVE IF YOU DON'T.
LET GO OF MY ARM. LET GO!
DAMN IT, DO AS I TELL YOU.
- THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU MADE A PROMISE TO COME
WITH ME TO THE CAPITAL
AND I'M GOING TO HOLD YOU TO IT.
YOU'RE NOT JUST MY CUSTODIAN,
YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
WHAT WAS ALL THAT CRAP
ABOUT NONE OF US
BEING ALONE IN THIS, HUH?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO COME
HELP ME SAVE THESE PEOPLE
OR EVEN COME WITH ME ON THIS
JOURNEY IN THE FIRST PLACE
BUT WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER NOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET GO!
- TAITO.
THE ALKAID SIGIL.
- ( screams )
- ( panting )
- YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
- YEAH, WELL,
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
- ( thunder rumbling )
- THE BOULDER!
- OUR SACRED BEAR.
- MY LORD, THE ROCK!
- WHAT?
- ( people screaming )
- I'M SORRY. WE REALLY
TRIED TO SAVE THIS PLACE.
- DON'T BE DAFT.
THE THREE OF YOU ARE HEROES.
ROADS AND BUILDINGS
ARE EASY TO REPLACE.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS THAT
LIVES HAVE BEEN SPARED.
AND FROM NOW ON,
OUR BELOVED GUARDIAN
IS THAT MUCH NEARER TO US.
- THAT CAPTAIN, WHY DID HE
SUDDENLY DECIDE TO HELP?
- I MEAN, HE SEEMED LIKE
SUCH A MEAN GUY AT FIRST.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- ( laughs )
I ALMOST FEEL SORRY
FOR THE MAN, FALLING FOR
SUCH AN OBVIOUS CHARADE.
JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU
HOW FAR GREED CLOUDS THE MIND.
- I MUST SAY, THOUGH,
COMING OUT HERE WAS CERTAINLY
PROFITABLE FOR US.
TOO BAD FOR THE TOWN.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE EXPECTED
THE SACRED BEAR
TO COME DOWN SO SOON.
- OH, WELL,
HE WHO MOVES MOUNTAINS
MOVES THEM STONE BY STONE.
THE BOY, TAITO. I'LL HAVE
TO REMEMBER THAT NAME.
- FINALLY, MAN. I WAS STARTING
TO THINK WE'D NEVER GET BACK
ON THE ROAD TO THE CAPITAL.
- HAVE SOME PERSPECTIVE.
WE ONLY LOST A DAY OF TRAVEL.
YOU ACT LIKE WE JUST GOT OUT
OF PRISON OR SOMETHING.
- HEY, SHUT UP. IT MIGHT
HAVE ONLY BEEN ONE DAY,
BUT IT WAS A LONG ONE!
- WELL WE'RE NOT GOING TO
MAKE UP FOR IT BY DAWDLING,
NOW ARE WE? COME ALONG.
- YOU'RE NOT LEADING.
- WHY IS HE IN SUCH A HURRY
ALL OF A SUDDEN? THAT'S ODD.
- WE'RE NOT GOING TO REACH
THE CAPITAL ANY MORE QUICKLY
BY DISCUSSING OUR PACE.
- OH, LIKE YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
- ( both laugh )
- OH, WELL, WAIT UP, GUYS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: SPURRED ON
BY THEIR DESTINIES,
THE STARS BEGIN TO CONVERGE
ON THE EARTHLY PLANE.
- Hosei: DIVINE WARRIORS?
I KNOW HOW THIS LOOKS,
BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO DO
AS MY REAL MASTER TOLD ME,
ALL RIGHT?
- Laila: YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD
AS MINE, BUT I SMELL STUPIDITY.
- Ryuko: KNOW THAT WHOEVER
ALIGNS THEMSELVES TO DUBHE,
I AM BOUND BY A SACRED DUTY
TO DESTROY.
NEXT TIME, ON HERO TALES,
HE WHO CARRIES THE PHECDA
SIGIL MUST CHOOSE HIS COURSE
IN, "CHAPTER FOUR
DIVINE WARRIOR."
- Taito: HEY, YOU STAY
THE HELL AWAY FROM HER.