- PATIENCE.
THE TIME ISN'T YET RIGHT.
- ( sighing )
- DINNER!
- ( men cheering )
( laughing )
- MEN ARE PIGS.
- ( theme song playing )
- LOOK AT YOU ALL. DISGRACEFUL.
FIGHTING OVER SCRAPS
LIKE ANIMALS.
IS THAT YOUR IDEA
OF HOW GROWN MEN
ARE MEANT TO BEHAVE?
- LOOK, ENKI, WE WERE...
- NO EXCUSES!
- YES, MA'AM.
- YES. THERE IS BUT ONE WORD
FOR THIS, SHAME!
THE ONLY REGARD YOU LOT SHOULD
HOLD YOURSELVES IN!
- YOU ARE
THE WORST OF THE OFFENDERS!
WHAT KIND OF AN EXAMPLE
DO YOU THINK IT SETS
FOR THESE MEN TO SEE
THEIR OWN CAPTAIN
COMPORT HIMSELF LIKE A BOAR?
- HM. THAT'S UNKIND.
I DID SAVE ENOUGH FOR YOU.
- Enki: NOT THE POINT!
- ( men laughing )
- Enki: SILENCE!
- JUST LOOK AT THEM.
MEN ARE THE SAME
NO MATTER WHERE YOU GO.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- YEAH. SURE, I GUESS SO.
- IT'S TAITO, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH.
- FEELING POWERLESS TO HELP
IS PRETTY AWFUL, HUH?
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT CONCERNS
THE PEOPLE WE LOVE.
- Laila: HEY, TAITO.
LISTEN, I KNOW YOU HAVEN'T EATEN
IN A WHILE.
RINMEI SHARED SOME JERKY
WITH ME, IF YOU'D LIKE SOME.
IT'S DELICIOUS!
( sighs )
UH... SO, UH...
OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
THE WOJIN GUYS
ALL WENT OUT TO HUNT
FOR EVERYBODY'S MEAL EARLIER.
'COURSE, WHAT THEY WOUND UP
CATCHING WAS WAY TOO SMALL
FOR ALL OF US TO SHARE...
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- TELL ME.
- TELL YOU WHAT?
- WHY WAS I SO HELPLESS
AGAINST KEIRO?
WHY DID RYUKO HAVE TO DIE?
JUST EXPLAIN IT TO ME!
- SORRY. I CAN'T.
- YEAH, WELL, I THOUGHT SO.
- I'M SORRY.
- THE ISSUE IS PROPORTION.
- Crewman: PROPORTION?
- UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN,
ENKI'S WRATH HAS ITS SOURCE
IN OUR PROVENDER'S
DIMINUTIVE SIZE.
- I'M NOT SO SURE
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
- THAT IS EXACTLY THE PROBLEM!
SO, THAT BEING THE CASE.
OUR SOLUTION IS TO GO AFTER
BIGGER PREY. CORRECT?
- UH...
- Men: ( reluctantly ) YEAH.
- Koyo: ENTHUSIASTICALLY!
- ( loudly ) YEAH!
- ( scoffing )
- ( footsteps )
( sobbing )
- Both: HUH?
- OH, I SEE.
- MAN, HAS HE LOST HEART.
THAT JUST DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
TAITO AT ALL.
- I'M SORRY.
- Hosei: YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR!
- Laila: I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DO SOMETHING, BUT...
- COME ON, YOU DID
WHAT YOU COULD.
I'LL BET HE WANTS TO IGNORE YOU
JUST SO HE CAN SULK OUT THERE
LIKE A BIG BABY.
HELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
HE'S THE ONLY ONE THAT'S
BROKEN UP BY RYUKO'S DEATH.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T CENSOR YOURSELF
ON MY ACCOUNT.
THAT SAID, HE'S GOT A LOT
ON HIS MIND.
I DON'T THINK RYUKO
IS THE ONLY THING TROUBLING HIM.
- ( spash )
- POOR GUY. HE'S AT A LOSS
AS TO HIS OWN PURPOSE.
I GUESS EVERY ONE OF US
BORN WITH A SIGIL
GOES DOWN THAT
ROAD EVENTUALLY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT THE
LEGENDS HAVE TO SAY ABOUT US?
- THE DIPPER BEARERS?
WHEN THE EARTHLY PLANE
IS IN CHAOS,
THEY'LL DESCEND DOWN
FROM THE SPHERE ABOVE.
- WELL. YOU'LL NOTICE
THE STORY LEAVES
WHETHER OR NOT
THE DIPPER BEARERS
BRING SALVATION, OPEN TO DEBATE.
SOME PEOPLE TAKE THE VIEW
THAT THEY'RE ACTUALLY
THE HARBINGERS OF THAT CHAOS.
WHETHER IT WISHES TO OR NOT,
A STAR AFFECTS ANY AND
EVERYTHING AROUND IT PROFOUNDLY.
FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE.
- SO THEN, YOU'RE SAYIN'
WHATEVER WE DO,
WE JUST MESS UP
PEOPLES' LIVES?
- WE'D JUST BE FOOLING OURSELVES
IF WE DIDN'T ADMIT IT.
WHEN YOU START DWELLING
ON THAT, THOUGH,
YOU OPEN THE DOOR
TO A HOST OF UGLY QUESTIONS.
EVERYTHING YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
SUDDENLY SEEMS NO MORE
THAN A MIRAGE.
YOU START TO FEEL CRUELLY
CHEATED BY YOUR OWN FATE.
- Hosei: TAITO'S JUST AT A LOW
EBB RIGHT NOW, THAT'S ALL.
HE'LL SHAKE IT OFF.
- Rinmei: ALL OF THIS WILL PASS,
LAILA. YOU'LL SEE.
- HMM.
- ( screeching )
- Koyo: HOW'S HE HOLDING UP?
- RATHER SULLENLY, I'M AFRAID.
- AH.
- I DON'T BELIEVE I'VE EVER
KNOWN YOU TO BE SO CONCERNED.
THIS UNSCHEDULED STOP
IS FOR TAITO'S SAKE.
- HARDLY.
FACT IS, I STOPPED
TO GET OUR BEARINGS,
SO TO SPEAK.
THE BOY'S MOOD IS STARTING
TO RUB OFF ON EVERYONE.
- SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
SORRY.
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
- OH, RINMEI ASKED ME
TO HOIST IT UP EARLIER.
IT'S THE INSIGNIA FOR
THE "MEN ARE HOPELESS" LEAGUE.
- UH... ( slowly ) OKAY.
- ( footsteps )
Hosei: TAITO!
( chuckling )
I'M STARVING. YOU?
- WHAT?
- ON YOUR FEET, SOURPUSS.
DINNER LEFT A LOT TO BE DESIRED,
DON'T YOU THINK?
SO WE'RE GONNA TRACK DOWN
SOMETHING WITH SOME
HONEST-TO-GOODNESS HEFT TO IT
AND FEAST LIKE THE MEN WE ARE.
HEY, WITH ME?
TAITO.
- SURE, WHATEVER.
- COME ON, MAN.
- Crewman: THERE IT IS!
- ( all gasp )
- COME ON!
- ( men shouting )
- SOUNDS LIKE WE GOT
A BANQUET HEADED OUR WAY!
- ( grunts )
- I'LL HANDLE IT FROM HERE!
- ( grunting )
- Hosei: WHAT?
GREAT, IT'S A SMART ONE.
HEADS UP, TAITO!
YOU'VE GOT COMPANY!
- ( pig grunting )
- ( screaming )
( groaning )
- TAITO!
- ( pig grunting )
- WHAT... WHAT THE...
- Hosei: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( both grunt )
- ( gasps )
HOSEI!
- THERE, NOW. IT SHOULD HEAL
BEFORE TOO LONG.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- THE HELL'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU COULD'VE BEEN KILLED!
YOU KNOW THAT?
- I... I DIDN'T MEAN...
- JUST SAVE IT! WHY DIDN'T YOU
FIGHT THE DAMN THING?
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE SHOULD'VE BEEN
ABLE TO TAKE IT DOWN
WITH A FLICK OF YOUR WRIST!
WHAT KIND OF CRAP
WERE YOU TRYIN' TO PULL?
- SORRY.
- IDIOT!
- THE MAN SAID HE WAS SORRY.
SURELY ONE INJURED PERSON
IS ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( grunting )
- Koyo: JUST AS I THOUGHT.
- KOYO.
- YOU'VE LOST THE ABILITY
TO CHANNEL, HAVEN'T YOU?
- HOW'D YOU...
- COME, NOW.
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST
TO HAVE EXPERIENCED THIS.
SO. WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO?
- WELL, I GUESS
I NEED TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
GET THE ABILITY TO CHANNEL BACK.
- IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT.
THE ONLY THING CHANNELING
IS REALLY GOOD FOR IS COMBAT.
BY TAKING IT BACK,
THE PRESUMPTION IS YOU WISH
TO RE-ENTER THE FRAY.
- WELL...
- CHERISHED FRIENDS, STRANGERS.
PEOPLE WILL DIE
BECAUSE OF THEIR LOYALTY TO YOU.
THAT IS, BECAUSE
OF THEIR LOYALTY TO ALKAID.
BUT TO TURN YOUR BACK
ON THE STARS IS TO CHOOSE
A POORLY LIT PATH INDEED.
THE PRICE OF ALKAID'S POWER
IS HIS KARMA.
REJECT THAT, AND, WELL...
- SO, WHAT THEN?
I'M JUST SUPPOSED TO ACCEPT
THIS ALKAID THING'S DESTINY
AS MY OWN ON FAITH?
HOW MANY PEOPLE DO I HAVE
TO HURT IN THE PROCESS?
- TRAGICALLY, THE BRIGHTEST
STAR TENDS TO ECLIPSE THOSE
NEAREST TO IT IN THE SKY.
THEN AGAIN, THAT SAME
HARSH GLARE CAN ILLUMINATE
THE DARKEST CORNER.
( chuckling )
GOOD, HUH?
THAT LITTLE NUGGET OF WISDOM
COMES FROM MASTER SONNEI!
- YOU KNOW MASTER SONNEI?
WHAT IS ALKAID?
WHAT'S ALL THIS "KARMA OF THE
STARS" STUFF? EXPLAIN IT TO ME!
- IN YOUR PLACE, SON.
I'D SEEK A BETTER VIEW.
CLARITY PREFERS DISTANCE.
A HAWK'S VANTAGE, AS IT WERE.
- A BETTER VIEW.
- Laila: AT THIS HOUR?
YOU JUST LET HIM GO
WANDERING OFF ALL BY HIMSELF?
- THE WAY HE IS NOW, TAITO'D
BE LUCKY TO BEAT A RABBIT!
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME,
OLD MAN?
- CALM DOWN. ( scoffing )
TRY NOT TO BE SO OVERPROTECTIVE.
- Enki: YOU ARE GUESTS
ON THE DOU YA.
AND THAT MEANS YOU SHOW
ITS CAPTAIN SOME RESPECT.
- THAT'S ABOUT
THE LONG AND SHORT OF IT.
FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
TAITO HAS THE RIGHT TO DO
AS HE PLEASES.
HE'LL RETURN IN HIS OWN GOOD
TIME. I SUGGEST YOU BE PATIENT.
- NEED YOU HAVE BEEN SO HARSH?
I MEAN, YOU COULD'VE AT LEAST
OFFERED YOUR TAKE
ON THE SITUATION.
MIGHT'VE CONSOLED THEM A BIT.
- OH, DEAR. DEFECTING TO
THEIR SIDE NOW, ARE YOU?
- YOU KNOW WHOSE SIDE I'M ON.
I JUST HAVE AN EXCESS
OF SYMPATHY
FOR ANYONE BARKED AT
BY A SELF-CENTERED,
OVERBEARING LOUT, THAT'S ALL.
- SELF-CENTERED LOUT, HUH?
MY KINDA GUY.
- ( laughing )
I'LL BET HE IS.
- "THE BRIGHTEST STAR".
RYUKO, WOULD YOU HAVE BEEN
AS CONFUSED BY ALL OF THIS
AS I AM RIGHT NOW?
- ( cheering and laughing )
- COME ON, LAILA.
HE'LL BE OKAY.
DUMB AS HE IS, AN ANIMAL'D
JUST THINK HE'S ONE OF ITS OWN.
- ( owl hooting )
- DEAD END.
- ( growling )
- WHAT THE...
NOT A GOOD SOUND.
( growling )
DAMN IT. STILL NO GOOD.
- ( rustling )
- ( gasping )
- ( growling )
- ( screaming )
- GO ON, DO YOUR WORST.
I DON'T CARE.
- ( panting )
I'M COMING. HOLD ON!
- ( men groaning )
- TIME TO SHOVE OFF, I SUPPOSE.
- ( footsteps approaching )
Enki: CAPTAIN!
IT'S LAILA. SHE'S GONE!
- NO LUCK! I CAN'T FIND
A TRACE OF HER ANYWHERE!
- Rinmei: SAME HERE!
- I SEE.
- SOMEBODY TOOK THE SWORD
FROM TAITO'S ROOM.
IT'S POSSIBLE...
- THAT SHE INTENDS TO BRING
THE SWORD TO HER BROTHER...
SHE'S PUT HERSELF
AT GREAT PERIL, I'M AFRAID.
- WE HAVE TO FORM
A SEARCH PARTY!
- ROUSE THE CREW IMMEDIATELY.
FIND HER.
- SIR!
- NOT ENOUGH HEFT TO ME
FOR A BEAST'S MEAL, HUH?
- JUST STAY STRONG.
SCARED AS YOU ARE, LAILA,
REMEMBER YOUR IDIOT BROTHER
NEEDS YOU.
- ( rustling )
- ( gasps )
( sighing )
A BUNNY. HOW CUTE.
HEY. WHY'RE YOU RUNNING OFF?
- ( growling )
- ( gasping )
( screaming )
- LAILA?
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
JUST STAY BACK!
TAITO! TAITO!
- LAILA!
- TAITO!
- ( growling )
- IT'S THAT SAME ONE!
HANG ON, SIS. I'M COMING!
( grunting )
THERE'S NO TIME!
- ( growling )
- ( guttural groan )
HEY, THERE. ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH. THANKS, TAI.
THAT MOVE.
YOU'RE ABLE TO CHANNEL AGAIN!
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT
WAS SAVING YOU,
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN...
- ( footsteps approaching )
( growling )
- NO, WAIT!
- UH.
- ( chuckling )
- Hosei: LAILA!
- SAY SOMETHING!
JUST CALL OUT!
- PLEASE. PLEASE BE ALL RIGHT.
- WE'RE ALMOST TO THE TOP.
- THANK YOU.
- ( both gasp )
- Laila: IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH. SO,
THIS IS MY ANSWER?
- THAT'S ENTIRELY UP TO YOU.
- KOYO.
- HOW LONG...
- WHAT DOES ALL THIS MEAN?
WHAT DOES IT HAVE TO DO
WITH ALKAID?
- TELL ME. WHAT DO YOU SEE?
- Taito: WELL. LOTS OF VILLAGES
AND LITTLE RIVERS
AND STUFF, I GUESS.
- Koyo: PRECISELY. YOU SEE
THINGS AS THEY ARE NOW.
BUT LONG AGO
THIS VALLEY WAS DESOLATE.
LONG AGO,
THE PEOPLE OF THIS LAND
WERE A WRETCHED LOT.
THEIR POVERTY WAS CRUSHING.
VIOLENCE AND STARVATION
WERE RIFE.
THEN OUT OF THE MISTS,
ONE DAY, EMERGED A MAN.
A WANDERER,
BEARING THE GIFT OF HOPE.
BY A SIMPLE GESTURE OF SEEDS,
THEIR COURSE WAS ALTERED.
HE LIFTED THE SCALES
FROM THEIR EYES AND TAUGHT THEM
TO RESPECT THE LAND.
HOW TO TILL AND IRRIGATE,
EVEN HOW TO MAKE PROVISION
FOR THE LEANER SEASONS.
OVER TIME, THE HARD-SCRABBLE
LIFE THEY'D KNOWN
GAVE WAY TO UNDREAMT OF
PROSPERITY AND PEACE.
ON THAT MAN'S SHOULDER,
EMBLAZONED, WAS WRIT
THE SAME SIGIL AS YOU BEAR.
- ALKAID?
- HIS NAME WAS SHUO.
THE FIRST EMPEROR
OF THE XIAN EMPIRE.
- REALLY? I MEAN,
I KNEW IT WAS HIM.
BUT WAIT.
I THOUGHT... I WAS TOLD
THAT SHOU FOUNDED THE EMPIRE
THROUGH BLOODSHED.
ISN'T THAT TRUE?
- TRUER THAN YOU KNOW.
HE FOUGHT TO PROTECT THIS LAND
AND ITS PEOPLE.
BE THAT AS IT MAY,
THIS IS ONLY ONE PATH.
THE QUESTION IS,
IS IT YOURS? TRULY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- TAITO.
- LAILA!
( laughing )
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
YOU HAD US ALL SO WORRIED.
- I'M SORRY.
- AH, WELL. AS LONG AS
YOU'RE IN ONE PIECE.
- Taito: KOYO.
- YES?
- WELL, I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
WHAT MY ANSWER IS JUST YET.
WHATEVER ALKAID'S
SUPPOSED TO BE,
WHATEVER IT IS
I'M SUPPOSED TO DO,
WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT ALL,
I JUST KEEP DRAWING A BLANK.
BUT I'LL BE DAMNED
IF I'M GONNA GIVE UP.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT MY PURPOSE IS,
SO I'M GONNA TAKE A SHOT
AT EVERYTHING UNTIL I FIND IT.
THAT'S CASTING MY NET
PRETTY WIDE,
BUT IT'LL GIVE ME
AN ANSWER EVENTUALLY.
THAT TOO CRAZY?
- NO. JUST CRAZY ENOUGH.
- ( laughing )
YEAH? WELL,
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M STARVING!
- CAST YOUR NET
PRETTY WIDE, HUH?
( chuckles )
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
YOU HAVE AN ANSWER.
- ( theme song playing )
- Koyo: ARE THESE THEATRICS
A MERE RUSE BY WHICH DUBHE HOPES
TO ENSNARE THE LAND?
- SEIZING CONTROL OF THIS EMPIRE
IS BUT MERELY ONE STEP
IN MY PLAN.
- WELL, WE CAN'T JUST
GO ALL CRAZY ON THESE GUYS.
- IN ORDER TO ENSURE
THIS LOVELY CATACLYSM,
ALKAID AND DUBHE MUST CLASH.
- Taito: IF PART OF MY BURDEN
AS ALKAID
MEANS I HAVE TO WIPE OUT
SCUM LIKE THIS, SO BE IT.
- Koyo: NEXT TIME ON HERO TALES,
DARKNESS ENCROACHES IN
CHAPTER SIXTEEN: "DUBHE,
DEVOURER OF THE HEAVENS."
- Keiro: ALKAID. YOUR LIGHT TOO
SHALL FALL VICTIM TO MY SHADOW!