- ( owl hooting )
- I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET.
- WE FINALLY REACH
THE CAPITAL TOMORROW, HUH?
RIGHT INTO THE LION'S DEN.
- INDEED, HENCE
TAITO'S NIGHTMARES.
THE CLOSER WE GET, THE MORE
VIVIDLY HIS BODY RECALLS
HIS FIRST CLASH WITH KEIRO.
- SO IS THIS GUY REALLY AS TOUGH
AS YOU MAKE HIM OUT TO BE?
- ENOUGH SO TO CONSIGN
OUR DREAMER TO THE GRAVE.
- REALLY?
- ( theme song playing )
- IT'S BREATHTAKING.
- THIS PLACE IS GIGANTIC.
AND FROM HERE IT'S LIKE WE'RE
STARING DOWN AT JEWELS IN
A RIVERBED OR SOMETHING.
HARD TO BELIEVE
WE'RE FINALLY HERE.
IT'S LIKE A DREAM.
- COME, I'LL SHOW YOU THE
HALLOWED WALLS THAT SHAPED ME.
TONG YO SHRINE.
WE CAN SLOUGH OFF THE DUST
OF OUR TRAVEL THERE.
I THINK WE'VE EARNED
OURSELVES A REST.
- SOUNDS GREAT. LET'S DO IT.
- ( chuckles )
WE GET TO MEET THE GIRL
RYUKO'S SWEET ON!
- GOOD. EVEN IF ENTHUSIASM
OUTSTRIPS SKILL, AT LEAST
THE BOY'S ARRIVED INTACT.
HOW SELDOM IT IS THAT TWO FIERCE
WARRIOR GODS DANCE.
UNLESS WE PREFER THEIR IMPENDING
MELEE TO RESEMBLE A DIRGE,
I'D BEST STEP UP MY EFFORTS TO
HELP THE NEOPHYTE FIND HIS FEET.
( smirks )
AND FOR THAT,
I'LL NEED THE RIGHT BATON.
- WHOA, WHAT IN THE HELL?
HOW CAN THERE BE SO
MANY PEOPLE IN ONE PLACE?
THIS IS A STREET?
OKAY, I'M CONFUSED.
HOW DO THE BUILDERS
GET IT SO WIDE?
DON'T THEY RUN OUT OF ROOM?
RIGHT? HOW!
- KINDLY LOWER YOUR VOICE.
- ( chattering )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I JUST DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THERE'S A BANQUET FIT FOR A GOD
WITHIN ARM'S REACH AND I DON'T
KNOW WHERE TO START.
I'VE DIED AND GONE TO PARADISE,
THAT'S ALL THIS PLACE CAN BE.
- TAITO! WILL YOU GET A GRIP.
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING US.
- BUT IT'S SO...
- IT'S A BIG STREET, SURE.
BUT, IT'S FOR WALKING,
NOT BAWLING.
- YOU'RE RIGHT!
LET'S GO UP AND DOWN IT RIGHT
NOW AND BUY WHATEVER
WE CAN LAY OUR HANDS ON.
- WAIT, WE DON'T...
- OH! AND WHILE WE'RE AT IT,
WE GOTTA FIND SOME
SOUVENIRS FOR DAD AND GRANDPA.
- ALAS, THE CHANCES OF
HIS GOING HOME ARE SLIM.
- WELL, WE'RE HERE.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG PICTURE NOW?
- TO BE HONEST, I AM
NOT ENTIRELY CERTAIN.
- YEAH, WELL, I KNOW WHAT'S
NUMBER ONE ON MY AGENDA,
SHIMEI'S BOSS.
I HAVE A SCORE THAT
NEEDS TO BE SETTLED WITH HIM,
FOR MY MASTER.
- WELCOME TO THE TONG YO SHRINE.
MY NAME IS RYUSHO,
THE TEMPLE'S HEAD PRIEST.
BUT I'M SURE RYUKO'S
TOLD YOU THIS.
- IT'S AN HONOR TO MEET
YOU, MASTER RYUSHO.
- THANKS FOR PUTTING US UP.
- SERIOUSLY.
- ARCHER HOSEI, DIVINE WARRIOR
PHECDA'S EARTHLY FORM.
AND TAITO, WARRIOR GOD
ALKAID'S FURY INCARNATE.
- UH, THAT'S WHAT THEY TELL ME.
- YOUR AURA IS A PURE ONE.
A CREDIT TO THE CARE MASTER
SONNEI AND SOEI TOOK
IN REARING YOU.
- UH?
- SIR, YOU KNOW MASTER
SONNEI AND OUR FATHER?
- OF COURSE HE DOES.
EXCEPTIONALLY WELL,
TRUTH BE TOLD.
- FATHER HERE WAS APPRENTICED
TO MASTER SONNEI IN
THE SAME SEASON AS SOEI.
- Taito: FATHER?
WAIT, ARE YOU TELLING US
THE HEAD PRIEST
IS YOUR OLD MAN?
- WELL, MY ADOPTIVE FATHER, YES.
I WAS A FOUNDLING, YOU SEE.
-WHOA! YOU SERIOUS?
- I'M SENSING A THEME HERE.
- YOU TOO, HUH?
NO WONDER WE GET ALONG SO WELL.
WE'RE BOTH ORPHANS,
WE GREW UP IN TEMPLES,
WE'RE TIED TO
THE FATE OF THE STARS.
IT'S LIKE YOU AND I ARE
PRACTICALLY BROTHERS
OR SOMETHING.
- WHAT AN INCREDIBLY
KIND THING TO SAY.
- BROTHERS, SURE. I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT "GETTING ALONG SO WELL"
AFTER SEEING YOU TWO BICKER.
- GEE. THANKS FOR
SPOILING THE MOOD.
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT, THOUGH,
I GUESS YOU DO HAVE A POINT.
- SUCH FRIENDS ARE
A TREASURE, SON.
- YES.
- CONSIDER THIS ROOM YOUR OWN.
- WOW! THANKS, I WILL!
- MY QUARTERS ARE
JUST ACROSS THE HALL.
WHO'S THERE?
- WELCOME BACK, RYUKO.
YOU LOOK WELL.
- THANK YOU, UH.
YOU'RE LOOKING
EXQUISITELY WELL YOURSELF.
- ( chuckles )
HERE WE GO.
- THE ONE IS REVEALED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WHO'S SHE?
- MY NAME IS RINMEI.
I'M AN ATTENDANT
HERE AT TONG YO.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
- LIKEWISE.
- SO WHERE'S THE KEEPSAKE
YOU PROMISED?
- OH, UH, I DIDN'T BRING ONE.
MY APOLOGIES.
- UGH, COULDN'T YOU HAVE SPUN
THAT INTO SOMETHING LIKE
"MY SAFE RETURN IS A KEEPSAKE?"
I SWEAR...
- THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A MOST REFINED WAY
OF FRAMING IT INDEED.
AS I'D EXPECT
COMING FROM YOU, OF COURSE.
WELL DONE.
- YOU'RE JUST AWFUL, RIGHT?
-YEP.
- NO DOUBT.
- UGH, ALRIGHT THAT DOES IT,
ENOUGH OF THIS CRAP.
OUT WITH IT.
WHAT ARE YOU ALL IN ON HERE
THAT I'M IN THE DARK ABOUT?
- HOW CLUELESS CAN YOU BE?
THIS IS THE GIRL THAT
RYUKO HAS FEELINGS FOR.
- WAIT, RYUKO'S
IN LOVE WITH HER?
- STOP! WHATEVER YOU'RE
THINKING, JUST DON'T.
I AM A MONK OF THIS TEMPLE.
MY TRAINING DOES NOT
INCLUDE TIME FOR GIRLS.
AND THAT IS THAT!
- I'M CONFUSED.
- OF COURSE.
- INTERESTING. SEEMS YOU'VE
FOUND QUITE THE KINDRED SPIRIT
IN EACH OTHER, HAVEN'T YOU?
- ( knife chopping )
- AH, THAT SCENT.
HOW MUCH I'VE MISSED
YOUR GIFTS AT THE HEARTH SIDE.
- IS THAT ALL YOU'VE MISSED?
- ( gasps )
- ( giggles )
UH!
- RINMEI, ARE YOU INJURED?
HAVE YOU...
- RINMEI?
- YES?
( heart beat )
YES, WHAT IS IT?
- THE POT'S BOILING OVER.
- ( cracking sound )
- I HAVE TO DRAW WATER.
- I'LL JUST WAIT HERE, THEN.
- HEH, HEH. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
MUSCLE MAKES A MAN, YOU KNOW.
- AH, GIMME A BREAK.
YOU WANNA SEE SOME STRENGTH.
TAKE A LOOK AT MY SHOOTING ARM.
- ( both grunting )
- UH, YEAH.
WELL, CHECK THIS OUT.
- NICE TRY.
- ALL LAUNDERED AND READY TO GO.
( gasps )
- ( wind blows )
- ( Laila screaming )
UGH, THOSE ANIMALS!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
- PLEASE, HOW BIG OF
A PRUDE COULD HE BE?
- IMBECILES MEN ARE HOPELESS!
- HEY, GREAT MINDS, YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, RIGHT ON THE SAME PAGE.
- KINDRED SPIRITS!
- ( Taito munching noisily )
- HOW DO YOU EVEN
HAVE ROOM LEFT?
YOU'RE GONNA EAT THESE POOR
PEOPLE OUT OF HOUSE AND HOME.
- SORRY. I CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
IT'S RINMEI'S COOKING.
THANK YOU!
( exhales )
WELL, GUESS I'LL BE OFF NOW.
- WAIT. OFF TO WHERE?
- WHERE DO YOU THINK, LAILA?
COME ON, DON'T START
PLAYING ALL INNOCENT ON ME.
I'M GONNA GO FIND MOUSTACHE
AND GIVE HIM HIS DUE.
JUST BECAUSE I'M COMFORTABLE AND
EATING GOOD FOOD DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I'M NOT STILL PISSED OFF
ABOUT WHAT HE DID
TO OUR VILLAGE.
- I ABSOLUTELY FORBID
YOU TO LEAVE!
- WHERE IS THIS COMING
FROM ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU CANNOT FIGHT HIM.
NOT AS YOU ARE NOW.
- LIKE HELL!
- HE WOULD CRUSH YOU
LIKE AN INSECT.
THE DISPARITY BETWEEN
KEIRO'S POWER
AND YOURS
IS NIGHT AND DAY.
- WHATEVER. YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
SO SHUT UP!
- I DO KNOW, AND BELIEVE ME,
RIGHTEOUS IRE ONLY GOES SO FAR.
IN THIS CASE,
FAR ENOUGH TO KILL YOU.
- YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE BROUGHT
ME HERE IF YOU DIDN'T
WANT ME TO FIGHT HIM.
- IT'S TOO LATE!
- EITHER WAY, COUNT ME IN.
- Ryuko: HOSEI!
- I DON'T CARE WHAT
THE ODDS ARE.
I'M IN THIS THING TO
AVENGE MY MASTER.
WE ARE DIVINE WARRIORS,
FOLLOWING THE PATH
DECREED BY THE STARS.
IF THE STARS HAVEN'T BEEN
LEADING US TO TAKE THIS GUY OUT,
WHAT HAS ALL THIS BEEN FOR?
- WHAT THIS HAS "BEEN FOR" IS TO
KEEP HE AND KEIRO FROM WREAKING
UNTOLD HAVOC ON THE REST OF US!
THAT'S OUR PATH!
- NO, RYUKO. THAT'S YOUR PATH.
I'M HERE TO KICK
LORD KEIRO'S ASS.
AND YOU'VE GOT NO RIGHT
BOSSING ME AROUND.
- IF THIS IS AS FAR AS YOU WANNA
GO, THEN STAY OUT OF OUR WAY.
- YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
PLEASE, I...
- HM, TALK DOES NOTHING TO DOUSE
A FOOL'S PASSION, RYUKO.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT.
I THINK IT'S TIME WE LET OUR
BODIES DO THE ARGUING.
- UH, RINMEI?
- UM, AND BY BODIES, YOU MEAN?
- THAT ACTIONS SPEAK
LOUDER THAN WORDS.
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS. WHAT THE
HECK DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
GONNA PROVE TO ME OUT HERE?
- DON'T WORRY.
THE NIGHT AIR IS BAD FOR
MY COMPLEXION, SO I'LL BE BRIEF.
- 'KAY. FINE.
- BEHOLD THE LIN SHAN HUA.
IN BATTLE, WE BECOME ONE.
- WAIT, SHE'S GOT A STAR SIGIL?
WHAT THE...
- YES. RINMEI'S STAR
IS A BRILLIANT ONE.
DIVINE WARRIOR MERAK.
- BUT I'M ONLY A GIRL,
AFTER ALL. HAVE MERCY, ALKAID.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH
I POSE A THREAT.
LET'S BEGIN!
- ( gasps )
- OH, MAN.
- HER STYLE IS MOST FORMIDABLE.
UNFAILING BALANCE
ITS CORNERSTONE.
- NO WAY I'M GONNA
LET A GIRL BEAT ME.
( grunts )
WHERE'D SHE GO?
- QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
YOU'D BE HELL IN A LONG FIGHT.
- ( grunting )
( screaming )
- ( gasping )
- YOU'RE A HANDFUL,
I'LL GIVE YA THAT.
BUT STILL, ONLY A CHILD.
YOU SLUMP AT MY FEET,
AND YET WHAT I'VE
DEMONSTRATED
PALES IN COMPARISON
TO KEIRO'S MIGHT.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND NOW?
- TAITO, YOU HAVE TIME.
THE MOUNTAIN WILL WAIT
TO BE CONQUERED.
AND THERE ARE MANY WAYS
TO REACH THE SUMMIT.
IF THE HEAVENS DEEM YOUR CAUSE
WORTHY, A PATH WILL UNFURL
BEFORE YOU OF ITS OWN ACCORD.
LET US HOLD A VIGIL FOR ONE.
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ERRING ON
THE SIDE OF PATIENCE, HUH?
- LOOKS LIKE IT.
TA-DA! IT'S OFFICIAL NOW.
WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
THE MEN ARE HOPELESS LEAGUE
HAS A FLAG!
- OH, LAILA, YOU'RE AN ARTIST.
IT SIMPLY EXUDES
"WHAT WOULD THEY DO WITHOUT US?"
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
- KINDRED SPIRITS!
- HEY LAILA, DO YOU KNOW...
( gasps )
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT EXACTLY IS MY
UNDYING DEVOTION TO YOU
COMPETING WITH HERE?
- NO, NO. IT'S NOTHING. WE...
SO, YOU, UH...
- OH YEAH. I CAN'T FIND
PRETTY BOY OR TAITO.
I'VE LOOKED.
- THEY WENT OFF TOGETHER
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- REALLY? THEY'RE CHUMMY?
WHAT'S ALL THAT ABOUT?
HOLD ON!
YOU DON'T THINK THOSE TWO
ARE MORE THAN FRIENDS, DO YOU?
- NO! WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- WOW. THIS PLACE IS
REALLY SOMETHING ELSE.
MAKES ALL THE OTHER TOWNS
WE'VE SEEN LOOK KINDA CRAPPY.
- IT SHARES MORE IN COMMON
WITH THEM THAN YOU THINK.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN? LIKE HOW?
- ( people chattering )
- SO, RYUKO,
YOU'RE TAKING ME TO SOME
KIND OF COURTYARD?
- SHUNYI SQUARE.
KNOWN COMMONLY AS
KEIRO'S TRIUMPH.
- HIS TRIUMPH?
HOW THE HELL DID HE MAKE
A PIT LIKE THIS BY HIMSELF?
- YES, WELL, FOUR YEARS AGO
A MARTIAL ARTS TOURNAMENT
WAS HELD HERE FOR THE EMPEROR.
KEIRO WON
BY MAKING THIS CRATER.
BARE FISTED, WITH HIS LEFT HAND.
- BARE FISTED?
YOU THINKING WHAT I AM?
- HE'S MASTERED WHAT WE'VE ONLY
BEGUN TO UNDERSTAND,
THE INNER RESERVOIR.
- SO THAT'S HIS SECRET.
- TAITO, YOU HAVE ONLY TO
MASTER YOURSELF, YES?
ONE DAY YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
CARVE OUT A HOLE JUST AS BIG.
LET ME HELP YOU TRAIN,
SO WE CAN BRING THAT DAY
A BIT CLOSER.
I'D RATHER NOT SEE
ANOTHER FRIEND LOST.
- IT'S A DEAL.
- COME ALONG. THERE'S MORE.
- RYUKO, SERIOUSLY.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
SO, WHAT, YOU'RE JUST
GONNA IGNORE ME?
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU DRAGGED US?
AM I SEEING THIS?
THE THOROUGHFARE'S
RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER.
I MEAN, THEY'RE SO CLOSE
TO ALL THAT WEALTH.
- RICH THOUGH THE CITY MAY SEEM,
IT DOES HAVE A SHADOW.
AND IN THAT PALL
ITS TRUE FACE.
- TRUE FACE?
- THE EMPIRE HAS CRUMBLED
TO BUT A HUSK OF
ITS FORMER GRANDEUR.
THOSE JEWELS IN THE RIVERBED
WERE NOTHING BUT REFUSE.
- BUT, THIS IS THE CAPITAL.
THE EMPEROR'S JUST
A STONE'S THROW AWAY.
THESE PEOPLE ARE PRACTICALLY
SUFFERING ON HIS DOORSTEP.
- EXACTLY.
- THEN THEY OUGHTA
STORM THE PALACE,
PEEL HIS MAJESTY OFF THE THRONE,
AND GIVE SOMEONE ELSE
A CHANCE TO RULE.
- IN THAT SENTIMENT,
YOU AND KEIRO ARE ONE.
- LIKE HE GIVES A DAMN
ABOUT THE PEOPLE.
I'D BE A BETTER CHOICE
THAN HIM, ANY DAY.
HOLD ON.
WHERE ARE WE NOW?
- THE KILLING GROUNDS.
I HOPE TO CAUSE LESS
COLLATERAL DAMAGE HERE.
SHOW YOURSELF, COWARD!
- BRAVO, MIZAR!
HOW THRILLING TO BE LURED
WHEN ONE THOUGHT
HIMSELF LURKING!
- BASTARD!
- SO IT WAS YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED THIS.
- THAT'S IT.
YOU'VE SHOWN THAT UGLY FACE
TO ME FOR THE LAST TIME.
THIS ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
CHEAP TRICKS YOU LIKE TO
PULL OUT OF YOUR ASS?
- MY, MY. HOW THAT FOUL
MOUTH BETRAYS YOU FOR
A FEARSOME BEAST.
I'D BETTER MIND MY STEP
WHEN YOU'RE ABOUT,
BUT RATHER THAN TUSSLE,
I'D PREFER WE AVAIL OURSELVES
OF CIVILIZED DISCOURSE.
DO YOU REMEMBER THIS LITTLE TOY?
- THAT'S THE SWORD YOUR
BUTCHER OF A MASTER BURNED
HALF MY VILLAGE DOWN TO STEAL.
- XIAN JIA LAN WU, ALPHA AND
OMEGA OF MANY A DYNASTY.
KNOWN MORE COMMONLY
AS THE SWORD OF RULE,
FOR ONLY AN EMPEROR'S
HAND MAY DRAW IT
LORD KEIRO WRENCHED
IT FROM OBSCURITY
MUCH AS HE HOPED TO WRENCH THE
VERY BLADE FROM ITS SCABBARD.
OH, HOW THE PEOPLE OF THIS
LAND WOULD HAVE TREMBLED.
ALAS, HE COULDN'T SO MUCH
AS MAKE THE BLADE TREMBLE.
- SO WHAT?
- COME, DON'T BE DENSE.
HEH, NOT EVEN THE CURRENT
EMPEROR IS FAVORED BY FATE.
BUT SOMEONE IS.
HE WHOM THE SWORD
WOULD SEE RULE IS ALKAID.
THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO DISCUSS.
SOMETHING TELLS ME YOU'RE
THE KIND OF BLEEDING HEART
WHO'D SET THE WORLD TO RIGHTS
GIVEN HALF A CHANCE.
DO I ASSUME CORRECTLY?
IF SO, THEN WHAT BETTER MEANS
TO ACCOMPLISH IT THAN A THRONE?
- WHAT?
- YOU AND YOU ALONE DREW
THE SWORD OF RULE.
FATE HAS MADE ITS CHOICE.
THE HELM OF THIS
BROKEN LAND IS YOURS.
RISE TO THE OCCASION, BOY.
TAKE THE SWORD.
- SHUT UP!
I'M MY OWN MASTER,
NOT SOME OLD RELIC.
AND NOT SOME CREEP LIKE YOU!
- ( explosion )
- YOU DISAPPOINT ME.
OH, WELL!
I'VE NO USE FOR
A PETULANT CHILD.
- ( gasping )
- THIS MAY SEEM A BIT COLD,
BUT IF YOU CAN'T
KEEP ME ENTERTAINED,
WHAT REASON HAVE
I TO LET YOU LIVE?
( laughing )
( groaning )
- USE YOUR INNER RESERVOIR,
JUST AS LADY KOEI
SHOWED YOU. QUICKLY!
- ( yelling )
- TAITO!
- WELL IT WOULD SEEM THAT
THE BOY HAS FORCED ME
TO EAT MY OWN WORDS.
QUITE THE LARK.
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN, ALKAID.
- WHO WOULD HAVE DARED TO
STEAL THE SWORD OF RULE?
- WHAT COULD SUCH BOLDNESS
IN ITS THIEF PORTEND?
- IT IS MEANINGLESS.
THIS IS LIKELY SHIMEI'S DOING.
- SHIMEI?
- FORGIVE MY IMPUDENCE,
BUT I MUST QUESTION THE WISDOM
OF ALLOWING SUCH A CURIOUS
BEING TO DO AS HE PLEASES.
- NO MATTER.
FOR THE MOMENT, AT LEAST.
- THAT HE COULD INVOKE
SUCH A PLACE FROM SKY
AND THOUGHT ALONE.
THE ENEMY IS KEEN
TO OUR PURPOSES NOW.
THIS IS GOING TO BE DIFFICULT.
( sighs ) WELL, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT AT LEAST, TAITO?
TAITO?
- ME, AN EMPEROR.
- SO SIX OF THE SEVEN
ARE GATHERED TOGETHER.
WELL, CAPTAIN,
THE CAPITAL WAITS FOR YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: WHETHER IMPRUDENCE OR
DESTINY BROUGHT THEM TOGETHER,
NONE CAN SAY.
- Taito: WE CAN'T LET THAT
MONSTER BREAK FREE!
- Ryuko: CALM YOURSELF, TAITO.
- Hosei: THE IDIOT'S
ACTUALLY GONNA DO IT.
- Taito: SO WHAT'S ALL
THIS FOR THEN?
WHAT'S THE EMPEROR ACTUALLY DO?
- Taiga: HE PRAYS FOR
CONTINUED PEACE AND
THE PROSPERITY OF HIS SUBJECTS.
- Taito: THE WAY I SEE IT,
UNLESS THE POOREST
PERSON CAN SMILE
JUST AS OFTEN AS THE RICHEST,
THE COUNTRY'S JUST NO GOOD.
- Ryuko: NEXT, ON HERO TALES,
TAITO'S RIGHTEOUS FIRE
THAWS AN ICY HEART
IN CHAPTER TEN,
"THE LONELY EMPEROR."
- Taito: IF HIS ROYAL HIGHNESS
GAVE A DAMN, THINGS WOULD
HAVE NEVER GOTTEN THIS BAD.