ALL FOUR OF US? YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE FIGHT TOGETHER, WE CAN
TOTALLY TAKE THAT BASTARD DOWN.
- MUST WE FIGHT TO TRIUMPH?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( Man grunting with effort )
- WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
- HEY, THERE. UP WITH THE DAWN?
- AS USUAL. APPARENTLY,
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
YOU CATCH ME OFF GUARD.
- YEAH, WELL, I WOKE UP EARLY.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- AH, RYUKO.
A VERY GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
- WELL, WELL,
DISCIPLINE IS CATCHING.
- SO IS NOT BEING ABLE TO
GET A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
- HEY! ENOUGH WITH THAT!
I SAID I WAS SORRY!
- DON'T STAND THERE AND ACT LIKE
YOU DIDN'T INTEND TO WAKE US UP.
YOU PRACTICALLY APOLOGIZED
AND CALLED US LAZY
IN THE SAME BREATH.
- YEAH, BUT WE'RE FORGETTING
HE'S AN IDIOT.
HE PROBABLY MEANT
THE OPPOSITE OF SORRY.
- STOP CALLING ME AN IDIOT!
BESIDES, TALK ABOUT NOT GETTING
A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP,
IT WAS YOUR SNORING
THAT WOKE ME UP.
- JERK-WAD! WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU TO SIT IN JUDGMENT
ON ANOTHER
MAN'S SINUSES?
MY SNORING
IS NOT THAT DAMN LOUD.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE POOR LAILA ALL
NERVOUS ABOUT OUR WEDDING NIGHT.
- ARE YOU STILL ASLEEP?
'CAUSE YOU MUST BE DREAMING
IF YOU THINK I'D
EVER LET HER MARRY YOU!
- AND YOU'RE DREAMING
IF YOU THINK I CARE!
SINCE WHEN IS MY BROTHER
THE ONE MARRYING ME OFF?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
- I BELIEVE THE LADY HAS SPOKEN.
AND IF WE WANT TO CONSECRATE
OUR UNION ONE DAY
BY MAKING LOTS OF BABIES,
IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- THERE IS NO "WE"
IN THAT PICTURE, HOSEI.
STOP BEING GROSS!
- WHERE'S HE GOING?
- AH, RYUKO, I THOUGHT
I'D FIND YOU HERE.
- YES, FATHER?
- ARE YOU TROUBLED?
- TROUBLED?
- I ASK BECAUSE SUCH
IS GENERALLY THE CASE
WHEN YOU SULK ABOUT
NURSING THAT DAGGER.
SUCH ARE THE TIMES
IN WHICH WE LIVE.
DUBHE AND ALKAID NEVER APPEAR
TOGETHER UPON THE WORLD STAGE.
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
- BECAUSE, AS GREAT WARRIOR GODS
OF OLD,
A HATEFUL BATTLE ENSCONCED
SAFELY WITHIN THE TILT
OF THEIR
RESPECTIVE STARS
WOULD PROVE ABSOLUTELY
DEVASTATING IF BROUGHT DOWN
TO THE EARTHLY SPHERE.
- AND YET, COME DOWN IT HAS.
THEY WILL LOCK HORNS,
IT'S ALMOST A CERTAINTY.
AND WHEN THEY DO,
IT WILL BE DEVASTATING INDEED.
YOU ARE ONE OF FIVE DIVINE
WARRIORS, A VITAL PART OF THIS.
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
- WHAT WILL I DO?
I'LL PREVENT THEIR COLLISION.
BY ANY AND ALL MEANS.
THAT IS MY DUTY.
KEIRO MUST BE SUBDUED.
- SO YOU SAY, AND YET,
WHY KEIRO?
THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
- THE ALKAID MAY BE SUBDUED
TO MUCH THE SAME EFFECT.
- ( gasps )
SO, YOU WISH FOR ME
TO STRIKE DOWN A FRIEND?
- WELL, OF COURSE
I DON'T WISH FOR IT.
BUT FATE CAN BE CRUEL,
YOU SHOULD UNDERSTAND
THAT BY NOW.
I SIMPLY WANT YOU TO BE
PREPARED FOR CHOICES
YOU MAY BE FORCED TO MAKE.
I'M SORRY.
IT WASN'T MY INTENTION
TO HEAP FURTHER WOE ON YOU
BY BRINGING THIS UP.
- TAITO. COULD I DO IT?
- ( thump )
- ( staff flying
through the air )
- THAT NEVER HAPPENS.
YOU FEELING CRUDDY OR SOMETHING?
- I'M FINE. YOU'VE IMPROVED
A GREAT DEAL IS ALL.
- UH, IT'S NICE TO HEAR YOU SAY
THAT, BUT IT'S ALSO KINDA WEIRD.
IF I'M IMPROVING THAT MUCH,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE I CAN BRING MOUSTACHE
DOWN TO HIS KNEES!
CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT DAY
TO COME, LET ME TELL YA!
I'M JUST KIDDING,
THAT SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
THE OLD TAITO
WOULD HAVE SAID.
I'M NOT THE HOTHEAD
I USED TO BE.
I GET IT NOW.
I'VE STILL GOT A LONG WAY TO GO.
KEIRO'S A HELL OF A LOT STRONGER
THAN ME.
IT'D BE POINTLESS
NOT TO ACCEPT THAT FACT.
- TAITO.
- AT FIRST ALL I WANTED
WAS REVENGE.
BUT THEN LOSING TO RINMEI
TAUGHT ME A VALUABLE LESSON
IN KNOWING MY LIMITS.
SHE WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
THAT MADE ME FACE REALITY.
I HAD HELP ALL ALONG.
ACTUALLY, THE PERSON
WHO'S HELPED ME THE MOST IS YOU.
- MY FRIEND, YOU'VE GROWN
CONSIDERABLY STRONGER AND WISER,
IT IS A PRIVILEGE TO BEHOLD.
- AW, COME ON. STOP THAT!
HEH, I MEAN THE PRAISE IS COOL.
I'M JUST NEVER GONNA
GET USED TO IT.
- YOUR GROWTH IS
A DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD.
ONE THAT MAY CUT DEEPLY.
- ( birds chirping )
- WHERE THE HELL IS THAT BOY?
THERE'S NO TRACE OF ANY OF THEM.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF THEY'VE
COMPLETELY VANISHED
FROM THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
BUT BY WHAT MEANS?
SOME ARCHAIC CHARM, NO DOUBT.
- Choka: WHEREFORE DO YOU
SLITHER, SHIMEI?
- AH, WELL, NO REST
FOR THE WICKED, YOU KNOW.
- NOR FOR PILFERERS OF IMPERIAL
RELICS, SO IT WOULD SEEM.
- WHY, MADAM,
WHATEVER DO YOU MEAN?
- WHY DID YOU TAKE THE SWORD?
THINK CAREFULLY
BEFORE YOU ANSWER.
- NOW, NOW! TRUTH CAN BE
PURCHASED WITHOUT BLOOD.
I'M AN UNFURLED SCROLL.
SUCH IMPLEMENTS ARE BEST
LEFT TUCKED AWAY IN THE FOLDS
OF YOUR EXQUISITE ROBES.
- TAKE HEED.
KEIRO WILL NOT BE MADE A FOOL.
YOU AMUSE HIM, BUT THAT IS
THE EXTENT OF YOUR APPEAL.
DON'T THINK TO OVERREACH.
AND, SHIMEI? RIFLE THROUGH
HIS PERSONAL EFFECTS AGAIN
AND YOU'LL ANSWER TO ME.
- OF COURSE.
I'D EXPECT NOTHING LESS.
- GOOD.
- SUCH VITRIOL, POOR THING.
WHEN HER MAN'S GONE AWAY,
SHE DOES TEND TO GET
A BIT OVERSENSITIVE.
- ( birds chirping )
- HEY. LAILA, DID I TELL YOU
THE MOON MARKET IS TODAY?
- WHAT'S THE MOON MARKET?
- YOU GUYS SAW THE RIVER
THAT FLANKS THE CITY'S
EASTERN QUARTER, RIGHT?
WELL, ONCE EVERY MONTH,
THIS FLEET OF CARGO SHIPS
COMES TO PORT THERE.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
TRUST ME, THE MARKETPLACE
THEY SET UP IS ONE OF A KIND.
- REALLY?
- YES. "EXOTIC" DOESN'T
EVEN BEGIN TO DESCRIBE
WHAT A SHREWD
BUYER CAN FIND THERE.
- OH, WOW!
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SHALL WE GO AND HAVE A PEEK?
- LET'S DO IT!
- HEY, IF THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
IS GOING, COUNT ME IN!
- SURE, WHATEVER.
TAI, DO YOU WANNA COME, TOO?
- UM, NOT REALLY MY THING.
YOU GUYS GO WITHOUT ME.
I'LL STAY HERE
AND KEEP TRAINING.
- OH, DID I NOT MENTION
THE GREAT FOOD?
THEY'VE GOT PRODUCE
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
HOSEI? GET OFF YOUR RUMP!
WE DON'T HAVE ALL DAY!
- SO NOW YOU'RE COMING?
I SWEAR YOU'RE JUST LIKE A GIRL.
WAY TO CHANGE YOUR MIND.
- I ASSUME
YOU'LL BE JOINING US, RYUKO?
RYUKO? HELLO, RYUKO.
OF COURSE.
YOU WEREN'T LISTENING, HUH?
- NO. SORRY.
- WE'RE ALL GOING
TO THE MOON MARKET.
DO YOU WANNA COME
ALONG WITH US OR NOT?
- COME ON. YOU NEED A BREATHER
JUST AS MUCH AS THE REST OF US.
- THANK YOU, BUT IF YOU
DON'T MIND, I BELIEVE I'LL PASS.
- OKAY. WELL, THEN, I GUESS IT'S
JUST GONNA BE THE FOUR OF US.
- SEEMS LIKE IT.
- NOW, IF YOU WILL EXCUSE ME...
- IS IT JUST ME,
OR DOES THAT GUY NOT SEEM
MUCH LIKE HIMSELF LATELY?
- RYUKO, ARE YOU GOING OUT?
- I AM. I SHOULD BE BACK
AFTER NIGHTFALL.
- YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE ACTING RATHER STRANGELY.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT,
I'M ALL EARS.
- I'M SORRY.
- WHY DO YOU
KEEP APOLOGIZING? IDIOT.
- PLEASE FORGIVE
THE SPARSE ACCOMMODATIONS.
I RARELY ENTERTAIN.
- NO, NO. IT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
I REALLY OUGHT NOT TO
HAVE BARGED IN ON YOU
UNANNOUNCED LIKE THIS.
- I HAD A FEELING YOU'D PAY ME
A VISIT BEFORE TOO LONG.
YOU'RE CARRYING SOMETHING
A BIT DANGEROUS, AREN'T YOU?
- SORRY TO BRING
SUCH A THING HERE.
I DON'T USUALLY CARRY IT
ON MY PERSON.
- HMM.
A RATHER SPLENDID
PIECE, ACTUALLY.
- FATHER WAS A WANDERER.
IN HIS YOUTH HE TRAVERSED
MANY FAR AWAY LANDS.
YOU SEE, THAT'S HOW... WELL,
THAT'S HOW HE FOUND ME.
FROM WHAT I'VE GATHERED,
THIS DAGGER WAS ALL THAT I HAD.
WHERE IT COMES FROM
OR WHY I POSSESS IT,
ARE A MYSTERY.
- SO IT WOULD SEEM.
NOW THEN, WHAT DID YOU WISH
TO DISCUSS, RYUKO?
- THIS MAY SOUND STRANGE
COMING FROM ME,
BUT DO YOU BELIEVE IN FATE?
- IN FATE?
- IF WE'RE GIVEN ROLES TO PLAY,
IF THE STARS TRULY DECREE
HOW WE ARE TO CONDUCT OURSELVES.
IF IT'S REALLY
SO STRAIGHTFORWARD,
WOULDN'T OUR PATHS
BE SELF-EVIDENT?
- INDEED THEY ARE, IF WE HAD
THE WHEREWITHAL TO SEE IT.
UNFORTUNATELY, MOST OF US
WOULD DENY FATE, TRAGICALLY.
IF, FOR EXAMPLE,
OUR PATH DECREES WE ARE
TO TAKE A FRIEND'S LIFE...
- THEN WHAT? WE COMMIT MURDER?
ARE YOU SUGGESTING SUCH AN ACT
WOULD BE JUSTIFIED?
- IT WAS ONLY AN EXAMPLE.
I UNDERSTAND. IT'S A FAIRLY EASY
THING TO PUZZLE OUT
WHAT'S BEEN TROUBLING YOU.
DUTY AND SENTIMENT
APPEAR TO BE AT ODDS.
- WHAT?
- YOU WOULD SALVAGE THE EMPIRE
BUT THE SACRIFICE
IT MAY WELL REQUIRE YOU TO MAKE
IS NOT ONE YOU'RE PREPARED
TO ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY FOR.
- BUT YOU...
HOW COULD YOU KNOW?
- I KNOW YOU. YOU CHERISH
THIS LAND PROFOUNDLY.
YOU'VE SAID AS MUCH.
- THERE'S NO DENYING IT.
AND MY JOURNEY THESE PAST FEW
MONTHS HAS ONLY STRENGTHENED
MY RESOLVE TO CHANGE THINGS.
BUT ALSO, THE BONDS I FORGED
ALONG THE WAY ARE STRONG.
AND NOW IT SEEMS THE VERY PATH
THAT LED ME TO FORGE THOSE BONDS
DEMANDS I BREAK THEM, VIOLENTLY.
- THE XIAN EMPIRE AFFECTS THE
OUTWARD APPEARANCE OF HEALTH,
BUT ONLY BY WAY OF A VEIL
THAT HIDES THE MALADY
ROTTING AWAY ITS CORE.
THE PROGNOSIS FROM ANY PHYSICIAN
WORTH HIS SALT WOULD BE DEATH.
- THE LAND WILL DIE?
- I CAN SAVE A LIFE,
INDEED HAVE DONE.
IT'S SIMPLE ENOUGH WHEN
ONE HAS THE PROPER MEANS.
HOWEVER, SAVING AN EMPIRE IS A
WHOLE OTHER ORDER OF MAGNITUDE.
ONLY SOMEONE CHOSEN BY THE STARS
CAN RISE TO MEET
A CHALLENGE LIKE THAT.
- SO, THEN, MY FATE...
- SPEAKING AS A DOCTOR,
I WOULD TRUST THE EMPIRE'S
HEALTH TO NO ONE ELSE.
PRECISELY BECAUSE THE PATH
BEFORE THEM IS FRAUGHT
WITH SUCH DIFFICULTIES.
- AH, WHAT LUCK!
I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
THE BROODING MIZAR
RIGHT AT MY FINGERTIPS.
- THE HEALTH OF THE EMPIRE.
- OH, MY, THINGS ARE GOING
TO GET INTERESTING NOW,
AREN'T THEY?
( chuckles )
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS IT ME?
- OH, YEAH!
IT'S TOTALLY AND COMPLETELY YOU!
I'M JEALOUS!
- WELL, DON'T KEEP ME
IN SUSPENSE. WHAT'D YOU GET?
- FEAST YOUR EYES ON THIS!
IT'S A MAGIC POWDER.
ALL I DO IS SPRINKLE SOME ON
THE SOIL AND VEGETABLES GROW
TO TWICE THEIR NORMAL SIZE!
( giggling )
- GOOD FOR YOU!
YOU ARE A SHREWD ONE!
- HOW THEY GET SO EXCITED ABOUT
SHOPPING I'LL NEVER KNOW.
MUST BE A GIRL THING.
WHO THE HELL COULD SAY?
COULD THESE THINGS
BE ANY HARDER TO EAT?
- YOU DON'T LIKE 'EM?
THE GUY SAID THEY WERE BANANAS.
THEY COME FROM SOME DEEP, DARK,
JUNGLE COUNTRY IN THE SOUTH.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE COOL
TO TRY 'EM OUT.
I MEAN, SURE,
THEY'RE A LITTLE TOUGH
ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT THEY'RE TASTY ON THE INSIDE!
- AH, LOOK
WHAT THE CAT DRAGGED IN.
- HEY, RYUKO! YOU WANNA TRY
ONE OF THESE BANANAS?
WE BOUGHT SOME AT THE MOON
MARKET THIS AFTERNOON, A...
- WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH HIM?
- EH.
- MOST OF US WOULD DENY FATE.
WE DON'T HAVE THE WHEREWITHAL
TO SEE WHAT MUST BE DONE.
- ALKAID MAY BE SUBDUED
TO MUCH THE SAME EFFECT.
- PERHAPS IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT YOU LOOK
SOMEWHAT DISTRESSED.
- YOU VERMIN!
- EAGER AS YOU MAY BE, I DIDN'T
COME HERE FOR AN ALTERCATION.
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
( grunts )
WHAT?
- JUST CALM DOWN.
BELIEVE ME, YOU'LL REGRET NOT
HEARING OUT WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
SEE, MY FRIEND, I'M A VERITABLE
FOUNT OF KNOWLEDGE,
KNOWLEDGE THAT CONCERNS YOU.
- ANOTHER SCHEME? WHAT NOW?
- WHY MUST YOU BE SO COLD?
SO, LAD, I HEAR
YOU WERE A FOUNDLING.
- IS THAT SO?
AND WHERE HAVE YOU HEARD THAT?
- I MAKE IT A POINT TO
KEEP MY EAR TO THE GROUND.
FOR EXAMPLE, I HEAR...
WELL, I KNOW WHO
YOUR REAL FATHER HAPPENS TO BE.
- WHAT?
- SURELY YOU'RE CURIOUS.
HOW COULD YOU NOT BE?
- YOU'RE A LIAR! I REFUSE
TO LISTEN TO THIS NONSENSE!
- THAT MYSTERIOUS DAGGER YOU'VE
GOT STOWED AWAY IN YOUR POCKET,
YOU'VE CLUNG TO IT
ALL YOUR LIFE,
BUT DID YOU KNOW THAT
THERE'S QUITE A BIT MORE
TO IT THAN MEETS THE EYE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU SEE, IT'S THE SORT OF
BLADE A PARENT GIVES A CHILD
FOR THEIR PROTECTION.
IF MEMORY SERVES, IT WAS THE
ONLY THING IN YOUR POSSESSION
THE DAY YOU WERE FOUND.
UNSHEATHE IT.
NOW THEN, HERE'S THE FUN PART.
HOLD IT OUT, GO ON.
LET THE LIGHT HIT IT JUST SO.
- ( gasps )
KE... KEIRO!
- AND THERE YOU HAVE IT, MY BOY.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- DON'T FRET, YOU COME FROM
GOOD STOCK. QUITE GOOD.
THE ONLY SON OF MY LORD, KEIRO.
- THIS CAN'T BE!
- ( Taito laughing )
- Laila: I SWEAR I'M GONNA
THROW YOU OUT A WINDOW!
- IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
I WON'T BELIEVE THIS!
- DENIAL IS YOUR PREROGATIVE,
ALTHOUGH THE FACT STILL REMAINS.
BUT BELIEVE AS YOU WILL,
WHY LET SOMETHING LIKE
TRUTH GET IN THE WAY?
( chuckles )
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE GOT COMPANY.
WELL, THEN, IT'S BEST
I GET OUT OF YOUR HAIR
SO YOU CAN ATTEND TO THEM.
GOOD SPEAKING WITH YOU.
- ( clanging )
- THE TEMPLE IS BEING LAID SIEGE
TO BY THE XUAN LONG PLATOON.
CURRENTLY WE'RE SURROUNDED.
FOR WHATEVER REASON,
THEY'RE CLAMORING FOR TAITO.
- OH, THEY ARE, HUH?
- WHERE ARE YOU RUNNING OFF TO?
- IT'S ME THE BASTARDS WANT.
I'M NOT GONNA LET
THE TEMPLE GET INVOLVED.
- DON'T START.
LET MASTER RYUSHO
FINISH WHAT HE HAS TO SAY.
- Ryusho: THIS GOES FOR TAITO
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
THERE ARE NO COWARDS HERE,
THE TONG YOU TEMPLE
WILL GIVE AS GOOD AS WE GET.
THEY CAN DEMAND ALL THEY LIKE,
BUT WE ARE NOT SIMPLY HANDING
OVER ONE OF OUR OWN.
THAT WOULD BE AN INSULT,
AN AFFRONT TO THE LIU JIA SECT!
EVEN IF THE EMPEROR HIMSELF
HAS ORDERED THIS TRAVESTY,
SO LONG AS THE TEMPLE STANDS,
TAITO WILL NOT BE DELIVERED
TO THESE THUGS!
- MASTER RYUSHO.
- GIVEN THAT THEY'VE ENCIRCLED
US, BUT NOTHING ELSE AS YET,
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
IT MEANS
THEY'VE NO LEGAL PRETEXT.
ENGAGING US WOULD BRING THEM
NOTHING BUT DISGRACE.
BUT STAY VIGILANT!
IF THESE MOUNTEBANKS ATTEMPT
TO BEND THE LETTER OF THE LAW,
MAKE DAMN SURE WE ACQUAINT
THEM WITH THE STRINGENT ESSENCE
OF THE EIGHT STYLES!
- All: SIR!
- THAT SAID, MUCH AS WE'VE
ENJOYED THE COMPANY OF YOU KIDS,
I THINK THE HOUR HAS COME
FOR YOU TO LEAVE.
- ( all gasp )
- HM.
- OPEN UP! THAT'S AN ORDER!
- ( scoffs )
THOSE IDIOT MONKS.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY
GOING TO RESIST?
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
MUCH FUN FOR YOU, DOES IT?
- SHIMEI, TARRY
ELSEWHERE, FILTH.
YOU'VE NO BUSINESS
WHATSOEVER HERE.
- ALWAYS SO STANDOFFISH.
I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
THE MONKS BEING UNCOOPERATIVE.
SO I'VE COME ALONG TO GIVE YOU
SOME USEFUL INFORMATION.
- AND JUST WHAT EXACTLY
IS THAT, PRAY TELL?
- ( chuckling maliciously )
- ( quick footsteps )
- HURRY IT UP!
IT'S NOT MUCH FARTHER!
ONCE WE'RE THROUGH HERE,
IT'S STRAIGHT OUT OF THE CITY!
- DO YOU THINK MASTER
RYUSHO AND THE OTHERS
WILL BE ALL RIGHT?
- I HOPE SO.
- DAMN IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M RUNNING AWAY
WITH MY TAIL BETWEEN MY LEGS
WITHOUT GETTING A SHOT
AT MOUSTACHE!
- I'M ACTUALLY KINDA HAVING
A HARD TIME BELIEVING
YOU WENT ALONG
WITH THIS WHOLE ESCAPE THING.
I FIGURED WE WERE GONNA HAVE TO
KNOCK YOU UNCONSCIOUS
OR SOMETHING.
EITHER THAT
OR LURE YOU WITH BANANAS.
- HEY, I'M NOT A TOTAL JERK.
MASTER RYUSHO DID ME A KINDNESS.
IF I'D REFUSED, I MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE SPAT IN THE GUY'S FACE!
- TAITO, REMEMBER
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SAY.
IN THE END IT WAS ALKAID
THE DIPPER BEARERS SAW FIT
TO RALLY ROUND.
DUBHE, KEIRO'S STAR,
DESPITE HIS GREAT STRENGTH, IT
WAS YOU THE OTHERS BEFRIENDED.
IN THE DAYS TO COME,
TAKE COMFORT IN THAT.
- YES, SIR.
- BUT THERE ARE MORE.
FIND THEM AND THE PATH
WILL OPEN OUT TO YOU.
AND RYUKO, TRUST IN HIM
AS YOU WOULD YOUR OWN ARM.
THAT'S ALL. GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
REMEMBER WHAT'S PASSED
BETWEEN US.
- TRUST RYUKO
AS I WOULD MY ARM, OKAY.
- I CAN SEE THE EXIT UP AHEAD.
- WE'RE FINALLY OUT OF THERE.
- HOPEFULLY OUR TRAIL
HAS GONE COLD.
- ALAS, NOT SO COLD
AS YOU MIGHT THINK.
- WAIT A SECOND,
YOU'RE THAT HAG!
- SURELY YOU DIDN'T COME
ALL THIS WAY TO TRADE INSULTS,
DID YOU, BOY?
- TELL ME! HOW DID YOU KNOW
WE'D BE HERE?
- I HAVE WAYS. EVEN A THORN
IN MY SIDE CAN BE USEFUL.
IN THIS CASE, IT ALLOWS ME TO
DEAL WITH ALL OF YOU VERMIN
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
YOU WANT A FIGHT, YOU GOT ONE!
- DAMN RIGHT!
( grunting )
WHO THE HELL ARE THESE GIRLS?
- ( Laila screams )
- I'VE GOT THIS ONE, LAILA.
GET BACK!
- OKAY.
- ( grunting )
- COME ON! LOOK ALIVE!
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT!
- SCREW YOU! HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY?
THEY'RE CHICKS!
- OH, SO NOW
YOU'RE A CHAUVINIST?
THIS IS HOW!
OH, YEAH!
CRAP.
- I COULD REALLY USE
A LITTLE HELP HERE!
LET HIM GO, NOW!
ALL RIGHT, THAT DOES IT!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
( grunts )
- RYUKO, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I AM NOW. THANK YOU, RINMEI.
- Laila: YOU FORCE ME
TO DO THIS!
- WHOA! GOOD CALL, SIS!
YOU JUST SAVED OUR BUTTS!
- YOU SURE GOT
YOUR MONEY'S WORTH!
- EVERYONE! LET'S GET OUT
OF HERE WHILE WE CAN!
- ( coughs )
DAMN YOU ALL!
- ( panting )
- STAY WITH ME, GUYS.
ONCE WE'VE MADE IT TO THE RIVER,
I'M PRETTY SURE
WE'LL BE OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- HURRY IT UP, RYUKO!
YOU'RE FALLING BEHIND!
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- I'M FINE. JUST KEEP GOING.
- ( both gasp )
- KEIRO.
- THE STARS...
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT.
- ALKAID, WELL MET.
DO YOU SEE NOW, BOY?
FATE WILL HAVE US COLLIDE!
- YOU BASTARD!
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryuko: HE BELIEVED THEY WOULD
REMAIN INSEPARABLE.
- Shokaku: I WILL DO ANYTHING
TO SEE THE LAND THRIVE.
- Koyo: ALKAID AND DUBHE ARE
ABOUT TO GO AT IT, FULL ON.
- Keiro: A MAN'S WORTH
IS MEASURED
IN VOLUMES OF BLOOD SPILT,
OF LIVES DEVOURED!
- Ryuko: IF SUCH IS YOUR
VERDICT, I AM PREPARED TO DIE.
- Rinmei: RYUKO! TAITO!
- Laila: WAIT, PLEASE! NO!
- Hosei: FAREWELL, RYUKO.
- Taito: RYUKO!
- Ryuko: NEXT TIME
ON HERO TALES,
THE STARS WEEP BITTER TEARS,
IN CHAPTER THIRTEEN:
"THE TWO CELESTIAL DEITIES."
FAREWELL, TAITO.