- SO YOU'RE BACK.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- OH, FATHER!
( crying )
- ARE YOU WELL, DAUGHTER?
- I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
- SO THAT BAD ASS OVER THERE
IS YOU GUYS' OLD MAN?
- HE IS A GREAT MAN.
LEADER OF THE QING LONG.
- AND A GOOD FATHER.
- HEY THERE.
- MASTER.
- Soei: TAITO.
- I'M BACK.
- YES.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( laughter )
- THE ADVENTURERS HAVE RETURNED.
BEARING WITH THEM NOT ONLY
NEW STORIES TO SHARE,
BUT NEW FRIENDS AS WELL.
EH, TAITO?
- YES, SIR. THAT'S TRUE.
BUT YOU SEE...
HE'S GONE. WE LOST RYUKO
TO MOUSTACHE'S ARMY.
I SWEAR I'LL AVENGE HIS DEATH.
- ON THE CONTRARY,
HE LIVES, MY BOY.
JUST LOOK UP.
ALL THE STARS ARE AS VIBRANT
AND RADIANT AS EVER.
THEY ARE ALL ACCOUNTED FOR,
INCLUDING OUR TERRESTRIALLY
ABSENT MIZAR.
- WHOA, NO WAY!
YOU MEAN HE'S ALIVE?
- HMM. YES INDEED.
AND WHAT'S MORE.
HIS STAR SHINES SO
BRIGHTLY IT COULD NOT
BE OBSCURED BY THE
DARKEST OF CLOUDS.
- ( LAUGHS )
ALL RIGHT!
- YEAH, I GOT TO SAY, THAT MAKES
A WHOLE LOT OF SENSE.
HE IS WHO HE IS AFTER ALL.
HE WOULDN'T JUST DIE WITHOUT
GIVING ME AN EARFUL
BEFORE HE KICKED THE BUCKET.
- YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
I THINK THE POOR GUY WOULD
HAVE GOTTEN LOST
ON HIS WAY UP
TO HEAVEN ANYHOW.
- WOW, HUH?
AREN'T YOU HAPPY?
- ( clears throat ) SO, TAITO.
SPEAKING OF FRIENDS,
I SEE YOU HAVE A NEW ONE.
THAT YOU'VE BEEN TOO RUDE
TO INTRODUCE.
- OH YEAH, SORRY.
GRANDPA, MEET RINMEI.
SHE'S AN ATTENDANT AT TONG YOU
AND KNOWS MASTER RYUSHO.
SHE'S THE EARTH FORM
OR WHATEVER OF MERAK.
BUT, YOU PROBABLY COULD
TELL FROM HER AURA
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
MY MASTER HAS TOLD ME
A GREAT DEAL
OF YOUR STRENGTH
AND WISDOM.
- THE PLEASURE IS TRULY
MINE, MY DEAR.
- TELL ME, ARE YOU FREE TONIGHT?
- WELL, I...
- OKAY NOW, SIMMER
DOWN GRANDPA.
RINMEI IS KINDA LIKE
RYUKO'S GIRLFRIEND.
- THAT SO?
IF I TOLD THEM HE WAS DEAD,
MAYBE I COULD HAVE HAD
A LITTLE FEMALE COMPANIONSHIP
FOR THE NIGHT.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- HELLO, SIRS! FIRST OF ALL,
LET ME TELL YOU HOW HONORED
I AM TO BE HERE IN THE
PRESENCE OF SUCH GREAT MEN AS...
- HEY, WHERE'D KOYO GO?
HE WAS JUST RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WANTED TO INTRODUCE HIM
TO FATHER AND MASTER SONNEI.
- KOYO, YOU SAY?
- YEAH, HE'S ANOTHER ONE
OF THE DIVINE WARRIORS.
HE PICKED US UP ON THE RIVER
IN HIS BOAT A FEW DAYS AGO.
I REALLY WANTED YOU
GUYS TO MEET HIM.
- HMM. IT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE I'LL SEE HIM SOON.
WHETHER HE WISHES IT OR NOT.
- HELLO! MASTERS SONNEI AND
SOEI, LET ME TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO HUMBLY
MAKE MY INTRODUC...
- OH, HEY, FATHER DID A BUNCH
OF KIDS SHOW UP HERE
WITH A NOTE FROM ME?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. THEY WERE
LIVING LIKE SCAVENGERS IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOWHERE SO WE
TOLD 'EM TO COME HERE.
THEY SHOULD'VE MADE IT BY NOW.
- Lien: HEY, TAITO.
- THERE YOU ARE.
- YOU'RE HERE. HEY.
- SLOWPOKES. WHAT THE HECK
TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
- YOU KNOW, I WAS PRETTY
SURPRISED TO SEE THIS BAND
OF KIDS SHOW UP TELLING ME YOU
SENT THEM HERE TO LIVE WITH US.
- AS GROWING CHILDREN,
THEY CERTAINLY DO EAT
QUITE A BIT OF FOOD.
- ACTUALLY THEY EAT ABOUT
AS MUCH COMBINED
AS TAITO DOES BY HIMSELF.
( laughing )
- LIEN HAS PROVEN TO BE A VERY
HARD WORKER AND HAS MORE THAN
EARNED HIS KEEP AROUND HERE.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE I'VE GAINED
MORE SONS AND DAUGHTERS
THAN I EVER DREAMED POSSIBLE.
- WOW. THAT'S REALLY GREAT TO
HEAR DAD. THEY'RE ALL GOOD KIDS.
I GUESS THAT MAKES US THEIR BIG
BROTHER AND SISTER NOW.
- UH, YEAH I GUESS SO.
- ( both laughing )
- WHILE WE'RE ON
THE SUBJECT, I...
- SO, I IMAGINE YOU'RE ALL
PRETTY ROAD WEARY.
WHY DON'T WE GET
YOU SETTLED IN THEN.
AND TAITO,
NOW THAT YOU'RE HOME,
YOU SHOULD START THINKING
ABOUT YOUR NEXT STEP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
WITH YOURSELF?
- HI, I'M HOSEI. I'M ONE OF
THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS
AND YOUR DAUGHTER IS
HOPELESSLY IN LOVE WITH ME.
- HOSEI. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
COME ON!
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU, SWEETHEART!
( laughing )
- WELL, WELL, WELL!
SO FATE HAS CHOSEN TO
BRING ME BACK HERE.
OLD MAN. YOU'LL GET WHAT'S
COMING TO YOU.
- AH, NOW, YOU SHOULDN'T
TROUBLE YOURSELF.
- YOU TOOK CARE
OF US AT TONG YOU,
SO I'M JUST
RETURNING THE FAVOR.
YOU'RE OUR GUEST AFTER ALL.
YOU SHOULD BE TREATED
LIKE ROYALTY.
TRY TO RELAX. WHAT ARE YOU
SEWING OVER THERE ANYWAY?
DID SOMETHING GET TORN?
- NO. IT'S NOTHING. ACTUALLY...
- THAT'S RYUKO'S.
- YES IT IS.
I WANTED TO GIVE IT BACK
TO HIM IN GOOD CONDITION.
IT'S SILLY AND I'M SURE HE
DOESN'T CARE HOW IT LOOKS.
IF HE EVEN NOTICES AT ALL.
- WHAT GREAT NEWS.
ISN'T IT AMAZING?
- I THOUGHT I'D LOST HIM.
BUT NOW IT'S JUST A MATTER
OF TIME UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN.
- SO, UH. HERE YOU GO.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME TAKE IT.
BUT TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
I'M NOT. I'M NOT REALLY
A "WEAPON" KIND OF GUY.
I'M MORE OF, LIKE,
A HANDS-ON FIGHTER, I GUESS.
- I KNOW, MY SON. YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN THE TYPE TO RELY SOLELY
ON YOUR OWN HANDS.
I IMAGINE YOU'VE GROWN
EVEN MORE SKILLED
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GONE.
BUT EVEN SO, YOU SHOULD
STILL KEEP IT WITH YOU.
PLEASE TAKE IT, TAITO.
NOT TO USE,
MORE LIKE ANOTHER
TRAVELING COMPANION.
- THANKS, DAD.
- IMPRESSIVE.
I'D EXPECT NO LESS
FROM AN EXPERIENCED
CHANNELER LIKE YOURSELF.
SUCH MASTERY.
SUCH CONTROL OF YOUR POWER.
- WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
- ALKAID AND HIS ENTOURAGE
HAVE RETURNED TO THE SAFETY
OF THEIR FAMILIAL DEN.
THEY AIM TO LICK THEIR WOUNDS,
MOURN THEIR LOSSES.
LET'S SMOKE THEM OUT AND COLLECT
THEIR HEADS AS TROPHIES.
MY LORD. I'M CONFUSED. YOU'VE
ALWAYS TAKEN THE MOST DIRECT
ROUTE DEALING WITH
YOUR ADVERSARIES.
BUT YOUR APPROACH
TO ALKAID AS OF LATE
HAS BEEN RATHER COOL.
THE IRON IS HOT NOW.
WE MUST STRIKE LEST WE LOSE
OUR OPPORTUNITY. FOR GOOD.
- SHIMEI.
- YES, LORD?
- YOU'RE EITHER BEING DENSE,
OR PERHAPS
INTENTIONALLY CONTRARY.
YOU KNOW WHY
I LEAVE HIM BE FOR NOW.
- I DO?
THEN PLEASE REFRESH ME.
- ALKAID IS NO MERE OBSTACLE
TO BE STEPPED OVER,
NOR IS HE A STONE
TO BE KICKED FROM MY PATH.
ALKAID'S ROLE IS INTEGRAL.
MY PLANS ENGULF MUCH MORE
THAN THE XIAN EMPIRE.
AND THE BOY WILL WEIGH INTO
THOSE PLANS INFINITELY MORE
THAN YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
- ( chuckling ) SO WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS WE SHOULD
LET OUR GAME LIVE WELL
AND FATTEN ITSELF BEFORE
WE SLAUGHTER IT
FOR THE FINAL FEAST?
- RUN!
( all laughing )
- DON'T RUN. I'M SO HUNGRY,
AND I LOVE TO EAT LITTLE KIDS.
- YA CAN'T CATCH ME,
YOU STINKY OLD MONSTER!
- ALL THIS RUNNING
IS MAKING ME HUNGRY.
- THAT BOY.
HE'S AS LIVELY AS EVER.
- YEAH, IT'S LIKE HE'S
A LITTLE KID TOO.
( sighs ) IS HE EVER
GOING TO GROW UP
AND STOP BEING SO STUPID?
- NOW GO EASY ON YOUR BROTHER.
TAITO JUST KNOWS HOW
TO ENJOY HIMSELF.
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- OH, WOW. I CAN SEE WHERE LAILA
GETS HER INTELLIGENCE FROM.
THE THINGS YOU SAY, FATHER.
LIKE PEARLS OF WISDOM.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- "FATHER," HUH?
- ARE YOU THIRSTY, DEAR FATHER?
I'VE GOT DRINKS!
- AH. SO YOU DID THAT
ALL BY YOURSELF, DID YOU?
- I HAD TO DIG DEEP INSIDE.
SOMETIMES I AMAZE EVEN MYSELF.
- GIMME A BREAK.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME? COME ON.
- NOW, LAILA. IT'S TRUE.
I'M BOTH HEROIC AND HUMBLE.
FOR IF I CAN SOMEHOW
HELP MY FELLOW MAN.
I SWEAR I'LL ALWAYS LEND A HAND.
- NOW DON'T YOU FEEL
BETTER, FATHER?
- YES, MUCH BETTER.
- ( sighs )
- ( laughs ) EVERYTHING
IS GOING ACCORDING TO PLAN.
IF I CAN GET POPS HERE
ON MY SIDE. I AM IN.
- HOSEI. YOU HAVE COMPLETELY
AND TOTALLY WON ME OVER,
MY DEAR BOY.
- I THINK YOU'D MAKE A
WONDERFUL ADDITION
TO THE FAMILY.
- AS LAILA'S HUSBAND. I KNOW.
- OH MY, IT'S SO EMBARRASSING.
BUT STILL...
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT. I WILL.
- I'LL MAKE YOU THE HAPPIEST
GIRL IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
( chuckling )
VERY HAPPY.
- SO IS THIS ONE A LITTLE
BIT SOFT IN THE HEAD?
- EXTREMELY SOFT.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO LURK ABOUT.
WELL, WELL. YOU'VE FINALLY
RETURNED. WELCOME BACK.
- IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE.
PLEASE FORGIVE THE RUDENESS
OF MY UNCEREMONIOUS DEPARTURE.
- I'VE MENTORED MANY YOUNG
MEN AT LIAN TONG,
BUT ONLY ONE HAS RUN AWAY
HIS VERY FIRST NIGHT.
KOYO, YOU ABSORBED MY
TEACHINGS WITH THE AVIDITY
OF A SPONGE THAT
THIRSTS FOR WATER.
I THOUGHT YOU TO BE WISE
WELL BEYOND YOUR YEARS.
- THANK YOU, MASTER.
- THAT WASN'T PRAISE.
TO THINK TAITO RETURNED HOME
WITH A PRODIGAL SUCH AS
YOURSELF IN TOW.
IT SEEMS FATE HAS A WRY
SENSE OF HUMOR INDEED.
- IS THAT SO?
I FAIL TO SEE THE COMEDY.
SCURVY WOULD GET MORE LAUGHS.
- NOW THEN.
LET'S NOT SIDESTEP THE
ISSUE FURTHER. GIVE IT BACK.
RETURN THE ITEM WHICH
YOU STOLE FROM ME
SO MANY YEARS AGO.
I'M SURPRISED YOU
HADN'T SOLD IT.
ISN'T THAT WHAT THIEVES DO?
- A RELIC OF THE LIAN TONG
TEMPLE WOULD FETCH SOME COIN.
I OFTEN CONSIDERED IT.
BUT ALAS, ONE HAS TO
CONSIDER THE FUTURE AS WELL.
I THOUGHT I'D SOMEDAY NEED IT.
AND HERE WE ARE.
IT SEEMS THAT DAY HAS COME.
- I APPRECIATE WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
- ( meows )
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs ) THIS'LL BE QUITE
THE STORY TO TELL MY PUPILS.
THE THIEF WHOSE GUILT DRIVES
HIM THIS FAR TO REUNITE
A CAT WITH ITS DISH.
- YOU MEAN IT WAS WORTH
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING?
- ASK THE CAT.
- ASK THE CAT? ASK THE CAT!
- ALL RIGHT, READY?
- TOO SLOW!
- ( all laugh )
- OW! OW! OW!
OW! OW! OW! OW!
- GEEZ, TAITO,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU GOT TO TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
I'M AS SERIOUS AS
A SHARK ATTACK HERE.
IT'S YOU GUYS' FAULT FOR
COMING AT ME ALL
AT ONCE LIKE SOME KINDA
PACK OF WILD DOGS.
- BUT YOU TOLD US TO.
- YOU SAID THAT WE SHOULD ALL
COME AT YOU AS A GROUP,
CAUSE YOU COULD HANDLE
A BUNCH OF KIDS.
- I CAN. BUT YOU CAUGHT
ME OFF GUARD.
- HEY, IS TAITO ALL RIGHT?
I REMEMBER HIM BEING STRONG.
HE WAS, WASN'T HE?
- I AM STRONG.
EVERYBODY SAW ME, RIGHT?
WHEN I TOOK OUT THOSE
THREE BAD GUYS?
AND THIS IS FOR PICKING ON
SOMEONE WEAKER THAN YOU.
THEY WERE SORRY THEY MESSED
WITH ME, HUH?
- THAT'S TRUE. BUT MAYBE
YOU BEAT 'EM 'CAUSE YOU JUST
GOT LUCKY THAT
DAY OR SOMETHING.
- THAT WASN'T LUCK.
- OH HEY. I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WE SHOULD HAVE TAITO
AND EVERYONE SHOW US ALL
THOSE COOL TRICKS THEY CAN
DO LIKE THEY DID THAT ONE TIME.
- AN EXHIBITION OF SKILLS, EH?
THIS SHOULD BE FUN.
- WE'LL FINALLY SEE WHAT
TAITO HAS LEARNED.
AND WHAT THE OTHER
DIVINE WARRIORS ARE CAPABLE OF.
- EVERYONE PLEASE DIRECT YOUR
ATTENTION TO THE COURTYARD.
TAITO AND DIVINE WARRIORS
HAVE GOT SOME AMAZING
THINGS TO SHOW YOU.
FIRST UP THE BEAUTIFUL RINMEI.
- ( grunting )
- NEXT IS MISTER
SURE SHOT, HOSEI!
- ALL RIGHT, THESE PEOPLE
WANT TO SEE A SHOW.
SO I GUESS I WILL JUST HAVE
TO GIVE THEM A SHOW.
THAT'S THE SHUANG CHAN BOW.
IN FULL BLOOM!
- MASTER OF THE
HIGH SEAS, KOYO.
- IT'S NOT A SOLO ACT I NEED
YOU TO BE MY ASSISTANT.
- OH, UH, YOU DO?
- UH, I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THIS.
HE CAN'T SEE THROUGH
THAT, RIGHT?
- YEAH, WHAT IF HE MISSES?
THIS COULD GET UGLY.
- BE CAREFUL, LAILA.
- LISTEN HERE, YOU OLD RIVER
RAT. YOU DO ANYTHING TO THAT
BEAUTIFUL FACE OF HERS,
YOU ARE GOING TO BE IN TROUBLE.
I AM NOT JOKING, YOU HEAR ME?
- I WOULDN'T HAVE ASSUMED
OTHERWISE, RELAX!
I ALMOST NEVER MISS.
- ( gasps )
- YUM! TASTY!
- AND NOW IS OUR VERY
OWN TAITO!
- YEAH, TAITO. SHOW 'EM UP.
- YOU CAN DO IT!
- ALL RIGHT.
NOW SHOW EVERYBODY THE
TRUE POWER OF THE
QING LONG SPIRIT.
- DON'T WORRY, YOU GUYS,
I'VE GOT THIS IN THE BAG.
RIGHT!
- I SEE
- HE'S GOING TO USE
CHANNELING, HUH?
- I'LL BE...
- INNER RESERVOIR CHANNELING,
IT'S QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
HE'S EXTREMELY ADVANCED
FOR HIS YOUNG AGE.
- HOW'S THAT?
COME ON. NO CHEERS AT ALL?
YOU SHOULD BE PICKING
YOUR JAWS OFF THE GROUND
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
SO, MAKE SOME NOISE!
- UH, WELL, THAT WAS
REALLY AMAZING.
- OH YEAH. BUT STILL...
- BUT STILL IT WAS
ALSO KIND OF BORING.
- THAT WAS BORING?
- KIND OF. I MEAN, ALL YOU
REALLY ENDED UP DOING
WAS BREAKING THAT PILLAR.
- ALL OF THE OTHER ONES PUT
ON A SHOW FOR EVERYBODY.
YOU JUST KINDA STOOD THERE,
AND THEN YOU BROKE THE THING.
- YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN A LITTLE
ON THE SLOW SIDE, HAVEN'T YOU?
- HEY! I AM NOT
ON THE SLOW SIDE.
YOU GUYS THINK I'M
JUST SO UNKEMPT
THAT I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT, IS THAT IT?
YOU WANT TO BE ENTERTAINED?
YOU WANT TO SEE A REAL SHOW?
WATCH THIS!
I'LL JUST, JUST, UH...
( imitates monkey chattering )
- NOW THAT'S GOOD!
- THAT'S IT.
NOW CLIMB THAT TREE.
YOU'RE SO FUNNY. MORE. MORE.
- OH, MY GOSH,
HE'S SUCH AN IDIOT!
- THAT BOY'S JUST NOT
RIGHT IN THE HEAD.
- ( laughing ) WHAT A SHOW!
- THIS IS MORE LIKE IT,
YOU AND ME WALKING
THE BEAT AGAIN, MAKING SURE
THAT THERE'S NO TROUBLE.
- I APPRECIATE YOU COMING WITH
ME YOU COULD'VE STAYED BACK
AND RESTED A WHILE, YOU KNOW?
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I MAY BE TIRED, BUT I'M
STILL A MEMBER OF QING LONG!
I'D GO ON PATROL WITH YOU
ANYTIME, POPS.
- THANK YOU, SON.
- YOU KNOW, THIS
WHOLE THING HAS BEEN
LIKE SOME CRAZY DREAM I HAD.
TO GO FROM THE CAPITAL TO BEING
BACK HERE AT HOME WITH YOU.
HEY, GUESS WHAT?
WELL, WHILE I WAS THERE,
I ACTUALLY MET
THE EMPEROR HIMSELF!
- IS THAT TRUE?
- IT'S TRUE. I HAD SOME
SERIOUS DOUBTS ABOUT
THE GUY AT FIRST BECAUSE
THE EMPIRE IS IN SUCH
A SORRY STATE RIGHT NOW.
BUT I THINK HE'S ACTUALLY A
PRETTY GOOD GUY IN HIS OWN WAY.
YEAH. HE'S DEFINITELY
DOING THE BEST HE CAN
AT THE VERY LEAST.
- IT'S WEIRD.
- HEY, POP. SOMETHING WRONG?
- SO THE BLOOD ATTRACTS.
TAITO I FEARED THAT THIS
DAY WOULD EVENTUALLY
COME TO PASS.
LISTEN, SON,
HIS BLOOD IS MINGLED IN WITH
YOUR OWN, YOU BOTH SHARE IT.
YOU AND HE ARE BROTHERS,
TWINS TO BE EXACT.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S BEEN SIXTEEN YEARS.
THE TWO OF YOU WERE BORN
SCREAMING INTO THIS WORLD.
THE WORLD THAT ONE WAS
DESTINED TO RULE.
THE FATE FOR THE OTHER
WAS NOT SO FORTUNATE.
HE WAS TO BE DISPOSED OF,
TO AVOID A CONSTANT POWER
STRUGGLE FOR THE THRONE.
IN THIS CASE, THE ANSWER
PRESENTED ITSELF,
IN THE FORM OF A SACRED
AND POWERFUL SIGIL.
DURING THAT TIME IN MY LIFE
I WAS WORKING AT THE CAPITAL
AS A GUARD.
ONE NIGHT RYUSHO
SUMMONED ME
TO TONG YOU TEMPLE
ON AN URGENT MATTER.
HE ASKED THAT I TAKE
YOU TO LIAN TONG,
WHERE YOU WOULD
LIVE IN OBSCURITY,
IMMUNE TO THE MACHINATIONS
OF THOSE WHO TRY TO CONTROL
THE THRONE.
THE OFFICIAL STORY
IS THAT YOU HAD FALLEN
TO A CHILDHOOD DISEASE.
LEAVING TAIGA TO BECOME
THE NEXT EMPEROR.
OF COURSE YOU
KNOW THE REST.
I RAISED YOU AS MY OWN
FLESH AND BLOOD.
FORGIVE ME FOR NOT TELLING YOU.
I FEARED THIS DAY.
- AW, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, POP.
SO FANCY DRESS IS MY BROTHER.
IT ACTUALLY EXPLAINS
A WHOLE LOT OF THINGS.
AND HEY, I'M NOT UPSET
ABOUT IT AT ALL.
THE ONLY REASON I'M AROUND
TO HEAR THIS STORY IS BECAUSE
OF WHAT EVERYBODY DID FOR ME.
YOU ALL RISKED YOUR LIVES.
AND THANKS TO THAT
I CAN LIVE MY OWN.
YOU REALLY ARE THE
BEST, POP. I MEAN IT.
- THANK YOU, SON.
- ( children laughing )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY DID YOU STOP PLAYING?
- UH, HOLD ON.
( gasps )
THEY FOUND US!
- I HAD PLANNED ON TAKING
THAT SECRET TO THE GRAVE.
I WANTED YOU TO HEAD
UP QING LONG,
AND NOT TO HAVE
YOUR MIND OVERRUN
WITH THOUGHTS OF THE EMPIRE.
YOU WERE NEVER TO KNOW
OF YOUR TRUE LINEAGE.
- SO IS THAT THE REASON YOU
WERE AGAINST ME GOING
TO THE CAPITAL
AT THE FIRST PLACE?
- YES. I DIDN'T WANT
YOU TO GO BACK THERE.
OUT OF MY OWN FEAR,
I WAS AFRAID YOU'D
LEARN THE TRUTH
AND NEVER WANT
TO RETURN TO LIAN TONG.
- REALLY?
GIVE ME A BREAK, POP.
I DON'T CARE IF THE EMPEROR
IS MY BROTHER, YOU'RE NOT
GETTING OUT OF BEING MY DAD
THAT EASY!
- STRANGE THE WAY
THINGS TURN OUT.
BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU,
THE ONE WHO DREW SHAWN
GHEE LAN WU,
THE ONE DESTINED TO RULE
LIVES IN EXILE WHILE THE OTHER
IS GIVEN CONTROL OF THE EMPIRE.
- EMPEROR, ME?
( laughs ) THAT'S HILARIOUS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO TELL 'EM.
THIS IS GOING TO BE GREAT
WHEN LAILA AND HOSEI
FIND OUT THAT THEY'RE
CALLING THE GUY THAT SHOULD
HAVE BEEN THE EMPEROR STUPID.
- DON'T BOTHER. THEY'RE
NEVER GOING TO BELIEVE YOU.
- MASTER SOEI! TAITO!
- LIEN?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- WHY ARE YOU JERKS EVEN HERE?
- WHY? WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO COME AND BURN LIAN TONG
TO THE GROUND?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO KILL INNOCENT
PEOPLE TO GET TO ME?
KEIRO!
- ( Japanese song playing )
- Koyo: WAN XIANG SHI MING.
FROM ITS EYE,
AN EVIL GLOW EMANATES.
- Soei: HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN THE
MOTTO OF THE QING LONG PLATOON?
- Taito: WE SWEAR TO WORK
FOR PEACE. TO HELP OTHERS.
AND TO LOVE OUR FELLOW MAN.
- IT'S HIGH TIME WE GOT
ON TO THE REAL SHOW!
- Taito: THAT COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN STRONG
ENOUGH TO PUT A CRACK IN
THE SWORD LIKE THIS.
- COME ON, "SON."
NOW, GET ANGRY DESTROY
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT!
AND UNLEASH ALKAID'S
CLEANSING HOLOCAUST!
- Koyo: WILL ALKAID'S RAGE
BE THE BEACON
USHERING ON A NEW ERA?
IN HERO TALES,
"CHAPTER EIGHTEEN,
LIAN TONG TEMPLE ABLAZE."
- Laila: YOU WERE
RIGHT BY HIS SIDE
THE ENTIRE TIME
AND YOU STILL
COULDN'T PROTECT HIM
FROM THOSE MONSTERS.
YOU LET HIM DIE!