- HOW DID YOU COME BY IT?
- THE DIVINE WARRIOR GIRL.
SHE HAD IT ON HER PERSON WHEN WE
ENSNARED HER AT TONG YO.
- IS THIS TRUE?
- AS HER EXECUTION IS NIGH,
YOU MAY WISH TO HOLD ON TO THAT.
- ( Japanese song playing )
- ( gasps )
- AS YOU SEE, THAT WHICH
WE REVERED AS THE SWORD
OF RULE IS COUNTERFEIT.
A GILDED PRETENSE.
- ( all murmuring )
- BUT THEN, WHITHER
THE GENUINE SWORD?
- WHAT IS THIS?
- WILL YOU ATTEMPT TO DRAW IT?
- ( grunting )
ALAS, I CANNOT.
- THE XIAN EMPIRE IS
BUT MERE PAGEANTRY!
FOUNDED ON LIES AND
ANCHORED IN DECEIT!
ITS LEADER, A PAPER TIGER!
AND YET STILL THERE IS HOPE.
THE TRUE SWORD BEFORE YOU
HAS CHOSEN THE TRUE EMPEROR.
BEHOLD! THE WILL OF THE HEAVENS!
- SUCH RADIANCE.
INDEED IT MUST BE!
- WHY DO YOU GAPE?
THE MAN BEFORE US HAS BEEN
DECREED BY FATE TO LEAD!
SHOW THAT YOU WILL FOLLOW.
BOW YOUR HEADS, NOW!
- ( laughing )
- RYUKO!
- YOUR BLADE.
- THEY TELL ME IT
WAS FOUND ON YOU.
- I HELD TIGHT TO IT
WHEN I THOUGHT...
WHEN I FELT IN MY HEART
THAT YOU'D MET YOUR END.
BUT NOW I KNOW THE TRUTH.
- RINMEI...
BECOME A PART OF ALL THIS.
YOU AND I CAN SERVE HIS
LORDSHIP ARM IN ARM!
- HOW CAN YOU ASK THAT?
- THE PRICE OF OBSTINACY
WILL BE YOUR HEAD!
A COST I CANNOT BEAR
TO SEE YOU PAY.
SWEAR FEALTY TO LORD
KEIRO AND I CAN INTERVENE.
RINMEI, PLEASE.
HELP ME TO SAVE YOU!
- THAT I CAN'T.
- DAMN YOU! SEE REASON!
YOUR LIFE IS AT STAKE!
- RYUKO, WHAT YOU
CALL REASON IS MADNESS.
THE ONE WHO NEEDS SAVING IS YOU.
MY LIFE WILL BE SPARED CARE
OF YOUR FORMER FRIENDS.
- SUCH CHARMING FAITH.
- WHAT OF YOUR OWN?
- WHAT?
- YOU'VE ALIGNED YOURSELF
TO LORD KEIRO.
IN YOUR HEART DO YOU
BELIEVE HIM TO BE RIGHT?
- I DO.
- YOUR KEEPSAKE YIELDS
ITS SECRETS TO THE MOON.
I HAVE SEEN THE NAME.
THE LOVE OF A SON
CAST ASIDE BLINDS YOU.
- PERHAPS IT DOES.
THOUGH YET, MY IDEALS WOULD
REFLECT HIS REGARDLESS.
OF THIS I COULD NOT BE
MORE CERTAIN. IT IS FATE.
- SPEAK AS YOURSELF!
- I SPEAK AS ONE
ALLIED TO THE EMPEROR!
INDEED. AS ONE
ALLIED TO THE STARS,
KEIRO HAS BEEN DECREED
THIS LAND'S SALVE.
- HAVE YOU HEARD THE RUMBLINGS?
THEY SAY GENERAL KEIRO
DREW THE SWORD OF RULE.
AND BEFORE A STAGGERED
EMPEROR NO LESS.
- BUT HOW CAN THAT BE? ONLY
HIS MAJESTY CAN DRAW THE SWORD.
- BUT THAT'S JUST IT, THOUGH.
THE ONE HE DREW WAS A FAKE.
APPARENTLY TAIGA WAS NEVER FIT
TO RULE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- WELL, THAT'D DEFINITELY
EXPLAIN THE SAD STATE OF AFFAIRS
THE REALM'S BEEN IN LATELY.
- YOU WHAT? YOU'RE JOKING!
TAIGA HAS BEEN DEPOSED!
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE'S DRIVEN FROM
THE CAPITAL LIKE A PLAGUE DOG
FROM ITS MASTER'S TABLE!
WOULD YOU JOIN
HIM IN BANISHMENT?
TAKI, PLEASE. YOU AND I
CAN LIVE OPENLY
AS FATHER AND DAUGHTER NOW.
- A MOMENT I HAVE LONGED FOR.
AND PLEASE DO NOT THINK ME COLD.
BUT I...
MY PLACE IS WITH HIM.
I WILL NOT ABANDON MY
HUSBAND IN HIS HOUR OF NEED!
- HE WHAT? LORD KEIRO HAS
DRAWN THE SWORD OF RULE?
- OH MAN, NO WAY!
- THE WHOLE CAPITAL IS
ASTIR WITH THE NEWS, SIR.
- WHAT AN UNSEEMLY
TURN OF EVENTS.
MY ENTIRE STRATAGEM IS A
PANTOMIME NOW.
WORSE, AN UTTER FARCE.
- NOW WHAT?
- THIS IS TERRIBLE. IF KEIRO
IS CROWNED EMPEROR...
- COME ON. IT'S NOT LIKE DRAWING
SOME STUPID OLD SWORD
AUTOMATICALLY MAKES
YOU THE EMPEROR, RIGHT?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT DOES!
- WHAT, HAVE YOU BEEN
LIVING UNDER A ROCK?
GIVE ME A BREAK, TAITO,
INFANTS KNOW THAT'S HOW
EMPERORS ARE CHOSEN.
- WELL I THINK THE WHOLE THING'S
A SHAM, I MEAN I DIDN'T HAVE
ANY TROUBLE UNSHEATHING
THAT THING.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU DREW THE SWORD?
- WELL, YEAH, SURE.
IT HAPPENED WHEN I FOUGHT
MOUSTACHE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- YOU IMBECILE! DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD HAVE SHARED THIS
WITH THE REST OF US BEFORE NOW?
- WELL, MAKE A MOLEHILL
OUT OF IT, WHY DON'T YOU?
I'M NOT YOU. I DON'T REMEMBER
EVERY LITTLE THING I DO WRONG!
- SHUT UP, JERK!
- GENIUS IS EMPEROR? SEEMS
LIKE A BIT OF A STRETCH.
OR, UH, IMPOSSIBLE.
- COULD THE HEAVENS HAVE
DECREED TWO RULERS AT ONCE?
NO, IT MUST BE THAT TAITO HAS
SOMEHOW MANAGED TO FALL
OUT OF THE BLADE'S FAVOR.
- WHO EVEN CARES? RULING
IS FOR CHUMPS, NOT ME.
EVEN WHEN SHIMEI TRIED TO
SWEET TALK ME INTO IT,
I FLAT-OUT TOLD HIM NO.
- YOU... YOU INGRATE!
- IN-WHAT?
- YOU THUMBED YOUR
NOSE AT DESTINY
AND FOR THAT THE HEAVENS HAVE
CHOSEN A MONSTER'S AMBITION
OVER A SAPLING'S PRIDE.
- SO YOU MEAN, IF HE
WOULD'VE ACCEPTED IT,
WE WOULDN'T BE IN
THIS MESS, WOULD WE?
- WE CAN'T BE SURE BUT IT SEEMS
LIKELY. THE SWORD IS FICKLE.
- ARE YOU'RE SERIOUS? SO IT'S MY
FAULT KEIRO'S THE EMPEROR NOW.
BECAUSE I TURNED MY BACK ON IT?
- WELL, EITHER WAY IT WAS LIKELY
BOUND TO HAPPEN EVENTUALLY.
- HOLD ON A SECOND. IF KEIRO'S
TAKEN THE THRONE ALL OF A SUDDEN
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO TAIGA?
- WELL, UH, IF HE GIVES IT UP
WITHOUT A FIGHT HE MAY LIVE.
USURPERS CAN BE MERCIFUL.
- AND IF HE DOESN'T?
- SURELY HE'S WILLING
TO ABDICATE.
TAIGA HASN'T THE
WILL BUT TO FOLD.
- NO! HE MADE ME A
PROMISE, DAMN IT!
HE SWORE HE'D TRY
TO CHANGE THINGS,
THAT HE'D MAKE THE
EMPIRE A BETTER PLACE!
- SHOULD HE CHOOSE TO HOLD
HIS OWN, MORE'S THE PITY.
KEIRO WILL CUT HIM DOWN WITHOUT
SO MUCH AS BATTING AN EYE.
- HEY! JUST WHERE THE
HELL ARE YOU OFF TO?
- TO GO AND HELP EMPEROR TAIGA.
- DON'T BE RASH.
- THE MAN'S MY BROTHER!
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO STOP ME,
SO JUST BACK OFF!
- YOU FOOL, WHY CHOOSE
TO BE A LONE WOLF?
YOU'VE AN ENTIRE
PACK TO RUN WITH.
- LORD KEIRO.
- YES, BOY?
- A RUMOR'S GAINED CURRENCY
THAT YOU INTEND TO KILL TAIGA.
- AND IF IT BE TRUE?
- I IMPLORE YOU TO RECONSIDER!
YOUR AIM HAS ALREADY
BEEN REALIZED!
PLEASE, LORD, WHAT NEED CRIES
FURTHER BLOODSHED TO THAT END?
- BLOODSHED HARBINGERS FEAR,
BEGETS OBEDIENCE,
BALLASTS ONE'S POWER.
- BUT SIR, HE'S...
HE'S YOUR SON-IN-LAW!
YOU'D AS GOOD AS
SHED YOUR OWN BLOOD!
WHY WOULD YOU VISIT
HARM UPON FAMILY?
- ENOUGH.
- MY LORD.
FATHER.
TELL ME. WOULD YOU STOOP
TO SPILL MY BLOOD?
- THAT DAGGER.
IMPOSSIBLE.
CAN YOU REALLY BE KEIKO?
- FORGIVE ME.
I HAD HOPED TO SPARE YOU
THE EMBARRASSMENT AND YET...
- RYUKO... RATHER, KEIKO.
I ABANDONED YOU
IN SERVICE TO A LOFTIER VISION
THAN FATHERHOOD. FORGIVE ME.
I SHALL RESCIND MY
DECISION TO EXECUTE HIM.
- DO YOU SPEAK THE TRUTH?
- MOREOVER, TAIGA
IS NOW IN YOUR CARE.
- MY LORD, I AM MOST GRATEFUL.
- KILL THEM ALL.
- LISTEN UP, MEN!
NOW, TAKE HEED!
OUR QUARRY IS ESPECIALLY
ELUSIVE FOR TONIGHT,
WE ENSNARE AN EMPEROR!
- BUT, BOSS. THAT'S CRAZY.
AND BESIDES, WE'RE PRIVATEERS.
- COME NOW. GIVE NOT
FEAR A FEAST! BE BRAZEN!
THINK OF THE GRAND ADVENTURE.
THE THRILL OF THE HUNT!
TREADING WHERE FEW ELSE DARE.
AND, WELL, NATURALLY THINK
OF AN EMPEROR'S RANSOM.
- WELL I FOR ONE THINK
IT'S A BRILLIANT IDEA, SIR!
- ACCORDING TO OUR SOURCES,
HIS MAJESTY IS CURRENTLY
BEING HELD AT TONG YO TEMPLE.
- SERIOUSLY?
- RINMEI IS THERE AS WELL.
- SO IT'S TWO FOR
THE PRICE OF ONE.
- REALLY?
- ALL RIGHT! THIS IS THE
SORT OF CRAZY I LIVE FOR!
- EXCELLENT. BUT BEAR IN MIND,
THE TEMPLE HAS ESSENTIALLY
BECOME A FORTRESS.
GET COCKY AND WE'LL BE FODDER
FOR THE XUAN LANG PLATOON.
- SO, THEN WHAT HAVE
YOU GOT UP YOUR SLEEVE?
- MY SLEEVE? NO FANCY TRICKS
THIS TIME AROUND, I'M AFRAID.
- COME ON! YOU'RE JOKING!
- TIME IS AGAINST US.
IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
- BUT SIR, CAN WE NOT
USE THE MACHINES?
GIVEN THE ENEMY'S NUMBER,
I BALK TO THINK WHAT OUR
CASUALTIES WILL BE
WITHOUT THE ELEMENT
OF SURPRISE ON OUR SIDE.
COME NOW. SURELY
OUR BRAVE CAPTAIN
WOULD GIVE HIS
BLESSING TO WHATEVER
ADVANTAGE WAS AVAILABLE.
- DO NOT SPEAK TO ME OF THEM.
WOULD YOU SEE PIGS FLY?
- SURE!
- NO, NO! I WILL NOT SUBMIT
TO THEIR INFERNAL WHIM!
- I DESPAIR MY CHARGE.
PLEASE, FRIENDS. FORGIVE
THE SPARSE ROOM.
- NOT AT ALL. MY GRATITUDE,
SIR. INDEED, MY UTMOST.
YOUR INTERVENTION MAY HAVE
SPARED MY LIFE OR AT THE LEAST
KEPT TAKI AND I TOGETHER.
- WON'T YOU CONSIDER
ABDICATION? PLEASE.
YOU MAY YET BE
TOGETHER IN FREEDOM.
- I WILL NOT ABDICATE!
I'VE A PROMISE TO KEEP.
ONE I'M LOATHE TO RECANT.
ONE THAT I MAY ONLY
FULFILL AS EMPEROR.
- FOR TAITO, YES?
- THAT'S CORRECT!
I TAKE IT YOU KNOW HIM?
- I DO.
- OUTSTANDING! TELL ME
HOW DOES HE FARE?
- WELL, SIR, RECKLESSLY
AS EVER, I FEAR.
- THAT RINGS TRUE. GOOD TAITO,
YOU MAY LAUGH AT THIS...
BUT EVEN FROM THE MOMENT HE
DROPPED THROUGH THE CEILING.
IT NEVER FELT AS THOUGH
WE WERE STRANGERS.
- SUCH IS THE BOND
OF BROTHERHOOD.
- ( gasps )
- THIS IS WHAT I CALL FUN!
- Man: TO ARMS, MEN!
WE'RE UNDER SIEGE!
- THE HELL?
- OH, WOW! THIS IS GREAT!
- NO KIDDING! THE WO JIN
GUYS HAVE IT ALL!
NOBODY CAN TOUCH US UP HERE!
- GOOD NEWS. HOSEI'S QUITE
TAKEN WITH HIS TASK.
- I HATE THIS!
WE WEREN'T MEANT TO FLY! EVER!
WE SAW FURTHER WEALTH
OF COMMON SENSE
WITH EVERY PUMP OF THE BELLOWS.
WHO DEVISED THESE
LUDICROUS CONTRAPTIONS?
- YOU, SIR.
- DAMN MY HUBRIS!
- WE'RE HERE.
- SAFE TO SAY WE'VE
ESCAPED THEIR NOTICE.
- IF THEY DIDN'T
HEAR YOU SCREAMING.
- GOOD POINT, TAITO. YOUR
FEAR OF HEIGHTS
ALMOST DESPOILED
THE PLAN, BRAVE CAPTAIN.
- WOW SERIOUSLY? I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE AFRAID OF ANYTHING!
- QUIET! ARE WE
DOING THIS OR NOT?
- ( yawning )
- DON'T MOVE! REFRAIN
FROM PLAYING GAMES
AND YOU JUST MIGHT LIVE.
- YES, MA'AM.
- ( thud )
- NO NEED TO BE SCARED. IT'S ME.
- RANK AMATEURS.
BUNCHED TOGETHER.
THEY MIGHT AS WELL FIT THAT
BUILDING WITH A TARGET.
- SO WHAT DO WE DO?
- WE PLAY IT SAFE.
BEST TO STAY PUT.
- WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR? COME ON!
- TAITO!
- LONG TIME NO SEE!
LOOKING FANCY!
- MY FRIEND, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M HERE TO RESCUE
YOU TWO, OF COURSE!
- RESCUE? ARE YOU MAD?
- SURE, WHATEVER. LET'S GO.
- BEFORE WE DO. WE'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONES BEING HELD.
A GIRL IS IMPRISONED
VERY CLOSE BY.
- OH, DON'T WORRY. WE'RE
ALL OVER THAT ONE, TOO.
- TAITO!
- DAMN IT! THEY HAVE
US BOXED IN!
- WHAT NOW?
- YOU FIREBOMBED LORD
KEIRO'S HOUSE TO DIVERT US,
THINKING YOU COULD
BAG YOUR QUARRY.
A CLEVER STRATAGEM, IN ITS WAY.
INTERESTING, SHOKAKU
SAW THIS. CLEARLY.
YOU'VE NOWHERE TO RUN!
SURRENDER PEACEFULLY, ALKAID!
- CAREFUL.
- STAY BACK, SIS.
- YOU GOT IT. BE SAFE.
- DON'T BE AN IMBECILE!
STAND DOWN! YOU CAN'T TAKE
THEM ALL ON! YOU'LL FALL!
- A REAL MAN STAYS AND FIGHTS.
WHATEVER THE ODDS.
PERIOD! YOU HEAR ME?
- YOU FOOL. JUST WHO
ARE YOU TRYING TO IMPRESS?
CAPITULATE!
- NOT A CHANCE,
OLD-TIMER. COME ON,
YOU WANT A PIECE OF THIS.
I CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES.
- YOU THINK SO?
ANTE UP THEN, ALKAID!
- LET'S SEE IF THAT FABLED MIGHT
IS ON PAR WITH THE
WARRIOR GOD YOU'RE SO HUNGRY
TO PIT YOURSELF AGAINST!
I'VE GOT HIM! DODGING THIS
BLOW ISN'T AN OPTION, BOY!
HOW WILL YOU COUNTER?
- TAITO!
- WHAT THE?
IMPOSSIBLE!
- ( chuckles ) AW, DARN. MY BAD.
- THIS CAN'T BE! HE FELLED
KOCHO WITH JUST ONE HIT!
- SO THIS IS ALKAID, THE
ONLY MAN TO HAVE
CROSSED SWORDS WITH LORD KEIRO
AND WOUNDED HIM, EVER.
- ( soldiers groaning )
- RYUSHO!
- WELL DONE. YOU'VE
MADE GREAT STRIDES.
QUITE THE WARRIOR INDEED!
- WELL, TO BE HONEST I HAVE
BEEN WORKING ON MY TECHNIQUE
A LITTLE BIT, YOU KNOW.
- YOUR MAJESTY.
- GENERAL? YOU'RE HERE?
- YOU'RE UNHARMED,
I'M SO THANKFUL.
- ( all screaming )
- TAITO! LET'S CLEAR A PATH!
- YOU BET!
- DID HE SAY TAITO?
COULD HE BE?
- FOLLOW ME! WE'RE MAKING
A BREAK FOR IT!
- TONIGHT'S NOT YOUR NIGHT.
I'M IN A FOUL MOOD.
THOSE WHO CHERISH
THEIR HIDES BEST MOVE!
- ( screaming )
- WHAT THE HELL?
THIS IS NO ORDINARY HUMAN BEING.
- LAILA! FEAR NOT, MY BELOVED!
I'M HERE TO WHISK YOU AWAY!
- THIS IS OUR WINDOW.
FALL BACK, TAITO!
- OKAY!
- OUR FIGHT MUST WAIT
FOR ANOTHER TIME.
- RINMEI! I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
- LAILA.
- BOSS!
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU.
LET'S MOVE OUT!
- RIGHT!
- WHAT THE? DAMN IT!
- SEE YOU AROUND, OLD TIMER!
- ALKAID?
- HEY, UH... NO HARD
FEELINGS, OKAY?
- WE ACTUALLY PULLED THIS OFF!
- I KNOW!
- WE ARE FOREVER IN YOUR
DEBT, FRIEND. THANK YOU.
- OH, NO. THIS ONE'S ON ME!
( laughing )
- ( screaming )
- ( air escaping )
- WE'RE FALLING! HELP!
- TAITO!
- DO SOMETHING, TAI!
WE'LL BE CRUSHED!
- IT'S RYUKO!
- ( screaming ) NO!
- ( Japanese song playing )
- Koyo: THE BITTER CLASH BETWEEN
ALKAID AND MIZAR BEGINS.
- I AM ALKAID! USER OF THE EIGHT
STYLES! CHOOSE YOUR STANCE!
- I AM MIZAR! I CHOOSE
YOUR ANNIHILATION!
- BUT WHO KNOWS? MAYBE IT'S OUR
FATE TO DISAGREE LIKE THIS.
- INDEED. THEN I'VE NO CHOICE!
- LET'S FINISH IT, RYUKO.
- Koyo: FATE RESERVES ITS
DARKEST TURN FOR WARRING FRIENDS
IN HERO TALES, CHAPTER
TWENTY-THREE, "CLASH."
- Taito: ONCE AND FOR ALL!