- OKAY, WHERE IS THAT BOY?
I SWEAR. EVERY TIME HE GETS
THE LEAST BIT BENT OUT OF SHAPE
ABOUT SOMETHING
HE JUST TEARS OFF.
I SUPPOSE SOME
THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( whimpering )
- Shimei: WELCOME BACK.
HOW ARE WE FEELING?
- BASTARD!
- OH NOW, THERE'S
NO NEED FOR THAT.
I LET YOU LIVE, DIDN'T I?
ANYONE ELSE IN YOUR
POSITION WOULD BE GRATEFUL.
- I'LL SHOW YOU
GRATEFUL, YOU JERK!
- HARK, DIVINE WARRIOR PHECDA.
YOU'RE TO KILL ALKAID.
- KILL ALKAID?
YOU WANT
ME TO KILL TAITO?
NO! YOU'RE OUT
OF YOUR MIND!
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT!
- BUT YOU WOULD,
MY DEAR BOY.
IF YOU VALUE THE
LIFE OF YOUR MASTER.
- STAY AWAY FROM HER!
- SORRY. THE TERMS
AREN'T NEGOTIABLE.
EITHER ALKAID DIES
BY YOUR HAND,
OR YOU AND
YOUR MASTER BY MINE.
A REFRESHINGLY
STRAIGHTFORWARD PROPOSITION
IF EVER THERE WAS ONE,
I SHOULD THINK.
- YOU AREN'T LYING.
AND FOR A GUY LIKE
ME IT'S A PRETTY
STRAIGHTFORWARD CHOICE.
EVEN MORE THAN YOU THINK.
HERE'S MY ANSWER!
- ( yells )
- SEE, I DON'T RESPOND
ALL THAT WELL TO THREATS.
BUT HEY, NO
HARD FEELINGS!
IF YOU WANNA KILL US,
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO GIVE IT A SHOT!
( laughs )
OKAY, THESE FREAKS ARE
OFFICIALLY NOT NORMAL.
WHAT THE HELL AM
I SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
- WATCH OVER THE HOUSE
WHILE WE'RE GONE.
WE'LL TRY TO BE BACK SOON.
- HOPEFULLY HE'LL TURN
UP BEFORE YOU HAVE TO
VENTURE ALL THAT FAR.
- I'M MORE CONCERNED
FOR LADY KOEI THAN
I AM HOSEI AT THIS POINT.
SHE SET OUT TO LOOK
FOR HIM HOURS AGO, NOW.
- THESE MOUNTAINS
MAY BE HER HOME. BUT STILL...
- COME ON THEN. WE'RE NOT
GONNA DO MUCH FROM HERE.
LET'S GO HAVE
A LOOK ALREADY.
- JUST AS I FEARED.
SO, IT WOULD SEEM MY
SENSE OF FOREBODING
WAS WARRANTED
AFTER ALL, EH, SHIMEI?
- HOW FLATTERING TO KNOW
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
REMEMBERS THE LIKES OF ME.
THE YEARS HAVE BEEN
AWFULLY KIND TO YOU.
STILL SO LUSTROUS AT FORTY?
- THIRTY-NINE, VILE SERPENT!
AND DON'T FEEL FLATTERED,
THAT THING YOU CALL A FACE
HASN'T AGED NEARLY SO WELL.
- COME NOW. IT'S
A BANDIT'S FACE.
IN THAT RESPECT
IT'S ON A PAR WITH YOURS.
STILL, I DO INTEND TO BE
MORE SELECTIVE NEXT TIME.
OH, YES. I STUMBLED
UPON YOUR PROTEGE.
- IF YOU TOUCHED
ONE HAIR ON HIS HEAD.
- OH, DON'T WORRY,
THE BOY'S FINE.
I MERELY ORDERED
THAT HE SLAY ALKAID.
NOTHING TOO OVER THE TOP.
THOUGH, I DID THREATEN TO SLAY
YOU IF HE REFUSED TO OBEY ME.
- HIS RESPONSE?
- THAT I WAS MORE THAN
WELCOME TO GIVE IT
A SHOT IF I CARED TO TRY.
LET ME ASK
YOU SOMETHING...
CAN ALKAID FILL THE ROLE IN
WHICH FATE HAS CAST HIM?
IS HE SUFFICIENTLY AMUSING
TO WARRANT ALL THIS WORK?
- TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
TAITO IS NOT THE SORT TO LET
HIMSELF BE DEFEATED BY YOU.
NOR FOR THAT MATTER ARE
LAILA, RYUKO... OR HOSEI!
- SO IN OTHER WORDS, THEY'LL
BE QUITE THE DIVERSION INDEED.
- ( gasps )
BUT THERE'S NOT
EVEN A DRAFT IN HERE.
- ( Hosei yells )
- HELP ME, LAILA!
THESE GUYS EVER
GIVE UP OR WHAT?
I'M SAVED!
- HEY.
- THERE YOU ARE!
WHERE THE HELL HAVE
YOU BEEN ALL NIGHT?
- DID LADY KOEI FIND YOU YET?
- WHAT DOES MY MASTER
HAVE TO DO...
- MORON!
WHAT? YOU THINK WE'RE
JUST TAKING IN THE NIGHT AIR?
SHE WENT OUT LOOKING
FOR A CERTAIN SOMEBODY
HOURS AGO NOW
AND HASN'T COME BACK YET!
- THEY'RE ALL YOURS!
- HOSEI!
- THAT LITTLE SON OF A...
- GREAT. JUST WHAT WE
NEED, ANOTHER DISTRACTION.
- WHAT?
- WAY TO TAKE HIM DOWN, RYUKO.
THE HELL'S WRONG WITH YOU?
( laughs )
HEY! YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO STAY DOWN!
- I DON'T THINK
THESE ARE ORDINARY MEN.
- YOU THINK?
- WHERE ARE YOU, MASTER?
MASTER!
- WELL LOOK
WHO CAME BACK.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU KNOW RUNNING OFF LIKE
THAT JUST WORRIES ME.
- WELL, I WASN'T
GONNA BE GONE LONG.
BUT THEN ALL THIS STUFF...
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO ACT LIKE SUCH
A BRAT EARLIER, IT'S JUST...
- OH, HOSEI. THERE'S NO
NEED FOR THAT, REALLY.
- COME ON! GIVE ME A
BREAK. I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
( chuckles )
- HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- JUST CLIMB ON. YOU'RE
EXHAUSTED, I CAN TELL.
THE YEARS ARE CATCHING UP.
SERIOUSLY THOUGH, GET ON.
TAITO AND THE OTHERS
ARE WAITING FOR US.
- VERY WELL.
DON'T YOU DARE FALL.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT YOU.
HEY, YOU'RE MUCH LIGHTER
THAN I THOUGHT YOU'D BE.
- OF COURSE I AM,
SILLY. LOOK AT MY FIGURE.
- SO, I'VE NEVER DONE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
- MASTER?
- HMM?
- WOULD YOU... WOULD YOU BE
UPSET IF I WENT WITH LAILA
AND THE GUYS TO THE CAPITAL?
- HONESTLY, WHAT A QUESTION.
WHY IN THE WORLD WOULD
I BE UPSET WITH YOU FOR THAT?
YOU STILL HAVE
SO MUCH TO LEARN.
THE BEST REMEDY
FOR THAT IS EXPERIENCE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HOSEI, PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL TAKE CARE
OF TAITO AND THE OTHERS.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO
YOU ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- FATE MAY HAVE BROUGHT
THE FOUR OF YOU TOGETHER.
BUT IT IS FRIENDSHIP
THAT WILL BIND YOU.
IF I LEAVE YOU WITH NOTHING
ELSE, PLEASE REMEMBER THAT.
- FRIENDSHIP?
- WHAT I'M SPEAKING
OF TRANSCENDS FATE.
SOMETHING RICHER
AND MORE BRILLIANT
THAN EVEN THE STARS
RESONATES BETWEEN TRUE FRIENDS.
- OH, YEAH, I
MEANT TO TELL YOU,
I RAN INTO SOME PRETTY
NASTY CUSTOMERS EARLIER.
EVERY TIME I TOOK THEM DOWN
THEY'D COME RIGHT BACK UP.
IT'S LIKE THEY WERE
INVINCIBLE OR SOMETHING.
- SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAD
A RUN-IN WITH THE UNDEAD.
- THE UNDEAD?
- YES, CORPSES.
WELL, SO TO SPEAK.
THAT WHICH NO LONGER LIVES,
AND CANNOT BE KILLED.
- BUT THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME WAY TO DEAL WITH THEM!
- THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY.
THE FOREHEAD...
STRIKE THEIR BROW,
AND ONCE AGAIN THEY'LL
RETURN TO THE EARTH.
- AH-HA! THEN THE
FOREHEAD IT'LL BE.
YOU SURE DO HAVE A LOT
OF THINGS RATTLING AROUND
IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS, HUH?
- NATURALLY...
I'M LADY KOEI, THE FOUNT
OF KNOWLEDGE, AFTER ALL.
DON'T YOU FORGET IT.
- NEVER. I'M PROUD
YOU'RE MY MASTER.
JUST MY LUCK.
I FINALLY PRAISE HER AND
SHE FALLS ASLEEP ON ME.
- THAT WAS A BIT AWKWARD.
BUT, I HAVE TO
GIVE HER CREDIT.
MOST FOLKS WOULD'VE DIED
IN A FRACTION OF THE TIME.
NOW, THEN, THE REAL FUN
SHALL BEGIN IN EARNEST.
- SERIOUSLY, WHAT THE
HELL WERE YOU THINKING?
YOU COULD'VE AT LEAST
STAYED BEHIND TO HELP US
FIGHT OFF THOSE UNDEAD
CREEPS OR WHATEVER THEY WERE!
- I COMPLETELY AGREE.
FORTUNATELY, THEY RETREATED
BEFORE THE SITUATION
BECAME TOO MUCH FOR
US TO HANDLE ON OUR OWN.
IF THEY HADN'T,
THOUGH, WHO KNOWS?
- AH, COME ON.
DON'T BE THAT WAY.
FOCUS ON THE
HERE AND NOW.
YOU BOTH CAME OUT
OF IT UNSCATHED.
RIGHT, MY DARLING?
- ACTUALLY, AS A MATTER OF
FACT, I CAN SEE WHY THEY'RE MAD.
YOU WENT FROM BEING
A CHILD TO A COWARD.
- WHOA. I THINK I COULD
LISTEN TO YOU SCOLD ME ALL DAY.
- PLEASE DO GO ON!
- SHUT YOUR FACE!
- IN ANY EVENT, WE'D BE
IN WELL OVER OUR HEADS
IF THEY ATTACKED AGAIN.
OUR ANSWER FOR THE MOMENT
AT LEAST SHOULD BE RETREAT.
BEFORE SUNSET,
IF LADY KOEI AGREES.
- Hosei: TRUST ME,
THERE'S NO NEED.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THEY HAVE A WEAK SPOT.
AND I, IT ALSO HAPPENS,
KNOW EXACTLY WHAT THAT IS.
RIGHT HERE...
HIT THE FOREHEAD AND
EVEN YOUR HEARTIEST
- UNDEAD FREAK'LL STAY DOWN.
- Koei: THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THE HEART IS WHERE THE
UNDEAD ARE MOST VULNERABLE.
HONESTLY, IT'S IN ONE EAR
AND OUT THE OTHER WITH YOU.
- YOU TOLD ME THE
FOREHEAD LAST NIGHT!
- I TOLD YOU
NO SUCH THING.
- "IN ONE EAR AND
OUT THE OTHER."
SORRY, "DARLING," I'M NOT READY
TO ACCEPT THAT YOU KNOW
SOMETHING KOEI DOESN'T.
- NICE GOING, SURE SHOT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN LISTEN RIGHT.
- BUT SHE... LOOK, I KNOW
WHAT I HEARD LAST NIGHT!
- LET IT GO. KOEI'S NOT GONNA
GET SOMETHING LIKE THAT WRONG.
YOU, ON THE OTHER
HAND, WELL, SURE.
- Hosei: COME ON! YOU
GOTTA BELIEVE ME, LAILA!
- ( grunts )
- MY ARM'S STARTING
TO HATE ME FOR ALL THIS
ENERGY I'VE PUT INTO IT.
I KNOW I COULD
DO THIS YESTERDAY.
- Koei: LET'S TRY A
CHANGE OF SCENERY.
- UH, OKAY?
- COME ALONG WITH ME.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- THIS IS WHERE HOSEI'S
TRAINING TOOK PLACE.
- NO KIDDING, HUH?
BET HE SPENT A LOT OF
HOURS HERE BEING DRILLED.
- SO, I GOTTA ASK.
IF HE'S SUCH A FLAKE NOW,
WHAT WAS HE LIKE BEFORE
YOU PUT YOUR FOOT DOWN?
HEY, I'M ALL FOR SERIOUS
TRAINING AND EVERYTHING,
BUT, AREN'T YOU TAKING
THIS A LITTLE TOO SERIOUSLY?
- ( shouts )
- WHAT THE HELL?
- JUST BACK
AWAY FROM HER.
- BUT WE... SHE AND I...
- TRUST US, IT'S
NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
- THE CONVERSATION THIS
MORNING TROUBLED ME.
SAY WHAT YOU WILL,
HOSEI IS A SKILLED WARRIOR.
HE DIDN'T GET THIS
FAR BY ATTENDING
POORLY TO WHAT
HIS MASTER SAYS.
I DON'T THINK HE
MISHEARD HER LAST NIGHT.
IF HOSEI IS CORRECT
ABOUT THE WEAK SPOT,
THE ERROR WAS LADY KOEI'S.
AND THE REAL KOEI
IS NOT PRONE TO MISTAKES!
- YOU MEAN, SHE...
- Shimei: BRAVO!
SHREWDLY DEDUCED.
- IT'S MOUSTACHE'S
DAMN ERRAND BOY!
- YOU! WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH
MY MASTER, YOU FILTHY BASTARD!
- WELL LET'S JUST SAY,
ON THE SUBJECT OF WEAK SPOTS,
THERE'S ONE IN YOUR THEORY.
THE LADY KOEI BEFORE
YOU IS THE GENUINE ARTICLE.
- THAT YOU WOULD DARE EXPLOIT
AN INNOCENT WOMAN AS A PAWN.
WHATEVER BLACK
ARTS YOU EMPLOY,
RELINQUISH YOUR
HOLD ON HER AT ONCE!
- AH, BUT YOU SEE, I CANNOT.
- JUST TURN HER BACK NOW
OR I'LL KILL YOU!
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
YOU SEE, MY FRIENDS...
- NO!
- ( screams )
- NO. WHAT THE
HELL HAVE YOU DONE?
- MASTER? NO!
- POOR LITTLE PHECDA,
THE ARCHER,
HIS BELOVED MASTER'S
LAST BREATH
EDDIES OUT WHILST
HE BEARS HER ON HIS BACK.
AND HE DOESN'T
EVEN KNOW.
- NO! NO, SHE...
- Hosei: YOU LIE!
- ( Shimei laughs )
- ISN'T THAT JUST
THE SADDEST THING?
SHE'S BEEN STONE-COLD DEAD
SINCE LAST NIGHT, YOU DAMN FOOL!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT? BUT HOW?
- MASTER. SHE CAN'T BE DEAD.
- OH, BUT HOW NOBLE SHE WAS.
EVEN AFTER I SKEWERED HER,
SHE BEGGED ME, TEARFULLY,
NOT TO TOUCH A HAIR ON ANY
OF YOUR PRECIOUS LITTLE HEADS.
NOT THAT THAT'LL
MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
- YOU EVIL SON OF A BITCH.
- YES, YES. THAT'S IT.
SHOW ME YOUR HATRED.
- LET IT SHINE OUT!
- DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, TAITO!
- ( roars angrily )
- TAITO!
- NO! THE HATRED
WILL CONSUME YOU!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SEETHE, ALKAID!
- ( yells )
- STOP THIS NOW!
YOUR BODY CAN'T WITHSTAND THIS
KIND OF POWER FOR LONG. PLEASE!
- TAITO! YOU MADE
KOEI A PROMISE
NEVER TO FIGHT IN
THE HEAT OF PASSION!
YOU OWE IT TO HER TO
TRY AND CONTROL YOUR ANGER!
PLEASE! STOP THIS NOW!
FINE! IF YOU WON'T
USE YOUR HEAD,
THEN MINE'LL HAVE TO
DO FOR THE BOTH OF US!
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, LAILA.
IF I CAN'T KEEP THE
PROMISE I MADE TO HER,
WHAT KIND OF EXAMPLE ARE
PEOPLE GONNA THINK SHE WAS?
THANK YOU.
- DAMN KILLJOYS.
OH, WELL, I LEAVE
THEM TO YOU, KOEI.
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA RUN?
- YES, I AM. WHAT WILL
YOU DO, THOUGH?
I THINK STAYING
TO FINISH THE FIGHT
PUTS YOU BETWEEN
A ROCK AND A HARD PLACE.
LEST YOU WOULD
HAVE HER DIE AGAIN?
- LOOK OUT!
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
- HIS MAGIC HAS GIVEN
HER INHUMAN STRENGTH.
SHE'S COMPELLED TO DESTROY US.
- RYUKO! NO! STOP!
- ( shrieks )
- TAITO! RYUKO!
HELP THEM, HOSEI!
- MASTER...
THIS... THIS ISN'T REAL.
I CAN'T DO IT!
I CAN'T FIGHT MY
OWN MASTER, LAILA!
I'M SORRY, I JUST CAN'T.
- YOU HAVE TO!
- WE... WE'VE BEEN
TOGETHER SINCE I WAS A KID.
IT'S MY FAULT THIS HAPPENED
TO HER BECAUSE I RAN AWAY
INTO THE WOODS LAST NIGHT
LIKE SOME STUPID LITTLE BRAT.
I...
I CAN'T DO THIS!
- THEN WHAT ARE
WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
- I DON'T KNOW!
- WE... WE CAN'T JUST...
GIVE IN TO THIS.
WE HAVE TO FIGHT!
- YEAH. KOEI WOULDN'T
HAVE WANTED...
FOR US TO JUST LET THIS HAPPEN.
- I'M SORRY, YOU
GUYS. SO SORRY.
WAIT, THAT'S...
- AND HOW EXACTLY
IS THAT A SHOT?
BUT MASTER, I TRIED!
- "TRY" MEANS NOTHING!
EITHER SHOOT AT THAT TARGET
WITH THE INTENTION OF
HITTING IT WITH ONE ARROW,
OR LAY DOWN THAT BOW.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE CHANCE
OF GETTING FED TONIGHT.
- NO!
HOLD ON...
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE STANDING
IN THAT EXACT SPOT FOR A REASON?
- ( both grunt )
- ARE YOU... ARE YOU
ASKING ME TO SHOOT?
- BUT...
NO, YOU CAN'T BE.
THAT ISN'T FAIR.
I COULDN'T BEAR TO BE
THE ONE TO KILL YOU.
- ( sobs )
DAMN YOU.
WHY IS IT ALWAYS ME
WHO GETS THE BRUNT END
OF YOUR CRUELTY, HUH?
WHAT'D I EVER DO?
- ( shrieks )
- HOSEI! YOU'RE NOT ALONE
IN THIS, YOU HEAR ME?
- ALL OF US WILL BEAR THE
WEIGHT OF WHAT HAS TO BE DONE!
- Hosei: MASTER...
THE BEST OF ME WILL ALWAYS
BE WHAT YOU PUT THERE.
THANK YOU.
- SEE THERE, DARLING?
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT!
- MASTER, WHAT'S WITH
YOU ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
FOR DINNER I'LL FIX WHATEVER
YOUR LITTLE HEART DESIRES.
WHAT'LL IT BE?
- GREEN PEPPER STEAK!
- GREEN PEPPER STEAK,
BUT, OF COURSE!
- ( both laugh )
- ( sniffles )
STUPID HAG-BEAST.
STUPID HAG-BEAST!
( sobs )
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryuko: BEFORE OUR FRIEND
CAN ABSORB THE STING OF GRIEF,
THE JOURNEY CONTINUES.
- Hosei: WHY ARE YOU SO
WORRIED, MY CHILD?
- Laila: ISN'T IT OBVIOUS
THAT HE'S HAVING TO FORCE
HIMSELF TO LAUGH LIKE THAT?
- Ryuko: BEING FORCED TO
STRIKE DOWN ONE'S MASTER
AND CHILDHOOD CAREGIVER...
- Taito: WE SHOULD DO
SOMETHING BESIDES JUST
STAND HERE AND TALK ABOUT IT.
- Ryuko: WE KNOW WHAT
HE TRULY DESIRES...
SOME ATTENTION FROM
YOU WOULD HELP.
- Laila: I TRIED, BUT JUST
COULDN'T GET THROUGH TO HIM.
- Ryuko: NEXT TIME
ON HERO TALES,
FRIENDS ARE A
COLD COMFORT IN
CHAPTER EIGHT,
"WHAT ECHOES IN THE GORGE."
- ( Hosei yells )