- TAITO.
- SO, THERE'S A LITTLE FIGHT
IN THE BOY AFTER ALL.
- I FEEL IT.
A DREADFUL POWER HAS AWAKENED.
- OH, THE CATASTROPHIC
DEEDS THAT HATRED
WILL SPUR YOU TO COMMIT.
WELCOME BACK, ALKAID.
IT'S BEEN SO MANY CENTURIES
SINCE YOU AND DUBHE
HAVE CLASHED IN
THE EARTHLY REALM.
WHAT A FIGHT IT'LL BE.
- ( screams )
- RYUKO.
- YES, SIR. I FELT IT, TOO.
- HE'S AWAKE. IT BEGINS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- OH. HOW TERRIFYING.
- ( grunting continues )
- NOT BAD. NOT BAD AT ALL.
YOU'RE QUITE VIGOROUS
FOR SOMEONE
WHO'S ONLY JUST WOKEN UP.
- ( grunts )
- ALAS, MY BOY.
IMMENSELY POWERFUL
THOUGH YOU SEEM TO BE,
I WOULDN'T COUNT ON LORD KEIRO'S
FULL SURRENDER JUST YET.
- ( screaming )
- HUH. NOW IF I DIDN'T
KNOW BETTER,
I'D SAY
HE WAS IMPROVING.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- WHAT... WHAT IS GOING ON?
TAITO. LAILA.
- ( screams )
- WHY IS MY
STAR SIGIL RESONATING?
IS THAT MARK ON TAITO'S
SHOULDER WHAT I THINK IT IS?
- HE BEARS THE MARK OF ALKAID.
MY SON'S DESTINY IS INTERTWINED
WITH THAT OF A WARRIOR GOD.
- WELL, WELL. WE LIVE
IN INTERESTING TIMES, DON'T WE?
- ( gasps )
- TAITO'S REACTING TO MY
OWN MARK, SIR.
HURRY AND USE THE DISTRACTION
TO GET YOUR DAUGHTER
OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
- UNDERSTOOD.
LAILA, LAILA! OH, NO.
- HE'S AVOIDING HER.
EVEN IN THE THROES OF
ALKAID'S TERRIBLE FURY,
PART OF HIM FIGHTS
TO SPARE HIS SISTER.
- ( grunting )
- AN AMATEUR MOVE.
- COME ON, SWEETHEART.
SPEAK TO ME.
- FATHER.
- I'M HERE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I WAS JUST DOING
THE LAUNDRY AND... TAITO.
- ( growls )
- WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO HIM?
- I'M AFRAID THE ANSWER TO THAT
QUESTION IS OUT OF OUR HANDS.
HE'S CONSUMED BY ALKAID'S RAGE.
- IF THE SOURCE OF YOUR POWER
IS WHAT I THINK IT IS,
THEN UNDERSTAND
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE IT KILLS YOU.
FORGIVE ME.
( screams )
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
YOU MONSTER.
- ( screaming )
- YOU WANNA KILL ALL OF US?
START WITH ME!
- LAILA!
- MY LADY, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
GET OUT OF HERE!
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE SUCH A PAIN, HUH?
LISTEN TO ME, TAI. YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A COMPLETE IDIOT! WAKE UP!
- ( gasps )
- ( exhales ) WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO, LAILA?
GIVE ME HEAD DRAMA?
- HEAD TRAUMA, MORON.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
I'M COVERED IN BLOOD.
WHAT IS THAT ALL ABOUT?
DID SOMEBODY JUST TROLL ME
DOWN THE SIDE OF A MOUNTAIN?
- SERIOUSLY? YOU MEAN ROLL ME
DOWN THE SIDE OF A MOUNTAIN.
- THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
IT'S INCONCEIVABLE.
- ( laughs ) I THINK
ALKAID'S MET HIS MATCH.
- ( birds chirping )
- NO ONE HELP ME OR ANYTHING.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE ALL THIS.
- IT WAS VERY COURAGEOUS
OF YOU TO TRY TO STEP IN
AND SAVE US LIKE THAT, MISTER?
- OH, HOW IMPOLITE OF ME.
I HAVEN'T FORMALLY
INTRODUCED MYSELF.
MY NAME IS RYUKO,
A MONK FROM THE TONG YO SHRINE.
THE HEAD PRIEST SENT ME.
- YOU CAME ALL THE WAY
FROM THE CAPITAL?
- YES, BUT PERHAPS ONLY BECAUSE
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I'D FIND.
DESTINY DOES LIKE TO
CATCH US OFF GUARD.
- LIKE FINDING MY BROTHER?
- HE AND I SHARE
A SIMILAR FATE.
ONE MIGHT SAY OUR PATHS
IN THIS WORLD
REFLECT THE
MOVEMENTS OF THE STARS.
WE BEAR THE KARMIC BURDEN
OF A BATTLE PLAYED OUT
IN THE HEAVENS ABOVE.
- MY FATHER DIDN'T WANT
TAITO TO LEARN THE TRUTH.
HE WANTED HIM TO KNOW
A NORMAL LIFE, A PEACEFUL LIFE.
GUESS DESTINY CAUGHT US
OFF GUARD.
YOU CAN'T BLAME HIM
FOR TRYING, THOUGH.
- Sonnei: THE HEAVENLY SPHERE
PIVOTS ON THE FORTUNES
OF THE GREAT DIPPER,
A CELESTIAL RETINUE COMPOSED
OF SEVEN BRILLIANT STARS
UPON WHOSE DEEDS
THE PRINCIPLE OF KARMA
IS SAID TO REST.
BUT JUST AS HERE IN
THE EARTHLY PLANE
YIN AND YANG HOLD SWAY,
SO, TOO, DO CONTRARY POLES
DEFINE THE GREAT DIPPER'S FORM,
DUBHE AND ALKAID,
THE WILD WARRIOR GODS
OF OLD FOREVER CLASHING,
CALLING THE
PEOPLE TO TAKE UP ARMS.
- THE DIPPER BEARERS
ARE AMONG US AGAIN, AREN'T THEY?
- INDEED. IN TIMES OF GREAT
TURMOIL, THEY DWELL THE LAND.
INCARNATE IN THE FORM
OF SEVEN HUMAN BEINGS.
EACH ONE BEARING A MARK
CORRESPONDING TO
A STAR OF THE GREAT DIPPER.
- FIVE OF THEM HAVE
A SPECIAL TASK.
MIZAR, MERAK, ALIOTH,
PHECDA AND MEGREZ
ARE KNOWN AS
THE QUINTESSENT,
OR THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS.
ALKAID AND DUBHE ARE KNOWN
AS THE WARRIOR GODS.
- THEY'RE PRETTY POWERFUL, HUH?
- SO, I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
THIS ALKAID GUY, RIGHT?
- ( chuckles )
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- SHUT UP!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS ALL CLEARLY BEYOND
HIS UNDERSTANDING.
HE MAKES JOKES BECAUSE
THE TRUTH ELUDES HIM.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THE NAME'S RYUKO, YEAH?
IF YOU WANNA CALL ME STUPID,
SAY IT TO MY FACE.
- I THINK THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE DID.
- AS I WAS SAYING, THE RIVALRY
BETWEEN ALKAID AND DUBHE
THREATENS THE VERY LAND ITSELF.
THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS
ACT AS LEVEES
AGAINST THE DEVASTATION
THEIR GRUDGE WILL INFLICT.
- SO, WHY SHOULD I CARE?
- BECAUSE I, TOO, BEAR A MARK.
MINE IS MIZAR.
I AM ONE OF THE FIVE.
- OH, BIG DEAL. I DON'T BUY
ALL THIS DESTINY STUFF,
SO, MIGHT AS WELL
JUST SAVE YOUR BREATH.
I'M MY OWN MASTER IN THIS LIFE
AND THAT'S THAT.
- ( Sonnei laughs )
EVEN YOUR DOUBT
IS DECREED, LAD.
NOT ONE OF US FORGES
HIS PATH THROUGH LIFE ALONE.
OF COURSE, YOU'RE WELCOME
TO BELIEVE AS YOU PLEASE.
- ( laughs )
- UH, GRANDPA.
- (scoffs ) LORD KEIRO AND
HIS MEN ARE ROUGHING IT, EH?
MUST BE PASSING THROUGH
AFTER CRUSHING SOME REBELLION.
SIGN OF THE TIMES.
- SO, YOU COULD NOT DESTROY HIM.
- AH, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT,
MY LORD. EVEN MIZAR JOINED IN.
ALAS, THE ONLY CASUALTY
WAS MY WARDROBE.
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
DUBHE AND ALKAID DEVOUR
EACH OTHER AS USUAL,
OR IS THERE ANY CHANCE...
- ENOUGH. THE HEAVENS HAVE
ORDAINED THAT HE SHOULD LIVE.
- YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO IGNORE HIM?
- I AM, YES. WHATEVER YOU CHOOSE
TO DO IS YOUR OWN AFFAIR.
- MY, MY, CRAFTY.
- BOY, LET US SEE
HOW MUCH OF AN OBSTACLE
YOU ARE WILLING TO BECOME.
- THEY'RE HEARTY AND CHEAP.
FROM OUR GARDEN TO YOUR TABLE.
FRESH PICKED ONLY JUST
THIS MORNING.
- ( children giggling )
- LOOK, IT'S TAITO.
- HI, TAITO.
- YOU'RE GONNA COME PLAY
WITH US, RIGHT?
- NO. NOT RIGHT NOW.
BUT WE'LL GO FISHING
REAL SOON, OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT.
- IT'S A DEAL.
- HEY, WAIT FOR ME.
- THE PEOPLE OF TAI SHAN
CERTAINLY TAKE
HARDSHIP IN STRIDE.
ONE CAN SCARCELY TELL
THERE'D BEEN A FIRE.
- WHAT? YOU EXPECT THEM
TO WALLOW IN MISERY?
REFUGEES TAKE JUST
AS MUCH PRIDE IN THEIR HOME
AS ANYBODY ELSE.
- HUH? I DIDN'T MEAN...
- ( chuckles ) IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE JUST SPEAKING YOUR MIND.
- SONNEI AND MY DAD WORKED HARD
ON THIS PLACE SO REFUGEES
WOULD HAVE A PLACE TO CALL HOME.
SO, DON'T GET ALL HIGH
AND MIGHTY.
- I APOLOGIZE.
I SPOKE OUT OF TURN.
PLEASE KNOW THAT I
RESPECT THEIR TENACITY.
- GOOD. APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
THESE PEOPLE ARE LIKE
FAMILY TO ME.
I LOOK UP TO THEM. ALWAYS HAVE.
KANYO. WE'LL BE BACK TO SEE YOU
AGAIN REAL SOON. PROMISE.
- IT'S A TRAGEDY.
SO MANY FINE WARRIORS
LOST IN ONE NIGHT OF BLOODSHED.
- THEY'RE OWED MORE THAN THIS.
A LOT MORE.
I'LL AVENGE THEM. IF IT TAKES
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- Soei: WHICH WON'T BE LONG
IF YOU RUN AFOUL OF ME.
- UH, FATHER.
- I FORBID YOU TO TAKE
ANY ACTION, TAITO.
THE BUSINESS OF
THE QING LONG PLATOON
IS SELF DEFENSE,
PURE AND SIMPLE.
I WILL NOT HAVE ONE OF OUR OWN
ACTING LIKE A MERCENARY.
- SO, WHAT?
WE ACCEPT IT AND MOVE ON?
TOO MANY GOOD PEOPLE
DIED FOR US
JUST TO LOOK
THE OTHER WAY!
- SILENCE!
ANGER AND HATRED ARE
BEGETTERS OF CATASTROPHE.
ESPECIALLY IN YOUR CASE.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT THIS ISN'T THE WAY.
- ( sighs )
- ( grunts )
- HIS SPEED IS ASTONISHING.
- I'LL LEAVE YOUR CHANGE
OF CLOTHES RIGHT HERE.
- THAT'S THE STUFF.
- TAITO.
- YEAH?
- YOU UNDERSTAND IT'S MY HOPE
THAT ONE DAY YOU'LL SUCCEED ME,
AS LEADER OF
THE QING LONG PLATOON.
- WELL, SURE.
THAT'S THE IDEA, RIGHT?
HAVE THINGS CHANGED
OR ARE YOU JUST BEING WEIRD?
- ( both laughs )
- DAMN KIDS.
- LET ME ASK YOU.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- EVER HEARD OF SOMEBODY
NAMED LORD KEIRO?
- KEIRO? THE ONLY MAN
I KNOW WITH THAT NAME
IS AN IMPERIAL GENERAL.
- SO, HE'S A PART
OF THE GOVERNMENT.
- WHERE'VE YOU HEARD...
- YOU HAVE TO LOAN ME
SOME MONEY.
- HUH?
- MONEY?
- I HAVE TO GO.
I HAVE TO LEAVE
FOR THE CAPITAL RIGHT NOW.
THE GUY WHO DID THIS TO US.
THAT'S WHERE HE IS.
- ( birds chirping )
- THIS ISN'T JUST RECKLESS,
IT'S SUICIDE.
- WELL, HE IS AN IDIOT.
- WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO DISSUADE THE BOY NOW.
- HEY, YOU KNOW, YOU'VE
ALWAYS WANTED ME TO SEE
THE CAPITAL FOR MYSELF.
- CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH.
- ONE OF THE EMPEROR'S OWN,
RAIDING OUR TEMPLE AND REDUCING
TAI SHAN TO EMBERS.
- DO YOU THINK
THE EMPEROR'S BEHIND IT?
- NO. IT'S MORE LIKELY
THAT KEIRO ACTED ALONE.
KEEP IN MIND HE WAS AFTER
THE LEGENDARY SWORD OF RULE.
SOMETHING THE EMPEROR
WOULD MUCH PREFER STAY
SAFELY HIDDEN AWAY.
- SO, THEN, THIS KEIRO GUY
WANTS TO USURP THE THRONE.
- WORSE YET. SUPPOSE HE'S
NOT JUST A USURPER
BUT DUBHE HIMSELF.
- IT CAN'T BE!
- NO! DUBHE AND ALKAID
HAVEN'T APPEARED IN
THE SAME ERA FOR AGES!
IT'S UNTHINKABLE!
- ON THE CONTRARY,
GIVEN DUBHE AND ALKAID'S
ENORMOUS POWER,
THE THOUGHT OF THEIR OCCUPYING
THE SAME STAGE, SO TO SAY,
IS A HUMBLING ONE, YES.
BUT, ETERNAL WARFARE
IS THEIR DESTINY.
WHETHER THEIR BATTLE
CONFINE ITSELF TO THE STARS
OR ERUPT INTO
THE LESSER SPHERES.
- ALL THE MORE REASON
NOT TO LET HIM GO.
- HUH?
- AND IF IT'S HIS FATE?
- HIS FATE. YOU AND THAT WORD.
- RYUKO. IT'S TIME I UNVEILED
THE PURPOSE OF YOUR PRESENCE.
I WISH FOR YOU TO ACT
AS TAITO'S CUSTODIAN.
- CUSTODIAN?
- AWESOME THOUGH IT IS,
THE POWER OF ALKAID MAY PROVE
OVERWHELMING TO A BOY HIS AGE.
HE NEEDS THE GUIDANCE
OF ONE WHO HAS MASTERED
THEIR STAR.
- IF MY STAR DECREES IT,
I SHALL DO SO.
HOWEVER, AS ONE OF
THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS,
IT IS MY DUTY TO PREVENT
HIS AND DUBHE'S COLLISION
FROM WREAKING HAVOC
ON THIS WORLD.
AND I WILL HOLD TO THAT
WHATEVER THE COST.
- NOW LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
IF I LOSE, I FORGET ABOUT
MOUSTACHE AND LIVE IN TAI SHAN
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
SO LET'S GO.
- INDEED.
- BE WARNED. I HAIL FROM
A VERY OLD SECT.
SKILLED IN THE
EIGHT GREAT STYLES. BEGIN!
- HEY, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU GET TO USE A WEAPON?
- THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A FAIR FIGHT
IN THE REAL WORLD, MY FRIEND.
EACH OF THE ETERNAL CHAMPIONS
BRANDISHES A WEAPON TAILORED TO
THEIR OWN SPECIFIC ATTRIBUTES.
AS MIZAR, THIS STAFF
IS AS MUCH A PART OF ME
AS THE ARM THAT WIELDS IT.
- OH, I SEE.
I HAIL FROM THE SAME SECT
AS YOU, BUDDY. THE EIGHT STYLES
ARE MY BREAD AND BUTTER.
MY WEAPON IS MY FIST!
( screams )
( groans )
OKAY. THAT KINDA HURT.
- IT'S CALLED CHANNELING.
A SECRET FIGHTING TECHNIQUE
THAT ENABLES ONE'S WEAPON
TO BECOME A CONDUIT
FOR THE BODY'S NATURAL ENERGIES.
WHEN LAST WE FOUGHT
I USED A TREE BRANCH.
TONIGHT MY TRUE WEAPON.
ONE HIT IS ALL I NEED!
( screams )
( gasps )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT. CAN
CHANNELING BE AN INNATE SKILL?
- SO, ONE HIT
IS ALL YOU NEED, HUH?
- IN ABSENCE OF A WEAPON,
THE BODY ITSELF HAS BECOME
HIS CONDUIT.
IMPOSSIBLE!
- OH, I'LL SHOW YOU IMPOSSIBLE!
- ( grunting )
- ( screams )
- FATHER.
- WHAT IS IT?
- YOU'LL PROBABLY SAY NO.
BUT I HAVE A FAVOR TO ASK.
- WELL, NOW, ISN'T THIS
A COINCIDENCE?
- HUH?
- TAITO, I HAVE NEVER
ENCOUNTERED YOUR LIKE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
A LITTLE REMATCH SOMETIME?
- DEFINITELY.
- AND A DRAW IS NOT
THE SAME THING AS A LOSS, RIGHT?
GET READY, CAPITAL, HERE I COME.
- GOT SOMETHING YOU WANT TO SAY?
- I HAVE BEEN APPOINTED
AS YOUR CUSTODIAN.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED ME.
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT
KIND OF TROUBLE YOU'LL
GET YOURSELF INTO OUT THERE
WITHOUT SOMEONE
TO WATCH YOUR BACK.
- JUST TRY TO KEEP UP.
- ( giggles )
- DON'T EVEN START, LAILA!
- IS THIS YOUR IDEA
OF SLIPPING PAST ME, GENIUS?
YOU'RE ABOUT AS STEALTHY
AS AN AVALANCHE.
- I'M COMING TOO, BY THE WAY.
- AH.
- OH, JUST FACE IT, YOU NEED ME.
EVEN WITH RYUKO IN TOW,
WITHOUT A LADY'S INTUITION,
YOU'LL BE HELPLESS.
HONESTLY, IS THERE ANY CREATURE
IN THE WORLD MORE PATHETIC
THAN A MAN?
- UH, YOU DO KNOW
THAT I'M A MAN, RIGHT?
- THAT MOUTH IS GONNA GET
A FAT LIP ONE OF THESE DAYS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
WHO EVEN CARES?
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT TAGGING ALONG.
NOW GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- FINE THEN. YOU WANNA
TRAVEL BROKE, GO RIGHT AHEAD.
HOPE YOU CAN SEW
IF YOUR CLOTHES GET TORN.
OH YEAH AND YOU'LL HAVE
TO DO WITHOUT THIS.
FATHER'S LOANING IT TO YOU
ON THE CONDITION THAT
I TAG ALONG.
WELL, GUESS THAT'S SETTLED
THEN. LET'S MOVE OUT.
- HEY, DON'T TAKE THE LEAD.
THIS IS MY JOURNEY.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONE
CRAWLING THE SHOTS.
- YOU MADE A WISE CHOICE
IN LETTING HIM GO.
- EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
HE'S THE CLOSEST THING
TO A SON I'VE GOT.
I'D MUCH RATHER HE STAYED.
- I'M SORRY TO PUT YOU
IN SUCH A DIFFICULT POSITION.
YOU HAD TO SACRIFICE
A DAUGHTER AS WELL.
- HE NEEDS HER. SHE MAY JUST
BE THE ONLY HUMAN BEING
ABLE TO STILL THE RAGING
TEMPEST IN HIS HEART.
- MORTALS CANNOT REDIRECT
THE HEAVENLY COURSE
OF THE STARS.
BUT TAITO, MY LAD,
DESTINY'S NO PUPPET SHOW.
YOU CAN IN FACT CHOOSE
TO BE YOUR OWN MASTER
IN THIS LIFE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: THE JOURNEY'S
FIRST STEP BRINGS US
FACE TO FACE
WITH A CRUEL REALITY.
- Taito: THIS IS A LOAD OF CRAP.
POOR PEOPLE HAVE TO DIE JUST
SO RICH BASTARDS LIKE HIM
CAN CLEAR OUT WITH EVERYTHING?
WELL, NOT ON MY WATCH!
- Ryuko: TAITO, UNTIL A WARRIOR
LEARNS SELF-CONTROL,
THINGS DO NOT
AUGER WELL FOR HIM.
YOU MUST TAKE THAT TO HEART.
- Koyo: TAITO, I'LL HAVE
TO REMEMBER THAT NAME.
- Taito: THAT'S NOT
GONNA HAPPEN.
YOU MADE A PROMISE TO COME
WITH ME TO THE CAPITAL
AND I'M GONNA HOLD YOU TO IT.
- Ryuko: NEXT TIME,
ON HERO TALES,
THE PLIGHT OF THE WRETCHED
STRENGTHENS THE BOND
BETWEEN NEWFOUND FRIENDS
IN "CHAPTER THREE, THE PLEDGE
OF ENERGY MANIPULATION"
- Taito: I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO DEAL WITH PISSANTS LIKE YOU.