- Taito: NO. THERE'S JUST NO
WAY. TELL ME YOU'RE LYING.
- KEIRO SEALED OFF
THE CITY GATES
SO THOSE LIVING CORPSES COULD
SLAUGHTER THE PEOPLE
WITHOUT MERCY.
IT'S SO HORRIBLE I DIDN'T
EVEN BELIEVE IT MYSELF
WHEN I FIRST HEARD.
- HOW COULD HE?
- THAT CANNOT BE ANSWERED.
I KNEW HIS REIGN
WOULD BE BLOODY.
BUT I THOUGHT SURELY HE WOULD
START WITH HIS SWORN ENEMIES,
NOT INNOCENT SUBJECTS.
- THOSE PEOPLE WERE THERE
TO WISH HIM WELL.
THEY WANTED TO CELEBRATE THEIR
WAR HEROES' VICTORY WITH HIM.
BUT HE...
- I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT AT ALL.
HOW COULD SOMEONE BE
SO TWISTED THEY COULD JUST
KILL PEOPLE LIKE THAT?
- KEIRO TOOK MANY PATHS
LINED WITH BLOOD AND TREACHERY
TO ACHIEVE THE POWER
HE SO DESIRED.
IT WAS HIS ULTIMATE GOAL TO RULE
THE PEOPLE OF THE XIAN EMPIRE
OR TO EXTERMINATE THEM.
- IS THIS IT? IS EVERYONE DEAD,
THE "PEACE" HE TALKED ABOUT?
- IT'S LIKE HELL ON EARTH.
THE CAPITAL'S A PLACE
OF TORMENT AND DEATH.
- Tokaku: NO. I FEAR IT'S FAR
WORSE THAN THAT, YOUNG LADY.
- THE PLAGUE SPANS THE EMPIRE.
- THE WHOLE EMPIRE?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryusho: ACCORDING TO
WHAT LITTLE WORD I'VE RECEIVED
FROM TEMPLES AROUND THE EMPIRE,
SIMILAR EVENTS
ARE OCCURRING ELSEWHERE.
UNHOLY MASSACRES
PERPETRATED BY THE LIVING DEAD.
LANDS ONCE VERDANT ARE NOW
STAINED BY BLOOD AND FIRES
RAGE RAMPANT
THROUGHOUT THE REALM.
MEN WHO ONCE LIVED IN HARMONY,
HOLD ONE ANOTHER
IN DEEP SUSPICION
AND LASH OUT AT THEIR
ERSTWHILE BRETHREN.
ALL THIS DESTRUCTION
CARRIED OUT UNDER THE BANNER
OF THE NEW EMPEROR, KEIRO.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND.
KEIRO SENT HIS LEGIONS OUT NOT
TO QUASH POCKETS OF REBELLION
IN THE EMPIRE AS HE SO CLAIMED,
BUT TO SEED THE LAND
WITH FRESH CORPSES
TO REANIMATE AND MURDER
THE LIVING.
- MASTER RYUSHO,
IS THE XUAN LANG PLATOON NOW
COMPOSED SOLELY OF THE UNDEAD?
IS RYUKO AMONG THEM?
- FEAR NOT, MY CHILD.
ALTHOUGH THE LAD'S MIND MAY BE
CLOUDED, THE LIGHT OF MIZAR
STILL BURNS ABOVE.
- THERE ARE STILL MANY IN
THE SCHWAN LONG WHO HAVE NOT YET
SUCCUMBED TO THIS AFFLICTION.
SOME HAVE TAKEN ARMS AGAINST
THEIR GRUESOME FORMER COMRADES
TO PROTECT THE CITIZENS.
- THIS MACABRE ARMY
IS THE CREATION OF SHIMEI.
UNLESS HIS THRALL
CAN BE UNDONE,
THEY WILL WIPE OUT THE EMPIRE
AND HUMANITY WITH IT.
- ONE SHOT TO THE FOREHEAD.
HIT THOSE WALKING BAGS
OF WORM FOOD RIGHT HERE.
WE JUST NEED TO LET
THE PEOPLE KNOW THAT!
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT. WITHOUT
THOSE UNDEAD CREEPS AROUND,
KEIRO WON'T HAVE
ANY KIND OF ARMY LEFT.
- THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN
UNLESS YOU TWO CAN
COME UP WITH A PLAN TO
PASS THAT INFORMATION ON
TO EVERY LIVING PERSON
IN THE EMPIRE.
EVEN IF ALL THE KILLING
WERE TO STOP TODAY,
SHIMEI WOULD HAVE A FRESH SUPPLY
OF BODIES TO USE AS HE PLEASED.
- WE'RE WASTING TIME.
ALL OF THIS TALKING
ISN'T GETTING US ANYWHERE.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS LET ME
TRACK THAT BASTARD DOWN
AND MEET HIM FACE TO FACE.
LIKE A WARRIOR. THEN HE'LL
BE DEAD AND THIS NIGHTMARE
WILL BE OVER.
I'M GOING TO THE CAPITAL
AT FIRST LIGHT TOMORROW.
MASTER RYUSHO, GRAND GENERAL,
I'LL LEAVE THE REAL EMPEROR
UNDER YOUR CARE.
- Ryuko: LORD KEIRO! LORD KEIRO,
PLEASE WAIT!
- WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
- SIR, ABOUT THE INCIDENT
IN JIALING SQUARE,
I CANNOT EVEN BEGIN TO
COMPREHEND WHY IT HAPPENED.
- ANY LOYAL CITIZEN WOULD GIVE
HIS LIFE IF THAT WAS MY WISH.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COULD YOU DO SUCH A THING.
THE FOUNDATION OF THE EMPIRE
IS ITS PEOPLE.
THEY ARE ITS LIFE AND FUTURE!
- SUCH CHILDISH IDEALS.
LOOK. IN THE EMPIRE
WHICH I REIGN,
THE WEAK HAVE NO FUTURE
SAVE DEATH.
I WILL RENDER THEM TO ASH
AND BID THEM RETURN TO
THE BARREN GROUND
UPON WHICH THEY TOIL.
IN THAT WAY, THEY ARE MUCH
LIKE THE WOMAN WHO
BURDENED ME WITH YOU.
IF AN EMPIRE CAN BRING
DEATH UPON ITS PEOPLE,
SURELY AN EMPEROR CAN BRING
DEATH UPON HIS EMPIRE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND NOW, KEIKO?
- YOU'RE WRONG. BLOOD IS
NOT CLEANSED WITH MORE BLOOD.
MOTHER'S DEATH WAS DECREED
BY FATE, NOT SOLELY BY
THE ACTIONS OF THE EMPIRE!
- THEN IT ALSO BE FATE THAT
CALLS UPON ME TO VIEW
THE EMPIRE'S DEMISE FROM
THE HILT OF MY BROADSWORD.
- NOW IS NOT THE TIME FOR DEATH.
THE TIME IS UPON US FOR
THE EMPIRE'S REBIRTH.
A TRANSFORMATION BEGOTTEN
BY THE PEACE AND PROSPERITY
OF WHICH YOU ONCE SPOKE.
PLEASE FATHER,
COME TO YOUR SENSES.
- IF YOU WISH TO
CALL ME YOUR FATHER,
YOU MUST HONOR ME AS SUCH.
YOU MUST MAKE MY DESIRES
YOUR OWN.
- FATHER, HOW CAN I
BELIEVE AS YOU?
- Koyo: WELL LOOK AT THAT.
DUBHE SHINES BRIGHTLY INDEED.
THE HEAVENS' WAY OF TELLING US
THEY SHARE OUR KNOWLEDGE
OF THE SKIRMISH TO COME.
- HIS STAR.
KEIRO'S CELESTIAL OTHER.
- ( yawning )
I GUESS IF THERE'S ONE THING
WE SHARE IN COMMON
WITH THE GUY,
IT'S LIKE IT OR NOT, WE'RE ALL
HELD TO WHATEVER THE KARMA
OF THE STARS
HAS IN STORE FOR US.
- KEIRO'S STAR IS ONE RULED
BY AGGRESSION AND BLOODSHED,
AS IS THE EARTHLY VESSEL
THAT CARRIES HIM PLAGUED BY
SUCH UNFORTUNATE BURDENS.
- HIS IS A DISMAL FATE.
HARD TO BELIEVE HE ONCE USED
THE GUIDING HAND OF COMPASSION
TO DIRECT HIS POWER TO AID
THOSE IN NEED.
BUT SUCH IS LIFE FOR THOSE WHO
BEAR DUBHE'S GHASTLY MARK.
- I DON'T THINK IT REALLY
WORKS THAT WAY.
I JUST DON'T BELIEVE
THAT IT'S TRUE.
I MEAN, I DON'T WANNA BE
DISRESPECTFUL TO WHAT GRANDPA
TAUGHT ME ABOUT ALL THAT STUFF.
BUT OUR LIVES DOWN HERE
HAVE NOTHING TO DO
WITH HOW A BUNCH OF LIGHTS
HAPPEN TO SHINE UP IN THE SKY.
KEIRO'S NOT THE WAY HE IS
BECAUSE OF SOME STAR.
IT'S BECAUSE HE'S NOT STRONG
ENOUGH TO BE ANY WAY ELSE.
- Ryusho: SO YOU'D DENY THE ROLE
OF THE STARS ALTOGETHER?
- Taito: YES, I WOULD.
I MAY BE ALKAID AND HE'S DUBHE.
BUT AFTER ALL
THE SUFFERING HE'S CAUSED,
I KNOW THAT I'D STILL BE
ON MY WAY TO THE CAPITAL
TO KICK HIS ASS NO
MATTER WHO I WAS.
SO YOU GUYS SHOULD JUST FORGET
ABOUT BEING THE DIVINE WARRIORS
AND COME TO THE CAPITAL
WITH ME IF YOU THINK
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
- ( laughing )
SO YOU MEAN THE CENTRAL FIGURE,
THE BOY RULED BY ONE
OF THE MOST POLARIZING STARS
TO WHOM WE HAVE SWORN
BLOOD ALLEGIANCE.
THE ONE AT THE CENTER
OF THIS WHOLE COSMIC DRAMA,
CLAIMS THIS IS
THE PRODUCT OF CHANCE? HA!
( laughing )
- ARE YOU LAUGHING AT ME?
- NOT AT ALL.
IN FACT, MY RESPECT FOR YOU
HAS GROWN, MY FRIEND!
- I THINK TAITO MAY
HAVE A POINT.
AFTER ALL, THE ONE OF US
WHO'S FOCUSED SO RIGIDLY
ON THE LIGHT OF THE STARS ABOVE.
- WELL, WE CAN ALL AGREE
THAT HE'S THE ONE WHO'S
COMPLETELY LOST HIS BEARING
ON THE EARTHLY PLANE.
- THAT'S TRUE.
BUT SERIOUSLY, TAITO,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
FIGURING ALL THIS STUFF OUT NOW.
I'VE COME ALONG WITH YOU
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO STUPID
TO BE BY YOURSELF,
NOT BECAUSE YOU'RE ALKAID.
- ONCE AGAIN, THE LADY'S RIGHT.
YOU BIG OL' IDIOT!
- NOBODY ASKED YOU, YOU JACKASS.
- HEY, IF LAILA SAYS IT'S TRUE,
IT'S TRUE!
- ( laughing )
CUT FROM THE SAME CLOTH
AS YOUR FATHER.
ONLY SOEI AND NOW ALKAID
HAVE BEEN BOLD ENOUGH
TO CALL SONNEI'S
TEACHINGS MALARKEY.
- HEY, COME ON. I DON'T KNOW
IF I'D GO ALL THAT FAR!
- OOH! WHEN WE GET BACK
HOME TO LIAN TONG,
I AM SO GONNA TELL GRANDPA
WHAT YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN
SAYING ABOUT HIM.
- THERE'S, UH...
NO NEED FOR THAT.
IT WOULDN'T BE
CONSTRUCTIVE, CHILD.
- THE LADY'S RIGHT AGAIN!
- BAH! SHUT YOUR FOOLISH MOUTH,
YOU HALF WIT!
- NOW, NOW, YOU MUSN'T
OVEREXCITE YOUR HEART,
MASTER RYUSHO.
- I WILL BE JOINING TAITO
WHEN HE LEAVES TOMORROW.
I ASK YOU KEEP WATCH
OVER OUR GUESTS.
PROTECT THEM WITH YOUR LIVES.
I EXPECT NO LESS FROM YOU.
GOT IT?
- Crewman: CAPTAIN, PLEASE,
TAKE ME WITH YOU!
- Crewman 2: ME TOO!
- Crewman 3: ME TOO!
- Crewman 4: ME TOO!
PLEASE, CAPTAIN!
- COME ON. THIS JOURNEY TO
OUR ONCE FAIR CAPITAL
IS TO HAVE THE
FINAL BOUT WITH KEIRO.
I'LL HAVE MY HANDS FULL ENOUGH
WITHOUT HAVING TO MAKE
YOUR FUNERAL ARRANGEMENTS.
- I WOULDN'T BE A BURDEN
TO YOU, CAPTAIN.
I SWEAR I WOULDN'T!
- YEAH, WE'LL STAY OUT
OF YOUR WAY.
- I REALIZE WE ALL SHARE
A DESIRE TO SETTLE OUR VARIOUS
GRUDGES WITH KEIRO.
BUT STILL...
- YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
WE JUST WANNA HONOR
OUR PLEDGES TO STAY WITH YOU
'TIL THE BITTER END.
- PLEASE!
- WHEN THOSE BASTARDS
IN THE SCHWAN LONG PLATOON
BURNED DOWN MY VILLAGE,
YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
TO GIVE ME SHELTER!
- YOU SAVED ME RIGHT WHEN
THAT SERGEANT'S BLADE
WAS SAILING TOWARDS
MY NECK, CAPTAIN!
- WHEN I WAS STILL HUNGRY
AFTER DINNER THE OTHER NIGHT,
YOU GAVE ME YOUR LEFTOVERS!
- ( chuckling )
- LISTEN TO ME, CAPTAIN,
NO MATTER HOW ROUGH
THE WATERS MAY HAVE BEEN,
WE HAVE ALWAYS BRAVED THEM
TOGETHER IN THE SAME VESSEL.
THIS TIME IS NO DIFFERENT, SIR.
- WE'LL NEVER LEAVE
YOUR SIDE, CAPTAIN!
- STOP BEING SO FOOLISH!
- ENKI, I...
- YOU WILL HONOR YOUR CAPTAIN
BY FOLLOWING HIS ORDERS,
BY PROTECTING OUR GUESTS.
REMEMBER OUR SWORN DUTY
TO THE WO JIN SQUAD
TRUMPS ANY OTHER BOND.
WE MUST REST FOR THE NIGHT.
I FEAR THE DAY TO COME
WILL BE THE LONGEST YET.
- A WORD.
- YES, CAPTAIN?
- I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR ONCE AGAIN FILLING
THE UNPLEASANT ROLE
OF DISCIPLINARIAN.
- THAT WASN'T MY POINT EXACTLY.
- IF I'M IN FACT ABLE TO AVENGE
YOUR BROTHER ENYU'S DEATH
AND RETURN HERE,
THERE IS A MATTER
I WOULD LIKE TO ADDRESS.
AND, UH, WE SHALL
DISCUSS IT THEN. FAREWELL.
- THAT DAMN FOOL.
HE'S HOPELESS.
ALL MEN ARE HOPELESS.
- AS LONG AS WE'VE
KNOWN EACH OTHER,
WE'VE NEVER HAD THE
OPPORTUNITY TO SIT DOWN
AND TALK AS FRIENDS.
- THAT WISE FOOL WAS
ALWAYS HOVERING ABOUT.
- A VERY APT DESCRIPTION.
SO THAT WAS THE REASON.
- WHAT DO YOU
SUPPOSE HE'S THINKING
ON THIS PORTENTOUS NIGHT?
- HIS MIND'S IN A FOG,
IN ABSOLUTE CONFUSION.
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S SO LIKE HIM, ALWAYS
GETTING LOST ALONG THE WAY.
- WHAT HE NEEDS IS SOMEONE
TO TAKE HIM BY THE HAND
AND GUIDE HIM
ALONG LIFE'S PATH.
RINMEI. YOUR HAND
SHALL BE HIS GUIDE.
- THAT'S GOOD.
IN FACT I HAVE
HIS FIRST LESSON READY.
ONE HE NEEDS TO LEARN.
- HEY, THANKS A LOT FOR
HELPING ME WITH THIS.
- NO PROBLEM.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
- SO. YOU'RE, UH...
YOU'RE GOING TO BE GOING WITH US
TOMORROW MORNING, AREN'T YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- YOU KNOW, IT'LL BE DANGEROUS.
WHEN WE MEET HIM FACE TO FACE
KEIRO WILL GO AT US FULL BORE.
I'M REALLY WORRIED THAT
NO ONE WILL BE ABLE TO
PROTECT YOU FROM HIM.
IF SOMETHING WERE
TO HAPPEN TO YOU,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IN
THE WORLD I WOULD DO.
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
THINGS WILL TURN OUT JUST FINE!
- LAILA! I'M A MAN ON MY KNEES
ASKING YOU.
PLEASE GET ON THAT BOAT
TOMORROW MORNING
AND GO SOMEPLACE SAFE
WITH ENKI AND THE OTHERS.
- HOSEI, I...
- I'M DEAD SERIOUS,
NOW MORE THAN EVER.
I CAN'T HOLD BACK. DON'T GO!
- I'VE HONORED MY WORD
TO MY FATHER THIS FAR
AND I'M NOT STOPPING NOW!
I SWORE I'D STAY WITH TAITO
'TIL THE END.
I CAN'T GO BACK ON MY PLEDGE
AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
WHEN IT'S DONE,
I'LL GO TO FATHER'S GRAVE
AND TELL HIM EVERYTHING.
TELL HIM HOW HIS SON
AVENGED HIS DEATH.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- IN THAT CASE,
I'LL HAVE TO BE EVEN STRONGER.
I WILL MAKE SURE YOU KEEP YOUR
WORD AND I TAKE MY REVENGE,
BOTH WITHOUT FAIL.
- THIS IS AS MUCH AS I CAN
TELL YOU ABOUT THE
LAYOUT OF THE IMPERIAL PALACE.
MY ONLY REGRET IS THAT
I CANNOT LEND MY FISTS
TO THE BATTLE AHEAD.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S FINE. JUST KEEP THESE TWO
LOVEBIRDS OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
- SO THE DIE'S CAST. WILL
NOTHING STAVE OFF THIS BATTLE?
- KEIRO'S PAVED HIS ENTIRE WAY
TO THE THRONE WITH THE BODIES
OF INNOCENT MEN,
WOMEN, AND CHILDREN.
SOMEONE HAS TO MAKE HIM
ANSWER FOR THAT.
- I KNOW. AND YOU'RE SO STRONG.
BUT MY POOR FATHER
WAS A STRONG MAN TOO.
- I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH TAKI,
AND AFTER I'M DONE
WITH THAT BASTARD,
HE WON'T MAKE ANYONE
FEEL THIS WAY AGAIN.
- YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- THANK YOU, BROTHER.
- BUT AFTER THAT, YOU'LL HAVE TO
HONOR YOUR END OF THE DEAL.
TO FIX THIS BROKEN LAND
AND MAKE IT A PLACE OF HARMONY,
A PLACE OF TRUE PEACE.
BUT HEY I HAVE A FEELING
YOU CAN DO THAT.
AFTER ALL, YOU ARE MY OWN
FLESH AND BLOOD, RIGHT?
- WHO GOES THERE?
SHOKAKU!
- I'M RELIEVED TO SEE
YOU'RE UNHARMED.
- PLEASE, SIR. RELEASE ME
FROM THIS CELL AT ONCE!
DUBHE'S TERROR MUST BE STOPPED!
- MIZAR, YOU MUST
REMAIN IN THERE.
- BUT WHY MUST I?
SURELY YOU DON'T AGREE WITH
THE WHOLESALE SLAUGHTER
OF THE EMPIRE'S CITIZENS!
IT IS OUR DUTY TO INTERCEDE
ON THEIR BEHALF!
- OUR DIVINE RULER'S WORDS
ARE SACROSANCT.
IF YOU BELIEVE OTHERWISE,
YOUR RIGHTFUL PLACE IS
LOCKED AWAY IN THERE.
- HE BELIEVES AS FATHER?
- ( coughing )
- Guard 1: MY LORD!
- Guard 2: LORD SHOKAKU!
- Shokaku: NO. NOT YET.
THE TIME IS NOT RIPE.
- Shimei: YOU'VE EXCEEDED EVEN
MY MOST GRAND EXPECTATIONS,
BY A CONSIDERABLE MARGIN.
IN FACT IN ALL MY YEARS
I'VE NOT THE PLEASURE
OF HEARING SUCH A LOVELY
CACOPHONY OF SCREAMS.
- SUCH NOVELTY CAN BE FOUND
AFTER EONS OF HAUNTING
THIS ABJECT TERRAIN?
- YES, TRULY. THIS CAME AS
A SURPRISE TO ME AS WELL.
THE WAR HERO DRAWS THE SWORD
OF RULE CLAIMS HIS PLACE
ATOP THE EMPIRE'S THRONE,
AND DECREES DEATH
TO HIS SUBJECTS.
THE BETRAYAL OF A WHOLE
POPULACE IS QUITE THE COUP
IF YOU'LL PARDON THE EXPRESSION.
THEIR SAVIOR REVEALS HIMSELF
TO BE THEIR EXECUTIONER.
I'D ENDURE EONS MORE ON THIS
EARTH TO WITNESS THAT AGAIN.
BUT WHAT TITLE SHALL HISTORY
BESTOW UPON YOU?
THE BLOOD STAINED EMPEROR,
UNITER OF HELL AND EARTH.
- WHATEVER THE TITLE MAY BE,
YOUR NAME SHALL BE WRIT
LARGE ACROSS ITS PAGES.
- IF I DEIGN TO LEAVE A SCRIBE
ALIVE TO TELL THE TALE.
- ALL TOO TRUE, MY LORD.
AFTER ALL, YOUR AIM IS
TO CURE THE LAND
OF ITS "HUMAN AFFLICTION."
AND THAT TIME IS ANON.
AT PRESENT YOUR FOE
IS SAYING HIS TEARFUL FAREWELLS,
READYING HIS MIND FOR
THE ULTIMATE CLASH.
THIS WILL NOT BE THE FIRST TIME
YOUR PATHS HAVE CROSSED.
BUT INDEED IT SHALL BE THE LAST.
AND WHAT WILL BE BORN OF
THIS PAIRING SHALL BE DEATH.
- SHIMEI.
- YES, MY LORD?
- OUR PARTNERSHIP WAS BUILT
ON A COMMON GOAL.
ITS FRUIT, THE BATTLE TO COME.
I BELIEVED ONLY WHEN ALKAID'S
STRENGTH EQUALED MY OWN
COULD SUCH AN EVENT TRANSPIRE.
IF WE WERE TO FIGHT PREMATURELY,
THE EARTH MIGHT WITHSTAND
THE FALLOUT AND HUMANITY REMAIN.
THAT WAS NOT AN OPTION.
- THE YOUNG LAD HAS CHEATED
DEATH TIME AND TIME AGAIN.
BY FATE'S WILL, HE HAS SURVIVED
TO SEE THIS DAY COME TO PASS.
THE HEAVENS DO TEND TO GET
THEIR WAY, DO THEY NOT?
- INDEED. I NOW HOLD DOMINION
OVER THE EMPIRE,
AS WAS THEIR WILL.
- AND I SHALL SEE TO ITS
ANNIHILATION AS IS MINE.
I WILL ACCEPT NO LESS
THAN THE END OF HUMANITY!
- YES. "THE TOLL FOR PEACE,"
AS YOU SAY.
- ANNIHILATION, HOWEVER...
- MY LORD!
- ...IS NOT ENOUGH.
OF WHAT AVAIL IS THIS
DIVINE CARNAGE WITHOUT
MY OWN EYES TO BEAR WITNESS?
- LORD, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THIS NEWFOUND POWER
OF ALKAID'S NOW EQUALS MY OWN.
SO TO CLASH NOW WOULD
ASSURE MUTUAL DESTRUCTION.
I WOULD NOT BE ABLE TO OBSERVE
MY DESIRES MADE FLESH.
WHY IS THAT?
- UNHAND THE SWORD,
MY LORD!
- SHIMEI, YOU HAVE LABORED
DILIGENTLY TO STOKE THE FIRES
OF RAGE INSIDE MY NEMESIS.
FOR THAT I COMMEND YOU.
THE TORMENT AT YOUR HANDS
HAS BEEN THE CRUCIBLE
FOR HIS TRANSFORMATION.
AT THE TIME I FORGED
THIS PARTNERSHIP WITH YOU,
I SAW THE FUTURE DARKLY.
BUT NOW I SEE ITS CULMINATION
IS THIS MOMENT.
- YOU VERMIN! HOW DARE A MORTAL
TREAT ME IN THIS MANNER!
- A MORTAL, AM I?
( laughing )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MY LORD?
WHY WOULD YOU HARM
YOURSELF THIS WAY?
- YOUR CORPOREAL FORM IS
NOTHING MORE THAN A MARIONETTE.
THE SPIRIT ANIMATING THAT VESSEL
RESIDES IN THE WEAPON ITSELF.
WAN SHAWNG SHE MING.
TO ENSURE MY SURVIVAL
THROUGH THE CATACLYSM,
I MUST ABSORB THAT
SPIRIT INTO MY OWN.
- YOU'LL ACCOMPLISH
NOTHING BY THIS.
JUST ENSURE THAT YOUR BODY
SHALL BE MY NEXT VESSEL.
( screaming )
- OH, YES!
I CAN FEEL YOUR DEMONIC POWER
BECOMING ONE WITH MY OWN.
AND WITH IT I SHALL SEE
WORLD'S END!
- ( laughing )
THE HEAVENS HAVE CHOSEN WELL.
YOU ARE TRULY A GOD AMONG MEN.
YOU'VE DEFEATED ME.
I ACQUIESCE WITHOUT DISHONOR.
I CANNOT HOPE TO RESIST YOU.
WAN SHAWNG SHE MING
HAS BEEN SWALLOWED UP WHOLE.
I HAVE FOREVER BEEN INTEGRATED
INTO THE PERFECT FORCE
TO END THIS PLAGUE-RIDDEN WORLD
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
YOU ARE A TRUE MONSTER, DUBHE.
ONE FIT TO DEVOUR ALL HUMANITY.
SUCH DIVINE ENTERTAINMENT!
( laughing )
- ( screaming )
- Choka: MY LORD!
WHAT IS THE MATTER?
- ( Keiro still screaming )
I LEAVE MANKIND IN MY WAKE!
DESTROYER OF WORLDS.
DUBHE! WILD WARRIOR GOD!
( laughing )
- BEST OF LUCK
IN THE BATTLE AHEAD.
WE'RE ALL BANKING
ON YOUR SAFE RETURN!
- THANK YOU.
KEEP A CLOSE EYE
ON TAIGA AND THE REST OF 'EM!
- BROTHER, PLEASE.
SAVE OUR LAND.
WE SHALL PRAY FOR VICTORY!
- Taito: THIS'LL PROBABLY BE
OUR FINAL BATTLE.
AND WE MIGHT NOT ALL
SURVIVE TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
ARE YOU STILL WILLING TO ENTER
THE FRAY THIS ONE LAST TIME?
- YEAH. I'VE LIVED
MY WHOLE LIFE FOR THIS DAY.
- TRY AND STOP ME.
LAILA, I WILL PROTECT YOU
NO MATTER WHAT
WE MAY BE UP AGAINST.
THEY WOULD HAVE TO
TEAR ME APART TO GET TO YOU.
- THEN I GUESS I'D JUST HAVE TO
PUT YOU BACK TOGETHER.
- YOU WOULD, REALLY?
- RYUKO WILL MAKE HIS WAY
BACK TO THE PATH.
TOGETHER WE CAN ALL BE
THE HANDS THAT WILL HELP
TO GUIDE HIM THERE.
- IT'S UP TO ALL OF US
TO PULL THE EMPIRE
OUT OF THE DARKNESS AND HATRED
AND MAKE IT A PLACE
OF HAPPINESS.
A PLACE OF TRUE PEACE.
SO, LET'S MOVE OUT!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koyo: THE WILD DANCE OF THE
STARS REACHES A STATE OF FRENZY.
- STRIKE ME DOWN.
- YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND? I SAID
I'M NOT GOING TO KILL YOU!
- Ryuko: IF YOU FALL BY MY HAND,
THE MONSTER WILL
REIGN UNCHALLENGED!
- PRECISELY. ONCE A FIGURATIVE
PAWN, NOW A PAWN IN FACT.
- Laila: STOP HIM.
HE'S GONNA KILL TAITO.
RYUKO OR NOT,
WE CAN'T JUST STAND HERE!
- Koyo: FED BY SORROW,
INHUMAN FIGURES WRITHE
AND REVEL IN DESTRUCTION.
IN HERO TALES, CHAPTER
TWENTY-FIVE, "THE DUBHE GOD."
- Taito: NEITHER ONE OF US
SHOULD HAVE TO DIE.