- ( girl screams )
- LAILA, WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( sobs )
- THAT CAN'T BE GOOD, HUH?
- HMM.
NO, IT'S NOT GOOD.
WHAT HAVE WE WALKED INTO?
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in English )
- ( panting )
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles ) WELL, WELL.
- ( girl screams )
- WHAT?
- OVER THERE.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
WE'D RUN INTO EACH OTHER
OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE LIKE THIS?
WHAT LUCK. EIRETSU'S
GONNA BE REAL HAPPY
TO SEE THE TWO OF YOU.
- LINLIN, DON'T BE AFRAID.
I'M HERE TO PROTECT YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
I WON'T LET THEM
DO ANYTHING TO HARM YOU.
NOW, JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES.
- YEAH, BELIEVE ME, YOU DON'T
WANT TO SEE WHAT WE ARE GONNA
DO TO YOUR FRIEND, GIRLIE.
- I'M STILL A PROUD MEMBER
OF THE ZHANG JIN SQUAD.
DON'T THINK I'LL GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
- HA! THAT PACK OF LOSERS
IS A THING OF THE PAST.
( cackling )
( groans )
- ( all gasp )
- STAND ASIDE. THIS IS NONE
OF YOUR DAMN BUSINESS.
- WHEN I SEE BASTARDS
PICKING ON THE WEAK,
I MAKE IT MY BUSINESS, FRIEND.
AND FROM WHERE I'M STANDING,
YOU GUYS PRETTY MUCH LOOK
LIKE A BUNCH OF BASTARDS.
- WE LOOK LIKE A BUNCH
OF BASTARDS? IS THAT RIGHT?
- UM, THAT'S KINDA
WHAT HE JUST SAID.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT IT, THOUGH.
HE DOES MAKE A REALLY
GOOD POINT.
- ( yells )
( groans )
- HA!
- ( screams )
- WHO, WHO IN THE HELL
ARE YOU, PEOPLE?
- SOMEONE WHO'S GONNA
TEACH YOU A LESSON.
WHAT THE...
- YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THESE THREE.
- Man: HOSEI.
- HE CAUGHT MY ARROW
WITH HIS BARE HANDS.
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
YOU WANNA RUN.
- WE'LL GET YOU FOR THIS,
YOU HEAR ME?
THIS ISN'T OVER
BY A LONG SHOT.
- HELLO.
- YOU PICKED THE WRONG GUY TO...
- SOMEBODY'S NOT FROM
AROUND HERE.
SO, HOW FAR
HAVE YOU TRAVELED?
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
PLEASE SAY NO.
THEY CALL ME HOSEI.
WHAT SHOULD I CALL YOU?
- UM, LAILA.
- LAILA. OH MAN.
I COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
A BETTER NAME FOR YOU MYSELF.
- HEY, YOU STAY
THE HELL AWAY FROM HER.
- I'M WORKING HERE.
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
- YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
BUT I SMELL STUPIDITY.
- CHINJO, CAN I LOOK NOW?
- YES. EVERYTHING IS ALL RIGHT
NOW. YOU CAN OPEN YOUR EYES.
- THAT ARCHER. CAN IT BE?
- I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH
FOR YOUR HELP OUT THERE.
MY NAME IS CHINJO, BY THE WAY.
THE LITTLE ONE IS LINLIN.
- AND YOU MAY CALL ME RYUKO.
THIS IS MY FRIEND LAILA.
THE ONE STUFFING HIS FACE
LIKE THERE'S NO TOMORROW
ANSWERS TO TAITO.
WE'RE TRAVELING
TO THE CAPITAL TOGETHER.
FORGIVE MY SAYING SO,
BUT THIS PLACE HAS CHANGED
CONSIDERABLY
SINCE I WAS LAST HERE.
- YES, IT HAS. I'M CERTAIN
ON YOUR PREVIOUS VISIT,
WE WERE A THRIVING TOWNSHIP.
SADLY OUR PROTECTOR,
THE ZHANG JIN SQUAD,
HAS DISBANDED SINCE THEN.
ITS LEADER WAS A GOOD MAN,
BUT WHEN HE PASSED AWAY
THREE YEARS AGO,
THERE WERE NO MALE HEIRS
TO TAKE UP THE TORCH.
WE WERE PLUNGED INTO CHAOS.
- Laila: YOU MEAN THERE WAS
A FIGHT OVER WHO WOULD
SUCCEED HIM?
- EXACTLY. EIRETSU, HIS FORMER
RIGHT-HAND MAN, STAKED A CLAIM
TO THE TITLE THROUGH BLOODSHED.
SEVERAL OF US
TOOK A STAND AGAINST HIM.
- Man: UGLY MUTT.
- Ryuko: AND THE MAGISTRATES?
- IF THERE WERE ANY, THERE'D
HAVE BEEN NO NEED FOR
THE SQUAD IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I'M AN ORPHAN, YOU SEE.
I OWE THE LEADER
FOR TAKING ME IN.
TO HONOR HIS MEMORY,
I'VE TAKEN HIS DAUGHTER
UNDER MY WING.
SHE DESERVES TO SEE THIS TOWN
RESTORED TO ITS FORMER GLORY.
AS DO THE FAMILIES OF MY
COMRADES WHO WERE CUT DOWN.
- Taito: YOUR COMRADES?
- TAITO.
- WHO TOOK THIS EIRETSU'S SIDE?
WHERE ARE THEY?
- AH.
- WONDERFUL.
I DON'T SUPPOSE TELLING YOU
IT'S NOT OUR PLACE WOULD DO
ANY GOOD AT THIS POINT?
NO, YOU'VE GOT THAT
LOOK IN YOUR EYE.
- WE'RE THIRSTY, OLD MAN!
- I WOULDN'T SERVE THE LIKES OF
YOU A PINT OF MY OWN DAMN PISS.
- THAT A FACT?
- HEY, LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- YOU? EIRETSU, SIR,
THESE ARE THE GUYS.
- EIRETSU, HE MEAN YOU?
- ( scoffs )
I HEAR YOU LOT GAVE MY BOYS
A RUN FOR THEIR MONEY
EARLIER TODAY.
CHINJO, YOU LOOK WELL.
OLD MAN, STOP GAWKING
AND BRING US BOOZE.
- OH, JUST TAKE A SEAT.
PRETTY BALLSY FOR SOMEONE
WHO'S ABOUT TO GET WHUPPED.
- Hosei: LIKE HE'S GOT
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
( gasps )
- SON OF A... YOU'RE THAT JERK
WITH THE BOW!
- WOW. IMAGINE SEEING THAT
PRETTY FACE TWICE IN ONE DAY.
- ( chuckles ) COME ON, BABE.
DITCH THIS HOLE IN THE WALL
AND COME BACK TO MY PLACE.
YOU CAN EAT YOUR FILL
OF WHATEVER YOUR HEART DESIRES.
- YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, IDIOT?
WE JUST TEAMED UP WITH THE GUYS
WHO ARE GONNA TAKE YOU DOWN.
- HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT. SO GET LOST.
- HOLD ON, CHIEF. WHAT ARE YOU,
LIKE LAILA'S MAN?
- MY WHAT?
- HER MAN? NO, DUMBASS,
I'M HER BROTHER.
- YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
- I DON'T SEE IT.
- DID I SAY WE WERE TWINS?
- LINLIN, CHINJO. OH, YOU'RE
SAFE. THANK HEAVENS.
AFTER WE HEARD YOU HAD
GONE OUT TO VISIT
THE LEADER'S BURIAL SITE,
WE FEARED THE WORST
FOR YOU, SIR.
- YOU WANNA LAY IN THE GROUND
BESIDE HIM, WE CAN OBLIGE YOU.
- THINK I'M GONNA PASS
ON THIS ONE.
I ONLY JUST REPLACED THE BOW
I BROKE THIS AFTERNOON, GUYS.
- DISGUSTING.
- I'M STAYING IN THE
BIG MANSION UP THE ROAD
IF YOU HAPPEN TO CHANGE
YOUR MIND, SO...
- YOU COME WITHIN FIVE
OF HER AND I'LL MAKE YOU SORRY
YOU WERE EVER BORN!
- THE ARCHER DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE HE'S FROM AROUND HERE.
- HE'S NOT. JUST SOME DRIFTER
EIRETSU HIRED AS A BODYGUARD.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING. I'M A BIT
PREOCCUPIED IS ALL.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- ( dog barks )
- ( snores )
- BE QUIET.
HEY, WHERE'D HE GO?
- Hosei: THIS ONE'S CRAP.
( sighs )
SO IS THIS ONE.
COME ON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
- ( door creaks )
- DON'T SHOOT.
- YOU, YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE
STROLLING IN HERE LIKE THIS.
- YES, WELL, I'D LIKE
A WORD, IF I MAY.
- STAY BACK, PRETTY BOY.
I'M WARNING YOU.
- ( yells )
- WHAT THE...
- DON'T BE ALARMED. YOUR BODY'S
ENERGY IS MERELY PASSING
THROUGH MY OWN.
I'M ACTING AS AN AMPLIFIER.
( yells )
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THE SIGIL OF PHECDA.
- THE WHAT?
- ACCORDING TO LEGEND,
EACH OF THE SEVEN DIPPER
BEARERS CARRIES A MARK
UNIQUE TO THE STAR
UNDER WHOSE AUSPICES
HIS FATE IS DIRECTED.
THE SYMBOL YOU CARRY REPRESENTS
PHECDA, THE STAR OF THE ARCHER.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- YOU'VE NOT YET HELD THE BOW
THAT COULD WITHSTAND
YOUR STRENGTH, HAVE YOU?
ALL YOU DID WAS LET
THIS ARROW FLY,
AND YET IT SHATTERED TO
SPLINTERS RIGHT IN FRONT OF US.
BELIEVE ME,
I KNOW A THING OR TWO
ABOUT WHAT IT MEANS TO BE
SINGLED OUT BY DESTINY.
- ( gasps )
WHY? YOU'RE ONE OF
THE FIVE DIVINE WARRIORS.
WHY WOULD YOU SUBMIT
TO TAKING ORDERS FROM
A MAN LIKE HIM?
- DIVINE WARRIORS? WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU EVEN TALKING ABOUT?
I KNOW HOW THIS LOOKS,
BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO DO
AS MY REAL MASTER TOLD ME,
ALL RIGHT?
- YOUR REAL MASTER?
- HOSEI, THE RIGHT WEAPON
WAITS FOR YOU.
GO NOW AND FIND IT.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER? WHAT DID
YOUR MASTER TELL YOU TO DO?
- SHUT UP. IF IT WAS ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU WITHOUT
YOU HAVING TO ASK ME.
NOW GET OUT.
- HMM. VERY WELL, THEN.
FOR THE MOMENT I SHALL
LEAVE YOU IN PEACE.
BUT, YOU'D DO WELL
TO REMEMBER THIS,
THE WARRIOR GODS, DUBHE
AND ALKAID HAVE BROUGHT THEIR
FIGHT INTO THE EARTHLY SPHERE.
THE LINES ARE ALREADY
BEING DRAWN AS WE SPEAK.
KNOW THAT WHOEVER ALIGNS
THEMSELVES TO DUBHE,
I AM BOUND BY A SACRED DUTY
TO DESTROY.
- DUBHE? ALKAID?
YOU JUST MAKING THIS
STUFF UP AS YOU GO ALONG?
- SCOFF IF YOU LIKE, FRIEND.
IT ISN'T MY PLACE
TO MAKE YOU BELIEVE.
THAT PRIVILEGE BELONGS TO FATE.
- ( exhales )
( sighs )
( gasps )
- LIKE I CAN READ THIS.
OH, WAIT. THAT'S THE CHARACTER
FOR "BOW," ISN'T IT?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. IT'S ONLY ME.
- OH, HEY BOSS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- FUNNY. I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO ASK YOU THE SAME THING.
- YEAH. WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
- HMM?
- IT'S WHAT YOU MIGHT CALL
A PURCHASE ORDER FOR A SHIPMENT
OF NEW WEAPONS
I'VE GOT ON THE WAY.
- AH, FOR THE BIG SHOWDOWN,
YOU MEAN.
- YOU BET. THEY SHOULD BE
ARRIVING SOMETIME
TOMORROW NIGHT.
AND, BY SUN UP THE NEXT DAY,
THE LAST HOLDOUTS WILL BE DEAD.
- I CAN COUNT ON YOU
TO BE THERE, RIGHT?
- DAY AFTER TOMORROW, RIGHT.
- I WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR THE WORLD.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT'S THIS ONE HERE?
- NOTHING SPECIAL.
- COME ON, BOSS. DON'T PLAY DUMB
WITH ME. I'M YOUR BODYGUARD.
I NEED TO KNOW WHAT KIND
OF WEAPONS YOU'VE GOT COMING IN.
I'M AN ARCHER. BOWS ARE MY LIFE.
HOW COME YOU HAVEN'T TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS ONE?
- AH, THE SHUANG CHAN BOW.
I'D ALMOST FORGOT.
- SHUANG CHAN BOW.
- ANOTHER STAR MOVES. DIVINE
WARRIOR PHECDA JOINS THE FOLD,
AND NEARS HIS FATE.
PREPARE TO CHOOSE SIDES,
OLD FRIEND.
- Laila: TONIGHT?
- YES. EIRETSU'S ORDERED
A HUGE STOCKPILE OF WEAPONS.
HE INTENDS TO LAUNCH A SURPRISE
ATTACK AGAINST YOU AND YOURS
FIRST THING TOMORROW MORNING.
- IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
- ( muffled ) I SAY WE HIT THEM
WHERE THEY LIVE TODAY BEFORE
THEY HAVE A CHANCE TO ATTACK.
- HEY, COULD YOU SAY THAT AGAIN
A LITTLE SLOWER, PLEASE.
AND WITHOUT A MOUTH
FULL OF SWEET BUNS?
- I SAID LET'S HIT THEM WHERE
THEY LIVE TODAY BEFORE
THEY ATTACK US.
IF WE CAN AMBUSH THE WEAPONS
SHIPMENT, THEY WON'T HAVE
A LEG TO STAND ON
AND WE'LL HAVE ALL
THEIR COOL STUFF.
- Ryuko: INTERESTING.
- YOU KNOW, COMING
FROM YOU, THAT'S ACTUALLY
AN EXCEPTIONAL IDEA.
- ( chuckles ) WOW, REALLY?
- THE MEANS BY WHICH THEY SOUGHT
TO AFFECT YOUR DOWNFALL,
WILL BE THE INSTRUMENTS
OF THEIR OWN RUIN.
- THERE'S POETIC JUSTICE
IN THAT. I LIKE IT.
- SO, THEN, TONIGHT WE'LL ATTACK
UNDER THE COVER OF DARKNESS.
- HMM.
- HERE WE ARE. HAVE AS MANY
AS YOU LIKE, SON.
- WHOA.
- LET'S GO OVER THIS AGAIN.
LAILA AND I WILL CALL THEIR
ATTENTION AWAY FROM YOU.
WHILE WE'VE GOT
THEM DISTRACTED...
- YEAH. FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
I GOT IT, ALL RIGHT? TRUST ME,
THIS WILL BE A BREEZE.
- OH GEE, THAT'S CERTAINLY
A LOAD OFF.
MY BROTHER, THE GENIUS,
SAYS IT'S GONNA BE A BREEZE.
- NOBODY WAS TALKING TO YOU.
- HEY, WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
I WAS JUST LOOKING
TO PLANT MY FOOT IN...
- LAILA, BABE. ARE YOU
EVER A SIGHT FOR SORE EYES.
CAN YOU BELIEVE MY LUCK?
DID YOU COME ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE TO LOOK FOR ME?
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- HEY, I TOLD YOU
TO STAY AWAY FROM HER.
- WILL YOU JUST RELAX?
WE'RE TRYING TO HAVE
A CONVERSATION.
- YOU ARE SO ON THE ROAD
TOWARDS AN ASS-KICKING
RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU EVEN
DOING OUT HERE?
- TECHNICALLY, I'M NOT
SUPPOSED TO SAY
BUT I'D NEVER LET A SECRET COME
BETWEEN ME AND MY SWEETHEART.
- SHUT UP. JUST TELL US ALREADY.
- YOU'RE NOT MY SWEETHEART, PAL.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS CRAP.
- HUH, WHAT IS THAT?
- Taito: WHAT THE HELL?
- Ryuko: I'M AFRAID THE SIEGE
MAY HAVE BEGUN.
- Taito: WHAT?
- Hosei: THEY'RE
DOING THIS NOW?
- BUT THEY WEREN'T SUPPOSED
TO ATTACK TILL DAWN.
- HEY, HOLD ON.
- LET'S GET MOVING.
WE'VE NO TIME TO LOSE.
- RIGHT.
- ( panting )
- HOW IS THIS HAPPENING?
- IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- WHY WOULD THEY MAKE
A MOVE BEFORE THE WEAPONS
GOT HERE?
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY COULD'VE
KNOWN WE WERE ON TO THEM.
- ( people screaming )
- ( cackling )
- OH, NO.
- WELL, WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE.
MY BODYGUARD
FRATERNIZING WITH THE ENEMY?
- I KNEW YOU WEREN'T
A MAN TO BE TRUSTED, HOSEI.
- TRUSTED?
- THERE WAS SOMETHING
IN YOUR ATTITUDE LAST NIGHT
I DIDN'T LIKE.
IT'S ACTUALLY WHAT DECIDED ME
ON ATTACKING NOW.
AS YOU CAN SEE FOR YOURSELF,
THE WEAPONS CAME
AHEAD OF SCHEDULE.
A PORTENT OF VICTORY
IF THERE EVER WAS ONE,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- ( gasps )
- WE HAVE TO GET LINLIN
AND CHINJO OUT OF THERE.
THE WHOLE PLACE WILL BURN TO
EMBERS IN A MATTER OF MINUTES.
THEY'LL BE KILLED.
- I'VE GOT THIS.
- DON'T MOVE ANY CLOSER.
- WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE THOSE THINGS?
- RATHER IMPRESSIVE, RIGHT?
CARE TO GUESS HOW MANY ARROWS
THEY CAN SHOOT AT ONCE?
LOOK, THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
YOU CAN DO TO SAVE THEM NOW,
SO, WHY DON'T YOU JUST SIT BACK
AND ENJOY THE SHOW.
- YOU MONSTER.
- TAITO, I LEAVE HIM TO YOU.
- RYUKO.
- KEEP HIS THUGS BUSY
WHILE I GET LINLIN
AND CHINJO TO SAFETY.
- YOU GOT IT.
- IDIOTS.
SHOOT MORE.
DAMN IT, TAKE THEM DOWN.
NO, THEY'RE NOT HUMAN.
WHAT? WHY CAN'T I...
- WHERE ARE YOU?
CALL OUT TO ME.
LET ME KNOW WHERE YOU ARE.
I'LL COME TO YOU.
- DAMN IT. THE FINEST
BOW EVER MADE, MY ASS.
STUPID PIECE OF JUNK
IS COMPLETELY USELESS.
- RYUKO, HURRY.
- OH, THANK GOODNESS,
YOU'RE SAFE.
- LET'S FINISH IT.
- INDEED WE SHALL.
LAILA, WATCH THEM.
- THIS IS IT.
THE SHUANG CHAN BOW.
- ( grunts )
- YOU LOSE, YOU BASTARD.
- Laila: NO!
- LAILA.
- LINLIN.
- CHINJO, CHINJO.
YOU HAVE TO GET UP, PLEASE.
- NOW I'VE GOTCHA.
- THAT'S IT, YES.
SHOW NO MERCY. KILL HER.
- LET HER GO.
- ( laughs ) IT'S TOO LATE, BOY.
- ( whimpers )
- ( laughs )
- AFTER EVERYTHING
IS SAID AND DONE,
I WILL BE THE ONE TO TRIUMPH.
- THIS IS IT.
I HAVE FOUND MY WEAPON.
HEADS UP.
I'M ONE HELL OF A SHOT, HA.
- ( laughs )
- CURSE YOU.
I WAS THIS CLOSE.
- YOU MAKE A BAD ARCHER,
OLD MAN.
HA, GUESS CROOKED
ARROWS CAN'T SHOOT STRAIGHT.
- COME ON.
WHAT'S WITH THIS THING?
- LINLIN, CLOSE YOUR EYES, OKAY?
( yells )
ALL DONE. YOU CAN LOOK NOW.
- ( giggles )
- Chinjo: YOU BROUGHT PEACE
BACK INTO OUR LIVES.
WE ARE FOREVER
IN YOUR DEBT.
- ONCE WE'VE FINISHED WITH
OUR BUSINESS AT THE CAPITAL,
WE'LL STOP BACK BY.
- OF COURSE. AND WHEN
YOU DO THIS PLACE WILL BE
AS TRANQUIL AS YOU LEFT IT.
OR BETTER YET, WE'LL BE
SUCH A BOOM TOWN, YOU WILL
HARDLY RECOGNIZE US.
- THANKS FOR HELPING
US OUT, HOSEI.
YOU CAN HOLD YOUR
OWN PRETTY WELL.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
MY AWESOMENESS MAY BE OBVIOUS,
BUT SOMEHOW IT'S ALWAYS
BETTER TO HEAR IT FROM
A PRETTY LITTLE THING LIKE YOU.
- ( sighs )
- SEE YOU SOON, LINLIN.
- THANK YOU.
- WELL, WE'D BEST BE OFF, YES?
- ( laughs ) GOODBYE.
BE CAREFUL. I'LL THINK
OF YOU EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- IT'S ENOUGH TO MAKE
YOUR HEART MELT.
COULD SHE BE
ANY MORE ADORABLE?
- NO KIDDING, RIGHT? WAIT.
HOLD ON. IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO WEASEL YOUR WAY INTO
JOINING US, IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE.
THEY'RE BOUND TO NEED YOU
MORE THAN WE DO.
- AH, THEY'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
ONLY REASON I CAME HERE
WAS TO FIND THIS BOW.
NO POINT IN MY STAYING
BEHIND NOW.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO
SOMEWHERE ELSE THEN?
- DON'T BE SUCH A STICK
IN THE MUD.
BETTER GET USED TO ME,
'CAUSE I PLAN ON FOLLOWING
LAILA TO THE ENDS OF THE EARTH.
YOU HEAR THAT, SWEETHEART?
I'LL PROTECT YOU NO MATTER...
- OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, YOU'RE
NOT EVEN REALLY THAT GOOD.
WANNA KNOW HOW CLOSE YOU CAME
TO HITTING ME WITH THAT ARROW,
MR. SURE SHOT?
TOO DAMN CLOSE.
- HOW DARE YOU.
THAT ARROW WENT RIGHT WHERE I
WANTED IT TO, BUDDY.
ONLY AN IDIOT WOULD THINK
MY AIM WAS OFF.
- ARE YOU CALLING ME AN IDIOT?
- WHADDYA SAY WE GET
A MOVE ON, GUYS?
- QUIT ACTING LIKE WE ARE
FRIENDS, JERK-FACE.
- JUST SO YOU'RE AWARE,
THE ONLY THING HOLDING
ME BACK
FROM KICKING YOUR ASS
INTO NEXT WEEK
IS THE FACT THAT
YOU'RE LAILA'S BROTHER.
- YOU KICKING MY ASS.
THAT'S GOOD. SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO HIT.
- OH, DEAR.
- FANTASTIC. ANOTHER IMBECILE.
JUST WHAT OUR PARTY
NEEDS RIGHT NOW.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK HOME?
- BECAUSE I WAS HERE FIRST.
- BECAUSE...
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: MUST THE WEAK
AND BEDRAGGLED TURN
TO PETTY CRIME
TO SURVIVE IN THIS WORLD?
- Taito: AND UNLESS YOU WANT
TO MAKE ME ANGRIER, YOU WILL
COME OUT NOW. UNDERSTAND?
- Laila: THE ONLY PEOPLE
THESE KIDS HAVE IN
THE WHOLE WORLD IS EACH OTHER.
- Ryuko: THEIR SITUATION
IS NO EXCUSE FOR LIVING
LIKE PARASITES.
- Hosei: ONLY SOMEONE WHO'S
NEVER WANTED FOR ANYTHING
COULD SAY SOMETHING SO COLD.
- Taito: ALL RIGHT, KID.
BRING IT ON.
- Shimei: LET'S SPICE
THINGS UP A BIT.
- Ryuko: NEXT TIME,
ON HERO TALES,
THE CHILDREN OF WANT
MEET THEIR CHAMPIONS
IN CHAPTER FIVE,
AILING EMPIRE.
- Taito: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
BUT YOU NEED TO STOP.