- Soldier A: HONORED FRIENDS,
HIS LORDSHIP KEIRO.
- I HAVE RETURNED, MY LIEGE.
- IMPECCABLY TIMED.
- YOUR BEARING
IS AS GALLANT AS EVER.
WE TAKE IT THE CAMPAIGN THEN
WAS A ROUSING SUCCESS?
- THE ENEMY WAS RESILIENT
DESPITE THEIR LOWBORN STATUS.
- DO NOT FEIGN INNOCENCE!
EXPLAIN YOUR SIEGE
OF LIAN TONG TEMPLE!
- THE BANDITS OF TAI SHAN
TOOK REFUGE THERE.
I MERELY FOLLOWED
WHERE MY QUARRY LED.
- QUARRY?
- THE EMPEROR CHARGED ME WITH
THE TASK OF FERRETING OUT REBELS
WHEREVER THEY MIGHT BE.
I DID SO.
- THIS IS TRUE?
- YOUR HIGHNESS,
I TAKE MY LEAVE NOW.
- LADY TAKI LONGS
TO SEE HER FATHER, MY LORD.
SO LONG AS YOU DEIGN
TO INDULGE THE COURT
WITH YOUR PRESENCE, SIR.
WHY NOT HER?
- HOW DEEP DO YOU THINK
TOKAKU'S SUSPICIONS LIE?
- HE MATTERS NOT.
THE STRATEGY WILL BE REVISED
SOMEWHAT, YES.
BUT NOT BECAUSE OF HIM.
- NO. I DIDN'T IMAGINE SO.
BUT SURELY REVISION
IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
OUR SITUATION
GROWS EVER DESPERATE.
YOU CANNOT DRAW THE SWORD.
I SPEAK OUT OF TURN.
- THE SWORD.
A PALTRY THING. WITH OR
WITHOUT IT, MY PATH IS ASSURED.
I PROMISE YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( birds chirping )
- ( speaking inaudibly )
- OH, MAN! WHOA! IT'S SO HUGE!
DON'T STAND THERE AND GAWK.
IT'S DISGRACEFUL.
- GIVE THE POOR YOKEL A BREAK.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST CITY
IN JING PROVINCE.
- WELL! SOMEBODY KNOWS
AN AWFUL LOT ABOUT THE REGION,
DON'T THEY?
- KIND OF, YEAH. WHEN YOU TRAVEL
AS LONG AS I HAVE,
TRYING TO FOLLOW
YOUR MASTER'S ORDERS,
YOU PICK UP SOME STUFF.
HEY! COME TO THINK OF IT,
I'VE PRETTY MUCH DONE
WHAT SHE ASKED ME TO.
GUESS THAT MEANS
I'LL BE GOING BACK SOON.
UGH. BELIEVE ME, IT'S THE
LAST THING I WANT TO DO.
- OH? COME ON, SHE CAN'T BE
ALL BAD. I'LL BET SHE'S PRETTY.
- SHE'S A HAG BEAST!
WITH A SOUL MORE GNARLED
AND TWISTED THAN
A WEATHER-BEATEN JASMINE TREE
GROWING ON A CLIFF.
HER ONE JOY IN LIFE IS WORKING
TENDER YOUNG LADS LIKE ME
TO THE BONE!
"TRAINING." THAT MIGHT BE
WHAT SHE CALLS IT,
- BUT IN REALITY,
IT'S JUST SLAVE LABOR!
- ( chuckles forcefully )
SHE, UH, SOUNDS INTENSE.
- YOU DON'T KNOW THE HALF OF IT.
I'M JUST AN INNOCENT LITTLE BOY
IN THE EVIL CLUTCHES OF A WITCH.
IF ONLY I COULD WEEP
ON SOMEONE'S AMPLE BOSOM!
- Taito: I'M STARVING.
- OH, LAILA, MY SWEET,
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL GIFT
YOU'RE GIVING ME.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO DRIVE
A WEDGE BETWEEN US?
I DON'T EVEN WANNA KNOW WHAT
I JUST MISTOOK FOR A BOSOM.
( whimpers )
- I'D BE CURIOUS TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'VE MISTAKEN FOR A BRAIN.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY, HAND OVER SOME GOLD.
- ( sarcastically ) WOW,
HOW POLITE.
HERE. JUST DON'T SPEND IT ALL
ON SOMETHING DUMB.
- I WON'T!
( laughs )
- Ryuko: HE ACTS
LIKE SUCH A CHILD SOMETIMES.
- Girl: RUN FOR IT!
- HEY! GET BACK HERE!
THOSE LITTLE RUG RATS TAKE
WHATEVER ISN'T NAILED DOWN.
- Taito: HEY, LADY.
SWEET BUNS, PLEASE.
I'LL TAKE ALL THAT YOU GOT.
- I'M SORRY, SIR. WE'VE ONLY GOT
ONE LEFT, I'M AFRAID.
- WELL, LIKE I SAID,
I'LL TAKE ALL THAT YOU GOT.
- HERE YOU ARE.
- MMM. THAT'S THE STUFF.
- Mo Gai: MOVE ASIDE, KID!
- BUSINESS IS PRETTY GOOD
TODAY, I SEE.
- YEAH.
- LUCKY FOR YOU, HUH?
SEE, WE'RE HAVING A BIT
OF A FINANCIAL DOWNTURN,
YOU MIGHT SAY.
- BUT JUST YESTERDAY, I...
- HEY, YOU WANT WE SHOULD
REDECORATE THE PLACE AGAIN?
- THIS IS EVERYTHING
I'VE MADE SO FAR TODAY.
- HMM.
QUITE A SENSE OF HUMOR
YOU GOT THERE.
- YOU OUGHT TO KNOW BETTER
THAN TO HOLD OUT ON US BY NOW.
OR DON'T YOU CARE ABOUT THIS
POOR LITTLE HOLE IN THE WALL?
- I'M TELLING THE TRUTH!
- GUESS THIS'LL HAVE TO DO.
- LET'S GO.
- WELL, WE'VE GOT OURSELVES
THE MO BROTHERS.
- THAT'S US. WHO'RE YOU?
- WE'RE THE GUYS
WHO'RE GONNA COLLECT
THE 100-SILVER-PIECE BOUNTY
ON YOUR HEADS.
QUITE AN HONOR.
- Mo Gai: 100 SILVER PIECES,
HUH? NOT BAD.
BUT THERE'S NO BOUNTY ON US
IN THESE PARTS YET, IS THERE?
- AFRAID SO. THE MAN YOU KILLED
THREE DAYS AGO
HAPPENED TO BE
A PROVINCIAL OFFICIAL.
- THREE DAYS AGO? SERIOUSLY?
NO BELLS HERE. HOW ABOUT YOU?
- EH, YOU KILL ONE OFFICIAL,
YOU KILLED THEM ALL.
- YOU THREE SCUMBAGS SHOULD
LAUGH IT UP WHILE YOU CAN.
WHEN I SAID THERE WAS A BOUNTY
ON YOUR HEADS I MEANT JUST THAT.
THE REST OF YOUR BODIES
CAN JUST ROT IN THE STREET.
- ( crowd panicking )
- OOH. FIVE AGAINST THREE.
THINK WE GOT A SHOT, BOYS?
- ( laughs )
THE ODDS CERTAINLY DO SEEM
TO BE STACKED AGAINST US,
DON'T THEY?
- TAKE THEM DOWN!
- OH, WHAT TO DO? THE BIG,
SCARY MEN ARE GONNA MAR
MY BEAUTIFUL FACE!
- ( both groan )
- NOW, THESE ODDS
ARE MORE LIKE IT.
- DAMN YOU ALL!
- ( bounty hunters yelling )
- INCREDIBLE.
- YEAH.
THOSE THREE KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE THEMSELVES.
- ( Mo Gai growls )
- ( bounty hunters groans )
LET'S GO.
- IT'S HORRIBLE. JUST BARBARIC.
- THEY COULD'VE GOTTEN AWAY
WITHOUT KILLING THESE MEN.
- IS THAT SO?
THIS KIND OF THING IS
A HECK OF A LOT MORE COMMON
THAN YOU'D CARE TO BELIEVE.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING I SHOULD
ACCEPT PEOPLE LIKE THAT
RUNNING LOOSE IN THE WORLD?
- WHOA, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
TAKE DOWN EVERY SINGLE BAD GUY
YOU COME ACROSS?
TRUST ME ON THIS, SOMETIMES
YOU GOTTA LET THE WORLD
HANDLE ITS OWN PROBLEMS.
RIGHT, TAITO?
IT'S JUST A SWEET BUN, MAN.
GET OVER IT.
- BUT IT WAS MINE.
ONE MORE, PLEASE!
- I TOLD YOU,
THAT'S THE LAST ONE I HAD TODAY.
- Taito: HEY!
- YOU THIEF!
- YOU LITTLE BASTARD!
GET YOUR ASS BACK HERE!
GET DOWN HERE! I'M NOT PLAYING!
- ( blows raspberries )
- OH, OKAY.
( laughs )
YUCK IT UP NOW.
BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA REGRET
YOU EVER PICKED ME
OF ALL PEOPLE TO MESS WITH,
YOU FILTHY LITTLE BRAT.
( laughs )
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
- ( thief laughs )
WHOOPS.
- ( screaming )
- ( chuckling )
- ( Taito panting )
LOOKIE HERE.
NO PLACE FOR YOU TO RUN TO, HUH?
GIVE ME MY MONEY. NOW!
- I WOULD STAY BACK IF I WERE
YOU. THINGS COULD GET UGLY.
- THERE'S NO "COULD" ABOUT IT.
THINGS ARE GONNA GET
PLENTY UGLY WHEN I GET...
( screaming ) HEY!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
( grunting )
- CAN'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YA.
- YOU LITTLE...
( grunting )
- SEE YOU AROUND. THANKS
FOR THE GIFT, BY THE WAY.
- GIVE THAT BACK TO ME.
GIVE IT BACK TO ME RIGHT NOW
OR I SWEAR I WILL BE
YOUR PERSONAL NIGHTMARE!
- ( girl laughing )
- SCREW YOU!
- Laila: SORRY.
- ( both laugh )
- THAT'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY GOOD LOOK FOR YOU.
- Taito: I HATE YOU SO MUCH
RIGHT NOW.
- LET'S GET HIM DOWN.
- NOT YOU, TOO, RYUKO! DAMN IT!
( guttural cry )
- OKAY. DOES HE EVEN KNOW
WHERE HE'S GOING?
- HE'S RUNNING ON INSTINCT,
I'M GUESSING.
WE'D BETTER JUST TRY
TO KEEP UP WITH HIM.
- Taito: YOU WILL SHOE
THE DAY YOU STOLE FROM ME!
- I DO HOPE HE MEANS "RUE."
- ( panting )
( sniffing )
THAT'S THE SCENT.
I CAN SMELL THE SWEET BUNS.
WE'RE VERY CLOSE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THE KID SMELLED
LIKE SWEET BUNS.
THAT'S HOW I'VE BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK HIM.
- WHAT, ARE YOU A DOG?
- LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
- I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE, THIEF!
AND UNLESS YOU WANT
TO MAKE ME ANGRIER,
YOU'LL COME OUT
NOW. UNDERSTAND?
- HA!
SO DID YOUR FRIENDS CUT YOU DOWN
OR WERE YOUR FORCED
TO CHEW YOUR WAY OUT OF
MY LITTLE TRAP BACK THERE?
- I FEEL FOR YOU. YOU'RE IN
FOR A WORLD OF HURT NOW,
YOU PUNK.
- I'M IN FOR A WORLD OF HURT?
YOU MUST BE DUMBER
THAN YOU LOOK, TOUGH GUY.
- HA! ALL RIGHT, KID.
BRING IT ON!
- TAITO, WAIT. IT'S A TRAP!
- TAITO!
- ( loud smash )
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE BACK DOWN TO THREE.
- YOU DIDN'T REALLY THINK
I'D JUST SURRENDER, RIGHT?
- ( grunting )
AS A MATTER OF FACT, I DIDN'T.
- THERE'S NO WAY!
- ( grunts )
THAT THE BEST YOU GOT?
- UH...
- TO GET TO LIEN
YOU'VE GOTTA GO THROUGH ME!
- ( all making guttural noises )
- MORE KIDS. OKAY.
- Girl: OH, WOW!
THAT LOOKS REALLY, REALLY GOOD!
- BE CAREFUL, ALL RIGHT?
THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH
FOOD FOR EVERYONE,
I PROMISE. NO NEED TO CROWD.
- GIVE HER SOME ROOM.
COME ON. LINE UP!
- Kids: OKAY!
( giggling )
- THAT'S MY MONEY,
MY FOOD MONEY.
- IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
AT LEAST THEY HAVE THE DECENCY
TO BE GRATEFUL FOR THE MEAL
YOUR MONEY PAID FOR.
- I KNOW.
- HI. MY NAME'S SHULAN.
YOU LIKE IT? WHAT'S YOURS?
- MY NAME'S TAITO.
- HERE, TAITO. YOU SHOULD HAVE
SOME OF THIS, TOO.
- WELL, AREN'T YOU SWEET?
- ( giggling )
- Kids: THANKS FOR THE MEAL!
- MOMMY, I...
- SORRY WE GOT OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT,
BUT IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE'VE BEEN ABLE
TO GET A DECENT MEAL.
- UH... YEAH, SURE THING.
- SO, YOU LIVE
ALL BY YOURSELVES?
- YEAH, WE'RE ORPHANS.
- ALL OF YOU?
- THEN WHY NOT TURN TO
THE OFFICIALS FOR HELP?
- TRUST ME, WE'D ALL RATHER
TAKE OUR CHANCES OUT HERE.
THOSE GUYS ARE BAD NEWS.
ALL THEY DO IS BEAT US.
- MY GUESS IS THAT WOULDN'T BE
THE CASE IF YOU DIDN'T STEAL.
- YOU GOT A BETTER WAY FOR US
TO SURVIVE, I'M ALL EARS!
- STOP IT. THE TWO OF YOU
WILL WAKE UP SHULAN.
- ANYWAY, THANKS,
BUT YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT
US POOR SOULS FOR NOW.
YOU'VE DONE YOUR GOOD DEED.
- THE ONLY PEOPLE THESE KIDS
HAVE IN THE WHOLE WORLD
IS EACH OTHER.
- I SYMPATHIZE WITH THEM
BUT I'M SORRY,
THEIR SITUATION IS NO EXCUSE
FOR LIVING LIKE PARASITES.
- ONLY SOMEONE WHO'S
NEVER WANTED FOR ANYTHING
COULD SAY SOMETHING SO COLD.
- WHAT?
- COME ON,
BE HONEST WITH YOURSELF.
YOU'VE LIVED A PAMPERED LIFE.
HUNGER'S JUST AN IDEA.
- SO HUNGER EXEMPTS US
FROM OUR MORAL OBLIGATIONS,
IS THAT IT?
- THAT ISN'T WHAT I SAID.
I'M SAYING NONE OF US HERE HAVE
THE RIGHT TO JUDGE THESE KIDS
AND WHAT THEY HAVE TO DO
TO GET BY.
ESPECIALLY A SELF-RIGHTEOUS SON
OF PRIVILEGE WHO SEES EVERYTHING
IN BLACK AND WHITE.
- ( angrily ) HOSEI!
- BOTH OF YOU, KNOCK IT OFF
RIGHT NOW. THIS IS ABSURD.
- Taito: WHAT HAVE WE
REALLY DONE TO HELP THEM?
- ( birds chirping )
- ( laughs )
- Kids: WOW!
- Shulan: WHAT'S
HE GONNA DO NOW?
- ( all gasp )
- NO WAY!
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
- NOW, IF WE CHANNEL
OUR ENERGY CORRECTLY...
WELL, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
YOU COULD DO THE SAME THING
WITH A BLOCK OF IRON.
- OKAY, YEAH.
- CHANNELING IS THE KEY
TO MASTERING
THE EIGHT GREAT STYLES.
THIS IS WHAT LORD KEIRO OF THE
IMPERIAL GUARD IS SAID TO USE.
AND THOUGH HE'S SELF TAUGHT,
HE'S VERY ACCOMPLISHED.
SO, UNLESS YOU CAN
TRULY MASTER CHANNELING
BEFORE CONFRONTING HIM,
HE WILL ALMOST CERTAINLY
DEFEAT YOU.
- I'M TRYING TO, REALLY.
I JUST CAN'T GET MY HEAD AROUND
TRANSFERRING THE ENERGY
INTO A WEAPON.
( sighs )
FOCUS, TAITO.
YOU CAN DO THIS, ALL RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- DAMN IT. I MEAN, DANG IT.
- ONCE AGAIN, I'M NOT SURE
HOW YOU'RE DOING THAT,
BUT IT SEEMS
THE ENERGY INSIDE YOU
REFUSES TO BE CONTAINED.
- ( kids laughing )
- THAT WAS GREAT!
- DO IT AGAIN!
- OKAY, OKAY. SETTLE DOWN.
HEY! STOP YANKING ON ME!
- WHAT THE HELL IS HE DOING?
- AH-HA! THERE YOU ARE.
HAVE YOU GOTTEN WATER
LIKE I ASKED YOU TO,
LIKE, FOREVER AGO?
- UH, I FORGOT.
- WELL, HOP TO IT, MISTER!
- ( groans )
- Mo Han: LOOK WHO WE HAVE HERE.
FEAST YOUR EYES, MY BROTHERS.
IT'S THE BOLD LITTLE AMATEUR
WHO RAN OFF WITH MY MONEY.
- OH, MY, SIMPLY SCRUMPTIOUS,
ISN'T HE?
- YOU KNOW, KID,
SOMETHING TELLS ME
IN ANOTHER LIFE
WE COULD'VE BEEN FRIENDS.
BUT YOU JUST HAD TO GO
AND TOY WITH US.
- YOU FREAKS
AREN'T GONNA GET ME!
- ( growls angrily )
- NO WAY!
- ( Mo Han laughing )
WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
AMATEUR ALL THE WAY.
I GIVE HIM CREDIT
FOR TRYING, THOUGH!
- ( grunts )
- IF YOU LIKE TO PLAY GAMES,
WHY DON'T WE INTRODUCE YOU
TO A FEW OF OUR OWN?
- ONE OF OUR FAVORITES IS CALLED
"HOW WE DEAL WITH PEOPLE
WHO PISS US OFF."
THOUGH I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GONNA LIKE IT VERY MUCH.
- GET OFF! LET GO OF ME,
YOU BASTARD!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO HIM?
- Lien: GET OUT OF HERE, SHULAN!
- STOP BULLYING LIEN,
YOU MEANIES!
- THE HELL'S THIS VERMIN?
- ( cries )
- EW, YUCK! SHE GOT GRIME
ALL OVER MY BEST ROBE.
- I'LL KILL YOU! YOU HEAR ME?
- AW, ARE WE UPSET?
WHATEVER HAPPENS TO HER,
THE ONLY PERSON TO BLAME IS YOU.
( laughs )
- DAMN YOU!
- WHAT THE...
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING
BUT YOU NEED TO STOP.
- OH, WELL.
ANOTHER LITTLE FRIEND.
- Taito: GET YOUR FOOT
OFF THE BOY.
- EH? COME AGAIN?
- I SAID
TAKE YOUR FOOT OFF THE BOY.
- DON'T GET ALL HIGH-HANDED
ON US, KID.
THE BOY HAPPENS TO BE A LIAR
AND A THIEF.
- OH, YEAH. LIKE THE THREE
OF YOU ARE UPSTANDING CITIZENS!
I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOUR BEEF IS WITH HIM.
YOU'RE GONNA ANSWER TO ME NOW.
- UH-OH.
- LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
A TOUCH MORE TO THIS ONE
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
- I ASSUME
WE DO THE USUAL ROUTINE?
- ( blades clanging )
- ( guttural ) HMM.
- ( chuckling )
- ( blows raspberries )
- GUESS I'LL START WITH YOU!
- ( Mo Han laughs )
WHAT'S WRONG?
I THROW YOU FOR A LOOP?
( continues laughing )
- OH, CRAP!
RYUKO!
- HEY! LOOKS LIKE FUN!
MIND IF I JOIN IN?
- CRAP. EXACTLY HOW MANY
OF THESE PEOPLE ARE THERE?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON OUT HERE,
BUT I'M MORE THAN HAPPY
TO BACK YOU UP!
- TAITO, HERE!
- HA! NOW YOU'RE IN FOR IT!
- OH, SO MANY HEAVENLY BOYS.
- YIKES. THAT ONE'S A LOOKER.
HEY, RYUKO, IF WE'RE CHOOSING,
I THINK YOU SHOULD GET THIS GUY.
- WHY DO I GET STUCK WITH HIM?
- DON'T BE SHY.
HE'S A PERFECT MATCH FOR YOU.
- STOP BEING VULGAR!
- ( angrily ) I CAN HEAR
EVERY WORD YOU'RE SAYING!
- Mo Han: YOU'RE FEELING
SO COCKY, GO AHEAD
AND MAKE A MOVE!
- I'D SAY A PRAYER
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- IDIOT!
- TAITO, WAIT!
- ( guttural cry )
- ( grunts )
- ALL RIGHT, STAY SHARP.
THESE CLOWNS HAVE GOT
SOME SKILL.
- Ryuko and Hosei: MORON!
- HONESTLY, AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
HAVE YOU NOT LEARNED
A SINGLE THING?
- NEVER CHARGE A GROUP
BY YOURSELF!
- BUT, I WAS JUST TRYING TO...
- LOOK AT THEM.
INDIVIDUALLY, THEY'RE
AVERAGE FIGHTERS AT BEST.
BUT BY WORKING
TOGETHER AS A UNIT,
THEY ACTUALLY POSE A THREAT
TO ANYONE UNABLE TO LEARN
BY THEIR EXAMPLE.
- WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO THEN?
- THINK, TAITO.
THERE ARE THREE OF US.
- NEVER MIND. FINE,
I'LL KEEP 'EM ON THEIR TOES
AS LONG AS I CAN.
- AND I'LL CREATE AN OPENING
FOR YOU.
- WHAT DO I DO?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
YOU FINISH THEM OFF.
- ALL RIGHT!
- MY NAME IS RYUKO.
I AM A MONK. I HAIL FROM
THE TONG YOU TEMPLE.
PREPARE!
- ALL THAT FANCY TALK'S
JUST GONNA MAKE YOU LOOK
PATHETIC IN THE END.
( grunts )
- HE DEFLECTED MY SHOT!
- OH, WOW.
- DON'T WORRY!
I'VE GOT HIM, BIG BROTHER!
- NO DICE.
BUT DON'T TAKE THIS PERSONAL.
- ( screams )
- ( cries out )
MO HAN, ARE YOU OKAY?
- RYUKO!
- Ryuko: NOW, TAITO!
- ( guttural cry )
THIS IS FOR THE SWEET BUN!
AND THIS IS FOR PICKING ON
SOMEONE WEAKER THAN YOU!
- ( all Mo Brothers scream )
- THEY... THEY'RE ALL MONSTERS.
- LIGHTS OUT, SHORT STUFF.
- ( giggling softly )
SO, YOU'RE REALLY LEAVING?
- Taito: AFRAID SO, KIDDO.
WE'VE GOT BUSINESS
IN THE CAPITAL.
- IF YOU LET ME COME ALONG,
I CAN HELP WITH STUFF!
TEACH ME HOW TO BE AS STRONG
AS YOU! PLEASE!
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE LITTLE ONES?
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO LEAD THEM
ALL SAFELY TO THEIR NEW HOME,
AT THE LIAN TONG TEMPLE.
IT'S QUITE A TREK,
BUT YOU'LL BE GREETED
WITH OPEN ARMS.
- SO, UH, IF I GO THERE,
WILL THEY HELP ME
GET AS STRONG AS YOU?
- WELL, AT THE VERY LEAST
YOU WON'T HAVE TO RISK LIFE
AND LIMB ANYMORE,
STEALING TO SURVIVE.
- OKAY, WE'LL GO.
- OH, YEAH. HERE, TAKE THIS.
- BUT THIS IS THE BOUNTY
FROM CATCHING THOSE GUYS.
ARE YOU SURE?
- OF COURSE I AM.
YOU NEED MONEY TO TRAVEL.
WE EVEN WROTE YOU GUYS A
LITTLE LETTER OF INTRODUCTION.
WELL, I MEAN...
- Laila: I DID.
- ( all laugh )
- Kids: BYE! SEE YOU! THANK YOU!
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELVES!
- SO LONG! WE'LL MISS YOU!
- THANKS AGAIN!
GOOD LUCK ON YOUR JOURNEY!
- SAME THING GOES
FOR YOU, KIDDO!
- THE ALKAID BOY'S A FOOL.
ABSOLUTELY IN THE DARK.
IF ONLY HE HAD AN INKLING
OF HIS STAR'S TRUE POWER.
ENOUGH OF THIS
LURKING IN THE SHADOWS.
LET'S SPICE THINGS UP A BIT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryuko: A NEWFOUND ALLY
CALLS FORTH A GREATER POWER
HIDDEN WITHIN TAITO.
- Laila: THIS IS HER? TOTALLY
NOT WHAT I WAS EXPECTING.
- Ryuko: AND DOES THIS
INNER RESERVOIR
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE EIGHTH STYLE
LONG BELIEVED TO BE LOST?
- Taito: HEY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
I'M THE ONE
WHO DID ALL THE WORK!
- Hosei: NOW SAY HELLO
TO KOEI'S NUMBER ONE PUPIL!
THIS MOUNTAIN'S DEFENDER!
- Shimei: SUCH A SPITFIRE.
I BELIEVE USING YOU
WILL BE QUITE THE ROMP.
- Ryuko: NEXT ON HERO TALES,
THE DARKNESS GATHERS
IN CHAPTER SIX,
"THE RED CHAMPION."
- Hosei: ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
SHE'LL ACKNOWLEDGE ME.