- TRAITOROUS FILTH, TELL ME,
EXACTLY WHERE WERE YOU
ESCORTING HIS FORMER MAJESTY?
- JUST WHERE DO YOU THINK?
TO A PLACE FAR AWAY
FROM KEIRO'S CLUTCHES!
- DON'T DELUDE YOURSELF!
THERE IS
NO SUCH PLACE NOW, NAIF!
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO WE GOTTA BUILD IT.
- IDIOT! YOU'RE JUST
BABBLING INCOHERENTLY.
- A PLACE WHERE PEOPLE CAN
LIVE SAFELY AND HAPPILY, FREE...
- YOU STILL CLEAVE
TO SUCH NONSENSE?
YOUR VISION IS AN EMPTY ONE,
IT WON'T COME TO FRUITION!
- OH, YES, IT WILL!
YOU JUST WAIT AND SEE,
OLD FRIEND.
BESIDES, TAKE A LOOK AT US.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE
THE REAL EMPEROR ON OUR SIDE
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED YET.
IF ANYONE CAN BUILT IT,
IT'S HIM.
MARK MY WORDS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ryuko: IS THAT YOUR
POSITION, THEN?
- Taito: THAT'S RIGHT.
AND NO AMOUNT OF FANCY TALK IS
GOING TO CHANGE MY MIND, EITHER.
BUT WHO KNOWS. MAYBE IT'S OUR
FATE TO DISAGREE LIKE THIS.
- INDEED. THEN I'VE NO CHOICE!
- LET'S FINISH IT, RYUKO,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- WITH PLEASURE!
- I AM ALKAID!
USER OF THE EIGHT STYLES,
CHOOSE YOUR STANCE!
- I AM MIZAR!
I CHOOSE YOUR ANNIHILATION!
- ( both screaming )
- STOP THIS! ACT LIKE MEN!
THIS IS INFANTILE!
LAILA, PLEASE, CONVINCE
THEM TO WITHDRAW.
- YEAH, SURE THING.
AND WHILE I'M AT IT,
I'LL MOVE A MOUNTAIN TOO.
- YOU JEST...
- NAH. WE'RE PRETTY MUCH
GONNA HAVE TO LET THEM
DUKE IT OUT, I'M AFRAID.
CALLING MEN BULLHEADED WOULD
BE AN INSULT TO LIVESTOCK.
- THAT REMINDS ME.
HAVE I TOLD YOU ABOUT THE LITTLE
CLUB WE'VE GOT, LADY TAKI?
- Choka: FORGIVE ME, MY LORD...
IT SEEMS ALKAID HAS
ABSCONDED WITH TAKI
AND HIS FORMER MAJESTY.
- ( Shimei chuckles )
QUITE THE FAUX PAS.
- Choka: SHIMEI...
- TAIGA'S TRUANCY ALONE
IS OF LITTLE ACCOUNT.
HE IS MERELY
THE DETRITUS OF A BYGONE ERA.
- BUT THAT HE'S NOW IN THE
COMPANY OF YOUR NEMESIS,
SURELY THAT IS
NO SMALL CONSIDERATION?
- THE SWORD OF RULE HAS
CHOSEN ME TO BE EMPEROR.
ALKAID CONCERNS ME
NOT IN THE LEAST.
MY AMBITION IS REALIZED.
BUT SHOULD OUR ABSENT FRIENDS
COLLUDE IN HOPE OF
BRINGING ME DOWN...
...I WILL SEE THEIR HOPES
DASHED PERSONALLY.
- TAKI...
- ( chuckles ) AW, COME ON.
YOU WORN OUT?
YOU'RE PANTING LIKE AN
OVERLOADED PACK MULE THERE,
HOTSHOT.
- IMBECILE. YOU'RE IN NO
POSITION TO MOCK ME.
- ( both grunting )
- EXPLAIN IT.
- DO WHAT?
- YOUR FAITH. HOW CAN YOU
PUT SO MUCH STOCK IN SOMEONE
AS INEFFECTUAL AS TAIGA?
- DO WHAT?
- NO QUALMS. NO HESITATION.
JUST BLIND FAITH.
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
WHAT KIND OF QUESTION IS THAT?
- ONE THAT BEGS AN ANSWER!
- LOOK, YOU EITHER GET IT
OR YOU DON'T, OKAY?
- AND I DON'T?
- LET ME ASK YOU, SMART GUY.
WHEN YOU BELIEVE IN SOMEBODY,
DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO KNOW WHY?
- OF COURSE I DO!
ANYTHING ELSE WOULD BE
THE SURRENDER OF REASON.
- IF YOU WANT A REASON,
JUST LOOK HIM IN THE EYE!
WHAT MORE DO YOU NEED?
HELL, THAT'S ALL IT TOOK
FOR ME THE FIRST TIME WE MET.
REMEMBER?
- DON'T THINK TO SWAY ME!
WHY DO HIS PLATITUDES LURE ME?
HE BRINGS OUT THE
BEST IN EVERYONE,
EVEN WHEN HE SPEAKS NONSENSE.
AM I LOSING SIGHT OF
THE HORIZON LINE
WHERE WISDOM BECOMES CLICHE?
OR IS HE RIGHT?
FOR THAT MATTER, WHEN
COULD I LAST EVEN LOOK
SOMEONE IN THE EYE
WITHOUT MY GUARD UP?
- NOW, PICK IT UP.
- DON'T PATRONIZE ME!
- OH, PLEASE. GROW UP.
I'VE BEEN LOOKIN' FORWARD
TO THIS.
COME ON. DO YOU WANT A REMATCH
OR DON'T YOU?
- TAITO. I HAVE NEVER
ENCOUNTERED YOUR LIKE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
A LITTLE REMATCH SOMETIME?
- TAITO.
- CALL IT FATE IF YOU LIKE.
LET'S SPAR. IT'LL BE FUN,
LIKE BACK IN THE OLD DAYS.
AFTER THE CRAP
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
YOU OWE ME A FAIR FIGHT.
- YOU IDIOT.
- VERY WELL. THOUGH I FEEL
I OUGHT TO REMIND YOU...
IN THE REAL WORLD "FAIR"
IS ENTIRELY RELATIVE.
- TRUST ME. I KNOW.
- MORONS. I KNEW IT WOULD
COME TO THIS.
WHY DO MEN HAVE TO BE SO...
- Taki: I BELIEVE THE WORD
IS "HOPELESS," IS IT NOT?
( chuckles )
- YOU DO GET IT.
- OH, YES.
- WHAT THE...
- Kocho: YOUR MAJESTY!
LADY TAKI!
- FATH... KOCHO!
- DAMN THEIR EYES.
TO HAVE KIDNAPPED YOU.
I'LL TEACH THEM
A LESSON IN RESPECT!
- NEITHER WOMAN NOR CHILD
WILL KNOW MERCY!
- KOCHO. STOP!
- Kocho: YOUR HIGHNESS?
- THEY ARE NOT OUR FOE.
LISTEN, PLEASE, THEY RISKED
BOTH LIFE AND LIMB
IN ORDER TO SET US FREE!
KEIRO WOULD HAVE SLAIN TAKI
AND MYSELF IF NOT FOR
THEIR INTERCESSION!
- THEY WHAT?
NO, YOU, YOU'VE BEEN BEWITCHED.
- BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
LORD KEIRO WOULD HAVE
SEEN US PUT TO DEATH!
- Kocho: BUT, MY NOBLE LORD,
SURELY HE WOULD NEVER...
- HERE WE ARE AT LAST.
IT'S THE END!
- BRING IT!
- ( screams )
- ( shrieks )
- Kocho: TAKI!
- ( both grunting )
- WAY TO GO, TAI!
- I AM BESTED. GO.
- Laila: TAITO!
( laughing )
- ( chuckles )
- I WAS HIS SERVANT.
HIS DOG.
- WITH YOUR BELOVED EMPEROR,
DIE AS ONE!
- TAIGA!
- LOOK OUT!
- ( screaming )
- ( groaning )
( grunting )
- FATHER!
- Kocho: STAY BACK!
I BEG OF YOU.
I WILL NOT HAVE
THE TWO OF YOU...
...STEEPED IN MY BLOOD.
- ( crying ) FATHER, NO...
- ( continues groaning )
FORGIVE ME, MY LORD...
SO STRONG A BOND
WOULD NOT BE RENT ASUNDER.
- FATHER!
( crying )
- TAITO.
- KEIRO!
- TAITO. PLEASE,
YOU MUSTN'T GIVE IN.
DISASTER WILL RAIN DOWN ON US
ALL IF YOU CLASH.
- LAILA. TAKE THE OTHERS
AND GO.
GET THEM OUT OF HERE, QUICKLY.
I'LL STAY AND HOLD HIM OFF.
- YOU SURE?
- JUST HAVE FAITH.
I PROMISE NO MATTER WHAT
HAPPENS, I'LL FIND YOU GUYS.
- YOU'D BETTER, TAI.
YOU HEAR ME?
- SO YOU'RE GOING TO HOLD
ME OFF THEN ARE YOU?
INTERESTING.
THE HEAVENS HAVE PAVED
A ROAD FOR ME, BOY.
CHECK MY PROGRESS
IF YOU DARE!
- OH, I DARE A LOT MORE
THAN THAT.
- FATHER. DON'T DO THIS.
- IT'S TIME TO FALL!
- ( both screaming )
- IMPOSSIBLE. TAITO TOOK
A DIRECT HIT FROM HIM
WITHOUT FALTERING.
- KEIRO!
( explosion booms )
- IT'S HAPPENED.
THE WAR OF ALKAID AND DUBHE
HAS BECOME MANIFEST.
- YOU ESCAPED UNHARMED, MAJESTY?
- YES.
- THAT'S GREAT, BUT WHO
GIVES A DAMN ABOUT YOU?
COWARD! YOU LEFT TAITO
TO FACE THE MUSIC ALONE!
- CALM YOURSELF, PLEASE.
TAITO WILLED HIS MAJESTY
TO BREAK AWAY.
HE DID NOT SIMPLY FLEE
THE SCENE OUT OF COWARDICE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
OUR MISSION WAS TO FREE HIM.
- FORGIVE ME. I WAS ONLY DOING
AS TAITO WANTED.
- DAMN IT, TAITO.
IF YOU DIE ON US, LAILA
WON'T HAVE ANY FAMILY LEFT.
WHAT KIND OF LIFE WILL SHE HAVE
TO LOOK FORWARD TO?
- I KNOW! YOUR SWEET SIS
AND I WILL HAVE TO GET HITCHED.
IT'S THE BEST WAY TO HONOR
YOUR MEMORY!
- Taito: NOT TO STEAL
YOUR THUNDER,
BUT MY MEMORY DOESN'T NEED
HONORING JUST YET.
- TAITO!
- THANK HEAVENS!
- TAITO, YOU
EAVESDROPPING SCOUNDREL.
- SO, UH, YOU DO KNOW ALL
THAT WAS JUST ME
KIDDIN' AROUND, RIGHT?
- SURE. WHATEVER.
- YOUNG TAITO.
IT WAS I WHO CAST YOU OUT.
I WHO TORE YOU FROM
YOUR BROTHER'S SIDE
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
- YOU WHAT?
- HEY, ITS ALRIGHT. YOU DID
WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS BEST.
- BUT...
- TELL ME, OF WHAT ARE
THE TWO OF YOU SPEAKING?
- MY LORD, IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO KNOW.
THE HERO BEFORE US
IS YOUR OWN TWIN BROTHER.
- TWIN BROTHER?
- YEAH. HOW'S THAT
FOR A SURPRISE?
- 'TWAS TO MY EVERLASTING SHAME,
BANISHING YOU FROM THE CAPITAL.
ALL DRIVEN BY FEAR
OF YOUR FATE. THE SIGIL.
WHATEVER PUNISHMENT YOU DEVISE,
I WILL HUMBLY SUBMIT TO.
- AW, DON'T TALK LIKE THAT.
AFTER ALL, I CONSIDER IT
AN HONOR TO BE RAISED
BY SOEI AND SONNEI.
ACTUALLY, SIR,
I SHOULD BE THANKING YOU.
WITHOUT YOUR HELP, I NEVER
WOULD HAVE MET THEM.
SO, I GUESS, THANKS.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR IT.
- AND I FOR YOUR KINDNESS.
- UH, WHAT'S UP?
WHOA, WHOA! HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
- BROTHER.
- THE TIME HAS COME.
- INDEED, YOUR HIGHNESS.
- Ryuko: YOUR LORDSHIP.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WHY DID YOU DO IT, SIR?
WHY DID YOU CAST
YOUR BLADE ALOFT?
- WHY ELSE? TO SLAY ALKAID.
- AND YET IT FOUND PURCHASE
AT LAST IN KOCHO'S BREAST,
NOT HIS.
- SO IT DID.
AND JUSTLY, TOO.
WEAKNESS IS THE WORST
BETRAYAL OF ALL.
DEATH, A COWARD'S
ONLY REWARD.
- BUT MY LORD...
- YOU QUESTION
LORD KEIRO'S JUDGMENT?
LEST WE FORGET,
THAT SAME JUDGMENT SAW FIT
TO SPARE YOUR HEAD WHEN
WHAT FILLED IT WAS TREASON!
YOUR MAJESTY.
NO SUCH VEIL OF DOUBT
SHROUDS MY LOYALTY,
I WOULD LAY DOWN MY LIFE
FOR YOU IF NECESSARY.
- OF THAT I'M SURE.
YOU'VE CONVICTION.
WHY ELSE WOULD I HAVE KEPT
YOU UNDER MY WING?
- TO SPEAK THIS WAY.
- CHOKA, GATHER UP THE CITIZENRY
IN JIALING SQUARE.
- YES. WITH HASTE.
- AND SO IT BEGINS
AT LONG LAST.
KEIRO'S ASCENT.
THE EMPIRE'S DEMISE AND
DUBHE'S SATISFACTION.
- HE'S REALLY GONNA TAKE
THE THRONE?
- YEAH. I'M AFRAID SO.
AND THAT'S JUST THE FIRST STEP.
- FIRST STEP?
WHAT MORE COULD HE DESIRE?
THERE'S NOT A SOUL LEFT
FOOL HARDY ENOUGH
WHO'D DARE CONTEST HIM.
DOES THE HELM OF THE EMPIRE
LEAVE HIM WANTING?
- WELL, WHATEVER HE'S GOT
IN MIND,
THERE'S NO WAY IT COULD BE GOOD.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP HIM BEFORE HE DOES
ANY MORE DAMAGE.
- WE CAN BET THE PURPOSE
HIS BLACK HEART'S CONCEIVED
BODES POORLY.
- ONCE HE'S GONE, IT'LL BE UP TO
YOU TO RESTORE THE EMPIRE.
REMEMBER THAT. THINGS
CAN'T GO BACK TO THE WAY
THEY WERE BEFORE.
YOU MADE ME A PROMISE.
- MAY I ASK THIS OF YOU, PLEASE?
- ASK ME WHAT?
- IN MY PLACE, I WOULD
LIKE VERY MUCH FOR YOU
TO SIT AS EMPEROR.
- HIGHNESS. WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I'M NOT EVEN SURE
WHAT SCARES ME MORE,
KEIRO OR A HALF WIT LIKE TAITO
PERCHED ON THE THRONE.
- PLEASE, SIR.
DO NOT DECIDE IN HASTE.
- BUT, I... I HAVEN'T THE
STRENGTH TO FIGHT EVIL MEN.
AND TAITO DOES. I'VE SEEN IT.
THE EMPIRE WOULD BE BETTER,
FAR BETTER SERVED BY HIM.
- SORRY, PAL. I'VE GOT
ABSOLUTELY NO INTENTION
OF TAKING THAT JOB.
- BUT YOU...
OW! WHY DID YOU STRIKE ME?
I WAS ONLY...
- TRUST ME. YOU DON'T NEED
STRENGTH TO FIGHT EVIL,
JUST A GOOD HEART.
LOOK. THE EMPIRE
DOESN'T NEED A HERO.
IT NEEDS SOMEBODY WITH
THE VISION TO LEAD IT.
SOMEONE WHO REALLY CARES.
- TAITO.
- BESIDES, WE'LL BE AROUND
TO HELP YOU. EVERY ONE OF US.
SO IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'LL BE
ALONE IN THIS FIGHT.
- THANK YOU. THANK YOU ALL.
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
IT'S KISMET.
THE DAY NOW BELONGS
TO THE YOUNG PEOPLE
WE HAVE THE PRIVILEGE
OF STANDING BESIDE.
- YOUTH IN REVOLT.
HUMBLING THOUGHT.
BUT THAT'S AS IT SHOULD BE. YES.
- ( bell ringing )
- ( crowd exclaims in surprise )
( murmuring )
- BEHOLD!
Man: THE SWORD OF RULE!
Man 2: THE SHAWN EMPIRE
WILL BE LIFTED FROM FILTH AND
DEGRADATION TO BE BORN ANEW!
Man 3: ALL HAIL EMPEROR KEIRO!
- HEAR ME. WITH THIS, DAWNS
A NEW STAR ON THE FORTUNES
OF THIS LAND. FOR ALL TIME!
- ( people cheering )
- THE SEEDS OF CONFLICT SOWN BY
POVERTY, SUSPICION AND MALAISE
WILL BE WINNOWED AND RENDERED
UNTO THE EARTH.
OURS IS NOW A SOIL IN WHICH
TRANQUILITY AND OPULENCE
WILL TAKE ROOT!
- ( crowd cheering )
- WHAT NOW? I CAN'T HELP
BUT WONDER FRETFULLY.
- SHOKAKU, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE CONFRONTED HIM
LONG AGO.
WHATEVER HAPPENS NOW,
THE BURDEN IS MINE.
- ( people cheering )
Man 4: THE EXITS.
- Keiro: TO BUTTRESS MY VOW,
MY FIRST ACT AS EMPEROR...
...IS TO CONDEMN THE LOT OF YOU,
FOUL, BEDRAGGLED SOWERS OF
DISCORD THAT YOU ARE, TO DEATH!
- ( crowd gasps )
( all screaming )
- WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
STAND DOWN IMMEDIATELY.
- ( growling )
- YES. NOW THIS IS WHAT
I'VE BEEN CHOMPING AT
THE BIT FOR. MASSACRE.
( laughing )
FINALLY. FINALLY.
OH SWEET STARS. FINALLY.
A DEMON'S DREAM, MADE FLESH.
DUBHE, MY EMPEROR,
YOU ARE WITHOUT A DOUBT,
THE MOST EXQUISITELY
DIVERTING OF GODS.
TRULY, A BEAST WORTHY
OF ALKAID'S BLOOD LUST.
( laughing )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koyo: DARK URGES COMPEL DUBHE
TO YET DARKER ENDS.
- Keiro: ANY LOYAL CITIZEN
WOULD GIVE HIS LIFE
IF THAT WAS MY WISH.
- IS THIS IT? IS EVERYONE DEAD?
THE "PEACE" HE TALKED ABOUT?
- Keiro: ANNIHILATION, HOWEVER,
IS NOT ENOUGH...
- UNHAND THE SWORD, MY LORD!
- OH, YES!
I CAN FEEL YOUR DEMONIC POWER
BECOMING ONE WITH MY OWN.
- Koyo: EVIL GLUTS ON TRIUMPH,
IN HERO TALES,
CHAPTER TWENTY-FOUR.
"KARMA OUT OF CONTROL."
- Keiro: I LEAVE MANKIND
IN MY WAKE!