( baby crying )
- ( chuckling evilly )
- Kocho: IS THE EMPIRE
IN SUCH DISARRAY?
THESE BANDITS ARE EMBOLDENED
ENOUGH TO ACT
WITHOUT FEAR OF REPRISAL.
- ( guttural cry )
- OUR FATE IS SEALED.
I'M SORRY I FAILED YOU, TAKI!
- ( screaming )
- WHAT? BUT HOW?
- ( baby continues to cry )
- MY LORD, IT'S YOU!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( birds chirping )
- LET ME TELL YA, I KNEW THE
EMPEROR'S PLACE WOULD BE HUGE,
BUT THIS WAS UNBELIEVABLE!
LIKE EVEN HIS OWN
PERSONAL BATHTUB,
THAT THING WAS AS BIG AS A LAKE!
A GIANT, WARM LAKE INSIDE!
I ACTUALLY RAN INTO THE MAN,
EMPEROR TAIGA...
I WAS WRONG ABOUT
HIM BEING SOME BIG GUY.
NOT AT ALL.
I MEAN, WE'VE GOT A REAL
SHRIMP FOR AN EMPEROR!
( laughs )
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- WHAT'S WRONG IS THE LACK OF
JUDGMENT YOU SHOWED
BY SNEAKING INTO
THE PALACE.
IT'S MORE THAN DISTURBING.
- GEEZ, RYUKO, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO ACT LIKE IT'S
THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST CRIME.
- THAT'S NOT REALLY THE POINT.
- THERE ARE THOSE LURKING
IN THE CITY WHO DESIRE
YOUR FOOLISH HEAD AS A TROPHY!
- THAT'S RIGHT!
WE WERE WORRIED SICK ABOUT
YOU BECAUSE WE ALL KNOW
HOW STUPID YOU CAN BE!
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I EVER
ASKED YOU GUYS TO WORRY
ABOUT ME OR ANYTHING, DID I?
- DID YOU REALLY JUST SAY THAT?
- ARE YOU GUYS WORRIED,
OR DO YOU JUST LIKE TO ANNOY ME
ABOUT EVERYTHING I DO?
- TAITO!
- Ryusho: ENOUGH!
- FATHER, LET ME EXPLAIN.
- UH, YES, SIR?
- HMM.
- UH...
( laughs nervously )
( grunts )
- ( both gasp )
- I CAN FORGIVE
YOUR SHORT-SIGHTED
AND FOOLISH MISADVENTURES
IN THE CAPITAL, BOY!
BUT I CANNOT FORGIVE
THE FOOLISH ARROGANCE YOU SHOW
TO THE ONES WHO CARE FOR YOU.
YOU MUST NOT FORGET,
POWER MEANS NOTHING
IF IT IS WITHOUT COMPASSION.
IT IS ITS GUIDING HAND.
UNDERSTOOD?
- I'M SORRY, SIR.
- NO WAY!
- DID HE JUST SAY SORRY?
- ( pants )
HA!
( yells )
UH, UH, UH! AAH!
- ( gasps )
WOW! THAT IS AMAZING!
I FEEL LEFT OUT. I WISH
I COULD DO THAT KINDA STUFF.
- TO BE TOTALLY HONEST, YOU'RE
PROBABLY BETTER OFF WITHOUT IT.
- OH? WHY IS THAT?
- WELL, BECAUSE...
IF THE MEN KNOW
THAT YOU'RE STRONG,
THEY USUALLY JUST
LEAVE YOU ALONE
TO TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
- ( chuckling )
THAT'S OKAY WITH ME.
I DON'T WANNA BE TREATED
LIKE SOME WEAKLING
THAT NEEDS TO BE SAVED,
I WANNA BE OUT THERE, TOO.
JUST KICKING SOME BUTT!
I THINK IT SOUNDS KINDA FUN!
- I SUPPOSE THERE ARE
WORSE THINGS THAN THAT.
- IT'S SO EXCITING!
I CAN JUST SEE MYSELF BEING
ALL BIG AND SCARY
TO ALL THE BAD GUYS!
- HEY, RYUKO.
- YES, WHAT?
- LET'S KNOCK OFF
FOR THE DAY ALREADY.
KILLING OURSELVES WITH TRAINING
KINDA DEFEATS THE PURPOSE.
- IF YOU'RE RESTLESS,
YOU AND TAITO CAN GO
AMUSE YOURSELVES TOGETHER.
- IF THAT WAS REALLY AN OPTION
WHY DO YA THINK I'M OVER HERE
TALKING TO YOU?
THAT GUY'S IN A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT WORLD RIGHT NOW.
( grunts )
- YES, HE IS INTENSELY FOCUSED
AT THE MOMENT.
- WELL, HE'S PROBABLY
GOT A LOT ON HIS MIND
AFTER YOUR OLD MAN
DECIDED TO REARRANGE
HIS FACE FOR HIM EARLIER.
- STAY CALM AND FOCUSED.
ENVISION A SOFT TUBE
STARTING AT MY HEART,
AND EXTENDING OUTWARD,
THROUGHOUT MY BODY,
IMAGINE THAT TUBE
SLOWLY FILLING WITH LIGHT
AND ENERGY FROM DEEP WITHIN.
- THE SIGIL. DOES THAT MEAN
TAITO IS NOW TRULY ABLE
TO HARNESS ALKAID'S POWER?
- ( shouting )
- ( rumbling )
- THE POWER RELEASED THROUGH
INNER CHANNELING IS INDEED
SOMETHING TO BEHOLD.
- ( panting )
BUT IT'S STILL NOT ENOUGH TO
DEFEAT THAT BASTARD, MUSTACHE.
( exhales )
( stretching )
WELL, I GUESS THAT MEANS
I JUST GOTTA KEEP ON TRYING.
- TAITO.
- OH, RYUSHO,
IS IT LUNCHTIME, ALREADY.
- LUNCHTIME. NO,
BUT COME WITH ME.
- I REALLY DON'T WANNA STOP
WHAT I'M DOING UNLESS
YOU CAN PROMISE ME FOOD.
- TO REALIZE YOUR
ENERGY'S TRUE POTENTIAL,
YOU MUST NOT
EXHAUST ITS SOURCE.
DO SO AT YOUR OWN PERIL, MY BOY.
- ( grunts )
- Taito: OKAY! OKAY! I'M COMING!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PULL SO HARD,
YOU'LL RIP MY ARM OFF!
- WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
- Taito: WHAT IS THIS?
- YOU COULD SAY THE TIAN YI
SHRINE IN WHICH WE STAND
IS THE HEART
OF THE TEMPLE.
- IT'S THE HEART?
- THE TONG YO TEMPLE
WAS ORIGINALLY BUILT
FOR THE PURPOSE OF PROTECTING
THIS SACRED CHAMBER.
- HMM.
- TAITO, LOOK UP.
- THOSE ARE THE SIGILS.
- INDEED, THE SACRED MARKS
OF THE DIPPER BEARERS.
AND THERE...
THE SEAL OF THE EMPIRE.
- THE EMPIRE? BUT WHAT DOES THAT
HAVE TO DO WITH THIS TEMPLE?
- THIS HOLY GROUND
IS THE BIRTHPLACE
OF THE XIAN EMPIRE.
BEHOLD, THE PAINTING
AT THE CENTER DEPICTS
THE SWORD OF RULE.
- THE SWORD OF RULE.
- Ryusho: 400 YEARS AGO,
THE WORLD ROILED
LIKE A GREAT CAULDRON,
RIFE WITH CHAOS AND EVIL.
HOWEVER, A WARRIOR
NAMED SHOU APPEARED,
INTENT ON TAMING
THIS PANDEMONIUM,
ARMED WITH TWO WEAPONS
OF UNSTOPPABLE FORCE.
THE XIAN JIA LAN WU,
AND THE DIVINE POWER OF ALKAID,
WHICH THE HEAVENS
HAD IMBUED DEEP WITHIN HIM.
- THE SWORD OF RULE
WAS ONCE WIELDED BY ALKAID?
- HMM.
AFTER SHOU SUCCEEDED
IN CALMING THE LAND
AND PEACE REIGNED THROUGHOUT,
HE DECLARED TO ESTABLISH
HIS EMPIRE ON THIS VERY SPOT.
HE WOULD RULE IT
JUSTLY AS EMPEROR.
- YOU MEAN THE EMPIRE WAS
ACTUALLY CREATED BY ALKAID?
- INDEED. AND THROUGHOUT
OUR HISTORY,
WHEN THE LAND
FALLS INTO TURMOIL,
ALKAID APPEARS TO RESTORE
ORDER AND PEACE.
"WHEN SUFFERING CLOAKS
THIS LAND IN DARKNESS,
THE STAR WILL PROVIDE US LIGHT."
CONSIDER YOUR FATE,
THINK AS TO WHY YOU WERE CHOSEN
TO BEAR THIS SACRED MARK
AND THE POWER GIVEN YOU.
- WHY WAS I CHOSEN TO BE ALKAID?
WHY ME?
TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND MY FATE
OR THE RESPONSIBILITY I CARRY.
ACTUALLY, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS
"KARMA OF THE STARS" STUFF.
BUT, IF ANY OF THAT STUFF IS
WHAT BROUGHT ME TOGETHER
WITH THE DIVINE WARRIORS
AND ALL THE OTHER
PEOPLE I'VE MET SO FAR,
I GUESS THERE'S A BRIGHT SIDE
TO THIS RESPONSIBILITY CRAP,
AFTER ALL.
I MEAN, THOSE GUYS ARE
A PRETTY WEIRD BUNCH AND ALL
AND WE DO KINDA GET ON
EACH OTHER'S NERVES
FROM TIME TO TIME,
BUT THEY'RE THE BEST FRIENDS A
GUY LIKE ME COULD EVER ASK FOR.
HEY, DON'T TELL 'EM I SAID
ANY OF THIS STUFF, OKAY?
I DON'T REALLY WANT 'EM
TO GET BIG HEADS OVER IT.
- HMM.
- YOU KNOW, I'M NOT JUST SAYING
ALL THIS ABOUT THEM
BECAUSE OF THE BEATING
YOU GAVE ME EARLIER, DON'T YOU?
IT'S REALLY HOW I FEEL.
- OF COURSE IT IS.
THE WARRIOR GODS OF OLD,
ALKAID AND DUBHE,
APPEARING SIMULTANEOUSLY.
I PRAY THIS DOES NOT PORTEND
A CONFLICT THE LIKES OF WHICH
WE'VE NEVER SEEN.
- Hosei: YOU WANT
A COUPLE OF MINE? HERE YA GO!
- YEAH. WOW, THANKS.
- OH, YOU'RE OUT OF TEA.
I'LL GO GRAB YOU SOME MORE.
- THAT WAS WEIRD. WHAT'S UP?
- WELL, I SUPPOSE SOMETHING
HAS FILLED HIM WITH
THE SPIRIT OF GOODWILL.
- IT'S STILL WEIRD.
- ( birds chirping )
- IS THAT SHOKAKU?
- YOU ARE IN PERFECT HEALTH.
NO DOUBT A RESULT OF YOUR
RELENTLESS TRAINING, SIR.
- AS HIS MAJESTY'S PHYSICIAN,
YOUR TIME IS TOO VALUABLE
FOR ME TO WASTE.
FORGIVE ME.
- NO NEED FOR THAT.
THE TIME SPENT WITH
AN OLD FRIEND HAS BECOME
FAR TOO RARE FOR ME THESE DAYS.
- Ryuko: SHOKAKU!
IT'S A PLEASURE TO SEE YOU.
- Shokaku: WHEN DID YOU RETURN
FROM LIAN TONG TEMPLE?
- A FEW DAYS AGO.
- TELL ME OF YOUR JOURNEY.
HOW WAS IT?
- IT WAS QUITE AN ORDEAL.
OFFICIALS IN THE REMOTE
PROVINCES USE THE DISTANCE
FROM THE CAPITAL AS A SHIELD
TO LINE THEIR POCKETS.
WHILE THE LOCALS OFTEN STEAL
JUST TO PROVIDE THEMSELVES
BASIC SUSTENANCE.
WAR AND DISORDER ARE RAMPANT
AND THE POPULOUS LIVES IN FEAR.
SORROW AND DESTRUCTION
SEEMED TO AWAIT US
AT EVERY NEW DESTINATION.
IT MAKES ONE QUESTION
NOT ONLY THE WISDOM,
BUT THE VERY MOTIVES
OF THE EMPEROR AND HIS CABINET.
PLEASE, FORGIVE ME, SIR.
I SHOULD LEARN TO
BETTER HOLD MY TONGUE.
I ASK THAT YOU DISREGARD
MY CARELESS WORDS.
GOOD DAY.
- ONE MOMENT, PLEASE.
IF YOU HAVE CONCERNS,
OR FIND YOURSELF TROUBLED,
PLEASE, SEEK ME OUT.
I SWEAR THAT I SHALL ALWAYS
WELCOME YOU FIRST AND FOREMOST
AS A FRIEND.
- THAT IS VERY KIND.
- Shokaku: IF I CANNOT
HELP EASE YOUR MIND,
I WILL INTRODUCE YOU
TO SOMEONE WHO CAN.
- ( Laila grunting with effort )
- ( staffs swooshing )
- Rinmei: NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
- ( Hosei grunting with effort )
- ( grunting with effort )
- THE PURPOSE OF THE DIVINE
WARRIORS IS TO MAINTAIN PEACE
AND ORDER IN THE XIAN EMPIRE.
IT IS OUR DESTINY,
OUR SACRED MANDATE.
WE CANNOT FAIL.
- ( grunts )
HEY, RYUKO!
( screams )
( laughs )
WHOA, SORRY.
- IF ALKAID AND DUBHE
CLASH SWORDS,
IT WILL MOST LIKELY RESULT
IN THE EMPIRE'S DEMISE.
BUT CAN I POSSIBLY CONVINCE
TAITO THAT HE GIVE UP
HIS QUEST TO DESTROY KEIRO
WITHOUT LOSING HIS RESPECT?
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH
THE LONG FACE THERE?
- AH, A TRIVIAL MATTER.
- OH, GOOD!
- ( Laila grunting )
- THAT'S THE EVENING BELL.
I SHOULD START
PREPARING TONIGHT'S MEAL.
- ( laughing )
SO, ARE YOU READY
TO GIVE UP THE CROWN?
- DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
HEY, RINMEI! WHAT ARE YOU
WHIPPING UP FOR US TONIGHT?
- STEAMED PORK DUMPLINGS!
ONE OF MY SPECIALTIES.
- I'M GONNA EAT THOSE THINGS
UNTIL I POP WIDE OPEN.
- DREAM ON, PAL, IT'S GONNA BE
ME STUFFING MY FACE TONIGHT.
- WHAT, YOU GONNA TELL US
TO STOP?
- I'M NOT.
- WELL, THAT'S WEIRD.
"A MEAL NOT QUARRELED OVER
NOURISHES BOTH BODY AND SOUL".
THAT'S MORE LIKE WHAT YOU'D SAY.
- THIS IS DIFFERENT.
- ( both gasp )
- I WOULD MOVE HEAVEN, EARTH
AND ANY FOOL THAT DARES
STAND BETWEEN ME
AND MY SHARE
OF RINMEI'S DUMPLINGS!
- WHAT A SHAME. THESE DUMPLINGS
ARE LEGENDARY,
AND YOU'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO
SETTLE FOR WATCHING ME EAT THEM.
- I'LL BE WATCHING YOU
EAT MY SCRAPS THEN.
I'LL PROBABLY GIVE YOU
ONE OUT OF PITY.
- GEEZ, IS IT REALLY WORTH
GETTING THIS WORKED UP
OVER PLAIN, OLD DUMPLINGS?
BOYS ARE SO PRIMITIVE.
( sighs )
LIKE CAVEMEN.
- WE GO AT HER SIGN!
- GO!
- ( all yelling )
( all grunting with effort )
- YOUR UNREFINED PALATES
COULD NOT COMPREHEND
THE COMPLEXITIES OF OUR COOKING!
THEY'D BE LOST TO YOUR RABID
GLUTTONY. SO TASTE DEFEAT!
- YOU'VE HAD THEM BEFORE AND
YOU WON'T EVEN LET ME TRY THEM?
WHERE THE HELL'S
THE JUSTICE IN THAT?
- YEAH, I SHARED MY LUNCH
WITH YOU TODAY, TAITO!
COME ON! CAN'T YOU EVEN
TRY TO BE THE KINDA GUY
THAT RETURNS THE
FAVOR ONCE IN A WHILE?
- NO WAY!
- SO DUMB!
- ( all grunting )
- ( screams )
- ALL RIGHT! THAT'D BE ONE DOWN!
- HM, DAILY TRAINING
HAS ITS BENEFITS, DOES IT NOT?
- ( both grunting )
- MAN, HE'S LIKE A BOULDER.
HE WON'T BUDGE AT ALL!
I NEVER KNEW HE WAS THIS STRONG.
- HIS POWER SEEMS TO INCREASE
BY THE DAY.
PERHAPS HE'S HARNESSED
WHAT HAD LAIN DORMANT IN HIM
ALL THESE YEARS.
- BUT STILL...
- I CAN'T LOSE!
- OH, WOW!
IT'S RIDICULOUS, BUT WOW!
( screaming )
- LAILA!
- THE COLUMN!
- LAILA, NO!
- ( exclaims in fear )
- ( all yelling )
- ( whimpering )
- LAILA, ARE YOU OKAY?
- I GUESS. THANKS, HOSEI!
( giggling )
- LET'S CALL THAT ONE A DRAW.
- SURE.
- Laila: YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING!
- ( Hosei chuckles )
- THAT'S RIGHT!
A THREE MAN FORCE! RIGHT?
- IF YOU THREE
CAN WORK LIKE THAT,
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU WON'T DEFEAT HIM!
- I CAN'T WAIT!
- YES, MA'AM!
AS OF NOW WE'VE GOT ALKAID
AND THREE OTHER DIPPER BEARERS
ON OUR TEAM.
TOGETHER WE CAN
TAKE CARE OF OLD FURRY LIP
WITH NO PROBLEM.
- ALL FOUR OF US? YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE FIGHT TOGETHER,
WE CAN TOTALLY TAKE HIM DOWN.
YEAH.
- THAT JERK DOESN'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST US.
- ( softly ) YOU'RE WRONG.
- I SEE. SO YOU'RE THE CHAMPION
AGAIN TODAY, ARE YOU?
- YOU BET!
- ALL I WANTED
WAS JUST A LITTLE TASTE.
- ( Laila grunts in anger )
GEEZ! YOU'RE SUCH A GREEDY PIG!
DON'T FORGET YOU'VE GOTTA
GIVE RYUKO HIS FAIR SHARE,
TOO. RIGHT?
- UH, NO, I'M FINE.
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
- HUH?
- OH, I THOUGHT YOU'D BEEN
"MISSING MY GIFTS
AT THE HEARTH SIDE"
ALL THIS TIME YOU'VE BEEN GONE.
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER, RYUKO?
- NO.
NOTHING IMPORTANT ANYWAY.
- MM.
- HAVE YOU SEEN LORD KEIRO?
- HE'S GONE.
HE AND ENSIGN KOCHO WENT AHEAD.
THEY'VE ENTERED
THE REBELS' BASE.
- ALONE?
WHY THE HELL DID THEY
EVEN BRING US ALONG?
- MY LORD,
THERE IS NO ONE LEFT STANDING.
- THIS VIEW WILL RESEMBLE
A MERE CANDLE FLAME
COMPARED TO THE
HOLOCAUST TO COME.
I'LL LEAVE MY WAKE IN ASH!
- AS IT SHOULD BE.
- ( baby crying )
- MY LORD, IT'S YOU!
MY LORD, I BEG OF YOU,
PLEASE TAKE US WITH YOU.
OUR SURVIVAL RESTS
IN YOUR HANDS.
A TRUE WARRIOR'S STEEL WILL RID
THIS WORLD OF SCUM AND CHAOS.
YOU WILL BE THE ONE
TO SET IT RIGHT.
- I HAVE NO DESIRE FOR
A GROVELING SLAVE. BE GONE.
- I AM BY NO MEANS A WEAKLING.
I WILL PROVE MY STRENGTH AND
PLEDGE MY FEALTY TO YOU, SIR.
- HERE IS YOUR WEAKNESS. CAN YOU
LEAVE THIS CHILD BEHIND?
- IF YOU REQUIRE IT,
I WILL SEVER MY BOND
TO MY BELOVED DAUGHTER,
AND TAKE UP YOUR BANNER
IN HER PLACE.
- ( cooing )
- LORD KEIRO, I GIVE YOU
ALL I HAVE, MY ONLY CHILD,
IN HOPES SHE CAN SERVE YOU
IN YOUR GOAL.
- TELL ME YOUR NAME.
- THAT DAY I SURRENDERED
MYSELF AND MY PARENTAL RIGHT
TO LORD KEIRO.
I AM HIS RIGHT HAND, HIS SHADOW.
- SHOW YOURSELF!
- TRULY NO MEANS TO PENETRATE
THE GENERAL'S SPHERE.
- I'LL PENETRATE YOUR SKULL,
YOU RAT!
- ENOUGH.
- BUT, SIR...
- I SAID, STOP!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YES, WELL, ALKAID HAS
SEEN FIT TO PLACE HIMSELF
AMONG THE "NON-CELESTIAL"
LUMINARIES IN OUR FAIR CAPITAL.
- WHAT? THAT BRAT IS THERE?
MY LORD!
- SO YOU'VE ARRIVED.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR THE CHALLENGE.
I DO NOT WISH TO BE
DISAPPOINTED, ALKAID.
- ( theme song playing )
- Ryuko: RYUKO'S HEART
IS IN CONFLICT WHEN LOYALTIES
THREATEN TO RIP IT IN TWO.
- Shokaku: MOST OF US
WOULD DENY OUR FATE.
WE DON'T HAVE THE WHEREWITHAL
TO SEE WHAT MUST BE DONE.
- Ryuko: TAITO. COULD I DO IT?
- Taito: YOU FEELING
CRUDDY OR SOMETHING?
- Ryuko: NOW IT SEEMS
THE VERY PATH THAT LED ME
TO FORGE THOSE BONDS
DEMANDS I BREAK THEM VIOLENTLY.
- Shimei: SEE, MY FRIEND,
I'M A VERITABLE
FOUNT OF KNOWLEDGE.
KNOWLEDGE THAT CONCERNS YOU.
- Ryuko: NEXT TIME
ON HERO TALES,
UNDER THE COLORLESS
GLOW OF THE LUNAR SPHERE,
A HARSH TRUTH IS REVEALED,
IN CHAPTER 12:
"A GLIMMER IN THE MOONLIGHT."
THEN WHAT?
WE COMMIT MURDER?