- ( thunder rumbling )
- CAPTAIN, DARE I ASK WHY
WE SEEM TO BE IN SUCH A RUSH?
JUST WHAT EXACTLY IS WAITING
FOR US IN THE CAPITAL?
- THE STARS OF THE GREAT DIPPER
CAST THEIR LIGHT UNEVENLY.
- I TAKE THAT TO MEAN
SOMETHING IS AMISS?
- INDEED, THERE IS.
THE FIERCE, WARLIKE TWO
STAND OUT AMONG THEIR BRETHREN
IN THE HEAVENS TONIGHT.
IF I READ THE SKY CORRECTLY,
ALKAID AND DUBHE STAND ON
THE VERGE OF BATTLE.
THAT BEING THE CASE,
I HAVE A DUTY TO FULFILL.
AS DOES EACH ONE OF THE FIVE.
COME NOW.
LET'S MEET OUR FATE HEAD ON.
- ( theme song playing )
- KEIRO!
CAN HE...
CAN HE REALLY BE MY FATHER?
- DIE, BASTARD!
- IF YOU INTEND TO KILL MY LORD,
YOU'D BETTER BE PREPARED
TO DEAL WITH ME FIRST.
FIRE!
- YOU CALL THIS A FIGHT?
COME ON.
GET DOWN HERE
AND FACE ME LIKE A WARRIOR.
- WE'RE OFFICIALLY
OUT OF OUR DEPTH HERE.
I SAY WE RETREAT AND LIVE TO
FIGHT MOUSTACHE ANOTHER DAY.
- HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
- RYUKO. THE PARADISE CAVE.
WE'RE NOT VERY FAR
FROM THERE, ARE WE?
- NO, WE'RE NOT.
NOW. THIS MIGHT BE
OUR ONLY CHANCE OF ESCAPE.
- ( panting )
- THERE'S THE ENTRANCE.
- THEY'RE FLEEING INTO
PARADISE CAVE. DON'T LOSE THEM.
- ( shouting )
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE COMING BACK
FOR YOU, MOUSTACHE.
MY BUSINESS WITH YOU
IS NOWHERE NEAR OVER.
- HURRY UP.
- DAMN IT! THE BASTARDS
HAVE SEALED THE ENTRANCE.
- ( grunting )
- JUMP ACROSS! LET'S GO!
RANK COWARDS.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
- LEAVE THEM.
A LARGE FORCE WILL
ONLY SLOW US DOWN.
YOU AND I SHOULD BE
MORE THAN SUFFICIENT.
- BUT, SIR, THE PARADISE CAVE
IS NOTORIOUSLY TREACHEROUS.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE
WE WON'T GET LOST.
- HOWEVER LABYRINTHINE
OUR PASSAGE MAY BE,
IF FATE DECREES IT,
WE WILL FIND THEM.
- ( chuckling )
MY MOST SINCERE APOLOGIES.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE THE TROUBLE
I MUST'VE CAUSED YOU.
BUT, THERE AGAIN,
LEARNING YOU'VE GOT
A WANTED MAN IN YOUR MIDST
IS A BIT PETRIFYING.
I COULD BUT WATCH
HELPLESSLY AS HE FLED.
- FORGIVE ME FOR NOT BEING
ABLE TO THINK YOU A COWARD.
- HOW KIND.
LOOKS DO DECEIVE, THOUGH.
STRIP AWAY THE GRUFF
EXTERIOR AND AT HEART
I'M A MEWLING CHILD.
NIGHT AIR IS BAD FOR THE SKIN.
I SUGGEST YOU TAKE YOUR LEAVE.
- ( scoffs )
- YOU'LL REGRET THIS, PRIEST.
I SWEAR.
- I'M SURE I WILL.
- SHOULD I NOT HAVE, THEN?
I'M CONFUSED.
LADY CHOKA WISHED
TO QUELL A PLOT AGAINST ME.
HOW COULD I NOT ACQUIESCE?
- INDEED, HIGHNESS.
DID SHE DESCRIBE THIS PLOT?
- WELL, NOT EXACTLY, NO.
I GAVE CONSENT FOOLISHLY,
DIDN'T I?
- TROUBLE YOURSELF NOT,
YOUR MAJESTY.
YOU'VE DONE NO WRONG.
- YES, WELL. IF YOU SAY SO.
- THAT WAS CLOSE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO SCARED.
- WELL, THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF FOR NOW.
- SO, I'M GUESSING THIS CAVE
WAS MADE BY PEOPLE, AM I RIGHT?
- VERY GOOD.
PARADISE CAVE WAS ACTUALLY
CARVED OUT
OVER A PERIOD OF CENTURIES
BY ASCETICS
FROM THE TONG YO SHRINE.
THEY USED IT
AS A TRAINING GROUND.
MONKS OF THE ORDER
HAVE KNOWN ITS LAYOUT BY HEART
FOR GENERATIONS.
- SO, KEIRO'S GOONS
ARE SURE TO GET LOST.
AND OUR SIDE'S
THE ONLY ONE THAT KNOWS
ALL OF THE SECRET EXITS?
- THAT'S THE IDEA.
HERE WE ARE.
- KOCHO.
- SIR?
- TAKI'S BIRTHDAY
IS APPROACHING.
- AH. SO IT IS, MY LORD.
SO IT IS.
- WHAT'S MORE?
THE AGE IS ALMOST UPON HER
WHEN SHE COULD MAKE THE
EMPEROR AN EXCELLENT WIFE.
AN ENCOURAGING THOUGHT,
IS IT NOT?
- QUITE, MY LORD.
- AGES AGO, I HAD A CHILD.
- YOU DID, SIR? YOU HAD
A CHILD OF YOUR OWN?
SO, WHAT BECAME OF THEM?
- I CHOSE TO LEAVE HIM
TO HIS FATE WHILE DOGGEDLY
PURSUING MY OWN.
- YOU WHAT?
- I DID SO OUT OF NECESSITY.
I FELT A SAPLING AT HEEL
WOULD ONLY ENCUMBER MY PROGRESS.
IF HE STILL LIVES,
HE DOES SO AT DESTINY'S WHIM.
- YOUR MASTER,
DO YOU THINK HE'S ALRIGHT?
- AH, THE OLD MAN'S GOT
A FEW TRICKS UP HIS SLEEVE.
- WHAT A GREAT GUY.
YOU CERTAINLY DON'T MEET
PEOPLE LIKE THAT EVERY DAY.
NOT THAT MINE'S A SLOUCH
OR ANYTHING.
BUT YOU ARE PRETTY LUCKY
TO HAVE HIM AS A DAD.
- YEAH.
- DON'T FRET.
YOU COME FROM GOOD STOCK.
QUITE GOOD.
THE ONLY SON OF MY LORD KEIRO.
- NO. I WON'T BELIEVE IT.
- OH, YEAH.
THAT'S JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
- SO, IF WE LEAVE YOU
TO DEAL WITH KEIRO
ALL ON YOUR OWN,
THE QUESTION BECOMES,
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO HANDLE HIS ARMY?
- THAT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH
CONSIDERING HOW HUGE IT IS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
HOW DOES A GUY LIKE HIM
GET SO MANY FOLLOWERS?
- BEST THING FOR US
TO DO RIGHT NOW
IS FIND THE REST OF THE FIVE.
I MEAN IT'S NOT LIKE
WE CAN TAKE ON
THE WHOLE XUAN LONG PLATOON.
- THE FIVE?
- YEAH. WE GET ALL THE DIVINE
WARRIORS IN ON THIS
AND WE MIGHT HAVE A SHOT.
- ALL FIVE OF THEM
FIGHTING ON THE SAME SIDE?
- THAT'D BE GREAT!
- YEAH. SWEET, HUH?
- FIVE AGAINST
AN IMPERIAL REGIMENT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- IT WON'T WORK?
- WELL, TO BEGIN WITH,
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
THAT THE OTHER TWO
WILL JOIN OUR SIDE.
THEIR POLITICS AREN'T
NECESSARILY OURS.
THE FIVE ONLY HAVE
ONE DUTY TO FULFILL.
BUT, DON'T YOU WORRY.
AT THE VERY LEAST,
I CAN PERSONALLY GUARANTEE
THAT THE THREE OF US HERE
WOULD NEVER THINK
OF TURNING AGAINST YOU.
RIGHT, RYUKO?
- OKAY, WHAT EXACTLY
IS HIS PROBLEM?
- ( whispering ) KEIRO. KEIRO.
( screaming )
- ( grunting )
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
SERIOUSLY.
- SORRY. I WAS A BIT
PREOCCUPIED THERE.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
- MUST I APOLOGIZE AGAIN?
- WATCH IT.
NICE ONE. REALLY.
- AH, OUR EXIT ISN'T FAR NOW.
- WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- ( all gasp )
- THING IS HUGE.
- ( loud rumbling )
- THAT SOUND. WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( all gasp )
- RYUKO!
- RYUKO! TAITO!
- ANOTHER CLOSE ONE.
YOU ASLEEP ON YOUR FEET?
COME ON.
- THAT'S IT. I DON'T CARE
IF YOU ARE "PREOCCUPIED".
SNAP THE HELL OUTTA YOUR MOOD
BEFORE SOMEBODY
REALLY GETS HURT.
DON'T GLARE AT ME!
- WHAT HE'S TRYING TO SAY
IS THAT IF YOU DON'T
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER,
WHAT KINDA HOPE
DO WE HAVE AS A TEAM?
I MEAN, I KNOW
I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
THE ONLY REAL CHANCE WE'VE GOT
OF DEFEATING MOUSTACHE...
- STOP PATRONIZING ME!
- RYUKO.
- THE DIVINE WARRIORS
ARE NOT ALKAID'S SERVANTS.
LEAST OF ALL, ME.
AND DON'T THINK
ME AN ALLY JUST BECAUSE
I'M ALONG FOR THE JOURNEY.
IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A ROLE TO PLAY.
- SO WHAT?
WE'RE NOT FRIENDS ANYMORE?
- TRUTH BE TOLD.
SINCE I'VE MET YOU,
MY LIFE HAS BEEN
IN COMPLETE SHAMBLES.
THANKS TO YOU,
I AM NOW THE ENEMY
OF AN IMPERIAL GENERAL.
I'VE HAD TO FLEE THE TEMPLE.
MY HOME.
IF NOT FOR YOU,
I MIGHT HAVE HAD
SOMETHING LIKE A NORMAL LIFE.
- ( chuckling )
DON'T HOLD BACK, MIZAR.
SPEAK YOUR MIND.
INDEED, THE MORE YOU LET FLY,
THE MORE RIVETED I BECOME.
- YOU MEAN THAT? REALLY?
- NO, I...
I LASHED OUT.
MY MIND'S IN A FOG.
- FORGIVE ME.
- A FOG?
- ( rumbling )
- NOT AGAIN.
- WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- IT'S GETTING CLOSER!
- IT'S MOUSTACHE!
- BUT HOW?
HOW DID HE FIND US?
- SO, THE HEAVENS DO CALL
FOR BLOOD TONIGHT.
YOU OUGHT TO BE PLEASED.
I'VE COME TO FACE YOU
LIKE A WARRIOR.
- WE HAVE NO CHOICE NOW.
HE'S FORCING OUR HAND.
- HIS LAPDOGS AREN'T HERE,
THOUGH, SO I THINK THE ODDS
ARE STACKED IN OUR FAVOR.
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
- YEAH. I'M READY LIKE
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
KEIRO, LET'S GO.
- RINMEI, PROTECT LAILA.
- YOU GOT IT.
- ALRIGHT.
IT'S THREE AGAINST TWO.
LET'S ATTACK THEM EN MASSE.
- YEAH.
- RYUKO!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YES!
- ( grunting )
- HOSEI!
- TAITO!
- YOU'RE DEALING WITH ME, BOY.
AH, AN OUTER RESERVOIR.
AS OBSOLETE A SKILL
AS THEY COME THESE DAYS.
- WHAT?
- ( grunting )
- JERK! THAT WAS
A DAMN CHEAP TRICK
YOU PLAYED ON HOSEI.
- SUCH IS OUR FATE.
I STAND HERE WITHOUT
THE AID OF MY SOLDIERS
AND, YOU, WITHOUT
THE AID OF YOUR FRIENDS.
DESTINY ALLOTS US NO BULWARK
IN THIS FIGHT, SAVE OUR FISTS.
COME, ALKAID.
BEDECK MY GLORIOUS ASCENSION
IN YOUR BLOOD!
- SHUT UP.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S GOING TO BLEED!
- OH, NO.
- I FEEL IT.
ALKAID AND DUBHE
ARE ABOUT TO GO AT IT FULL ON.
- YOU'VE MANAGED
SOME DEGREE OF CONTROL
OVER YOUR INNER RESERVOIR.
COMMENDABLE.
- I'M FULL OF SURPRISES,
AREN'T I?
- NO. DON'T DO IT.
- RYUKO, WHY DID YOU HESITATE?
- HOW COULD YOU?
YOU AND YOUR FORCE'S SUBMISSION
TO THIS WARMONGERING TRAITOR
CASTS A PALL OVER
THE EMPEROR'S GOOD NAME.
- YOU SEE, BUT, DARKLY.
WHAT MATTERS THE EMPEROR'S
NAME IF THE EMPIRE DIES?
HIS LORDSHIP KEIRO
IS THIS LAND'S LAST,
BEST HOPE FOR SURVIVAL!
- UNLIKE YOU,
I DON'T NEED TRICKS.
THE ONLY THING I NEED
TO SEND YOU STRAIGHT
TO HELL IS MY FIST.
- ALKAID!
- ( screaming )
- IF KEIRO REALLY IS MY FATHER,
THIS ISN'T MERELY A CLASH
BETWEEN TWO CELESTIAL DEITIES.
IT'S A FIGHT BETWEEN
MY CLOSEST FRIEND
AND MY OWN FLESH AND BLOOD.
- ALKAID, HAVE YOU EVEN
THE FAINTEST NOTION
OF WHY SOMEONE OF MY ILK
CONDESCENDS TO FIGHT LIKE THIS?
POWER, YOU FOOL.
A MAN'S WORTH IS MEASURED
IN VOLUMES OF BLOOD SPILT,
OF LIVES DEVOURED.
FOR HE WHO WOULD RULE THE WORLD
MUST FIRST SEE THE WISDOM
OF ABSOLUTE CRUELTY.
- OH, YEAH? WELL, I DON'T THINK
YOU KNOW THE FIRST THING
ABOUT BEING A MAN.
WHAT GOOD IS POWER
IF IT MAKES YOU A SAVAGE?
- SIMPLE, IMPUDENT VERMIN!
I AM THE TOLL THIS LAND
MUST PAY FOR PEACE.
- FOR PEACE?
- AND IF SAVAGERY BE THE MANTEL
I MUST DON TO SECURE
THE PEOPLE'S FORTUNE,
SO BE IT!
- TAITO!
- FEAR NOT.
THE WARRIORS I'VE SLAIN
SURVIVE WITHIN ME.
THEIRS IS THE STRENGTH
BY WHICH I WILL LEAD
THIS EMPIRE TO PEACE.
- THEY'RE NOTHING MORE
THAN SACRIFICIAL LAMBS TO YOU.
- ONLY WHEN I'M ATOP THE THRONE,
WILL THE FALLEN TRULY HAVE REST.
- TO HELL WITH YOU.
- IN YOUR PLACE,
I WOULD COUNT MYSELF PROUD
TO BE SUCH A SACRIFICE.
- TO HELL WITH YOU!
( screaming )
- OH, NO. ALKAID'S POWER
HAS TAKEN THE REINS.
- DIE, ALKAID!
- ( Laila screaming ) TAITO!
WAKE UP!
COME ON, YOU GOTTA WAKE UP.
- ( shouting )
RINMEI! HOSEI!
GET TAITO AND LAILA
OUT OF HERE NOW!
I'LL STAY AND FEND OFF KEIRO.
- NO, DON'T.
- RYUKO, YOU CAN'T.
- GO!
- WAIT, PLEASE. NO!
- FAREWELL, RYUKO.
- THAT HAS TO BE THEM.
- THROW THOSE PEOPLE A LIFELINE,
IMMEDIATELY.
- FAREWELL, TAITO.
IF SUCH IS YOUR VERDICT,
I AM PREPARED TO DIE.
DO AS YOU WILL.
- YOU WOULD FORFEIT YOUR
OWN LIFE FOR THEIR SAKE?
QUITE AN ADMIRABLE TRAIT,
I HAVE TO ADMIT.
MY LORD, I BEG YOU
TO SHOW THIS MAN CLEMENCY.
- YOU BEG ON BEHALF
OF THE ENEMY?
MY LORD, THIS MAN
SHOULD BE EXECUTED.
- A WORD WITH YOU, SIR?
IF I MAY.
- WHAT?
- DOCTOR, YOU'RE...
- FORGIVE MY INTRUSION,
YOUR LORDSHIP.
- SHOKAKU,
WHAT IS YOUR BUSINESS?
- I HAVE COME HERE TO PLEA
FOR THIS YOUNG MAN'S LIFE.
HIS ACTIONS WERE COMMITTED
AT THE BEHEST OF FATE,
NOT BY HIMSELF, PER SE.
NOR NEED HE BE AN ENEMY.
AS A DIVINE WARRIOR,
HIS ONLY NECESSARY ROLE
IN THIS LIFE
IS TO ACT AS A LEVEE.
AND IF I MAY BE SO BOLD, SIR,
THAT IS ALL
ANY OF US REALLY ARE.
- ( gasps )
- YOU, YOU'RE ONE OF US.
ONE OF THE FIVE.
- MY STAR IS ALIOTH. THE WISE.
AND IF IT PLEASES YOU,
MY FIRST DUTY IS TO THE EMPIRE.
NEITHER TO DUBHE NOR TO ALKAID.
I WILL DO ANYTHING
TO SEE THE LAND THRIVE.
WHATEVER THE COST,
WHATEVER THE SACRIFICE.
AND, I KNOW
IN MY HEART OF HEARTS,
FROM THE FIRE IN HIS EYES
AS I SAY THIS NOW,
MY FRIEND WOULD AVOW THE SAME.
BEFORE YOU METE OUT PUNISHMENT,
CONSIDER THAT CLOSELY, LORD.
WOULDN'T YOU PREFER INSTEAD
HAVING MIZAR AND I
AT YOUR BECK AND CALL?
- AM I THEN TO CLING
TO KEIRO'S HEEL?
- ( laughs ) WELL SAID, DOCTOR.
- ABSURD.
MUST WE BEFRIEND A FOE?
LENIENCY INVITES DISASTER.
HE IS OUR SWORN ENEMY!
- I BELIEVE THE OLD ADAGE IS,
"KEEP YOUR FRIENDS CLOSE,
KEEP YOUR ENEMIES CLOSER."
RYUKO, HAVEN'T YOU
ANYTHING TO SAY?
- ANSWER ME THIS.
WHILE TRADING BLOWS WITH TAITO,
YOU AVERRED TO BRING
PEACE AND PROSPERITY
TO THIS LAND.
DO YOU STILL?
- YES.
- RYUKO.
- ( Japanese song playing )
- Koyo: HE TURNS AROUND,
BUT HIS FRIEND
NO LONGER REMAINS.
- WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
PROTECTING ONE ANOTHER
OUT HERE.
NO ONE IS ALONE!
- ALL WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
IS ACCORDING TO OUR FATE.
RYUKO KNEW THAT.
HE WOULDN'T BLAME YOU.
- I THOUGHT WE WERE
OF THE SAME SPIRIT.
THAT WE COULD COMMUNICATE
WITHOUT WORDS.
THE TRUTH IS, I DIDN'T KNOW
HIM AND HE DIDN'T KNOW ME.
- Koyo: NEXT TIME,
ON HERO TALES.
THEIR SHIP SAILS ONWARD.
IN CHAPTER FOURTEEN,
"THE DOU YA CHANGES COURSE."
- Taito: I DON'T WANT TO BE
ALKAID ANY MORE.
I DON'T WANT THIS CURSE.