[roars]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[growls]
No way!
The town is busting
at the seams with youma!
For real?
Do we know if any people
have been hurt?
No idea, but they've already
issued an evacuation order.
Let's hurry!
♪
-[yells]
-[sword clangs]
-[growling]
-[YOMI grunts]
♪
Ikaruga!
Yomi?
Where's the rest
of your squad?
We got separated.
I don't know
where anyone else is.
Yeah, it's the same
for me, too.
Our enemies are very strong.
True.
At least we're not
fighting alone.
I've got your back!
Hmm.
And I've got yours!
[growling]
[BOTH]
Fuenzan!
[yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[HIBARI whimpering]
[NARAKU] There are a lot
of youma out there.
The shinobi are doing
their best, but...
[KAGURA]
We gotta be careful.
We don't want any people
to get hurt in the fray.
That means...
Kagura,
you're going to do it,
aren't you?
Mmm. Ha!
Right, here I go!
Super Shinobi Kekkai Barrier!
[pulsing]
♪
A barrier of this magnitude
should minimize
the overall damage to the city.
Wait a second.
That's right, Naraku.
There will be
a few side effects.
[gasping]
[ALL gasping]
-[RYOBI screams]
-[RYONA giggles]
[screams, cries]
What the...
What is that?
[YOZAKURA]
It looks like a kekkai barrier!
[gasping]
What's happening?
[shrieks]
That's weird.
[KAGURA] Good news, in the
kekkai barrier I just made,
all shinobi gain
"Frantic" status!
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[IKARUGA]
I can't fight naked!
You saved me! Thank you.
[YOMI] Ikaruga.
Your breasts are under attack!
Uh...
-[giggles]
-[IKARUGA] Hey, Katsuragi!
The super shinobi kekkai barrier
is the one responsible
for our clothes going MIA.
It also grants us
"frantic" status
which means our attacks
will be crazy powerful.
[KATSURAGI giggling]
I know! But you have to focus!
[KATSURAGI] I don't get why
you're freaking out so much.
I mean, come on,
it's not like
we haven't fought
this way before.
That is enough!
Uh, guys?
I hate to interrupt,
but we kind of...
[BOTH gasp]
[YOUMA growling]
...have some bigger problems
at the moment.
Homura, this sucks!
Fighting youma in my underwear
is way too embarrassing!
You think so?
I mean, I don't have feelings
so I couldn't care less.
Yeah, me either.
It doesn't bother me at all.
You're only saying that
because you have
ginormous watermelon tits,
you big braggart!
[HOMURA] Mirai, there's no time
for embarrassment.
[MIRAI]
Hmm.
Let's go, ladies!
Yeah! I think I may actually
fight better in my underwear!
It's the same for me.
I feel like
I'm way more aerodynamic.
[MIRAI]
Take this!
[chuckles]
Time to make the best
of a bad situation.
[FUBUKI]
Rasetsu.
I'm going to join the fight.
Right.
I'll kill
all those shinobi myself.
[whooshing]
Yes, what do you want?
Gekkou. Senkou.
No.
Why are you doing this,
Lady Fubuki?
[FUBUKI]
I told you why.
The shinobi must be destroyed.
Hold on, is that where your
sense of justice comes from?
That's correct.
I don't understand.
We had nothing
but respect for you.
You left us behind,
but that respect still remained.
Regardless...
We won't allow you
to continue this mad scheme!
[BOTH] No matter what,
we will stop you!
How humorous.
Juju!
♪
[wind whooshing]
[gasps]
♪
[grunts]
[gasps]
Too easy.
[grunts]
[panting]
[growls]
Oh. You still have
some fight left.
[grunts]
[yelling]
-[MIYABI yells]
-[sword clanging]
Uhh! Beautiful!
You're flawless, Miyabi!
[fawning]
Wow, your attacks
are so adorable,
how can you possibly be
that cute, Hibari?
My sweet Miyabi!
[BOTH chuckle]
[IMU/YAGYU] The super shinobi
kekkai barrier is awesome!
[MIYABI] Imu!
Attack the enemy!
[HIBARI]
Yagyu, I could use your help!
[IMU/YAGYU]
You got it!
[whooshing]
Our attacks
are totally working!
Yeah, it's like
we're super-duper strong!
[YOZAKURA] Even so, we can't
afford to let our guard down!
[wolves growling]
[grunts]
Check it out, you guys.
I defeated a bunch of youma
all by myself!
-[YUMI gasps]
-[MINORI yelps]
Yeah, this is
probably bad news.
[gasps]
What the...
[rumbling]
[SHIKI] Is it just me
or is that thing getting
really big, really fast?
♪
[roaring]
[gasps]
What is that?
[roars]
[RENKA]
Whoa.
[MINORI] How are we gonna fight
a youma this big?
[screams]
[grunts]
It's so fast!
[HOMURA]
Yumi!
[YUMI]
Homura! Miyabi!
[MIYABI] Did that thing
just get bigger?
We have to be careful.
It's very agile.
Great. So it has both
speed and power.
That's awesome.
[RYONA]
Hey there!
Perhaps I could be
of assistance!
Ta-da!
Uh, I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
I'm saying that I can totally
tie myself up bondage style.
Isn't that like super amazing?
Hey, Yumi,
since you're back there,
would you mind dripping
some hot wax on me?
Shut up, you pervy dog!
Ryona, you said
you could help, right?
What did you have in mind?
Not only do I have a plan,
I have lots of extra rope, too.
Here, see for yourself.
As you can tell,
this rope is made
from a super durable material.
We can use it to weave
an even bigger rope,
tie up the youma,
and save the day!
What you guys think?
Mm. Well, it's at least
worth a try.
Sounds pretty crazy.
But hey, sometimes crazy works.
[blades clanging]
[screams]
[clanging]
[MINORI screams]
Let's go, Ryona!
'Kay!
[yelling]
[grunts]
[whooping, laughing]
Just leave the rest to me!
[RYONA giggling]
[roaring]
♪
[YOUMA grunting]
[RYONA] It's tied up good
and tight! Have fun!
Secret Ninja Art: Black Ice!
Secret Ninja Art:
Resonate!
Purgatorio of Good and Evil!
Let's go!
[ALL yelling]
[YOUMA roars]
[rumbling]
Nailed it!
Hooray!
It's finally immobilized.
-Now, kill it!
-[ASUKA] No!
[MIYABI]
Asuka?
Why on Earth
would you stop us?
Because...
I wanna handle this one.
Are you sure?
♪
Super-Secret Ninja Art:
Fuma Korin!
I've never heard
of "Fuma Korin."
♪
What is this?
Where's that thing going?
♪
[chuckles softly]
-Bye bye!
-It worked!
Way to go, Asuka!
[ASUKA groaning]
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt
defeating the youma?
I didn't defeat it.
I sealed it away.
Huh?
Please hang in there.
So she used "Fuma Korin."
[footsteps receding]
We have failed, again.
It's just not fair.
Why can't we stop her?
Excellent job, everybody!
Thanks, Kagura!
Hey, Asuka,
looks like it worked!
Yeah.
Okay then,
I'll lower the barrier.
No, wait!
[YUMI]
But why?
The fight is over.
The youma are gone.
Yes.
But there's
a much more pressing matter
-we must deal with.
-[YUMI] Huh?
[KATSURAGI]
It is...
the deadly boob youma!
And the only way to defeat
this new foe
is with my Super-Secret
Ninja Art: The Fun Bag Fondle!
Let go of me this instant!
Kagura,
ignore her lecherous demands.
-Lower the barrier.
-[KAGURA] Uh, okay.
Katsu never changes,
does she?
[IKARUGA]
That's the truth.
[KATSURAGI laughing]
[YUMI] I am not above using my
skills as a ninja to stop you!
Katsuragi!
[HOMURA]
Asuka...
what kind of secrets
are you keeping from me?
♪
Come on, everyone,
check out our super special
Christmas discount!
Take one.
Christmas is right around
the corner, you know!
Not buying presents will
land you on the naughty list!
Hey.
What's your deal, Homura?
You haven't said anything
since we've been out here.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
I guess I was just lost
in my thoughts.
Try to cheer up.
You're the one
who wanted a turkey.
And we'll need money for that.
Plus I'll make us dessert, too.
Doesn't a bean sprout cake
sound absolutely scrumptious?
[HOMURA]
Sure.
Hey, look who it is.
[MURASAKI] That doesn't seem
like something
that would be fun
to wear in the cold.
Well, to rogue shinobi
such as ourselves,
a job is a job no matter
what we have to wear.
Except it appears that no one
is actually looking at you.
Huh?
Yeah, she's right.
Ahh!
Man, this blows!
We'll have to do a show
or something to draw attention.
As if! That's not what consumers
wanna see, you sillyhead!
[HOMURA] So what, are you saying
you have a better idea, Ryona?
Uh-huh!
I have a surefire trick
for success!
[HOMURA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Hey! What do you think
you're doing, you pervert?
[RYONA giggles]
-MAN: Yeah, baby!
-[running footsteps]
[men clamoring]
That's quite the increase
in attention.
It actually worked!
Wow, that crowd is crazy.
Suzune-Sensei has gone
to Kikai Dome.
She's requested that you look
after things in her absence.
Understood.
Something wrong?
I was thinking
about the technique
that Asuka used.
Oh, yeah.
I've never heard
of that move before.
More importantly, why would
she seal away the youma
instead of just
killing it outright?
No clue.
To be honest, Asuka's been
pretty secretive lately.
She refuses to tell me anything.
I see. Still, though.
I hope she's hasn't chosen
to side with the youma.
I won't forgive her
if she does.
After all, it is
a shinobi's duty
to eliminate threats
like the youma.
♪
-[YUMI] Asuka.
-Huh?
[ASUKA]
Yumi.
Hello there.
I was hoping we could chat.
♪
[ASUKA]
So, what did you need?
Hey, there's no rush.
Let's drink some tea
and warm up a little bit.
[slurping quietly]
Right.
[chuckles]
Delicious.
Have you ever been
to this cafe before?
Yeah, a couple of times.
It's pretty close to home.
So I used to come here often.
Sometimes, Grandpa
would even join me,
and we would eat together.
That sounds wonderful.
I'm glad, you seem more like
your old self lately.
Really?
Then I guess
that's a good thing.
[YUMI]
I think so.
I've been so worried.
What happened to you?
[ASUKA gasps]
[wind whooshing]
♪
[footsteps approaching]
I've decided
not to kill you, Asuka.
I need you alive
so you can share a message.
The shinobi's dark past.
Which is...
[inaudible dialogue]
[gasps]
There you have it. Those are
the sins of the shinobi.
♪
[ASUKA sobbing softly]
[ASUKA]
I can't tell you.
Why not, Asuka?
I wish you would
at least explain
why you won't talk
about what happened.
Fine, we're not
friends anymore.
[gasps]
♪
A real friend would never be
so secretive.
I guess that means
we're not friends.
That's not fair!
I can tell you're carrying
some sort of burden,
and that's fine.
But Asuka, it shouldn't have
to be something
that you carry
all by yourself.
As a shinobi and your friend,
let me help you.
[ASUKA]
Yumi.
It'll be okay!
No matter what,
we can overcome it together!
♪
All right then.
Guess I'll just be leaving.
You've put me
in a tough spot.
But you win.
I'll tell you, okay.
It's about time!
[FUBUKI] In that case,
perhaps she should hear
everything from me.
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[YUMI]
It's Fubuki!
[FUBUKI]
But first,
I have a question.
Since you are a shinobi,
how do you define justice?
Well, it's a belief
that we have to protect.
[FUBUKI] And what is
that belief, exactly?
To fight against evil
until the very end.
How interesting.
And what is that evil?
Where does that evil lie?
[gasps]
[FUBUKI] Ignorance really is
a sin, you know.
I'm not sure what you mean.
The shinobi hunt down youma
like beasts.
All in the name
of so-called "justice."
Because they're evil.
However,
what if I told you
that youma could feel love
the way that humans do?
[YUMI gasps]
[FUBUKI]
Just what would you think
of the shinobi's actions, then?
[YUMI] To be honest,
I don't really know.
I was told
the youma were all evil,
so they must be defeated.
Therefore, it's hard to believe
that the justice
of the shinobi is wrong.
Still though,
if what you've just told me
is really the truth,
then I, I think
that it's unforgivable.
[FUBUKI]
Very well, I will show you.
[gasps]
I have proof
the youma feel love.
Just like you.
[YUMI/ASUKA gasp]
Wait, her aura.
It's like a youma's!
How can that be?
[FUBUKI]
Haven't you figured it out?
The answer's rather simple.
It's because I am a child born
from a youma and a human.
[gasps]
I feel it.
A door to the other world
is starting to open.
Really?
It's larger
than the previous one.
If it finishes opening,
something terrible
is going to happen!
Where's the door?
Um, let's see.
[grunting]
It's in the hot springs town!
Seriously?
[KAGURA]
Yes.
Hah! The battle
is just beginning!
Huh! Bring it on, then!
So this is it.
The final battle.
Let's have as much fun as we can
until we fight the youma!
For sure! It'll be
a hot springs party!