[ASUKA]
In this episode
of Senran Kagura
Shinovi Master...
No!
-Ah!
[ASUKA] As you can see,
it'll be a ton of fun!
[YOZAKURA and YUMI]
Let's fight fairly!
[yells]
Shinobi...
transformation!
[clanking]
Shinobi transformation!
[yelling and grunting]
[YOZAKURA] Listen.
I think that's enough.
But why stop now?
We just got started.
Maybe I got started,
but you're not even here.
I can't fight you
when you're this distracted.
[sighs]
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I was wondering,
should I buy
a cell phone?
Look, if this is about Asuka,
then let it go already.
I'm sure you'll see her again,
and you can't let it
keep you from your training.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
-[arrow swishes]
-[YUMI gasps]
-Watch out!
-Yumi!
I'm okay.
Where the heck
did that arrow come from?
[YUMI]
There's a letter attached.
It's an invitation
to a spa resort.
[SHIKI]
Spa.
-[MINORI] Resort?
-What?
[MURAKUMO]
Again?
Let's go!
That sounds like a ton of fun!
Can we please?
[MURAKUMO] Going to the spa
is an excellent way
to train our bodies and minds.
All right, I can't wait!
I'll break out
my extra sexy swim suit.
[YUMI]
I hate to burst your bubbles,
but this invite was attached
to an arrow.
Who would walk into such
an obvious trap?
[ALL]
We would!
[excited chatter]
[MURAKUMO] I hope
I don't lose my mask
-like last time.
-[sighs]
-[SHIKI] O-M-G!
-[MINORI] That was crazy!
[giggling]
-[MURAKUMO] Remember that?
-[MINORI] I do.
Yozakura,
what do you think of all this?
Well, it does seem
a bit suspicious,
but who knows?
Maybe it's just
a harmless invitation.
Perhaps. But then again,
that could all be
a clever ruse to trick us.
Are we really going
to make it that easy?
Yumi, quit your worrying!
We got free tickets
to the resort last time, too,
and that turned out okay.
Yeah, that was so much fun!
Even you had
a good time there, remember?
Well, yes,
but this is different.
[gasps]
[MURAKUMO] If we can't come
to an agreement,
then we'll have
to settle this another way.
Huh?
We'll play "Boob Rock, Paper,
Scissors" to decide our fate!
Yay!
Here we go, Yumi.
Rock, paper, scissors,
but with our boobs!
[MURAKUMO]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[MURAKUMO/SHIKI]
Boobs!
Okay. Again!
[YUMI gasps]
Yumi picked scissors,
and Shiki picked rock!
We're going
to the spa resort! Yay!
[SHIKI] And it's all thanks
to the power of my boobs!
[MURAKUMO]
Nicely done!
[YOZAKURA]
Hold on, I call foul!
There's no way
that was a fair match!
Murakumo was the one calling
the shots with Yumi's knockers!
No, that's not true.
Yumi's gazongas were the ones
who chose scissors.
That's right!
Her boobs are so large,
they can actually move
by themselves.
[YUMI]
Fine, you win.
It's no use fighting.
We'll go to the resort.
[dog howling]
Since we're
renegade ninjas now,
we can't afford
to mess this up.
It's been far too long
since we've had real work.
Okay, then
let's review the plan.
Once the car reaches the gate,
Mirai shoots out the front tire.
You've got it.
[HARUKA] Yomi will handle
the mansion's security.
Hikage will take out
the bodyguards.
Homura's in charge
of detaining our target.
Yep. Just leave it to me.
As for my part,
I'll use this to get
Mister Bad Guy
to confess his naughty deeds.
And when he does,
I'll record everything
and upload it to the internet.
Exactly, sounds like
you all know what to do.
[vehicle approaching]
They're coming.
Get your game faces on.
[MIRAI]
Time for an evil politician...
to finally face justice.
Gotcha!
[tires squealing]
[groans]
[YOMI giggles]
Hey, what the hell's going on?
What is all this?
[HOMURA]
Shut your trap, old man.
Ah!
Who are you?
Why are you in my car?
You know perfectly well
why I'm here.
Now be a good boy
and don't do anything stupid.
Aah!
[HARUKA]
Oh...
Now, this may sting a bit.
Please!
Don't kill me.
I'll do anything you want!
-[gunshot]
-[glass shatters]
What?
[YOMI] Ugh, what are you guys
doing here?
Duh. It's obvious.
[HOMURA]
Now I get it.
You're here to act as this
worm's bodyguards, aren't you?
Why are you just
standing around talking?
Hurry up
and get rid of them already!
[MIYABI]
I'll give you one chance.
If you clear out now,
you won't get hurt!
[HOMURA]
Argh! Shut up!
Do you really think
you'd beat me that easily?
[swords clanging]
[BOTH yelling]
[chuckles]
Show yourselves!
Save your breath. They're gone.
I don't sense anyone.
This battle isn't over!
Hey.
You're gonna hold
a little press conference
where you'll tell the world all
the terrible things you've done.
I would never.
That's career suicide!
-[MIYABI] Are you sure?
-Okay!
I changed my mind.
I'll tell them everything!
As instructed, we saved
this man's life tonight.
And you got him to confess
to his sins.
Congratulations,
you and your team
have completed your mission.
Then perhaps we should
call it a draw this time.
-[chuckles]
-[whimpering]
[HOMURA] Besides, fighting over
this piece of human garbage
is a waste
of everyone's skills.
[MIYABI]
Fine by me.
But next time,
you won't be so lucky.
[HOMURA]
That's what I was gonna say.
[MIYABI chuckles]
Let's go.
We're leaving, too.
Wait a second.
Look at the arrow.
[HOMURA]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
Hmm?
Let's go in.
Hey, guess what, Ryobi?
I went shopping and bought
a brand new swimsuit
to wear on our
spa-day-mini-vacay!
By swimsuit, I mean
a few scraps of fabric.
I'll practically be naked.
So, you know...
you can totally check out
my body all you want, okay?
In fact, I want you
to undress me with your eyes!
Oh, my God,
shut your dirty mouth, Ryona!
I came here to relax,
not to see you naked!
You tease!
Enough, both of you.
The real question is,
who sent us these free passes?
Since we don't know
the sender's motive yet,
it would be best
if we just played their game
for the time being.
I still think it's dangerous.
Well, that's a risk
I'm willing to take.
No matter what happens,
I'm going inside this spa.
Oh? You seem
quite dedicated.
Yes, of course!
Nothing's gonna keep me from
seeing you in a swimsuit today!
This really isn't the time
for your shenanigans, Imu.
How shameful.
Uh, I was just kidding!
[RYOBI]
You too, Ryona!
[RYONA]
What? Why are you mad at me?
[giggles]
This looks like
the changing area.
Uh, that you, Miyabi?
Yumi? So I see you also
got an invitation.
[YUMI]
Yes. Via arrow.
[chuckles]
Yet you still came.
You do know this could be
a trap, right?
I'm well aware
of that possibility,
but I'm prepared.
We'll be sure to keep
our guard up at all times.
[MINORI]
Hold on!
Are you saying we're not allowed
to go swimming?
Didn't you hear anything
we just said?
Do you really want
to play around
when it might be a trap?
What else do you expect
from the good ninjas?
Their heads are filled
with naive thoughts.
No worries though,
I have the perfect proposal.
Just hear me out.
You should change
into your swimsuit
before we decide if it's a trap.
-[MIYABI] Imu.
-I know!
I get it, okay?
I just really wanna see you
in a swimsuit!
It's not like I'm asking
for that much!
Yeah! I wanna wear
my swimsuit, too!
Caress my body
with your dirty stares!
There you have it, Yumi!
We're not the only ones
who wanna go swimming.
[chanting]
Pool! Pool!
Pool!
-[chanting continues]
-Well, then.
It looks like
they've outvoted us.
Yes. True.
[HOMURA]
What's this?
Good and evil ninjas arguing
about whether or not
to take a little dip?
[MIYABI]
Homura!
Just pretend to fall
for their trap
and the enemy
will let their guard down.
Besides, we're all shinobi.
I'm sure we can handle it.
If you insist.
I guess we could
play along for now.
If nothing else, it'll be good
for the girls' spirits.
-Yes!
-[MURAKUMO] Victory!
Can you guys please calm down?
[YUMI]
Then let's get changed.
-Yay! Right! Okay.
-[MURAKUMO] Will do!
[excited chatter]
[RYONA] This suit is so tight,
I keep losing it.
[chatter continues]
-Hooray!
-[giggles]
[MURAKUMO]
Yay!
Ah! It's a dream come true!
-[camera shutter clicking]
-Finally!
Miyabi in a bikini!
Victory! I got the shot!
Now I can die happy.
Ah! I have no regrets!
Look, everybody!
Feast your eyes
on my scandalous tiny swimsuit!
So dirty!
I can feel you all undressing me
with your eyes,
and I love it!
There's nobody here
to undress me.
[RYOBI] 'Cause it's
a private party, duh.
We've got the whole place
to ourselves today.
Geez, then there's no reason
for me to even wear this thing!
It's a lot more fun to go
swimming commando anyway!
[RYOBI]
You perv!
What if we don't want
to see you naked?
Hey, is something
bothering you, Homura?
I just thought it was strange
that Asuka's not here.
Actually, now that
I think about it,
I haven't seen any of the
Hanzo Academy girls around.
Maybe they're just
running late.
I'm sure they'll show up
soon enough.
[YUMI] Perhaps, but why
do I feel so uneasy?
[GIRLS laughing]
[RYONA] [screaming]
It was an accident!
[RYOBI]
Come back here!
[SHIKI] What's the matter, Yumi?
You seem down.
Stop being such a stick
in the mud
and come play
in the pool with us.
It'll be so much fun!
Indeed! It's time
to cut loose!
I'm fine. Please
don't worry about me.
They've got a good point.
We've got renegade shinobi,
good ninjas, and bad ninjas
all in one place,
so let's have some fun.
How about a good old-fashioned
water gun fight?
Ha! You always wanna fight.
Don't you ever feel like
doing anything else?
You scared? Feel free
to admit defeat then.
You can just sit out
and watch us destroy
the girls
from Gessen Academy.
You know,
because you're all losers.
Tell me what
the rules are right now!
Hebijo will wipe the floor
with you sorry renegade ninjas!
[HARUKA]
Why not use this then?
It's a special chemical
that renders
any clothing it touches
see-through.
Okay, I put it in every
water gun, so if you get hit,
anything you're wearing
will turn transparent,
and you'll look
completely naked.
[YOZAKURA] What?
That's so indecent!
Personally, I think
it sounds like a lot of fun.
Once you're in the buff,
you're out of the game.
And whichever team has
a girl still standing
will be named the victor.
Any questions about the rules?
On one hand, I really want
our team to win,
but on the other hand
I'd also like to see
Miyabi naked.
I have no idea what to do
in this situation.
I think the obvious
answer is that
you should focus
on winning.
[HARUKA]
Okay, I'll be the judge.
Everybody ready?
Right, it's time to play
"Peach Beach Splash,
Totally Nude Version!"
Ready? Go!
Come on, everyone,
aim your water at me!
I've got ya!
Ah!
[HOMURA]
Look out, Yomi!
This would go better for you
if you just shot
your guns at me!
No!
Ah!
Yah!
[HARUKA]
Oh, no!
Looks like Yozakura, Yomi,
and Murasaki are all out!
-Ah!
-Too slow!
[screaming]
-She got us!
-No fair!
[IMU]
They're too fast!
-[YUMI] You're mine!
-[MURAKUMO] Prepare to die!
No, not me!
[groans]
I can't believe I lost.
[HARUKA]
Another three bite the dust!
Imu, Shiki, and Minori
are all out!
Hey!
No fair. You're not supposed
to shoot the judge!
Bring it on, I'll destroy you!
I have no emotions or shame,
so being naked isn't going
to make me quit fighting you.
Embarrassed or not,
if we can see your goods,
then you're disqualified.
That won't stop me.
You'll have to try harder!
Ah!
Oh, no!
[MIRAI]
Have some more!
[screaming]
[HARUKA]
Murakumo is out of the game.
[RYOBI]
Ryona!
Come on, let's take out
Mirai together!
Okay!
[BOTH yelling]
Uh...
Give it up, you're going down!
No hogging the spotlight.
I want you to get me
all wet, too!
Shoot me harder.
It feels so good!
I love it!
Whoa, what the heck
are you doing?
We're on the same team, dummy!
-[MIRAI] Ah!
-[RYONA] No!
[HARUKA] Ryobi, Ryona,
and Mirai are all out!
Only three players are left!
It's down to Homura, Yumi,
and Miyabi for the win!
Now, it's all up
to the team captains!
I will destroy you!
Hebijo will be the winner!
I won't lose to you!
[ALL gasp]
Huh.
Ah!
[grunts]
[bell ringing]
[HARUKA] That's the end
of the match! Since you all
shot each other
at the same time, it's a tie!
There's no way that was a tie,
because I was the last one
to get hit
by that stupid
chemical stuff!
I demand we check the playback
for a second opinion!
Yeah, there's no
playback, silly.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-We're fine with a draw.
Yes, why don't we
call it a draw?
More importantly,
can you tell us how to turn
our clothes back to normal?
[HARUKA]
It's easy.
Just wash them in clean water
and they'll reappear.
[sighs]
Well, that's a relief.
You guys worry too much.
I think a transparent
swimsuit is awesome!
-Aw!
-[giggling]
[RYOBI]
Don't run away, you stupid cow.
[YOMI]
Isn't there hot water?
I'm surprised Asuka
and her gang never showed up.
Yeah, it's kinda weird.
What's this?
A kekkai barrier?
So you've finally
shown yourselves.
I was tired of waiting.
Never seen you before.
Hello, ladies.
I'm Gekkou.
And my name is Senkou.
[YUMI] Were you the ones
who sent the invitations?
And set up this trap?
[SENKOU]
We are.
Then you owe us
some answers.
Miyabi!
There's no need
for you to worry.
I'm not injured.
[SENKOU]
Calm yourselves.
We invited you here
to see if you're willing
to participate
in a little challenge.
[MIYABI]
What do you mean?
We've come to invite you
to a battle
that will determine
who is the strongest shinobi.
We're calling it
the Shinobi Masters.
Shinobi Masters?
Ha! You really think
we'd be stupid enough
to go along
with something proposed
by two highly
suspicious people like you?
-[chuckles]
-[giggles]
I'm sure
you'll change your mind
once you see our next surprise.
[ALL gasp]
[SENKOU] If you choose
not to play our game,
these girls are dead.
[gasps]
We'll tell you where
it's being held later.
Until we contact you,
I suggest you keep on training.
Gekkou and Senkou, huh?
I can't believe they managed
to capture the girls
from Hanzo Academy.
I'm not really sure
what's happening.
They've got four
of the Hanzo girls.
We have to find
a way to save them.
[HOMURA]
Agreed.
Asuka wasn't with them.
[ASUKA]
Yumi.
We need to talk.
Come alone.
[YOZAKURA]
Hey. Is something wrong?
Oh. I just remembered
there's something I have to do.
Go on without me.
I'll be home soon.
Okay, see you later.
Don't stay out too late
or you'll be tired!
[ASUKA]
Over here, Yumi.
[YUMI]
Asuka!
I'm glad to see you're okay.
I was so worried!
[ASUKA] Did you hear
about the Shinobi Masters?
So you know about that already?
Does that mean the other girls
from Hanzo Academy are--
I won't let you participate.
There's no way you're going
to be a part of it.
[YUMI]
What are you talking about?
I've come to realize
there is no justice for us.
Both the sword and the shield
are utterly useless.
[YUMI]
Asuka.
Tell me where Kagura is.
[MURAKUMO]
Listen,
if there are breasts,
then they're mine to fondle!
[HARUKA]
Okay, Mirai.
It's time for you to give up.
Hot springs?
I'm in.