♪
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Yeah, that's right.
Yumi's more than capable
of winning this thing.
[ASUKA]
They don't get it.
That's not what I meant!
Because Yumi doesn't know
the truth yet.
No.
None of these girls
truly understand.
[YUMI] I know the purpose
of the Shinobi Masters.
However...
I still object
to your views of justice.
Our beliefs are
far too different.
So, what exactly
do you plan on doing?
I'm going to fight you
and win this battle.
And then I'll show you
a new type of justice,
for all shinobi!
"The justice of the moon."
Talk about naive.
♪
[gasps]
[YUMI]
Wait.
A black fan?
Now then...
shall we begin?
[KAGURA] All this in the name
of Kurokage, huh?
[KAFURU]
Did you know him?
The man they're talking about?
Sure did!
Wasn't he like
Asuka's grandpa's partner
or whatever?
I only ever heard rumors
about the guy.
Yeah, tell us
what they were like.
Okay.
If you want my honest opinion,
they were both pretty stupid.
[HANAMI]
Huh?
In a way,
you could also say
they were very pure of heart.
Kind of like clear water.
Never knowing any impurities.
♪
[dog barking in distance]
[footsteps]
[MAN]
Kurokage!
Another mission complete, eh?
Yep.
So then, how about you
and I go grab a drink
after the debriefing?
You can drop
the pretentious act, Hanzo.
Drinks are something
you get with a friend,
and we're not friends.
Geez, loosen up.
So yeah, maybe
we're more like rivals.
But that's a type
of friend, right?
Still counts if you ask me.
Whatever shuts you up.
I'll be waiting for ya!
[plays melancholic tune]
[PATRONS chattering]
♪
[HANZO]
Ah!
Hey, I'm ready for another!
-[BARTENDER] Sure thing.
-Ha-ha!
-Yeah, that's the stuff.
-[liquid pouring]
Thank you!
[WOMAN]
Sorry I'm late.
-[KUROKAGE] Yume?
-[giggles]
[HANZO]
I invited her.
Here, grab a seat.
-[shuffling]
-[YUME] Thanks so much.
[HANZO]
Ah!
Pick your poison.
Let's see.
Whatever you're drinking.
[HANZO]
Whoa, you like this stuff?
Hey, bartender!
[BARTENDER]
Coming!
[HANZO]
Okay, here's to you!
[KUROKAGE]
To me?
Yeah, a toast
to your relationship with Yume.
You're dating, right?
We shinobi have our ways
of getting information.
He means me.
[KUROKAGE]
You told him?
Relax, Kurokage.
Just enjoy your drink.
Try to unwind
and have some fun.
Yeah, why not?
[HANZO]
All right.
-Cheers!
-[glasses clink]
[MAN 1]
We need some help!
[MAN 2]
Put her down over there!
[MAN 3]
There's no room!
[MAN 2]
Well then, make some room!
They fell into a trap
set by evil ninjas.
Hey, wait!
[KUROKAGE] If they get you,
get them back.
Since those dirt bags
love traps so much,
I'll show them
what a real one looks like.
You can't repay a dirty trick
with more dirty tricks.
[KUROKAGE]
Don't try to stop me!
I'm going to wipe out
every evil ninja.
Can you really call
fighting out of rage
and hatred "justice"?
This is a dangerous path.
If justice goes too far,
it becomes evil.
Shut up!
What the hell
would you know about it?
Man, poor Kurokage.
His parents were ninjas, too.
But they were captured
by evil shinobi.
♪
[YUME]
Yes. He's told me about them.
They were both tortured
before being killed.
[HANZO]
I get why he hates evil ninjas
more than
the average person does.
♪
[HANZO]
But that's also why I'm worried
about what he'll do next.
♪
[footsteps]
Who are you?
You're all evil.
Die!
[sword swishes]
[MEN grunting]
[grunts]
Now, hold on.
This isn't right.
I thought you were a good ninja!
This isn't sanctioned.
You'll never get away--
-[blade strikes]
-[groaning]
♪
[MINORI]
Hey, that black weapon.
Doesn't it kinda look
like Yumi's fan?
Indeed, it does.
[SHIKI]
If I remember correctly,
didn't she get hers
from Kurokage himself?
[SENKOU]
This match isn't over yet.
Lady Fubuki is even stronger
than we are.
Yeah.
[wind blowing]
Ha!
[blades clanging]
[yells]
[chuckles]
Ah, it would seem that Fubuki
has finally begun her match.
Whoa. How the heck is a youma
talking like a real person?
[SUZUNE] There have been reports
of youma saying things
that sound like words,
but this is different.
Now what?
It's safe to say
that this youma
is on a completely new level.
It's as intelligent as a human.
[RYOBI]
No way. That's impossible!
[MURASAKI]
Wait, this youma,
it smells like a human.
Tell us who you really are!
I see.
You must be curious.
But seeing as how
you are all shinobi,
you could always try to get
the answer by force.
Unfortunately for you,
that particular action
may result
in your untimely deaths.
That's the most intense
murderous aura I've ever felt.
Yeah, this probably
won't end well for us.
Oh! I'm really scared.
I might even pee myself!
Allow me to make
the first move.
[whooshing]
[SHINOBI screaming, grunting]
-[blades clanging]
-[YUMI grunting]
-Ah!
-[tinkling]
[screams]
[chuckles]
♪
[grunts]
Secret Ninja Art!
Black Ice!
[whooshing]
[ice shatters]
She's so strong.
Poor Yumi.
Is something wrong?
Don't tell me
you're tired already.
[breathing heavily]
Not even close!
Well then.
I'll stop holding back.
♪
[wind whooshing]
[FUBUKI grunts]
♪
[wind whooshing]
[moans]
♪
Wait, what's this form?
Ultimate Secret Ninja Art:
Ice Queen!
♪
This technique carries
Grandfather's hopes and dreams.
Take a good look.
It's over!
[KUROKAGE]
You're banishing me?
[MASTER 1] You were the one
who attacked evil ninjas
when you weren't on a mission.
It's only natural
there would be consequences.
[MASTER 2] As of this moment,
you are relieved of your duties.
[KUROKAGE] Evil ninjas
are our sworn enemies.
And it is my duty
as a good shinobi
to destroy evil
regardless of our orders.
[MASTER 1] Your recklessness
is a result of your youth.
[MASTER 2]
Unless you know of the youma,
it is not your place
to act without permission.
[MASTER 3] Indeed,
your ignorance affects us all.
[KUROKAGE]
What are you talking about?
What's a youma?
[MASTER 2] There are
certain important members
of the shinobi world
who are considered gray,
which means they are
neither good nor evil.
[MASTER 1] There are times
when good and evil
must help one another.
In fact, the world
of the shinobi
is connected
more than you know.
[MASTER 3]
Yes, and white and black
will occasionally mingle
to form gray.
Those were the shinobi
you ignorantly attacked.
So what you're saying
is they get a free pass?
[MASTER 2] Listen, we admire
the talent you wield as a ninja.
But that doesn't mean
you can ignore our orders
or the way of the shinobi.
-[sword whooshes]
-[curtain rustles]
That's enough!
Everything but justice is evil!
They deserve to die!
If you refuse to accept
the punishment
we've decided upon,
then we'll have to discipline
Hanzo and Yume too.
It would be easy
to find something
to convict them of.
You bastards.
You're... all... evil!
Yume and Hanzo
had nothing to do with this.
Leave them alone!
♪
[HANZO] Look, I know
you're in a bad place.
But honestly, in my opinion,
I think the act
of eliminating evil
is evil within itself.
-[fist thumps]
-[glasses clink]
-[PATRONS gasp]
-[KUROKAGE] Hanzo!
What the hell?
Are you calling me evil?
My parents have been murdered!
My friends have been killed!
You don't get to judge me!
So just back off!
[breathing heavily]
[HANZO] Listen,
whether you like it or not,
all humans have evil
inside of them.
You're not the exception,
do you understand that?
Get it through your head!
[grunts]
You know what, whatever!
I'll just have to make
a new world, then!
One that's devoid of evil
and is only good!
[HANZO]
That's impossible, you idiot!
You don't get it!
[grunts]
But I do.
That world.
It's a dream!
-[HANZO grunts]
-[boxes clatter, bottles clink]
[breathing heavily
[groaning]
[footsteps]
[KUROKAGE]
Hanzo.
Just wait.
I'll make it a reality.
No matter what,
I'll create a world
of pure good.
Yume.
[HANZO]
Kurokage!
Don't forget about
the sword and the shield.
I know you'll come
to understand their meaning.
[footsteps]
[HANZO] After he parted ways
with the good ninjas,
Kurokage began to hunt down
those who were evil on his own.
-Of course...
-[KUROKAGE plays harmonica]
...this wasn't something
that could be allowed.
It wasn't long before
both good and evil ninjas
began looking for him.
His life was in grave danger.
♪
[chuckles]
Hey, Yume.
You're looking just
as healthy as ever.
Thanks.
[laughs]
Uh!
Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt.
[laughs]
[HANZO] Oh, I, uh,
brought you some supplies.
Thanks for being
so helpful.
Sure. Really,
I should apologize.
I wish there was
so much more I could do.
Have you heard anything
from Kurokage?
[YUME]
No.
Of course not.
[YUME]
Hanzo.
I believe that he's still alive.
I know in my heart that
he's out there somewhere.
Yes.
I think so, too.
[YUME] I'm going to raise
these children to be shinobi.
He may behave foolishly.
But he is still honorable.
They should know that.
And if I pass on
their father's legacy,
they'll learn
to be proud of him.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'm sure of it.
♪
[body thuds]
[clinks]
♪
[MAN 4]
He was a talented shinobi...
[footsteps]
...but because
he was Kurokage's son,
he always got
the hardest missions.
[MAN 5]
And his wife.
For her to die too.
So sad.
[MAN 6]
What about the daughter?
I heard she has
no surviving relatives.
[KUROKAGE] My son
and my daughter-in-law are dead.
And I never even saw them
in the flesh.
So this is the result
of the path I've chosen.
[YUMI]
One, two, three!
♪
I'm so sorry.
Are you all alone?
I am.
What now?
Where will you go?
I'm not really sure.
I just know that I want
to be a shinobi.
A good one, like my mom
and dad were.
[KUROKAGE]
I see.
You're sad, aren't you?
[YUMI]
Huh?
You're not letting it show,
but I can sense it in you.
I've lived most my life
the same way.
Hiding my sorrow behind anger.
I'm your grandfather, Yumi.
But of course
I don't expect you
to believe that.
[YUMI]
My father and my grandmother
told me my grandfather
had a scar.
A big one, right on his cheek,
just like the one you have.
They always said
that he was also
a very good Shinobi
and super talented too.
They looked really proud
every time
they talked about him.
But...
I think they were also
kind of sad too.
♪
[cries softly]
Huh?
Excuse me,
but why are you crying, sir?
♪
[KUROKAGE]
Actually...
I'm not sure.
♪
[KUROKAGE]
Yumi.
Uh?
Will you come
with your grandfather?
♪
Hmm.
Yes.
[KUROKAGE]
Yumi.
Your hands are so warm
and full of life.
[YUMI]
So are yours,
Grandfather Kurokage.
[KUROKAGE]
Are they, now?
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH gasp]
Lady Fubuki!
[YUMI]
Stand down.
The battle is over.
Accept that I've defeated you.
[FUBUKI laughing]
[YUMI]
Why are you laughing?
Because it's so delightful that
you think you've won this match.
The fight has just begun.
And I don't think
you're prepared.
[FUBUKI]
Shinobi Transformation.
-[whooshing]
-[snap]
[moans]
[bands creaking]
Now then...
come and get me.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Is that the attack
you thought would beat me?
-[blades clanging]
-[giggles]
How sad!
Not good.
She's on the run.
That transformation
must have a time limit, right?
I'm starting to get worried,
Yumi needs to end this
right now!
[YUMI groans]
[sword shatters]
-[YUMI gasps]
-[grunts]
-[whooshing]
-[gasps]
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[ASUKA]
Yumi!
Oh, no.
[MINORI]
Impossible.
[SHIKI]
Yumi... lost the fight?
[moans]
Wait, I remember now.
You were there!
[KUROKAGE]
Yumi.
I'd like you to meet someone
who's going to be living
with us from now on.
Please think of her
as an older sister.
[FUBUKI]
That's right.
I lived with you
when you were young.
We trained together.
With Grandfather Kurokage.
Wait, if that's true,
then it had
to have been sometime
before he took us in
and started training us.
You're right.
I feel like I'd remember
if I'd ever met anyone like her.
If you think about it,
you and I are like sisters.
Only... we've followed
two very different paths.
There's too much
that you don't know.
That's why
you can still talk about
"the justice
of the moon" seriously.
Listen well.
I now declare war
on every last shinobi
in this world.
Oh, wow.
So that's her goal.
What do you mean
when you say "war"?
Lady Fubuki.
You didn't tell us
about this part.
The shinobi are nothing
but hypocrites.
But...
that won't matter
once you don't exist.
[rumbling]
Everyone!
[grunting]
Wait, Homura?
And Miyabi!
Watch out!
There's a youma coming!
♪
[whooshing]
[gasps]
A youma?
But why?
My intention is
to eliminate both good
and evil shinobi alike.
With this, my blade of revenge.
Not to mention,
this ferocious youma!
The reason should be obvious.
The youma are a threat
to everything in this world,
and that includes humanity!
The door to another realm
is now open.
♪
Finally, the fun can begin.
-[ASUKA screams]
-[laughing]