♪
[MINORI]
Ah!
Cool. I've never been
to a place like this before!
Looks super relaxing.
Doesn't it, Yozakura?
Yeah, I guess so.
♪
The door to the other world,
where will it open, Kagura?
Uh. I'm really sorry, Yumi,
but unfortunately, I don't know
where it is at the moment.
But don't worry!
If there's one thing
I'm sure of,
it's that the door for the youma
will definitely open sooner
rather than later.
So, what should we do, then?
[NARAKU] Well, we can't
exactly go back home.
So, it looks like we'll have
to hang out in this area
until something happens.
The other girls
should be here soon.
It's not that I mind
waiting around.
But we can't just stand outside.
She's right. It's practically
freezing out here!
I know a place.
We can all stay there.
[BOTH]
Really? All right!
♪
This is it.
[SHIKI]
Ah!
It looks just like
a traditional inn!
[YOZAKURA]
Yeah. Very classy.
[YUMI gasps]
[KAGURA]
Hmm!
It's Fubuki.
♪
[FUBUKI] Wait, so are all of you
staying at this inn, too?
What a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence,
you liar!
[YUMI]
Shiki, wait!
[GIRLS gasp]
I have a question.
Can you tell us where the door
to the other world will open?
I can't.
I don't know any more
about it than you do.
Ah, so we're in the same boat.
It's one big waiting game.
How unfortunate.
Uh, hello?
Are you forgetting that
she declared herself our enemy?
That's right!
She even said she was going
to destroy the shinobi!
[MINORI] We have to defeat her
before she defeats us!
Look, I understand
what you're saying.
But regardless,
I'd still like
to try talking to her.
The answer's rather simple.
It's because I am a child born
from a youma and a human.
[YUMI gasps]
[chuckles]
Wait, I beg of you!
Please tell me
more of your story!
♪
[FUBUKI]
Why should I?
Considering what I've told you,
you should see my rage
is justified.
I'll never forgive the shinobi.
I don't want to talk.
And honestly,
I have nothing more
I wish to say on the matter.
[YUMI]
But, Fubuki...
[FUBUKI] The impending rift
will be largest tear
that's ever occurred
between worlds.
It will be the last one.
After this, we're done fighting
with the shinobi.
So this is it, then.
The final battle.
Yes, so you'd better be ready.
Hello there, and welcome!
Oh, how interesting.
Do you ladies know each other?
Like I'd know
such a huge creep!
Just make sure our room is as
far away from hers as possible!
-[MINORI] Hmm.
-Okay.
[GIRLS groaning]
So, what did you mean earlier?
When you said
you wanted to talk?
The thing is...
Go on, Yumi.
[YUMI]
It's going to sound crazy.
But I just have a feeling
that we're going to regret it
if we end up fighting
Fubuki like this.
[MINORI]
That's fine.
I get it.
If you insist,
then I'll support you.
Seriously?
On one condition.
[YUMI]
Yes?
[grunts]
We get to have a little fun
until the youma show up!
Totally. We are at
a hot spring after all!
[BOTH chuckle]
[YUMI]
Have it your way.
[grunts]
Get her, Miyabi!
Nice return, Homura!
-[GIRLS shouting]
-[MINORI gasps]
-Huh?
-[MIYABI grunts]
[grunts]
Hey, no fair!
-Homura.
-I was distracted, Miyabi!
And naturally, I took advantage
of that, so deal with it.
[IMU scoffs]
[MINORI] I didn't know
you guys were here.
Uh-huh.
The girls from Hanzo Academy
are here, too.
[MIYABI]
Enough stalling, Homura.
It's time to strip.
Talk about your weird requests.
Well, the way we play is
that if you get scored upon,
then you have to strip off
all your clothes.
That's the one and only rule
of "Strip Ping Pong!"
Wow, like, seriously?
But Homura.
Aren't you only wearing panties
underneath there?
[growls]
[HOMURA]
Rules are rules!
[ALL gasp]
[MIYABI]
What? A cloth bra?
The battle is just beginning!
[chuckles]
Bring it on, then!
[MIYABI] Crimson Homura
in a ping pong game?
-[HOMURA yelling]
-[MIYABI] You dirty cheat!
[TV ANNOUNCER]
But wait, there's more!
-Oh. That's pretty cool!
-Katsuragi.
You're way too close to the TV.
[KATSURAGI chuckles]
Okay, Mom.
[heart beats]
[groans]
[ASUKA] This must be the price
of using Fuma Korin.
Asuka?
Is everything okay?
Yep! I'm all good!
I guess it just felt weird
that Katsu wasn't fondling
my boobs like normal,
so I decided
to do it myself instead!
I have to go do something
that's not here, bye!
[MINORI]
Guess what?
I heard this inn has a lot
of really awesome baths!
Yeah? Good.
I need to do
some serious relaxing.
I think I'm going to try
the open air bath.
Yeah, me too.
I want to use the pot bath,
but I'm not sure
how many people it can hold.
Well, how about
we let you have it then?
-Huh?
-You could probably use
some time to relax
by yourself for a bit, huh?
Thank you, Yozakura.
We're going out, but feel free
to join up with us later!
[YUMI]
Fubuki.
It looks like someone else
is already using the bath.
[water splashing]
[giggles]
Oh, hey, you guys!
Fancy seeing you here.
Kagura!
And Naraku's with you!
[YUMI gasps]
[gasps softly]
[inhales sharply]
Isn't that...
Do you recognize it?
Yes.
It's something that
Grandfather Kurokage gave to me.
Oh.
♪
I get it.
Now everything makes more sense.
-[YUMI] Huh?
-Oops, just talking to myself!
-See ya!
-Goodbye.
Oh! Hey!
Wait for me!
♪
It looks like
there's only one bath.
Yes, so it would seem.
Well, I suppose there's no harm
in us getting in together.
Besides, if we continue standing
out here with no clothes on,
we'll risk catching a cold.
Yes.
So...
this is a nice bath.
Indeed.
[YUMI]
It's really warm, huh?
Indeed.
And look, the sky is so
pretty today, don't you think?
Indeed.
[gasps]
[YUMI gasps]
[chuckles softly]
We've done this before.
Back when we were just children.
That's right.
You forget what happens
when you're little,
but now I can
remember it clearly.
[FUBUKI] My father was a shinobi
and my mother a youma.
My family...
wasn't exactly normal.
You may have learned this
from Rasetsu.
But there are youma out there
who have feelings,
the same way that
a regular human would.
Yes.
[FUBUKI] And with
those feelings comes love.
Is that so strange?
Isn't love a common emotion?
♪
[YUMI]
Yes.
[FUBUKI]
I was born into this world
because my parents
loved each other,
and yet, our story wasn't meant
to end happily ever after.
My mother was strong and said
to be the ultimate youma.
Eventually, the shinobi
gave up any hope
of trying to defeat her.
Until one day...
they used Fuma Korin on her.
If they use that technique
to seal you away,
then you will
never again be able
to return
to the human world.
[YUMI gasps]
Wait, so you're saying
your mother got sealed away
and now you can't
see her anymore?
-[water splashes]
-[YUMI gasps]
[FUBUKI] Yes, they took
my mother from me,
and that's when
Grandfather Kurokage
decided to take me in.
It wasn't for very long
but, while we lived together,
you and I
were close like sisters.
Not that it matters.
As long as you continue to walk
the path of the shinobi,
there's no hope for the two
of us becoming friends.
But, Fubuki, I...
[FUBUKI] The shinobi slaughter
the youma indiscriminately.
And they are the ones who tore
my mother away from me.
♪
[water splashes]
[YUMI]
Does it have to be this way?
Do we really have no choice
but to fight?
[FUBUKI]
Prepare yourself for it.
It's either the youma...
or the shinobi who will die.
That is the only ending
this story will have.
We're evil,
so we must be defeated.
Those are the words
that you told me.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[ASUKA] Yumi?
I just came to tell you
that dinner's ready.
Is there something
bothering you?
I saw Fubuki,
and she told me everything.
I see.
I think I understand now.
That's why you tried to seal
the youma, isn't it?
[ASUKA]
Mmm.
After I met Fubuki, I decided
it was wrong to kill them.
But that's also against
our orders.
[chuckles]
In fact,
I'll probably get expelled
for this.
Yes, I see.
And that's why you've been
fighting by yourself.
So nobody else has
to get in trouble.
Would it be okay
if I told Homura and Miyabi?
[ASUKA]
Sure.
I doubt there's any point
in hiding it now.
[YUMI]
Thank you, Asuka.
♪
Do you think they'll come?
Yes. I am quite sure of it.
Now that they're aware
of my true identity,
they will have no choice
but to fight.
♪
You see?
Listen, Naraku, I'm guessing
that this is gonna be
a pretty long battle.
But no matter what,
you can't get involved, okay.
Yes, I know.
But somehow I doubt
you're going to lose, Kagura.
I'm not terribly concerned.
I appreciate
your vote of confidence.
But I'd say the odds are about
fifty-fifty either way.
♪
I'm impressed you came out here.
Knowing that I'm going
to kill you.
Well, I finally
figured something out.
About why things were off
when we fought before.
It's because you're actually
half youma, aren't you, Fubuki?
Indeed, that's correct.
♪
And this is the proof, Kagura.
Looks like
I'll have to kill you, then.
[wind whooshing]
[HOMURA]
I get it.
It all makes
a little more sense now.
So why are you telling us this?
It doesn't matter
what the reason is.
The youma are still responsible
for attacking humans,
so there's no point
in justifying it
with ridiculous excuses.
Personally, I don't care
who struck first.
I sympathize with Fubuki,
I really do.
But her story isn't
that different from ours.
Like, take the girls
from Gessen,
you've all lost your parents,
as well, right?
Yes, but even so.
I agree with Asuka that we
should seal the youma away,
not kill them.
Well, then count me out.
A shinobi's job is
to destroy the youma,
and I refuse
to stray from that.
Now, we're done here.
I'm through talking.
[HOMURA]
Poor girl.
Her mother was killed
by a youma, after all.
[sighs]
I'm not surprised she's mad.
Yeah.
Hey, doesn't not killing
the youma
go against our orders
or whatever?
I mean, we're rogue shinobi,
so we don't care,
but what about
the other students?
A-Asuka?
Even if I'm punished,
I'll still do it.
I've made my choice.
[gasps]
We heard everything
you said in there.
You really are ridiculous.
You should have told us, silly!
Besides, we're all
in this together!
Like we always are!
And hey, if we get expelled
from Hanzo,
then we'll figure
something else out.
We can be rogue shinobi.
Just like Homura's weird group.
I already have an idea
for a name!
"Asuka's Royal Guards"
sounds good, right?
[GIRLS laughing]
[IKARUGA]
I actually like it.
-Thanks a lot, you guys!
-[HIBARI] Yay!
[ALL laughing]
[ASUKA]
I'll have to do my best.
Because this will be
the last time
I'll be able to fight
alongside them.
[HOMURA]
Fubuki's mother was said to be
the strongest youma
to ever exist.
So which shinobi could have
sealed her away?
Who would be strong enough?
[GIRLS snoring softly]
[YUMI]
Kagura?
Sorry to bother you so late.
But I was wondering
if I could have a word with you.
[gasps]
Are you there?
[grunting]
Ah.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[KAGURA gasps]
[yells]
[BOTH chuckle]
♪
[NARAKU]
Impossible!
I didn't think they'd be
on the same level.
[RASETSU]
Please, Fubuki.
You have to win.
For the sake
of our great desire.
♪
[FUBUKI]
What's wrong?
You seem out of breath.
[chuckles]
Save your worrying for yourself.
I promise I'm just fine.
[wind whooshing]
[KAGURA]
Now,
what should my next move be?
♪
-[BOTH grunting]
-[weapons clanging]
[grunting]
[NARAKU]
Kagura!
Stay there!
You can't interfere, remember?
This fight's gone on
long enough.
Yes. Why don't we end it?
♪
-[wind whooshing]
-[ice clinking]
♪
Susanowo!
[yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[YUMI]
Kagura!
[gasps]
Yumi?
What are you doing here?
[groans]
[KAGURA]
I see.
I'm not the one who's meant
to finish all this.
So, this is my true destiny?
[groans, screams]
-[NARAKU] Kagura!
-[YUMI] Are you okay?
[NARAKU]
Kagura! Speak to me!
[YUMI]
Open your eyes!
-[footsteps approaching]
-[BOTH gasp]
I have decided
that I won't kill you.
I want you to see us destroy
the shinobi.
At long last,
justice will prevail.
You're awake!
What happened?
You could have easily won
that fight.
[chuckles]
Yeah, looks like I messed it up.
Sorry, Naraku.
So now...
it's up to you, Yumi.
You'll have to find a way
to stop Fubuki.
But what if I can't do it?
You'll be fine.
And I think
you're the only person
who can do it.
Just focus.
Why was she still
carrying around
that accessory
that's the sword and the shield?
You may find an answer there.
♪
[whirring, rumbling]
[chuckles]
I'm just getting started!
One thing the youma and I
definitely have in common
is how much we adore
super cute girls!
[KATSURAGI]
What's this?
[FUBUKI]
With every passing moment,
my hate only finds a way
to run even deeper!