[Council B]
The Deucalion!
[Crewman A] The Deucalion's
systems are powering up!
[Captain A] What?!
Emergency shutdown!
[Crewman A]
No response!
[Captain A] Stop
it! At all costs!
[Crewman A] The ship's
N-Layers are activating!
[Captain A] Damn!
[Crewman A] It- It's
starting to move!
[Captain A] All hands!
Get clear at once!
So, d'Autriche...
it's you...
All of our hopes...
All of our plans...
He's going to
ruin them all!
Issue a
priority alert!
Order all ships in the vicinity
to converge on the target!
Secure the
Deucalion!
The
Deucalion!?
Sister...
How could this
happen...?
Tactical, I want
a 4-D Auto-Lock.
All turrets, prepare
to fire on my mark.
Targeting
failure!
It's a gravitational
anomaly, sir!
It's interfering
with our systems!
Sir... The Deucalion...
It's preparing to warp!
Stop it!
Hurry! Run a
warp trace!
Right. Initiating scan...
There's too much interference!
There it is. Hardly a
moment's journey in this ship.
Aineias...
The Deucalion
is here.
What are you doing? You're
in no shape for this!
I'm still your partner!
I can't let you go alone!
Wait!
Stubborn girl...
[Crewman C] The target craft
is beginning to transform!
[Captain B]
Impossible!
Something that massive
shouldn't be able to-
Sir! I'm reading a large output
of terraforming nanomists!
They're inside
the Roche Limit!
Truly... This
is Atlas.
The titan that holds the
world in his hands...
I'm scared, Mom...
It's all right...
It'll be all right...
At present, wide fluctuations
in barometric pressure
are being experienced
all over the planet.
Tsunami warnings have been
issued for all coastal regions,
and violent shifts
in weather patterns
are expected
to continue.
All citizens are
urged to seek shelter,
until normal communications
and transportation routes
can be
restored...
Once again, this is a
special news bulletin...
First wave,
intercept!
Prepare to clear the
8th Fleet for launch!
Conditions won't
allow it, sir!
I'm picking up a new
reading on sensors!
A G.O.T.T.
High-Speed Cruiser!
Nearing escape velocity...
Acceleration L-3...
Initiate an emergency
command override...
Route all planetary management
control to my station.
For the entire system?
Are things really that bad?
What happened to
repeating my orders?
Sorry, Chief.
Initiating
command override,
and rerouting all planetary
management systems.
So that's it.
The Deucalion.
Yes... That's our target. The
ship... And the man inside.
Éclair... So, you've
come, after all.
The Chief of the
G.O.T.T. has just issued
a formal declaration
of emergency
and is raising the
planetary shield
over all regions
of Aineias.
Current weather
conditions shou-
conditions should
begin to stabilize,
however...
...all citizens are
requested to remain where-
...indicates that all regions
of Aineias have been affected
by this wave of
environmental disaster...
This global crisis follows
the sudden appearance
of the spaceship
Deucalion,
and is the result of the
massive gravity disturbance
created by its close
proximity to the planet.
The Atlas-class intergalactic
spaceship Deucalion
is the first
of its kind,
and the largest
vessel ever created
in the history of
the human race...
The completion of this
technological marvel
was expected
to usher in
a new era of exploration and
planetary development...
However, one day before
its scheduled launch...
the ship was stolen
by an as yet unknown-
Wait, we're receiving
some new data...
It's breaking
through?!
Chevalier... I
don't understand.
Why are you
doing this?
The defense system. It's locked
onto us, but it isn't firing!
Chevalier!
So sorry to barge
in like this.
But there didn't seem to
be much point in knocking.
You two
again...
And after all
the care I took
to stay one step ahead of
you... Most impressive.
[Alv] Thanks for warming
up the engines for me.
You really
shouldn't have...
No, Alv.
It's an uncharacteristically
efficient move by the Council,
sending you here
so quickly...
They didn't send me. I told
you, I work for myself.
Another betrayal.
And all this time...
I thought "Absorb" was your
only ability. Silly me.
Stop Alv! We've got
what we came here for.
I see no reason for any
more senseless killing...
You think you can
order me around?!
No, I-
I'm sorry...
Why, Alv...?
It's not what we came for,
it's what I came for.
And I see no reason to
share it with anyone.
Not even your
own mother?!
No...
don't...
You mean
you knew?
I- I
knew...?!
You've known
all along!
And you still shot
her in cold blood!
Oh, shut up.
A shield...?
Nothing like a little appetizer
before the main course...
I'm sure you'd swallow us all
if you could. Parasite...
I won't give
you that chance.
Wh- what's this?
A gravity well?
Wh- Where am I?
What the-?
What's happening?!
No!
The Reception
System chamber...
It essentially
duplicates
your "Absorb"
abilities mechanically.
Alv...
Oh, no...
It will break down
any form of matter
into its component
particles
and convert it
to pure energy.
It's one of this ship's main
power processing facilities.
Stop it!
Make it stop!
Alv...
The La Muse, Mark
Zero... Calliope...
The nanomist layer is most
likely acting as a shield.
We'll need to find
an entry point
where we can
punch through.
This is
too easy.
I'm going in
with you.
The Deucalion is just
one large machine, right?
Even without
my ability...
I still have a few tools
that might come in handy.
She'll be
here soon.
Yes...
This is it.
After more than half
a century of waiting...
The moment has
finally arrived...
Chevalier...
Well, now... That's quite an
entrance, albeit unnecessary.
I should think it
obvious by now
that I've been
expecting you.
I would have gladly
opened the door.
Secretary
d'Autriche.
Under our authority as
G.O.T.T. ES Members,
we hereby charge you as
being in direct violation
of interstellar law.
More specifically, you have
committed multiple violations
of the Global
Union Charter
and Interplanetary
Navigation statutes.
All told, you are
being charged
with three hundred
and seventeen
separate criminal
offenses.
Really?
Is that all?
I'd say the number of
crimes I've committed
is actually closer to
80,000 at this point..
That's a rough
estimate, of course...
What?
I'm afraid I don't have the
time to name all of them...
Which is why, a few minutes
before your arrival,
I submitted the full
details to the public...
We have only just
begun to sift through
the vast
quantity of data
that we've
received, however-
...clearly indicates a
long history of corruption
within the highest
levels of-
...illegal dealings with
prominent corporate executives
and government
officials,
which would seem to
imply a vast conspiracy-
...news of these crimes
has spread rapidly
over the
galactic network,
and already the first cries of
public outrage are beginning...
Why are you doing this? What
do you hope to accomplish?
I wanted... I wanted
to save you, Éclair.
You remembered me?
After all this time?
Fifty years. Yes. I
remembered. Or rather...
I couldn't
forget...
Oh, you poor thing,
are you hungry?
No, no.
Nothing there...
We'll have to find milk
for you someplace else.
What do they
mean, "G.O.T.T."?
What do they mean, "For the
service of the Global Union".
I can't...
I can't go...
Mom? Are
you okay?
How many times
have I told you?
You don't have to
call me "Mom".
It's just
"Éclair", okay?
But why not? Is
it because...
Is it because I'm
not your real son?
You silly boy...
Éclair...
We might not be
related by blood...
but you are still every bit
my beautiful little son.
You have no idea what
a wonderful difference
you've made
in my life.
You've given me more happiness
than you could ever know...
But...
But what?
Someday you'll have
your own life,
and you'll forget
all about me...
Éclair! Éclair!
Everything's going to be
fine. You'll be happy.
They tell me you'll
have nothing
but the best
from now on...
After all, you're
an Earthling.
It's only right you should
be with the Nouvlesse.
Éclair... I won't forget
you. I'll never forget...
And I promise,
when I grow up,
I'm going to be strong
enough to protect you...
And then,
someday... Someday...
From now on, you'll be known
as Chevalier d'Autriche.
You are expected to
conduct yourself
as a proud member of
the d'Autriche family.
Yes...
Dirty
Nouvlesse...
Éclair...
ES Member?
So... She works for
the G.O.T.T. now?
What you got there?
Anything interesting?
No... not
really.
Let me guess... More
studying. Am I right?
Sort of. I just
chose a career.
I'm going to be
a politician.
[News Anchor] Planet
Azlantia has suffered
a second
major disaster,
but in an unprecedented
show of cooperation,
hundreds of planet-states
have agreed to contribute
to the
reconstruction effort-
one more sign of the radical
shift in economic policy
taking place
throughout the galaxy.
In response to the
changing times,
the Global Union
has recently named
a new Minister
of Finance.
The youngest man to
ever fill the post,
Chevalier d'Autriche
will also serve
as the Secretary
of the G.O.T.T.
Chevalier... A word of
caution from an old man...
These commoners have become far
more clever than you realize.
Don't let things
get out of hand.
Sir...
The Deucalion...?
What is this?
Éclair... you may have
lost your memories...
But I still
have mine.
So then, why
steal this ship?
Because it's proof. Undeniable
proof of the Nouvlesse's plan
to rid themselves of the
"commoners" once and for all...
I'm not sure I follow.
You're talking about what?
Less than
100,000 Nouvlesse?
What can they do against
a galaxy of billions?
I have already made the public
aware of the illegal means
through which
the assets
to build the Deucalion
were acquired.
However, that is not the extent
of the Nouvlesse's betrayal.
Upon its completion,
they intended to flee-
Earth and all- to
another galaxy...
"Earth and all"?!
Is that possible?!
It is, with
this ship...
So, if they all
left, then...
Yes. Chaos. The entire galactic
economy would collapse.
After which, those planets that
require continuous terraforming
to remain habitable would
suddenly find themselves
without
resources.
They would not be able to
sustain themselves for long.
That's
terrible...
To further
prevent recovery,
this ship has also been
programmed to launch a virus
that would destroy all of
the Warp Gate networks...
All the evidence you
need is right here.
The Deucalion
itself-fully complete,
and on the eve
of its launch...
So unless it was
stopped before hand...
by the time anyone realized
what was happening,
it'd be
too late.
And now that
you understand,
there is only one thing
left for me to do...
[Council B] Shut down that
transmission, at once!
The signal's already being
carried by every media outlet
in the galactic
network.
It's too
late...
We're going to have a full
scale revolution on our hands.
It might be prudent
to re-establish our ties
with the
Rosenfeld Group.
We're at the mercy of
the filthy "commoners".
So what's the
one thing?
The Nouvlesse will all
but disappear after this.
But not until they've had
their revenge. My life is over.
That is the price
of my actions.
Éclair... If you feel you
can bring yourself to do it-
Don't
say it!
If I must die,
I prefer it to be at the
moment of my own choosing.
I ask you to do me the
favor of taking my life.
But before
you do...
Allow me... to call you
"Mother", one last time.
It's all I've really
ever wanted...
For all these years, I've
labored under the belief
that if I could
somehow free you
from the rule of
the Nouvlesse...
Maybe then, and only then,
would my one wish be granted.
Chevalier...
I'm glad it was not
in vain... Mother...
[Chevalier]
What did you-??
I can't
shoot you...
Not when everything you've
done was all because of me!
I'm sorry, Chevalier...
I'm so sorry!
Mother!
Chevalier!
Chevalier...? Chevalier!
Why'd you do it?
As much as I've
enjoyed watching
this ridiculous
little drama,
I think it's time
I made my entrance!
That
voice...
Alv... Is
that you...?
You mean... she's
taken the ship?!
Time has come
full circle.
But when the
beginning is the end,
and the end the
beginning...
nothing can
exist in between.
Next time on Kiddy Grade:
"Annihilation / Zero".