Of course, you're not really
the "Chief", now are you?
The official title is
"Acting Chief", right?
What are you
doing?! Kill them!
You've done enough
for one day. Rest now.
Who sent you? The Global
Union? The Nouvlesse?
Whose ES Members
are you?
Sounds like you've been busy
making enemies, huh "Éclair"?
Answer me!
Who are you?!
Well... You're right about one
thing. We're not your friends.
Sorry we can't stay
and chat more...
But we'll be
seeing you around.
After them!
That was
incredible!
Whoever
they were,
I'm glad someone stood
up to this nonsense...
This is an emergency alert of
the 3rd and 4th battalions...
Secure the escaping
antisocial elements at once!
All units, outfit for
anti-terrorist combat!
Extend security to a
300-kilometer radius!
Verify ID on all civilians
before evacuating!
What are you two doing?
Get back to the office.
You're to stay there and
wait for further orders.
Are we clear?
Yes, Acting Chief.
Understood.
So, what are
you thinking?
The same thing that you're
thinking, by the sound of it.
Those girls are...
are probably...
Two of the units
are still unstable.
We'll need to watch
them closely.
Are you sure?
Well, if you ladies are in need
of an auditor... Here I am.
Armblast.
How did you get
past the guards?
That was quite a
commotion earlier.
I guess I must have slipped
between the cracks.
I'm surprised
you didn't run.
Now why would I
do that, Éclair?
You know how fond
I am of you two.
All right... I'll give you a
chance to prove you're useful.
I won't
disappoint.
Care for
a lift?
A lift? No. But thank you
for your concern, Auditor.
I... I think we've recovered
enough to manage on our own.
I'm sure. It's me
I'm worried about.
You think
this is wise?
We might as well keep all
the risky elements together.
Target acquired, fleeing
westbound on Route 5-3-8.
Red Squadron,
in pursuit.
1st Division, approach
from the west-southwest.
2nd Division, approach
from west- northwest.
Converge on
our position.
All civilian traffic
has been diverted.
Your target is the only
moving vehicle in the area.
Get a lock.
Oh, look! They called out the
whole cavalry, just for us!
So it seems... I'm sure
"Acting Chief Éclair"
was all too eager
for the chance
to show off
her new army.
Funny... You'd think a former
ES Member would be able to
take care of
things herself!
Our goal here
is containment.
Try to lead them
with your fire.
They just had to start
blowing things up.
We need to get
out of the city.
One thing
at a time!
Heads up!
See ya'!
I think it's time you started
taking this seriously.
Here we go...
That trick may have
worked on your partners
back at
the assembly,
but you'll have to come up
with something better for us!
Here... Let me show
you the right way
to use a
nanomist javelin!
Get off the street!
Find some cover!
Tell you what- you guys
keep practicing, okay?
Something wrong?
No. It's
nothing.
Attention,
all units...
Steady...
The targets have escaped
the security perimeter,
and are headed into the El Lac
forest, southwest of Kolkia.
All ES Members are to proceed
to that location immediately.
That is all.
Proceed... to location...
immediately...
Right. Just
point the way.
Another order from 'Her
Majesty', I take it.
5th Division is
searching Block E-6.
I want the 6th
Division covering F-7.
Now move out...
I'm told the Chief
is on her way.
She's leading a unit
into the field herself.
If they get too deep
into that forest,
we're going to have real
problems pulling them out.
Well, we'll just
have to stop them.
I'm not above getting my hands
dirty every now and then.
You sure
about this?
She did more or less order
us to sit this one out.
The only thing
I'm sure of...
is things are about
to turn ugly.
I'd say that's pretty much
a given at this point.
Besides, the
last I checked,
we were already the Chief's
new "whipping boys".
I can't see how it
makes much difference
if her opinion of us
gets any lower.
But if you're so
worried about it,
maybe you should've
stayed behind.
Well I would have, except
you're forgetting one thing-
Since when can you
look after yourself?
At the very least, we get to
enjoy some interesting scenery.
The rock formations
in this area
have a strong magnetic
quality to them.
You don't say...
So then... why don't
we take a break?
How are you? Are you
feeling all right?
I don't
understand...
I never... I never
swore an oath...
Not to follow the
Chief's orders...
Not to uphold the laws of the
G.O.T.T... So then... why?
Perhaps I could
tell you a story.
It's a story
about two girls
I once had the
pleasure of knowing.
They were lovely...
much like yourselves.
Except one of them did
have a tendency to slap me.
Auditor, I hope
this won't turn out
to be some strange
fantasy of yours.
Did I mention that both
of them were ES Members?
They were very
young in appearance.
So much so,
that one might easily
mistake them for children.
However, their appearance
belied the truth-
that the two of them had
lived a long, long, time.
Hundreds
of years.
They were giving, gracious,
and always cheerful.
It was only by the
slightest of chances
that I came to know
them for a time.
Unfortunately, it was
brief. In the end...
they disobeyed
a direct order,
and were
both expelled.
They were
expelled?
From the G.O.T.T.?
That's terrible!
It might seem that way
to some. However...
For them, it was a
small price to pay
for following
their hearts.
So what happened
to them?
They're dead now...
or so I have heard.
Don't you think this
might be too extreme?
If the sun goes down, it's
only going to make our search
that much more
difficult,
so I intend to settle
this before it does.
But still...
All who oppose us
must be eliminated.
I want these two to be an
example for the entire galaxy!
Output calibrations
complete.
Target set. Search
program initiated.
Find them.
Turn them
loose!
So, she's brought
the Genetic Beasts.
What
are those?!
It would appear
that Her Majesty
is a bit short
on patience.
What?
Why'd
they stop?
Control! What's
going on in there?!
Status on
Number 3.
Malfunction. Specific
cause unknown.
It's not
responding at all!
This is Point G4! Taking
heavy fire. We need back-up!
The most destructive of
all Genetic Beasts...
The D-32,
E-Type.
How
unfortunate.
This particular model is
controlled via radio waves.
The magnetic ores
in these rocks
must be causing
some interference.
A costly oversight,
to say the least.
Wait! Where
are you going?
Where do
you think?
I'm going down there
to stop those things.
Are you sure you should
be acting without orders?
I'm sure Her Majesty won't be
so forgiving a second time.
I know, but...
...but... I can't
just let them die!
Wait!
Were you going to
leave without me?
Fall back!
Now hurry.
Get moving!
Thanks!
Come on, then! It's
just you and me now!
Stop!
I did not give you the
order to get involved!
What you're doing now could be
considered an act of treason!
I- I'm sorry, Chief. It's
just- people were dying!
This is valuable
military property.
We will
restore control.
Go back to your
positions, at once.
But, Chief, we
thought that-
You will
follow orders!
It is not your
place here to think.
Your first and only duty is
to follow orders, understand?
...m-my duty...
follow orders...
That's right. Now be
a good little girl,
and return to
your position!
No.
I'm sorry...
I can't do that!
Don't tell
me she's-
Easy now...
All who oppose us
must be eliminated.
must be eliminated!
All who oppose us
must be eliminated.
Do it!
Ta-daa!
Here we go!
What are you doing? Don't
just stand there! Attack!
Your turn!
Yes, I can
see that.
W-where...?
I- I don't...
Was I...?
Is that...?
None other.
I hope you
don't mind.
I took the liberty of giving
them a neural net de-inhibitor.
Or in
other words:
you don't get to play with
your dolls anymore. Sorry!
You two... So you've
managed to come back.
I'm sorry but...
who are you?
I'm Éclair. Hi.
Lumiere.
We're your
originals.
It can be stolen...
It can be broken...
but as long as you never
stop following your heart,
the wounds
will heal...
and the time will
come to take it back.
Next time, on Kiddy Grade:
"Take / Revenge".