This just gets worse
every time I see it.
But don't forget
what Nobel said...
Each scholarly
discovery is neutral,
but can be used both
for good and bad.
Well, don't you two
seem enthralled.
So, watching records of
the first Limited War
is more interesting
than your jobs?
No Ma'am! We're just
doing some research...
on the Geo
Sort bomb!
It's an amazing display
of weaponry and-
The Geo Sort is no
longer used as a weapon!
It's classified as a
'planetary restructuring
tool'. That clear?!
Ma'am! Sorry! We were just
getting back to cataloging
all of the active Geo
Sorts when you came in!
Oh, brother. Can't leave
those two alone for a minute.
[Éclair] So, it's a
planet being terraformed,
or what do they call it now?
Planetary restructuring?
[Eclipse] Actually,
that's a planet
being destroyed by a
Geo Sort bomb.
[Éclair] Oh yeah! I've seen
the old history films.
This happened about
two hundred years ago,
in the First
Origin War, right?
It's current. That's
taking place right now.
That's correct. And the planet
Atoth was heavily populated
at the time the
detonation occurred.
There's more.
Last spring deposits of a
valuable quantum material,
used to run E-3 power systems,
were discovered there.
But that's-
So, someone destroyed an entire
planet just for a profit.
Actually, there were
several companies
that were trying to buy
out the inhabitants.
I guess they didn't
want to leave.
You should
also know that
the Management Association
of the Global Union
is already
investigating this case.
It appears that the
rumors are true
about ES members
of G.O.T.T.
not covering their
faces! How foolish!
Most disconcerting
is the fact that
G.O.T.T. is
responsible for
possession and distribution
of all Geo Sort bombs.
Then that means the bomb
used on the planet was ours.
So, an inside
job. Not bad.
N-No. Not that I
had anything to do
with this one,
you understand.
Éclair, Lumiere - Your mission
is to identify the bomb's
distribution route
and shut it down.
Yes Chief!
Understood!
So, Miss, now that
you've had the tour,
what is your opinion
of our system?
Huh?
Well, I, uh...
I have to say my pupil
is exceedingly impressed
with our
Global Union,
the energy systems you develop
here in order to sustain it,
and, of course, your very
beautiful explanation.
Oh!
The problem is, with you around
there's no need for a tutor.
Nonsense!
Since we're on the subject of
developing energy systems,
it might
interest you
to know that here at the Energy
Development Center, or EDC,
we direct and supervise
the energy acquisitions
for systems
E-1 through E-4.
Our laboratories
are also developing
the next generation
of energy systems.
There's the Planck
hyperspace scalar system,
which seems
to be
the strongest candidate
for the upcoming E-5.
Of course, my
personal favorite is
the E-8 dimensional
folding system
for small-scale
stabilization.
But that's far
down the line.
--Well?
It's really
quite easy.
At the moment I am removing the
three-thousand-twenty-eighth
and final
firewall.
It's obviously apparent
they don't follow
the G.O.T.T.'s example
for logical firewalls.
What's
that?
An interceptor? No.
Someone got here before me.
Well, now what do we have
here? An ace hacker?
Wait. Is that
you, Lumiere?
Hello,
Tweedledee!
[Lumiere] I don't
understand.
Chief Eclipse assigned both
of us to the same case?
It certainly
seems so.
Not that we
needed the help.
That's quite enough
out of you, Tweedledum.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Wait. So does this mean
the chief doesn't trust us?
Do you mean for
your abilities?
Or on a
personal level?
Gimme that! And just who
are you to talk about trust?
Well, seeing as we're all
members of the G.O.T.T,
we should should probably work
together, don't you think?
That would be the
logical thing to do.
I assume I'll be contributing
in my usual capacity as decoy.
Tweedledum!
I'm sorry.
[Tweedledee] Let's get
started, shall we?
If you'll excuse me
for just a moment.
What's
all this?
Ah... It's Lumiere's
little good-luck ritual.
She says it's
grape juice.
Thank you
for waiting.
I'm ready to begin
now, if you'd like.
So, you're still using
classic methods. However...
There is an easier
way to search
for information
on the Galactic Net.
It's a virtual sphere! You
have the most elegant taste!
Well,
thank you.
Now where's the
data we gathered
from the Energy
Development Center?
Here! I
compressed it!
Great. Let me
have it, please.
That's what I
call compressed!
Okay. Let's
search everything,
starting in order of
highest priority.
Now typically,
secret data files
are encoded with random
number sequences.
They're very difficult to find.
It becomes a game of patience.
Not necessarily.
I have a little trick
to speed things up.
Oh, how sweet!
Search parameters center
around all Geo Sort Bomb data,
as well as planetary
restructuring information.
Cross-reference
E-3 systems.
Refer to earlier data for
priority rank. Everyone ready?
Ready!
They replicate themselves to
perform simultaneous searches.
What a
wonderful tool!
I can make
you a copy.
That's okay. Once
I've seen a tool,
I can usually recreate
it for myself.
We'll have what we
need in no time at all.
[Éclair] You already found
the distribution routes
and the coordinates of
the weapons arsenals?
Even with the latest hardware
at the Office of the Peace,
I would never have dreamed
of finding this so quickly.
It's not that hard
to believe, is it?
You have
to realize...
We E.S. members
are different.
You see, when it comes
to us and our abilities,
one and one doesn't
always equal two.
Point taken. I
won't argue there.
My only concern
is the fact that
so much power could
be easily abused.
I can't speak
for her
but my sister would
only do what is right.
Interesting. Do you know the
reason most wars are fought?
Everyone has his or her
own sense of what is right.
[Tweedledee] Transferring
Geo Sort distribution
data to G.O.T.T
headquarters.
Upon completion, C-Squared
and La Muse are bound
for reported coordinates
of the weapons arsenal.
[Worker] Move it!
There's no more time!
Once you've loaded all
you can carry, get out!
C'mon, hurry up with
those data files!
And don't you guys
forget that control core!
Go!
[Tweedledee] Well, they
certainly seem busy!
Hurry! It's a
G.O.T.T raid!
What the- ?
What are you doing, Lumiere?
You know they can't hear me!
The stealth
shield is up!
Éclair, there isn't
a shield in existence
that can silence
your big mouth.
Either way, they know we're
coming. We've got to move now!
Come in, Chief. This is
G.O.T.T. E.S. member Éclair
urgently requesting immediate
arrest authorization!
Hey, Chief!
Where are you?
That's strange. The signal
should be going through.
Talk about
bad timing.
Uh,
Chief?
Don't you
ever knock?
Well, I did, but there's an
important call coming through!
Éclair is requesting immediate
arrest authorization!
Thank you. I know.
Is that all?
But,
Chief!
You may go
now, Mercredi.
Pardon me.
Chief Eclipse
speaking. Right.
It's coming through.
That's correct.
Yes sir, I have carried out
your orders as instructed.
Any
problems?
Well, there were a few, but
nothing to be concerned about.
Remember the sensitive
nature of all this.
Yes, of course, sir. I
understand completely.
We can't wait for
the chief to respond!
If we don't
stop them now,
there won't be anyone
left for us to arrest!
Let me guess. Her ability
must be recklessness.
Something
like that.
[Armblast]
Well, well...
There it is. It looks
like the show has begun.
Éclair... such
need for extremes.
[Tweedledee]
Tweedledum.
Don't forget. This is
all material evidence.
We need to disable them without
destroying them completely.
Use some
restraint.
Yes, I know.
I know.
Of course, that may
prove to be difficult.
Sorry, sister, but...
well, that one had to go.
Tweedledum, don't call
me sister on assignment!
Uh, sorry,
Tweedledee!
[Lumiere] Aw, it's
such a waste!
It's the ships! They're
moving on their own!
It's a genetic beast!
And my energy shield
is out of power. No!
Ta-da!
Éclair!
Let's see, if this was
Little Red Riding Hood,
I guess that would
make me the hunter.
What's that?
The transport
ships!
Ah, good.
You're awake.
[Lumiere]
Where are we?
I'm not sure. I had to get
out of there pretty fast.
Thank you,
Éclair.
Don't you think the siblings
are going a bit far?
It's not them. The smugglers
must have given up
on escaping and decided
to destroy the evidence.
We've got
to hurry!
[Tweedledee] What
a bunch of fools.
Tweedledee?
We managed to
secure our targets
and restrict the
surrounding area, but...
They did it. They
really are fools.
What did
they do?
They... the smugglers
detonated a Geo Sort bomb.
It didn't leave
us much choice.
We're doing our best
to suppress the blast.
Tweedledee!?
Oh no!
Sorry about that. I don't
think we can hold this thing
for much longer.
Take the evidence and
get out while you can!
No! Tweedledee!
You are just a
C-class member!
Your duty is to follow the
orders of your superiors!
Are we clear
on this?
Good! Now do as
you're told C-class!
Lumiere. My
only regret is...
Well, it would
have been nice
if we could have
become better friends.
Lumiere!
Éclair! No!
Sister, please! You've
got to stay focused!
Why couldn't Cesario and Viola
be here? With their ability,
they can disrupt
intermolecular forces,
the same way
this bomb does.
They could've
nullified this blast
without even
breaking a sweat!
[Éclair] Maybe you
can ask the Chief
to pair you up with
them next time.
Not that you
need the help.
It's Éclair
and Lumiere!
What are you doing?
The mission!
Don't worry. It's all
been taken care of.
We packed up the suspects
and all the evidence,
and Lumiere
programmed a ship
to take 'em straight
to headquarters.
But what would possess
you to come back here?
There's nothing
you can do now!
Don't mind them. They were
just giving us directions.
Oh great,
it's Alv.
This is quite a
mess you've made.
Well, Dvergr,
let's clean it up.
Okay, run
along now.
Unless the two of you want
to be absorbed as well.
All right, fine!
Come on, Tweedledum!
Right behind
you, sis!
One!
Two!
Three!!
Oh, yes!
The power!
So this is a Geo
Sort bomb! Amazing!
Raw energy,
feeding on itself!
The resonance... It keeps
building! And building!
So that's their ability.
Absorb... It's incredible.
What is your
primary duty?
[All] To collect and
secure any objects
that might be used
for evidence! Ma'am!
Very good!
Now snap to it!
[All] Ma'am!
You have...
my thanks.
It's nothing. I understand that
covering for weaker members
is just a part of the job.
Besides, we owed you.
[Dverger]
Come in, Chief.
We've completed
our mission.
Dverger. Alv. Excellent
work. Now head back.
I'l be looking forward
to your safe return.
Why didn't she
respond to my call?
Something isn't
right here!
Chief Eclipse, I'm only asking
that you not abandon her.
I know it's not my place. I'm
sure you know what you're doing
and you obviously
have your reasons.
But what I'm
trying to get at here
is that I want to
make certain that-
Inspector.
You're quite correct.
It isn't your place.
It poses as a friend. Then
creeps up from behind.
When the truth is discovered,
it's already too late.
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: Mirage/Snare