Care to share
your thoughts
on the completion of
the Atlas Project?
Could you tell
our viewers
your plans for tomorrow's
launching ceremony?
It's unbelievable...
How massive it is...
Yes. The
Atlas-class
intergalactic
spaceship, Deucalion...
Total length:
Sixty-three thousand,
fifty-eight
kilometers...
With an indefinite fuel supply,
independent warp capability,
and even a state-of-the-art
terraforming facility.
I'm aware of
what it is...
What it's for is
another matter.
This ship represents everything
we've accomplished as a race.
It's human kind's
crowing achievement.
Man has built a machine
with the powers of a god.
Human kind? You mean
the Nouvlesse, right?
You make it sound like
they're somehow separate
from the rest
of humanity.
The Nouvlesse are a
different breed...
They're
Earthlings.
Sure is coming
down out there...
It certainly is...
"Lightning"... Well, how 'bout
that. Just like my name, huh?
So it would
seem, yes.
That looks
so tedious.
Tedious, but
necessary.
After all, even if I
can't use my abilities,
I still need to know
this information
to do my job
properly.
Lumiere...
Okay,
that's it...
Next time, we're using
a nanomist shield.
Or an
umbrella even!
Oh, come on!
Do we really need to dissolve
every single molecule that-
Can I...
help you?
Don't play
dumb with me!
You still owe us some
serious payback, Lummi!
Payback?
Sorry if this comes
as a surprise...
But evasion tactics are
one of my specialties.
Hey, Viola! Just
let it go, okay?!
Your choice: We can do
one million dinners...
or we can go out for
three million lunches.
But they're all
your treat, got it?!
That sounds fair...
I mean it, Lummi! One
million! I'm not kidding!
This office is a bit more
luxurious than your old one...
You've done well
for yourself.
I'm not sure what
to tell you...
Besides, we have more
important matters to discuss.
Yes, I understand you've
given the siblings
the all-important task
of carrying the champagne for
tomorrow's launching ceremony.
That's right. Those two
will serve as my eyes.
Then does that
make me your ears?
Information is a
valuable commodity.
[Eclipse]
In which case,
I believe I've already
paid you more than enough,
thanks to
your partner.
[Armblast] Nothing
gets by you, does it?
[Armblast] Well, then. As
I'm sure you are aware,
the Atlas Project was
largely financed
by the G.U. itself. And its
publicly declared intent
placed it under the
direct oversight
of the G.O.T.T.'s
Development Bureau.
There it is, in
all its glory.
That big hunk of metal
just cost the Global Union
a couple hundred years'
worth of its general fund.
Not to mention the thousands of
corporations, financial groups,
and planet-states
that have their assets
tied up in
this ship.
There's a lot
riding on it...
No. Actually, it's a
fairly safe investment.
The Deucalion should more
than pay for itself, right?
Planetary development...
That's the key.
With its terraforming
capabilities,
the Deucalion will
be able to produce
whole worlds of
prime real-estate
in a relatively short
amount of time.
Aren't they worried about
over-saturating the market?
...but it's not
what it appears.
As its name would suggest,
the Deucalion is an ark.
[Council A] Has the Council
reached a consensus?
By show of hands, all
those in favor...
Very well. Let the record show
that, by unanimous decision,
Chevalier d'Autriche is hereby
dismissed from the post of
Global Union
Minister of Finance,
and relieved of his duties
as G.O.T.T. Secretary.
Personally, I'll be
glad to be rid of him.
Yes... d'Autriche has caused
us nothing but
trouble from the start.
We put this off
for far too long...
The completion of the Deucalion
marks the perfect opportunity
for us to drop our
excess baggage.
Perhaps you're interested
in taking over his position?
Please... You
must be joking.
I have no intention of
getting my hands that dirty.
Yes? Come in...
I'm sorry it took
so long, Chief.
I have the records
you requested.
That's all right.
Thank you, Vendredi.
[Armblast]
Records?
[Eclipse] A complete accounting
of the G.O.T.T.'s affairs,
from the
top down.
Interesting... Are you sure
I should be seeing this?
Well... you're used
to sticking your nose
where it
doesn't belong.
What can I say?
It's my job.
So, if you
don't mind...
What do we have here? Corporate
bribery, judicial tampering...
Several payoffs to regional
government officials,
illegal market
manipulation -
and that's just
the first page.
You've been busy
here at the G.O.T.T.
Actually, the events
you describe...
they are the actions of one
man, working behind the scenes.
One man?
You mean...?
So...
You two...
You don't sound too
happy to see us.
I thought we agreed to
restrict our communications
to Security
Line 606.
So we did. But today we're
acting as messengers.
We've come to inform
you that, moments ago,
the Privy Council
unanimously voted
to remove you
from office.
You are hereby
relieved of your duties
as the Global Union
Minister of Finance
and G.O.T.T.
Secretary.
Is that a fact?
How unfortunate.
I've grown
rather accustomed
to the view from
up here. Though...
I can't say
I'm surprised.
At least...
not like I was
when I learned that the two
of you were still alive,
and that I wasn't
your only employer.
Old fool... I
work for myself.
But I am willing to
play the part of puppet
if it gets me
what I need.
That's very
clever of you.
I couldn't have said
it better myself.
How could all of
this go unnoticed?
It just doesn't
seem possible...
Not unless other high-ranking
G.U. officials were involved.
Which would then imply
that these crimes
were committed
by the G.O.T.T.
with the sanction
of the Nouvlesse...
That is an accurate
assessment.
I don't understand. If
you've known about this-
There is a vast
difference
between knowing
about something,
and being able to do
anything about it...
Isn't there?
Of course. My apologies.
So, why give this to me now?
You don't mean-?
It's incredible,
isn't it?
What is?
This new office. The
exterior may look the same,
but the internal systems have
been upgraded significantly.
We now have direct access to
every network on Aineias.
Wow, so with your
ability, you can-
No, I'm afraid I still
can't do much of anything.
Well, then we'll just have
to get that new body of yours
back to normal,
won't we?!
Yes, but how?
So, that was your whole
point in coming here?
To tell me I've
been fired?
Mostly... Except I was hoping
I'd get to tell you in person!
Were you now? Well,
it's the same result...
This is a reliable
security line.
I assure you, the
reception is quite clear.
Why you...! Where
are you?! Tell us!
I think not. You don't
need to know right now,
but you'll find
out soon enough.
Actually, there is
one more thing...
We want
the key!
The key entrusted to you as
the head of the G.O.T.T.!
Give it back, and then
make yourself scarce...
You'll find that you'll
live a lot longer.
Tell the Council... I am
no longer their puppet.
I believe we've
made the wishes
of our client
exceedingly clear.
Indeed.
Consider
yourself warned.
I wonder if this is the last
time I'll ever see this view.
Lumiere?
Is something wrong?
Nice to see you...
Éclair. Lumiere.
Me- Mercredi?
Where have you been all
this time?! I thought-
Well, I... I didn't
know what to think.
After all the
commotion around here,
when I heard you'd
turned up missing-
You could've at least
called me or something!
I'm sorry... so much has
happened since then...
So, that's a new
look for you, huh?
If you hadn't
said anything,
I wouldn't have
recognized you!
You've changed quite a bit
yourself since I saw you last.
Yeah... I guess a lot's
happened to us, too.
Right,
Lumiere?
Anyway, why don't we find
somewhere we can sit down
and talk for
a while?
I wish I could. I only came
in to deliver a message...
Oh. Well, okay.
So what's the deal? You
sure are acting strange...
Am I
really?
You're telling me you didn't
notice anything unusual.
You mean with Mer? Well, sure,
I mean she looked different...
I'm not merely talking
about outward appearances...
According
to this data,
Mercredi was removed from the
employee registry, since...
since it was unclear whether
she was alive or dead.
So, in terms
of access,
she should be treated
as a general visitor.
And yet, somehow, she managed
to enter the building
without passing by us
at the reception desk.
You don't think there might
be something to that?
You won't
find her.
Besides... didn't you think
her messege was interesting?
"Go to the Chief's
office immediately!"
What are you
two doing here?
Yes?
Excuse me, Chief.
ES Members Éclair and
Lumiere are here to see you.
Very well.
Send them in.
Terribly sorry, ladies. But
I'm afraid I was here first.
So that's it...
Wh- what is
all this?
It's a little glimpse
at what the G.O.T.T.'s
really been up to
behind the scenes.
Like they say, "the
truth hurts." Right?
Chief Eclipse!
How could you?!
No, Éclair! Read
it carefully!
Each of the things
listed here was done
under the direction of
the G.O.T.T. Secretary,
not the Chief.
The G.O.T.T. Secretary? You
mean he... he did all this?
That's right...
Chevalier d'Autriche.
Bye!
All right! See
you tomorrow!
It's a shame,
really...
School
lets out,
and the children have to
go rushing off to work.
They don't have
to, they want to.
This might be their
only chance...
I mean... they'll have plenty
of homework to keep 'em busy
once school's in full swing.
And it's gettin' there!
It certainly is.
The Rosenfeld Foundation's
done so much for us.
It just goes
to show you,
not all of the Nouvlesse
are bad people.
Even so... we can't
let our guard down.
Well, it's a good thing we
have you to look out for us.
Hey,
Bateau!
Do you mind if I go
ahead and call it a day?
Timothy! I didn't know
you were still here.
That's all right, Tim!
Go have some fun, okay?
Thanks!
Master Timothy, I do hope
this is the last time
you'll
do this.
What with your
schedule and all...
Sorry... We're just gonna
have to make the time.
I wanna keep coming back
until that school's finished.
So, what's next?
I've got that dinner with
the Prime Minister, right?
Yes. Immediately
following which,
you have a meeting
with the leaders
of the Trade
Union. After that,
we will be relocating
to the second continent.
At Oh-Nine-Hundred
hours local time,
you are scheduled
to appear before
the Financial
Board of Trustees,
where they will be submitting
the first of the Fair Trade
Éclair...
This planet is going
to be all right...
Thanks
to you,
Aure will
finally be free...
This is most
inopportune...
Just as we rid ourselves
of one little nuisance,
another one
rears its head.
I take it you are referring
to the Rosenfeld Group.
They were expelled
from this Council
as of our last meeting,
were they not?
Still, further
reprimand is justified.
Nouvlesse who have lost
their pride as Earthlings
are even worse
than commoners.
Granted, but even if
they continue to aid
the anti-Nouvlesse
movement,
it changes
nothing.
With enough time, they'll
spread their influence
throughout the galaxy
and foul everything...
Including our
precious Earth, here.
Isn't that why we've
built the ark?
Isn't that what the
Deucalion is for?
Even so, it's still
distasteful...
In the end, it
means retreating...
Surrendering the
galaxy to them.
There's nothing that can
be done about that now.
Or would you prefer
we destroy them all?
It would be
simple enough.
But such barbarism, I
leave to the commoners.
We are
above them.
As pureblooded
Earthlings,
it is our duty to
remember that fact.
A phase
fluctuation?
Tweedledum... Run a
perimeter sweep, level 5.
I'm on it.
Initiating sweep...
It's a canceller! A small ship,
on approach to the Deucalion!
Can you
I.D. it?
Negative! I'm
losing the signal!
It just...
disappeared.
[Control] Attention,
G.O.T.T. vessel.
You are entering
restricted space.
You have not been cleared for
approach to the Deucalion.
Break off your present
course immediately.
Our ship has detected
an irregularity.
Requesting permission to
approach and investigate.
Negative. I repeat: discontinue
your present course at once!
The Deucalion!
It's powering up!
No, that's
impossible!
[Council B]
The Deucalion!
[Council H] But how?!
This can't be happening!
[Council D] There's
only one person
capable of
starting it up...
[Council C] Stop it! Stop
the Deucalion at all costs!
When a man wields
tremendous power,
he will appear in
the eyes of others
as a god
or a devil.
However, there is no one who
can truly know his heart.
Next time on Kiddy Grade:
Demolition / Titan.