Status?
Everything is running
smoothly, Chief.
The nanomachines
in the atmosphere,
crust and magma are
fully operational.
Coffee?
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Looks like the
energy supplies
to the islands
are working fine.
Her atmosphere has already
settled into the Earth model.
Now, if we can
just maintain
the mantle plume's stability
and sustain the plate,
seems as if our
job here is done.
Thanks, Chief.
They say that in a
hundred and thirty days..
They're expecting to
have eighty percent
of the oceans'
water filled in.
But, of course, it'll
still be a few years
before plants can grow and she
can sustain any human life.
That's true, but that's
work for another team.
We'll be long
gone by then.
I doubt we'll have any
reason to come back here,
unless it's
on vacation.
Heh, Sounds
good to me.
We'll certainly
have the time.
Once the new Atlas models
are put into service,
it's going to make
our jobs a lot easier.
Careful, Éclair. You're
upsetting Donnersclag.
I'm not upsetting
you am I, Donner?
But I sure wouldn't blame
you if you were upset...
being on the run and having
to fight your friends.
I guess things aren't
really working out
like you thought
they would, huh?
Does this mean you're
having regrets?
Why should I have any
regrets, Lumiere?
I mean, it's not like I
did anything wrong here!
Well if that's
the case,
then why do you keep
beating yourself up
over something that
isn't your fault?
Here, I have
an idea,
why don't you help
me repair La Muse?
That way we'll be
ready to take off
if they find out
where we are.
But we don't have
any spare parts.
Actually, we
have plenty...
It's just that
at the moment,
they're scattered
all over the planet.
You didn't think I brought
us all the way out
to this
frontier region
just for the
seclusion, did you?
Right then...
Now let's
get to work.
Thank you.
I don't think I ever
could've made it this far...
not by myself, anyway.
You, Donner, and La Muse are
all I have to keep me going.
This is no time to get
sentimental, Éclair.
We have a
job to do.
There's an unmanned island
about to pass over us.
You're sure we're not gonna
run into anyone up there?
[Lumiere] There should
be a small team
aboard the Central
Command Island...
But since the planet's
surface is still forming...
We're the only ones who
can survive out here.
See, there she is. Just like
I told you. Let's do this.
Fine.
Does this really
bother you so much?
Yes, of course
it does.
What? Do you think I should
be happy about this?
Sister, if it bothers you...
Maybe you shouldn't do it.
How many times
have I told you-
don't call me 'sister'
when we're on assignment.
Especially not
one like this.
Please forgive me for
what I'm about to do.
Donnersclag...
Wirbelwind...
[Lumiere] A terraforming
operation like this
requires an
enormous number of
nanomachines to affect
change on a planetary scale.
These islands
inject the nanomachines
into the environment,
supply them with power,
and relay commands
from Central Control.
Yeah?
So what?
In order to get from
one planet to the next,
the island itself
functions as a spaceship.
Which means we should
find a few parts
that we can
use inside.
I think that should take care
of La Muse for a while...
What? What's
the matter?
A small craft approaching
us at tremendous speed.
Determining model...no
time! 3...2...1...!
Donnersclag?!
Donner?
What's wrong
with him?
His AI must have
been tampered with.
How can
that be?
It's supposed to be impossible
to hack into his system.
Wait a
minute...
Who could possibly be
capable of tampering with
Donnersclag's AI system
from the outside?
It's
Tweedledee!
Okay, ladies, I'll come
right to the point...
By order of the GOTT,
your crafts have
been reprogrammed...
They now have only one
primary function...
...And that is to ensure the
destruction of you both.
What're you
talking about?!
No! Not
Wirbelwind, too!
I'm sorry, but I
have my orders...
Under normal
circumstances,
these are not the methods I
would have chosen to use.
La Muse's security
will soon be down
and it's new
program in control.
You have about
five minutes left.
Use that time
to decide
if you're going to
die quietly or fight.
There's one
more thing...
It may
sound selfish
but I would like to ask
for a personal favor.
Please do everything
within your power
to spare
these children.
Very well. Goodbye.
And good luck.
Tweedledee... Do you think
you handled that well?
I mean they can easily
scan your memory
and play back
what you said.
Get that thing
out of my sight.
Tweeledum! I said
get rid of it!
What could the
GOTT be thinking?
It's bad enough
that the Chief
is ordering friends
to kill each other...
but to make me do
something so awful...
so disgusting... They've
gone too far this time.
This is the worst mission
I've ever been on!
I don't get it. What
kind of program is this
that has you
so worked up?
The worst kind.
The special assassination
program... Hashish.
[Éclair] Can't you
control him?
[Lumiere] No... Not with
his nanomist shield up.
Even under normal conditions
it would take me hours
to hack into
his system.
I certainly couldn't
do it in five minutes.
It's not like Donnersclag
to keep missing like this...
especially at
such close range.
What are
you saying?
This will buy
us some time!
It seems to me... his
actions are forced.
I don't think the program has
complete control over him...
at least
not yet.
So there's
some hope.
Do you think you might be
able to get through to them?
I might, but it
won't be easy.
And besides, I would
hate to have to
subject them to
my usual methods.
Oh, this is hopeless!
We have to destroy them.
It's either that or
let them kill us!
Well I say...
Neither!
No! Éclair, wait!
Go!
I'll hold off
Donnersclag somehow.
You go take
care of La Muse!
If I can just make it to
the emergency control room,
I may be able to
utilize the nanomists
in the environment
to our advantage.
You'd be easy enough for
me to destroy, my friend..
But don't worry... I'll
find a way to save you.
Come on then... I'm
ready, Donnersclag.
Hey, Chief! You wanna
take a look at this?
A high concentration
of nanomist
has created a
tropical cyclone
on the other side
of the planet!
Impossible!
Wait a second. This
can't be right!
There also seems to be
a massive energy drain
in the airspace
over that region!
Readings from Islands
Alpha through Gamma
show all energy plants
operating at full capacity!
I need an immediate analysis!
Find out what's happening!
The storm is centered
on Island Theta.
I'm measuring a
40-kilometer radius!
[Lumiere] Okay, I've gained
control of the nanomists.
I should be able to create
a protective barrier.
Don't worry,
Wirbelwind...
I'll get you back to
normal... somehow.
Just
in time.
I should have known it would
take a lot more than that
to stop you,
Wirbelwind!
I've got to do
this just right,
or the La Muse
will be vaporized.
It's spreading! Nanomists
all over the planet
are behaving
erratically!
I don't
believe it!
The nanomists in the
stratosphere are condensing!
It's acting as
a giant lens!
The chlorophoric value
is off the charts!
There's just no
precedent for this...
What in the world is
going on out there?
Well, this will be
trickier if I can't see you.
I doubt that move's going
to work a second time...
My girl is as crafty
as she is cautious.
I wonder where she
gets that from?
This must be so
hard for her!
My goodness... You're...
a tough boy aren't you...?
I guess I can't go
easy on you anymore.
Sorry... Donner!
Don't worry I'll put
you back together
better than
new... I promise!
Forgive me...
She's redirecting energy
to her flex phasers.
Oh no! She going for
a point-blank attack!
Stop it!
Wirbelwind! No!
Please...stop
it...Donner...
Oh no...! Please
don't shoot!
She's getting more
aggressive with each attack.
The program must be
gaining control...
What am I
going to I do?
Magma concentration readings
below Theta are off the scale!
And the viscosity
is dropping.
I'm reading a massive
build-up of Lorentz forces...
Pressure levels are
approaching critical mark!
Is there anything
we can do?
Cheif, I hate
to say this,
but it's been out of our
hands for some time now!
Some outside force has taken
control of the region.
At this rate, it's going to
break through the crust!
It's over now.
I gotcha.
Donner...?
Donner... No...
Activate!
Now initiate
cooling systems!
Good. Her shield is down...
and she's immobilized.
I need to hurry and rewrite
the program while I still can.
Donnersclag activated
his self-destruct mechanism.
Do you think it
was... Hashish?
Hashish...
what's that?
Originally,
it was a drug
given to numb the
emotions of assassins.
It created the
perfect killer.
One who fears nothing.
Not even his own death.
Now, it's a
viral program
created to mimic
those same effects...
A machine's
primary function
under the virus'
influence is to kill.
It will stop at nothing
for that objective,
even if it destroys
itself in the process.
Oh no! That means
Wirbelwind too...!
She's activated
her inertial drive!
It's no use...!
I can't stop her!
Please, Wirbelwind!
Don't do this!
Stop it,
Wirbelwind! Stop!!
No!!
Wha...? Hey, what...? It all
just went back to normal!
What just
happened?
[Lumiere] Even if they had been
successful in killing us...
they were programmed
to self-destruct
after their
mission.
Wirbelwind and
Donnersclag knew this
and spared us by
destroying themselves
before they lost
complete control.
In their
final moments,
they were doing everything in
their power to save our lives.
I get it... So they were
considered disposable
right from
the start.
So this is...
...This is how
the GOTT works?!
Donnersclag...
No more... This time
they've gone too far.
I'm going to put an end to
this... One way or another.
I won't let
you stop me.
Well, then I'm
going with you.
What did you
expect me to say?
If there's a time for
elegance... this isn't it.
Complete destruction. All that
was once held dear is gone.
But after everything's
been taken away,
there's nothing
left to lose.
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: "Break/Down".