I finally have a
whole day off!
Okay, okay, okay!
Hello? Hi, Ricky!
Huh...? Dinner...?
Sure! I'd love to...
Just tell me what
time you want to meet!
Uh, Right now...? Well,
it's a little early...
What do you mean
it's almost dark?
I don't
believe it.
I overslept.
I'm still
kicking myself.
How could I sleep
through the whole day?
At least you won't
have to take a catnap
at work tomorrow
like you normally do.
But this was
my day off...
Hey, cheer up! We're
young, we're single,
and we're about to
have dinner at Ubu!
Ubu! Really?!
You're the
best, Ricky!
Um, we're splitting
the bill... 'kay?
Wow! But I
don't know.
I hear this place
is pretty pricey...
Let's live a little,
Éclair... Besides,
my frequent diner's card
will get us a discount.
Miss?
I'm sorry, but the restaurant
does not admit anyone
under the age
of eighteen.
Hey, wait. She's with me,
and I'm a frequent diner.
I'm afraid those
are the rules.
Our money's just as good as
anyone else's here, pal!
Sorry, I'm just a
waiter, ma'am.
It's okay, Ricky. Let's
go someplace else.
Ladies...
Welcome to Ubu.
Sir, I tried
to stop them.
Sorry,
he's new.
This way.
Thank you, sir.
Are you sure
about this, sir?
Turning away customers will
only draw unwanted attention...
Got it?...
Besides, who do you think
our benefactors would blame
if a customer complaint
brought down their operation?
We've got enough to
worry about tonight.
Good evening,
gentlemen.
[Mercredi]
Insider trading?
[Eclipse] Yes. With
economic regulations
here on Aineias
being relaxed,
criminal organizations
are conspiring
to take advantage
of the situation.
Our sources believe that
Laughing Jester is involved.
Laughing Jester...
They steal and sell secret
financial information
to the
highest bidder.
I've been told they're
meeting with another group
to discuss a
partnership...
and we're hoping that we
can catch them in the act.
But on a planet of this size,
finding the meeting place
is going to be
extremely difficult,
even for our
best agents.
Keep me apprised of
any reports, Mercredi.
Wow! This place looks
absolutely fantastic!
It is. Hey, should we
have invited Lumiere?
I see her everyday.
I don't think it'll
hurt either one of us
to spend a little
time apart, you know?
So that's
how it is.
Uh-Huh, that's
Miss Lumiere,
are you sure that Miss Éclair
wouldn't want to accompany you?
I'm sure... This
is her day off too,
and I think she'll appreciate
spending a little time
away from
me for a change.
Besides,
knowing Éclair,
I'm positive wouldn't have
wanted to go to the opera.
Okay then.
Good night, all.
Good evening, ma'am.
That looks great!
Almost too good to eat!
A partnership, huh?
It's a win-win
situation for everyone.
So tell me,
why do we need to get in
bed with Laughing Jester?
You get inside information
that will let you
make a killing
in the markets,
and we get a piece of
that fancy technology
I've heard so
much about.
Basically... you scratch our
back and we'll scratch yours.
Oh, I'm so full!
Then why did you
order dessert?
No matter how
much you eat,
there's always room
for ice cream!
I agree!
Excuse me?
May I have
this dance?
It's yum-yum-yummy!
If you acted a
little older,
maybe some guys would
ask us to dance tonight.
You say
something?
Hmm...
This
should work.
What are
you doing, Ricky?!
Wait a minute!
Knock it off... No!
Here I come!
All done...
Now you look like a
sophisticated mature woman!
Uhh.. Ricky,
this is a bad idea!
You look great.
And you should really wear
lipstick more often I mean,
I can't remember the last
time I saw it on you...
That's because
wearing lipstick
makes it difficult to
control my powers.
Éclair?
Uh-huh?!
Éclair, you look
beautiful... I mean it!
Miss?
Yes?!
May I have the
pleasure of a dance?
With me?
But I don't-
No! No! Go ahead
and have some fun!
Are you sure?
No, wait!
Come.
I take it... you're
not a dancer.
Nope. I've got two left
feet... Sorry about that.
What?!
A bomb!
Must have been
an earthquake.
Maybe it's a sign...
of the power our two
organizations could have.
We'd be
earth-shattering, huh?
I knew this lipstick
would get me in trouble.
Did the earthquake
scare you, my dear?
Don't worry... Heh...
I've got you.
You're an
exquisite woman...
but I must have a name to
match your lovely face.
É- Éclair.
That means... Lightning,
correct? How heavenly.
Éclair.
Do you believe in
fate? ...I do.
I believe that fate has brought
us together this very night.
Our destiny is written
in the stars above...
and our story
begins with a kiss.
Is this one of
your assassins?!
No, we've never seen
this man before!
I knew we couldn't trust
you lousy jesters!
What's happening?!
What's...
going on here?!
...and I just
bought this one!
A cyborg!
We can't let
her escape!
This is supposed
to be my day off!
Éclair! Where are
you?! Éclair!
Éclair!!!
Éclair!
La Traviata... I'm
practically in tears already.
Seems I'm not
the only one...
Excuse me... Hi...
Hey... There, there,
now. What's the matter?
Did you get separated
from your mother?
Good girl.
What do we have here? An
illegal cyborg, huh?
Do you know how much damage
you caused us tonight?
Hey, don't blame me. I just
came here to eat dinner...
And with service like this,
I won't be leaving a tip.
Thanks to you,
sweetheart...
we can no longer use this
establishment as a front...
and you ruined
the plans we had
for our now-dead
associates in the other room!
This isn't my fault!
That guy grabbed me-
Ah, shut up...
We were planning on killing
them eventually anyway.
However, you've forced us
to accelerate our schedule
more than a
little bit...
and we expect to be paid
for our inconvenience.
M- Me pay you? But I could
barely afford dinner tonight!
Don't want money...
We want your body!
Where am I?
This definitely isn't
the evening show
at the
opera house.
The bosses didn't check
in. We need to leave.
Don't freak out... No one's
got the balls to take us on.
Laughing
Jester does...
Let's get these brats to
the treatment facility.
Treatment facility?
[Kidnapper 2] We've
gotta get out of here now!
Prepare to blast-off!
That means... we're
at... the spaceport!
[LJ Leader] In
order to succeed,
you've got to have
a competitive edge.
Our late friends
used to have that edge,
but now we're going
to take it from them.
What's
their secret?
Children.
Children?!
[Leader] Sons and daughters of
this planet's upper classes.
They kidnap 'em,
zap some post-hypnotic
suggestions
in their
little minds,
and then send 'em
home to mommy and daddy
seemingly no worse for wear.
It's brilliant, really.
They even use the kids
to kidnap more kids...
and we're finally gonna get
us a piece of that action!
[Lumiere] Timed
hypnotic suggestions...
They take effect when the
children reach adulthood
and have become
prominent members of society.
They're being
turned into puppets.
And you'll be the one
pulling their strings...
Wow... That's what I
call a long-term plan.
We're prepared to wait.
One day little Johnny
and little Suzie
are going to control
this planet's finances
and government. But all
their influence and power
will
belong to us.
Huh... Sounds like you've
got it all worked out.
This has got to be the
most interesting job
that I've
ever had.
If you do what you're
told, keep quiet,
and shoot straight... maybe
I'll forgive your debt.
Uh, okay!
I'll do my best!
Well, now
that I'm here,
I can't very well leave without
doing something about this.
I've gotta break
away from these guys...
I told you those bastards
would double-cross us!
Alright! Alright! We're
going! We're going!
Go make sure those
brats are secured!
Roger!
How did you get out?
Hey! Stop that whinin'!
I really hate
these whiny kids.
Come on... Get back
in your chamber!
I know how
you feel...
I fell for the
same trick.
But, I suppose you really
should have seen it coming...
They could certainly learn a
thing or two about elegance...
Hey! Someone's hacking
into our mainframe!
They're trying to override
our assault fighters!
Hacking in...?
So hit 'em with an EMP
and shut the punk down!
Yes, sir!
I can't!
What the-
I'm losing control!
Hackers, great! Where's
Lumiere when I need her...?
Uh- what is that girl doing?!
C'mon! Get us out of here!
I... can't, sir!
Official G.O.T.T.
business.
[Lumiere] The children we
found on board the ship
have already been taken to
the hospital for treatment.
I also discovered
a database
with the names of
all the children
they had ever kidnapped...
With a little follow up,
we should be able to
reverse the damage.
You and Éclair sure
did a lot of work
on your day off...
Didn't you?
Hush now,
my child
Close your
little eyes.
Slumber awaits... and
all the sweetest dreams
Rest now,
my child
Close your-
Oh, Mer!
What a pretty song...
Where did you learn it?
Beats me.
What...? Really?
I just know
it somehow.
Don't cry,
little baby...
Mommy will be here
very soon, okay?
I know. How about I sing
to you a little more? Okay?
Rest now, my child...
looks pretty good at that,
doesn't she?
Yes, she does.
Let mother rock you, Un-der
The Heavenly skies...
[Eclipse] We're lucky
Lumiere and Éclair
stumbled on this
when they did...
How are those
two holding up?
What...? A lullaby? I see...
Thank you, Mercredi.
Tell the girls not to be
late for E-Shift tomorrow.
[Éclair] The mirror
reflects an image,
but what it shows
is not the truth.
Just as right turns into left,
the truth becomes a lie...
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: Twin/Star