Ta-daa!
Here
we go!
W-where...?
I'm sorry but...
who are you?
My name's
Éclair. Hi.
Lumiere.
With so many of the
same faces around,
even I almost
have a hard time
keeping them all
straight. Except...
Except what?
Well, you've got the
look down pretty good.
But you always did wear
too much makeup... Alv.
What are you
talking about?
I agree... And I'd say the
same goes for you... Dverger.
"Absorb." The ability to
assimilate and copy...
I'm not sure what good
you thought copying us
was going
to do...
But in any case, this Little
Miss Look Alike contest
has gone on
long enough.
You can say
whatever you want.
We'll see who's real...
and who's dead!
Please...
What do you think?
Should we help?
Let's give
them a chance.
The full might
of the G.O.T.T.
has been turned to
ridding the galaxy
of antisocial
elements like you...
One way or another,
you're going to be purged.
Just make it easy on
yourself and give up!
Just 'give
up' huh?
I'm sorry, I don't
know what that means.
Those words aren't
in my vocabulary!
You'd do well to
pay attention
when someone gives
you free advice.
That depends on
who's giving it.
You idiot! What
are you doing!?
What?!
Did you
see that?
Yes...
Wait!
Is she-?
No! Don't get
close to her!
You stupid, stupid girl...
You'll never learn.
That really does
come in handy...
Everyone!
Start climbing!
I'm sorry... I
wasn't much help.
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
What
happened?
She absorbed your powers
when you attacked.
Looks
like it.
But from everything
we've seen so far,
it appears her
"Absorb" ability
only lasts for a
short period of time.
Once the time
limit has expired,
she has to absorb energy
from someone else
in order to 'recharge her
batteries', as it were.
So then... she was
almost out of power?
If I hadn't just gone
rushing in like that...
I probably would've
done the same thing...
...if I
were you.
Now then... don't you
think it's about time
we made
our stand?
As the old
saying goes:
"borrowed wisdom is
a tenuous thing."
Theirs is only growing more
tenuous by the minute...
We don't know
that for certain.
This may be our best
chance to find out.
And why
is that?
In mountainous
warfare,
it's generally favorable
to take the high ground.
If the theory
holds true,
that would give us
the clear advantage.
For my part, I'll
do what I can
to keep all of our new friends
here out of harm's way.
The rest... I
leave to you.
'Kay... Ready?
Ready.
Go!
My power!
That got her!
You see? Now what
did I tell you?
No!
Ah, perfect. Our little
delivery boy's right on time.
Here's your tip...
You've earned it.
You're mine!
Fools!
No! Don't,
Armblast!
Get out
of the way!
Go.
Now why would
I do that?
I believe I've
already mentioned
how fond I am
of these two.
In that
case... Die.
Dextera!
Sinistra!
I'm sure you would've done
fine without our help...
We just couldn't pass
up the opportunity
to give the good "Acting
Chief" a little payback.
We've been watching
for a while.
I wanted to come
down sooner, but-
Don't worry about it.
Your timing is perfect.
Of course,
I'm not sure
everyone would agree
with you on that...
We've run out of
time. The game is up.
You're wrong. We haven't
lost this fight yet.
And we're not going
to lose it now.
Not when I'm so
close to my revenge!
Your
revenge?
Everything I've done: absorbing
your G-Class abilities...
disposing of
the Chief...
assuming control
of the G.O.T.T...
It was all part of my
plan to take revenge
against the
Nouvlesse!
What is the
"Global Union"?
Or even the G.O.T.T.?
Empty names...
In the end, it's still the
Nouvlesse who control the lives
of every single
person in the galaxy!
You of all people
should understand.
You've seen the way the
Nouvlesse exploit the masses
to serve
their whim.
You know the hardships we've
been made to endure...
And all the suffering we've
caused in their name!
The G.O.T.T. you serve so
proudly is a mockery.
It was only created as a
tool for the Nouvlesse.
All these years,
the only thing we've ever
protected is their interests.
We have no choice but to
act the part of pawns.
We aren't even
allowed to die!
If there's a worse
hell than this,
then you tell
me what it is!
But now it's their turn to
suffer, just as I have.
The Nouvlesse and all
of their puppets...
I'm going to pay you all
back - ten times over!
I'll stop at nothing. Even
if it costs me my life!
I understand that you
hate the Nouvlesse.
So do I... But you're
acting like a selfish child!
I think we all share your
feelings to some degree.
Even so, that doesn't
excuse what you've done.
What else was I
supposed to do?!
You had the option to become
fugitives, just as we did.
What are
you saying?
If it was what you truly
wanted, with your abilities,
I'm sure the
two of you
would've had little
trouble escaping.
That's
absurd!
You say everything
you've done
has been in the
name of revenge...
But I
suspect
that you're only trying to
convince yourself of that...
to justify your
true lust for power.
Believe what you
want. I don't care.
In another five minutes...
it won't matter.
Like I said, we haven't
lost this fight yet.
Come on! We need
to fall back!
Well... So much
for the advantage.
Yeah... Any more
bright ideas?!
They're
coming!
Faster!
I've got
them...
You know, it's really
something of a shame
that things had to
turn out this way.
How's that?
I mean, in the end, we all
basically want the same thing.
It's just a thin line that
separates us from them.
Perhaps... Except
their goals included
the destruction of
G.O.T.T. headquarters.
However noble
their motives,
that's a line that should
never have been crossed.
And let's not forget the
murder of Chief Eclipse...
I can't say I agree with the
way the Nouvlesse operate
any more than
they do...
But there's a difference
between changing the system
and throwing
it into chaos.
If they succeed in
destroying the G.O.T.T.,
it could potentially lead to
the complete financial collapse
of the galaxy!
Yeah, but how do
you really feel?
That's irrelevant. I'm
only stating the facts.
More than
anything,
I think Dextera here is
just a little bitter
about being made
to play the fool
through all
this business...
Sinistra!
Well, you guys can sit around
and argue about that later...
Right now, I think
we can all agree
the only thing
that matters
is defeating Alv
and Dverger, yeah?
Do you have to ask? I'd think
that obvious at this point.
Okay
then!
Where do they think
they're going?
Nowhere. We're coming
up on a dead end.
A 'dead end'?
How appropriate.
It will be for them in
more ways than one.
We can't keep
this up...
Oh, my,
my....
What?
You surprise me. I didn't
think the words 'give up'
were in your
vocabulary...
This is not the time
to start joking around!
Sorry. I was only
making an observation.
Hurry! Just
keep moving!
[Armblast] Should
we swim for it?
[Éclair] Don't
be ridiculous!
[Lumiere]
They're here!
It's over.
Such a nice
breeze...
They say that if you die in
a gentle breeze like this,
it will carry
your soul
to better fortunes
in your next life.
It'd be nice if
that were true.
But we both know better
than that, don't we?
Well, then there's
nothing left to say...
Except the
final "goodbye".
What the-?
Is that...?
It's about
time...
Well, a lady has to wait
for the right moment
to make a
proper entrance.
It... can't be!
Yes, the High-Speed Cruiser
La Muse... Prototype Zero...
Or, as it was formerly
known: Calliope.
But how?!
Donner!
This is the upgraded
version of Donnerschlag...
But for the
La Muse,
we actually had to go back to
the original production model.
Impossible...
Eclipse?!
Un-oh...?
It's like I
told you...
We found a job with more
interesting prospects.
How, Eclipse?! You were
dead! I watched you fall!
You know I was an ES
Member myself at one time...
My ability was known as
"Quandt"... or Quantum Jumping.
Surely, you've
heard of it.
The short version is it's
what brought us back to life.
Her ability is what
encoded all of us
as ES Members
to begin with.
Do you have any idea what I've
been through to get this far?
Do you?! The pain
I've suffered?
The humiliations I've
been forced to endure?
And at long last... Revenge
is finally within my reach.
It's mine! I won't
let it slip away!
It's all right.
I knew about
this... All of it.
I've known
from the start.
You see, you two
aren't the only ones
with access to
Security Line 606...
No!
...nor are you the only
ones with the ability
to absorb
and reflect.
Thank you...
Thanks for helping us. But
I guess this is goodbye...
We're just
shadows, really...
Disposable puppets Alv
created in your image,
so she could continue
to absorb your powers.
You could say our lives were
built on "borrowed wisdom."
They were never
meant to last...
But, you-
Understand,
Éclair...
the Global Union Charter
strictly prohibits
the creation of
clones such as these.
The law is very
clear in this matter.
They cannot be
allowed to exist.
Chief
Eclipse!
My advice to you
now is to forget
that they ever existed
in the first place.
After all,
something that doesn't exist
can't be judged, correct?
La Muse's
prototypes...
Number 1 is Clio...
Number 2: Terpsichore.
Number 3: Erato. Then Euterpe,
Thalia, and Polyhymnia!
All of you must
leave now.
But to help you on your way, I
present you with these ships.
I trust you
will use them
to make the most of
what limited time
you might have
in this life.
Good luck,
ladies...
They'll be just fine.
After all, they're us.
And look how
we turned out.
Chief
Eclipse...
Éclair... I want
you to know-
It's all right. I think
I understand now...
You did what you had to.
We can leave it at that.
Now things are really
getting interesting...
I'm sure the Global
Union Council
will have more than a few
words to say about all this...
A new day. A chance
to start a new life.
But time does
not stand still.
In the blink of an eye, the
future becomes the present,
becomes the past...
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: Lost / Days.