So... the time has
finally come...
You're welcome, sir, and enjoy
your visit to the G.O.T.T.
1030 hours..
All clear..
Nothing abnormal to report
on sensors or optics.
Ricki?
What is it?
I don't know.
For a second,
I thought I saw
Éclair and Lumiere.
You could at least
try to cheer up...
Cheer up? So you want me
to be happy about this?
Sister...
No matter what happens, I'll
be right there by your side.
Tweedledum...
No matter
what...
This stinks. We shouldn't
even be here today.
Don't give
me that look.
I heard the orders
just like you did...
"All ES Members not
on active duty
are to remain on stand-by
'til further notice."
But this was supposed
to be my vacation!
What about
all my plans?!
Don't worry... I'll be
ready when the time comes.
But that doesn't mean
I have to like it.
Interesting. First Éclair and
Lumiere.. Now Un-ou and A-ou..
Looks like all the
G.O.T.T.'s brightest stars
are falling
from grace.
Does it?
I beg to
differ.
ES Members, by the very
nature of their work,
must live in the shadows.
They are not bright stars.
I forgot... that's an honor
reserved for the Chief, right?
They've certainly picked an
opportune time to come,
with Dextera and Sinistra
still on assignment.
So it
would seem.
Just leave it to us. We've got
it all worked out. Trust me.
New explosion! Tower 2!
Section 35-A! Sir!
I'm reading fifteen
separate disturbances!
What's
the cause?!
Unknown! But they appear
to be both physical
and logical
attacks!
Silence
those alarms!
Start listening for anyone
still trapped inside!
Understood!
Everyone! This
way! Quickly!
Stay calm!
You'd better get
outta here, too!
All the explosions were
in Towers 1 and 3, right?
That's what
I heard.
We can still take
the express elevator!
Forget it! That's suicide!
I'm taking the stairs!
Your
funeral!
I told you you couldn't
escape your past...
And now, just
like before,
you're going to die...
The same way we all died.
That's as far as
you go, Éclair!
Tweedledee!
Traitor... You should never
have come back here.
Tweedledum...
It doesn't have to end like
this.. Surrender quietly.
No harm will
come to you.
That's assuming you can
still convince the Chief
to lift the
purge order.
Tweedledee...
What the-?
It's true, isn't
it, Éclair?
You've reawakened your past
memories and abilities...
...and you've remembered
that you're the most powerful
of all the
ES Members.
My gun's not
working either.
Ready men!
Fix bayonets!
Advance!
Now!
Release!
The fun stops
here, Lummi. Sorry.
A nanomist
shield?
That's Lummi!
She's probably controlling
all the security nanomists
in the building
by now.
Well, we can play
that game, too...
You're making
this too easy.
I thought
you knew...
'Containment' is sort of
one of our specialties.
I'm glad I can count on
your aim being so precise.
Sorry if this comes
as a surprise...
But evasion tactics are
one of my specialties.
Now, if you'll
excuse me...
I really don't
have time to waste
dealing with you
right now. Good day.
So you've opted for the
direct approach, huh?
It might've worked,
too, except...
we knew you
were coming.
Took you
long enough.
Lummi...?
I know it's not too 'elegant'.
But you have to admit...
a few modifications, and
even a simple extinguisher
can be quite
effective.
Cesario?
Cesario?! Cesario!
Cesario!
No more
running!
It's time we found out which
of our abilities is stronger...
Your 'Power'... Or
my 'Magnetfeld'.
Look out!
Tweedledum... When
I give the signal,
we're going to use
our 'Windstob'.
Sister! She's
still human!
She's more than that...
She's a G-Class ES Member.
What...?
Éclair...
Sister...
Tweedledum!
Hold on!
No... It-
It's... impossible!
Sister!
Get down!
Lumiere...?
After all that, they think a
door is going to slow us down?
Lumiere should know
better than that.
She's getting desperate.
They know they can't win!
Tweedledee!
Sister...?
Lumiere...
I wouldn't worry about
her, if I were you.
I can't open it. The
circuits have been severed.
I guess the little
fireworks display
was more than
they could take.
So... this was your
plan all along.
Was it your idea? Or is someone
still pulling your strings?
I am not anyone's
puppet... Not anymore.
No, Eclipse...
I want this.
Good bye, Chief.
And good riddance.
[Soldier] Look! There! Is
that someone on the roof?!
Even the mighty
G.O.T.T...
blown down like a
house of cards...
Perhaps it's time I
took my leave as well...
[Soldier 1] Move in! If
someone's trapped up there,
we need to
get him out!
[Soldier 2] Right!
He's gone...
Sensors!
I'm not reading
any life signs!
Move! Take us up,
now! It's collapsing!
So... this is
how it all ends.
No...
It's not
the end...
It's a beginning. A whole
new chapter is about to start.
The things we
have lost...
and the things we
have thrown away...
They lay forgotten
along the wayside.
The only trace
we've left behind...
Next time on Kiddy
Grade - "Look / Back"