Ta-daa!
[All]
Éclair!
That's
impossible!
The reception
chamber!
Just for that... I'll
wipe you all out at once!
Nice to see you back out
in the field, Chief...
Thanks, but... all I've
managed to do is get your
dog-fight bridge
destroyed...
As long as you and
Wirbelwind are still safe,
that's all
that matters.
Oh, Lummi... is
that really you?
Yes, it's me, Viola....
We're all here.
I'm sorry if we
made you worry.
What's
going on?
What happened to your body?
And how'd you come back?
You know I cried when I saw you
get turned into particles...
And there's
your answer.
My primary ability is not
"Puppet", but "Particle"...
In addition to the
flow of electrons-
In addition
to electrons,
she can control every
type of quantum particle.
It's a
G-Class ability.
I'd heard rumors that
such a power existed...
but until now, I never
believed they were true...
Cesario...
Unfortunately, it's
quite draining...
Are you
all right?
We've lost the starboard
flex-phaser...
Our total power output
is down, over 35%!
[Éclair] Viola? Cesario?
Viola! Cesario! Say something!
Let me know you're
still there!
[Alv] Another
G-Class ability?
Even if it
is true,
what good can it do in the
hands of a mere human?
It's nothing
compared to me now!
The fading light of a person's
life as they pass away...
At times
like these,
the sight of it is
enough to make me regret
that I have
this ability...
Tell me
about it...
We're really not
going to get involved?
The only way the galaxy
will ever know the truth
of what happened
here...
is if someone
lives to tell it.
This is hard
for him.
I know in his heart,
he's dying to help...
Sinistra...
Sinistra!
Dextera... Glad to hear
you're still in one piece...
Sinistra!
So then... does anyone have any
requests for their epitaph?
Stop this, Alv!
I didn't realize you were
still alive, Éclair...
Please, Alv... You and
I are so much alike.
Don't make the same
mistakes I made.
How dare you?!
What gives you the right to
compare yourself to me?!
I'll kill you for
even thinking it!
When I was human, all my
life consisted of was pain!
Suffering!
Humiliation!
I'll never go
back to that.
I'm going to take
the Nouvlesse.
I'm going to take the
miserable little planet
that spawned them.
And I'm going to
destroy them all!
It... may be hopeless
at this point.
No, it's not.
You'll find my daughter's weak
point is still her left side...
The blast this ship
reflected back at us that day
nearly
killed us.
My injuries were mainly to my
right side. Alv's to her left.
We survived, but we were
both left without feeling
in half
our body...
[Lumiere] So aboard
the Deucalion,
the reason she stopped
attacking at one point...
That's right. Even with all
the power of her new "body".
Her mind still remembers
the old body's scars...
Are you sure
you're up to this?
I think so...
Please... You're wasting
your time, human!
Why isn't
it working?
I'm sorry.
It seems I still haven't
recovered enough power...
Donner... We need
your help up here.
Éclair, I hope you
know what you're doing.
Lumiere needs power, and well,
that is my ability, right?
Here's
the plan:
we're going to use
Calliope's reception shield
to absorb my
"Power"...
Once that's done, Wirbelwind
will act as a converter
and send it back
to Lumiere...
Have you lost
your mind?
Listen,
Éclair...
You do understand what
could happen to you
if you actually go
through with this?
Unless you two have
a better idea,
this is our only
chance to stop her...
And besides...
It's me!
I'm the ES Member who
never dies, remember?
Good luck,
girls...
[Éclair] Okay! Donner's
ready, too! Let's go!
Their shields are
completely down!
A malfunction? Or are
they up to something?
Shields are cut. You have full
reception system power...
We won't survive
a direct attack.
[Éclair] It's all
right, Eclipse.
I have of faith in
your piloting skills.
I wish I could
say the same...
It doesn't matter what
you're planning...
Without your shields, how do
you expect to withstand this?!
Oh no... I can't
avoid that!
Your ship will
be vaporized!
And with it, the last reminder
that I was ever born human!
We won't make
it in time!
It's the C-Squared...
Oh, Tweedledee!
Hit the
eject!
Do it! Éclair!
Lumiere! Hurry!
What?!
Is it over?
Oh no...
not yet.
You want my left
arm so badly?
Fine! Then take
it. It's yours...
I'll just make
a new one.
Don't just
sit there!
Are you trying to give her a
chance to repair herself?!
We're right behind
you, Chief...
Can you
make it?
I better... you're pretty
useless without me.
Well, Éclair... You really
did it this time, huh?
I hope it was
worth it.
Thank you, Éclair.. I promise
we won't let you down...
Amazing, how quickly
time can pass...
Has it already
been so long
since we put the
Deucalion incident behind us?
Superintendent General.
What a pleasant surprise.
Even so. No matter
how much time goes by,
I doubt anyone in
the galaxy will
ever forget what
happened that day,
or in the
days since...
Éclair, no...
I'm sorry,
Éclair...
What are...
you doing?
I'm sorry, but...
I have to go.
But before I leave all
of you... a gift...
I've never used this power
on anyone other than Alv.
"Transmission"...
It's a reversal of her
"Absorb" abilities...
Éclair,
you're alive!
You
made it.
T- Ta-daa...
Oh,
Éclair!
Th-Thank you. Thank you
for saving... my mother.
You're
welcome...
I hope you
don't mind...
I just need to borrow a bit
of your energy, Wirbelwind...
With this...
I'll be able to stay with
my daughter until the end.
Mother?
Mother...
Mother!
Mother's
here now.
I promise I'll never
leave you again, Alv.
Look, son. You
see? That's Earth.
That's the place where all of
us humans first started out.
See how blue and
pretty it is?
Yott, is... is that really
it? That's the Earth?
Sure is... Just like the
pictures in my textbook.
Mother...
É- Éclair?
I'm right
here... son.
Will you
smile for me?
Time for a
shift change.
I thought I was about to
die of boredom in here...
Don't
complain.
I'm not sure you'd want any
excitement on this watch...
Never thought I'd live to see
the day when us "commoners"
would pass through the
gates of the G.U. Senate...
It definitely feels like
the start of a new era...
Sir Isaac! I just want to
thank you for everything
you and the
Rosenfeld Foundation
have done for all of us.
You're a great man, sir...
[Chairman] As its first
order of business,
this Council will
launch a full inquiry
into the details
surrounding
the construction
and intended use
of the
Atlas-class
intergalactic
spaceship Deucalion,
and into the
current whereabouts
of those most
directly responsible.
At the same time, a new
Global Union charter...
[Eclipse] Yes... so much
has happened since then...
[General]
Unfortunately,
my committee schedules
here have changed again,
so I'm afraid I may have to
put my visit off even further.
[Eclipse] I'm sorry
to hear that.
But I understand.
You're very busy.
[General] Yes, well, I
feel it's important
that someone
remain here
and represent the late G.O.T.T.
Secretary's final wishes.
After all, he had such great
visions for the future,
and for the
G.O.T.T...
I'm afraid I have to get
to another meeting...
But it's been a pleasure
talking to you, Chief.
You wanna live in the past
forever?! We've got work to do!
That's why your eyeballs are in
the front of your head, people!
So you'll keep
moving forward!
Yes,
ma'am!
His skin is
so soft!
Don't be shy... It's
okay to pick him up.
You just have
to be careful
until he can hold his
head up on his own.
Is that
your baby?
Oh, no. We're
just visiting.
He belongs to a friend of
ours. His name's "Chevalier".
Pleased to meet
you, Chevalier.
Is that your baby
girl? She's cute.
Oh, thank you...
Did you hear that? She
thinks you're cute, Éclair!
I know... Everyone
tried to tell us
it's an unusual
name for a girl...
But we really
wanted to name her
after this nice young
lady who helped us...
We like it just
fine, don't we?
It's such an exciting
time, isn't it?
To think that when
these children grow up,
the fact that there
were once people
like the Nouvlesse
in the galaxy
will just be
an old fable.
There you are. They said it
was time to come get you...
Uh, Ma'am? Do you ever
get, you know... nervous?
Most of the people
you'll talk to
are here for the
first time...
Chances are, they're pretty
nervous themselves...
Just relax and
put on a smile,
and you've got the biggest
part of the job covered...
Right. "Relax and
smile". Got it.
You know, when I
was in school,
my social studies class took
a tour of the G.O.T.T.,
and while we
were here
this group of cyborgs
attacked the lobby...
Really?
When it
happened,
it was one of the girls
behind the reception desk
who jumped out
and saved us.
That's the day I decided
to join the G.O.T.T.
Excuse me...
I wonder if you'd point
us in the direction
of the Branch
Management offices?
Yes, sir! I'd be glad to! Just
follow the main hall here...
All right, that's
it for your shift.
It's time for E-Shift...
Ready, Éclair?
I'm ready...
Let's go, Lumiere.
And so, even today...
I continue the fight...
But my biggest battle
is with myself...
With the memories that
still sometimes haunt me...
I won't let myself repeat the
mistakes of my past any more.
I'm going to
keep fighting...
so I can protect the
promise of the future.