My, you're up early
today, Éclair...
Wha- É- Éclair?
What's the
occasion?
Don't tell me you're
actually going into
work early for
a change...
No no- that would be
just too crazy...
Let me guess - you've
been up all night...
So, should I get you
your usual? Cafe latte?
Actually... I'll try some
tea... have the day off today.
In that case, how 'bout
a nice chamomile?
It'll help
you relax.
Here
you go.
Th- Thank you.
Hey, what are
you doing?
You shouldn't be taking
sedatives with tea!
You're right,
Caprice. I'm sorry.
Good morning, sir! I'll
be right with you, okay?
[Man] I'll
be here.
It's happening
again...!
[Eclipse] Now you can't
just go charging in there.
Try using some
restraint for once.
[Éclair] Oh, c'mon.
We'll be fine
as long as the
backup's in place.
[Lumiere] There. I've
bypassed the security system.
[Éclair 3] Good. Let's go.
Try to keep up, Eclipse!
Chief Eclipse?!
What is she-?
[Éclair 4] It's
been half a year
since I first looked upon your
dirty faces here, Recruits.
Six long and
difficult months.
Your ranks have
thinned since then.
The weaklings,
the wash-outs,
they are gone now.
Only the best remain.
And now, the time has come
for you to prove yourselves.
As you know, our National
Planetary Federation
has been thrust
into a state of war
Is that me?
with the Planetary
Republican Union.
The time has come
for you to earn your pay
as Federation Soldiers!
Training is done...
As of this moment,
you are each appointed to your
respective ranks and duties...
But before you go... I will
give you one final order:
Don't get killed...
That is all.
[Éclair 5] Let me out
of here! Let me out!
We can't let them do this!
If we don't stop them,
millions of people are
going to die! Millions!
Please!
Why...? Why?!
It's time...
Aren't you
going to fire?
No. I can't do this...
I won't do it...
Not of my own
free will.
Hands in the air...
Away from the console.
It's
no use.
[Éclair 6]
No...
It's been set to fire since
before we left Aineias.
Aineias? But that means the
G.O.T.T. was responsible for-
What is
this place?
[Éclair 7] Oh, you poor
thing, are you hungry?
Hehe! No, no!
We'll have to find some
milk for you somewhere else.
Please,
no more.
Are you
okay?
Were you having a bad
dream or something?
Sorry.
No, it's... it's my fault...
Sorry if I caused any trouble.
What's
that for?
That should be enough
to settle my tab.
What, are you saying you're
not coming back anymore?
Well, fine! Don't come
back! We don't need you!
Stupid.
Stupid to think normal
drugs would work on...
someone like me...
It's starting to
make sense now...
It's been a long
time, Éclair!
Yes, I'd recognize
you anywhere!
I don't remember who I was
before! This is who I am!
He was talking about my
Predecessors... Pre-holders-
the women who carried the
codename Éclair before me...
Predecessors...?
Pre-holders...?
Don't pretend to be so naive...
Those words mean nothing...
They don't
change the truth.
Stop! I already know
what you're going to say!
But it's not true...
...I'm not like you...
Oh, no?
You can't escape
your past.
You can't erase the
harm you've done.
No matter how many times
you die and are reborn,
you cannot change
who you are.
Predecessor..?
Do you really think that you
are somehow separate from me?
Look
closely...
You're the one with
blood on your hands.
Yes... This
is Éclair.
[Mercredi] Chief. Éclair
is here, as you requested.
Good. Send
her in.
Chief, um...
Éclair is still-
Thank you, Mercredi.
That will be all.
Of course.
Excuse me.
It's me.
Yes, I've been
expecting you.
This is Omega. The
operation is proceeding...
But we've hit a couple
unexpected snags...
The good news is,
we've secured eighty
percent of the scheduled data
and a sample of the E-4
material. The bad new is,
these crooks are being
aided by another ES unit.
From what
we've seen,
I don't think they work
for the Pelian government...
But they're no small-time
smuggling outfit, either.
My guess is, they've been
sent in by a third party.
We can deal
with them.
But we'll need to move our
schedule back a few counts.
Omega Out.
I need the two of you to
help extract Anoh and Eioh
from their
current situation...
Ordinarily, an
assignment of this nature
would go to Tweedledee
and Tweedledum.
But I'm afraid time
will not allow us
that option
in this case.
Yes, Chief.
Understood.
Right.
Understood, Chief.
I'm sorry, we're
in a bit of a hurry.
I think the usual
should suffice.
What's this?
If you're planning to
save someone's life,
take the
forty-five...
If you're planning to put
the barrel in your mouth,
the nine-millimeter
is more than enough.
[Lumiere] Planet Pelias is
located in this region,
on the edge of
the frontier.
It is technically a part
of the Global Union...
[Armblast] However, that hasn't
stopped the criminal element
from making
it their own.
Thanks to the lax
local government,
it's become something
of a Smuggler's Heaven.
Which I guess...
would make it hell for
anyone sent in to investigate.
[Lumiere] Units have
been put in place,
and are
preparing to move
against a number of smuggling
operations simultaneously.
But we'll be going in in
advance of the raid,
to make sure Anoh and Eioh
escape safely with their data.
I see, just a quick jaunt
through the gates of hell.
You must really be looking
forward to this, Éclair.
That's
right...
You know, I'm starting
to get the feeling
they don't like
us very much...
I don't think they found
your disguise very funny...
Yeah, but did you see
their sorry faces?
Even their ears were red!
I thought they were gonna-
What was
that?
I don't know...
It's as if...
We're caught in some
kind of force field.
It's the
ES Members.
Oh, great... These guys
again. Don't they ever quit?
Eat this!
Come on! Why aren't
the torpedoes
getting through
the shield?!
Phase interference. Looks like
they're one step ahead of us.
So, they've
got us...
[Lumiere] Well, with that
sort of negative attitude,
it's a wonder you've even
managed to make it this far.
It's nice to see
you two again.
Uh,
Lumiere?
Where's
Éclair?
She stepped outside
for a moment...
You're
kidding!
Punch it!
I can't
get a lock!
Yeah? So try again!
I can't shake it!
[Lumiere] It's a
biological homing array.
Standard countermeasures
won't work.
Well that just
figures, doesn't it!
Éclair!
Donner!
Is she-?
Don't do it!
Stop, Éclair!
Éclair! No!
Goodbye...
Éclair!
After all
I told you,
you're still trying
to escape your past...
Is that what
you think?
Where am I?
Grandma!
I hate you!
What's
the matter?
Grandma said she's
going to die...
But it's not
true, is it?
Maybe it's
her time...
When someone's
accomplished everything
they have to do
in this life...
They get called away
to the next one.
Your Grandma knows
that... Look at her,
sitting there. She
isn't sad, or afraid...
But I... I want her to
stay with me forever...
Yes... which is why you
should stay with her now.
We only have the
time we're given.
One day...
everyone dies.
Even you...
...and me...
Well... that's
quite a speech,
coming from someone
like you...
Considering what you've
done with your time...
You're right... I do
have blood on my hands.
I know I can't
change that.
But that doesn't mean
I can't change myself.
It doesn't mean I
have to be like you...
Right now, this life
is mine to live...
And I'll do what
I have to do...
until I've made
peace with my past,
like that woman
over there.
Go ahead. You can
try all you want...
But I am a part of you...
I will always be with you.
Yeah... keep watch
over me, okay?
So... Will you be needing
these any longer?
If not, I'll be happy to
throw them away for you.
Good morning!
Be right with you!
The usual?
We cry for
release...
But the moment we break
through our heavy chains,
the weight of
freedom falls upon us...
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: Set / Free