Éclair and
Lumiere, huh?
They've been expelled
from the ES?!
Control: this is
2-0-5-6-4-5-4,
G.O.T.T. Destroyer Priamus
and L.S.U. Canopus.
Priority code:
Emergency.
Requesting immediate departure
clearance on linear shaft one.
This is Control. G.O.T.T.
Priamus and L.S.U. Canopus,
you are clear
for launch.
I don't like
this, Commander.
I don't like it either,
Yusef. But it's our job.
We're not paid to
question orders.
We're paid to
follow them.
You have a son,
don't you?
Yes, sir... He'll
be five next month.
Well, if you love
him, take my advice.
Start teaching him now:
No matter what happens,
never work
for the G.O.T.T.
I'll do that. That is,
assuming I make it home alive.
Start the
countdown to warp
as soon as we've cleared
the shaft. Two minutes!
Yes, sir.
Registrations
deleted.
We'll be entering the Zero
Star System in five minutes.
Our best bet is to go to one
of their lesser-known colonies
and hide out there for a
little while. Let's see now.
Here we go. This one
seems pretty obscure.
LAV- Seven Eight.
Immigration:
eighty-seven percent.
Political stance:
neutral.
And it looks like it's pretty
easy to get permission to dock.
I feel like we're fugitives
behaving like this!
It can't be helped, Éclair.
After all, you are fugitives.
You're deleting
our registrations?
This mandate comes directly
from the Privy Council,
with full support
by the G.U. Senate.
I have no choice but
to give the order.
Is something wrong?
Well, let's see.
How 'bout the
way the Chief
just gave those purge
orders without question?
And what
of it?
It means there's absolutely
no one here we can turn to
to plead
our case!
No one.
Life is long, Éclair. So many
unexpected things can happen.
Especially for someone who's
lived as many lives as you.
How dare you. Do you think
I wanted it this way?
My ice cream has
lost its flavor.
You're thinking about
those two, aren't you?
About what we'll
have to do.
Tweedledum!
Right.
Sorry.
"Humans are greedy;
therefore, they are human."
It's an interesting
saying, don't you think?
Everyone dreams of
having eternal youth.
However, once they
finally obtain it,
they don't know what to do with
it, and say they don't want it.
What's your deal?
You make these observations
from a distance
and assume that's
the way everybody is.
I am an Auditor,
Éclair. That's my job.
So if you want to shoot
me, go right ahead.
But, you might wish you'd
saved your ammunition later.
Now that the orders
have officially cleared
the proper channels,
SO Members, either
Team 1 or Team 2,
will be dispatched
to pursue us.
And depending on how
badly they want us,
Internal Section 13 may
have already been deployed.
What? Section
Thirteen?
Yes. That's right.
The G.O.T.T.'s infamous
"purging unit".
We won't be able to stay
in one place for long.
Our best chance for
hiding is in open space.
Which means you might
want to consider
re-stocking
your supplies.
He's right. We're
going to need it.
They think they can get away
clean? Fine. I say let 'em try.
I feel sorry
for them.
Are you
kidding me?
I feel sorrier for whoever
has to go after 'em.
They're the
ones in danger.
Mmm... Where did you
find this tea?
The aroma is perfect.
It's delicious.
Is something
the matter?
Sorry. It's just, I
was hoping to share
that with Éclair
and Lumiere.
I was saving it
for their return.
I guess I'm having
a hard time
getting used to the idea that
they won't be coming back.
Broken brooms only
make more trash.
That's why we throw useless
tools away, Mercredi.
It's nothing
personal.
I might be the next
tool to be disposed of.
Check your equipment three
times and then check it again!
Any oversights could
cost you your life!
Yes, Sir!
All eyes here, men! The
Commander is ready to speak!
We will be
disembarking soon!
Our primary targets are the ES
Members Éclair and Lumiere!
However, our mission
in this case
will be limited to
containment only!
In other words, we
will be negotiating.
Commander, I
don't understand.
I thought our orders were
to purge the targets.
Have they
been changed?
My first responsibility
as commander
is the safety
of my men.
And I intend to bring you all
back to Aineias in one piece!
Any more
questions?
Good! Now, under
no circumstances
are you to engage
the targets
without a direct order from
me! Don't do anything rash!
Remember, the purpose
of negotiations
is to arrive at a
peaceful settlement!
Commander!?
I know a four-year-old boy
who wants to have his Dad
at his birthday
party next month.
Yusef, don't
disappoint him.
Yes, Sir. I'll take
that as an order.
All right! All units, battle
stations! ETA is five minutes!
Sir!
Guess that's it. Well,
at least for the food.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I just think you were a
little too harsh, that's all.
He's only doing his
job as an Auditor.
I'm sorry.
For not having
better tea.
We do have very good
wine if you'd like some.
Well, I think I'd better pass.
Thank you for offering though.
You're
welcome.
Funny. I don't think
I was too harsh at all.
He's always been
supportive of us, Éclair.
He's even helping us
right now as we speak.
We should
be grateful.
I guess I'm
just angry.
I am too, but we need to direct
our anger at the Nouvlesse.
Not at Armblast
or the Chief.
Yeah, yeah. That
all sounds good.
But forgive me if I can't
be as "logical" as you.
What? You've got to be
kidding me! Are you sure?
Oh my, gosh! Éclair and Lumiere
purged! Who would have thought?
This is
ridiculous.
They put enough garlic in
my pasta to kill a horse.
Approaching "C" Colony
LAV Seven Eight, Commander.
It's on the view
screen now.
The head office has already let
them know that we're coming.
Cut off the
identification beacon.
We'll go in stealth style
and moor at the northwest
general purpose docks
on the standard bar!
Yes, commander!
I mean, a purging order? I
don't get it! Why so extreme?
That's not all.
They've authorized us
to use the D-Command!
I take it you're
from Section 13 then.
That is correct.
I see. But then, why
are you telling us?
Clearly, you had the element
of surprise on your side.
According to
standard protocol,
we have to confirm
your intentions
before resorting
to force.
Intentions?
You still have the
option to surrender.
An inquiry session
would be held.
You two could
plead your case.
Yeah, right. I'd
rather not, thanks.
How about you?
If Section Thirteen has
already been deployed,
there's little hope of
winning an Inquiry Session.
Is that so?
I understand.
Good luck.
Why aren't they
attacking us?
They're probably waiting
for another team to arrive!
Huh?
Section Thirteen
is a smaller unit.
It was probably sent for
reconnaissance and containment!
One of the main units
must be on the way.
Either Team One
or Team Two!
They're mobilizing an
entire army just for us!
How flattering!
They mean business,
I'm afraid!
Ironic,
isn't it?
She erased all
of her memories.
And now she's making the
same choices all over again.
No matter how many times it's
played, a waltz is a waltz.
The rhythm doesn't
change its time.
Well, you'll be
glad to know
that I just finished
loading the suppli-
We're escaping!
Come on! Let's go!
Now how could
you be escaping?
Wouldn't that mean that
they're already here?
Yes! That's exactly what
it means! Hurry, Please!
Release them!
Restraining Mortars
to the front!
Fire!
All units
take aim!
This is Commander
Lyall of S.O. Team 2!
As of 16:43, on orders
from the head office,
we have taken measures
to restrict your movement!
Resisting will put us
all in grave danger.
I ask that
you surrender.
And what if
we refuse?
Then I'll ask you a second
time. Please surrender.
No, we won't.
Activate it!
Yes, Sir.
You heard
him! Activate!
Oh, no.
As you can see, those are not
ordinary restraining wires!
The joints in the
middle of the wires
have been rigged
with explosives!
The slightest movement
from your ship
will cause the
joints to pull apart
and the explosives
will be detonated!
If that happens, more
than half of this colony
will be destroyed
in the blast!
More than half? That means all
of you people will die, too!
Yes! Precisely! That's why
we're asking you to surrender!
Most of us have
wives and children
and we'd like to make it
home to them alive!
This'll be our last
sit-down meal for a while.
Things're about
to get hectic.
Do you think that Éclair
will beg for her life, Alv?
No way.
So if we refuse
to give up,
all of your men are
going to die right now?
That is
correct!
You're treating
them like hostages.
What about you? Don't you
have a hostage as well?
When you
ran away,
you took an agent
of the Global Union
with you against
his will.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
made a distress call.
What? How
could you?
That's how they
found us so quickly.
You told them
where we were!
"Humans are greedy;
therefore, they are human."
You'd do well to
remember that.
Go ahead and shoot me
if you want, Éclair.
Although, I still
think you'd wish
you'd saved your
ammunition for later.
I owe you
one, Commander.
We're not out of
trouble yet, Sir.
I'll ask one more time:
Please, surrender.
So you can take us
back to the G.O.T.T.?
No thanks,
Commander.
I think we'd rather take our
chances out here with you.
Fair enough.
But I'm afraid you'll
leave me no choice
but to execute
the D-Command.
The D-Command! I might
be able to survive it.
But what
about Éclair?
Please
surrender!
That's not an
option! Forget it!
The restraint wires have
been neutralized, Commander!
Yusef, execute
the D-Command!
That's not what
we agreed upon!
I don't have a choice.
The negotiations failed.
Commander.
Yusef! I gave you
a direct order!
As you wish, Sir!
All right, men.
Prepare to activate
the D-Command!
Ignition on standby.
Awaiting your numbers, Sir!
Don't do it!
Two! Three! Sixty-two!
Zero! Six! Seven! Nine!
Pass code confirmed,
Commander! Executing D-Command!
The D-Command is
transmitting a signal
to the nano-machines
inside their bodies,
forcing them to reproduce
at an accelerated rate.
L-L-Lumiere...
Éclair...
The resulting
increase in mass
puts enormous
pressure on the body.
Enough to crush their
internal organs.
I'm well aware of
that, Commander.
So why did you
execute the command?
The Head Office said that
these two are fugitives!
If you have any evidence
to the contrary,
I demand to hear it right
now. I'm a soldier!
I don't give the orders!
I carry them out!
And if I don't follow
the purging protocol,
these two could send my
entire team home in body bags!
An anti-mist vaccine...
I have to make them
work as antibodies.
Éclair
Oh no... It's too late...
Hold it! That's
far enough!
What are
you doing?!
These girls have lived
very long lives, Commander.
But in many ways
they are still young. I
won't let you destroy
what future they
have left.
Not like this.
You're one of them,
aren't you, Auditor?
You're an
ES Member!
Lumiere, I've stopped time
within her for a little while.
You can try making
the antibody now.
But I'm afraid that this will
cause her memories to awaken.
All of her
memories, Lumiere.
It's better than letting
her die, isn't it?
Everyone dreams of
having eternal youth.
The problem is how
one comes to live
with it once
they have it.
Éclair, I'm giving you
the antibodies now.
[Armblast] "Humans are greedy;
therefore, they are human."
In other words, you cannot
fight your own nature.
[Éclair] What
do you mean?
It's simple. You
have to learn to accept
things the
way they are.
Your past, the
choices you've made,
and the future laid
out before you.
That doesn't sound
so simple to me.
If I know you,
you'll do just fine.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
have helped you.
Then, all
this time?
They say that to
deceive your enemies,
you have to begin
with your friends,
don't they?
Thank you.
Yes. But now, sad
as I am to say it,
I think it's best if I didn't
accompany you from here.
After all, I am
still an auditor.
I'm sorry. I've said so
many terrible things to you.
Don't worry. I know
you didn't mean it.
Sir! This power! It's
equivalent to a G-Class!
How can he be
that strong?!
It's not
coming from him!
This is beyond the
scope of our mission!
It seems that they've
both run away!
17:49: Both
targets lost.
Let's go,
men! Move out!
Good luck, girls.
We move through
life blindly,
guided only by
the hand of fate.
But fate is not always kind.
The open hand can also strike.
Next time on Kiddy Grade:
"Conflict / Destiny"