Hey. Relax.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
for flying B0L flight 9216,
non-stop to
Planet Satyros.
We are currently
approaching the orbital rim,
and will be passing through the
deceleration field momentarily.
Please remain seated until we
have completed our descent.
Look, we made it this far.
Nothing is going to happen, ok?
This is unit three
five, reporting in.
Initial check is
negative, over.
Yes, I'm
afraid so.
I don't know how
but they managed
to get the ratification
draft. We failed.
It just doesn't
make any sense.
Clear.
So all the passengers
are clean, huh?
It certainly
appears that way,
and it's exactly the
same M.O. as before.
Amazing.
How can someone steal something
in a shuttle full of passengers
and then just walk
past our screening?
I don't know. But this
is the eighteenth case.
Nineteenth. We've got
to do something fast.
We can't
do that.
What?
Why not?
Satyros is a
planet of commerce.
And this spaceport
is a major hub
for shipping and transit
routes from all over the galaxy.
You don't seem to realize
how many spacecraft
arrive here
in one minute,
much less an
entire day.
There's no way
we could stop--
Excuse me.
We're not asking you that
you stop the flights,
just check them.
A simple pre-flight screening
should be enough to-
What's the
difference?
The G.O.T.T. will
just have to realize
we're already doing
everything we can.
Eh...
but uh...
It's alright.
The G.O.T.T. does realize that,
which is why they've sent us.
We've collected data from
every planet, state, business
and vessel that
uses this spaceport,
which should provide
some useful clues
as to how these robberies
are perpetrated.
Now it's a simple
matter of transporting
a hard copy of this
data to Aineias,
where it can be
properly analyzed
at G.O.T.T.
headquarters.
Uhhh, you mean you're
G.O.T.T. agents?
E.S.
members!
That's correct.
ES Member Dextera.
And Sinistra,
at your service.
Well, I guess
that settles it.
We don't have anything
to worry about now,
not with these
two on the case!
But thank you
for all your help.
Control tower,
this is UAS 0003.
Pre-flight systems
check is complete.
Engines prepped and
ready for launch.
Requesting final
clearance for departure.
UAS 0003, you have
been cleared for take-off.
Please proceed to
linear shaft number six.
So, those are
the E.S. Members?
Yes, but there's no
way we can stop them.
If the G.O.T.T.
analyzes that data,
they'll have no problem tracing
the robberies back to us.
Let them go.
They're just decoys.
Our operatives
discovered the data
is actually being carried
on a commercial flight.
That'll make things easier.
This might just work.
Wait! We're going to steal
from G.O.T.T. agents now?
Don't worry. These are just
two low-level members.
Getting the jump on the
G.O.T.T. would be remarkable.
Ok. Then it's all
settled. Let's go.
Would you hurry? We have
to check in! Miss Montague!
Hello,
Miss Montague?
Éclair
Montague! Hey!
Oh, sorry about
that Miss Padushka!
I need you
to focus.
Our mission is
very important.
You see, the ES Members
are just a decoy.
We are the ones
carrying the data.
I've got it
inside this case.
Oh, I get it! That's
a perfect plan!
Try not to
tell everyone!
Look, I know
up until now
you've been just
a receptionist,
but they've given you
a big responsibility.
So... so
straighten up!
Okay. Do you feel all
right, Miss Padushka?
What? Well... well
of course I'm all right!
I mean, I have been
an S.O. Member
for over seven
years now, you know!
And besides that,
Miss Montague...
It's, um
Mrs. Padushka.
Really? Oh, that's wonderful!
And he's very handsome!
My husband happens
to be commander
of C-force's
third detachment.
And yes, he
is very handsome.
But enough of this,
Miss Montague.
We've got to
check in. Come on!
Yes Miss, uh...
Ms. Padushka!
Huh?
Well, Mrs. just sounds so
old, and you're so young.
It doesn't matter what you
call me. Let's just check in.
She's pretty high strung
for an "S.O. Member."
Ok, just need
to check your bag.
Oh, no. Please this
must be carry-on!
All right, in that case I just
need you to fill out a form.
So, if you wouldn't mind
getting up off the floor.
Yes,
of course!
Sorry about
this.
You see, there's been a
rash of burglaries lately.
We can't be
too careful.
Um, right.
Oh, please!
I'm in a hurry!
Where can I find
flight BNL 3522?
You're just
in time.
They're making the final
boarding call now.
Go around the corner
and down to Gate 82 A.
Thank you,
sir.
The...
the case!
Ms. Padushka.
Miss Montague! Oh, I've
made a terrible mistake!
[Éclair] It's called
"distract and snatch."
One person gets
your attention
while the other
steals your stuff.
It's an old con
but it still works.
Thank you so much,
Miss Montague!
Say, would it be ok
if you called me Éclair?
It just isn't
so formal.
Thank you
then, Éclair.
Your baggage
request, ma'am.
Oh right.
Sorry.
Excuse me sir, I
have something, too.
I see. You'll be carrying
cargo as well, huh?
Yes sir.
That's right.
I'll get
the form.
[Pilot] Control tower, this is
BOL 3600, non-stop to Aineias.
All systems are
green for launch.
Now requesting final
departure clearance.
Ma'am, could I
stow your luggage?
What? Oh no,
I can't!
I keep all my travel
sickness medication in here!
[Lumiere] Looks like
they're finally taking off.
Don't you think that we
should be following them?
Are you that concerned?
You follow her then.
But if you'll excuse me,
I have my own work to do.
You're not worried about
Éclair? That seems a bit cold.
I find it's best not
to get too attached.
Because you're
afraid of losing her?
Oh, I think
that's it.
[Flight-Attendant]
Good morning passengers.
We have now entered
the orbital rim.
And in just 23 minutes we'll
be arriving at the warp-gate.
[Flight-Attendant] The captain
has asked that you please
remain in your
seats at this time,
with your seatbelts
securely fastened.
Thank you for chosing
BOL Space Shuttles.
Now please, sit back and
enjoy the rest of your flight.
Are we
there?
We just left!
Please be still!
Thank goodness everything
went off without a hitch.
Look I'm
sweating here!
Well, you do seem
a little tense.
Oh, I guess I am tense.
I must be getting old.
But Ms. Padushka!
You're very young.
It's ok.
Y'know, the truth is this
is the first big job
entrusted to me
in seven years.
And it's also
the last one.
Why's that?
I told Gluck,
Gluck's my husband,
I told him that's what
I wanted and he agrees.
After this I'm
going to resign.
GOTT will be a
thing of my past.
Why are
you leaving?
Well,
congratulations!
Thank you. You can see
why I want this mission
to succeed
without inci--
What's
that?
My nano-mist?
Oh! It's some
kind of gas.
Sleeping gas from
the air vents!
Get ready. Obviously they
weren't fooled by the decoys.
S-Stand
back, Éclair!
Y-You are obviously
the criminals
who have been victimizing
this spaceport.
Well, I was sent here to
end your cycle of crime.
You will not take
what is in this case!
Oh,
boy.
Hehe...
Right.
Get up!
Oh uh, Nano-mist
shield, expand!
St-Stay where you are!
Don't come any closer!
Uh, retreat!
Now! S-Surrender and put
your hands in the air!
It's ok now, Ms. Padushka. You
must have scared them all away.
Huh? What? How...
How'd I do that?
I guess they couldn't get
through your shield. Good job!
Thank goodness! I have no
idea what I would've done
if they had
gotten through.
Someone's still
flying the ship.
The gas should've
affected them too,
unless they were
prepared to neutralize it.
You think the
pilot's in on it?
Looks
that way.
Wait!
So they probably
weren't expecting us
to neutralize the gas
with our nanomists!
Uh...
okay.
--And so that means we have
the element of surprise!
--Oh, no.
Come on!
Uh, yes,
Ms. Padushka!
Hold it!
Very
nice.
Y'know, this is the first
time I've used this thing.
Works well
doesn't it?
Ms. Padushka,
listen!
You're gonna have
to take the controls!
[Ms. Padushka] Mayday!
Mayday! This BOL 3600!
We have been attacked
by serial robbers!
We managed to
frighten them off,
but unfortunately the
pilot was in on it
and had to
be detained.
He and the co-pilot both
are currently unconscious!
There's no one left to
fly this ship now but me,
and I'm just one
of the passengers!
Mayday! Mayday!
Come in! Mayday!
Éclair! They're
not responding!
What?
Where'd she go?
And at a time
like this!
TA-DAH!
Wait a sec. Their ship!
It's an Orbital Police Cruiser!
You mean they're
the robbers?
Éclair!
Come in!
Ms. Padushka?
Just stay where
you are! Hang on!
Oh, no!
Ms. Padushka,
good job!
Oh great,
more troops.
What's this? Controls
aren't responding!
[Commander] They
know who we are!
We've got no choice
but to eliminate them.
Make sure it seems
like an accident!
Looks like these guys
are playing for keeps.
All right then, if that's
the way they want it.
Okay, Donnerschlag.
This is your cue!
Please straighten
out! Come on!
What now?
Right! Let's show
'em how it's done!
It works!
[Éclair]
Round two!
Little brat!
Now I've
got you!
Oh no!
Donner,
hang on!
C'mon!
Where is it?
Let's see
you dodge this.
Oh, there.
Die!
What is that?
[Sinistra] Sorry
we're a little late.
[Dextera] Did we
miss the party?
[Éclair] Oh no, you
guys are right on time!
Well, that's
a relief.
[Sinistra] You'll
be happy to know
that their base is being
raided right about now.
[Sinistra] As it turns
out the criminals
were just a small faction
of the police department.
They were very clever
in the way they operated.
In addition to
the sleeping gas,
they manipulated acceleration
and deceleration velocities
to give themselves
more time to work,
not to mention the pay-offs
they made to the pilots.
There were
actually a few cases
where the victims
themselves were in on it,
cases of insurance
fraud, and the like.
But, all of this isn't
really important right now.
The important thing is,
they've been stopped.
Thank you
very much.
If the two of you hadn't
arrived when you did,
I don't know what would
have become of us.
No, we should
thank you.
If you hadn't been
so conspicuous
drawing them to
the shuttle,
we might not have
tracked down their base.
You mean to tell me
that the whole time
we were risking
our lives,
we were
the decoys?
It's called
"distract and snatch."
It's an old technique,
but effective.
Oh, boy. I think I'm
gonna pass out now.
Hey, Ms. Padushka!
Ms. Padushka!
Thank you everyone! And
thank you especially, Chief!
We're the ones
who are grateful!
You cracked a very big case
and on your last assignment!
Unbelievable!
Remember you are always welcome
back here, Mrs. Padushka!
Thank you, sir. Thank
you all, very much!
You know, Éclair,
without your help
I would not have
ever succeeded.
Thank you!
But a girl your age
shouldn't be so reckless.
How are you ever
going to find a husband?
A lady should be more
elegant. You know?
[Ms. Padushka] Still,
you're pretty sharp.
Keep it up, and you might
just be an ES Member someday.
Well, goodbye!
The day of reckoning.
Barriers that must be overcome
stand squarely in the way.
Do you leap over them?
Do you avoid them?
Or do you break them down?
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: "Trial / Child"