We scrap in order
to rebuild.
We destroy, so that we may
create anew from the rubble.
Throughout
human history,
the cycle has repeated
itself time and again.
As a race, we've learned
to rebuild entire worlds...
But we still can't heal
our hearts and souls.
Not by ourselves... That's
why we have each other.
Then there's hope. After
all, you still have me.
And don't forget, you
will always have me.
You're
unbelievable...
Even after everything
that's happened,
you think you're just
going to settle right back
into the same
old routine?
How quickly
you forget...
I haven't
forgotten.
So you say,
at least...
You'll keep the
memories that suit you.
But as always, you'll
lock the rest away,
along with the truth
of who you really are.
I'm done trying
to escape my past.
I'm tired
of running.
What's the point? No
matter how hard I try,
I always end up back
at the same place.
So from now on, I'll just
save myself the effort.
That is what you wanted me
to say? Isn't that right?
Yeah... I guess you
finally understand.
So this is the last
I'll be seeing of you.
Now that you've
decided to take back
all of your memories
and abilities,
I'll become more and more
integrated within you...
until, finally,
I fade away.
No, you won't disappear
completely...
We'll both go on
living... but together.
Excuse me...
I'm trying to find the Fair
Trade Offices, Section 3.
Oh, sure! You'll need to take
the first hallway on your left.
Fair Trade, Section 3 is
located in the west wing
of the main
building...
Great idea, Ricki. It's a
perfect day for a picnic.
Isn't it
though?
Hey! This stuff's
actually pretty good today!
Oh, what'd you get,
Bonita? I wanna try a bite...
Don't you have enough
on your own plate?
There, see?
No harm done.
I haven't put the
jam on it yet, so...
it's still
all right.
A lady should be
more elegant.
Well... At least it's good to
know Éclair is still Éclair...
I was beginning to
get a little worried,
what with the
new look and all.
So'd you get the plastic
surgery done for an assignment?
It's not like
you needed it.
I'm jealous! I wish
I were an ES Member!
Cut it out, Ricki!
I'm ticklish!
And wait... if I
didn't know better,
I'd say you got 'em to add
a little bit extra up top.
No, that's not how it- Well...
maybe just a little bit.
That's a clear abuse
of your authority!
I've got half a mind to
blow the whistle on you.
Even after all
the trouble,
she's still the
same old Ricki...
Ricky, this
is a bad idea!
Oh, come on. You
look great! Éclair?
Uh-huh?!
Éclair, you look
beautiful! I mean it!
On second thought,
the "same old Ricki"
could mean trouble for me.
But...
then...
With so many of the
same faces around,
even I almost have a hard time
keeping them all straight.
That's for
sure...
We'll be fine as long as
the backup's in place.
Don't get
killed.
It's been set to fire since
before we left Aineias.
No, you won't disappear
completely...
We'll both go on
living... but together.
Again? Really, Éclair...
That one does
have jam on it...
So what are you
going to do now?
Is it okay for pigeons
to eat that stuff?
They look like
they're enjoying it.
I still haven't completely
adjusted to my new body.
I guess
for now,
that's a bigger problem
than my memories.
Right then,
back to work!
Yeah, I'm sure
Selena and them
are probably wondering
where we are by now.
Bye, guys! Don't
work too hard!
So, should we go take
these dishes ba-?
Are you feeling all
right, Lumiere?
You hardly even
touched your lunch.
I- It's nothing...
I'm fine...
Lumiere!
Lumiere...?
Lumiere...? Lumiere!
Lumiere!
I'm afraid there's nothing
more we can do for her.
Eclipse...?
She's okay...
Isn't she?
She's okay,
right?!
Éclair...
Just tell me my partner's
going to be all right!
I'm sorry... But as an ES
Member, you should understand.
She's not used to
her new body, right?
No... It's
more than that.
In Lumiere's case, her
ability puts her in contact
with a vast amount
of network data...
And combined with the
memories of her past...
It's too much information for
her to process all at once.
But she's always been able
to handle it before...
This shouldn't
be happening.
You're supposed to
be the one in charge
of encoding
ES Members!
Why can't you
do something?!
I wish I could. But even
with my Quandt abilities...
I can't heal
her soul.
I'm sorry I
snapped at you.
It's alright.
Good bye, Chief...
And good riddance.
[Eclipse] During "Encoding",
we can regenerate the body...
assign
abilities...
but even with all
our technology,
some things are still
out of our hands.
Actually, the most
important thing...
Lumiere...
We've done everything
we know to do for her...
And the G.O.T.T.'s
Quantum Physiology Unit
is the best
in the field.
From this point on, everything
depends on Lumiere herself.
All we can do is
watch... and hope.
Lumiere...
How is it going? The
optimization process...
Tweedledee...
You've always had such
amazing abilities...
It saddens
me greatly,
that you should have to be
punished for it like this.
Be strong,
Lumiere...
I hope you and I will
have another chance
to play in the
virtual sphere...
I'm sorry there isn't
something more we can do.
But if it's
any help,
know that our thoughts
are with her... and you.
You beat us pretty good
last time we met...
I'm willing to let
that go for now,
but as soon as your
partner recovers...
I think my sister and I
are ready for the rematch.
Tweedledum...
No, it's all right.
I hope someday...
we can take you
up on that.
Sister...
Yes, I know.
It looks like we aren't the
only ones who are worried...
La Muse... I'm sure I have no
right to ask this of you...
But if there's anything you
can do to save Lumiere...
then, please...
Oh, hello,
Chief...
Just "Eclipse",
please...
I'm sorry I couldn't come
to check on you in person.
How is she doing
this morning?
It's been over a week,
and still no change.
What happens if the
optimization isn't working?
Go on, say
it, Eclipse.
She will die. And it will
be a slow, painful death.
Éclair... A lady should
really be more elegant.
And there's...
nothing we can do.
I'm sorry...
La Muse!
Come out!
I know you're
there...
Lumiere...
La Muse... or I guess I
should say "Wirbelwind"...
You have to know what condition
Lumiere is in right now...
Her memories are too much
for her new body to handle.
If my case was
bad... hers is worse.
She's in so
much pain...
And if this optimization
doesn't work, it...
it's going
to kill her!
And there's nothing I can
do! I'm a G-Class ES Member.
I'm a G-Class ES Member,
and I'm so helpless!
It doesn't matter how fast I
can move, or how strong I am...
I took back all of my
powers and memories...
but if I can't
save her...
And that's why... I
need your help now.
You're Lumiere's terminal.
You're an extension of her!
You know her mind better than
anyone, even better than I do!
So if there's anyone
who can save her...
Come back,
Wirbelwind!
I'm using a
9 millimeter.
That means I've still
got thirteen shots left.
I'm sorry, but... when
it comes down to it,
Lumiere's a lot more
important to me than you are.
[Young Lumiere]
Who are you?
Éclair...
Just "Éclair".
"Éclair"... That's
an unusual name.
So I've
heard...
Another whole
city, wiped out...
If there's
one thing
Earthlings have always
been good at, it's war.
Maybe so... But
this isn't Earth!
So you're the Quandt we've
been hearing about...
I didn't really expect
you to be a woman.
I don't like this,
Éclair. Watch out!
[Buyer] What the-? She's
some kind of monster!
I'm the monster? I'm not the
one shooting at little kids!
Don't worry, you're
in good hands.
You sacrificed
yourself to save me?
But the Three Laws
of Robotics...
they're just
a program!
I think it's time we gave
you a name. Let's see now...
How does
"Wirbelwind" sound?
It's only
fitting
you should have the most
elegant body in the galaxy...
Right,
Wirbelwind?
Such a detestable
assignment...
That's it. It's time...
Aren't you going to fire?
No. I can't do this...
Not of my own free will.
I knew that you
would say that...
I only wish I
could do the same.
Hands in the air...
Away from the console.
It's no use.
No...
I can never forgive
myself for this...
It's been set to fire since
before we left Aineias.
No... I mustn't let myself cry.
For Éclair's sake... and mine.
I have to lock
this inside.
[Lumiere]
That's not true...
Where am I?
You've done enough.
You don't have to carry these
painful memories any longer.
Open your eyes... And
leave the past behind.
You still have the
entire future to face.
The entire
future...?
What's
happening?!
You're
awake!
Éclair...
I remember...
the optimization.
This... This
is... This is...!
Oh, yeah, that...
Wirbelwind gave it to me.
I hope you don't mind, I had to
give it to you mouth-to-mouth.
[Lumiere] You wasted
the entire bottle!
Why, Wirbelwind?! How could
you?! Answer me, Wirbelwind!
Hey, what's
the matter?
I- I'm not sure...
My power... It
seems to be gone.
There are some doors
that, once opened,
can never be
closed again.
And sometimes, the
fate of mankind
hangs on the turn
of a single key.
Next time, on Kiddy
Grade: "Nouvlesse/Ark"