The Nouvlesse
have ignored
our human rights
for too long!
Go back
to Earth!
We will not allow this
tyrannical oppression
to continue!
We are not slaves!
How I detest
this noise.
Yes. It sounds
like they've managed
to acquire a
few megaphones.
Uh, please excuse me, sir.
Continuing with my report-
Enough! Let's hear
these supposed
"radical measures"
you've concocted.
Of course. As I was saying,
this last rash of sabotage
could technically be
considered economic terrorism.
And...?
And.. therefore,
we could file suit
with the Galactic Organization
of Trade and Tariffs.
Very well. But understand,
I want this handled quietly.
Ah... So they do actually
have troubles in paradise.
Then, this is a suit filed
by the Aurean government?
In a sense. But to
be more precise,
it comes from the
administrative offices.
Aure does not have an
independent government.
The planet is privately
owned by the Nouvlesse.
Th- The
whole planet?
Authentication complete.
G.O.T.T. cruiser La Muse,
approach on course A-3-0-7
for entry inspection.
Code 3-3-5-7-2-1-2. Over.
They call that an entry
inspection? It's a violation!
And on top of
everything else,
they say we can't bring La
Muse or Donnerschlag?!
Who do they
think they are?!
There's no sense in
kicking the wall.
Besides, was it
really so bad?
I know I for one
didn't mind seeing you
without your
clothes on.
You'll never
learn, will you?
I'm an auditor. It's
my duty to observe.
Oh... It's so blue!
Even bluer than Aineias!
It's just like all
the pictures of Earth.
As it was intended,
I'm sure.
"Aure" is an ancient
word meaning "garden".
That's exactly what this planet
has become. A beautiful garden,
created in the image
of an ideal Earth.
It's
incredible!
So does this mean you're
not angry anymore?
Just smell that air.
All those flowers!
We're going
in now.
Right! Coming!
Welcome to Aure, the
'Secret Flower Garden'.
I am Assistant
Director Mister.
I hope you were
not put off
by the stringency of
our entry inspection...
Uh... No.
Spoken like a
true ES Member.
Always elegant,
even under pressure.
Thank you, sir.
As you know, Aure
prides itself
on its long history
as a vacation planet.
Is that right?
Unlike other planets, every
aspect of our environment -
gravity, atmosphere,
vegetation-
has been recreated here
exactly as it is on Earth.
The only difference,
of course,
being that we've removed
the season of winter.
But, why? I mean, it must
take constant terraforming
to maintain
this place.
I'd think
that obvious.
We Nouvlesse are
very particular
when it comes
to our comfort.
Ordinarily, the
costs involved
in terraforming
an "ideal planet"
like this one
are prohibitive.
Therefore, humans
have been forced to
adapt themselves to a wide
variety of environments.
But the Nouvlesse
are an exception.
They refuse
to adapt,
in order to maintain their
"purity" as Earthlings.
Yeah, yeah. I know that much.
They're just... so stuck up.
They're the
Nouvlesse.
They're arrogant because
they can afford to be.
We're coming up on the
manufacturing facility now.
Quiet, isn't it? Not
even half the laborers
have bothered to
report to work.
It's the same
everywhere...
Aure's jewelry is the
finest in the galaxy,
but with these recent trends
of sabotage and worker unrest
taking hold
over the planet,
our production has virtually
been ground to a halt.
I don't mean to interfere with
your internal affairs but,
have you
considered listening
to what the citizens
have to say?
But the opinion of the
citizens are of no-
But they are not citizens.
They are laborers.
Right, I
just meant...
For generations, these
laborers have been bound to us
under a perpetual lifetime
employment contract.
In other words,
we own them.
Let's hurry along. We haven't
even been through half
the scheduled
inspection yet.
So, if you "own" these
laborers, are they cyborgs?
Of course not.
I'm proud to say
there isn't a single
cyborg on all of Aure.
We do not use
machines or androids.
All of our goods are
luxuriously handcrafted.
This may not be the most
efficient means of manufacture,
but we find it adds
to the aesthetic.
Well, it seems we've
stumbled onto a demonstration.
Build schools!
Give us the
freedom to relocate!
Don't you allow them to leave
the planet for any reason?
Heavens, no.
We can't have the laborers
thinking they can
shirk their contractual
obligation-
Speaking of which,
I wonder if you'd mind
doing a little job for me.
Assistant Director, what
is it you want me to do?
I'd like you to stop this
demonstration, all by yourself.
You what?!
The military police will be
standing by to assist you.
But I thought we might
first give them the chance
to see a G.O.T.T.
ES Member in action.
But...
Don't
hold back.
Éclair you to make a firm
example of these protesters.
And if I won't, the
military police will.
Each planet has its own set
of rules and regulations.
And regardless of whether
or not we agree with them,
that's the way things are
throughout the galaxy.
We can't
change it.
Yeah, but... who do these
Nouvlesse think they are?
Have you forgotten the
reason why we're here?
We are to do
whatever's necessary
to help the Aurean
administration
restore normal
economic activities.
Those were the Chief's exact
orders. She was very specific.
And an ES Member can't
disobey a direct order
from the Chief
of the G.O.T.T.
Is that what
you're saying?
Yes,
that's right.
Hey, why did
everybody stop?
Who is that?!
Doesn't look like
the military police.
One'a the
administrators dogs.
Whoever she is, she can't stop
all of us! Let's keep moving!
An ES Member can't
disobey a direct order
from the Chief
of the G.O.T.T.
Stop! I can't let
you go any farther!
Don't stop! Push
your way through!
Please, listen to
me! Turn around!
Put your
backs into it!
Go back! Please,
don't make me do this-
She's not human! She's
a cyborg or somethin'!
Some kinda'
machine!
She's a puppet
for the Nouvlesse!
Please!
Stop!
I beg you.
Go back.
Well. It would seem
your reputation
for "elegance
under pressure"
has been greatly
exaggerated.
I will be waiting at the
Administrative Offices.
A hotel room has been
arranged for you.
Once you've cleaned off
the filth, come see me.
About face!
It's not true, what he said.
You've never been more elegant.
Hi there! Would you
like some flowers?
Excuse us,
please.
We are here as guests
of the administrati-
No. It's okay. I can clean up
in the fountain at the park.
Éclair!
Are you two
all right?
Kanoe!
Did you
see that?!
So, anyway, thanks
for saving my sister.
You're welcome. But I'm
sorry I was so dirty.
I guess I made a mess
of us both, didn't I?
Don't worry
about it.
She's always rollin'
around in the dirt anyway.
Am not!
Sorry I thought you
were scary before.
You're really
pretty, Éclair!
Thank you!
See?
Pretty!
She's
beautiful.
Ah, so you've been looking
after Yott and Kanoe, eh?
Here. It's
nothing fancy,
but eat as much as you
want. On the house.
Come on, Aunt Etta,
don't you have something
better we can
give her?
What's that supposed to mean?
I know it may not be gourmet,
but I've never heard
anyone complain.
Oh, really? So
all these years,
I guess I just haven't been
complainin' loud enough.
And if you start
now, Garrett,
you're gonna be eating
that hat instead!
Hey, Bateau.
Come on in.
It's her! She's the one who
broke up our demonstration!
One of the
administrators' dogs!?
A spy!?
Who brought
them here?
She's one
of them?
If the administrators have
discovered our plan, then...
I don't feed dogs
at my table.
It's not true, is it Éclair?
I mean, you're not really a...
I was at the demonstration
earlier today.
I work for
the G.O.T.T.
But, I didn't come
here as a spy-
Go away!
Please, just... get
out. Get out now.
Some turnout
tonight.
It's a reception for
those G.O.T.T. pigs.
The administrators
wanna show 'em off.
Really?
Sounds serious.
Hmph. What difference can
a couple people make?
Those are the ES Members? They
look like ordinary girls to me.
Oh, but appearances
are deceiving.
There's more to them
than meets the eye.
Did you hear?
One of them supposedly
overwhelmed
an entire crowd
of demonstrators!
You mean children,
making play at revolution!
In any case, I'll just be glad
when all of these troubles
are safely
behind us.
What I wouldn't have given, for
just a spoonful of that soup.
Is it all
happening again?
Men! Are
we cattle?
No!
Men! Are
we machines?
No!
No. We are humans, all of us!
Humans, born to live our lives,
to work out our days, and to
raise our children in peace!
That's right! We're not gonna
be toys for the Nouvlesse!
Our ancestors, dying of
thirst, gasping for air,
living in
desperate poverty,
turned to the
Nouvlesse for help.
Yeah! They signed
away our freedom!
Our ancestors' lives were
saved by that contract.
And their children, and
their children's children!
For this, we owe
the Nouvlesse
our deepest gratitude and
respect. But nothing more.
We are not cattle!
We are not machines!
We are humans!
Just as they are!
And after 300 years of slavery,
our debt to them has been paid!
We will no longer
be deprived!
Of the fruits of our hard
labor! Of our dignity!
Or of our freedom!
And to the administrators
and their puppets,
we will cry
out as one!
There she is, Yott.
Just like I told you.
Laborers! I order
you to disperse!
What you are doing constitutes
a serious breach of contract.
What you're doing constitutes a
serious breach of human rights!
If you refuse to
comply peacefully,
I have been
authorized to use any
and all means of
force at my disposal.
In other words, if they don't
leave, he's going to kill them.
We will not be intimidated
by your threats!
Even if we
die here,
our cause
will live on!
The Nouvlesse will one day
be expelled from Aure!
You have
been warned.
They
shot them!
Stop!
You have no right
to do this!
I don't care what
your contract says!
They're humans!
You don't own them!
Well, once again,
you disappoint me.
I'd have thought a
G.O.T.T. ES Member
would be better able to
maintain her composure.
You call killing people with
that smug look on your face
maintaining composure?!
Not yet.
You've exploited these
people for generations,
but you call them
the criminals!
So you shoot them
in cold-blood!
And all because you Nouvlesse
are too weak or too afraid
to adapt yourselves to
the rest of the universe!
I knew it.
I trust you've been following
the situation, Chief Eclipse?
No! You deal
with me!
This is most
unacceptable.
How do you explain the
actions of this ES Member?
Mister!
My deepest apologies,
Assistant Director Mister.
Chief...!
No! Don't do it!
ES Member Éclair. I
order you to stand down.
You will apologize to the
Assistant Director at once.
Chief, no...
Listen to me! An ES Member
cannot disobey a direct order
from the Chief of
the G.O.T.T.!
Hey! Now you
splash me, too!
Let me out
of here!
You have
been warned.
Hands in the air...
Away from the console.
I gave you an
order, Éclair.
Éclair!
Fire!
What is this?
She's gone mad!
Stop it,
Éclair!
I told you, didn't I?
You can't escape your past.
You will always be
destined to repeat it.
You are in direct
violation of orders!
Stand down,
Éclair!
If you want to shoot them,
you'll have to shoot me first!
But before
you try it,
you better be ready for
me to shoot back!
Éclair!
Kill all
of them!
Lumiere!
What did you expect?
We're partners, aren't we?
Hey...
Yes, I know.
Enact Plan C-5!
Citizens of Aure!
Our time has come!
...To revolt!
So much for handling
things quietly.
I don't know what
happened, sir.
We have decided it best to cut
our losses... Aure... and you.
There. Quieter already.
The last thing we Nouvlesse
need is more trouble.
So, a bloodless
revolution...
Without the funds for
continuous terraforming,
this planet
won't last long.
Winter is
coming to Aure.
This order has been issued
by the Privy Council,
and with full support
by the G.U. Senate.
Mister Secretary, are
you saying that this
is the consensus
of the Nouvlesse?
No, Superintendent General.
I'm saying this
is the consensus
of the ruling bodies
of the Global Union.
Is something funny
here, Chief Eclipse?
I'm sorry. I just find
the thought amusing,
that the galaxy's great
Nouvlesse could be so upset
by two
little girls.
Éclair and
Lumiere, huh?
They've been expelled
from the ES?!
Registrations... deleted.
In other words,
they're being purged.
It is an
endless cycle:
somewhere, a person is
born and another dies.
It cannot
be broken.
It is as inevitable as
the passing of time.
Next time on Kiddy
Grade: "Frozen/Life"