[TAIKO] Listen, Tenka.
[TAIKO] You don't have to be the greatest man there is.
Or the best brother that ever was.
Mother... Father...
[TAIKO] Instead...
...be the one to make them laugh.
Mind if I stay for a while?
[VILLAGER A] See? I thought that'd make you happy.
[OLD MAN A] No! Don't you dare!
[THUG B] Let's go!
--[VILLAGER C] Get back here! --[VILLAGER D] Thieves!
[VILLAGER B] Somebody please help!
[THUG A] Hey, move it!
That was too easy!
[THUGS grunt]
[THUG B] Huh?
Hey, brat! Out of my way!
[THUG B yells]
Sorry, was I in your way?
My bad.
[TENKA] The year is 1879.
Japan is amidst great transformation.
An uprise in crime and unrest herald this chaotic time.
With a monster known to emerge every 300 years destroyed,
the skies over Shiga have never been more clear or vibrant.
[wooden sticks clashing]
[SOSEI] Take a break.
[SORAMARU] Thank you, sir!
The prison's moving to Hokkaido?
Yes, it has vast, open spaces with a limited population.
They plan to incarcerate the more dangerous convicts there.
I see...
Guess that means the end of Gokumonjo.
Afraid so...
It'll be decommissioned before too long.
[SORAMARU gasps]
[SOSEI] I received official notice yesterday.
The Yamainu will disband.
[SORAMARU] But why?
[SOSEI] The Yamainu mandate was to destroy the Orochi.
Needless to say, with the serpent gone,
Ministry of the Right, Lord Iwakura,
no longer requires our services.
[SORAMARU] What happens now?
[SOSEI] Many of us have been given the opportunity
to join various military ranks.
Inukai and Shi are hesitant.
[SORAMARU] Are you joining the military?
Eventually, yes.
For me, protecting and defending our nation
is the only true contentment.
[SORAMARU] Please continue to train me until you've joined.
Shiga may be losing Gokumonjo and a fierce group
of warriors, but not me.
I'm almost head of our shrine.
Tenka won't be the strongest brother forever.
I wouldn't get too cocky. Break's over.
[BOTH grunting]
His physical strength is improving alongside the mental.
Yes.
His skills continue to flourish.
Soramaru is remarkable.
What's this?
Did you prepare something for him?
Indeed.
Apparently, it's good for the constitution.
I hope he'll enjoy every morsel.
[BOTAN] I'm certain he will find it memorable.
Hi, love.
You scared me, Hirari.
My apologies.
I missed you.
Don't you have work?
I gave my notice.
What?
I won't waste a moment of my life being away from you.
Your forethought is lacking.
How will you make a life for yourself now?
[HIRARI] Don't worry. I have savings, I can feed you.
But that isn't the issue, Hirari.
It was nice seeing you both...
I think I'll go inside and see Soramaru now.
Of course. Sorry for keeping you.
[NISHIKI] Don't be.
--Take care, you two. --[HIRARI] Bye.
[SOSEI, SORAMARU grunting]
Think she's uncomfortable here?
Must you continue to miss what is so painfully obvious, Hirari?
She's a Fuuma. I know that much.
A ninja.
One whose base is the Kumou Shrine.
Sometimes we'll sit and chat over tea.
I think she's wonderful.
Huh... Well, you sure are spending a lot of your time
with this strange girl.
She has no home. No kin or comrade.
Nothing of her old life can be returned to her.
Yet here, no longer donned in shadow,
she smiles easily.
She's going to face so much doubt and uncertainty.
She will fumble as she learns to accept our support,
but she is nonetheless endearing.
I want to see her happy.
I want to see that smile of hers more.
[SOSEI, SORAMARU grunting]
Tell me... How's he been doing lately?
Who?
Pretty much the same, more or less.
He hasn't changed.
[CHUTARO] Tenny! You've got a visitor!
[TENKA] 'Kay.
[KIIKO] Hope you're decent.
How're you feeling?
I'm back.
Missing him? It's okay.
Look who's back. Welcome home.
I'm just not used to it, is all.
You know?
[SORAMARU] Yeah, I do.
There is no getting used to it.
I'm glad you're back.
Is Nishiki with you?
Uh... She's out shopping... for dinner.
Huh?! What?! No way!
You promised you would do the cooking tonight, Sora!
I know, and I tried to talk her out of it, but--
It'll be another disaster!
[clattering]
[TENKA] How many times do I have to tell you to leave me alone--
[KIIKO] For once, would you just--
--[SORAMARU] Déjà vu. --[TENKA] I said no, Kiiko.
[KIIKO] Tenka, would you stop?!
Tenka?
Tenny, wait!
My bad.
[TENKA] I'll be out for a bit! Don't wait up!
[SORAMARU] Stop doing that inside the house!
Idiot...
Figured you'd be training with Sosei today.
[SORAMARU] We just finished up.
[KIIKO] I see. Sorry for the hysterics.
Don't worry about it.
We're just grateful that you care.
Tenny's acting strange...
Something's very wrong. I feel it.
[ASHIYA] Failed again?
Sadly. I don't know why thought I could do it today.
[ASHIYA] I know all too well that some things
--can't be helped. --[SORAMARU] Kiiko!
We deserve the truth.
Please.
What is it that's upsetting him so much?
[SORAMARU] He hasn't said anything about it to us.
But it's impossible not to notice how livid Tenka gets
when the Yamainu come to visit him.
[KIIKO] I've noticed too.
A year...
It's been a year since Orochi.
You're right. You both deserve to know the truth.
Your brother carries a heavy burden...
...for those he loves.
[KIIKO] It all began about 11 years ago.
[TAIKO] 89... 90... 91...
...92... 93... 94... 95...
...96... 97...
Don't stop, Takamine.
98... Faster, Ashiya!
Fight through the aches and pains.
If this training is enough stop you,
what chance do you have of destroying the Orochi?
99... 100.
Think you're done? 30 more.
[GROUP] Huh?!
[TAIKO] 1... 2... 3...
...4... 5... 6... 7...
...8... 9... 10...
[TENKA] This hurts!
--[SOSEI laughs] --Gah! You're disgusting!
What are you guys doing?!
Tenka!
--[TENKA laughs] --[TAIKO] Knock it off, Sosei!
[SOSEI] It wasn't me, sir! It was Tenka!
Don't you dare!
Come here!
[TENKA] Kiiko, stop him!
[KIIKO] Don't drag me into one of your squabbles!
--[yelps] --[SOSEI] Tenka!
[TENKA chuckles]
--[slapping] --[TENKA grunting]
That's enough, boys.
[SOSEI, TENKA] Yes, sir.
Still have some energy?
How about five laps?
Go around the oval.
Tenka and Sosei, do ten.
On your feet, now.
[SOSEI] Tenka!
[TAKAMINE] This is all your fault!
So young.
Perhaps it is their youth that gives them such promise.
Maybe it is. What's your assessment?
[SHI] The progress of strength and body continue to prosper.
However...
[INUKAI] They need more experience.
Yes, I agree.
About those laps... We don't have to run, right?
You had better catch up.
[TAIKO] A recurrent manifestation of the great
snake, Orochi,
led to the formation of a secret unit.
They're called the Yamainu squad.
Heroes working in obscurity.
The Yamainu will save the nation.
I hate running!
Anyone else starving?
So what do you say, old man? Should we feed these guys?
[TAIKO] Hmm...
Suppose everybody here's earned grub.
Listen up! Dinner at our place tonight!
[TENKA] All right!
First thing's first. I need a bath!
And there he goes...
Always the first one to leave every time.
Don't tell me you're taking it personally.
Each of us has a modus operandi.
Taiko!
[TAIKO] What is it?
We need your help.
There's a situation.
[RONIN HEAD A] We're not joking here!
Hurry it up or we kill the girl!
[RONIN HEAD B] You better meet our demands!
[ONLOOKERS chattering]
[TAIKO] A hostage situation?
Appears so, sir. Desperate, common criminals.
Well. Their demands?
It involves Gokumonjo.
Seriously?
[TSUCHIYA] They make up the remains of a pretty big
gang of thieves and bandits.
If we free the rest of their men,
they'll release the hostage.
[KITAMURA] Taiko...
We don't want these dangerous men
back on our streets, but...
...we don't want the girl harmed, either.
[TAIKO] Tenka?
Think you can handle this?
Now's the time to prove yourself.
Yes, sir!
[TAKEDA] Hey!
Why aren't you saving her?!
[OFFICER A] Hey! Stop him!
[TAKEDA grunts] Put me down!
Who's this?
[OFFICER A] It's his little sister that's the hostage, sir.
[TAKEDA] If you're not gonna do anything about it, I will!
Just give them what they want!
If he's calling you "sir," that means you're in charge,
doesn't it? She has to get out of that place!
She has to!
Please do whatever it takes to bring her back to me!
You're a good brother.
She'll be all right.
You'll see her soon.
What're we dealing with?
Ashiya.
[ASHIYA] Every one of them has a blade.
Long swords.
Damn...
One has a gun on him.
Firearms complicate things.
Harder to plan around with a hostage.
Where's the girl located?
[ASHIYA] They've got her tied up here,
right at the back of the building.
[KIIKO] Which makes just swooping in to grab her
problematic.
It's quite the risk.
[TAKEDA] What're you waiting for?
Please... Don't waste any more time.
You have to save her.
[TSUCHIYA] Hey, kid...!
You can't keep sneaking off like that.
Do you understand?
[KITAMURA] Everybody get back!
[TENKA] As far as I'm concerned,
the situation goes beyond a simple rescue mission.
[INUKAI] We're with you!
They don't have a lot of time.
[TSUCHIYA] Please just trust us.
[TAKEDA] My sister...
[RONIN B grunts]
[RONIN SPY B] Yamainu are on the move!
Everyone inside now!
Get ready for a fight, boys!
I want them found this instant!
They saw us.
But that's impossible.
Keep moving.
[RONIN HEAD A] This is the last thing we need.
If the Yamainu have found a way to slip inside,
we're screwed!
[RONIN HEAD C] Calm down. There's only seven of them
and we've got twice that many guys out there.
And let's not forget about our little hostage!
[RONIN C grunts]
Huh?
[RONIN C yells]
Come down here!
[RONIN G yells]
What the--?!
[RONIN C yells]
[INUKAI, RONIN D grunt]
[RONIN E] Take this--!
Here goes.
[RONIN grunt]
[TENKA] Hey, there. Ready to go home?
[HOSTAGE yelps]
[RONIN HEAD C yells]
Now, now.
[RONIN yelling]
[RONIN HEAD C grunts]
[RONIN HEAD C yells]
[RONIN HEAD C chuckles]
Damnit, kid.
What's he doing?
[TAKEDA yells]
[RONIN HEAD C yells]
--Father! --Sensei!
[TAIKO] You okay?
[TAKEDA] Yeah.
[TAIKO] Kiiko, go see to his sister.
[KIIKO] Yes, sir.
They were expecting the squad and that left
every one of you vulnerable.
You opened yourself to an ambush.
A bystander in the crowd...
He was the one that warned their lookout.
What is all this?
Who are you people?
[TAIKO] We're the Yamainu.
Yama... inu?
Welp, that's our cue.
Come on, guys! Dinner isn't gonna eat itself!
Where you off to?
Well you haven't been going home...
Makes wonder where you've been sleeping.
[ASHIYA] Don't see how that's your business.
[TAIKO] Watch the attitude.
I'm your mentor and guardian.
Your safety is my business.
[ASHIYA] Fine, you wanna know?
I stay with whatever girl I happen to be with that night.
Ashiya, I'm just trying to help you.
It's what family does.
[ASHIYA] Don't talk to me about family.
You don't know the first thing about mine.
[TAIKO] I'll lend you an ear if you want to change that.
[ASHIYA] Yeah, not interested.
[TAIKO] Well that's too bad, isn't it?
[ASHIYA groans]
We have problems.
Not just you, but all of us do.
The Yamainu share laughter, burden, and fate.
It's foolish to think otherwise.
I'm not asking you to tell me all your secrets.
What we need from you is trust.
Every single one of you already has mine.
Tenka?
[ASHIYA] What's this for?
[TAIKO] You come from a long line of Onmyo mages,
don't you?
Your mystic abilities are unmatched as a scout,
but what use are those magics in a fight?
Think it's about time we found out.
[ASHIYA] And here I thought training was done for the day,
but if seeing an onmyouji fight is what you want...
...it's what you'll get!
Disappointing!
You lack focus.
[ASHIYA gasps, yells]
[ASHIYA coughs]
[TAIKO] You're too dependent on your Shikigami.
[ASHIYA] Save me the speech.
Get to the point already.
[TAIKO] If you want to destroy the Orochi,
you need to be at your best.
[ASHIYA coughs]
[ASHIYA] My leg...
He's a lot stronger than he looks.
[ASHIYA] You have what it takes to kill me.
What?
[ASHIYA] His resilience is remarkable.
He could be the one to end it.
You of course know why I was chosen
for the Yamainu squad.
Same as the others.
Tenka Kumou, Sosei Abeno, Kiiko Sasaki,
Zenzo Inukai, Seiichirou Takamine, maybe even Shi.
We're all potential vessels for the Orochi.
How'd you put it?
"The Yamainu share laughter, burden, and fate"?
We were brought together because of the Orochi.
If it were one of us, it would be easier, wouldn't it?
Apparently, no one told Mother the big secret.
Imagine her surprise when learning of my father's
connection to the Orochi bloodline.
Abomination!
[ASHIYA grunts]
[ASHIYA] She couldn't see me as anything other than
a monster after learning the truth.
Blood ties shouldn't sever so cleanly.
But my mother still left Father and I.
Be honest with me...
Do you believe the Orochi is going to choose you?
Can you blame me?
It's not that I'm frightened of the serpent itself.
I just know who I am.
I know that I'd devour everything.
Friends, family, home--
anything doomed to cross my path.
I don't want to become the monster she thought me to be.
I don't want my mother to feel justified
when it finally happens.
--If I-- --[TAIKO] I'll make it quick.
I have what it takes after all, right?
I think I can handle it.
If it comes down to it, I'll kill you.
Yes, Taiko.
I trust you will.
Ever the virtuous man.
Yeah. Amazing, isn't he?
Look, guys...
If the Orochi chooses me to be the vessel--
[SOSEI] I'll kill you.
And should I be chosen,
I'd expect you to do the same for me, Tenka.
Well...
I think it's about time we caught up with the others,
don't you?
[TENKA] But...
...what if it were one of them?
[SORAMARU] Welcome back!
Been good for your mom?
[SORAMARU] Yes, sir!
Tenny!
Oh, Tenka, you're soaked to the bone, honey.
Let's get you inside and dry off.
[SORAMARU] Anybody home, Tenny?
[KOYUKI] Sweetheart?
Oh, I'm sorry. I think somebody missed me.
Your friends are already inside the house.
I hope we're not imposing or anything.
[KOYUKI] Not at all...
I'm pleased to see Ashiya finally coming around, too.
[TENKA] What if the Orochi chose Soramaru
or Chutaro?
Do I have what it takes to... kill them?
[SORAMARU laughs]
Open up, buddy! Eat your dinner!
Come on, Tenka. Don't force him.
All right! You eat it, then!
[TENKA] A good dog does as it's told without forethought.
The Yamainu squad is meant to protect their country
and defeat the Orochi.
Nothing more.
[GROUP laughs]
[TENKA] Death is not permitted to any Yamainu.
No Yamainu shall waver until the Orochi is taken down.
No one...
No matter what happens.
[CHUTARO crying]
Mommy! Mommy!
[SORAMARU] Chutaro...
[crying continues]
[BOTH crying]
--[strike] --[TENKA grunts]
Stop it!
What the hell did you just say?!
I said I'm leaving.
You're not doing this to us.
Where the hell is your sense of duty?!
What about everything we were supposed to accomplish?
I'm quitting. That's all there is to it.
You bastard!
[KIIKO] Sosei!
Just like that?!
After all that crap about becoming heroes?
You made me believe it!
You and your father did!
He wouldn't let you throw this away!
He wouldn't want you to forget us, Tenka!
The Yamainu need a leader!
Then it's a good thing they have you.
I was never meant to lead the Yamainu.
[SOSEI] I don't believe you.
Think about this.
Oh, I have. Believe me.
I'm just not cut out to be a leader like you.
As of this moment, we're done.
I never want to lay eyes on you again.
Same goes for anyone else thinking of quitting.
With or without you, the Yamainu will endure.
[ASHIYA] I'm not going anywhere.
As long as there's a squad, you can count me in.
If you'll shoulder the burden of leadership,
I'll follow you anywhere.
Trust me and I'll trust you.
Sound logic.
[TENKA] Don't stay behind for my benefit.
Keep them together no matter what, Kiiko.
You're a fool.
Yeah, I know.
Just a damn fool.
So you're back...
The boys tried waiting up for you.
[TENKA] Thanks for watching them.
[OHTA] All that crying really took a lot out of them.
They've earned a rest.
And how're you adjusting?
Feeling good, Doc.
Those Orochi cells must be adapting to my body
pretty well.
[TENKA yelling]
I wouldn't be certain of that.
The experiment only ends one way.
But I'm sure I don't have to tell you this, Tenka.
It'll be fine.
Reuniting with my parents will be a nice comfort.
Why must you sacrifice yourself?
[TENKA] The first thing a child learns is that they are loved.
Such concentrated emotion is a lesson in and of itself.
How does it feel to be a big brother now, Tenka?
Just look at him...
He's so tiny, isn't he?
[TENKA] Being the eldest means making sure they know
just as much love as I did.
And that's exactly what I'm going to do.
I've got plenty of love to give you guys.
[TAIKO] Listen, Tenka...
You don't have to be the greatest man there is.
Or the best brother that ever was.
Instead, be the one to make them laugh.
No matter the problem or worry,
you can't let your brothers take life too seriously.
Night, boys.
I love you with all that I am.
[SORAMARU] So what you're saying is
if it weren't for us, Tenka might not have quit?
Don't concern yourselves too much
thinking about the past.
And I'm certain that worrying about you two
wasn't the only factor at play.
He had a lot to consider.
Let's just say the love your brother has for you
made Tenka's decision an easier one.
Leaving the Yamainu squad was beneficial, Sora.
The Orochi chose you.
If Tenka hadn't left when he did,
he would've been bound by his oath.
[ASHIYA] Tenka Kumou is his father's son, after all.
[SORAMARU] We appreciate how much you all care for him.
Obviously, some care more than others.
If everything you're saying is the truth,
why is Tenny so mad at the Yamainu?
[KIIKO laughs]
Well... at the very least, he isn't mad at you.
[CHUTARO] Huh?
[KIIKO] I don't think you need to worry.
[VILLAGER E] Stop! Thief!
[TENKA grunts]
Heavens, are you all right, sir?
[OFFICER B] Stop!
[CROWD chattering]
[TENKA chuckles] I'm right as rain.
[VILLAGER F] Do be more careful.
[TENKA] You got it!
[TENKA] Guess who showed up to complain.
Kiiko keeps visiting.
The guys come by, too.
How does any Yamainu have enough free time
to bug me?
I'm taking long walks and picnics with all my free time.
Wish they'd take the hint and leave me alone.
They were done with me.
Now I can't get rid of anybody.
I know, Mom...
They're just coming around because
they're concerned for me.
I mean, I understand why and all.
They can see what's happening to me and want to pretend
everything's fine...
But this whole side of my body is paralyzed.
Half of my face is totally numb.
I can barely manage a smile now.
[TENKA] No more Orochi...
No more Gokumonjo...
It's finished... and now I'm useless.
[TENKA] The last thing either of them needs is a burden.
Truth is...
...I should've gone when the Orochi did.
[SOSEI] This is why you've been sulking?
Ever the fool.
Sosei.
Hey. Been a while...
Haven't seen you since the Orochi.
Is what you're saying the truth?
Do you think you should've died alongside the Orochi, Tenka?
Show reverence to the hallowed ground laid here.
Your parents deserve that kindness.
Ugh. Can't a guy catch a break?
Of all the people that could've overheard, it had to be you.
[SOSEI] Air out grievances here often?
Yeah. I do.
Looks like I'm not the only one?
I... made a point to not visit until the Orochi
was no longer a threat.
How honorable of you!
[SOSEI] My vow to your family isn't a joke, Tenka.
Sorry, Sosei.
What's this apology for?
You're sorry for leaving the squad?
Being complicit in Orochi experimentation?
Saying asinine things to your parents' headstones?
Stealing my daifuku and lying about it?
I could continue, so you'll have to be more specific.
For all of it.
From this apology, a person might infer
that you knew what you were doing wasn't above board.
What else do you need to hear?!
Given the chance again,
would you walk a path different from that which
brought you here?
I don't regret protecting my brothers...
But still...
I hate that I wasn't honest with you about what was
really going on.
I do, too...
You're forgiven.
The Orochi is dead and gone...
Sosei Abeno's mission has been accomplished.
The man I am now has no interest in old scores.
I stand before you as someone ready to begin a new life.
[TENKA] A fresh start...
That's just what you need.
[TAKAMINE] He's not the only one that could use a fresh start.
Ain't that right, Tenka?
Why are all you guys here?
And what's with the uniforms?
You've been disbanded.
What is all this, Kiiko?
[KIIKO] I'd think it would be fairly obvious by now.
Then again, you never did let me explain, did you?
The squad has one more matter to see to.
All members are now present.
Commander of the Yamainu, Sosei Abeno.
Second-in-command, Seiichirou Takamine.
Yamainu, Kiiko Sasaki.
[ASHIYA] Yamainu, Mutsuki Ashiya.
Yamainu, Zenzo Inukai.
[SHI] Yamainu, Shi Qian-Lang.
Yamainu, Rakucho Takeda.
[SOSEI] Yamainu, Tenka Kumou.
Sir...
The eight of us are reporting to you for the last time.
With the Orochi gone, our mission has ended.
To all Yamainu: you are now relieved of duty.
Sensei...
Though paths may have faltered...
...your spirit kept us strong.
We'll always be grateful to you and your teachings.
The Yamainu squad strived to maintain the honor
you bestowed upon us.
I am pleased to report not a single member has been lost
because of you, Sensei.
You're the reason we're all still here...
There's no disputing that.
You will not be forgotten.
Master Taiko Kumou.
We are forever thankful.
Tenka...
You have something to say.
Why not do it among friends?
[TENKA] Father... Mother...
Have I--
Was this my best?
[TENKA yelling]
[TENKA] The pain was excruciating.
[TENKA] And it wouldn't stop.
[TENKA sobbing]
[TENKA] But no matter how much I cried or screamed for you,
you weren't there.
You weren't...
And I--
I tried my best.
Was it enough?
I don't know anymore.
Soramaru.
Chutaro.
You're more than enough, Tenka!
My brother's the best in the world, sir!
The absolute best and I don't care who knows it, Tenny!
I love you so much!
Hey... What're you two doing here?
You're here, so we're here, sir! Obviously!
[TENKA] Why are you crying?
[CHUTARO] Because you are!
Why are you crying?
Come back! You can't just leave me here!
Nobody is leaving you, Tenka.
Haven't you realized that yet, you idiot?
How much proof do you need?
Go on.
Let's get you home.
We're having beef hotpot, sir!
[SORAMARU] But Nishiki's making it.
[TENKA] Who let that happen?
Whoa!
Soramaru!
We should hurry. It'll be dark before too long.
Keep up, Chutaro!
Yes, sir!
[GROUP laughs]
[TENKA yells]
[CHUTARO] Coming through!
Hey... Be careful!
[TENKA] Well damn...
These boys are turning into men.
When the hell did that happen?
Mom and Dad!
We love you! We'll be back!
Soon!
[SORAMARU chuckles]
[GROUP chattering]
[SORAMARU] I thought I told you not to drink!
[TENKA] I don't remember that.
Besides, it's a celebration, and that means booze.
Tenny, I don't want you to go!
Still leaving!
Spent my whole life here.
It's past time I saw the world.
Are you sure about this?
There's no arguing with him once he's made up his mind.
[TAKAMINE] Will you be all right on your own?
Huh? I'm hurt you even have to ask that.
Besides, it's not like he's traveling alone.
[GROUP] Huh?!
[TENKA groans]
It's supposed to be a solo trip.
Well that's too bad.
I could use a holiday and you could use the help.
[TENKA groans]
There is no point in arguing with her, Tenka.
Could be a lot worse, kid.
[SHI] I hear wedding bells.
I get to decide all the destinations.
Of course.
[ASHIYA] Where'll your first stop be?
[TENKA] Huh?
Excellent question.
Is something the matter?
Just thinking...
Hard not to think about where he is right now,
you know?
Yeah, I really do.
[FUUMA NINJA] Master...
We're ready to leave when you are, sir.
Very good.