THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future, to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a Spirit Evolution!
I am the one!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all!
I am the one!
Digimon!
[phone ringing]
-5:40?
-Here comes!
-Huh?
Huh?
[static]
-Dad, the ball!
-I'm sorry.  The phone.
That noise!
-I'll get it!
Kids these days.
Oh, perfect!
[screams]
This is my destiny?
[clock chime]
[phone ringing]
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Oh, honey,
you can't be late tonight.
It's Shinya's birthday.
-And tell Dad I want
something big!
A forklift!
-[groans]
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Mind
your manners, Shinya.
And don't even think of eating
that cake, Takuya.
Now, honey, I know that you're
busy, but how would you feel
if the kids didn't acknowledge
your birthday?
-Man, I'm bored.
My whole life is boring.
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Oh,
well, OK, well, that
wasn't their fault.
The calendar wasn't on
the right month.
-Bored, boring.
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
but that time, the kids
were away at camp.
Oh, come on.
The kids weren't
even born then.
-Incoming message?
No name?
Weird.
Well, it's bound to be better
than being bored.
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON PHONE):
Takuya Kanbara.
-Huh?
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON PHONE):
It's time to decide your
future, Takuya.
-Hey.
Wait a minute.
Who is this?
What do you mean, my future?
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON PHONE):
Your destiny is calling.
Take the 5:45 outbound train.
-This is way better
than being bored.
My destiny?
That's downright cool.
Huh?
Oh, I'll never make it!
But that's never stopped
me before!
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Getting an
ugly tie is not the Cuban
Missile Crisis!
And Takuya, be careful
out there!
And no playing in the street!
It's dangerous!
[screeching brakes]
-Man, why do moms always
have to be right?
-You OK?
-Yeah.  I'm fine.
Oh, no!
Hey, buddy, what time is it?
-What? uh, a couple
before 5:45.
-[groaning and panting]
Oh, why does this always
happen to me?
ANNOUNCER (OFFSCREEN): 5:45
train, now boarding.
-Whoa!
Excuse me!
Whoa!
Huh?
One minute?
Oh, great!
I knew I should have asked
for more allowance!
Huh?
A ticket?
Maybe this is destiny!
Wait, my destiny!
I can't believe I made it.
[phone ringing]
-Huh?
-Uh.
Huh?
-Whatever.
-Huh?
Uh.
Wait a minute.
Did he get a message too?
FEMALE VOICE (ON PHONE):
Transfer to the
6:00 westbound train.
[beeping]
-[screams]
Oh, come on!
Give me a break!
I'm doing the best I can!
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Now what?
Huh?
Maybe he knows.
Hey, wait!
[groans]
Hey, did you get
a message, too?
Uh, you could answer
me, at least!
Whoa.
Whoa!
Oh, no!
My destiny's really
starting to bite!
Man, I really gotta stop
landing on my head.
Whoa.
So weird!
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON PHONE):
It's up to you now.
Which one will you choose?
-Uh.
Um.
Hey!
Which one are you choosing!
Jeez, my phone talks
more than that guy.
[clock chime]
-[screaming]
-[laughing]
-Destiny sure involves
a lot of running!
Huh?
Oh, way to think
ahead, Takuya.
Wherever you're going, you're
going to get there in a hurry!
Huh?
No one?
It's like a ghost
train in here.
What if it is a ghost train?
Um.
You here because of
the phone thing?
-Uh-huh.
With him here, there's
four of us.
I wonder if that means
something special.
-Something special?
What?
Why did you guys get
on this train?
-Um.
-I mean, was it the message?
-Hey, kid, this is the closest
train to the elevator, OK?
Now, look, just leave me alone.
-Oh.
Gee, sorry.
-I'm just nervous.
-But there must be a reason why
you picked this particular
train, right?
-I'm like him.
It was closest to
the elevator.
-Watch this.
Hey, honey, you want
some chocolate?
Move!
So, my name's JP.
What's yours?
-I'm Zoe.
It's nice to meet you.
-And I'm--
I'm Takuya.
Hi there.
-I'm--
-What?
-I'm Tommy, but I didn't want
to get on this train.
-What are you saying?
-[whimpering]
Two kids-- bullies--
and they--
pushed me on the train
and shut the door!
Why are kids always
picking on me?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Jeez, that
kid's like a faucet.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): JP!
Don't worry, Tommy.
You're safe now that
you're with us.
[growling]
-Huh?
[screaming]
Huh?
Whoa!
[beeping]
-What's going on?
FEMALE VOICE (ON PHONE):
Welcome to the
Digital World, Takuya.
This is your D-Tector.
-Digital World?
You're kidding.
What have I gotten
myself into?
[growling]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Did you
guys get that message?
I'm guessing yes.
[yelling like a train whistle]
-Oh, you can hear
that on Mars!
Man!
-Are those ghosts?
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): They
look like it.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Or
marshmallows.
They'd go great with
chocolate.
[laughing]
-[screaming]
-Probably ghosts of kids
that came here before.
What have gotten myself into?
A-and what if there's no way
of getting back out?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Jeez,
calm down, Takuya.
We're all in this together.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I bet that's
the train station.
I hope there aren't any more of
those ghost things there.
Not that I was scared
or anything.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Yeah, I always
scream in terror
when I'm not afraid.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Ugh. Boys.
-[groans]
-Human kids!
-Someone to play with!
-Just don't break
them this time!
-Hear that first
step's a doozy.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
-Is it me, or did the
train just talk?
-Hey, but, I'm not just
any old train.
I'm Trailmon, and I'm
alive just like you.
Although I am more handsome than
you scrunched up little
pugs, thank you very much.
Anywho, this here is
Flame Terminal.
You're in the heart of
a Digimon village.
-Digimon village?
-Be our pals!
-Our last friends didn't
last very long.
-I have enough friends.
-[crying]
I didn't even wanna
be on this train!
-Sorry you feel bad, kiddo,
but I can't stick around.
If you want to go home,
you'll have to
find a Spirit or something.
-This kid should get a
job as a fire alarm.
-What's a Spirit?
And where do we get one?
Hello!
-Where are you going?
Give us an answer!
Hey!
-Hey yourself!
I've got a schedule to keep!
-So guess that's it.
We're all alone.
-Wait!
Come back here!
-Yeah!
Pretty please?
-[crying]
Take me home!
-Hey, wait!
Tommy, stop!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Why do I get
the feeling we're going to
spend all our time rescuing
the baby?
-Tommy!
-Go away!
-This isn't helping!
You're gonna fall!
-At least I won't
be here anymore!
-I'll take you home!
That's right!
Trailmon said that if we
find this Spirit, we
can go home, right?
-Right.
OK, I'm coming back.
Whoa!
-Tommy!
-Don't move!
I'm coming to get you.
-Look what you've
gotten me into!
-It's a human.
-You think everything's
a human!
-Don't start with me, you!
-I'm human.
Would you mind getting
off me now?
-I'm so sorry.
His fault.
-Yeah, my fault.
Hey!
-What is that?
-That is one bad dog.
Bad dog.
Cerberumon, special attack
Emerald Blaze, and that's why
we need your help.
-Where's the Ancient Spirit?
-So whenever you're ready,
go and get him!
-That would be good.
-I can sense the Spirit's
presence all over this town.
I must destroy it!
-No way!
It's mine!
I-- uh.
-[nervous laughter]
-Then you shall be destroyed
with it!
Emerald Blaze!
-What?
Are you crazy?
Run already!
-Yeah, but where am
I supposed to go?
-Anywhere but here!
That mutt is going to eat
up the whole village!
-Oh, great!
-There go the train tracks!
-Takuya!
-Oh, no!
-[screaming]
-[beeping]
-Hey, my D-Tector!
No way.
What is--
-It's the Spirit.
Spirit of Flame.
-Spirit?
That wasn't so hard.
Time to go home!
But how am I supposed
to get it?
And what do I do with
it when I do?
-No need to worry about that!
For it will soon be destroyed.
Ha!
[growling]
-[whimpering]
-This sure rates pretty high on
a scale of one to stupid!
Oh, man!
-[growling]
Get out of my way, human,
or suffer my wrath!
-No!
But I hope his wrath isn't
as bad as it sounds.
-Augh!
The Spirit's power!
Oh, that hurt.
-But what about Takuya?
-I'm fine.
But--
Ancient Spirit.
Huh?
Spirit!
FEMALE VOICE (ON PHONE):
It is time.
-[yells]
Execute Spirit Evolution!
Agunimon!
[yells]
-What is this?
A human turned into a Digimon?
-What did he turn into?
-Well, let me see.
Hmm.
-No way.
-Every way.
-Big and red, likes flame,
not Santa Claus-- oh!
Agunimon!
Oh, my!
I mean, oh my!
-No matter who you
are, you'll lose!
Emerald Blaze!
-Wow!
-Molto cool!
-Portals of Darkness!
-Whoa!
-Now we'll see how you fare
on my turf-- darkness!
[cackles]
No one escapes the darkness!
Emerald Blaze!
-How about I defeat you
without escaping?
Pyro Tornado!
-No!
You can't!
-I have to admit it,
I'm impressed.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): But what
if he's in trouble?
-Trouble?
No no no no no.
-A human child defeated me?
No!
-That's amazing!
-He's beautiful!
-Now to take the Fractal Code.
-Hey, look at the pretty
little light.
-You nincompoop.
That pretty little light is
Cerberumon's essence.
So it looks like we're
not done with him.
Buzz off!
You said you didn't want
to carry the book.
-Whoa.
Hm?
-[panting]
Wow, that's tiring.
But what-- what happened?
How did I know how to
do all that stuff?
FEMALE VOICE (ON PHONE):
You are Digidestined.
-I'm what now?
FEMALE VOICE (ON PHONE):
Digidestined.
Chosen for great things.
But don't be frightened.
The one who chose you is you.
-I chose myself?
I guess this means we're
not going home.
FEMALE SPEAKER NARRATING: These
guys have no idea what
they've gotten themselves
into.
But I'll bet you know.
Find out on the next Digimon:
Digital Monsters.