NARRATOR: After their battle
with the Royal Knights, the
gang found themselves marooned
on the moon.
Even worse, everyone was
unconscious, except Bokomon,
Neemon, and Koichi.
Suddenly, a Starmon appeared and
took everyone to safety.
Once the gang was revived, they
had to figure out how to
get off the moon and back
to the Digital World.
They tried everything, and
eventually settled on using an
old rocket that the
Burgermon built.
They used a slingshot to
get it into orbit,
but ran out of steam.
Luckily, along came a Trailmon
to push them
the rest of the way.
Now they're back on Digi firma
and looking to stop Lucemon
and his royal rats.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the the lessons
we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Hi-ya-moo-ha.
Huh!
Hi-ya-moo-ah.
Digimon!
-Beautiful.
But now it's my turn.
And now for a late
night snack.
Beautiful.
Delicious.
[wicked laughter]
-Full yet?
-Never.
-Then let's see.
Ah, beautiful.
-Steel Town.
We'll scan everything there!
-Thanks for the lift.
-I'm just glad I didn't
mess it up.
-Bye!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Where
are we anyway?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Steel Town.
The whole place is
made of steel.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Gee, never
would've guessed
that from the name.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Wow, it's
all so shiny and bright.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
bright is right.
Some of those buildings are
reflecting right in my eyes.
-I bet you guys wish you
had a cool pair of
goggles about now.
-Yeah right.
All the cool kids
wear goggles.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Well, they will.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): It's not
so shiny and clean here.
[laughter]
-Huh?
-What is that?
[gasp]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Sagittarimon.
Half man, half horse, and all
mean, his judgment arrow
attack is three prongs
of pain.
-Stop right there, humans.
While I have nothing against you
personally, I must demand
that you hand over all
of your obsessions.
-Obsessions?
-No, wait I mean your
possessions.
I should've just said stuff
like I usually do.
I never should have bought
that thesaurus.
-So, you have nothing better
to do than rob us?
-That's right.
Now, if you don't want to
get hurt, hand over your
obsessions.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): I can't
believe we're being robbed by
someone this dumb.
You mean possessions, right?
-Yeah, right.
That's what I just
said, isn't it?
-OK, just give us a sec.
-There's no way he's with
the Royal Knights.
-Yeah, let's just get rid of
him and be on our way.
-What's wrong?
Hand it over.
-I'm afraid we're going to
have to say no to that.
-Wha?
-Look, we don't have time for
this, so why don't you just
leave before you get hurt?
-Trust me.
You're the one who's
gonna be hurting.
YOUNG VOICE (OFFSCREEN): Stop!
-What now?
-Who's that?
-Human kids.
But how?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Well, uh,
perhaps other humans are
working to save the
Digital World too.
-Hey you.
Are you the no good Digimon
who's been stealing from
everybody around here?
-So what if I am?
-Well, then you're
gonna get it.
-From who?
You guys?
A bunch of puny little kids.
I could take you easy, even
if you teamed up with
these guys over here.
-Yeah, but we're not the ones
you should be worrying about.
-Who's that?
-Whoever he is, he sure
is impressive!
-It's Angemon.
-I'm gonna be like him.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): And you
could certainly do worse.
Angemon has a virtuous and
compassionate heart, and few
can withstand his Hand
of Fate attack.
-OK.
Judgement Arrow.
-Time for you to go.
[cheering]
-I thought I told
you to leave.
-I'll remember this!
-Wow.
-Wow and a half.
-Awesome job Angemon.
-Are you kids OK?
What?
Wait a second.
-Hey, look.
It's Tommy!
-Huh?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Looks like
more friends for Tommy.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): So, wait.
Are you telling me that you've
been in the Digital World the
whole time that we've
been here?
You came on the trains too?
-Yep.
-Come on.
-Huh?
-We're gonna get left behind!
Wait!
KATSUHARU (OFFSCREEN):
Slowpoke.
I shouldn't even bring
you with me.
Wherever it is we're going,
well, at least we'll get there
in a hurry.
After we got on the train,
we ended up at the Forest
Terminal with a bunch of
other confused kids.
I mean, we weren't confused
like them, but
you know what I mean.
Anyway.
We started talking to some other
kids, and that's how we
met Teruo and Chiaki.
Then this chick told us all to
get back on board and go home,
but we were like, forget that.
This place rocks.
We want to stick around and
see what happens next.
So, that's what we did.
Pretty soon, we met Angemon,
and we've been traveling
around ever since.
You know, like having
adventures, fighting
injustices, that
kind of stuff.
-It's just like TV,
only we're in it.
And sure it's been dangerous,
but we have Angemon with us.
-Hm?
Hey, Tommy.
We're sorry about
picking on you.
-Hmph.
-It's not safe here.
You guys really should have
gotten on that train if
Ophanimon told you to do it.
-Ophanimon?
Oh, is she the one who's been
sending us those emails our
cell phones?
-Yeah, we used to get messages
all the time when we first got
here, but we haven't received
any for a while now.
-Your phones?
Why's that?
Did you have your D-Tectors
stolen or something?
-What's a D-Tector?
-Wha--
-All right.
We get to ask some
questions now.
Like, what are you doing here?
-Actually, we're trying to
restore peace to the entire
Digital World.
-World peace?
-Totally groovy.
-How are you guys gonna save
the entire world by
yourselves?
-Yeah, look what you
have for Digimon.
They couldn't fight their
way out of a paper bag.
-Hey.
-Yeah, it looks like the most
that those things could do to
save the world is volunteer
to pick up the trash.
-Oh yeah?
Well, we have the spirits
of the 10 legendary
warriors, so there.
Well, we do.
KATSUHARU (OFFSCREEN):
They probably get
hurt even doing that.
-Listen.
You should go home.
You're just going to get hurt
if you stick around here.
-Huh?
-Come on.
You guys don't even know
what you're doing.
You've been lucky so far, but
sooner or later, you're gonna
run into something that you
won't be able to handle.
-What do you know?
-We know there's some real
dangerous stuff here, like the
Royal Knights.
-Yeah.
They're the reason why pieces
of this world keep
disappearing.
-They want to destroy the whole
place and don't care who
goes with it.
And you guys could be next.
-Hey, you guys can't
tell us what to do.
You're not our fathers.
-Yeah, we've been doing
just fine so far.
Maybe you're the little babies
who need to run home to momma.
We're out of here.
-And you know what, Tommy?
I'm not sorry for
picking on you.
-Good riddance to bad rubbish,
that's what I say.
Anyway, it's all out
of our hands now.
-J.P.'s right.
We can't be worrying
about those guys.
Come on.
We have enough worries
of our own.
-And besides, we did warn
them after all.
It's not our fault if they
didn't listen to us.
-But we can't let them
go off on their own
and get into trouble.
It just wouldn't be right.
-Hey, look, we did everything
we could, OK?
Yeah, just trust
me on this one.
-Why?
Have you been right before?
-Well, sure, at least once.
ANGEMON (OFFSCREEN): Most times,
the right thing to do
is easy to see, if you're
willing to look and to do
what's necessary.
-Huh?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Angemon.
ANGEMON (OFFSCREEN): Ophanimon
foresaw the wickedness coming
to the digital world and knew
she might not survive.
But she nonetheless
stood up against
the forces of darkness.
She also saw that humans could
help defeat the evil ones, but
she didn't know which humans
would succeed.
So she risked putting them all
in danger and called them to
the digital world.
Luckily, most were brave enough
to swallow their pride
and leave when she asked.
Those four remained, and as
Ophanimon ordered, I have
continued to protect them.
-Why?
What you should do is
send them home.
You know how dangerous
this world is.
Plus, you could be helping us
fight the Royal Knights or
something instead of babysitting
that bunch of
selfish brats.
You have to explain to them that
they have to go home, and
if that doesn't work, then just
throw them onto a Trailmon.
-I have tried to explain many
times, but they will not
leave, so I must protect them.
-He's just doing what's
necessary.
-What do you mean?
-You can't blame him if
they decided to stay.
And maybe they're not wrong for
wanting to stay and make
something of themselves
either.
-He has a point.
-If someone said you were
useless and tried to send you
home, what would you do?
-You'd probably stay and try
to prove them wrong, right?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
I don't know.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Well, I do.
That would be the first,
second, and
third thing you'd do.
At least after yelling and
complaining a lot, you would.
-Argh.
Jeez, Bokomon, change
your mind much?
Fine.
We'll help them, or send
them home, or whatever.
-(THINKING) Great.
We're stuck with
those bullies.
-Well.
If it isn't little Tommy.
What's wrong?
Friends not around
to protect you?
So, Tommy.
-What?
-Well, I guess you think you're
all big and tough now
that you found some older
friends to protect you, huh?
So tought you want the
world to yourself.
So tough that you think you
can boss us around.
But know what I think?
We're staying, and you and
your friends are leaving.
That's why you're gonna tell
them you want to go home.
-What?
-I know how goodie two-shoes
like them work.
Cry hard enough and they'll have
you home faster than you
can yell momma.
And with them gone, we can be
the heroes who save the world.
Now, are you gonna tell them,
or am I gonna have to get
rough with you?
KATSUHARU (OFFSCREEN): Hey!
TEPPEI (OFFSCREEN): Katsuharu.
CHIAKI (OFFSCREEN): Sure, there
have been times when I
wanted to go home.
I mean, sometimes I miss my
friends and family, and I've
never had to walk so much
in my whole life.
But, here we're living this
incredible adventure, like
something out of a book.
-And really, that's just about
all we would go back to.
Books, and school, and
everything else that makes the
real world boring.
-Well, sure it's exciting, but
it's really dangerous too.
-You guys should be worried
about getting home alive, not
about being bored once
you get there.
Don't you ever think
about that?
-Not really.
I mean, Angemon's been there
right from the start to
protect us, and he'd
never let us down.
-Besides.
Katusharu looks out for us.
-Let him go, Teppei.
You're not gonna beat anybody
up unless I say so, got it?
-Yeah.
-What were you hoping
to do, Teppei?
Start a fight with those guys?
There are more of them
than us, remember?
-I know, but I was just
thinking that--
-Well, don't.
I mean, you are right
about him.
He's just hiding behind
stronger kids.
But then, that's what weaklings
like him always do,
and it would be stupid
to expect him
to do anything different.
-Argh.
-This world is for the strong,
Tommy, and little weaklings
like you shouldn't be here.
-You're wrong.
-What?
-I'm strong.
You're the one who's weak.
-Huh?
-You're hiding behind Angemon.
[explosion]
-What happened?
-Our friend is back.
-That's right.
Your friend is back.
But this time, he brought a
few friends of his own.
Ooh, you little brats
are in for it now.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Centarumon
isn't to big on
brains, but he's huge on brawn,
and his Solar Ray
attack won't brighten
up your day.
-It's like a whole army.
-This is what you all get.
It's payback for not handing
over your obsessions.
-You mean possessions,
not obsessions.
-I know what I mean.
I have a mind like
a steel flap.
Ready to attack Centarumon?
-Ready!
KATSUHARU (OFFSCREEN):
Guys, get back.
-We'll take care of this guy.
-Huh?
-Look, just stay
out of the way.
You guys can't handle this.
-We can't?
Sure we can.
Angemon'll fight them.
-I'll handle this.
Katsuharu.
You and the others find
somewhere to hole up out of
harm's way.
-Fool.
Do you really think you
can take us all on?
Judgement Arrow!
-Should we do something?
-Well, I don't know.
Should we Spirit Evolve?
-You just stand back and
watch Angemon go.
-Yeah, he's a fighting machine,
and there ain't no
one in the whole world who
could stand up to him.
-You see what we mean?
-Go Angemon.
Yeah!
Haha.
-Hehehe.
Charge!
-It's a trap.
-Yeah, and we fell
right into it.
-No!
-Don't forget about
little old me.
-What are you doing?
Run!
-Yeah!
-Solar Ray.
-Teppei!
-Katsuharu help me!
-(THINKING) I can't.
I can't.
Get out of there!
-Are you OK?
-I guess.
Yeah.
-Hm.
I'm strong.
You're the one who's weak.
-He was right.
-You're a bunch of bullies,
but you're not
gonna bother us anymore!
Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
Korikakumon!
-Huh?
-Wha?
-Whoa!
-Still wanna fight?
Not so tough now, huh?
-Come on, let's help him out.
-Right.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Agunimon!
-Lobomon!
-Kazemon!
-Beetlemon!
-Loweemon!
-How about we start
with a hot hoof?
Pyro Punch!
-Lobo Kendo!
-Hurricane Wing!
-Lightning Blitz!
-Shadow Lance!
-No way.
They all turned into Digimon.
-They're so brave.
-I'm surprised you know what
courage looks like.
-Huh?
-Their bravery is why the
spirits chose them.
-I had no idea these humans
could evolve.
ANGEMON (OFFSCREEN): And don't
forget about little old me.
-Huh?
-I believe we have unfinished
business.
[groaning]
-All right.
If you guys are smart, you'll
turn around and run
right out of here.
-And you run fast.
-OK.
-Man, we are good.
-Roar!
-Sorry.
For real.
I shouldn't have called you
weak, because you're braver
than I've ever been.
-You saved my life.
KATSUHARU (OFFSCREEN): It would
be an honor if you'd let
me call you my friend.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
Sure, you bet.
-Well, guys.
Now it's our turn to be brave
and do something we don't
really want to do.
We've had a great time here,
but these guys are right.
It's too dangerous.
So, I think we should go home.
-Seriously?
-Yep.
[shouting]
-How moving.
-The Royal Knights.
-But it would've been even more
moving if you were defeated.
-I guess we'll just
have to do that.
-Not so fast.
-Angemon, no!
-Ha ha!
-Laser Luck!
Now, now.
Not everyone is lucky enough to
be captured by someone as
beautiful as me.
Come along.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Tommy!
-Hey, you ugly tin can.
Come back here.
-Hm?
-Fret not, Dynasmon.
Allow me the pleasure of
handling these knaves.
Ah, the sweet smell of defeat,
even if you're
not worth the effort.
Scarlet Tempest!
So unsatisfying to
fight weaklings.
Now, let's finish this world.
-NARRATOR: And it looks
like they just might.
I mean, who can stop them?
Find out who will
win on the next
Digimon, Digital Monsters!