NARRATOR: When we last left
Koji, he had Fusion Evolved
into BeoWolfmon and was trying
to catch up with Duskmon.
He wanted some answers from
the dark dude, but blondie
gave him the slip.
Meanwhile, while everyone was
celebrating the birth of
Patamon, Sakkakumon decided
to crash the party.
He used the gang's own attacks
against them so he could take
away their spirits.
It looked bad for our heroes
until Aldamon figured out that
by combining their attacks, they
might get the upper hand.
Mixing up their attacks
mixed up Sakkakumon
and spelled his defeat.
Wow!
When these guys work together,
it really works.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
-Where did he go?
Duskmon!
-Who are you?
-I could ask you the
same question.
DUSKMON (OFFSCREEN): Why
did you follow me?
-Because I felt I had to.
DUSKMON (OFFSCREEN): Your
presence is painful to me.
-Is that why you hide from
me in the shadows?
-It is not.
-Then why?
-Destiny.
-Destiny?
DUSKMON (OFFSCREEN): Darkness
hides from the light until it
is ready to destroy it.
You, warrior of light,
are my destiny.
Darkness will prevail.
Your light shall be
extinguished.
-Frozen Hunter!
-Deadly Gaze!
[demonic laughter]
-At least we're mostly
all together.
I'd hate to be out
there alone.
-Me too.
-I bet it doesn't bother Koji.
-Well, yeah, if he's OK.
-Mhmm.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go!
-We'd love too, but we kinda
have to know where.
-Yes.
Let's not go rushing off
in all directions.
-You can do that?
-Let's see.
[shouting]
-We spend half our time
in this world
wandering around lost.
-Let's just pick a direction
and get moving.
-I pick this way!
-Works for me.
Beats standing around yacking.
-Looking for me?
-Aw.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Dying
of curiosity down here!
-Sorry, nothing.
I'm out of ideas.
What about you, Beetlemon?
-No joy.
Koji could be anywhere.
Or nowhere.
[grunting]
-Patamon.
You're too young to be flying
off on your own.
-You might get more
lost than us.
-But the light boy's this way.
-Huh?
-The light boy.
The light boy.
The light boy, buddy!
-Is he saying light boy?
-Does he mean Koji?
-Yeah, but how would he know?
-Duh.
Because it's all bright
this way.
-Huh?
-He just seeing things?
-I don't know, he seems pretty
sure of himself.
-Of course he's sure
of himself.
After all, Patamon was born
in Seraphimon's egg.
It wouldn't surprise me in the
least if he has some sort of
special powers.
And besides, he's my baby.
What did you expect?
-Are we gonna stay
here or what?
-Beans, they've gone off
without us again.
-Oh, did you say they
have beans?
Ooh, beans will be really
good right now.
-Perfect.
[demonic laughter]
Those children are surprisingly
persistent, but
they have interfered
for the last time.
-I'm just saying.
I didn't know anyone
could waddle and
fly at the same time.
-J.P., I can do anything
I want.
-Do you think maybe you could
do it a little faster?
-Sure, here goes.
Wee!
-Yeah, wee.
-I'd hate to see him
in slow motion.
-Patamon, I'll be happy to carry
you if you point us in
the right direction.
-No way.
This is fun.
I'm flying like the wind!
Ah!
-Dear, what's wrong?
-A bad thing's coming.
-A bad thing?
-What do you mean?
-That.
-Could you be more specific?
I'm sorry I asked!
-Ah!
[squeals]
[shouting]
[demonic laughter]
-Beautiful.
-You are mine.
Koji.
-Darkness will never
defeat me.
Cleansing Light.
-Lord Cherubimon.
-That is Cherubimon?
-Warrior of light, you are
a blight on my realm.
The time has come for me
to show you true fear.
Did you really believe I would
allow you to defeat the son of
darkness, my own creation?
[demonic laughter]
-His creation?
-Is everybody all right?
-I think so.
-So far.
-Mostly.
-Where are we?
-How did this thing get here?
-How, I couldn't begin to tell
you, but it's obvious we've
been sealed in by someone
who doesn't like us.
-Bad thing.
-Well, I'm sorry, but
that's just too bad.
I'm not going to stay
stuck in this place
like a rat in a trap.
How about you guys?
Ready?
Execute, now!
Fusion Evolution!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Aldamon!
-Kozemon!
-Beetlemon.
-Kumamon.
-Atomic Inferno!
-Tempest Twist!
-Thunder Fist!
-Frozen Tundra!
-Man, what's up with
this wall?
-With all of us working
together, we didn't even dent
this stupid thing.
-Gotta dig, gotta dig, gotta
dig, gotta dig, dig, dig.
-Blech.
-Playing in the dirt.
Isn't that cute?
-Patamon, really.
What on Earth are you doing?
-Silly, I'm trying
to dig a tunnel.
-A tunnel?
-Of course.
-If the wall is only
ground level--
-Then we can dig
right under it.
-I take back everything I
said about him earlier.
-Ha ha.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Patamon,
how clever of you.
I'm so proud of you,
I could just cry.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): I forget.
Which one are you?
The momma or the poppa?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): That's
actually a good question.
-Duskmon, it is time for you to
remember the day you came
to the Digital World.
Allow me to assist you.
-Argh!
Hello.
Is someone here?
Anyone?
P-Poppa?
You are my dad, right?
Poppa, I--
Grandma?
Grandma!
Koji.
You're Koji, right?
I wanted to meet you.
I know you don't know me, and
I know it sounds a little
weird, but I know you.
No, don't go!
Koji, don't leave me!
Why won't anyone pay
attention to me?
Pay attention to me.
-You have my attention, boy.
The darkness in your heart
drew me straight to you.
Your loneliness and sadness,
your angry soul.
It's like honey to me.
Sweet, pained darkness.
-Darkness?
-I like you.
-Who are you?
-I am the one who will
set you free.
I will release the darkness in
your heart, and it will give
you great power.
You will become one with this
spirit of darkness.
[screaming]
-It hurts because you
still remember your
pathetic human heart.
Let go.
Let its darkness
fill your soul.
This time, your heart shall
not trouble you.
Yes.
Now you see.
You are a creature
of darkness.
My creature.
With this spirit, you
will become a
true warrior of darkness.
You will not have to fear the
light, Duskmon, ever again.
-Duskmon Slide Evolution,
Velgemon!
-What are you?
-Yeah, baby!
-Really?
VELGEMON (OFFSCREEN): Roar!
-W-what was that?
-Something big.
-Something big, he says.
How about huge?
That can't be a Digimon.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Of course
it can, young man.
Haven't you learned anything
in this world?
Have you forgotten Sakkakumon
so soon?
-I haven't.
Let's get going.
We gotta help Koji.
-Velgemon.
It is time to make this a
world of true darkness.
Destroy the light.
-Velgemon?
-Light.
Enemy.
Destroy light!
Destroy!
-Frozen Hunter!
-Dark Obliteration!
-Why isn't it ever just
an earthquake?
-But Koji's there.
-Koji!
-Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
-Koji.
Light.
Destroy Koji!
Destroy!
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): You
must remember now.
Remember.
Remember your life in the
human world, Velgemon.
-What does she mean?
The human world?
Could that thing
still be human?
-I was in the human world?
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
You must remember.
It is time.
-Koichi.
-What?
What is it, grandma?
-You need to know.
Koichi.
You have a brother.
You must find Koji.
-Koji.
My brother.
[soft rock music playing]
-Koji.
Koji!
[soft rock music playing]
-K-Koji.
-What on Earth is he?
He looks exactly like me,
but how could that be?
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Be patient, Koji.
Soon, everything will
become clear to you.
What will?
What'll become clear.
What are you?
Answer me!
Come back.
Velgemon!
Just who are you to me?
[groaning]
NARRATOR: Poor guys.
How long do you think it'll be
before they figure it all out.
I guess we'll just have
to keep watching
Digimon, Digital Monsters.