RIKA NARRATING Everybody in
town was getting strange
messages on their cell phones.
Takuya, being a gogglehead,
followed the directions and
this other kid, Kouji, and ended
up with JP, Zoe, and
Tommy on a train to
the digital world.
Tommy wanted to go home,
but he picked a really
stupid way to do it.
Takuya tried to rescue
him, but things got a
little out of control.
Bokomon and Neemon were running
away from Cerberumon,
a Digimon trying to destroy
something called a spirit.
To make a long story short,
Takuya merged with the ancient
spirit of flame, and turned
into Agunimon.
Not bad for a gogglehead.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Huh?
What just happened to me?
-You mean before or after you
turned into a Digimon?
-Me?
-A Digimon?
-Yes, through the process
of digivolution.
-Digi-what?
It had to be something
I pressed.
Huh?
Come on, digivolution, start!
Operation Turn Me
Into a Digimon!
Execute!
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
Fractal code, rendered.
[all exclaim with wonder]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Oh, boy,
I think I broke it.
-I knew it.
It's a fractal code.
-Oh!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): There's
no way this is happening.
Whoa, did I do all that?
-What is--
hm.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): It's the
dawn of regeneration.
PAGUMON (OFFSCREEN): No more
living in a train station.
Trailmon will never go "whoo,
whoo" in my ear again.
-Nice going, my human friend.
By the way, I'm Bokomon, keeper
of the book, at your
service.
-And I'm Neemon, keeper of my
pants, also at your service,
you awesome human.
-On behalf of the digital world,
accept our thanks, O
human who restores what
has been lost.
-Call me Takuya.
And I still don't know why all
this fractal code stuff is
such a big deal, anyway.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): What?
You really don't know?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Ohhh,
he doesn't know!
-Hey, why are we running?
-I don't know.
-Behold!
Before the evil Cherubimon
came, our world was a
beautiful place.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Flowers,
trees, and butterflies.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Neemon!
I'm in the middle of
something here.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Sorry.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): His power
made many Digimon go wild, and
our world started to die.
The only way to bring back
everything that was lost is
with the fractal code.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): And
I made it happen.
With this little device.
-Huh?
-Wow.
I wonder if I could
do it, too.
-Hmm.
I know.
Hey, Tommy!
-Ahh!
-Our devices look the same.
-Maybe girls aren't meant
to be Digimon
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Excuse you!
-Hey, Shorty, I have an idea.
[train chugging on tracks]
-Hwaah!
Hwaah!
[brakes squealing]
[hiss]
JP (OFFSCREEN): This
place sucks.
It sucks to a T. You
with me, kid?
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
well, I guess so. But--
-But?
But what?
-When Takuya turned
in to Digimon, he
looked killer cool!
Just like a superhero.
-(DISGUSTED) Gah.
He wasn't that great.
-Well, I--
I've always wanted
to be a hero.
-Kid, take it from me.
This hero stuff is way
overrated, and I should know.
It's entirely too much work.
It's dangerous, not to
mention annoying.
And there's always some sap,
yelling, oh, save me!
Save me!
-Mm, I guess.
-Attaboy.
Now what say we find our
way out of this dump?
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
Kouji Minamoto.
Commence your search.
-Search?
For what?
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
The spirit.
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): How do
you know my name, hm?
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR): Find
the spirit, and you will find
the answers to all
your questions.
-Not good enough.
I'm not some lap dog you can
just order around, you know.
[beeping]
-What is this spirit, anyway?
-I mean, how do I know
where to look for it?
[beeping]
-Aw.
What's this?
Huh?
[hiss]
-This gets weirder
by the minute.
-Yeah, you said it.
[beeping]
-Yo, Tommy, check this
little guy out.
Hey, egg-shaped dude with
ears, what's shaking?
-Aah! Hnh?
-Listen, this world of yours
isn't really our scene.
Thing is, we don't know
how to leave.
So what do you say?
Can you help us out?
-Buzz off!
-I'll make it worth
your while.
Here.
-Dohhh.
-Heh, heh.
How about a bar of premium
chocolate?
-Yowlp!
-Ahh!
All right, Egg Face.
Talk to me, and you
get the whole bar.
-Mmm, ahmm, ah.
Hmm, take Angle the Trailmon
at the station.
He can take you to back
where you came from.
-Wow, for real?
-Now fork it over!
-Thanks, bud.
-Mmm, mnmm.
It's delicious!
I'll bet there's a lot
more of that stuff!
[laughter]
-There goes an accident
waiting to happen.
[laughter]
-They really shouldn't be
wandering alone in this place,
but oh well.
I'm not here to play
babysitter.
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
JP (OFFSCREEN): Hey, there,
you sleek mode of
transportation, you.
Feel like taking a ride
to the real world?
-Yeah, please?
-Uhhh, take a hike.
-Aww.
-How about a tasty
down payment?
And two more bars once
you get there.
[ding]
-Hmm?
-Aaaaahhh!
-Mmnf, mmmnh.
Yummy!
[laughter]
[whistle blows]
I'm off.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Wait!
You're supposed to--
[coughs]
to take us.
-With you.
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
-(IN UNISON) Mmm.
-Huh?
-Hey, Chocolate Boy.
We want more.
[cackling]
-No way!
[whispering]
-(IN UNISON) Uh-oh.
-Whoa!
-Wha?
-Attack!
-Aaaahhh!
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
[jp and tommy yelling]
-Aaaaahhh!
[jp screaming]
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
-Woo-hoo.
-Lots of space.
-More room for Poyo people!
[poyomon chatter happily]
-Huh.
[tap tap]
-Ahh.
Huh?
Hey, where's Tommy?
-He's with JP, I think.
-Maybe they're playing
hide-and-go-seek.
-Maybe they got eaten by a
bunch of big ol' bears.
-All right, now I'm worried.
-[groan]
We'd better go look for them.
-Ohh!
-Ahhhh!
Aaah!
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
-They're gaining on us!
[PAGUMON CHATTERING
AND CACKLING]
-Tommy!
Where are you?
-JP!
-Where could they be?
-Hey, Poyomon.
POYOMON (IN UNISON): Huh?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Have you
seen any human children?
POYOMON (IN UNISON): We saw
two being chased into the
forest by Pagumon.
Over there!
-Aahhh!
Oh, that's worse than bears!
-Pagumon?
-Nasty little Digimon
with bad attitudes.
-Mnnnh.
[beeping]
-Wow, this is getting old.
[beeping stops]
-It's probably safer to
stay away from creepy
holes in the wall.
Awww.
But I didn't come all this
way to play it safe.
This better not be someone's
idea of a joke.
Anyone here?
OK, I suppose not.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): No!
Come on!
Oh, come on, digivolve!
Make me digivolve now!
-Keep it down!
-I am keeping it down, but I
want to digivolve like Takuya
so we can beat them!
-That's crazy talk!
What do you think a runt
like you could do, huh?
Besides, digivolving looks
kind of painful.
Ever think about that?
-I bet digivolving's not as
painful as being eaten alive
by those crazy Digimon.
[beeping]
-Huh?
Aaaahhh! Oh! We--
hide-- lots--
[PAGUMON GRUNTING
AND CHUCKLING]
[jp and tommy yelling]
-Aaaaaahhhh!
[PAGUMON GRUNTING
AND CHUCKLING]
[PAGUMON CACKLING
AND CHATTERING]
JP (OFFSCREEN): You OK, kiddo?
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Uh, I--
I think so.
-Cool.
Let's scram, before we become
someone's lunch.
-(CALLING) Tommy!
-Tommy!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): JP!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Answer me!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Where are you?
-Just as peaceful as
I remember it.
Except for the screaming kids.
-They are loud.
-Rather.
But where'd they go?
-We've lost them!
-Just follow the noise, silly.
-Where could they have
gotten off to?
-Poor Tommy.
He's such a little guy.
He didn't even want to be
here in the first place.
-Yeah, you're right.
He really shouldn't be out
without his parents.
I guess I'm just going to have
to keep my eye on him.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Look at you,
pretending to be all mature.
How adorable.
-Hey, what do you mean,
pretending.
I'm in the sixth grade!
-Really?
You're in the same
grade as I am?
Who'd have thought?
I was sure you were two or three
years younger, at least.
-Wait a minute.
What's that supposed to mean?
-When's your birthday?
-In August.
-Hah!
I knew it.
I am older.
I was born in May.
That makes me a grand total of
three months older than you.
-Huh?
Grrrr.
That doesn't mean anything.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Whatever. [giggles]
-Hey, check it out.
-[gasp]
That belongs to Tommy.
BOTH: Aaaahhhhhh!
-Hm?
Hmm.
BOTH: Whoaaaaaa!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I'm alive!
I'm alive.
Oh, I could just kiss you!
-Uh-huh?
-Wha!
Aahh!
Get away from me!
-Uh, what?
Girl, you're the one who grabbed
me in the first place.
-My name it's girl, it's Zoe.
And keep your hands to yourself
in the future, little
boy!
-Uh, so are all mature
girls this crazy?
-That is so like a child,
sitting here yapping away,
when we should be looking
for Tommy.
Fine, let's go.
They're probably in there.
[gulp]
After you.
Heh, heh.
-The wind's blowing in this
direction, so if we walk this
way, we should find a way out.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Why?
-So there's no chance we're
walking around in circles?
-What gave you that idea?
-This cross.
Here.
-Huh.
So it's a cross.
So what?
-Well, I drew it when
we started out.
-Wha?
-That means we're lost.
We'll be stuck down
here for days.
-That's if we're lucky.
It could be months.
-[bursts out crying]
-Not again.
Here, this'll make
you feel better.
[tommy crying]
-Go on.
-Unh?
-Look on the bright side.
At least we won't starve.
-Mm-hm.
Ahh.
[both laugh]
[pagumon chattering]
-We're back!
-Aaahghhh!
Ahhhh!
-Get away from me!
Here, just take 'em!
-The human smells
like chocolate!
Eat the human!
[pagumon cackle]
-What's this?
JP (OFFSCREEN): (YELLING) Help! Somebody!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): (YELLING)
I'm not a chocolate bar!
[both scream]
-Huh?
JP (OFFSCREEN): (YELLING)
Help!
Anyone, please!
-It's Tommy and JP!
We have to help them!
-(SHARPLY) I know that! Hm.
-Hm.
[both panting]
[PAGUMON CACKLING
AND CHATTERING]
-Aaahhhhhh!
-Huh?
Aaaahhh!
PAGUMON (IN UNISON):
More chocolate!
-Mmm.
Aaahh, mmm.
Aaaahh!
Unh!
-Who's that?
Whoa!
-That guy's serious!
[pagumon screeching]
-Hyaaanh!
Hyah!
[pagumon screeching]
-Hyahhhh!
Hyaahh hunh!
[pagumon screeching]
-Yowww!
Hynnaaaaaaaanh!
-Aaaah!
-Aaaahh! -Yaaaaahh!
-Hm.
-Oh, yeah, human?
Don't smile yet!
-Ahhhh!
[DIGIVOLVE BEEPING
AND ZAPPING]
-Yehhhhhrawwwrrrr!
-Whaaaa!
-I'll eat you up!
-Hyah!
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
Raremon.
A sewer Digimon.
If the smell of its rotting
flesh doesn't knock you out,
its Acid Sludge attack will.
-Wha?
-Rawwwrrr!
-Aaaahh!
-Acid Sludge!
Rawwwwrrrr!
-Aahhh!
Whoa!
-Ooh, it smells!
-Spirit, wake up!
I need you!
Come on, I'm not kidding here!
Grrr!
-Hey, Takuya, no pressure, but
you might want to think about
spirit evolving before Stinky
there turns your
friends into goop.
RAREMON (OFFSCREEN):
Going somewhere?
-Come on, come on!
-[chiing!]
-Rrwwwaahhhh!
-(YELLING) Spirit!
Yaaahhhh!
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
It is time.
-Yahhhhh!
[digivolve beeping]
-Execute spirit evolution!
-Hyaahh!
Akunimon!
Aaaahhhh!
Rrrraaahhhh!
-Rwwwwahhhhhrrr!
-Hyah!
Now's your chance! Run!
-Ahhh!
-What's going on?
I turned back into me?
Whoa!
-Still here!
Bllauuuughhhh!
-Watch out!
Oh no!
-Aaaaahhhhh!
Bllauuuughhhh!
Ha, ha, ha!
-Aaaaaahhhhh!
What's going on here?
Uhhh! Aaahh!
Ohhhh.
SPIRIT!
[digivolve beeping]
OPHANIMON (ON D-TECTOR):
It is time.
[digivolve beeping]
-Execute spirit evolution!
-Hyahhhhh!
Lobomon!
-Oh, wow!
-Man, did I look that cool?
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, but different.
-That's the legendary warrior
of light, Lobomon.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I've never seen
anything more beautiful
in my whole life.
-Me neither.
-You can say that again.
-Acid Sludge!
Blaauuughh!
-Lobo Kendo!
Yah!
Aaaahhh!
-Blauughh!
Aaahhhhh!
-Yaawwrrrr!
[fractal code beeping]
-Now, you talking trash heap--
LOBOMON (OFFSCREEN): Prepare
to be recycled!
[fractal code beeping]
-Fractal code, digitize!
-Molto bravissimo!
[digital beeping]
-Huh?
Hey!
Hey, you OK Let me
help you up.
-Don't touch me.
-Wha?
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): I don't
need your help.
Or anyone else's.
But I guess I should thank
you for saving me.
I always repay my debts.
-I didn't do it so you'd
owe me, you know.
-My name's Kouji Minamoto.
And you are?
So are you going to tell me?
I can't repay you if I
don't know your name.
-I'm Takuya Kanbara.
-Takuya, huh?
See ya.
-What's his deal?
-Come on, guys.
Let's get out of here.
This place smells
like dead fish.
[poyomon hooting and giggling]
RIKA (NARRATING) Wolf Boy has
some pretty sweet moves.
But what's with the attitude?
To find out, keep watching
"Digimon, Digital Monsters."
(theme music)