NARRATOR: The gang headed into
Burgermon Village hoping to
enjoy some of their famous
hamburgers, but the town was
broken and battered.
Petaldramon and his cronies had
ravaged the Hamlet on a
quest for the ultimate burger
and took the town's top
burgermeister hostage.
Our heroes decided to help the
missing Burgermon's family by
creating their own burger
masterpieces.
Fortunately, Tommy made a burger
the beasties liked, but
they liked it so much
they took Tommy, Zoe
and J.P. Away too.
But as usual, the kids saved
the day and reunited the
Burgermon family,
but Petaldramon
isn't finished yet.
THEME MUSIC: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned as we
work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
I am the one-- huh.
I am the one--
Digimon.
We're the rhythm
united as one--
Digimon.
Together the battles are won--
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
Everyone for one world, there's
a world for us all.
We're all for one world, there's
I am the one--huh.
I am the one--
Digimon!
-One, two, three, four-- use
Digi kids to mop the floor.
Five, six, seven, eight--
they're the kids
I just don't like.
-Thou has more enthusiasm
than wit.
-Thanks, there Mercurymon.
It's like I always say, a little
training before saves a
lot of trouble after, right.
-Your diligence confirms your
allegiance, my piney partner.
-I know.
Lord Cherubimon wants me ready
at all times to serve up a
healthy helping of havoc.
-It plays warmly on my ears to
hear you speak thusly. 'Tis
truly most apt to call you
a legendary warrior.
-Yeah, well I'd love to chat
more, but I got some road work
to tend to, you understand?
Forget about it.
-Hmp.
Ahh-- victory.
Seraphimon's fractal code
and it's all mine!
With this there's only a few
ticks of time before the
digital world bows before me!
[evil laughter]
-But why is Cherubimon
coming here?
One of you two must
have messed up.
-Yeah, what are you
looking at me for?
I didn't do nothing, right?
-He's coming for the fractal
code, you nits!
Lord Cherubimon.
-Power is everything
and the only thing.
Greetings, my most faithful
followers.
It appears someone is missing.
-Indeed--
Duskmon is absent.
-He's flakier than pie crust.
-Don't worry.
He'll get his, right.
-And alas, Grumblemon has
fallen in battle.
-So he has.
It was the humans who sealed
his fate, was it not?
-Uh, [inaudible].
-He knows.
-But no matter.
With you, my three legendary
warriors, this entire world
will submit to my power.
[grunting]
-My lord and master, I humbly
give you all the fractal code
we have gathered thus far.
-Well, it's gratifying to see
how much you've compiled.
Well done my minions.
-We live to serve
you, mighty one.
-How disappointing that you
chose not to present me with
the most vital data you have,
Seraphimon's fractal code.
-Oh.
I--
I can explain.
[evil laughter]
-I see.
Consider that code a gift I may
demand to have returned
whenever I wish it.
[sighs]
-Beware, the earth children have
found their beast spirits
and their strength is growing.
-With all due respect, those
little rugrats can't hold a
candle to us.
We are the only true
legendary warriors.
-Then why have you been unable
to eliminate them?
-I-- um--
hmm--
-Grumblemon may not have
been able to handle
the job, but I will.
I'll make those human
kids the weeds and
I'm the weed whacker!
-Excellent, but don't fail me.
[nervous laughter]
-Wooo-wooo!
Well, whatever.
Blah, blah, blah.
Woo!
Blah.
-Oh, wow!
Check it out!
The Rose Morning Star's
gotta be close now.
-Yeah.
-Fantastico!
But it's mid day.
Are the clouds supposed
to be that dark?
-Uh.
Hey, Bokomon, what does this
book have to say about this
area?
-Hmm, let's see.
I haven't found anything that--
[gasps]
[screaming]
-All right.
Who was the nimrod who slammed
on the brakes?
-That'd be me, blue boy.
End of the line.
-That can't be right.
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
-It looks like the tracks
don't stop for miles.
-How observant of you.
Look, if I say it's the
end of the line, it's
the end of the line.
Go on. Get out. Get lost.
-Kogi, how did you ever
race with this guy?
-You can't do this!
We have Digirail passes!
-Yeah, yeah.
Write it down.
You'll sell millions.
Look, you want to go, then go!
I ain't stopping you!
[screaming]
-Let me be the first one to
wish you the best of luck.
You're gonna need it!
-I would have to admit, I've
been dumped before but never
quite like that.
[grunts]
-So everyone in one piece?
-Yeah.
Aren't there any normal
trailmon?
-I think I popped a waistband.
-Bokomon.
-Welcome to the Dark Gate.
ALL: Huh?
-That temple-like structure
behind you is the Dark Gate,
through it lies the Continent
of Darkness.
[gasping]
-Why do I get a feeling that's
not a good thing?
-Is it as bad as it sounds?
-I wish I could tell you, but
to be honest, I have no idea
what awaits us there.
It's an eerie land shrouded
in utter darkness, but the
dangers it holds are as
legendary as its mysteries.
-There's got to be something
written in the book about it.
-Well, let's take
a look shall we.
Continent of Darkness,
Chapter 12.
-Whoa, it's pitch black.
-How come?
-It appears that there's
really no firsthand
information on this place.
Many a brave Digimon have
ventured within, but it seems
none of them have ever returned
to tell of its secrets.
-Whoa.
-Only the foolhardy would
dare enter the
Continent of Darkness.
We'll have to find another
route to the Rose Morning
Star.
-But the shortest route
is straight ahead!
Nothing ventured, nothing
gained, right?
-Uh-huh!
-Uh, I think we should
take a vote.
-Agreed.
-You know, when all of us work
as a team, we've overcome some
pretty tough stuff.
So what's the point in backing
off here and giving up?
-Yeah, if something major
happens we'll just spirit
evolve.
-There isn't any trouble
that we can't handle.
-Exactly.
We're the five legendary
warriors who stopped
Grumblemon and that guy
was no pushover.
-You guys know I'm in.
-Well, we took a vote.
Motion carried.
[gasping]
-Move out!
-But what about me and
Seraphimon's egg?
Naimon!
-Don't forget to write!
[grunting]
-I know I'm going
to regret this!
Oh, wait for me!
[eerie music playing]
[moaning]
-Shh.
-I'm wondering, do you think
Digimon could somehow end up
being ghosts?
-What kind of talk is that?
Next you'll start telling
ghost stories.
-It was a dark and stormy night,
luckily there was this
terrific guy there waiting
to come to your rescue.
-Give me a break.
[gasping]
-Uhh.
Tommy, it's just the wind.
[moaning]
-Sorry about that.
-No problem.
[grunting]
-Stop acting like my
Aunt Mabel's dog!
-Aunt Mabel's dog would have
turned tail and gone by now!
-We're not going back!
We've all been walking
for hours!
-Let's walk back a few hours
and then we can all get
ourselves out of this poor
excuse for a dark closet once
and for all.
-Aw.
Hey-- hey, guys.
-Something's glowing.
[grunts]
-Fireflies?
-Maybe there's a town up ahead.
-Come on.
Let's check it out!
[grunts]
-How did he know?
How could Cherubimon divine that
I possessed Seraphimon's
fractal code?
-Uh-huh.
-I will not be made
sport of, Duskmon!
-I was clearing my throat.
-'Tis unlikely!
-Well, aren't you
self-centered.
-Master Cherubimon noted
your absence at
the meeting he requested.
-Just because Cherubimon gets
you three to obey his requests
doesn't mean that you are
truly loyal to him.
-Bite your tongue!
-Do you deny it?
-You dare to question our
loyalty, you jackanapes.
You who have never even set
foot on the battlefield.
Well, perhaps the little humans
be too much for you?
-I see what you're doing,
getting Ranamon and Arbormon
to do the menial labor while
you wait for the
right moment to strike!
-Those are strong words
for someone whose
actions are so weak!
You are a coward!
Leaving to mope, you
mollycoddle.
He knoweth too much.
I must keep my guard up against
this treasonist toadie.
-Maybe I should get
out and fight.
After all, those young
humans are
becoming quite an annoyance.
They need to be restrained.
[panting]
-Whoa!
Look at that!
-That moss is actually
glowing.
Wonder if it's safe to touch?
-Let's see.
Sure is.
We can use it to light our way.
Ha-ha.
-Wow!
This stuff works great!
-Look, it's a cave.
-It's almost too perfect, like
it was dug out by someone.
-Or dug out by something.
-Hey!
Anybody in there?
-I guess not.
-Whoa!
[moaning]
-Pokemon, what is it?
-I feel like this place is a
ghost cavern full of evil
ectoplasmic dishy spirits.
I knew I should have
stayed behind, but
did I listen to myself?
No.
-Huh?
-Did you guys see that?
-Who's there?
Show yourself!
(OFFSCREEN): Show yourself!
-What are you, a parrot?
(OFFSCREEN): What are
you, a parrot?
What are you, a parrot?
-Knock it off!
(OFFSCREEN): Knock it off!
Knock it off!
-Ooh-hoo!
They'll mock us 'til
we all go insane!
We're doomed!
Doomed I tell you!
-Hey, I know.
Beetles battle better
in butter!
(OFFSCREEN): Beetles battle
better in butter!
-Just as I thought.
-That's great.
Do you want to clue us in?
-They're repeating what we say
so let's confuse them with
tongue twisters.
-Uh-- kay.
Sick, sick bricks might
bring back a snack!
(OFFSCREEN): Sick, sick bricks
might bring back a snack.
-Peter Piper poked and picked
a pack of pickled peppers.
(OFFSCREEN): Peter Piper poke
and picked a pack of pickled
peppers.
-Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boy, oui-- ahh!
(OFFSCREEN): Toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy
boy, oui-- ahh!
-It's no use.
We just can't trip them up.
-Oh, yeah?
-My goodness.
Those creatures are pipsmon.
They're mutant Digimon whose
power is greatest in the dark.
They can reflect the sound back
exactly as it's heard.
ALL: Oh.
-Hmm.
-For cave dwelling Digimon,
they're really rather gentle
even if they are a bit
scary looking.
-Well, just between us, I think
they're kind of cute.
-I think they're kind of cute.
I think they're kind of cute.
-I'm amazed to find peaceful
Digimon in such a dark place.
-So, I guess it turns out
you're glad you came?
-What?
-You just learned something.
If you hadn't come, you'd never
have known about this.
It's good that you
took a risk.
-If you're not sure about
something, there's really only
one way to find out--
that's to take a risk and go
experience it for yourself.
-Well, bless my buttons.
You're right.
-Why don't you write it
down in the book?
You'll be the first Digimon
to chronicle the
Continent of Darkness.
You'll be famous.
-Uh.
Well, I--
Really?
-Sure, and since you're writing
about Digimon, maybe
you could write about us--
The True Adventures of the
Legendary Warrior.
You can say how I controlled
my beast spirit.
-I'd like to be mentioned.
You can write about
my cool hat!
-And mention how
fearless I am!
-All right then, I'll do it!
Today I'll begin the greatest
novel of all time, The
Legendary Warriors of the
Continent of Darkness.
-So, will you write
about me as well?
-Oh, I think not!
-Aw.
[laughter]
-Well, a great novelist needs
great material so let's
continue our journey
into the unknown.
-Sounds great!
ALL: Let's go!
[screaming]
[coughing]
-You's and your journey about
to be cut short, small fry.
-Yeah, says who?
-Take a guess!
[gasps] -Ooh!
Not Arbormon again!
-Good guess!
[evil laughter]
-Power pummel!
[fighting]
-Oh, yeah!
View the power, baby!
Oh, yeah!
It's good!
-Uh!
-No way!
-That was an appiteaser!
You kids are the main course!
Open my slide evolution,
Petaldramon.
[growling]
[screaming]
-Right, let's do it!
[music playing]
ALL: Execute the spirit
evolution!
[music playing]
-BurningGreymon!
-KendoGarurumon!
[music playing]
[screaming]
-MetalKabuterimon!
[music playing]
[screaming]
-Zephyrmon.
[music playing]
[screaming]
-Korikakumon!
[groans]
-You know what I think?
It's petal pulling time!
Petaldramon, you're all
bark and no bite!
[fighting]
-Man, talk about getting
fiber in your diet.
[groaning]
-Oh!
It looks like Petaldramon
is growing into
a king sized pest!
-He looks cool!
-He is not cool!
-Yeah!
Eating good makes you grow
up big and strong, right?
-Right!
Follow thunder!
[moaning]
-My turn!
Ahh!
-Oh, boy!
[growling]
-Pyro barrage.
[battle sounds]
[grunts]
-Plasma pods!
-Come here!
[grunting]
-Throwing star!
[fighting]
-Frozen arrowheads!
(OFFSCREEN): Five legendary
warriors and that's the best
they can do?
[fighting]
-Hornjab, baby!
-Leap cyclones!
-Hang on, guys!
Wildfire tsunami!
[fighting]
[moaning]
-Giving beast spirits to you
puny humans is like giving
piles to pigs!
So why don't you just do
yourselves a favor
and hand them over?
[grunting]
-Never!
-If you want these spirits, then
you're going to have to
come here and take them!
-Hmp!
Right!
Lupine laser!
[moaning]
-Electron can!
[fighting]
-Wildfire tsunami!
-Hurricane gal!
[moaning]
-KendoGarurumon slide
evolution, Lobomon.
-Heldramon, it's
kindling time!
Fractal code digitized!
-Lobomon did it!
-Now he's cool!
-Arbormon, now will you
give up attacking us?
-Well, I, uh--
-Yes.
-Huh?
-He will.
-Uh, Duskmon.
-Who is that?
-Well, here comes the cavalry.
A friend in need's a friend
indeed, right?
-Wrong, with your beast spirit
gone there's really no use for
you now, is there?
-What are you talk-- aww!
[gasps]
-Yesterday's outlaw
is today's enemy.
[screaming]
-He destroyed his own friend!
-Okay, I'm confused.
Just which side is this
guy on anyway?
Guess we'll find out on the
next "Digimon Digital
Monsters!"