NARRATOR: Feeling guilty about
what happened to his friends,
Takuya took DarkTrailmon
back to the real world.
But on the way home, he turned
into this freaky half human,
half Digimon.
Talk about an identity crisis.
Then to make matters worse,
Takuya returned to the same
day he left for the
Digital World.
Thinking everything would go
back to normal if he never
left, Takuya tried to stop
himself from getting on the
train, but Duskmon kept
getting in the way.
Takuya finally realized he
couldn't run from his fears,
so he decided to go back
to the Digital
World to face the music.
But something tells me
this time, things
are gonna be different.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-mooh-ah!
Huh!
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Digimon!
-(THINKING) Everyone's gone.
How could they have
survived this?
Ugh.
Guys, I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
My plan was useless.
Koji was right.
I risked everyone's lives.
I have to find them.
Tommy!
Koji!
Zoe!
J.P.!
Bokomon, Neemon, anyone!
-I don't get it.
Why didn't Duskmon finish me
off when he had the chance?
Huh?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Stop!
Leave that alone.
-Hey stop messing around
with our D-Tectors.
-Hm.
-Come on.
Give them back to us.
-Hm.
-You'll break them!
-I'm warning you!
-Stop it!
-Execute now!
Yes.
No.
Aw, man.
What's the use?
-Don't say that.
We can't give up now.
I'm sure Koji or Takuya will
find a way to save us.
-We have to believe in them.
-I want to, but it's hard.
-What's the good word?
Have you pried loose
the spirit?
-Mm mm, mm mm.
-T'would be well for you
children to reconsider and
give us what we seek.
-Forget it, metal head.
We're not telling you anything,
not today, not
tomorrow, not ever.
So you might as well just let
us down before we get mad.
-Oh, I don't think so.
Mercurymon, can't I squash
just one of them?
All of this whining's giving
me a headache.
-Patience, my anxious urchin.
Methinks thine humor
ill received.
No.
We shall use these three
as bait to lure the
other two out of hiding.
-Oh, but sugar, aren't
you sick of waiting?
It'd be faster to just make
them tell us where their
friends are right now.
-I fear it will be a fool's
errand, m'lady,
but do as you wish.
-Oh, goody goody.
-What are those?
-Not goody.
-Oh, this won't hurt a bit.
-What are you doing?
And now the fun begins.
-No!
No!
Not the belly button.
No, stop it.
Haha haha.
Come on, seriously, cut it out.
-Zoe.
-Ha ha ha!
-Tommy!
-All right, Slim.
Give us your spirits and tell us
where your friends are, or
the tickling continues.
-Do your worst.
I can take it.
-All right, you asked for it.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Ah!
You're mad, Ranamon.
Mad!
-Come on, guys.
Where are you?
Where'd everybody go?
Huh?
Wow.
Nothing.
That's weird.
I could have sworn
it was raining.
Huh?
How is this possible?
It's like I knew that it
was going to rain.
I can feel the power
of nature.
Everything's finally starting
to make sense.
Ophanimon told me that coming
here was my destiny.
It's funny.
I had always felt that I was
meant to do something special,
and when I stood in that circle,
surrounded by light, I
thought I knew it was.
I remember that first moment
when the power of Agunimon was
coursing through me.
I felt as if I could
do anything.
There wasn't anyone
who could beat me.
I knew that I was going to save
the digital world and
destroy any evil Digimon
that tried to stop me.
Battle after battle, my strength
grew, and so did my
confidence.
But that was the problem.
I was so wrapped up in myself,
I never realized what being a
Digimon was all about.
There was no connection
between me and the
world around me.
But now there is, and
I won't forget it.
-'Tis but a matter of
moments 'ere your
spirits shall be mine.
Why not save yourselves
from this misery and
tell us what we wish.
-Huh?
-I don't know where they are,
but sooner or later, they'll
show up, and then you'll pay.
I promise you.
-Now that's funny.
-Oh.
-Ha ha hee haha.
Stop it!
Ah hahaha.
Come on.
-Don't make me come down
off this wall!
-A force field?
If I could just get
through that.
Then I could get
the D-Tectors.
But there's five of them
and only one of me.
[laughter]
-Now, you're gonna tell
me what I wanna know.
-I already told you,
I don't know.
-I can't just sit here
and do nothing.
-Ah!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Oh dear.
It's coming back.
Please don't hurt me.
Can't you see I'm with egg?
Take my friend.
He's a bit annoying, but
a good listener.
-What did you say?
I wasn't listening.
-You two are funny.
Will you be my friends?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Sepikmon.
This lonely Digimon has no
friends and spends all his
time throwing his spirit
boomerang to himself.
-We'd love to be your friend.
-Then let's dance!
-I can't dance.
I have no rhythm and
two left feet.
-Well, you have to dance,
or we can't be friends.
What's it gonna be,
boogie or bye bye?
-B-But I never learned
how to boogie.
-Then bye bye.
-Are you guys OK?
-Where have you been?
-Yeah, we missed you.
-I missed you too.
Where is everyone?
-After the fierce battle with
Duskmon, they were captured by
Mercurymon and Ranamon.
J.P., Zoe, and Tommy are all
trapped, poor things.
And Duskmon's disappeared.
-Where's Koji?
-I don't know, do I?
SEPIKMON (OFFSCREEN):
Excuse me.
Could I have my boomerang
back?
That depends.
Will you be more careful
with it?
-Huh?
What do you mean more careful?
It's a boomerang.
I through it and
it comes back.
I'm confused.
-Just watch where you
throw it, pal.
You could hurt someone.
-Mhmm.
-Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to hurt anyone.
I just wanted some friends.
Friends.
-Maybe you're just trying
too hard, buddy.
Be yourself, you know?
See ya.
-You mean people will like
me if I'm just myself?
-Well, of course.
-Does that mean that you guys
would really be my friends?
-Sure, why not?
-Ooga chaka.
Ooga chaka.
Mercurymon has our other
friends, right?
Well, maybe I can help
you find them.
-What do you mean?
-Just follow my spirit
boomerang.
It should lead you
right to them.
-We will, thank you.
-Aren't you forgetting
someone?
-Wait for us!
-Goodbye my new friends,
and good luck!
-Come on, talk already.
-What news, m'lady?
-Zero, hun.
I don't think they're quite
getting the message.
Is it all right if
I do something
a little more drastic?
-Do as you wish.
-You, sweet thing!
-Ah!
No, not Zoe.
-Let's see how pretty you are
when you're squashed like a
bug.
-Let's not.
-Ah!
-Leave her alone, fish face.
Take me instead.
-J.P., don't.
-No one touches Zoe while I'm
around, right, my little
snuggie pie?
-Oh, J.P.
-Snoogie woogie face.
-J.P.!
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Pay attention, son.
I'm trying to threaten
you here.
Hello.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): What
are you doing?
-I was just--
it's a long story.
-Don't worry, precious.
I'll get to your little
girlfriend soon enough.
No offense, but I'm saving
the best for last.
Dark Vapor.
-Stop it.
-Leave him alone!
-Oh man, this has got
to be a dream.
A really bad dream!
-Stop!
OK, we'll talk!
-Ah!
-J.P.!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Lobomon!
-Wha?
-It's Lobomon.
-That is no way to
treat a lady.
Didn't your parents teach
you any manners?
-And so, the fourth
hath joined us.
-Hang on, you guys.
We're coming!
-Hehe heheheh.
-Enough.
-They can't be much further.
(THINKING) Please
let them be all right.
Lobo Kendo!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): I'm
getting shoulder sick.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Who cares?
My baby's half scrambled.
-I think not.
Dark Reflection!
-Ah!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Wee,
I'm all dizzy.
-Heh heh.
-Hi honey!
Acid Ink!
-Yeah, you're quite a lady.
-So, where are they?
Lobomon!
-Oh my.
He's taking on Mercurymon and
Calmaramon all by himself.
-Bokomon, why are the others
stuck to that wall?
-They've been captured,
you witless nit.
-Guys!
-Wait!
-Howling Laser!
-Lobomon needs our help!
-But what can we do?
-Man, if only we could
Spirit Evolve.
Hey, you better not throw
our D-Tectors in there.
-Now what?
-I'm gonna need a plan.
-Tell me something.
It's obvious you don't care
about yourself, but can you
promise me the others
won't get hurt?
If you can't, then we'd better
just go home now, because I
won't let you risk
their lives.
-I'm gonna need to do
this carefully.
-That would be nice.
-I can't just jump in without
thinking first.
Tommy and the others can't
Spirit Evolve, and if those
two goons get their hands
on them, they
won't stand a chance.
I'll need Lobomon's help.
-I think he might need yours.
Look!
-Hurry, Takuya.
Hurry.
Run like the wind.
-Oh sweetie, don't tell me your
done playing with me.
-Maybe the poor lad just needs
a bit of refreshment.
-You are so thoughtful.
One drink of water
coming right up.
Draining Rain!
-All right.
I want you two to stay here.
-But what are you gonna do?
-Wait until the time is right.
-Well, when is that?
So, we ran all this way and my
tummy got upset for nothing?
-All right, quiet please.
I have a feeling Takuya
is right.
-Really?
OK.
-(THINKING) That smell.
The sound.
The atmosphere is changing.
-This doesn't seem like
Takuya at all.
It's as if he's become
different somehow.
-A storm is coming.
-What kind of storm?
-I don't know.
(THINKING) I thought Takuya
had some sort of plan.
He certainly thought about
it long enough.
But now I'm not so sure.
All this waiting and wondering
about the weather.
Who cares about the weather?
The others are in danger.
-Have you no control?
-Why are you mad at me?
It was your idea.
-Ugh, I'm surrounded
by buffoons.
-Lobomon!
-Give me your best shot.
-As you wish.
Ha ha ha.
-Look there is a storm.
-(THINKING) Wind.
I'm getting stronger.
-Well, what do you know?
Takuya was right.
-Yes, but how could
he have known?
-(THINKING) And a little snow.
Right now!
-You're freaking me out.
-Oh, that's cold.
-Wind and snow.
Thunder and lightning.
Forces of nature lend
us your strength!
-He's talking to the weather
and it's listening.
-Now I understand what it
means to be a Digimon!
I'm ready to accept the
responsibility that comes with
great power.
To truly become Agunimon,
Warrior of Flame!
-Had enough?
-Leave him alone!
-Oh, can it.
At least, the final player
hath arrived.
-Then let's get this
show on the road.
-Pyro Dirt.
-Missed me, missed me,
now you gotta k--
-Thanks, but no thanks.
-That little whelp is much
stronger than I remember.
-Pyro Tornado!
Now Lobomon, free the others!
-Lobo Kendo!
-All right, guys.
It's your turn.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Beetlemon!
-Kozemon!
-Kumamon.
-Ah, isn't this sweet?
Together at last.
I love reunions.
Ha ha.
It appears it's time for the
final act of our little play.
-I should put on something
more appropriate.
Ranamon Slide Evolution!
Calmaramon!
-You don't really think
you can win?
Haven't you heard?
It's not nice to mess
with Mother Nature!
-Let's finish this.
Thunder Fist!
-Tempest Twist!
-Argh, what is going on?
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Ah!
-Lobo Kendo!
-How did y'all get so strong?
-We have a stronger ally than
you could ever imagine.
-Odds bodkins!
They're using the forces
of nature to
amplify their attacks.
The master will be displeased.
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Forget the master!
What about us?
-Will you stop sniveling,
woman?
-Argh!
You won't defeat
us ever again!
[screaming]
-Ah, I just love the theater.
Takuya
-Takuya, my boy.
You've matured.
-Well, now what do we do?
-Retreat and regroup.
-You little brats.
This isn't over!
-Yeah!
-That is the last time that I
listen to you, Mercurymon.
You should've let
me squash them.
-The little humans are smarter
than I thought, but fret not,
m'lady, for within me,
a plan is hatching.
All we need is a more
advantageous location to spin
our web of woe.
-I'm so sorry, you guys.
This was all my fault.
-What are you talking about?
You're the one who rescued us.
-But--
-It's OK, Takuya.
We were worried about you, but
I knew you'd come through.
-I guess I really owe
you one, Koji.
-Nah, all of us owe Takuya.
You've really changed.
-Yeah.
I hardly recognize myself.
-Huh?
-I don't feel like
a kid anymore.
I think I finally understand
what being a
Digimon is all about.
We're in for an amazing ride.
All of us.
NARRATOR: Wow, who ever thought
Takuya would be the
responsible one?
Well, you live and learn on
Digimon, Digital Monsters.