NARRATOR: Bokomon took the gang
to get their futures told
by Shamanmon the fortuneteller,
but just as
Shamanmon started the
Premonition Tango, Grumblemon
attacked, and this time
he brought a friend.
With the strength of Golemon
behind him, Grumblemon stole
Tommy's spirit, then
BurningGreymon joined the
fight, but he didn't know the
difference between good guys
and bad guys.
Goggle head figured out that it
was Shamanmon possessed by
a Beast Spirit, but when he
freed Shamanmon, the Beast
Spirit possessed him, instead.
When he started attacking his
friends, Koji had to digivolve
to KendoGarurumon to stop him.
Man, did these guys have
control issues or what?
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[music playing]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we head for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
there's a wold for us all.
Digimon!
-Takuya, stop!
-Put me down!
[screaming]
-There has to be a
way to stop him.
-But how?
-Isn't there anything
we can do?
-Yes.
Get out of here before
it's too late.
KENDOGARURUMON (OFFSCREEN):
All right.
If it's a fight you
want, fight me!
-Don't look at me!
-Is he really going to
try to fight him?
What if they hurt each other?
-Lupine Laser!
[shouting]
-Not so fast!
Come on, before one
of us gets hurt!
-Pyro Barrage!
-We have to do something before
he levels the whole
forest, or the whole world.
-I'll stop him.
-Howling Star!
-You were supposed to stop him,
not help wreck the place!
-If we ever have to fight
trees, he'll be deadly.
-Then count your blessings
we're not trees.
Let's go.
-(THINKING) If I could only
Spirit Evolve to Kumamon.
-Crystal Breeze!
-(THINKING) But I can't.
-Tommy, this is no time
for daydreaming.
Come on.
-Oh, man.
If he keeps this up, they're
going to have to rename it the
Burnt to a Crisp Kingdom.
-Takuya, don't!
It's me!
TAKUYA (THINKING): Wait.
What am I doing?
-I can't believe this is how
I'm gonna check out.
Gotta stay calm.
Stay in control.
TAKUYA (THINKING): These
guys are my friends.
I have to keep reminding
myself that.
Wait a second.
If they are my friends, why
are they attacking me?
Maybe they are the enemy.
[roaring]
-What a horrible noise.
It doesn't even sound
human at all.
-Well, of course not.
That's why they call
it a Beast Spirit.
Isn't it obvious?
-But it's like Takuya
isn't even in there.
Can't we help him?
-Not really.
He has to learn to control the
Beast Spirit on his own.
Sooner or later, he will.
-It's the later part
I'm worried about.
[shouting]
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): When's
sooner gonna get here?
-Back to the burning forest!
I can't believe I said that.
-(THINKING) I can't
keep running away.
Takuya needs me.
-This is going well.
-(THINKING) This is
just like before.
Back in the real world.
BOY (OFFSCREEN):
Come on, guys.
Knock it off!
Hey!
BOY (OFFSCREEN): Aw, did the
baby drop his books?
Next thing you know, he's
gonna fall down.
-Quit it!
[crying]
[laughter]
-You're a wimp, kid!
Look, there's another baby!
-Oh, no!
BOY (OFFSCREEN): Better
run, kid!
-(THINKING) But what can I do?
Those kids were bigger
than me, and
BurningGreymon is way bigger.
Takuya, no!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Tommy!
-(THINKING) I'm not just gonna
stand by this time.
Takuya!
Please, you've gotta
stop this!
Fight it, Takuya!
I know you don't want
to hurt any of us!
This isn't really you.
You're just out of control
and afraid.
[roaring]
-Takuya, listen to him!
-Come on, Taki.
It's us.
[roaring]
-Don't you get it?
We're your friends.
We're here to help you.
KENDOGARURUMON (OFFSCREEN):
Tommy!
-Takuya, wait a minute!
Don't you remember
what happened?
-Stop, Tommy!
-Frozen Tundra!
-Tommy, you have to stop this.
-My name is Kumamon, and you're
nothing but a big bully.
-No, you're wrong.
-Kumamon, you're under
the spell of
Bakemon's Nightmare Syndrome.
What you're feeling
isn't real.
You have to fight it!
-Agunimon, you're
not my enemy?
I learned that true courage
isn't paying bullies back.
It's just standing up to them.
You helped me see that fighting
back in fear is just
as bad as being a bully.
You can't let fear
control you.
You have to fight it.
I know you won't hurt me if you
remember we're friends.
TAKUYA (THINKING): Wait.
Tommy?
What was I going to do?
What did I do?
-Hey!
Wait!
[shouting]
[roaring]
[crying]
-(THINKING) I could have
destroyed them all.
Some DigiDestined I am.
-Um, Takuya, are you OK?
-I should be asking you that.
Thanks, Tommy.
-Oh, it was nothing.
But you're welcome.
-It wasn't nothing.
It was one of the bravest
things I've ever seen.
-Well, I owed you one.
Now we're even.
-Oh, the trials of friendship.
Take note, you two, for when
you get your Beast Spirits.
-Um, why don't you go first?
-Oh, no, you.
I insist.
-Yes, well, of course you still
have to get back those
spirits that you lost
to Grumblemon.
-Thanks for the reminder.
(THINKING) But what good does
it do us if we get all those
spirits back, and we can't
even control them?
-How are we going to find
Grumblemon, anyway?
-Jeez, it seems harder to avoid
him than to find him.
I think we should
just keep going.
I bet we'll run into him
sooner or later.
-Sounds good to me.
JP (OFFSCREEN): I knwo yo want
your spirit back, but how can
running into Grumblemon
sound good?
That's the dumbest thing
I ever heard.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): You better
hope you'll get your Beast
Spirit first, pal, because
I'm coming after
you when I get mine.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Now I know
what Bokomon meant by the
trials of friendship.
-The book says the roots make
the forest paths treacherous.
Oh, that's ridicu-- oh!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
check it out.
What's up with these roots?
Oh, do those symbol stands
for hugs and kisses?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
Like you'd know.
-Hey!
-It's like a maze.
-Well, not really.
All the roots connect.
-Well, make it a maze.
Everyone get your own
vine, and let's go.
-Cool, I'll take this one.
-And this one's mine.
-Ready? Set?
Go.
[laughter]
-We win!
-Yeah, so what's the big deal?
[shouting]
-Help me up!
-Stop struggling.
You're only gonna make
things worse.
-Easy for you to say.
-Here!
-About time.
-Look who here.
-It's Grumblemon!
No!
-Grumblemon yes!
And you just where I want you.
Ha ha ha!
Looks like you two won race.
Too bad winners now
big losers!
It's spirit taking time!
-Actually, I think it's getting
stuck in the mud time.
-You not quiet!
You learn hard way it really
hammer smashing time!
Got it?
And I'll take care of you!
-Why can't we just be friends?
-Quiet now!
No one give me much
trouble as you.
You know you lose.
Why not you play nice?
-So what?
We should just hand
over our spirits?
Forget it.
That's never going to happen,
especially now that I have my
Beast Spirit!
-Now, why me not
afraid of that?
-Well, you should, because
it's very powerful!
-Only powerful if you can
control, and I betting that
you not learn yet, or why
you look so afraid.
See, you tell me all
I need know.
-Hurry!
-Execute!
Slide Evolution!
Gigasmon!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Agunimon!
-Hasn't the forest had
enough fire today?
-Right!
Quagmire Twister!
[shouting]
-Whoa!
-Agunimon!
Ah!
-Gigasmon, put him down!
-If you want him, you
have come take him!
-Don't worry, we're fine now.
I mean, we're kind
of stuck here.
-OK.
GIGASMON (OFFSCREEN): If play
hide and seek, you really need
seek, you know?
-Tommy!
-Not bad.
Course, not good, either.
-When I get my hands on you!
-No!
-Agunimon!
[screaming]
-Yeah, you tough guy.
Ha ha ha!
-No!
This is gonna hurt!
-Oh, no!
-Oh, my!
-I was right.
-Takuya!
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
But Tommy's still in trouble,
and I don't
know how to save him.
-Looks like a Human Spirit
just can't compete with a
Beast Spirit.
You back to turn into
BurningGreymon.
-But I can't.
What if I lose control again?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Don't
be afraid.
Just remember what Tommy said.
-Huh?
-I learned that true courage
isn't paying bullies back,
it's just standing up to them.
You helped me see that fighting
back in fear is just
as bad as being a bully.
You can't let fear
control you.
You have to fight it.
I know you won't hurt me if you
remember we're friends.
-Wait.
Tommy?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Remember
who your friends are,
and you'll be fine.
-What?
Not want to help friend?
-Tommy!
-Ha ha ha!
Play time over, now
give me spirit.
You hurry, maybe you save him.
-No, don't do it, Takuya!
Don't trade your
spirit for me!
It's OK. I'm not afraid!
No!
GIGASMON (OFFSCREEN): Hm.
Some friend you be.
Won't even give up Beast
Spirit to save friend.
-I'm not afraid of you!
-You should be.
[shouting]
-No!
Tommy!
That's it!
If Tommy can show courage
in the face of that
freak, then so can I!
-Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
[screaming]
-BurningGreymon!
-So, let's see if can control.
-Takuya!
-Whoa!
GIGASMON (OFFSCREEN):
Not going make it!
-Tommy, you OK?
-Yeah.
Hey, check it out!
You got control of your
Beast Spirit.
-Thanks to you, buddy.
-I'll help the others.
Now go get him!
-Right!
You're the one who likes
twisters, right?
Well, enjoy!
-That fun!
Now your turn!
-Pyro--
wait, I'll set fire to
the whole forest.
OK, I'll do it the old
fashioned way.
Execute!
Slide Evolution!
Agunimon!
I have to lead him away
from the others.
Tag, you're it!
What's the matter, slowpoke?
Can't you catch me?
Hey, Gigasmon.
You're not getting tired
now, are ya?
[panting]
-You gotta start working
out, buddy.
-Even if me tired, you still
get defeated good.
Did you forget me warrior
of earth?
-Actually, I did forget
about that.
-Tectonic Slam!
-Oh, man!
-Ha ha ha!
-What are you excited about?
You missed me, earth boy.
By the way, I think you
forgot something, too.
Execute!
Slide Evolution!
BurningGreymon!
Out here there's no forest
to catch fire.
-Uh-oh.
-Pyro Barrage!
Wildfire Tsunami!
-You did it!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Gigasmon's spirit.
-And now for Tommy's.
Here ya go, buddy.
Got a little present for ya.
-Hey, my spirit.
Yeah!
This is better than birthdays
and Christmas combine!
-And now to get Zoe's spirit.
-Hm?
-Me leave while behind!
-No!
He still has my spirit.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN): Can't
believe me get spirit taken.
Me make kids pay, and
pay big time.
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN): Goodie.
The beast with brains of dirt
has another incompetent plan.
Honey, you couldn't
outwit a nitwit.
-What?
Who there?
That you, Ranamon?
-How many warriors of
water do you know?
Now listen up, rockhead.
Stop sneaking around behind our
backs trying to impress
Cherubimon.
-You back off.
What I do no business of you.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Thou art mistaken.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Mercurymon.
Warrior of steel.
-Thy thoughtless acts reflect
badly upon us.
Thou should study an opponent
first, not just boorishly rush
into battle.
-Got that right.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Arbormon, warrior of wood.
-Yo, you want I should rough
'em up for ya's?
-Enough.
Our circle is complete.
-But Duskmon, warrior
of darkness--
-Oh, sugar, he wouldn't join
us in a million years.
-Forsooth.
He hath no heart for battle,
and does little more than
stare at the moons.
We shall rule this world, whilst
his only domain shall
be the world he sees when
he closeth his eyes.
[laughter]
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Me no get.
-Ugh, I'm surrounded
by buffoons.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Isn't
that pretty?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN):
Yeah, I guess.
-Come on, guys.
We've got a long road
ahead of us.
NARRATOR: That's for sure.
They barely beat Gigasmon,
and now there are
four other bad guys?
This could get ugly on the next
Digimon, Digital Monsters.