NARRATOR: After losing a fight
with Grumblemon and tumbling
down hole like Alice, you'd
think it couldn't get much
worse, right?
Wrong.
Takuya, Koji, and Tommy fell
into a world of living toys,
where they fought, and fought,
and fought with each other!
And then an overgrown teddy
bear working for the
ShadowToyAgumon captured
Tommy.
Takuya and Koji Spirit Evolved
and made quick work for the
bad toys, but when they got to
Tommy, they found him playing
with his captor.
Oh, well.
At least they all got a free
ride to the Forest Kingdom.
Now all they need to do is find
the rest of the gang.
Yeah, good luck.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
-The entrance to the Forest
Kingdom should come up after
this field.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Field?
This is more like a jungle.
-To succeed, one must
have faith.
One must stay positive.
One must--
JP (OFFSCREEN): Get
off my head.
-Hm?
-For a little guy,
you weigh a ton.
-Party pooper.
-Don't worry, Z. I'm sure
we'll find the way.
You want to know why?
-(SIGHING) Why?
-Because we're fighters,
that's why!
We don't give up, and
we never quit.
I give up.
I quit.
Ugh.
-What happened to that
fighting spirit?
-It got hungry.
-We'll take a break after we
get out of this field, OK?
-If I can make it that far.
-Now what?
We don't have time
to horse around.
Here.
-Huh?
Whoa!
What in Pete's name
is that thing?
-Tsunomon, come back
at once, young man.
I've had enough of your
shenanigans for one day!
Huh?
Oh, oh!
My goodness gracious, what
a lovely surprise.
You're humans.
-Human beings?
Aw, come on.
Let me go.
I'm never going back to
that nasty school.
-Huh.
I didn't know Digimon
had to go to school.
-That's where they learn the
skills they'll need as
full-grown Digimon.
-What kind of skills
do they learn?
Jumping and eating?
-How exciting.
I've never seen real
live humans before.
I know.
Why don't you come to
the school with us?
I'm sure the children would
love to meet you.
-Not me.
I'd rather go home.
I'd rather watch grass grow.
-We'd love to see the school,
but I'm afraid we don't have
time to stop and chat.
You see, we're headed for
the Forest Kingdom.
-This is an important mission,
one that cannot be delayed.
-You know, things to
do, people to see.
You understand.
-Oh, I was hoping you'd join us
for afternoon snack time.
-Afternoon snack time?
Why didn't you say so?
We are there, lady.
-JP, could you not think with
your stomach for once?
Of all the people I could be
stuck with, why'd it have to
be you?
-Because it was written
in the stars?
-Save it.
-That's the Digimon
school over there.
-Huh.
-That's it?
It looks like one of
the houses the
three little pigs built.
I've seen garages bigger
than that.
-JP!
Keep your voice down.
-(SINGING) Welcome, humans, to
our school where we learn and
play all day.
We think our teacher's really
cool, so we hope
you'll want to stay.
Welcome, humans, to our school
where we learn the Digi-Rule.
Stay and play, that
would be cool!
-You are so cute.
-Huh.
-YukimiBotamon, if I've told
you once, I've told you a
thousand times!
Don't ice the visitors.
I am so sorry.
-Oh, it's OK.
-I'm sorry.
-Poor thing.
Did I frighten you?
-Yeah.
Just a little bit.
-Hah.
I was all by myself when
I ran into the humans,
and I wasn't scared.
Not even a little.
-Whatever.
-Show-off.
-Kids today.
So young.
So mean.
But with proper guidance, that's
they'll love school as
much as I did.
-Didn't you get tied
to a flagpole?
-That was a rumor.
-Storytime!
Class, we're in for a
real treat today.
Instead of a regular old story,
our human guests will
tell us all about the wonders
of the human world.
Would you like that?
-Yes, please!
-Yeah!
-Well, perhaps the big blue
human would like to go first?
-Do you mean me?
The name's JP.
-Very well, Professor JP.
The class is yours.
-Professor?
I'm no professor.
I'm only in the seventh grade.
-Oh, don't be so modest.
Your class awaits, professor.
-Professor.
CHILDREN (OFFSCREEN): Professor,
professor!
Yay!
JP (OFFSCREEN): (THINKING)
All right.
Just stay calm.
How hard can this be?
They're just a bunch
of little kids.
I mean, they're so little, they
don't even have feet.
Here goes nothing.
So, uh, the human world has a
lot of cool things, like, um,
pinkies to wipe your
nose with.
If you had those.
And toothpaste that
fights plaque.
Awesome stuff, am I right?
-These kids need leadership.
Children, I am Bokomon.
I am here to talk to all of you
about the responsibilities
of a young Digimon.
One day you will evolve
into a big, strong
Digimon like myself.
You'll join the effort to
restore the Digital World to
its glory, and like the
legendary warriors of yore, we
shall prevail!
Oh?
Hm.
Where did they go?
-I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry.
Please--
-So young, so mean.
-[chattering]
TOGEMON (OFFSCREEN): Recess!
-That was fun!
-Let's go again!
-So tell me, what do you
guys want to play now?
-Digi-Wrestling,
Digi-Wrestling,
Digi-Wrestling, yeah!
-That sounds great!
-Galactica Manum Tail!
-Oh, you got me that time.
-Hey, buddy.
Tsunomon, what are you doing?
Why don't you come over
and hang with us?
CHILDREN (OFFSCREEN): Not him!
-Hey, guys.
Where are you off to?
-Fine.
I didn't really want to play
with those losers, anyway.
Digi-Wrestling is lame.
-I just don't get it.
-Way to go, JP.
-What?
We were having fun.
I didn't want him to
feel left out.
-Not everyone wants to
be part of the fun!
-So, what's gotten into you?
TOGEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Time for P.E.
[whistle blowing]
-I can't tell which is the ball
and which are the kids.
-I'm open.
Pass it here, Kapurimon.
Aw, hey.
-Atomic Bomber Tail!
-Whoa!
-Ha ha!
What did you do that for?
[crying]
-Whoa.
-Kapurimon, are you OK?
-But I'm the one who got hit.
-Poor Tsunomon.
I don't get why the other kids
won't play with him.
-They all probably think he
doesn't fit in with them.
I know just how he feels.
-You?
I would have guessed you were
the most popular girl in
school, Zoe.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN):
You'd be wrong.
-Hey, Zoe.
You wanna come to the
bathroom with me?
-I don't need to.
You can go by yourself,
can't you?
-Yeah, I guess I could go.
-These dolls are so
totally cute!
-Hey, Zoe.
You should get one, too.
We're both gonna buy one.
-I don't think so.
It's not really my thing.
-What a snob.
-I guess everyone thought
I was uppity
because I lived abroad.
-Well, where did you live?
-Italy.
My family lived there since
I was a little girl.
We moved to Japan a year ago.
-Wow, Italy, huh?
That sounds pretty cool.
-Tell that to my classmates.
They just want me to
act like them.
-Well, then act like them.
It can't hurt if it helps
you make friends, right?
-JP, I won't pretend
to be someone I'm
not just to be popular.
-Yeah, I guess that
would hurt.
-Still, no one likes
to feel lonely.
-Snack-time!
All right now, everyone.
You know the drill.
Open wide!
-Ahh!
-Here they come.
-Does that include us, too?
-I guess.
-Togemon Jab!
-Yum!
-Huh?
-Hey, come on.
Chin up there, little guy.
I'll bet I have just the
thing to cheer you up.
Everybody, listen up.
-Huh?
-I have a bar of chocolate here
for anyone who will play
with Tsunomon.
-You doofus!
You can't just bribe
kids like that.
-Why not?
I mean, what's the big deal?
-Because, you just can't!
-Thanks a lot.
Now I'm the freak that those
guys won't play with even if
you pay them.
-We wouldn't play with
Tsunomon, anyway.
He's not like us.
-Got that right.
-Mm-hm.
-Children, how could you?
-That poor little guy.
-Mm-hm.
-Man.
Now what have I done?
-Tsunomon!
Come back!
Just hear us out!
-Or at least slow down!
Come on, buddy!
-Tsunomon, please!
-I just want to be left alone!
Leave me alone!
-Your plan to get him friends
totally backfired.
Nice going.
Tsunomon!
-Aw, come on, kid.
Let me make it up to ya.
[shouting]
-It's Tsunomon!
-Yeah, he's over there!
-I can't get out!
Help me!
-Tsunomon!
-I'm coming!
-What are you gonna do?
[shouting]
-Hold on!
Just a little more.
I've almost got you.
-'Atta way, Zoe!
What do I do now?
Huh?
-OK, boys.
No peeking.
-Wow, I didn't know you
could Digivolve.
-I sure wish I couldn't.
It's been nothing but a royal
pain in the neck.
-Aw, come on.
You don't really mean that.
-Yes I do.
-What should we do?
-I don't think I can reach it.
-Hey, guys.
Don't worry.
I can get it down.
-Whoa!
-Check it out.
I can Digivolve.
Is this cool, or what?
There, piece of cake.
Huh?
What's wrong?
So I Digivolved to help them get
their ball back, but all
they saw as a big,
freaky monster.
Now they won't even play with
me because they're afraid.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I
wasn't afraid.
I don't know what would have
happened if you hadn't
Digivolved and pulled
me out of the water.
You saved my life.
Thanks, Tsunomon.
-Now, what do you say we
get back to the others?
-Yeah, maybe there will
be more snacks.
[thunder rolling]
Uh-oh.
-Oh, perfect.
And I just got my
clothes all dry.
Are you kidding?
You use electric attacks
all the time.
You can't be afraid
of lightning.
-I'm different when
I'm a Digimon.
Haven't you figured
that out yet?
Ah!
-Really, JP.
Just when I thought you couldn't
get anymore quirky.
-This isn't good.
-Huh?
-I gotta get back to school.
-Tsunomon?
Hey, what's the big hurry?
The water's so high.
-No kidding.
-Miss Togemon said when it
rained this hard before, the
water overflowed and
flooded the school.
If it keeps up, they'll
all be washed away.
-Washed away?
JP, we've got to do something.
-We have to Spirit Evolve.
-Huh?
-We'll get to them
faster if we fly.
Then we can use our combined
strength to try to save the
school from the floodwaters.
-Good thinking, JP.
Mm-hm.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Beetlemon!
-Kazemon!
-You Digivolved.
Awesome.
-Oh, I wish I knew that Tsunomon
was all right.
-Well, if my eyes don't
deceive me,
they're coming back.
And they've brought Tsunomon
with them.
-Oh!
-Oh, my.
I didn't know humans
could Digivolve.
-Uh, hello?
A little help?
-Here you go, kid.
-Thanks a lot, Beetlemon.
-We'll have to divert the water
with something big, like
one of those rocks.
If we work together, we should
be able to save the school.
-Why JP, you're pretty brave
when you want to be.
-Uh, thanks.
-Let's move it!
-I summon the power
of Thunder Fist!
All right, let's rock.
-I can't believe that JP and
Beetlemon are the same person.
He was scared before, and now
he's not afraid of anything.
-Now tell me, where would
you like this?
-How about a little
to the left?
-You've got it.
Hey, Z, a little help?
-At your service.
Hurricane Wave!
-They did it!
-Excellent work.
-Whoa!
-Kapurimon!
No!
[screaming]
-Help!
-Kapurimon!
Please, just hang on, dear!
I'm coming!
-Togemon, don't do it.
You'll be swept away.
The current's just too strong.
-But Kapurimon!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Tsunomon! Go get him!
-Huh?
-You're the only one
who can do it!
-I can't.
-You saved me.
You can do the same
for Kapurimon.
-Someone help!
-Tsunomon!
-You can do it!
-I can't hold on!
-Tsunomon!
-Tsunomon, Digivolve
to Gabumon!
Time for Blue Blaster!
It's OK, Kapurimon.
I'll get you back to
safety in no time.
-Oh, thanks, Tsunomon.
Thanks so much.
-Teach me to Digivolve!
-Gabumon, you were terrific!
-No kidding?
-Is that really you, Tsunomon?
-You mean I don't scare
you anymore?
-Not a bit.
-You were really awesome.
-We're sorry for being
scared of you.
-Aw, shucks, guys.
-Gabumon?
Thank you for saving me.
I can't wait for the time
I can Digivolve, too.
Hope I'm as cool as you are.
-Kapurimon.
You're making me blush.
-We made this boat for
you in craft class.
We hope it'll help you.
-Thank you, madame.
We'll get to the Forest
Kingdom in no time.
-And I won't have
to carry you.
-It was nice meeting
all of you.
-Hey, Tsunomon.
You're not afraid
to Digivolving
anymore, are you, buddy?
-Nope.
I'm gonna keep on Digivolving.
One day I'll be as strong as
the legendary warriors.
-Actually, Zoe and JP are
two of the legend--
-Bokomon!
-Zip it, would ya?
-Thanks for everything,
you guys.
-It was our pleasure.
-Bye!
-Thanks for the snacks!
-Be careful!
-I'm flying like a
mighty fruit bat.
Ha ha ha!
-This feels great.
-Yeah.
You know, I'm sure glad
those kids changed
their minds about Tsunomon.
-You want to know what else?
-Uh, sure, Zoe.
-I think I've changed my mind
about you a little, too.
-Really?
-Just a little.
-(THINKING) Tsunomon changed
peoples' minds about him by
showing his true colors.
Maybe I could do that.
-Oh.
Look, our comrades
have returned.
-What is that?
-It looks like a boat.
-It's Zoe and the others.
-Good timing.
NARRATOR: So JP redeemed
himself in the
eyes of fair Zoe.
Wonder how long that'll last?
Find out on the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.
(theme music)