NARRATOR: Koji confronted
Koichi, and the truth
finally came out.
They really are brothers!
Cherubimon used the darkness in
Koichi's heart to turn him
into Duskmon.
But after meeting his equally
tortured twin, Koichi realized
that darkness doesn't have
to be a bad thing.
Then Cherubimon came after the
Digigang to coax Koichi back.
But the kid's change of heart
transformed him with the true
spirit of darkness.
As JagerLoweemon, Koichi
conquered Cherubimon, only to
find out that he
was a big fake!
The real big boss fatty is
waiting at the Rose Morning
Star.
-Digimon.
THEME SONG: We look to the
past, as we head for the
future, to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a spirit evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together, the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
[evil laughter]
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Children hear me.
-We've made it.
The Rose Morning Star.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Hear me.
-Huh?
-I know that voice.
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): Children,
you finally made it.
-It's Ophanimon.
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): With
the spirits of the 10
legendary warriors, you must
defeat Cherubimon here.
-Huh?
-What?
-Cherubimon is here, too?
-Oh.
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): He is
anticipating your arrival.
-Oh, where's all that
data going?
OPHANIMON (BREAKING
UP): The digital--
-Her signal dropped out.
That huge data stream must
have overloaded things.
We just got cut-off!
-Where do you think that
data's coming from?
-Maybe Koichi knows something
about it.
-Huh?
-Yeah, he was Duskmon.
He must know what's going on.
Hey, Koji, your brother
was on the dark side.
Ask him what gives!
-Gah!
-Now, that was subtle,
palazzo.
You ever thought of becoming
a diplomat?
-Well, somebody's got to ask.
-I wish I knew.
Cherubimon's gathering data
for some reason, but
I don't know why.
Sorry I can't be of more help.
-Anyway, what we really need
to do now is to find and
rescue Ophanimon.
-But how are we going to
get there from here?
-Seems to me the only choice we
have is to use those big,
floating rocks.
-I'll bet it's another trap.
-Ah!
A trap?
But I'm too young to fly!
-You ninny.
Need I remind your friends have
overcome much greater
obstacles than this.
They are fearless warriors
to whom traps
are part of the game.
Takuya, am I right?
-Uh, actually, Neemon
does have a point.
-Huh?
-Gotcha!
Of course we're going!
Now, let's do it!
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
[yelling]
-Agunimon!
-Lobomon!
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
[growling]
-Loweemon!
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
[yelling]
-Kazemon!
-Beetlemon!
[yelling]
-Kumamon!
[grunting]
-Quickly, post haste!
Ophanimon is in peril!
-Next time, no hitchhikers!
-Careful, this altitude might
cause a nosebleed.
-Wee!
[evil laughter]
-They are here.
Our long-awaited guests
have arrived.
Ophanimon, have you
changed your mind?
-Your heart is evil.
I cannot align myself with you.
-Ha.
Keep in mind, if you join forces
with me, the digital
world will be ours to
do with as we wish.
-How can you be so misguided?
-What?
-My only wish is to bring
peace to this world.
I have no desire to impose my
will upon it, as you do.
-I see you are still
against me.
Do what you will, Ophanimon, but
very soon you will regret
this folly.
-All life will one day
be annihilated.
Whether the end happens
now or later is
simply a matter of fate.
It appears their fate
is not a lucky one.
For by meeting us, their
destruction is at hand!
[grunting]
-Um, does this remind anyone
else of the dark gate, or is
it just me?
-This must be the entrance
to the castle!
-OK, but there's nothing back
here for us to enter into!
-Well, you'd have to think this
gate leads to somewhere.
Wow!
Nice reception!
-It is time for the harvest,
of your souls!
-Ah!
Those are Phantomon Digimon,
the grim reapers of the
digital world!
Phantomon always carry
a scythe and
know how to use them.
They wear crystals around their
necks which give them
clairvoyant power.
And they're just dying to see
into the future to know who
their next victim will be.
-Soul chopper!
[grunting]
-Whoa!
Lobo kendo!
[grunting]
[evil laughter]
-Eh?
[roars]
-Shadow meteor!
-Hey, nice shot.
-Hurricane wind!
-Ah!
-Frozen tundra!
-You sure froze him out.
-It was my pleasure.
-Thunder fist!
-Slippery little devils,
aren't they?
-Pyro punch!
[grunting]
-Nice try.
[laughs]
-Great, they vanished!
[whimpers]
-Use extreme caution.
The clairvoyant crystals they
wear can capture and hold you
in another dimension forever.
-That doesn't sound good.
-Phantomon, show yourselves!
-Don't wander off too far.
-Huh?
Uh.
Oh!
-Beetlemon!
Ah!
-Kazemon!
-It's no use.
We can't see them in time to--
-Uh!
-No!
[whimpers]
-Oh beans.
[evil laughter]
-Once trapped inside our
crystal spheres,
you can never escape.
Join them!
-No!
I won't let you!
-They're waiting for you.
-To react quickly, I
must clear my mind.
[yelling]
[crash]
[groans]
-Huh?
-Shadow lights!
[yelling]
-Confused evil souls, be buried
in darkness and sleep.
Let the shadows purify you.
[grunting]
Fractal code, digitize!
-Outstanding!
-Wow, Loweemon, you
saved everybody.
-Thanks, Koichi!
[gasps]
-The gate!
-Right, let's go!
[grunts]
[evil laughter]
-Excellent.
Just a little more.
Once I have absorbed all the
digital world's data, I will
possess even greater power.
The spirits of the 10 legendary
warriors are drawing
ever closer.
And when I have their power
within my control, the digital
world will be mine.
[breathing heavily]
-What in the world
is this place?
-Who knows?
This world just gets weirder
and weirder!
[yells]
-I'm shutting my eyes!
Tell me what happens!
[grunts]
[screams]
-How do we stop these things?
-Whatever that is,
it stopped them.
[bell]
-This is the hall of shadows.
All those who have fallen prey
to Cherubimon's treachery are
locked forever within.
-And just who are you?
-My name is Oryxmon.
I am not your enemy.
NARRATOR: Oryxmon is
a great black goat
who acts as a sentry.
He is programmed to hold large
amounts of data which help him
protect the secret treasures
and ruins
of the digital world.
-Cherubimon's castle is a deadly
labyrinth, filled with
pitfalls and traps.
But I can lead you safely
to Lady Ophanimon
-What do you think?
-I don't know.
I'm not sure we can
trust this guy.
-Tell us, what proof do you have
that we can trust you?
-Ah!
-Wha, wha, where are you
going, Patamon, my boy?
-[inaudible].
Oryxmon won't hurt anybody!
[delighted squeals]
-Well, kind of hard to
argue with that.
-No kidding.
-Sorry for doubting you.
We'd appreciate you showing
us the way.
-Very well, let's begin.
Lady Ophanimon is being held
in the sphere above us.
Sealed within the light
of that golden orb.
-It's so bright.
-And warm.
-What is that?
-That glowing entity you see
before you is one of the three
great angels, Lady Ophanimon.
-You made it.
The legendary warriors
have returned.
[grunts]
-Come on, Z, we got to
get her out of there!
-Thunder fist!
-Hurricane wind!
[grunts]
-Whoa!
-That seal's too strong
to break through.
-Thank you, children, but
you must not waste
your powers on me.
-But why?
-Because there is a greater
purpose for your being here.
But before you put yourselves
into any more danger, you must
know what all of you were
called to this world.
Ages ago, there was
a terrible war.
A fierce battle raged
between the human
and beast-type Digimon.
Then Lucemon appeared and
stopped the fighting, bringing
peace to this world.
But soon after, Lucemon grew mad
with power, tormenting and
oppressing all Digimon.
It was then that the 10
legendary warriors rose up,
carrying the light of truth
and right in their hearts.
Oh, how bravely they fought
against Lucemon and the evil
of his injustice.
And after finally defeating
him, the 10 warriors
disappeared.
Cherubimon, Seraphimon and I
worked together to bring peace
and harmony to the digital
world once more.
-Hey, that's the exact same
story Seraphimon told us.
-Hoi!
-Ah!
Ah!
-But it wouldn't last.
Seraphimon upheld our world's
system of law and order.
Cherubimon protected all our
knowledge and legends.
And I fostered the
appreciation of
all life and love.
And yet, it soon became obvious
that Cherubimon's
ideas and philosophies were
quite different from ours.
-To honor these simplicities
is absurd!
Love, law, order--
this world is a wild place!
Chaos is its natural state,
but you human-type Digimon
can't understand this!
-Seraphimon and I decided we
should meet alone to try and
find a way to reconcile our
views with those of
Cherubimon.
But when Cherubimon found
us talking together, he
misunderstood our intentions.
He thought we were trying to
undermine him and subvert the
beliefs he held.
-Seraphimon and his
laws are only for
the human-type Digimon!
It's up to me to give
the beast-types a
new system of order.
[grunting]
-Our world exploded.
We were treated like traitors
by Cherubimon's followers.
He had convinced the beast-types
that we were the
cause of all their problems.
Cherubimon led them in an
aggressive campaign against
the human-type Digimon.
He had become a monster
steeped in evil.
[screams]
[roar]
-Seraphimon!
From now on, I am the
law of this world!
And you are nothing!
[evil yell]
[screams]
-Seraphimon, no!
Ah!
I will do whatever
you ask of me.
But I beg you, please
spare his life!
Ever since that moment, I have
been imprisoned in this castle
waiting for Seraphimon
to awaken.
-Wow.
-I wish everybody would
just play nice.
-I wonder if all of this
happened because Cherubimon
liked Ophanimon.
-No way!
-When he gained power,
Cherubimon possessed five of
the 10 legendary warriors'
spirits.
He took four of these spirits
and created his own group of
evil warriors.
Then he commanded Digimon all
over our world to begin
collecting the digital
world's data.
They ruthlessly carried out his
edict, creating chaos for
our beautiful planet, and
turmoil for its inhabitants.
At the rate they were pillaging
our world, I knew it
would soon be destroyed.
With the survival of our world
in the balance, I desperately
called out to another world in
which Cherubimon had no power.
-Huh?
Hello?
-This is a game to determine
your future.
Are you willing to play?
-Only those human children
who were pure of
heart answered my call.
Your positive response
encouraged me, but your level
of commitment has
astounded me.
Thankfully, I had been told by
Seraphimon that the other five
spirits of the legendary
warriors were hidden.
Without Cherubimon knowing,
I led you to them and
you found them all.
Then Cherubimon planted the
remaining spirit that he held,
a spirit of darkness,
into Koichi who had
wandered into our world.
But you were strong and turned
away from the darkness.
Your strength and courage
triumphed over the many
ordeals you have faced.
Now you face the truly daunting
task of defeating
Cherubimon.
But you possess the power
of the spirits of all 10
legendary warriors.
You are our greatest hope
to conquer his evil.
-You are a fool, Ophanimon.
[gasp]
-It's Cherubimon!
[growls]
[gasps]
-I hear him, but where is he?
-Haven't you wondered why I
would allow the human children
to come here without
destroying them?
Surely I had the strength
to do it.
-What are you saying?
-The spirits of the 10 legendary
warriors are
gathered here, and
within my grasp.
When I combine them with the
data I've collected, total
control of the digital world
will at last be mine.
And it's all thanks
to you, my lady.
You and these humans have
brought my plan to fruition.
Let's end it.
-My spirit!
-It's starting to glow!
-What's going on?
-Oh come on, what is happening?
[screams]
-The spirits!
-Cherubimon, no!
-Finally, it has all come to
this shining moment when my
evil will reign supreme!
NARRATOR: Oh man,
this is serious!
If Cherubimon gets to the
spirits, the digital
world is done for!
You have got to watch the next
Digimon Digital Monsters!