NARRATOR: That freak Cherubimon
knew that Duskmon
was slipping out
of his control.
So the evil dude made Koichi
remember how much his mother
had been hurt by the breakup
of their family.
Duskmon slide evolved to
Velgemon and set off to avenge
his mother by destroying
his brother.
Now that's logic for ya.
Anyway, Takuya showed up just
in time to save Koji but the
fight was far from over.
Koji didn't want to fight
Velgemon now that he knew that
Kalichi was his brother, but
Takuya convinced him it was
the only way to save
his brother's life.
Man, this is one funky
family reunion.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
Digimon.
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon.
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon.
-What have I done?
How could I have let
this happen?
-Um, is it he?
Oh, man.
He's Duskmon?
-Huh?
-I remember.
It's him--
the guy that came after you
on the train to Shibuya.
How could I forget that face?
It looked just like you.
-Wait!
-I was there.
Well, I wasn't exactly myself,
but I was there.
Hm.
-All right, spill it.
Is it true?
I have to know.
And I need to hear
it from you.
Are you my brother?
And if you are is our
mother still alive?
Tell me right now!
Hey!
What's the matter with you?
Say something!
-It's all true.
-You need to know Koichi.
You have a brother.
His name is Koji.
-Koji?
That was all my grandma said.
It was all she could tell me.
But I wanted to know more.
I wanted to know who you were,
and why we were separated.
But I had to find
out on my own.
[barking]
-You all right, Koji?
-Yeah.
-Ouch.
That had to hurt.
You OK to walk?
-I'm fine.
Let's go.
-I wanted to say something,
but I never could.
I didn't tell anyone.
I was afraid to.
I couldn't talk to
my mom about it.
She had enough problems
to deal with.
-Thank you.
Much better.
So what did you do today?
-Uh, nothing.
Hey, Mom what do you say we go
out there and find you a less
stressful job?
-That's sweet.
What made you say something
like that?
-Well, it seems lousy that they
won't let you off, even
if you're really sick.
-I can't just take off
any time I want.
They need me.
Now, why don't you help
me get dinner ready?
-Poor mom.
-She never complains.
Anyway, it was later that
same day that I
saw you on the train.
-I was right.
You were the same one I
saw trying to get in!
But wait--
you didn't get on that train.
So how did you end
up in the digital
world without a trailmon?
-Actually, I can't remember.
-Koji.
It's all like a giant
blur after that.
Next thing I know, I'm here.
I thought I had died, that this
world was the afterlife,
and that I was just some spirit
floating around in it.
I didn't know where to
go or what to do.
[laughter]
-They had to choose Koji.
Mother!
All alone in a strange world.
I felt angry and betrayed.
But then I met him.
What do you want?
-I can help you.
[gasping]
-Who are you?
-I am the emancipator
of darkness.
Your burden is heavy, Koichi,
but you can turn your pain
into great power with this--
the spirit of darkness.
[screams]
[evil laughter]
[train whistle]
-I wish we would just
get there already.
-I know.
Hey guys, I can see it.
It looks like there's a castle
under the rose morning star.
-Yeah, Punimon's
waiting there.
-My baby's so perceptive.
-Uh huh.
-What's that mean?
-Can't wait.
-Come on, people.
Why don't you lighten up here?
-I'm light.
-The resemblance between them
is kind of creepy, huh?
-And they look the same.
-It's still hard for me to
believe that Duskmon turned
out to be Koji's brother.
Hey, he looks so sad.
Maybe you should
say something.
-Yeah.
But what do I say?
-Oh, I'm so hungry.
I've got the grumbly tumbly.
Oh.
-Ah, chocolate--
the original fast food.
Perfect for those in a hurry.
-I really feel bad for
Koji and his brother.
Isn't there anything we can
do to help them get along?
-Beats me.
-Good question.
-I say leave them alone.
-Well that's real
helpful, J.P.
-I just think their problem is
a private one and out of
respect, we should keep
our noses out of it.
They'll eventually work it out
if we just give them time.
-Well, out of respect I
need to do something--
now.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-I hope I'm not being too nosy
but I just wanted you to know
that I'm here if you
want to talk.
-Oh, yeah.
Great.
He's annoyed.
-Stop it!
-And there's one more thing--
uh, I'm sorry.
-What are brothers
supposed to do?
-Huh?
-I mean, I really don't know.
I was raised alone.
-Well, you just do what comes
naturally, I guess.
I have a little brother and
most of the time we can't
stand each other.
Let's see.
In my case, my brother always
wants to hang around with me
and my friends.
But I don't let him because
he's just a
bratty little pest.
And when I do play with him, I
usually end up making him cry.
And I can't really help it.
The twerp just bugs me.
I suppose I really should
work on that.
Oh, but he still likes me.
Does that help?
-I guess.
-Guys, I have a brother, too.
He's in college so we don't
see each other much.
And sometimes he's
kind of mean.
But I guess he's just that
way for my own good--
not that it feels good, but
you know what I mean.
-Hey, at least you guys
have siblings.
I wish I did.
-I don't know that I'd want the
responsibility of having a
little brother or sister to
take care of, unless they
turned out just like
me, of course.
-Well, I'd love to have a little
brother or sister.
-Better get busy.
-What exactly are you saying?
-Hey, thanks a lot you guys.
-No problem.
Look, there's no right
way to be a brother.
You have to do it and eventually
you'll find out
what works, you know?
What do you call it when you
try a bunch of different
things?
-Oh, are you talking about
trial and error?
-That's it, trial and error.
-Right.
Hmm.
-Don't worry.
It just takes time.
-Why don't they hate me?
After everything I did--
I tried to destroy them.
I can't even stand
me right now.
[train whistle]
-Did you know that light
and dark are brothers?
It's true, Koichi.
One can't even live without
the other one.
Darkness isn't a bad thing
unless you choose to
make it that way.
-You're right.
And I guess you would
know, having been a
great celestial Digimon.
Unless you're just trying
to make me feel better.
Did you really mean that?
-Really, silly.
-Thanks, Patamon.
Something wrong?
-Yeah, and that something's
coming and it's big and scary!
-Wha--
[brakes screech]
-Stop in the [german]!
-Whoa!
-What happened?
-Cherubimon.
-He looks mad.
-Hey, what do you say we kick
it for a while and talk this
through, huh?
-With pleasure.
[screams]
[evil laughter]
-Payback time!
-All secure!
This spirit of evolution!
-Beetlemon!
-Zephyrmon!
-Korikatsumon!
-Execute now!
Fusion evolution!
[glass shatters]
-Ah!
Ah!
-BeoWolfmon.
-Avalanche action!
-Lightning blitz!
-Hurricane gale!
-Wrenching light!
-Atomic inferno!
[evil laughter]
-It's him.
-This isn't working.
-Well, he is the big boss.
We got to tag team him.
Korikakumon, I think it's time
to break out our combo attack.
-Right!
-Here goes nothing.
-Wait a minute!
Proton cell!
Avalanche axis!
-How's that feel?
-Ah.
How refreshing.
My turn.
-Oh no!
-Thanks.
We'll need more than that
to beat this guy.
Now stay back.
I'm going to try something that
could get a bit messy.
-Hey, don't worry about me.
I'll be right here.
-Yeah, I'm OK with that.
-Koji, back me up.
-No prob.
-Solar wind destroyer!
-Game over.
[evil laughter]
-Man, I've got to work
on my serve.
-Next.
-That's it.
I've had enough.
Frozen hunter!
That did it.
-Indeed.
It showed just how
pathetic you are.
-What's with this guy?
-Shall I destroy you now or do
you want to play some more?
-We'd better think of something
quick or he's going
to squash us like a bunch
of little beetles.
-Great.
Thanks a lot for
that visual, Z.
-You had your chance.
My turn.
-What is he doing?
-Form of judgment.
[screams]
-Koichi!
-Is he alive?
Koichi?
-Never felt better.
[groans]
-Do you suppose he'd
want a rematch?
-Well, I'm disappointed.
I expected at least a shred
of challenge today.
And you, how pathetic
losing to them.
-I'm glad.
-Koichi!
Don't!
-I lost when I listened
to you.
You made me fight
my own brother.
-It was your choice.
Isn't that what you wanted?
-No!
You lied to me.
You used me.
-You're wrong.
I merely set the stage.
The spirit of darkness
chooses its owner.
To be selected, one must possess
a very dark heart.
Otherwise, the spirit's
powers are useless.
I offered it to many before you,
but the spirit rejected
them one after another.
The power of darkness is
your destiny, Koichi.
It's where you belong.
Accept it and be my
servant once more.
You've only tasted
a fraction of the
great power of darkness.
I'll teach you everything.
Time to choose.
What's it going to be, Koichi?
-Don't listen to him!
He's lying!
-No, it's true.
My heart was filled with anger
and jealousy and darkness
became the only comfort
from my pain.
[evil laughter]
-But that's in the past.
I don't want revenge anymore.
I'm done hiding in the dark.
I'd rather die than
betray my brother.
-Hm, so be it.
Koichi!
The spirits of darkness
are changing.
A D-Tector!
Koichi!
I can feel it-- the
power of darkness.
But it's different now.
It doesn't have to be evil.
The pain is gone.
I'm not afraid anymore.
-He has discovered the
spirit's true power.
-Yeah.
Execute spirit evolution.
-I'm having trouble
keeping up here.
Didn't he used to be Duskmon?
-He used to be.
Now he's a completely new one.
-Impossible!
Somehow you've awakened the
true power of darkness.
-Shadow meteor.
Shadow meteor.
Keep it going, Loweemon.
-This nightmare's over.
-Lightning spear!
-Loweemon slide evolution,
JagerLoweemon.
Prepare to be illuminated.
Ebony blast!
How does the darkness
taste now?
Dark master!
[groans]
-He did it!
-Sure did.
-Wait!
Something's wrong.
-Huh?
-He's dissolving but I don't
see a fractal code .
-That wasn't the real Cherubimon
we were fighting.
It was like some kind
of projection.
Unfortunately, he's still
very much alive.
I can feel him.
-If that was just a projection,
I don't think I
want to meet the real one.
-You have impressed
me, Koichi.
Awakening the true spirit of
darkness is no small feat.
But make no mistake, you'll
never be a match for me.
I look forward to meeting
you in person at the
Rose Morning Star.
-Wait!
What are you doing?
-I have to face him alone.
You guys should just leave.
-Sorry, bro.
I can't let you do that.
The only thing that can
defeat him is the
true power of darkness.
You'll only be in the way.
-I have to help.
True darkness must depend
on the light.
-Sorry, but I'm going, too.
Somebody has to get in there
and save Ophanimon.
-I want to go, too.
I mean, after all we've been
through, we should help fight
the bully that caused
all of this, right?
-Kid's got a point.
And of course, if he goes, I
have to come along, too,
because I'm the oldest.
Besides, I've got to make sure
he stays out of trouble.
-And I have no intention
of going home now.
Can't let you boys have all
the fun now, can I?
-We're coming and that's final.
Yeah!
NARRATOR: All for one
and one for-- wait!
Are they out of their minds?
Let's see if they survive this
one on the next Digimon
Digital Monsters.