RIKA NARRATING: Just when they
thought they had beaten that
rat, Cherubimon, the guys
realized that the worst was
yet to come.
So Takuya and Koji unified the
spirits and evolved for the
final battle.
Unfortunately, Cherubimon had
been compressing all the data
he'd collected into a little
glowing orb that he shoved
into his forehead, making
him the most
powerful Digimon ever.
As EmperorGreymon and
MagnaGarurumon, along with the
spiritual support of the entire
Digi Gang, Taki and
Koji eventually vanquished
the vicious villain.
But they unleashed a whole new
horror in the process.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we head for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Huzzah!
Huzzah!
-Yeah!
-Now the Digital World can
be at peace once more.
-Feels like a dream.
Well, wake up, buddy,
because we did it.
Cherubimon's gone, and the
Digital World is safe again.
-Yeah.
-That's strange.
-What is, Koji?
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): The land that
was lost should have come
back by now, but the
Digital World's
surface still looks damaged.
-What?
-Hey, you're right.
This doesn't make sense.
When the data was restored,
the land should have been
restored with it.
-I don't believe it.
-That doesn't look good.
-Oh, dear, what now?
-Those mountains just
disappeared.
-What's happening?
-The data was scanned!
-Could Cherubimon
still be alive?
-It can't be!
-Let's go see.
-Huh?
-Hey, Taki.
What is it?
-Did you see something?
-I'm not sure.
Let's keep moving.
The mountain-- huh?
[gasping]
-Who's there?
-I am Baromon.
I cannot allow you to pass.
-I see.
You're the one who scanned
that mountain.
-Great spirits of the
universe, hear me.
Give me your power!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Agunimon!
-Beetlemon!
-Kazemon!
-Kumamon!
-Loweemon!
-Lobomon!
-Don't attack.
I have no intention
of fighting the
10 legendary warriors.
I know you are protectors of the
peace, but all of you must
hear what I have to say.
I have a prophecy.
It concerns the rebirth
of an ancient evil.
Lucemon.
-Takuya, speak to me!
-Is everybody all right?
-They look all right.
Thank goodness.
-So Lucemon's coming
back, huh?
-That's not good.
-You got it wrong, pal.
Lucemon was defeated
a long time ago.
-I will show you.
The truth is about to happen.
-OK.
-Look.
This is where the Holy Mountains
once proudly stood.
Now our great protectors have
fallen to the evil that
struggles to return.
Listen.
The Digital World is crying
out for your help.
Follow me.
-Follow you where?
-You see before you the Digital
World's Tunnel of History.
-Tunnel of History?
-Yes.
This place holds the entire
recorded history of our world.
-Whoa.
-At the start, our world began
from 10 spirits and 10
different types of data.
There are human and beast
type spirits.
-Yes, yes, yes.
That much we know.
-There is more.
The 10 ancient legendary spirits
banded together to
defeat Lucemon, and then sealed
him in the world of
nothingness, the Dark Area.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): All
of us have heard this
history lesson before.
-Be quiet and listen.
Behold and learn.
Lucemon's demise led do this.
The warriors freed
the spirits.
All 10 were released
into our world.
The spirits needed to be
protected, so they were
entrusted to the three celestial
Digimon who had
chosen to rule.
Five were given over to
Cherubimon, two were placed in
the care of Seraphimon, and the
other three to Ophanimon.
And then the warriors fell to
sleep, and it was wonderful.
You see, the next period of time
was characterized by a
long and lasting peace that
existed throughout the entire
Digital World.
But Lucemon was waiting, biding
his time, knowing the
day would come when he
would be revived.
Waiting patiently
for his chance.
Then one day, an opportunity
arose.
He projected his aura into one
of the celestial Digimon.
Cherubimon was a
victim of evil.
His heart was drowned
in darkness.
After that, Lucemon used
Cherubimon to collect the
Digital World's data for him.
The result is the ravaged world
you see before you,
eaten away by the treachery
of Lucemon.
When you vanquished Cherubimon,
the massive amount
of data he gathered
was released,
and absorbed by Lucemon.
-Hey, wait.
So Cherubimon didn't really
know anything.
-It was Lucemon, but he acted
through Cherubimon.
-All of this brings
us to the present.
Bear witness to the deplorable
condition
of the Digital World.
-Who is that?
-They're sucking up
the Fractal Code.
-The mountains are
disappearing.
-All right, so tell
us, who are they?
-I don't know.
I'd say now that Cherubimon is
gone, these are the other
underlings that have been
sent to collect the
Digital World's data.
Now you understand what
is happening.
Lucemon will use any means
to achieve his goal.
If they succeed, Lucemon
will be revived!
That is my prophecy.
-You mean--
-The entire Digital World
will be destroyed.
-The end?
It can't be.
-We thank you, humans.
You tried valiantly to help,
but now you must return to
your world.
Go now, before it's too late.
-We are not leaving.
-What did you say?
-Ophanimon and Seraphimon helped
us battle to save the
Digital World, but now
it's up to us.
We haven't come this far
and given this much
to let it all go.
We will save this world.
-But how will you do it?
-Easy.
We all possess the power of
the spirits of the 10
Legendary Warriors.
-Lucemon will never have the
chance to destroy this world
while we're here.
-Impossible.
The prophecy is right.
Lucemon will be revived.
-If he is, we'll stop him.
-We may look like a bunch of
kids to you, but we can handle
this.
-Mm-hm.
-If we don't take care of this,
then who else will?
You think we're just humans,
but we're Digimon,
and proud of it.
-Your pride won't help here.
The prophecy will
come to pass.
-Them again.
-Hurry.
We must get outside.
[evil laughter]
-Hey!
Knock it off!
Just who are you two?
-I am Dynasmon, the passionate
warrior.
-And I am Crusadermon, the
indifferent warrior.
-We are here for Lord
Lucemon's justice.
-We have come to fulfill
Lucemon's destiny as his
emissaries of evil!
-We are supporters of his right
to become this world's
supreme ruler.
We serve Lord Lucemon by
collecting Fractal Code.
-And we are known to all
as the Royal Knights.
-The Royal Knights?
-Why?
Why would the Royal Knights, who
have always been known as
defenders of right, align
themselves with Lucemon?
-This world is disordered.
-And the only one who can
fix it is Lord Lucemon.
This is our task, and we
shall complete it!
-Stop!
Stop it now!
-Execute now!
Fusion Evolution!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Aldamon!
-BeoWolfmon!
-Beetlemon!
-Kazemon!
-Kumamon!
-Loweemon!
-So, i you.
-The humans have been
evolved into the
10 legendary warriors.
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN): You can't
keep up your destructive ways.
BEOWOLFMON (OFFSCREEN):
The digital
world belongs to everyone.
KUMAMON (OFFSCREEN): You have
no right to wreck it.
KAZEMON (OFFSCREEN): Don't you
understand what will happen
here if Lucemon is revived?
-For now, there is only chaos.
Lucemon will restore order.
-Putting things into their
natural order is necessary,
and beautiful.
-Lord Lucemon will
be the supreme
salvation for this world.
-Not quite.
-Crusadermon, proceed with the
data collection while I handle
these nuisances.
-Let's do it!
-Very nice.
But not effective.
-Thunder Fist!
-And now I will take my
leave of you so I
can gather more data.
I bid you adieu with
all my heart.
[screaming]
-Oh, no you don't.
Shadow Meteor!
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Thunder Fist!
-I warn you, do not interfere!
DNA Disintegrator!
[screaming]
-Yes.
Strength is justice.
-Solar Wind Destroyer!
-Frozen Hunter!
-Ha ha ha!
You think to challenge me
with such weak attacks?
Dragon Thrower!
-Oh, dear.
Oh, dear.
Patamon, it's time for you
to come back home.
No need to wiggle, my boy.
It's for your own good.
-My good, too.
-Get away!
-The forest.
-Oh, no.
-Slide Evolution!
-JagerLoweemon!
-Zephyrmon!
-Korikakumon!
-MetalKabuterimon!
-Ebony Blast!
-Hurricane Gale!
-Frozen Arrowheads!
-Bolo Thunder!
-Please.
[laughter]
-Spiral Masquerade!
-Justice is beautiful.
-These two are tougher
than I thought.
We've got to find a better
way of going at them.
-I feel like an egg.
An egg salad.
-I know.
Let's give our spirits
to Takuya and Koji.
-The wind into flame!
-The ice into flame!
-The thunder into light!
-The darkness into light.
-Uni-Execute!
Unified Spirit Evolution!
[shouting]
-EmperorGreymon!
-MagnaGarurumon!
-The spirits of the legendary
warriors.
-Honestly, why you sound
surprised, I have no idea.
We did try to tell you more than
once, MagnaGarurumon and
EmperorGreymon are very tough.
They are the greatest champions
that defeated
Cherubimon.
-I see.
-Oh, a new challenge.
This may require us
to get serious.
-Dominating our enemies
for Lucemon is
truly a thing of beauty.
-They'll lose.
I have predicted you cannot
beat the Royal Knights.
-You missed.
-Oh, did I?
Dragonfire Crossbow!
-Magna Missiles!
-He did it!
-How is this possible?
Hm?
[laughter]
-It can't be!
-Dragon Thrower!
-First of Athena!
-They're so fast!
-Unreal!
-Hello!
-I predicted this.
-You can do it, you two!
-Come on!
-Oh, man.
-I can't believe it.
-They got clobbered.
-They lost?
-No way.
-EmperorGreymon.
-And even MagnaGarurumon.
-But how?
-Great spirits of the universe,
give me power.
Meteor Dance!
-Hm?
Begone!
-Your ugliness is intolerable.
-What are we gonna do?
-Spirits, hear me.
Give me the power to protect
these brave humans!
-He saved us.
Everyone all right?
Oh!
Those brutes knocked the Fractal
Code out of them.
-But how?
-Yeah.
They're humans.
How come their data
is showing?
-Human data is exquisitely
beautiful.
I had no idea.
-So, we can turn even
humans to data.
-Allow me to scan it
right out of them.
-As you wish.
-No!
-Guys, wake up!
-Oh, not you again.
-It's not over yet!
You've got to go through us!
-How brave and noble you are.
-I think we already
went through you.
-Dynasmon?
-Breath of Wyvern!
-No!
Dynasmon!
Stop!
[screaming]
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Dynasmon!
What are you doing?
Don't you realize, everything
will disappear?
Everything!
LUCEMON (OFFSCREEN): Hurry,
my Royal Knights.
The data.
Bring me the data.
All of it.
Now.
NARRATOR: Man, our heroes'
fate is pretty
much up in the air.
Find out where they'll
land on the next
Digimon, Digital Monsters.