RIKA NARRATING: After getting
this weird email, Kouji broke
away from the others to
find his Beast Spirit.
Not wanting to miss the show,
Neemon and Bokomon
decided to tag along.
The three of them ran into
Gotsumon, a rock Digimon who
was looking for this jewel that
was supposed to awaken
the spirit.
Anyway, their old pal
Grumblemon came back
for some more fun.
When Takuya and the rest of the
gang showed up, Gigasmon
defeated them and ended up
taking Zoe's spirit.
So Kouji used the jewel Gotsumon
found to unleash his
Beast Spirit.
He digivolved to KendoGarurumon
and sent the
legendary mole right
over the edge.
Sure hope he can swim.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a Spirit Evolution!
I am the one!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
If we're all for one world,
I am the one.
Digimon!
-Them stupid children.
They think can me defeat.
Me teach them lesson or two!
KendoGarurumon keep me from
stealing everyone Spirits.
Me have to take him
out of picture.
-[roars]
-And me think me
know just how.
[cackles]
By power of great spirit of
darkness who live beneath
ground, me command big
thing that was sealed
away to be free then.
My sword you be, my
shield you be.
Me commanding you!
Not even legendary Beast Warrior
of Light can stand up
to power of earth itself!
[cackles]
-[roars]
-[laughing]
Good morning, new friend.
How was nap?
-Master.
D-TECTOR NARRATING: Golemon.
Made almost entirely of stone.
His special attack, Sulfur
Plume, is a blast of volcanic
gas that turns his
enemies to ashes.
-[roars]
-Watch out, kids.
Here me come.
Going down!
-Isn't it nice to have a moment
of peace and quiet?
-Let's have some fun
and play charades!
-I thought you said fun.
-[laughing]
-I've always wanted to try that
thing where I'm trapped
in an imaginary box.
-If only the box were real.
-Oh, man.
I really messed up.
-You're finished!
-Kazemon!
-[growls]
[cackles]
-Zoe!
He got her Spirit!
-Zoe, no!
-It's OK, Tommy.
What happened wasn't
your fault.
-Well, the next time I see that
guy, I'll get your Spirit
back, even if I have
to do it by myself.
-Why would you want to do
something like that?
-Based on your last encounter,
I don't think that
would be very wise.
-So what?
It sure beats sitting around
here doing nothing.
She needs my help.
-You have a one track
mind, buddy.
We can't just run
out and fight.
We have to get to the
Forest Terminal.
-So what?
Then we just let him win?
I can't just sit back and let
Grumblemon run around with
Zoe's Spirit!
-It's OK, JP.
-No, it's really not OK, Zoe.
The Spirit Of is yours, and you
were destined to find it.
So we're going to get
it back for you.
-Nice sentiment, but we have
more important things to do
than fight a battle
we can't win.
-What is your problem, Kouji?
You'd be going crazy if your
Spirit was stolen!
-Hmph.
-But hey.
I understand if you're afraid.
Even the great Kouji has no
chance against Grumblemon.
-What?
-Who cares if you have
your Beast Spirit?
You can't even control it.
-Hey, stop it!
-Knock it off, JP!
-I guess I'm the only one
who wants to help Zoe!
-Guys, forget it.
Let's just go to the
Forest Terminal.
-Don't you start talking
crazy, too.
-All right.
That's it.
I've had enough.
I think it's time to do
something more productive than
stand here and argue.
But do I dare reveal this
great secret to you?
Are you ready?
Well, I guess there's only
one way to find out.
Ahem.
My friends, I believe the
time has finally come.
-Has come for what?
-What do you mean?
-Time to show you the
path of wisdom.
-Well, there's a change.
-Yeah, no kidding.
-Wisdom is a path which
is not easily walked.
You must think about every
choice, consider every option,
and know where each
step will lead.
-[laughing]
-Oh, dear.
It seems that wisdom has
landed in a mud puddle.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): So what's
your wise solution?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Fortune telling.
ALL (OFFSCREEN): Fortune
telling?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Shamanmon
is the wisest
Digimon of them all.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): If I'd have
said that, you'd have
told me I was crazy.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
You are crazy, but
that's beside the point.
-Step right up.
Play Squeeze the Pudgy Bear.
Go away, kid, you bother me.
-Wow, I've never had my
fortune told before.
-I had my palm read once.
It took a week to get
the paint off.
-Come on.
Do you actually think
any of these weirdos
can tell the future?
-Oh, yes, round one.
And it's all so clear.
-I don't really believe in
any of this mumbo jumbo.
-There is a girl in your life
who thinks you're quite
special.
-Huh?
-[laughs]
-I'm, uh, special?
-You know who I mean.
You were meant for each other.
-Really?
Yahoo!
-Come on, JP!
Let's get married!
-Indeedley-doo!
-Oh, JP.
This is a dream come true.
-You can say that again.
-Kiss me.
-[laughing]
-Look at me, guys!
I'm king of the world!
[laughing]
-JP, what are you doing?
-We're leaving now.
-Come on, come on, you can ask
me anything, short stuff!
-OK.
How do you polish that tuba?
-Wait a second, let me guess!
You're rather new to this
fortune telling stuff, aren't
you?
-Just ignore him.
What have you got?
-I shall conjure up a potion
made from orange juice and ear
wax, which I will place in a
hat and then drink while
standing on one leg.
-[groans]
-The result will be inspiring,
my friends.
Don't knock it until
you've tried it.
Where are you going?
-Over here.
-Check it out.
So what's your deal,
masked dude?
-Carrywood Method.
-Um, OK.
What exactly is the
Carrywood Method?
-I give you these heavy wooden
sticks, and then you to carry
them, one at a time.
-And?
What exactly would that tell
you about our future?
-That in the future, you
will be stronger.
The more wood you carry,
the stronger you get.
[laughs]
Carrywood! Get it?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Why
are we here, Bokomon?
All these fortune tellers
are fake.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Like
my Grandmamon's teeth.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Have
a little faith, please.
I do know what I'm doing.
Shamanmon is the real thing.
Shamanmon, I call upon your
wisdom, your insight, and
basically, well, ask you for
two cents' worth of advice.
-Who calls upon Shamanmon?
-Weary travelers in need of
guidance from the universe.
-Oh, you'll get guidance,
all right.
[laughs]
-Wait a minute.
I remember you!
-You're one of those
nasty Goblinmon
from the Wind Factory!
-Come on, you guys!
Let's get him!
-No no no!
Shamanmon's one of
the good guys!
Shamanmon is a medium.
This all-seeing Digimon does a
ceremonial dance, and uses his
magical club to see
into the future.
-You should be very careful.
Ahead, you face much danger.
You will come up against a foe
you have faced before, but
this foe has a friend, and in
beating him, you will find a
friend is your foe.
-Huh?
-I don't buy it.
-Then listen to this!
The greatest test will
be faced by you two!
This test has the power
to destroy you all
if you're not careful.
Heh.
-Hey, come back!
-Yeah, we don't want
to get destroyed!
-Then remember who you are, and
trust in each other and
your friendship--
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Right.
Run for it!
-Whoa!
-[growls]
-Old foe, big friend!
-It's Golemon!
-Grumblemon back with big angry
surprise for little
Spirit kids!
-One of these days, I'm gonna
beat this jerk for good.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): When
are you gonna learn?
How about working with
the rest of us, huh?
-[growls]
-Oh, my.
Just remember what you
have been told,
and you will prevail.
Huh?
-[growls]
-Oh, save me!
-Just give me a minute!
-Whoa!
-Right!
Minute's over!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Execute!
-Agunimon!
-Beetlemon!
-Kumamon!
-Now for the Beast!
Execute!
Beast Spirit!
-Me no think so!
-What's going on?
I can't move.
-Sorry!
KendoGarurumon no play today.
[laughs]
You no move 'til Grumblemon
say so.
-Crystal Freeze!
Whoa!
-Kumamon!
Thunder Fist!
Uh-oh.
-Sulfur Plume!
-[laughing]
Please not to tell me that
best you can do.
-[laughing]
-My turn.
Pyro Tornado!
-Sulfur Plume!
-[screams]
-You can do it!
Just work together!
-Enough.
You finished.
You surrender Spirits now or
be destroyed big time.
-Boy, would I like to
shut that guy up.
-Yeah. Me too.
-There's got to be something
I can do.
Anybody got any suggestions?
-Yeah.
Work together.
Hit him hard!
-Right!
-I'll chill him out!
Blizzard Blaster!
-Lightning Blitz!
-Pyro Tornado!
-No!
-Don't let him get away!
-Execute!
Slide Evolution!
Gigasmon!
Now myself me fix you.
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Quagmire Twister!
-Whoa!
-Tommy!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Tommy!
Wake up!
-Little yummy bear!
Me have two now.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Get out
of there, you guys!
-Tectonic Slam!
Hm?
-[roars]
-What is that thing?
-Oh, you mean other
than bad news?
-Now, just hold on.
That thing may be on our side.
-OK, but somehow, I
don't think so.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Whoever he
is, he seems very upset.
-[laughing]
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Maybe not.
-You go bye now!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Quick, let's
get out of here!
-Huh?
-I go bye now!
-[roars]
-Oh, man.
-He's really strong.
-Too strong.
-If he comes after us, there's
no way we can beat him.
-Right.
Time to go.
-Agunimon, come on.
-Yeah.
-Help me!
-Huh?
-I'm possessed by the
Beast Spirit!
-Shamanmon?
-Please, rescue me!
I was in the temple when the
Beast Spirit was revealed.
The instant I touched
it, I was possessed.
Please, help me!
-Agunimon, what are you doing?
-Don't worry, Shamanmon.
I can help you.
-Agunimon!
-Pyro Tornado!
Huh?
-[laughing]
-No!
-[groaning]
-I was trying to help you.
-What is he waiting for?
-Strike now!
Now!
-Pyro Tornado!
Now to free Shamanmon!
My D-Tector should
release him.
Fractal Code, Digitize!
[screaming]
-Something's wrong!
[interposing voices]
-Takuya, no, back off!
-Holy sock!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): For once,
I completely agree with you.
-[roars]
-Oh no, Takuya!
No!
-It seems that the Beast Spirit
has possessed him.
-Takuya, it's me!
-[roars]
-Take cover, everyone!
-Takuya, that's JP!
-[roars]
-Fine!
Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
KendoGarurumon!
[howls]
-You guys, this is crazy!
Think about what you're doing!
[growling]
-Kouji, Takuya, stop this!
-[roars]
RIKA NARRATING: Takuya wanted
his Beast Spirit,
and did he get it!
Find out if Kouji can
save him on the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters!