NARRATOR: Taking Cherubimon out
seemed like the end of our
heroes' troubles, but this
Digimon named Baromon show up
with some bad news.
Super bad Lucemon is coming
back into the picture!
Baromon predicted Lucemon will
soon rule the Digital World
with his two Royal Knights,
Crusadermon and Dynasmon,
doing all the dirty work.
When the gang tried to stop
these chumps, the Knights took
our hero to the cleaners!
Baromon tried to shield
the kids, but
ended up checking out.
Even with MagnaGarurumon and
EmperorGreymon on their side,
the future is pretty
much up in the air.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past, as we head
for the future to reclaim
the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
I am the one.
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
I am the one.
Huh!
Digimon!
PATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Koichi, wake up!
Koichi, please!
Wake up!
-Is that you, Patamon?
-Thank goodness.
Hey, guys, get over here.
Koichi's awake!
-Really?
-I hope you enjoyed nap time.
-Where is everyone?
Where's Koji?
-Out cold, I'm afraid.
They've been like
that for hours.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): They didn't
even respond to my
wakee-wakee little
flaky dance.
-Ah!
Koji!
Oh, man.
Please be OK.
-I'm sure he'll be just
fine once he wakes up.
-What should we do now?
-We need to get these guys
to a safe place.
But where in the world
are we, anyway?
-Well--
-Uh--
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): I got it!
We're at the bottom of a hole!
-What a brilliant deduction,
Commander Obvious.
-I'm going to go find
us some help.
[music playing]
-Oh.
-This air is so thin.
No oxygen.
-Ah!
Ahhhh!
-Oh!
-Oh, no!
[yelling]
-Hey, what's up with this?
-Wow, how'd he do that?
-Koichi, since when do
you know how to fly?
-I don't know, but I dig it!
Ha!
-Oh.
Time out.
What is going on here?
Huh?
-No offense, little feller,
but you got that
human-in-the-headlights
look on you.
You need a ride, don't you?
-Yeah, thanks.
-We're where?
You're telling me we're
on the moon?
-Yessiree, Mr. Greensleeves.
This here's one of the three
moons of the Digital World.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Starmon, a
helpful star-shaped Digimon.
His special attack
is Meteor Squall.
-I guess that explains why
I could jump so easily.
-What do you mean, Koichi?
-Well, the gravity here is a lot
less than on Earth, so we
all weigh less.
-Oh, now I'm really confused.
-Weight loss by relocation
is something
I could live without.
-I don't get it.
How did we all get to
the moon, anyway?
-I couldn't say for sure, but
you probably caught a warp
from an observation point.
That's how we got
here, uh huh.
[yelling]
-Heads up, fellas.
company's comin'.
-Yeah, that makes sense.
-Well, at least you're doing
all right, Koichi.
It's amazing.
You don't seem to be
injured at all.
-Yeah, you're right.
But how come I'm not?
-I guess you just got lucky.
KOICHI (THINKING):
But why just me?
Everyone else got hurt.
-Well, this is the Moon
Base where we live.
Welcome to home sweet dome!
[laughing]
-Yeppers.
It may not be much, but if
you're into tubes and
mountains, it's perfect.
Now let's get your friends
fixed up right.
-So you really think they're
going to be OK?
-Our scientists are very good.
Your friends are
in great hands.
Don't worry.
-Hmm.
-The commander's calling.
Let's get you to the bridge.
-There's a bridge?
I didn't even see the river.
-Well, look at that there, man.
Um hmm.
-Oh.
-Shake it, don't break
it, kiddies.
SuperStarmon, at your
service, baby.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
SuperStarmon, a
legend in his own time.
His special attack is
Halley's Squall.
-Well, thank you, thank
you very much.
Now, listen, people.
I got a favor to ask.
-Oh?
What is that?
-Well, you see, the Digital
World is deteriorating, baby,
a little more every day.
Get a good look at that, man.
-Now, that's where you all came
from, am I right, babies?
Any idea what's happening
down there, uh huh huh?
-Yeah.
The Royal Knights
are to blame.
They're scanning all the fractal
code of the Digital
World in order to
revive Lucemon.
-More data for Lucemon!
-They're doin' what!
-What about our old home?
[worried chatter]
What old home?
-Out sweet little corner of the
Digital World It'll get
eaten faster than fried peanut
butter and banana sandwiches,
I'm tellin' you, baby.
[gasps]
-Give me more data.
-As you command.
-You shall have all the
data you require.
And in exchange, you must
keep your promise.
LUCEMON (OFFCREEN): Of course.
When I am revived, you shall
have what you desire.
-Beautiful Lucemon.
-But I fail to understand why
you would want to go to the
human world.
-To control it!
The humans are weak, but their
data is oh, so sweet!
LUCEMON (OFFCREEN): I see.
-We seek to do as you have
taught us, to dominate the
weak, to destroy anyone who
would oppose us to prove how
worthiness to follow you.
-Flattery will get
you everywhere.
Now bring me more data!
[thunder]
-So we're on the moon?
-I can't believe it.
-Well, I couldn't, either.
But it's true.
-I guess it isn't made
out of cheese, huh?
-No.
-All right, all ready!
Now's not the time
to get flaky.
We've got to return to
the Digital World and
save it from Lucemon.
-And how exactly are we
supposed to do that?
-SuperStarmon said there are
no terminals around, so we
can't take a Trailmon.
-So that means we're
stuck here?
-No!
There has to be a way back!
-And that is?
-You don't know, do you?
-Well, let's all brainstorm.
We've got to come up with
something, right?
-Hmmm.
-Let me get into my
thinking pose.
Hmmmm.
-Right.
[snoring]
-Hm?
Ah!
Oh, would you wake up!
-Ah ha!
-Oh, man, we gotta hurry!
Spirit evolving may not
help us think, but
it's worth a shot.
-Mm hmm!
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
-Yaa ha!
Agunimon!
-Huh!
Loweemon!
-MetalKabuterimon!
-Haaaaa!
Kazemon!
-KendoGarurumon!
Huarr!
-Haa-uh!
Ha ha!
-Kumemon!
-All right, everyone!
Fire on my signal!
And give it all you got!
Aaaaaaa!
-You got it!
Huh!
Shadow Meteor!
Yaaaa!
-Bolo Thunder!
-Tempest Twist!
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Lupine Laser!
-And last but certainly
not least, Pyro Punch!
-Well, that ought to take
care of whatever we
were shooting at.
What exactly were we shooting
at, anyway?
-Well, nothing specific.
We were just firing that way.
-Now I'm confused and annoyed.
-What were you trying
to do, genius?
-I don't know.
I thought if we all fired in one
direction, maybe we could
move the moon.
You know, we could use the force
of our attacks to nudge
it closer to the
Digital World.
-Uh, what?
-Well, at least we gave
it our best shot.
[laughing]
-Come on, you guys.
Let's go.
-I'm a genius!
I'll give it a best shot!
-That's just wrong.
-He's lost it.
-Hey!
Wait up, you guys!
-Up!
Up!
And awayyyy!
Or not!
Uh!
Whoa!
-So, what do you think
he's doing?
-I don't know, but it sure
is funny to watch.
-One for the money, two for the
show, three to get ready--
and here we gooo!
Ohhhh!
Uh!
-Hey, look.
He bounced!
-You were right.
[cheering]
-Whoaaaa!
Uh!
-Crackers!
Get your hot crackers here!
-Don't forget to try our
bouncing bear special.
You'll love it!
-Order lunch number one,
hold the pickles.
-I'll take a space burger
with cheese.
-Yeah, make that two for me.
-Coming right up!
-Uh!
I give up.
-Well, nice try.
-Leave this to me.
-Huh huh.
Look, he made it.
-I think he's in trouble!
-Ahhh!
[gasps]
-Koji, no!
-Ahh--
ah, ahhh!
-[inaudible]
-Koji, are you OK?
-What the heck happened
to you up there?
-I got stuck in something.
It drained all my energy.
It was all I could do to keep
from dedigivolving.
-That would be the
electromagnetic stream.
-Yep, it's the stream.
[chattering]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Gotsumon.
This Digimon eats
meteor burgers.
His special attack
is Cosmo Flash.
-The stream is a river of energy
in space that separates
us from the Digital World.
Its flow is changed by the
pull of the moons, and no
one's ever crossed it.
-But we must have
crossed it OK.
I mean, we're all
here, aren't we?
-Yes and no.
-Huh?
-We must have bypassed it.
We got here through a
warp created by the
Royal Knights attacks.
-Great!
Which means we're never going
to find a normal way to get
off this stupid rock.
-Star light, star bright, get
us off this rock tonight.
BURGERMON (OFFCREEN):
Oh, dear.
-Huh?
-I sure am worried.
-I hope they're all right.
-Hey, you guys are Burgermon,
aren't you?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Burgermon
are Digimon with a
burger-shaped head.
-Well, you guys must have
crossed the stream, right?
-Oh, why would we?
The moon is where all we
Burgermon come from.
-But we saw Burgermon down
on the Digital World.
-They were very nice to us.
-My goodness, you saw them?
Those are our friends who
moved down there.
-Oh, I see.
-But we haven't heard from
them in forever.
[yelling]
-Beautiful!
At this rate, we shall gather
enough data for
Lucemon in no time.
[laughing]
-Uh!
There's gotta be a
way outta here!
-Calm down.
-How can I be calm at
a time like this?
-Hang on a second.
You said your friends move
to the Digital World?
How did they get down there?
-Simple.
They built a rocket.
-That's the ticket!
-OK, let's see.
Times the square root of pi,
divide by 5, carry the 2.
-Where'd you get those
equations?
-I saw them in a book.
-That's reassuring.
-Hey, are you sure this
is going to work?
-Of course it will.
Trust me.
All right, here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one--
blast off!
-Woo hoo!
Ahh!
Oh!
-OK.
Maybe it was divide by
2 and carry the pi.
If at first you don't
succeed--
hey, Agunimon!
You ready to try again?
-No!
I can't believe I let you talk
me into it the first time,
metal head.
-Ah, come on.
-There's gotta be
a better answer.
-I should hope so.
-I'd let you guys shoot
me out of a canon.
Come on, it'll work this time!
-You got any ideas?
-Hey, what is that?
-Fire!
See?
I knew it.
That work, no problem.
And those guys doubted me.
This is definitely the answer.
We just need to build a rocket
big enough to carry us all.
-I just looked down,
and there it was.
-I can't believe it.
-Amazing.
-Hey, you guys!
Check it out.
I know how to get us back
to the Digital World.
You're gonna love this.
All we have to do is
build ourselves--
AGUNIMON (OFFCREEN): A rocket?
-Yeah!
How'd you know?
Hey, where did that come from?
BURGERMON (OFFCREEN): Our
friends built it.
-Huh?
-That's the one they
used for testing.
But as you can see, it
didn't work so good.
-Hey, can we use it?
-Of course you can.
KENDOGARURUMON (OFFCREEN): Then
what are we waiting for?
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN): Let's
get that thing out of the
ground!
-It's pretty heavy.
Maybe we can help.
-Yeah, we'll help you, too!
-Thanks, guys.
We'd appreciate it.
-If we help you get back to the
Digital World, maybe you
can help our friends
down there.
[grunting]
-Yeah!
We finally got it out
of the ground.
-Now how do we launch it?
METALKABUTERMON (OFFSCREEN):
We could-- um--
-We could answer that!
-Yeah, we know exactly how
to get us into space.
-All right.
How?
-We can use those.
-Huh?
[chatter]
-I like your style, people.
Lookin' good, there.
That's right, honey.
-I get it.
We glue those ban together and
make a giant slingshot.
[laughing]
-All right, now, check it out.
When those two moons line up
with of the Digital World, the
electromagnetic stream will form
a path to bring you right
on home, baby.
-Um, are you super
sure about that?
-Super is as super does.
A fool such as I can never
lie, my little hound dog.
You got one shot, but
hit it right, and
it's return to sender.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Wow.
A few repairs, one big elastic
band, and this
ship's ready to fly.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Cool!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Thanks
for your help, everybody.
-And thank you for helping our
friends on the Digital World.
You will do that, won't you?
-We promise.
[cheering]
-OK, guys.
Next stop, the Digital World.
-Hmmm.
KOICHI (OFFSCREEN): Well, we
may not remember how we got
here, but we're sure going
to remember getting back.
-The moon's are aligned.
-Yeah.
-Oh, wow.
This is exciting.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): This
waiting is unbearable.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Let's
have a singalong.
Who knows "Wheels On
The Bus?" [singing]
The wheels on the bus--
-Here we go!
-Rock 'n roll!
Halley's Squall!
[yelling]
[cheering]
-The ride may be bumpy,
honey, but don't get
all shook up, now.
Uh huh.
-This doesn't feel right.
-We don't have enough speed!
-Don't worry, I'm all over it!
-Execute!
Beast Spirit evolution!
Ahhhhh!
-BurningGreymon!
-Wildfire Tsunami!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): We're
gaining speed.
Way to go, Takuya!
-Nice work!
-Now we're right
back on target.
[yelling]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): We're
almost through it!
-All right, we're save!
-Not for long.
-Huh?
-Oh, man, an asteroid belt!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
More good news!
-Yaaa!
-Full speed ahead!
-Here comes a big one!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Hold on!
[yelling]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): We're
out of the stream again!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
But we're OK.
Neemon, what are you doing?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Standing
on the ceiling.
Why?
-Hey, this is fun!
[? -legs ?] go up, [? head ?]
goes down.
-Yeah, this could be fun, but
I'm over it all ready.
-My skirt keeps falling up--
I mean down--
I mean up!
Whatever!
Just nobody look!
-You heard her, J.P.
-What are you looking
at me for?
[crash]
-What was that?
-Excuse me, but you're
in my way.
-Wait, you guys!
It's a Trailmon!
-Move it, please.
Road hog!
-Oh!
-Um, excuse me.
Would you mind giving us
a little push home?
-Well, I suppose I could leap
over you, but that seems like
an awful lot of work.
Eh!
Pushing, it is.
-Gratzi, Mr. Trailmon.
-My nose is going to be
so sore tomorrow.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Would
you look at the
damage they've done?
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): At the rate
they're going, there won't be
much of the Digital World
left to save!
-Ah, yes.
My strength is growing.
It won't be long now.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Now that we're
back, we've got a score
to settle with those
Royal Knights.
-And Lucemon.
We're not going to lose twice.
The whole Digital World
is counting on us.
NARRATOR: The gang made it back
from the moon all right,
but are they too late to
foil Lucemon's plans?
Find out on the next Digimon
Digital Monsters!