NARRATOR: As the battle between
Duskmon and BeoWolfmon
raged on, Patamon was
doing his best to
lead the gang to Koji.
But Cherubimon trapped them
in this spiky dome thing.
Then Cherubimon took advantage
of Koichi's amnesia and gave
Duskmon his Beast Spirit.
When Duskmon Beast Spirit
Evolved to Velgemon, he forgot
what little he still knew and
tried to destroy Koji!
Thank goodness Ophanimon
intervened in
time to stop him.
Now Koichi remembers that Koji
is his brother, but both of
them are still clueless.
Boy, what a mess.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we head for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
How can this be?
A human brother?
If it's true,
then who am I?
I need some time
to think about this.
Duskmon! Who are you?
Koji
Huh
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
-That's good news.
-Yeah, we all heard that huge
explosion and thought that
maybe you were in it.
-Well, I kinda was.
-You were?
What do you mean?
-It was Velgemon.
He used Cherubimon's
power to evolve
from Duskmon and attack.
-Man, I'm sick of that guy.
-My boy, there aren't many who
can stand up to Velgemon and
still walk away.
I'm flabbergasted.
-Gazundheit.
-Yeah, I guess.
(THINKING) It was really
more Ophanimon than me.
If it weren't for her, I'd
have been finished.
-Well, hello there.
-And who are you?
-I'm Patamon.
-He hatched out of Seraphimon's
Digi-Egg.
-So, really, it's because of him
that you're able to fusion
evolve to BeoWolfmon
-So that's what it was.
Thanks little guy.
-Haha, it's my pleasure.
-I can't believe I can finally
say this, but now that Koji's
here, we can head to the
Rose Morning Star.
-Yeah!
So let's get it in gear, guys.
-Hey, I've been ready
this entire time.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
ready to eat.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): Soon it
will all be clear to you.
This mystery will be resolved.
-(THINKING) Clear to me?
What did she mean?
Of course.
Duskmon.
He must have answers for me.
-Hey, where are you going?
Koji, come back!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Wow, you
sure know how to make him run.
-Man, we're never going to get
to the Rose Morning Star now.
-Well, maybe he thinks we're
all supposed to race each
other there.
-He was thinking hard
about something.
-Yeah, probably planning
his escape from us.
-When will he learn that he
can't solve his problems all
by himself?
I'm gonna go get him.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Just wait here.
I'll be back before
you know it.
-You can't leave too.
-Yeah, it's just like
a scary movie.
-It's like a what?
-Never forget the horror
movie rule.
-The Boogieman strikes when no
one can hear you scream.
That's what happens every time
someone goes off on their own.
You break the rule
and you're toast.
ALL: Ugh.
-Does it look like
I'm laughing.
-Why would you?
I'm being serious.
-Yeah, well I'll take my chances
with the Boogieman.
-Fine, go.
-Come on, guys.
Let's not fight over nothing.
-Zoe's right.
There's no need to
get all riled up.
You guys wait here, and I'll
just go get him and
be back in a jiffy.
-It better not be
a long jiffy.
-I guess that's that.
Well, why don't we just go
ahead and make dinner?
-Let's eat, yeah!
-Z, you can't be serious.
-Huh?
-Listen, I'm going to hang
around here just because
Takuya says we should.
No siree.
-Oh boy.
-We can't leave.
He told us to stay here.
-If Takuya told you to shave
your head and run around in
circles, would you do it?
Besides, remember these?
We can take care of ourselves
if there's trouble.
-But we can't just take off
and leave Koji and Takuya.
-Well, duh, Zoe.
I never said we should go to
the Rose Morning Star by
ourselves or anything like that,
but we don't have to sit
here doing nothing.
-So, what do you want to do?
-A scouting mission!
-ALL: A scouting mission?
-To get information.
Don't you wonder what the
Rose Morning Star is?
We should know what to expect
when we get there.
I'll bet that if we look, there
are some Digimon around
here who know something
about it.
-Are you completely mad?
I'm beginning to think
that all of
you want to be destroyed.
-I think this is
what I'm here.
-Hm?
-Seriously.
I've been thinking that each
one of us has a certain
purpose in this world.
Maybe that's true
of any world.
But I've never been able
to figure mine out.
-I think he has a point.
-I really hated it at first
when everyone but me found
their spirits right away and
were able to evolve.
It was like being held back
a year in school.
I felt useless, you know?
Like I was only here with
you guys by mistake.
-Oh J.P..
-And then when Koji and Takuya
got this new kind of
evolution, I was
happy for them.
I really was.
But at the same time, I couldn't
help wondering why it
couldn't have been
me who got it.
But, after a while, I realized,
maybe there are
things that only those guys can
do, which means there are
things that only I can do.
I think that this
is one of them.
-Hold on.
-What's wrong now?
-You're not going without me.
-Tommy, I don't know.
-Young man, what are
you talking about?
I thought you were
on my side here.
-No, you're not going!
-All right.
-But Zoe.
-You're not going anywhere
unless you take me with you.
-Oh beans.
-Well, we better get going if
we want to get back before
Koji and Takuya do.
-Mm-hm.
-Come back, you nincompoops!
-We'll be back soon!
-Maybe we smell.
-But I'm new.
-Jeez, how can we tell if the
Digimon around here know
anything if there aren't
actually any
Digimon around here?
-Guys, check it out.
What are those?
-They look like train tracks.
-Well, they must
lead somewhere.
I guess I was wrong.
They lead nowhere.
-Nowhere's too good of a
word for this place.
-Hey guys!
Look.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Well, it
does look like something.
-Yeah, but what is it?
-It's better than nothing.
Yeah.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Let's
check it out.
Man, even this is just a
whole lot of nothing.
But I guess we ought
to poke around.
-What is this weird
place anyway?
-Gives me the creeps, like
a haunted house.
-Don't be silly.
It's just a junkyard.
[creaking]
-Ah!
Now you can't tell me
that was nothing.
-No way, I heard
it too, Tommy.
-Calm down, would you?
Look, I'll prove that there's
nothing here but rusty metal.
GERMAN ACCENTED VOICE:
Ach, [german].
Who disturbs mein sleeping?
-Mommy!
Mommy!
-Ah!
-Trespassers be gone.
Leave me in peace, or else!
-OK, I'm out of here!
-No.
No, Tommy.
Remember what we've
always said.
Whenever there's trouble, we
have to stick together.
-Why?
So all of us can be destroyed
in one easy swipe?
-You [german].
Stomping and banging just when
I was about to fall asleep.
What, nothing to say?
-Huh?
-Hmph.
-Wait, it's just a Trailmon.
-It's not a ghost that's
gonna get us.
-Hey, watch it.
I'm not just a Trailmon, and
I'm not a ghost yet either,
you rude little creatures.
I'm an burly Trailmon.
I'm an angler, thank
you very much.
-Burly, huh?
-Yeah, that's not the first
word I would have picked.
-Ach nein!
You are the rudest creatures.
I would teach you some manners
if I had any strength left.
But I'm as weak as a baby, and
I'm here all alone in this
Trailmon graveyard.
A Trailmon graveyard?
-Scary.
-Nein.
It's simply the place where the
Trailmon come when they
reach the end of the line and
lack the strength to perform
their duties.
It's not scary.
At least not to a real man.
But I suppose it is
a smidgen sad.
-Gee, can't you just get
repaired or something?
-Can we help you?
-Well, a good start would've
been to not wake me up in the
first place.
Mein Gott, I'm tired.
-Wait.
Um, I was wondering if I could,
um, ask you a question.
-This isn't the best time.
-I know, but there's no one
else around here to ask.
-I can hear you just
fine, you know.
-Oh.
-I just have a little
question for you.
-Then ask and leave me to my
dreams of Wienerschnitzel.
Even when you're trying to
be nice, you're rude.
-But aren't you being rude not
in response to our rudeness?
-Tommy, will you be quiet?
-Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
You have moxie, little one.
Now, what did you want to ask?
-You see, we were wondering
if you could give us any
information about the
Rose Morning Star.
-Th-th-th-the Rose
Morning Star?
Why?
You're not thinking about
going there, are you?
-Yeah, we have to.
-Why?
Is it dangerous?
-You do know something,
don't you?
-I--
Lederhosen.
-Please.
You have to tell us.
The future of the digital
world depends on it.
[coughing]
-No.
You have to tell us.
Please! Please!
-I think that it may
be too late, J.P.
[coughing]
-I do--
--know something.
But first, can you do one
tiny favor for me?
-(GERMAN ACCENT)
Anything.
(AMERICAN ACCENT)
I mean, anything.
-Could you help me--
[coughing]
--stand up?
-Huh?
-But how are we supposed
to help a big thing
like you stand up?
-This one's mine.
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Beetlemon.
Man, am I good, or what?
Now, the Rose Morning Star.
-I didn't realize you
could evolve.
-Sure can.
-You bet.
And so can the two of us.
-Most interesting.
[coughing]
-You OK, train guy?
-You know, there is one
thing I'd like to do
before my time is up.
-I thought we already did
one thing for him.
A bath?
-Yeah.
I'd love to feel all squeaky and
clean just one last time.
-Well, OK, but how are we
supposed to do that?
-Yeah.
There aren't any brushes or
water around here anywhere.
-Relax, fun boys.
There's a lake nearby and
brushes inside me.
-And then you'll tell us about
the Rose Morning Star.
-This Rose Morning Star
you speak of--
-Remember?
-Oh, yeah, sorry.
I'm afraid my memory isn't
what it used to be.
[coughing]
-Aw.
-I should let you know that if
you three don't hurry up and
wash me, what I was going to
tell you about the Rose
Morning Star might just pop
out of my head entirely.
-Fine.
We'll get washing.
Thunder Fist!
OK.
-Hurricane Wing!
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Kumamon.
-Crystal Freeze!
-Great.
Just had to be cold water.
So, of course that means--
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN): Ah!
You trying to clean
me or freeze me?
-It's not that bad.
-We're being nice enough
to wash you.
Don't complain.
-Little to the left.
Oh, wunderbar.
Yeah, that's good.
Oh yeah.
-Hurricane Wing!
-You know, I, for one, wouldn't
be too upset if you
accidentally grazed him
with that attack.
-Please, don't tempt me.
-Ah, squeaky clean
and scrubbed.
-Like a whole new Trailmon.
-You're all shiny now.
-Yep, you're all clean.
So maybe now you can tell us
what we want to know, right?
-Hm, I can't quite remember.
Maybe one little favor
would jog my memory.
-Ugh, give me a break!
-Well, my memory isn't what
it used to be, I'm afraid.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I already say that?
-Forget it, guys.
Come on.
He's not gonna help us.
-Yeah, we should probably
get going.
-I bet he just wants
to be alone.
[whimpering]
-But I'm so tired.
[coughing]
-Wait!
My wheels.
They're--
They're rusty.
And I- Oh, you're not buying
this at all, are you?
-I cannot believe it.
You were faking this
whole time.
Weren't you?
-No.
Maybe I don't feel quite as bad
as I let on, but you were
so nice to me I just didn't
want it to end.
When you're a Trailmon, everyone
likes to ride on you,
but no one ever treats you
like you really are.
A living creature
with feelings.
You were the first people who
were ever nice to me.
But you can go if you want to.
I understand.
[crying]
-Nein.
Leave me alone to die.
I'm just glad I got the chance
to meet someone nice before I
go into the final beyond.
-OK, enough.
We'll do it.
We'd be More than happy to
do whatever you want.
-Oh, I'd leap for joy
if only I had feet.
-Thunder Fist!
-Oh, that's great.
That dent's been bugging
me for years.
A little gentler would
be nice, though.
-Hey, how would you like
to try some chocolate?
Ah.
-Ah.
Mm.
-So, how does it taste?
-Like sweet, milky kindness.
That tickles.
-Hey mister.
Quit moving around.
-This, I could do without.
Yeah, very funny.
[snoring]
-Well, I guess this
is goodbye.
-Even though we got upset,
we had a good time.
-Mm-hm.
-Me too.
By the way.
About the Rose Morning Star--
-Please, don't worry about it.
-Yeah, we're not upset with
you for lying about it.
-Yeah, right.
Don't beat yourself
up about it.
-Well, thank you, but I wasn't
lying about having been there.
-Huh?
-Are you serious?
You were there?
-I wouldn't lie about it.
-So, spill the beans already.
-OK, then listen.
[coughing]
-What are you doing, pretending
to be sick again?
-I don't think he's
faking this time.
-Maybe he's dying.
[coughing]
-This is horrible.
-Hold on.
-Angler.
-I think that my time
has come at last.
-Why do we keep losing friends
just when we make them?
-Nein.
Nein.
Don't cry.
I've had a good life
while it lasted.
I'm just sad that I couldn't
help you after all.
-Angler, no.
-It's not fair.
-Huh?
-I don't believe it.
-Did that really happen?
-All that, and he's
still alive?
-Yeah, well, I guess things
weren't quite as bad as they
seemed, hm.
In fact, they're wunderbar.
Wunderbar.
Wunderbar!
[whistle blowing]
-Yay, I'm young again.
Free to ride the rails and
eat pound after pound of
sauerkraut.
Uh, heh.
Can't we talk about this,
my little dumplings?
-Time for talking's done.
-Hm.
-Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
-MetalKabuterimon.
-Zephyrmon!
-Korikakumon!
-I liked you better
all dented up.
Now, what can we
do about that?
-I have an idea.
Angler's not gonna like
it, but we will.
-Haha ha ha.
You really have to learn not
to lie to your friends.
-Well, I have to go.
-Not so fast.
-Um.
I--
Oh, I deserve it.
-Jeez, this guy's too pathetic
to beat up on.
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN): Thanks
for forgiving me.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Just
don't lie anymore.
-So, were you really at
the Rose Morning Star?
-Without a doubt.
When I was still old,
I was forced to
carry a container there.
Forced by Cherubimon.
-By Cherubimon?
-Well, his henchmen, so that's
not really a lie.
I was afraid of what they might
do to me-- well, not so
much the cute one-- so I
didn't ask questions.
But the battle between the three
celestial Digimon had
just happened, and the way those
henchmen were guarding
the container, I'm sure
it had either
Seraphimon or Ophanimon.
Ah, it's shameful that I was
ever a part of that debacle.
-Hey, blame Cherubimon.
-So, if Seraphimon's
now Patamon--
-Then it must've been Ophanimon
who was inside of
that container.
-I remember there's
a castle there.
-Huh?
-What?
-A castle.
That's where they took me.
-That's where they're
keeping Ophanimon.
-Oh.
-Imprisoned.
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): We're getting
close now, guys.
NARRATOR: Yeah, but getting
close to something good or something bad?
Gee, I wonder.
But there's only way
to find out.
Tune in to the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.