BOKOMON NARRATING: No one ever
promised our heroes the moon
and the stars, but that's
all that was left.
Everyone was wondering
what was next when
we got a happy surprise--
baby Digimons!
We frolicked with the cuties.
But those nasty Knights crashed
the party and scared
off the babies.
MagnaGarurumon and
EmperorGreymon had the Knights
on the ropes when Lucemon
showed up.
He scanned the Knights'
data and evolved
into his Chaos mode.
Then he slammed our heroes back
into their human forms.
And if that wasn't enough, the
force of the fighting shook
the moon apart!
Who can stop this fiend?
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World!
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned
as we work towards one
solution, through a
spirit evolution!
Digimon!
Forever united as
one, Digimon!
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
there's a world for us all!
Digimon!
[blasts]
[screams]
[blast]
-Hm!
-Whoa!
Where did that come from?
-Is everybody OK?
-Uh-huh.
-[groans]
-I guess so.
-I'm still standing.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Yes,
you are on my head!
-Ooh!
-He blasted the moon to bits!
-Where's Takuya?
-And Koji?
-Maybe the flying eggs
have seen them.
Hello?
Eggies!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
How very tragic!
Lucemon must have scanned
the data of every
Digimon on the moon.
-Well, I don't see an egg big
enough for Takky or Koji.
-Look, what's that?
PATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Here we come!
-[laughing]
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Takuya!
KOUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Koji!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Man, am
I glad to see you, guys!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Hey, not
nearly as glad as
we are to see you!
[laughs]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): I got to
tell you, it was a little
touch-and-go there
for a while.
But then Patamon and his
buddies helped us out.
-They stopped Lucemon?
They're awfully powerful
for such little guys.
-Kind of like you, Tommy.
-Hey, well, don't forget who
these guys used to be.
-Well, you can bet
Lucemon hasn't!
He'll be ready for
them next time.
And us!
[burbling]
-Out of chaos, I bring order.
Beautiful order, my order.
-I don't like it out here.
-Me either.
What do we do now?
-What can we do?
Lucemon is so powerful.
-There has to be a way
to defeat him.
We just have to come
up with a plan!
-[sighs]
That's what you always say.
-Um, Koji?
I wanted, uh, I just--
well, it's about our mom.
-I made a promise
to only call my
step-mom "mom."
-Huh?
-But I would really appreciate
it if you'd tell me about our
mother, Kouichi.
OK?
-My mom's terrific.
She works so hard, you know?
It wasn't easy.
There was just the two of us.
We had no one.
She raised me by herself.
Everything my mother did,
she did for me.
-She must be incredibly worried
about you right now.
Is that what's been bothering
you lately?
You can tell me.
-Hey, Bokomon, you said
the Legendary
Warriors sealed up Lucemon.
Do you know how?
-The legend only says that
they joined forces.
Then it says they
sealed him up.
I'm afraid it's not very
enlightening, is it?
-Not at all.
I don't get it.
We have the power of the Ten
Legendary Warriors, so we
should be able to do it, too.
-It's light and shadow!
-That's it!
-The light and the darkness
must become
one for it to work!
-If it's about the light and
darkness, then Koji and
Kouichi are involved.
-It does kind of figure that
those two hold the key.
[thunder rumbling]
-OK, but how?
-Well, you see, the
trouble is--
-(TOGETHER) We don't
really know.
-Don't you wonder what
those two are
talking about over there?
They look so serious.
-I don't have to wonder.
I'm sure I know what they're
talking about.
-Really?
What?
-About what Crusadermon
told Kouichi.
What else could they
be talking about?
-Hey!
You told them!
You promised Kouichi you
wouldn't say anything.
And you just told them!
-I did not!
I didn't tell them anything!
-Not yet.
But you are going
to tell us now.
Aren't you, Bokomon?
-Huh, uh.
[PATAMON, LOPMON, SALOMON
GIGGLING]
-Tell us!
-[groaning]
Oh, beans!
I guess I have to
tell you now.
Kouichi noticed that whenever
the rest of you were hurt,
your fractal code
became visible.
[static]
BOKOMON NARRATING: It bothered
him that no matter what
happened, his fractal
code never appeared.
At first, he was just curious.
But now, he's worried
and very confused.
Poor thing.
-You mean his data?
-But Kouichi was never
really hurt!
-Well, maybe he's
just been lucky.
It's nothing to worry about.
-I'm afraid it is, Zoe.
Crusadermon told him it's
because he doesn't have a
physical presence
in this world.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Do you think that maybe it has
something to do with the
way he came to the
Digital World?
I mean, the rest of us
came on a Trailmon.
But when we asked him,
he didn't even
remember getting here.
That's kind of weird,
isn't it?
-Something's wrong.
-And he's been freaked
out all this time?
I wonder if there's something
we can do.
I feel bad for him.
[thunder rumbling]
-Now, you shall become my
road to the new world.
-You know, I've been thinking
a lot about the two of us
meeting here and all.
It's kind of strange when you
really think about it.
I mean, really, what are
the chances of that?
I guess, it must be destiny.
We are light and darkness,
after all.
We are bound together.
That's how I know there's
something bothering you.
-No, it's nothing, really.
-Kouichi, I know.
I'm not guessing, I know.
When you're hurting,
I feel it, too.
When you suffer, I suffer
along with you.
Don't you know that?
-Koji--
[screeching]
-Ha?
[strange rumbling]
-What is that?
-Wow, guys, look
at that thing?!
-I'm betting it's
not good news.
-It's the Dark Area!
-I was right.
That can't be good news!
-Guys, I'm betting that's where
Lucemon is hiding out.
-How do we get there?
-Patamon!
Will you and your buddies
take us there?
We need to get to the
Dark Area A-S-A-P!
-(PATAMON AND PALS,
TOGETHER) Sure!
-Koji, listen.
I want you to promise
me something.
When you go back to the
real world, I want
you to visit my mom.
Will you do that?
-Huh?
Uh.
-Promise me.
-I promise, Kouichi.
Of course, I'll go
visit your mom.
I really don't see how I could
keep from meeting her.
-Thank you, Koji.
Let's go!
-(THINKING) That's odd.
Did he think I was going to
avoid her or something?
-Are you, guys, OK?
-We're just tired.
This is hard work.
-JP, why aren't you helping?
-Gee whiz, Z. What the heck
am I supposed to do?
-Hm.
Uh!
[group shrieks]
-That was a little too close.
-Yeah, no kidding!
What was that?
-It must have been the magma
that was once at the core of
the Digital World.
I suspect we will see
a lot more of it.
We have to be careful.
-Do you, guys, smell
something burning?
-Ngh?
[shrieks]
Pants on fire!
-Oh!
-Ah!
-Look!
There it goes again.
-Yeah, but it's even
longer this time.
-I got a bad feeling
about this.
What's Lucemon up to now?
[hissing gas]
-Guys, help me out a little.
Is that real?
-Huh?
No way!
It can't be.
But it is!
It's Shibuya!
It's our home!
Oh, no, guys.
What's he done?
[thunder rumbling]
[radio static]
-That's Shinjuku!
-[gasps]
No, he can't!
-Shibuya?
Shinju--
Shinjuku?
-Those names sound funny.
-What are those?
-That's the world we
all came from.
-It looks like Lucemon
is building a
road to the real world.
-Oh, that's ridiculous!
Everyone knows it's impossible
for Digimon to
go to the real world.
-You didn't tell Lucemon.
-Bokomon, isn't there anything
in the Book about this?
-Something's very wrong here.
From cover to cover, there's
nothing but blank pages!
Everything has just
disappeared!
-(KIDS, TOGETHER) Whoa!
-Uh!
-That's new!
-Look, it's not blank anymore.
-How did that happen?
-I have no idea.
But it looks like something
is answering us.
-What's it say?
-It says that if Digimon are
allowed into the human world,
they will create chaos.
And eventually, uhh, uhh--
-And eventually what?
Tell us!
---eventually, they will
destroy it, utterly!
-(GROUP TOGETHER) Destroy it?
-[laughs diabolically]
-We have to stop him!
-But how?
-I know we'll find a way.
We have to!
I don't think we'd all still
be here if there wasn't
something we could
do about it.
[zooming, hissing noises]
-If we don't stop him now,
Lucemon is going to make our
world look just like that!
-We already know that long ago
the Ten Legendary Warriors
found a way to defeat Lucemon
and seal him away.
There must be a way for you
six to do it again.
I just know there is.
-Then we'll find it!
[digital sounds, various]
[blast]
-(DIGIDESTINED TOGETHER)
Execute!
Spirit evolution!
-Aah!
Hah!
Beetlemon!
-Haa!
Um!
Kazemon!
-Haa!
Ah!
Ha-ha!
Kumemon!
-Urrh!
Lowemon!
-Execute!
Fusion evolution!
-Rrrh, aaah!
-Rrrahh!
[glass shatters]
-Uh!
Beowulfmon!
-Rrrahh!
Uh!
Rrrah!
Aah!
Aldamon!
LUCEMON (OFFSCREEN): This
will be even more
satisfying than I expected.
Look at the little insects
pretending like they matter.
Soon they will learn the folly
of their false beliefs.
They will taste the sweetness
of utter oblivion.
[snickers]
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN): Lucemon!
Stop this, right now!
[blast]
-(IN UNISON) Whoa!
Whoa, oh!
-Please, how very tedious.
What are you doing
still alive?
Ah, well, it might be nice to
have an audience for my next
performance, no?
[laughs]
You're not actually going to
try and stop me, are you?
How amusing.
-(SHOUTING) Do you
see us laughing?
-We will stop you.
LUCEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, very well.
If you insist.
My entrance into your world will
be even more impressive
if I use each of you as
my stepping stones.
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Aah!
-Uh!
-Uh, uhh.
-Aaah!
-Ah!
-Why you--
Thunder Fist!
Aah!
-Atomic Inferno!
Ngh, aah!
Uhh.
-[growls]
Shadow Meteor!
-Cleansing Light!
Uh!
-[chuckles]
-Arrgh!
Aah!
-Koji!
Aarrh!
-[grunts]
[blast]
[grunts and growls]
-No!
-Uh!
-Ahh!
-Ohh!
-I don't think we're winning.
Are we winning?
-For once in your life, you're
absolutely correct.
We are definitely not winning.
[groans]
-Although your pathetic
struggles amuse me, you will
never defeat me.
Shall I show you
the reason why?
Behold, the power of light and
the power of darkness.
[screams]
-Oh!
[group gasping]
[static noises]
-Huh?
What have you done?
[group screams]
-You want off my little ride?
[group groans]
-Light and darkness appear to
be opposites, never together
in the same place at
the same time.
Imagine what it would take
to bring them together.
But you don't have to imagine.
Allow me the pleasure of
showing you, shall I?
It's just too bad you won't
survive the experience.
It is now time for you to return
to nothingness, so you
can be reborn into my world.
-Light and darkness together.
-I hope you enjoy oblivion
because it's the last thing
you will ever experience.
-Everyone, please,
you must get up.
If that thing catches
you, it's all over!
-Run away!
-I call light--
[group gasping]
[group screams]
---and darkness!
-No!
-Hm?
-(TOGETHER) Huh?
-[gasping]
-Kouichi!
-Aargh!
-Aaargh!
-You, fool!
Not even the Warrior of Darkness
can stand against the
power of darkness
that I command!
-Aargh!
Aah!
[group gasping]
LOWEMON (INSIDE ORB):
I know now why I
came to Digital World.
I wasn't Cherubimon's pawn.
I was his greatest gift!
Lucemon!
You are not the only one
who can bring light
and darkness together.
I'm glad I met all of you.
Thank you for being
my friends.
I wish I could see you back
in the real world.
But I don't think I'll
be able to go.
-(DIGIDESTINED TOGETHER) Huh?
-What does he mean?
LOWEMON (INSIDE ORB):
Protect our world.
That's all I ask.
-Kouichi!
LOWEMON (INSIDE ORB): I--
I think I'm ready.
-No, please!
[glass shatters]
-Kouichi!
[group gasping]
-It's up to you now, Koji.
Take the Spirits of Darkness.
-Uh, haah.
-My brother, I can't tell
you what it means to
me to have met you.
I have no regrets, no regrets!
-No!
Kouichi!
Aargh!
-It looks like you can't
control it, little boy.
I'm not surprised.
How could a mere human have the
strength to control both
light and darkness?
-[grunting]
-What is happening?
-Kouichi!
-What a shame your little
playmate had to go away.
But I'm still here.
-How could you!
Uh!
Lucemon, you go too far!
Aaah!
-Oh!
-Huh?
-Whoa!
-(TOGETHER) Ancient
spirits, unite!
-Susanoomon!
[gasps]
-Amazing!
Wow!
-The ancient spirits
answered our call!
-Look at them!
They're one Digimon.
-He's beautiful!
-My friends, we have
just witnessed the
birth of a new warrior!
BOKOMON NARRATING: Well,
bless my pink belt!
The Book never said anything
about this.
You'll just have to keep
watching "Digimon--
Digital Monsters."