ZOE NARRATING: Neemon told the
gang they could take the train
back to reality, but they all
decided to stick it out in the
Digital World.
Things were going well until
they found the marks of the
Ten Legendary Warriors.
Bokomon took this as his cue
for another lecture.
Fortunately, he was interrupted
by the Candlemon.
Unfortunately, the Candlemon
weren't too happy to see them.
They turned up the heat on
Agunimon, who seemed to be in
big trouble until Tommy's spirit
evolved to Kumamon and
took on Wizardmon and the
whole Candlemon tribe.
It turns out it was all
some kind of test.
This makes math look like
a piece of cake.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World!
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
there's a world for us all!
Digimon!
[train rolling on tracks]
-Whoo-hooh!
Hail path!
D-TECTOR VOICE: You must go
to the Forest Terminal.
-The Forest Terminal, sure.
Why not?
[trailmon groaning, gasping]
[trail rolling on tracks]
-[yawns]
Just call me the Nap
Time Express.
[snores]
-[yawns]
I better catch a snooze, too.
This looks like as good
a place as any.
Ah, this quiet really gives
a guy time to think.
JP (OFFSCREEN): So, guys,
are we there yet?
Let's see, what's wrong
with this picture?
Desert-looking wasteland,
Forest Terminal?
I'd say no.
-Oh, I'm tired.
Let's take a rest.
-But there's a scenic
lookout just ahead.
You know, JP, if you hadn't
fed chocolate to that
Trailmon, we'd be riding
in air-conditioned
comfort right now.
-So he made a mistake.
What are you going to do?
Take away his bowling shoes.
[train horn honks]
-Hey!
Hey!
It's a Trailmon!
[squeaking]
-Uh! Finally!
-Hey, Trailmon, what's up?
Can you take us to the
Forest Terminal?
-Oh, I overate at
my last stop.
Besides, I'm a freight train.
No riders, no exceptions.
-Trailmon, I am as light
as bubble wrap.
Andiamo!
-Just think of us
all as cargo.
-[laughing]
Oh, your little fingers.
You're tickling me
something awful.
It's too much!
I'd like to bend the rules,
but I'm just too ticklish.
Sorry, kids.
Keep on this track.
You'll get there!
-So much for getting
there soon!
-Uhh, come back here!
Trailmon!
-Uh-huh, oh.
Uh!
I've got a track split here.
Now, which way to go,
left or right?
Right or left?
Or up or down?
And on or off?
Fast or slow?
Time to make a decision.
[groans]
I made myself sick.
-This way.
-That way.
-Hm, you're wrong.
-Why?
Just because I disagree
with you?
Don't you think the Forest
Terminal just might be
surrounded by trees?
-Trailmon says stay
on this track.
And your way curves left.
You think you know everything!
-Well, I'm right!
-So you want to go right?
-No, I'm going the way
that makes sense.
Later!
-See 'ya!
-Wait up, Takuya!
-Hey, we should stick
together!
-Humans!
You know, Neemon, those two
might be next to digivolve.
It's imperative that when they
spirit-evolve, we are there.
We wouldn't want to miss
that now, would we?
-"It's imperative."
What's that mean?
-It's a 30-cent word that
means "we have to to be
there." I can't wait to see
that happen in person!
-But don't we have to
be there for that?
-Snap out of it, mon!
-Aah! Ooh!
-I can't believe that Takuya and
Tommy went the other way.
I mean, it's pretty obvious this
is the right way, I hope.
He can be a real
jerk sometimes.
-You got that right.
-It's, like, I'm the beef,
and he's the jerky.
-Do you think she's listening?
-Nope.
-[grunts]
Hold up, Z!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): That is
one humongous tree!
JP (OFFSCREEN): So then this
must be the Forest Terminal,
right?
-This is Breezy Village.
-It's called the what, now?
-Welcome, tourists.
So this isn't it?
-You're right, it's not.
-[giggles]
Hey, Koji, what's up?
-Hmph.
-Uh, where are you going?
-Where I go is my
own business.
Thanks for asking.
-Oh!
You're so anti-social!
-He reminds me of
white chocolate.
He may look good,
but no taste.
-Oh, this isn't quite right.
Breezy Village is known for its
spectacular view of lush
forest greenery.
But there's not much to see.
-Spectacular view?
Of what? A dump?
Eh, let's check it out, Z!
[electronic beeps]
-Oh, wow!
My D-Tector's doing something.
Maybe my spirit is somewhere
close by.
-From up here, I'll get a better
idea of where we are.
Bella!
What a view!
Hmm.
Smell that air!
[wind whooshing]
-[humming]
[sighs]
-Zoe!
My D-Tector is flashing!
-[shrieks]
[floramon squeaking]
-Hm?
Is this a spirit?
MUSHROOMON 1 (OFFSCREEN): Ha!
So the strangers are
in the village, eh?
That's trouble.
MUSHROOMON 2 (OFFSCREEN):
They're human children!
MUSHROOMON 3 (OFFSCREEN): Ahh,
you think those whiny
wallflowers called them
in to come and help?
MUSHROOMON 1 (OFFSCREEN):
Who cares?
Nobody can stop the Mushroomon
Brothers!
MUSHROOMON 2 (OFFSCREEN):
We'll get them, right?
[mushroomon laughing]
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): How thoughtful
of you to
invite us for lunch!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Yeah, thanks.
Hmm.
I wouldn't mind a bowl or 10.
-[slurps]
Molto buono!
Yum!
-Um, "melted" what?
-"Molto Buono" is Italian for
"delicious." This seems great!
[floramon cheering]
-I must know.
What do you call this soup?
-Well, soup a la Floramon.
It's all in the way
it's prepared.
-Allow us to demonstrate
how we do it.
-(TOGETHER) Uh-huh.
-To make it, you use your head
and a ripe wham fruit.
-Oh?
-"Use your head"?
-Two, three, four.
-(FLORAMON IN UNISON) When you
take a little wham fruit and
you mix it in your skull, you
make the most delicious soup,
the flavor's never dull.
We shake our heads, move up and
down, and sing this song,
quite cheerful.
A little bit of us resides
in every yummy spoonful!
-And it's ready!
Enjoy!
-(JP AND ZOE TOGETHER) Uhh!
-There, it's fresh.
Eat up!
-Uh-uh.
-Yech.
-Thanks.
-Delicious.
-It's brain food.
-Thanks. That was great.
Hm, the breeze feels so good.
-Thanks to our special
mung tree.
The wind's filtered through the
mung tree's many branches,
cooling all of Breezy Village.
-Wow!
This wind is like Hawaii,
a vacation
paradise in our world.
Do a lot of visitors
come here?
-Not like before.
No one comes to visit
our village now.
So many trains filled with happy
travelers made stops
here in the past.
Our village was a shady
green hamlet.
Many visitors came to relax
in our lush landscape.
Blooming bushes and pretty
plants were spread out all
over the station.
Our village was a perfect park
that everyone wanted to see.
-Well, I'd say that mung
tree still looks good.
-Thanks for your kindness.
But we know this place looks
like a dried-up dump.
-Now, we're lucky if we see one
train come through here a
month.
-Maybe you should put
in a video arcade.
-You and your friends are the
first tourists we've had here
in four months.
-Ah!
-We salute you.
We're indebted to you
for your kindness.
-"Indebted"?
Does that mean you're
going to charge us?
-No, no, no.
It means we thank you.
-If you've enjoyed your stay
here, spread the word that our
village is fun to visit.
-You bet!
Your soup's great, even
if it's different.
-With your help, we might just
see the return of trains,
visitors, and happiness
to our Breezy Village.
-Even if we tell everyone we
meet about your village, you
need to do something.
Plant new flowers.
-We've tried that, but
we have a problem.
We're just not strong enough to
dig in this hard soil, are we?
-No.
And to replant takes
a lot of strength.
-Well, I can help.
I know this strong guy.
-Hm?
-Who?
-Ah!
[floramon giggling]
JP (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
what are you doing?
-You have arms like
tree trunks,
you'll be a good digger.
-Me?
No way!
-You know what impresses me,
strong guys that help out
without even being asked.
-That's me.
Ha!
Why, I've got an eyebrow that
can clean and jerk 250.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Should we
find a gas station and ask for
directions?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): No way.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Wha--
what do we do?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Keep walking.
Something's bound to--
[earth rumbling]
-Ahh!
Tommy, run!
[kids screaming]
[earth rumbling]
-I don't know what's happening,
but just keep moving!
[kids screaming]
-Tommy, move slowly.
-Aiiee, aiiee, aiiee.
Oh!
-This might be a good time to
go find that gas station,
little buddy.
Hehehe.
-[sobbing]
-Uh, listen, I think we
went the wrong way.
So let's be calm.
-[bawling]
-Oh, if this is your "calm," I
don't want to hear "upset."
[tommy bawls]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): I should
call you Miracle Worker.
It's a miracle when you work.
Onward!
-Hm!
-[shrieks]
-There.
If we keep working, this
place will look
fantastic in no time.
-Hm.
-No?
-The Mushroomon will wreck it.
[mushroomon snickers]
-Mushroomon?
-Whoa!
-Nice try, bye-bye!
[explosions]
[floramon screams]
-Aahh!
-Ahh!
[critters chirping]
[floramon and others coughing]
-Uh?
-We are--
---the Mushroomon--
---brothers, yeah!
-(FLORAMON IN UNISON)
Oh, not again!
-We thought you understood--
---planting trees
and flowers--
---is a big waste of time.
-Please don't wreck
all our plants!
-[snickers]
-(MUSHROOMON TOGETHER)
Giggle Grenade!
[blast]
[floramon giggling]
-What's so funny?
They're troubled.
-Hehehe.
If you were a Floramon, you'd
be laughing, too.
Our Giggle Grenades keep
them in a good mood.
-They get so tired from busting
a gut that they can
barely move, let alone
plant stuff!
-What did we ever do to you to
deserve all this meanness?
We used to greet the
visitors at the
station together, remember?
-[giggles]
She's right.
In those days, you were
real fun guys!
[floramon laughing together]
-You, Floramon, were
always more
popular with the tourists.
They all like you better!
-No matter how hard we tried
to please those looky-loos,
they thought you flower-girls
were cuter and nicer than us
spore-guys!
-But that's not true.
They like you guys, too.
-And your mushroom mousse was so
popular with the tourists.
[giggles]
They like it better
than our soup.
-That is enough!
Mushroom Mash!
-Ooh-oh!
-Uhh!
-They're toasting this place
like an English Muffin.
-It's over.
We've had it with your
flower power.
-And we're going to--
---totally flatten
Breezy Village.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): You know,
Neemon, I'm not a genius, but
I think those Mushroomon
Brothers had their attitudes
adjusted for the worse by
Cherubimon's evil magic.
-Cherubimon?
Who is that?
-Here's a snap, don't
forget to write!
-[shrieks]
Sorry I asked!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Fool!
How can someone like Cherubimon
ever slip your mind?
He's the source of all that's
evil in the Digital World!
-She's starting a parade!
-Huh?
-Hold it!
-Ha?
You just stand aside, girly.
Ungh!
-Hm!
-Hey, now, that's my brother!
Why did you slap him?
-You need to learn
how to get along!
-(TOGETHER) Ha?
-Just because you feel like
you're getting the short end
of the stick, that doesn't give
you the right to just go
around destroying things!
Try solving things peacefully.
-Yeah!
Now, listen up!
You, toadstool-heads can't just
go barging in here with
your purple mushroom
caps because
they're just plain ugly.
Right?
-You insulted them.
That's totally wrong!
-Ha?
Uh, ungh.
-You shouldn't have said that.
You're going to get it!
-(MUSHROOMON TOGETHER) Charge!
-Take this!
-Uh!
I didn't mean it!
Hello?
Spirit awaken! Hello, spirit? Come on!
-Nice try, bye-bye!
-Evolve!
Spirit, come on!
[blast]
-Ungh!
-JP!
-Yeah! My spirit!
Spirit evolution!
-Uh-huh!
-JP's spirit-evolving!
[MUSHROOMON NERVOUSLY
SPEAK INDISTINCTLY]
-Hey!
D-TECTOR VOICE: It is time.
-Hah?
Execute!
Spirit evolution!
Hah! Huh! Ah!
Kazemon!
-So you evolved instead of me.
-Wow!
She's a big butterfly.
-She's not a butterfly.
She's one of the Legendary
Warriors.
She has bonded with the Ancient
Spirit of the Wind.
She's Kazemon!
-Aah! Oh.
-Evil creatures, be purified
by the wind.
-Nice try, butterfly!
-(TOGETHER) Bye-bye!
-Hurricane Waves!
[explosions]
-Ehh.
You pesky insect!
Aah.
Ungh.
-Tempest Twist!
-Uh!
-Eh!
-Ooh!
-Think what she can do
with vegetables!
-And that could have been me!
-Hm, hm!
-So--
---we're not through yet!
-Revenge time!
-[laughs diabolically]
Uh!
Rrh!
[roars]
-That's Woodmon, a plant Digimon
whose Branch Smash
attack is one of tremendous
strength.
And his bark is like armor.
-Hmm, hm!
How about a little Love Tap?
Uh!
-Hm?
-You're bark's much tougher
than your bite!
Uh!
-Enough!
-Hmm, uhh!
Uh!
Man, am I good!
-That really kind of tickled.
My bark's feeling all funny.
(ANGRILY) But you see
I'm not laughing!
There is no escape from
my Branch Smash!
-Uh!
[screams in pain]
-Whoa!
Out of the way!
-[whimpers]
-Zoe!
-[laughs diabolically]
-Hey, cut it out!
-Branch Smash!
Here we are!
-Uh!
-No!
-You can't do that
to my friend!
Uh! Hm!
[thud]
[digital beeps]
-Hm!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Aaah!
Lobomon!
-Hm?
-Rrhaah!
Lobo Kendo!
Aaah!
-Ngarh!
Huh?
[laughs]
Was that a Love Tap?
-Howling Laser!
-Hm?
[blasts]
-Aahh!
-Ha?
-Obviously, you've been
taken over by evil.
-Hrmp, rrrarh!
-Shadow creature, be purified
by the light!
-Arrrh!
Aargh!
-Farewell, Woodmon, for good!
[woodmon screams in pain]
-Fractal code, digitize!
[mushroomon groaning]
-Hey, what happened to us?
-Where are we?
-Oh, no!
-Were we on a bad dream?
-Oh, Koji?
-Is that all there is to it?
That's it?
-[gasping]
[electronic beeps]
D-TECTOR VOICE: Fractal
code, rendered.
-Huh.
-Breezy Village's fractal
code is returning.
[floramon oohs and aahs]
MUSHROOMON (OFFSCREEN): We
have come up with a juice
drink that's great with
our mushroom mousse.
-Sounds delicious.
-You can taste test it for us.
-They're all pretty happy,
thanks to you.
You know, Koji, you could
try being friendly.
I don't get him.
Why do I try to like a guy
that acts like that?
I don't care what that Koji
thinks, we were a great team.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
We have returned!
-You blew it!
Where were you, two?
[tommy panting]
-Ah-ha, that's quite a story.
After a while, we thought you
might need us, so we decided
to check back in.
-No, you made a wrong turn.
You missed a once-in-a-lifetime
show.
-Yeah, right.
Don't try to psych
us out, Zoe.
You know we didn't
miss a thing.
-Well, you didn't get to
see my spirit evolve.
-Wait!
-Huh?
-You did what?
-You spirit-evolved?
-Hm-mm.
-Huh?
[both laughing]
-Yeah, right.
-Like you could!
-You really thought
we'd believe that.
[both laugh]
-I've had it with you, guys!
You run off, and then you don't
think that a girl like
me could spirit-evolve?
I'll evolve your heads!
-Uh, uh, hey, OK!
Uncle, uncle!
-I did it!
-Who am I?
Nobody?
Why don't I have a spirit?
Tell me that.
ZOE NARRATING: Poor JP.
It's tough being the
last one picked.
But I bet he doesn't have long
to wait on "Digimon--
Digital Monsters."
(theme music)