RIKA (NARRATING): The gang tried
to hitch a ride to the
forest terminal on another
Trailmon, but they tickled him
right out of the picture.
While trying to decide which way
to go, Takuya and Zoe had
another zingfest, and
the group split up.
Zoe, JP, Neemon, and Bokomon
ended up in Breezy Village.
There, the Floramon used their
heads to squeeze out some
lunch, but the kids
weren't biting.
Then the Mushroomon appeared
and bombed the group with
giggle grenades.
When the Fungus Brothers
digivolved to Woodmon, Zoe
spirit evolved to Kazemon.
But when the butterfly blew
it, Lobomon showed up and
knocked the sap out of him.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves, and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work toward one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Whoo whoo!
[giggles]
Ooh, coming through!
Whoo whoo!
[giggles]
-Ugh!
-Ahhh!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Ha ha! Ooh!
Hey, cool!
My ears of full of sand!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Yes, and
your head is full of rocks.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Wow, I
haven't been in a wind this
strong since-- well, ever.
[train horn blaring]
-Huh?
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN):
Comin' through!
-Aaaahh!
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN):
Ha-ha ha!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
That was close.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Oh, why do
things in the Digital World
always come out of nowhere?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): What
do mean, nowhere?
We're walking along
train tracks.
JP (OFFSCREEN): So?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
So where there are
tracks, there's a train.
It's kind of like the whole
smoke-fire thing.
[whooshing]
-Wow, awesome.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Welcome to
Wind Factory, Incorporated.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Wind Factory,
Incorporated?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): A division
of Mother Nature Enterprises.
-(IN UNISON) Buzz,
two, three, four.
-Hey, some Digimon.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Kokuwamon.
Machine Digimon.
When they feel threatened, they
let out a million-volt
electrical charge.
Their special attack
is Power Surge.
-(IN UNISON) Buzz--whoa! Whoa!
-Well, if there are that many
Digimon around, then there
must be some food around
here somewhere.
-All right!
Then let's have us a feast!
-But Takuya, hold on.
-Why?
What's up?
-Listen, Taki, as long as you're
heading out to get some
food, would you mind bringing
me an order to go with extra
everything?
-What?
I'm not the Pizzamon.
It's every tummy for itself.
Rawr!
-Well, hey--
-Last one to fill their
plate is a rotten egg.
Woohoo!
[alarms ringing]
-Huh?
MINOMON (OFFSCREEN): Warning,
warning, warning!
A warning from Minomon!
-Hello there.
-Hmm.
-Are you not listening to me?
I said warning, warning!
-They're larva Digimon.
-Warning!
No trespassers allowed
in the Wind Factory.
No entry!
Leave now!
Go home! Stop!
If you don't obey our
warning, we will
commence our fierce attack!
-(IN UNISON) You have
now been warned.
Stop!
What we're trying to
say is, GET OUT!
-Now would be a real
good time for me--
-Uh-huh?
-To wait in the car. If we had one.
-Ugh, boys.
Excuse me, but we're just here
for a tour or the factory.
[MINOMON CHATTER
TO EACH OTHER]
-Let's make the first tour
stop the exit door, OK?
-(IN UNISON) Then
come on down!
-Aaahh!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
This is cool.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Look at that pipe!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN):
Check this out!
This is so amazing.
JP (OFFSCREEN): This is great.
I love watching other
people work.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): We're not
the only ones watching.
Ahem.
-[menacing chuckle]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Goblimon.
This ogre Digimon
loves being bad.
His special attack
is Goblin Strike.
MINOMON (OFFSCREEN): Are
you enjoying your tour?
-Yeah.
-Do you have any questions?
-Can we slide on this
floor in our socks?
-If you feel you
must, go ahead.
-Ohhh.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
What's wrong?
-I really need to
find a bathroom.
Like right now!
-It's on the left!
-Oh boy!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Hey you!
-Huh?
What was that?
Whatever it is can wait!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Come on, hurry it up!
[KOKUWAMON MOANING
AND GROANING]
[toilet flushing]
-Ah, so much better.
Hm?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): (CALLING)
Hey, JP, hurry up!
Did you fall in?
-I'm coming already.
[KOKUWAMON GROANING
AND MOANING]
MINOMON (OFFSCREEN): This is the
backbone of Wind Factory.
It's where all the latest,
ultra-high-tech
supermachines are made.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): So cool!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): You call
that an ultra-high-tech
supermachine?
Please.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): A fan?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): And an
ugly one, at that.
I mean, grey is so out.
-What's so high-tech
about a stupid fan?
-Hey, it beats a folded
piece of paper.
-Huh?
-Now before we get you some
lovely parting gifts, are
there any questions?
ALL (IN UNISON): Yeah!
Where is the cafeteria?
-Aahhh.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): So what exactly
do you call this?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN):
A 9-volt omelet?
MINOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Eat up, everybody!
-They're really lovely
batteries, but--
-Oh, you'll love them!
It's our chef's special!
Just look at the Kokuwamon.
It can't get enough.
[gobbling greedily]
-Oh.
[crackling and sparking]
-Be sure to save room
for dessert.
It's alkaline.
-(IN UNISON) We can't
eat this stuff.
-Say, don't you have any sugary
treats lying around?
You know, for special guests?
MINOMON (OFFSCREEN): How
about a double-A pie?
-(IN UNISON) No thanks!
-Aaaaahhh!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I'm worried
we might have
offended the Minomon.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): More
than lunch offended us?
-Can we get back to worrying
about my stomach?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Stupid batteries.
-Unnh?
[laughs nervously]
-Hey, what's that?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Is "a
building with a fence around
it" too obvious an answer?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Well,
let's check it out.
-So this--
-Is where the Kokuwamon live.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): At least
they're out in the sunshine.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Yes, where
they can sweat and rust.
LITTLE KOKUWAMONS: Ohhh.
-Huh?
-You're kinda funny-looking.
[giggling]
[slurp]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, that's good, ohhh.
[slurp]
GOBLIMON (OFFSCREEN):
O, my leader.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
What?
-We have reports from Security
of some pink, soft outsiders
who have toured the factory
and are now in
the Kokuwamon barracks.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): I
hate pink, soft outsiders!
[glass shatters]
[wind whooshing]
ELDER KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Where once there was there,
there is now here, which is
neither here nor there.
-If I said that made any
sense, I'd be lying.
-Yeah, I'm lost, too.
-[clears throat]
Sorry.
The Elder's charge is a
little low these days.
Perhaps our story will
make more sense if we
begin at the beginning.
We Kokuwamon lived peacefully in
the forest for generations.
We played among the trees and
had games of Electric Tag.
Until one day, without warning,
the Goblimon attacked.
The wind at the Wind Factory
had gotten weaker, and the
energy for the generator
had gotten low.
So their leader had
us rounded up.
They took us all from our
beautiful wooded home and put
us to work in the factory.
-Here, not there.
-Mmm.
-Man, that just blows.
-Yeah, and everything seemed
so normal when
we toured the factory.
-I had a feeling something
was wrong.
My gut told me.
-Great, even your stomach's
a know-it-all.
So how come they needed
your labor in
such a modern factory?
-Our labor is more of a bonus
for the Goblimon.
It is not the main reason
they keep us.
You must understand.
They would never let you
outsiders see what
really goes on there.
We Kokuwamon are a timid and
cowardly breed by nature.
But when we we're frightened, we
emit electrical currents up
to a million volts.
So they scare us constantly.
Sometimes they even pour water
on us to short us out, then
they use the electricity we
give off at the factory.
Or even worse, they threaten to
hang us upside down so the
charge rushes to our heads.
And if all of that doesn't work,
they show us pictures of
people's feet.
I've gotten so jumpy be these
days, I feel like there's a
kangaroo in my pants.
-So that was the noise
I heard when I
came out of the bathroom.
ELDER KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Scary here.
-We are in the factory
every day.
This really isn't very much
fun for us at all.
-It's low pay and hard work.
-And no vacations.
-Can't go there.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Well,
why don't you leave?
-Hmmm?
-Yeah, when the going gets too
tough, the really smart ones
take off.
-Are you out of your mind?
If they take off, then the
Goblimon will track them down
and smash them all into
little pieces.
-Let me guess, Taki.
You got some bright idea
they should band
together and fight back.
[both growl]
KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN): We're
not really fighters.
And as for running away, we
can't, because the Goblimon
security is just too tight.
-Well, it seems like those are
your only two options.
-I suppose if we had to choose,
we would prefer the
running option.
-If you run now, you'll
never stop running.
But if you fight them, you
could be free forever.
You won't have to do it alone.
We'll help you beat them.
-Huh?
-Hey, who died and made you
Decision Guy, anyway?
What if we don't want any
part of this fight, huh?
-I'm in.
-Yeah, when do we start?
-Excellent.
-Mm-hm.
-Mmm.
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON): Oooh,
-All right, let's do it!
-This could be the most
important moment of our lives.
-However short they may be!
-Hear, hear.
-Well, something tells me those
Goblimon are going to
get the shock of their lives.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): OK,
is everyone ready?
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON):
Ready when you are.
-Hmmph.
Ready to get ourselves killed.
-I knew it!
Anyone who turns down double-A
pie has got to be trouble!
Snimon's not gonna like this!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): OK,
everyone, listen up.
We're going to do
this tonight.
First, Zoe will cause a
distraction right here.
She's going to try to get as
many Goblimon as possible over
to the gate.
That is, if you think
you can handle it.
-No sweat.
-Then the rest of us will move
into the factory and wait for
the right moment to attack.
And when the signal comes, we
all hit the same target.
Destroy the assembly line,
and that's it.
So what do you say?
Are you with me?
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON):
Affirmative.
-Great!
This is teamwork, guys,
and a great plan.
Just like the ones I used to
draw up for my army men.
Except this time
it's for real!
Pretty cool, huh?
-Yeah, pretty cool
for you, Takuya.
-What's that mean?
-I get it.
So if there's no place for them
to work, I guess they'll
just get to go home again.
-It's not quite that
simple, Tommy.
We'll still have the Goblimon
leader to get rid of.
-I'm not going.
ALL (IN UNISON): What?
-Why don't you guys take care of
this one and just holler if
you need me.
-What are you saying, JP?
-I'm saying that you guys
are on your own.
You don't need me.
You probably don't
even want me.
I can't become a Digimon
like you guys.
I'm just tall, and sweet,
and cuddly.
-Man, I will never understand
what your problem is.
-My problem is you trying to
make me do what I don't want to.
-Oh yeah?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): You two
loudmouths are going to make
the Kokuwamon cry.
-We understand what JP
is going through.
-You see, before we met you,
we never even dreamed of
fighting back.
KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN): But you
have given us hope, and that
is something we haven't
had in a long time.
And you have seen how strong we
can be if we just believe
in ourselves.
ELDER KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
We believe.
-You do?
-Hmph.
Believe in yourself.
Like it's just that simple.
Give me a break.
-Mmmm.
JP (THINKING) Why did I get on
that stupid train, anyway?
I can't do anything right
in the Digital World.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Hmm?
-Can we really go back to
the forest tomorrow?
I miss the trees.
-Don't worry.
We'll get you back home.
LITTLE KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Gee, thanks, Mister.
-All right, it's go time.
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON): Go.
-Are we ready?
TEAM (IN UNISON) Ready.
D-TECTOR: It is time.
-Aaahhhh!
(IN UNISON) Execute
Spirit Evolution!
-Raaahhhh!
Hyah! Hyah!
Agunimon!
Waahhhhh!
-Hahhh!
Hah!
Kazemon!
-Ha-ha!
Kumamon!
Ha-ha!
[explosion]
[alarms blaring]
-(IN UNISON) Warning!
Warning!
-Go away, you mouthy
pine cones!
Hurricane Waves!
[shoooooom]
[explosion]
-That ought to wake
up the neighbors.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
[giggles]
-Grrrr!
-Yeah, what he said!
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN): Quickly
now, follow me!
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON): Buzz,
two, three, four, buzz, two,
three, four--
-Hyah!
Hah!
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON):
Bzzzzzz!
GOBLIMON (IN UNISON) Grrrr!
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON):
Power Surge!
-Whhhooooaa!
[glass shatters]
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON):
Power Surge!
[explosion]
-Crystal Freeze!
Yeah!
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN):
All right!
Nice work, Kumamon!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): He
made Goblimon-pops.
-Wait up!
KOKUWAMON (IN UNISON): Bzzzzz.
-Everybody gets to spirit
evolve but me.
That so figures.
KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN): This
should get us past the lock.
[zap]
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Open, says me!
-Next stop, the assembly line!
Huh?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Oh no!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): I don't
like the looks of this.
[evil laugh]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Snimon.
This praying mantis Digimon
has blades for hands.
His special attack
is Twin Sickles.
SNIMON (OFFSCREEN): Well,
look what we have here.
You destroyed part of my
factory, so I'll destroy you!
-Oh, boy!
JP (THINKING): Here I
am, where it's safe.
Talk about useless.
Takuya's got the firepower
of Agunimon.
Zoe's flying around like
she's queen of the sky.
Even Tommy's got the power to
turn anything he wants into a
frozen dinner.
All I have is a constant
craving for chocolate.
Well, let 'em fight
with Kokuwamon.
-It's not like I care
or anything.
'Cause I don't.
ELDER KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
You can't!
You're too small!
-Only on the outside.
Remember what Takuya said?
I believe in myself.
I do.
-Yes, but you must also believe
in others to fight
when you can't.
-He can't, but I can.
-Mister?
You can do it!
GOBLIMON (OFFSCREEN): There's
only one of her!
Goblin Strike!
-Ahh!
Ahhh!
KAZEMON (THINKING)
I've got to run!
I just hope I bought
them enough time!
[goblimon yelling]
JP (THINKING): Hang on, guys.
Here comes reinforcements!
-Power Surge.
[zap]
[goblins laughing menacingly]
-Pyro Darts! Hah!
-Yaaahhh!
-Pyro Darts!
Hah!
-Aaahhh!
-Hurry!
The others are at the
end of this hallway!
-I gotta get into shape.
-Oh!
-Aahhh!
SNIMON (OFFSCREEN): There
is no escape!
Yaahhhh!
Ahhh!
AGUNIMON (THINKING): This
guy's too strong!
-What's your name?
Or should I just call
you Lunch Meat?
Ha-ha-ha.
-None of your business!
-You dare to taunt me?
Ahhhh!
[thud]
-Huh?
-Uuuuhhhhh ah!
-Twin Sickles!
-Aaaaaahhhhhhhh!
-[evil laugh]
Now I shall destroy
all of your little
friends, one by one.
AGUNIMON (THINKING):
I've failed.
-Isn't there any way
to stop him?
-How about giving me a lift?
That's it, guys.
Just a little higher.
[evil laugh]
-Nnnyyaaaaaaah!
-Ahhh!
[goblimon hooting]
-JP!
-Yeah ha-ha!
-Quick thinking, buddy!
Huh?
-Rrrryah!
Hah!
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN): JP!
[crash]
-Is that--
-A spirit!
-Now where do you suppose
that came from?
-The metal surrounding it must
have been too thick for the
D-Tector to, well, detect it.
Heh, heh.
-This time, that spirit's
got to be mine!
Aaaahhhhhh!
Aahhhhhh!
SPIRIT!
D-TECTOR: It is time.
-Execute Spirit Evolution!
Hyyyyahhhhh!
Beetlemon!
-Look, JP's spirit evolved!
-Yes, to Beetlemon, the
Warrior of Thunder.
-I-- I can't believe it.
I'm Beetlemon!
I did it!
Let's get this party started!
Ha-ha!
SNIMON (OFFSCREEN): Dance while
you can, Monkey Boy.
Soon you will taste the
fury of Snimon!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN): The only
thing I want to taste is
a cheeseburger with
a side of fries!
-Yaaahhhh!
Yaaahhh!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Beetlemon
1, green guy, nothing.
Woohoo!
Missed me!
-Yyyaahhhh!
Those are my Twin Sickles!
-Oh, yeah?
I call forth--
-Yyyahhhh!
-The power of--
-Thunder Fist!
[crash]
-Where once your power was used
for evil, let it now be
used for good.
Fractal code digitize!
[goblimon hooting and yelling]
-Huh?
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN): The
fountain's gonna blow!
Everybody out!
[kokuwamon cheering]
ELDER KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Finally, there is here!
KOKUWAMON (OFFSCREEN): Our story
has come full circle.
-You can all go back to
your real homes now.
-I was right to believe
in you.
ALL: Huh?
-Warning!
Hey, warning!
We're getting carried
away here!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN): Now
can we find some food?
Please?
Guys?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
What?
More human child get spirit?
Yummm.
RIKA (NARRATING): I don't know
who that guy is, but he's
creeping me out.
Maybe we'll find it next time
on "Digimon, Digital Monsters."
(theme music)