NARRATOR: Koji and Takuya were
still stuck inside that
bug-eyed Sakkakumon.
Zoe, JP and Tommy Spirit Evolved
to help them, but they
couldn't get back inside.
Unfortunately, Dusmon did.
Desperate to determine his
connection with Koji, he
squeezed Koji's memories
about his dad and
step-mom out of him.
Duskmon was about to destroy
Koji when Bokomon's baby
unleashed a new power source.
Lobomon and KendoGarurumon
Fusion Spirit Evolved into
BeoWolfmon!
Meanwhile, Takuya battled and
beat IceLeomon, but couldn't
get to Koji in time to help.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-moo-ah! Huh!
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Digimon!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Ugh, this
is driving me crazy.
Why I can't I get out of
this stupid place?
I can't even tell which
is up anymore.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I don't know which way is up,
down, sideways, inside out, or
any other kind of way
in this darn maze.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Precisely.
[laughter]
Trapped like the rat thou art.
Methinks it's time for the
cat to have his sport.
-Huh?
Ay-yi-yi.
Which is the right one?
Huh?
Whoa!
Great choice, Takuya!
I can't believe I
survived that.
Huh?
Jeez, how many mirrors
does one world need?
Just a mirror.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Or is it?
-Huh?
Mercurymon!
What do you want?
-Just a trifle, really.
To defeat thee, destroy
thy companions,
and claim this world.
But first, I have
a little secret.
-Hey.
Do you think this would bounce?
-Ugh.
Give me that.
Do you think this will bounce.
You nincompoop.
-Zoe?
Are you OK?
-I'm just wondering if we can
get in there and help Takuya,
and if he'll ever make
it out without us.
-Look!
Something's happening.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Something's
always happening, kid.
-Huh?
Takuya!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
Not just Takuya.
Check it out!
-Keep your stupid secret,
metal brain.
It's time you and I
went head to head.
I've been itching to defeat
you since day one.
-If only thy mouth were thy
weapon, then surely thou
couldst never be defeated.
-Enough talking!
-Eager to perish?
For truly, there is no other
option, if thou art so foolish
as to face me alone.
Thou hast days of experience
with this world.
I have a lifetime.
My knowledge could fill a book,
and of course, chapter
one would begin with an
attention catching surprise.
Like this.
Impressive, is it not?
Thou couldst never hope to
move with such speed.
Thou art doomed to failure
before thou even starts.
-Oh, yeah?
Huh?
Man, you sure like
to talk a lot.
Must be because you're
too afraid to clam
up and fight me.
All right, fine.
I get your little joke.
I guess you're ready
for a fight, then!
Huh?
[laughter]
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN): I see
thou hath reached chapter two,
about the futility of sparring
with me in mine own world.
Here I can move with
ease from any
polished surface to another.
I can dodge thy punches,
strike without warning.
Look around thyself.
I can be anywhere.
Even right behind thee.
[laughter]
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Quit cheating!
Come out and fight like a
man, fair and square.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Peek-a-boo.
-Ah-ha!
There you are.
-What's fair for me
is deadly to thee.
And so is this.
See if thou can dodge these.
Dance for me, fool!
Ha ha ha!
Chapter three, the so-called
hero runs for his life, even
though there is no escape.
I am everywhere in this world.
Here I have absolute power,
and thou hast nothing!
Well, 'tis not quite true.
Thou hast the chance
to be destroyed.
Ha ha ha!
-You're the one who's
going down!
Come out and fight!
-Very well.
Then chapter four shall be about
how I crush thee like a
boot crushes the tiniest bug.
Oh-ho!
No!
Nice try, but breaking mirrors
will only bring thee bad luck.
-I have plenty of bad luck
to send your way.
You're going to find that I'm
more than you bargained for.
-Heh.
-So let me start by
heating things up.
Pyro Punch!
-Didst thou forget this?
-Dark Reflection!
A taste of thine own medicine.
[screaming]
-Now, follow me to
the next chapter.
-What for?
-'Tis time to bear witness
before thou art defeated.
-How about I defeat
you, first?
-Plan to sneak up on
me, didst thou?
-Know nothing know it all!
[screaming]
-Where am I now?
How many places are there
in this stupid place?
Whoa.
Is this what he wanted
to show me?
Aw, who am I kidding?
I'm sure whatever it is is gonna
be a lot less pretty,
and a lot more painful.
All right, Mercurymon.
Let's get this over with!
Mercurymon!
[organ sounds]
-Come on.
Aren't you sick of hiding
from me yet?
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Who's hiding?
-Stop doing that!
-My aren't thou jumpy?
One might accidentally get the
notion that thou art afraid.
-Quit messing around, or I'll
burn this place down!
-Very well, but surely thou
can ask nicer than that.
-Quit stalling!
-Huh?
-Chapter five, Revelation.
-It's Seraphimon.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Very good.
It seems thou art not quite
as dull as I thought.
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN): But
that's not possible.
He was turned into a Digi-Egg!
-Strike of the Seven Stars!
-It's impossible!
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN): How
little thou knowest of the
Digital World.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Seraphimon?
-It can't be.
I mean, it can't be, right?
-It's probably another one
for Mercurymon's tricks.
-My eyes are stuck.
-Release him now!
-Alas, 'tis not really
a him to release.
-What do you mean?
-'Tis only a shadow,
a copy of his data.
But, if thou insist.
It need not be restrained
for me to use it thus.
-No!
This can't be!
-But it is.
I have become more powerful
than thou canst imagine.
I am ShadowSeraphimon!
Wish to fight me now,
pathetic whelp?
Ha ha ha!
Prepare for thy doom.
-People keep saying that,
but I'm still around.
-Well then, let's change
that, shall we?
[screaming]
-Takuya!
-Why is Seraphimon fighting
Agunimon?
And how is Seraphimon even there
if we have his Digi-Egg?
-He's not.
Mercurymon is using Seraphimon's
data to evolve
that evil no-goodnik.
-How'd he do that?
-I'm not sure, but I'd recognize
that felonious fiend
even if he were disguised as a
little girl selling cookies.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Cookies.
-Had enough?
-I'm just getting started.
Slide Evolution!
BurningGreymon!
-Oh, you again?
-Pyro Barrage!
-Shadow Starbust!
[screaming]
-Ha ha ha!
Nothing in this world can
stand against me.
-I won't give up.
I can't.
-I can't believe we have
to watch this happen.
-Mercurymon was so strong
before, but now with
Seraphimon's power, there's just
no way Takuya can defeat him.
-Not quite.
There is one way.
-Fusion Evolution!
-You mean like what Koji
used against Duskmon?
-Exactly.
Then he might be powerful
enough to defeat
ShadowSeraphimon.
-And I bet he'll have a
nifty costume, too.
-But will Takuya even
know to try it?
-And can he evolve before
it's too late?
-Pyro Barrage!
-Thy antics bore me.
Shadow Shockwave!
'Tis time to write thy final
chapter, you meddlesome child.
Strike of the Seven
Dark Stars!
[screaming]
-Takuya!
-Ah, but first, one last gift.
A little place for thee to
take a long, long nap.
-You haven't beaten me yet.
-Then allow me the pleasure of
correcting that oversight.
-No!
Takuya!
-It's all over.
How's he supposed to Fusion
Evolve if he can't even pick
himself up?
-Don't say that.
One thing about Takuya, he
never, ever gives up, no
matter what.
So we are not gonna
give up on him!
We just have to help
him somehow.
-He's right.
We just have to figure
out how.
-Yes, but I don't know if
there's anything we can do if
we're so far away.
-Well then, let's get
back in there!
-Back in?
Do you know how bored I was
waiting for you to get out?
-I don't care.
-Takuya needs our help!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Beetlemon!
-Kazemon!
-Kumamon!
-Hold on, Takuya.
We're on our way!
-But how are we gonna get in?
-Our old standby.
Working together.
Lightning Blitz!
-Ready?
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Come on, come on!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Hurry!
We don't have much time!
-Fear not.
Soon it shall all be over.
What?
No witty quips?
-Why waste my breath
on a jerk like you?
-'Twill be purest pleasure
to destroy thee.
-If you can hear
me, Seraphimon,
please, please help us.
[screaming]
-Takuya!
-Huh?
My baby helped, too.
-What trickery be this?
-Huh?
My Human Spirit and
my Beast Spirit.
This is a new evolution.
You're in for a big surprise.
-Do your worst.
What?
This cannot be!
Thou doth not frighten me.
Seriously.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, then tell me something.
Do I scare you now?
[screaming]
-Execute now!
Fusion Evolution!
Aldamon!
-Impossible!
-Yeah!
-Get him, Aldamon!
-It really worked.
Of course, I knew it was going
to work all along. hen have I
ever steered you guys wrong?
Now, get that data
stealing creep.
-Impressive.
But thou still cannot stand
against my power.
Strike of the Seven
Dark Stars!
No!
Stay back!
-You know, that thing really
seems to be more
your size than mine.
Atomic Inferno!
[screaming]
-It's purification time.
And it couldn't have happened
to a meaner guy.
Fractal Code Digitize!
-Hey, look.
-I don't like the looks
of this thing.
-I'm sure glad you're in
charge of the egg.
-I think we're all glad
about that right now.
Huh?
-Is it over?
-Not yet.
-That plan was ruined.
But I can still win here.
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Don't be so sure.
-Aldamon.
Looking to repeat
thy defeat here?
-No.
To teach you what defeat
really means.
-Hah!
Thou art a confident opponent.
I shall grant thee that.
But confidence is still
no match for the
skill and power I possess.
-Just like you're
no match for me.
Solar Wind Destroyer!
-This can't be.
-I have a book of my own
with a surprise ending.
You're finished, Mercurymon.
-No!
Even without my mirrors, I
possess enough power to
destroy thee.
-Right.
-No!
Stop!
Thou cannot get past
my shield.
It shall repel thy attack.
-Hah.
I'll go around it, then.
-No!
[screaming]
-It's over.
You won't hurt me or my
friends ever again.
Fractal Code Digitize!
Hey, everybody!
Guess who just kicked
Mercurymon's patootie?
So how are the rest
of you guys doing?
What the heck's wrong
with Bokomon?
-We don't know.
-He was zapped by Seraphimon's
data.
-What is happening?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): The egg.
It's hatching!
-You mean Seraphimon's
being born right now?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): This is the
most beautiful thing ever!
And the smokiest.
-Hey.
Who is that?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, it's Patamon.
-Hi, everybody.
-He's my-- he's my
little baby.
Now come say hi to mama!
-Huh?
-You want it to call you mama?
-Mama.
-Well, who else carried that egg
for weeks while the rest
of you lollygagged around?
-Lollygagged?
-Is he crazy?
[arguing]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Fine.
Then no one gets to
play with him.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): But
he's so cute!
NARRATOR: Great.
Someone else to worry about.
See if they can handle this
crisis on the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.