NARRATOR: Finally, the guys made
it to Forest Terminal.
Only no one was there.
Down the road at a castle,
they met Sorcermon and
Seraphimon, who told everybody
how the legendary warriors
came to be.
But then Grumblemon and the
other goons attacked.
Mercurymon beat Seraphimon
and all that was
left him was a Digi-Egg.
Takuya and the others escaped
on a trailmon but Sorcermon
stayed behind to fight.
So here they are, left alone
again with nothing but a
Digi-Egg to keep them company.
And they won't even know what
to do with it until they can
find Ophanimon.
Too bad no one knows
where she is.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a spirit evolution.
Digimon.
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon.
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon.
-Whoa!
-Hey, bud.
Could you possibly
go any faster?
-No problem.
Just hang on your bandana.
-Koji!
-What?
-Whoa!
-I was being sarcastic.
-Zoe, is everyone
OK back there?
-We've all been better.
-One way is fun, the other
way we're done.
-Oh, man.
There's two of them.
-What?
-How do tell which
is the right way?
-Don't know.
The direction of the trails
is up to the rails.
We're on the right track now.
-Well, at least it's a little
bit smoother in here.
[whimpering]
-Hm.
May I have a word?
I want you to give me
Seraphimon's egg.
I'll take care of it now.
-Huh?
-I'm sorry, but I happen
to know more
about its special needs.
-Special needs?
Like what?
-It must be protected and
nurtured by someone with life
experience.
-Have you been a mommy before?
-You sure look like one.
-Hands off, bub.
We must wash our hands before
touching the egg.
Honestly, what were
you thinking?
You might get germs on him.
Don't worry, baby.
Mama will keep you
safe from them.
-Hold on, guys.
It's getting rough again!
-Mama's got you.
Mama's got you.
Huh?
Hm.
This is definitely not
good for the baby.
-I always say one good track
deserves another.
End of the line and
all is fine.
Happy trails.
-Bye.
-That's pretty scary.
He's got to go backwards
all the way home.
-Hey, everybody.
There's an opening up ahead.
-Let's just hope it
gets us outside.
-Yeah.
-Hey--
Huh?
Aw.
-This doesn't look like
outside to me.
Does this look like
outside to you?
-Well, duh.
It's an underground cavern.
-Where's the exit?
-Must be one somewhere.
-Right.
-Hey, wait for me!
If Grumblemon finds us down
here, we'll be in big trouble.
-Let him find us.
I'm not afraid of that
stupid runt.
-Wow.
Are you trying to impress me
with a show of courage, J.P.?
-I'm not trying to
show anything.
Give me a break, will you?
Grumblemon stole your spirit
and I want to get it back.
It's as simple as that.
-I'm uh--
-Maybe we should just turn back
and fight him and get
this over with.
-Do you really mean that?
-Yeah, you better believe it.
-Well, it's your funeral.
-Can I change my mind?
-Which way those brats go now?
Why my life have to
be so difficult?
Only matter of time before
me get back beast spirit.
Me find them no matter
where they hiding.
Where you going?
Me not finished talking,
Arbormon.
-Talk is cheap.
Come on.
Time waits for no mon, right?
-Him make no sense but maybe
him know right direction.
-Mercurymon?
Anybody in there?
You holding out on me, spiky?
Hm?
So, tell me.
What are you going to do the
data you swiped from
Seraphimon?
I mean, you are planning
to give it to
Lord Cherubimon, right?
-Dost thou not trust me?
-Take it easy.
I was just wondering.
Come on.
What's the big secret.
You must be hiding something.
-Ah.
Alas, poor Grumblemon.
-Huh?
-He searcheth in vain
for yon children.
-Well, even if he found them,
what would he do?
The brats pilfered his beast
spirit last time.
Some warrior.
[laughter]
-Hm.
Thou shouldst take care to speak
ill of Grumblemon when
thou has yet to find thine
own beast spirit.
-Hey.
That was a mean thing
to say to me.
-'Tis not mean. 'Tis but the
simple truth, Ranamon.
-When I want your truth,
I'll ask for it, sugar.
-What fools these mon can be.
-Doesn't seem to be
any give at all.
These walls are made
out of solid rock.
-Yeah, this stupid cave
is a dead end.
Beans!
-Guess we got to go back.
-That's what I was saying.
-I wonder if we passed an exit
somewhere back in the tunnels.
It's worth a try.
-Tommy!
-I don't feel so
good, J.P.
-Oh, Jeez.
Are you all right, little man?
-Mm hm.
-Hey, how come nobody
yelled out my name?
[screams]
-Mama mia!
-Definitely not good.
[roars]
-What's Whamon doing
down here?
He lives in the ocean.
-Who is Whamon?
-He's a whale, Digimon.
And he seems to be quite
out of his element.
-I can't stand it anymore.
Do you hear me?
I can't stand it.
-He's ordinarily a
gentle Digimon.
Something really must
be upsetting him.
-I want to go home.
I want to go home.
-We've got to stop him.
-Um, all right.
I'm ready to go when you are.
-Execute spirit evolution.
-Lobomon.
-Agunimon.
-All right big guy.
Just calm down.
Yeah, what is the
matter with you?
-Leave me alone!
-More same.
Which way this time?
-I say we choose the path
of least resistance.
-Why for you always
make things up?
-Yeah, I'll don't make this
stuff up on purpose.
It just sort of comes
to me, right?
-What?
Now me more confused
than before.
Huh?
What that noise?
Oh, the trailmon.
Now I see.
Brats in cave.
But that did end.
Go get them.
[singing]
Me know where you stop.
Me find there no escape.
-You seem to be feeling a little
bit better now, Whamon.
Can you tell us why
you were so upset?
-Oh, I hate this place.
I just want to go back to
my home in the ocean.
Until very recently,
I was swimming--
happy and free under the sea.
Not a care in the world.
Then one day, I saw
these delicious
looking glowing plants.
I couldn't help myself.
I decided to take
a little nibble.
Oh, they were good.
-Mm hm.
This look like good place
eat fractal code.
Me hungry.
Seismic sledge.
Tasty.
-Whoa.
What--
what's happening to me?
Help me!
Whoa.
Next thing I knew, I was stuck
in this place with no way out.
No!
-Here we go again.
You don't have to be such
a big cry baby.
-He's sure losing a lot of water.
Is that normal?
-No idea.
-This is embarrassing.
Does he really think all
that blubbering is
going to help him?
-Hey, are you OK, J.P.?
-I'll be fine once I get
this pain to go away.
-And-- and-- and-- it's all my
fault that you guys got hurt.
I'm so sorry.
-You're forgiven, all right?
-Well, at least you have
some company now.
We're stuck here, too.
Maybe with your help we can
figure out a way to escape.
-Huh?
OK.
[screams]
-What is happening?
-Whamon!
-Now that is not normal.
-Grumblemon!
-Nowhere hide now.
-Me find you.
Me so glad we see each
other again.
Only this time, me steal
your spirits good.
-You're an annoying
little gnome.
You know that?
-Yeah.
What he said.
Oh, by the way, you're not
stealing anything from anyone
ever again.
We're not afraid of you
anymore, Grumblemon.
-Na na na Grumblemon.
You will be.
Looking good.
You may taken Gigismon spirit,
but me have other powers.
You no can beat me.
Your spirits be mine.
Me first to find you, so
Mercurymon and others no will
have you now.
Me too late for them.
Meet my new friends.
Get them!
-Let's turn these rocks
into pebbles.
Pyro tornado.
-Lobokendo.
-Excuse me, gentlemen.
We could use some assistance
over here.
-Be right there.
-We're on the way.
-Prevention is always the
best medicine, right?
-Hey!
Let go!
-No!
You can't fight in
this condition.
-She's right.
The best thing we could
do now is hide.
-Hey, good hiding.
You're invisible.
-Over here, brainiac.
-Oh, wow.
You're pretty fast, too.
-You meat head.
The only reason I'm hiding is
because I have to protect
Seraphimon's egg.
-Mm hm.
-I refuse to just hide
and give up.
-J.P., you're too badly
hurt right now.
Agunimon and Lobomon will
think of something.
We have to trust them.
-Come on, Zoe. Think.
If only I could spirit evolve.
-Come here.
How about a little dance?
Dance!
Come on, dance.
There.
That's better.
-Stay on ropes, Arbormon.
Keep going.
-These guys are very graceful.
-Me can smell spirits.
Hurry up and get for me.
-I don't know how long they
can keep this up.
-J.P. what are you doing?
-Tommy--
-Yeah.
-I'm going in.
You watch out for Zoe.
-He's lost it.
-Yeah.
He can't stop them.
-That it biggy boy.
Spirit evolve.
Fight me!
Or is you too weak?
-He's just egging you on.
Get out of there.
-I'm not going to let him win.
I won't stand here and let
Grumblemon hurt my friends.
-I'm with ya.
-Are you sure?
-Uh huh.
-Execute spirit evolution.
Oh, Kumamon.
-Beetlemon.
-Go Golemon!
-You ready to rock
these blockheads?
-Yup. Let's roll.
-Thunder fist.
-Crystal breathe.
-I'm tired of playing
with you.
I'm going to make you pay
for what you've done.
-You're kidding right?
-Thunder fist.
-Super plume.
-Weak human.
Fighting you I not even
work up sweat.
Arbormon, take care of them
while me get spirit.
-I'm on it Grumble.
But first I gotta change into
something more comfortable.
Arbormon slide evolution.
Petaldramon.
-Huh?
-Much better.
-Seismic sledge.
-Blasting spout.
-No way!
Whamon.
I can't believe it .
The beast spirit.
Could that be mine?
-Hey! No fair.
That spirit mine.
-Oh, so that's what it was.
It did taste a little
gamey for a plant.
-You can't have spirit.
It's mine, mine, mine, mine.
-Not today.
It's my turn to play.
-Ow.
-Execute beast spirit
evolution.
MetalKabuterimon.
-Oh my.
It's the legendary beast
warrior of thunder.
-Molto bene.
J.P. turned into him?
-Ball of thunder.
-Yikes!
Run for your lives!
-Uh oh.
He's completely out
of control.
Head for cover.
-Right behind you.
-Into every life, a little
ice must fall, right?
-Don't he hasty now, friend.
-You're no friend of
mine, Grumblemon.
You don't even understand the
meaning of friendship.
Electron cannon.
[screams]
-MetalKabuterimon
slide evolution.
Beetlemon.
It's back to the egg
for you, pal.
Fractal code digitize.
-Hey, welcome back.
[grunts]
-J.P. J.P. are you all right?
-Got your spirit back.
At least I did something
to make you happy.
-That's so sweet.
Thank you, J.P. I
really mean it.
-Happy day.
-Friends!
Dim your hearing!
-Did we die?
-I don't think so.
It smells like something did.
Pee yew.
-Whoa.
-It's the ocean.
-It's Whamon.
-I don't know how you saved
us, but thank you.
-Yeah, and welcome
home, Whamon.
-Oh, I'm the one who should
be thanking you.
Without your help, I might
have been stuck
in that cave forever.
Hold on everybody.
We should be reaching the
island very soon.
-Uh, island?
NARRATOR: Now that Grumblemon is
out of the way, you'd think
it'd be smooth sailing.
But I bet there's another storm
brewing on the next
Digimon Digital Monsters.