NARRATOR: Sakkakumon decided the
guys needed a little one
on one attention, so he split
them all up to face their
personal demons.
Tommy had some unresolved stuff
with his brother to work
out, and Asuramon was more
than willing to help.
Meanwhile, Koji was plagued
by his deepest fears about
friendship.
Karatenmon thought he got the
best of him, but he didn't
count on KendoGarurumon.
Koji promptly beat him
just to shut him up.
As it turns out, Asuramon was
just pretending to be Tommy's
friend so he could
steal his spirit.
But Tommy's spirit evolved to
Korikakumon and digitized the
three faced freak!
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we head for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards on solution
through a spirit evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Oh.
I really am gorgeous.
Wait a minute.
Why am I looking at this dinky
thing when I could use the
whole darn ocean as a mirror?
Looks like I have yet
another fan here.
All right, sugar.
Tell me, who's the fairest
of them all?
-Prepare thyself.
-Hey, that's Mercurymon.
-It takes not a genius to see
that the fairest in all the
land is thee.
-Now, that's what a girl
wants to hear.
-Or 'tis what I would have said
before the fairest of the
fair entered the land.
By that, I mean Kazemon.
-You what?
-And the strongest and bravest
must surely be Zephyrmon.
-Hey, watch it, metal head!
-But I merely repeat what
everyone says, that you
couldst never hope to
defeat her, my lady.
-We'll just see about that.
She'll go from the fairest to
the foulest faster than you
can whistle Dixie.
-This is too easy.
No matter who wins the fight, I
shall have one less problem.
-The others must still be
inside of that thing.
-Yes.
Let's just hope they make
it out in one piece.
-A piece of what?
-You've got to have faith.
If I was able to make it
out, then so can they.
-I hope you're right, Tommy, but
if they could get out, why
haven't they?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Takuya?
JP?
Where is everyone?
Jeez, if you yell in the forest
and no-one hears you,
is there really any point
in yelling at all?
-I can't believe what
I'm beholding.
The mean one really exists.
-It's beyond me that
anyone could be so
beastly to our beloved.
-It's because she's jealous
of Ranamon.
But we'll put her where she
belongs, right boys?
-No-one messes with Ranamon
and her fans!
Yeah!
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
The Honeybeemon's
speed makes them dangerous.
Luckily, they're not
so sift upstairs.
-Alone again.
You'd think I'd be used
to it by now.
(THINKING) Seems like I
always end up alone.
-Ow.
-You OK?
-I guess, but my shoe's
hurting my foot.
-That doesn't look too bad.
Here, try this.
-That feels great.
-I'm glad.
-Wow, thank you.
-Why don't we walk together
for a little while?
You know, just in case that
bandage doesn't hold.
-I didn't think you'd be so
nice after what the other
girls said.
-Oh.
-Sorry, that didn't really
come out right.
-That's OK.
I'm kind of used to it by now.
Those girls have been mean
to me ever since I
came back from Italy.
But listen, I'll totally
understand if you want to go
and catch up to them.
-Are you kidding?
You're nicer than all of
them put together.
-Thanks.
-Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't you join our group
for dinner later?
-(THINKING) She seemed
so nice, too.
Oh, well.
Better find the others.
-Be prepared.
When she's beneath
the cage-- hey.
She's making a beeline
for the other path!
-Huh?
Aw.
-Come on!
-We were so close!
-Huh?
Look like you guys could
use a little help.
-If you'd be so kind.
-Hold on a second.
I'll get you out.
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Kazemon!
-Unbelievable!
KAZEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Stand back!
All right, guys.
You're all clear.
-Thank you!
-We don't know what would
have become of us.
Thanks so much.
-Take care.
-Ugh.
Can you believe her?
-Being all phony about caring.
-She'll be sorry.
-This web will catch her before
she can believe it.
-Ah!
I don't believe it.
Here she comes!
-Betrayed by our own trap.
-Sorry, but would it be
too much trouble?
-No problem.
Hurricane Wing!
-We owe you beyond
a mere thanks.
-You sure do.
-Ah!
Before long, she'll want
to enslave us.
-Then we must stop her.
-And when we do, Ranamon
will love us forever.
-Right!
Let's get her!
-Here she comes!
-We have her for sure.
-Ah!
[shouting]
-Oh, great.
A dead end.
Wait, maybe it's not.
I hope this works.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Now where am I?
And where's everybody else?
Man, this world takes confusion
to a whole new level.
Hey, at least there's nothing
here I have to fight.
[screeching]
-Whoa.
[roaring]
-Well, here we go again.
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN): If
he doesn't get you with his
razor sharp claws, Parrotmon
will defeat you with his Sonic
Destroyer attack.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Agunimon!
-Sonic Destroyer!
Sonic Destroyer!
-Pyro Darts!
How's that for a hot foot?
No way I'm going out
as bird food!
Pyro Punch!
[shouting]
-Time for some purification.
All right, bird brain.
Let's put you back
in your cage.
Fractal code digitize!
Bye bye, birdy.
Huh?
What are you looking at?
Wait a second, what is this?
It almost feels alive.
Whoa.
-Honey bread, oh
beautiful one?
-Before that, try
some honey ice.
-I--
-Let her finish her
honey juice.
-Thanks.
-It's our most beloved drink.
-Well, it's great.
-Just be sure to have some ice
before you get too full.
I beseech you.
-Well, of course I will.
I'm sure if it's anything like
juice, I'll just love it.
-And please don't be
afraid that it's
going to make you fat.
That's what always
worried Rana--
-Thanks once again for bailing
us out of everything that
befell us.
-I was glad to do it.
And anyway, I should be thanking
you for all this
delicious food.
-No problem.
Besides, if not for you, we
wouldn't even be here.
-Hey, you guys need
to eat, too.
Food's always better if you
eat it with someone else.
-Ah!
-Dirty double crossers.
I've got to do everything
myself.
-There.
Ranamon!
-My, what lovely flowers.
Are they for me?
-Sure.
Who else would they be for?
-And now, here's a little
something for you and your
numbskull friends to give
to that bratty girl.
Make sure she eats it.
This apple's going to
give her the worst
nightmares she's ever had.
And just a word to the wise,
if you mess this up, you're
out of the fan club, honey.
-Yeah, but--
-Just do it!
-An apple for us?
-No.
I brought this for her.
Here.
-For me?
Thank you.
Looks delicious.
HONEYBEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Wait!
-What?
-Oh, nothing.
-OK.
Mm.
Thanks, guys.
This turned out to
be a great day.
HONEYBEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Zoe!
[laughter]
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN): What's
the matter, sugar?
Feeling a little under
the weather?
Let the nightmare begin!
[laughter]
-Hey, guys.
Can I help?
-I doubt it.
-Yeah, besides, if it isn't
pasta, she probably
wouldn't eat it.
GIRL (OFFSCREEN): Zoe!
-Huh?
-What are you doing just
standing over there, Zoe?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Well, I--
-Are you gonna join us
for dinner, or what?
-Yeah.
-Well, come on.
GIRL (OFFSCREEN): You
must be kidding.
Her?
-Huh?
-If she's going to eat
here, then I'm not.
-Me either.
Weirdo.
-Go back to Italy.
Maybe somebody likes
you there.
-I guess, then, maybe you
should, you know, go back to
your own group, Zoe.
We're already using all of our
pots and pans, and junk.
Sorry.
-Liar!
-I'm sorry!
-Wait!
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN): Oh,
what's wrong, sugar?
Did our little beauty queen
wannabe just realize what I
always knew?
That no one really likes you?
Must be hard to be
s unpopular.
-Man, I would kill for
a cheeseburger.
Actually, knowing this world and
my luck, I'd probably get
eaten by a cheeseburger.
Hey, wait, what are those?
Cherries?
Those are better than a
cheeseburger, because they're
actually here!
-Come here, I got somethin'
for ya.
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
Cherrymon,
evolved from Woodmon.
He's like Woodmon's
older, bigger,
and much meaner brother.
-Cherry Blast!
Chew on those, pallie.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Beetlemon!
-Oh, I'm scared.
Not.
Cherry Blast!
-Thunder Fist!
Lightning Blitz!
Looks like someone's hungry for
some purification pie, and
I'm just the guy to pass
out the plates.
Fractal code digitize!
Huh?
Aw.
I can't eat that.
Wait, maybe it's a way out.
[shouting]
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
We'll catch you!
-That was a bad idea.
-You made it out!
-We were worried.
Did you bring me a present?
-No.
-See?
They are gonna make it out,
just like I said.
-Oh, no!
Look, it's Zoe and Ranamon.
-I have friends.
-Please.
They're just pretending,
sugar.
When you're not around, they
say all sorts of bad things
about you.
-That's not true, is it?
My friends wouldn't
be that mean.
But then again, how could I know
for sure whether or not
they're lying to me?
Lots of people seem
nice at first.
GIRL (OFFSCREEN): Sorry.
-Liar!
-I'm sorry!
-Wait!
-So I was cruel right
back to her.
That's not right.
I shouldn't have been mean.
I'm gonna try harder
to be nicer.
I'll be a better person.
-Oh, you are such a
goodie two-shoes!
Uh-oh.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Kazemon!
-All right, miss perfect.
You think you're so hot?
Well, you're not as smart
as you think.
See those Honeybeemon
over there?
You thought they cared about
you, didn't you?
Well, let me let you in on a
little secret, honey pie.
They're really working for me,
and they despise you like
everyone else does.
What's that look for?
-Wha!
-You're still in the fanclub,
so you little insects better
start cheering for me, or
you're next on the list.
Got it?
-Yeah.
Yay.
-Ha!
-Now, that's better.
Draining Rain!
-Whoa!
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Whipping Waves!
-Whoa!
-What's the matter?
Hard to do your little
kicks when you're
so far off the ground?
Here, let me help you down.
It's all over, girlie girl!
-I can't believe it's
over so quick.
-Huh?
-It's not!
Tempest Twist!
-Why, you horrible
little brat!
Oh, you're going to pay
so big for that.
-Oh, yeah?
Slide Evolution!
Zephyrmon!
-So beautiful!
-Oh, please.
Slide Evolution!
Now, what do you say?
-So ugly!
But it's still Ranamon.
Quick, before she gets mad.
Yay!
CALMARAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Lay off the face!
What's wrong?
Little water logged?
-Yay, yay!
Yay, yay!
Yay!
-See?
No one's on your side.
It's time I clipped your
wings for good.
Titanic Tempest!
Well, well.
Looks like everything's right
with the world again.
What's more, I am the prettiest
and the strongest.
Now, give me that cheering!
Huh?
-Sorry, but you're still as
ugly and weak as ever.
-Yeah!
You are beyond great.
-So strong.
-And really nice.
-From now on, we're gonna
be your number one fans.
-Thanks, guys.
CALMARAMON (OFFSCREEN): What?
How dare you turn on me,
you little runts!
Acid Ink!
Take a good look, boys, before
your new queen melts into an
ugly ball of muck!
-Don't listen to her.
You still have inner beauty.
-The only thing that's melting
is our hearts.
[shouting]
-Where's my cheering?
-How about this instead?
Hurricane Gale!
[shouting]
-[inaudible], remember?
-For you, I'll make
an exception.
Plasma Paws!
[shouting]
-A gift?
You shouldn't have.
Slide Evolution!
Kazemon!
Ranamon, your reign is over.
I'd say it's been fun,
but it hasn't.
Fractal code digitize!
See ya, "sugah." It's one thing
to be nice, but it's
another to be a big pushover.
[cheering]
-Huh?
Hey, guys.
Guess what?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): You
brought me a present?
-No.
-What is it, Zoe?
-Why not?
-Ranamon's gone.
-Yes, and long live Zoe!
-She's the best.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Let
me see that.
You guys might be members
of the Zoe fan
club, but I'm the president.
-Wait, where are the others?
-I'm afraid the eyes
have them.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): I thought
they'd be here by now, but I'm
starting to wonder if they'll
ever get out.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): They will.
I hope.
NARRATOR: But if they
don't, how will they
save the Digital World?
Or get home?
See if everything will work
out on the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.