RIKA (NARRATING): On their way
to Forest Terminal, the gang
wound up at Wind Factory,
Incorporated.
There, they met the Kokuwamon, a
group of machine Digimon who
were being forced into slave
labor by the Goblimon.
So Takuya came up with a plan
to save the little guys.
Once the fighting started,
they all met the
head honcho, Snimon.
Poor JP, being the only one who
didn't have a spirit, felt
totally useless.
But when the Spirit of Thunder
was uncovered, JP jumped at
the chance to spirit evolve
to Beetlemon.
He used his Thunder Fist to
squash Snimon like the big ol'
bug that he was.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we leave
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together, the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
If we're all for one world,
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE
ECHOES FROM ABOVE]
[grunting with effort]
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): Hello?
-Huh?
-A hero!
Quickly, please.
You must release us.
KARATSUKENUMEMON (OFFSCREEN):
You'll scare him off!
Don't be so pushy!
KARATSUKENUMEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Don't want to stay in here.
Release us, release us!
[karatsukenumemon scream]
-Aaahhhhh!
What?
No money?
Out!
-(IN UNISON) Whoooa!
-Please come back--
when you're not just a
bunch of deadbeats.
-But we're really hungry,
and we do have money.
See?
Right here.
Awww.
-You have money?
Let me see it.
Oh, mm.
You call this stuff money?
Frankly, I would have
thrown you out of
that restaurant, too.
Ugh.
-Wha?
-So what's money like in
the Digital World?
You're so smart, how do we get
our hands on some, huh?
-Uh, it's simple.
Stop being so lazy
and go to work.
-Huh?
-You want us kids to work?
That's what an allowance
is for.
-Can't you just lend us some?
-(IN UNISON) Yeah,
hand it over.
-Ah.
-Ha-ha!
-Big bucks!
-As you can see, I'm without
funds, as well.
ALL: Hmm.
-Now come on, you nincompoops.
Follow me.
JP (OFFSCREEN): [whining]
-Oh!
It's time to go.
-That's not going.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): We're
still hungry.
-Yeah, we gotta eat something.
-Anything!
-Aaah, huh?
-Uh-huh?
-Hey, you guys, take
a look at that.
-Huh?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
"Heroes Wanted.
All your meals for free."
Rock solid!
-I'm brave enough to eat.
[laughter]
-Hey there!
-Huh?
-Uhhhh.
-We're heroes?
-Ahhhhh!
[train whistle]
-There's the train.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Duh.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Shouldn't
we hide?
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN): Chugga,
chugga, chugga.
Oh boy!
Tunnel!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Wish
we knew what these guys
wanted us to do.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Relax.
I'm sure they have a good plan.
[all yell]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): I hope
all their plans aren't as
crazy as this one.
-One day, a mean creature named
Grumblemon attacked.
We're peaceful.
We can't fight him
by ourselves.
-He demanded our mountain's
fractal code, and we told him
we don't even know
where it is.
But he thinks we're lying, so
that's why we need you heroes.
Whoo, whoo!
Whoa, that's bright!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Don't worry.
We'll take care of him.
Right guys?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Right.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): I guess.
-Whatever.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Boys?
I'm not sure I understand
this.
Why can't he just take
the fractal code?
-We already talked about this.
As I said, the source
of all energy in the
Digital World is data.
Everything-- mountains,
rivers, villages--
everything that's solid matter
is made up of energy, so it
has fractal code.
Only in some places, the code
is out in the open, and in
some places, it's hidden.
Try to remember that.
-I'm afraid there's more
of our story to tell.
Grumblemon took all of our
women to trade for the
mountain's fractal code.
-That's horrible!
-Man, guys can sure be
jerks sometimes.
So that's why you
wanted our help?
To save your women?
-Yes.
-Just leave everything to us.
-(IN UNISON) We are in
your debt, heroes.
-Mmm.
All right, now about
that chow.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Uh-oh.
-Huh?
Hold on, you want us to
ride through that?
In this?
Are you snails insane?
[all screaming and hollering]
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): At least
this incline can slow us down!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
Slowing down?
We're speeding up!
[screaming]
-How is it staying
on the tracks?
-Actually, I don't
think it is.
[screaming]
[crash]
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Well,
that wasn't so bad.
JP (OFFSCREEN): What's your
definition of bad?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Falling
off of this cliff.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Cliff?
[whining with fear]
SNAIL (OFFSCREEN):
Come on, heroes.
What are you all waiting for?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Are
you kidding me?
Sticking to the side of a
mountain may be fine for you
guys, but one slip, and
we're gravel pancakes!
-Just how do you propose
we get up to you?
We can't cling to walls.
Uh?
Aaah!
-Climb up, you guys.
It's fun.
-Oh, I'm and learning a bunch
of new definitions.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Come on.
[all whimpering with fear]
-Well, you know what say.
Ladies first.
So, after you.
-Mmm.
-Guhh?
-Hmpf!
-I, uh--
-Ugh.
I'm wearing a skirt.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Oh--
no, wait, I--
no, really, I--
As if you didn't know, sicko!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Aaah!
[all grunting with effort]
SNAIL (OFFSCREEN): You're
almost there.
-That's great.
-Huh?
Who's that?
Hey, wait!
-Yes!
Huh?
You're here?
-You're the people these
guys found to help out?
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-Kouji.
-Yeah, none of us could
find any food either.
-Hey, don't lump me
in with you guys.
These kids aren't going to be
able to help you at all.
-I'll help you, right
upside the head.
-Well, at least give
us a chance.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
I mean, look at you.
The only thing you guys'd
do is get in my way.
Can I help it if you're
not up to my level?
-Watch it, Stick
Boy, or I'll--
-Gentlemen, please.
My thanks to all of you
for coming to help.
And now, it's time to eat.
-(IN UNISON) All right!
Time to chow down!
Huh?
Aaahhhhh!
-Well, at least we'll get
some good food to
make us feel better.
-Is that what I think it is?
-I don't know.
Looks like rabbit food.
-Well, at least rabbits
get to eat.
-Oh!
-Here goes nothing.
Alllp.
Mm, mmm.
(SURPRISED) Mmm.
Molto bono.
Dig in!
Tastes like steak.
-(IN UNISON) Huh?
Huh.
Hmm.
[satisfied chewing]
-Mine tastes like chicken.
-Mine's like a potato.
-Mine is just like asparagus.
ALL (IN UNISON): Yuck!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
I like asparagus.
How'd he get here, anyway?
-Oh, he fell from the sky.
-He did what?
-He fell.
Aaaaaaaahhhhhhh!
-Well, we finish, and the
universe throws a
human into the works.
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): Grumblemon
has the captives in a cave.
It's right about here.
We'll have to get in
and out quickly.
[snails groan worriedly]
-Just relax.
SNAILS: Aaahh.
-Have no fear.
Leave everything to us
legendary warriors.
-Aaaaahhh!
-What's the matter?
-(CHATTERING) You mean all of
you are legendary warriors?
-Yeah!
In the flesh.
[snails grumbling]
-Hey, what got them
so worked up?
-Believe me, I'd have trouble
believing you're legendary
warriors, too.
-I bet they're in awe of us.
-Ahem.
It's time to go to bed.
-And I say it's time for
us to rescue the girls.
-Uh, no, no.
Get some rest first, and
then you can tackle
the job in the morning.
-Huh?
Uh, OK.
SNAIL (OFFSCREEN): Now
off to bed with you.
[snoring]
-What?
-Huh?
Hey, you know, I didn't like you
at first, but you're all
right, helping out the
KaratsukeNumemon and all.
-Hmph.
-Huh?
-They helped me first.
But don't think I'll help you.
-Hmph.
TAKUYA (THINKING): Yeah, like
I'd even want your help.
Man, that's a long way down.
[gasp]
Long way down?
[screaming]
-What's going on here?
-You don't wanna know!
-Rrrrrngh.
-What are you doing?
-We'll give you back
to your partner in
exchange for our women.
-You dirty sneaks!
Is that why you brought
us here?
-Hmph.
I think it is you who are
the dirty sneaks.
Pretending to be caring, helpful
strangers, when you're
really legendary warriors.
-I don't understand!
What's wrong with that?
-The time for your games
and lies is over.
Soon you'll be back
with your ally.
-Ally?
What are you talking about?
-Don't play dumb.
We know you're all in league
with Grumblemon.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): This
can't get any worse!
-Huh?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
(GUTTURALLY) Now give fractal
code, or bad things be happen.
-Oh, yeah?
Says who?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Say me!
And you say me two words,
you know who I am.
You call me Grumblemon!
-Aaaahh!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Ooh,
look at that symbol.
-He's also a-- a legendary
warrior?
-Give fractal code, or else.
You not want see what
"or else" is.
-I didn't realize there were
bad Legendary Warriors.
-Why for you make yo-yos?
-Grumblemon, if you want to save
your allies, give us back
our women now.
-Those knives a little
close there.
-What so?
Me no care what happen
to weak human things.
-Hm?
Hmph.
-No!
ELDER KARATSUKENUMEMON
(OFFSCREEN): Wait!
You mean you really don't
care about them?
But they're Legendary
Warriors too.
-Huh?
These weaklings be Legendary
Warriors?
Hm.
Me think somebody got their
hands on some spirits and took
them when they shouldn't have.
Now I to put my hands on you and
take them all right back!
-(IN UNISON): Huh?
-So!
-Wait, what's going on here?
You mean you aren't allies?
-That's what we've been
trying to tell you!
-Nnnnnnngggaahhhh!
-Watch out!
-Grrr.
-Aaaaaaaaahhhhh!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Kouji!
(SHOUTING) Spirit!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Lobomon!
-Aaauughhhhh!
Yaaaaahhhhhh!
-Nnnnnggghhhhhaaaaah!
-Howling Laser!
-I'm so sorry.
I have made a grave mistake.
-Look, there's no time
for that now.
But later--
Huh?
[grumblemon snarling]
-[chortles menacingly]
Nnngah!
-Aaaaahhh!
-Nngggah!
-Aaauughhh!
-Nnnggghhh!
-Aaaaghhhhhh!
-Lobomon!
-We have to Spirit Evolve, too.
-Right!
-(IN UNISON) Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Rrrahhhh!
Rah! Rah!
Agunimon!
-Beetlemon!
-Hyah!
Hah!
Kazemon!
-Kumamon!
Hah!
-[cackling]
Huh?
-Careful.
You can hurt someone
with this.
AGUNIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Don't you think it's
time you gave up?
-Give me your hand!
Cut the macho act, and
give me your hand!
-Ohhh.
-Hwah!
Pyro Dart!
-Lightning Blitz!
-Yaaaaghhhh!
-So you want to start digging,
or should I?
-Thanks.
-Prego.
Glad to do it.
-OK, guys.
Here's the plan.
While I'm finding Grumblemon,
you free the captives and get
all the KaratsukeNumemon
someplace safe.
You got it?
-You bet!
-Mm-hm.
-Grrrngh.
-What's wrong now?
-We don't know where
Grumblemon is.
-You don't know?
-Huh?
-You trying to get shot?
-Rrrahhhhh!
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): Away now!
-You should have just
let me handle it.
-Aauuughhhhhh!
-Peeky-boo.
-Agunimon!
Get out of the way!
-That's enough!
-Yes!
Arggh.
Now where are you?
GRUMBLEMON: You want guess?
-Huh?
GRUMBLEMON: Too late!
-Auuughhhhhhh!
-Hurricane Wind!
-Right this way, ladies.
[KARATSUKENUMEMON CHATTERING
HAPPILY]
-We owe you a great debt,
brave heroes.
[thunderclap]
-Oh, rain!
ELDER KARATSUKENUMEMON
(OFFSCREEN):
Careful, it's slick!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN): You
don't have to tell us.
Whoa, look at that!
All that rain is tumbling down
the mountain like a--
wait a minute.
That gives me an idea.
Hey, Grumblemon, were are you
hiding, you fraidy-cat?
-Yaaaarrrrghhh
-Thunder Fist!
-[cackling]
Nice shot, dorkus.
Huh?
Wwwwaauuuuughhhhhhh!
-Nice job!
-Yeah, it was, wasn't it?
But where are the captives?
-There!
-Huh?
KARATSUKENUMEMON CHATTERING]
-Boy, it sure must be nice to
get back to your family.
Hey, what's that?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): It must be the
mountain's fractal code.
Oh, no!
Grumblemon!
GRUMBLEMON: Oooh, look like
I find what I want anyway.
And thank you.
I never find without you.
Now get rid you!
-(IN UNISON) Huh?
-Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
Gigasmon!
-Ahh!
-Rawwrr!
Quagmire Twister!
-Whoaaa!
-Aaaahh!
-Auuugghhhh!
-Hey, grab on to me!
Frozen Tundra!
-Whew, that was close.
-Execute.
Slide Evolution!
That it?
That best you do with
your spirits?
That pathetic.
Even make pathetic look good.
Execute.
Beast Spirit Evolution!
You joke!
-Wait a minute, what's
going on?
Rhino Boy has two evolutions.
-Now I take fractal code
in name of Cherubimon.
Hah!
Fractal Code Digitize!
[rumbling]
-Our mountain is no more!
[screaming]
ELDER KARATSUKENUMEMON
(OFFSCREEN): Our homes!
Our life!
Gone!
[karatsukenumemon weeping]
RIKA (NARRATING): Can anyone
stop that lamebrain?
Can the guys even
save themselves?
Find out on the next "Digimon,
Digital Monsters."
(theme music)