BOKOMON (VOICEOVER): With only
four areas of the digital
world left unscanned, it was up
to poor little Gotsumon to
save his home.
But even Takuya and the gang
couldn't stop those rotten
royals from stealing the data.
Seraphimon's castle was next
on the list, so Gotsumon
joined the team and they all
set off to protect it.
Koji and Gotsumon took on the
Knightmon while the rest ran
off to find the key to
the castle's data.
When Gotsumon evolved to
Meteormon, it looked like the
tide had turned, but Dynasmon's
bad breath of
wyvern turned the place
to digital dust.
Oh, dear.
Now there are only
two areas left.
THEME SONG: Digimon.
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
I am the one.
Digimon.
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon.
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
If we're all for one world
I am the one.
Digimon.
NARRATOR (VOICEOVER): The
digital world is in ruins.
There's not much left but small
pockets of ravaged land
and the occasional
Trailmon track--
all of this destruction caused
by the Royal Knights.
[evil laughter]
-It's beautiful.
-The revival of Lord
Lucemon draws near.
[evil laughter]
-My spirit boomerang
lets me see things.
And in this case I see
the Royal Knights.
This is bad news, my friends.
They are headed this way.
-Oh.
-Just as we thought.
-Yeah.
-What do you mean?
-See that machine?
That's our way of seeing things
from far away, except
it looks busted.
-I look into this box and
see nothing, and yet
I can't stop staring.
-Hey.
Come one you recycled hunk
of-- ah, there we go.
-It's like we're looking
down from the moon.
-There are only two parts of
the digital world left
unscanned--
Ophanimon's castle, that's this
green area, and the snowy
area here, the Autumn Leaf
Fair, where we are now.
So we had a choice to make.
-OK, so?
-So nobody's ever been able to
figure out where the fractal
code for the area surrounding
Ophanimon's castle is hidden.
Am I right?
-Right as rain, my
bandana-headed friend.
-And that means the Royal
Knights will be heading here
first, just like we figured.
And we'll be here.
-So that's what you meant by,
just as we thought, huh?
Oh, my friends are so smart.
I shall do the dance of smarty
pants, smarty pants, smarty
pants.
-Uh, dude?
We really do appreciate
that a lot, but, uh,
you can stop now.
[nervous laughter]
-All full.
Move them out, please.
-Yeah, baby.
Whoa, we're moving now.
Oh, yeah.
-Wait!
Hey, wait for us!
Don't leave.
You gotta take us with you.
[whistle blowing]
-Wait!
-Hold on.
And just Where do you
think you're going?
-Please save us.
-Hey, don't worry about it.
We're gonna make sure we take
every one of you to a nice
safe place.
-Do you really mean it?
-Of course she does.
Now get in line like
everyone else.
-This is fun.
We should have a sing along.
Who knows "Wheels
on the Train?"
(SINGING) The wheels on the
train go round and round.
-Neemon, you are really
not helping.
-Looking good there, J.P.
NEEMON (SINGING): Round and
round all through the town.
Woo, woo!
-Neemon!
I am going insane.
J.P. (VOICEOVER): This is by far
my biggest, coolest magic
trick ever-- nothing up my
sleeve, and presto, a whole
new neighborhood layout.
-There's more than one way to
protect this fair's data, and
this is it.
Almost got it.
Breaking up this town
will break up it's
fractal code as well.
Then the Royal Knights won't
be able to scan it, and the
town will be safe.
Do I rock or what?
-Heads up.
-Datamon, Does this
thingy go in here?
-You got it.
-OK.
-We got it.
-So what are you guys
working on?
-A snow catapult.
-When those Royal Knights show
up here, we're gonna greet the
two of them with a face
full of snowballs.
Pow!
They won't know what hit them.
[laughing]
-You mean a snowball fight?
-Yeah.
Well, I know it won't defeat
the Royal Knights all by
itself, but it might help,
and it's better than
doing nothing at all.
-Hm.
You're right.
EmperorGreymon and
MagnaGarurumon are pretty strong,
but they're going to
need every bit of help
we can give them.
-Mm hm.
[yelling and crashing noise]
-Oh, are you OK?
-Yeah.
-Here, let me help.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Gee, Tommy.
Who would have imagined that
after we stole everybody's
detectors and caused you all
that trouble, we'd actually
end up working together?
-It's always best to
forgive and forget.
-Well, we won't forget.
None of us will ever
forget you.
You could have just gone home,
but instead you came
back to help us.
I know we might have gotten off
on the wrong foot, but I
sure am glad we got to be
friends in the end.
And you know what?
We've been keeping
an eye on you.
And every time we hear about
your victories and progress,
it gives us the strength
to keep going.
So I guess now we're
your biggest fans.
-There you are.
-We got all the Digimon to
safety except you guys.
-Ah, hold your horses.
We're almost done.
-Well, hurry up.
[shudder of distress]
-What?
What's wrong?
-The Royal Knights.
Something is heading
right for them.
They've got friends.
-Who are they?
-Well, uh, let's see.
Zanbamon.
Gryphonmon.
Pteramon.
Grankuwagamon.
Airdramon.
-Open fire.
-Right!
-Ah, they're going to attack
the Royal Knights.
-They'll get creamed.
We gotta help them.
Unity execute.
Unified spirit evolution!
[yelling]
-Unity execute.
Unified spirit evolution!
[yelling]
-EmperorGreymon.
-Magnagarurumon.
-You guys hold down the fort.
We'll be right back.
-Gotcha.
-And get these guys
someplace safe.
-You got it.
-Mm hm.
-Be careful, you guys!
All right, everyone.
The last Trailmon is waiting to
take you guys out of here.
Let's go.
-Well, goodbye.
-Good luck.
-See you soon.
-Adios.
-We believe in you, friends.
-Mystic flame.
[strangled yell]
-And who might you be?
-We've come to put and end to
your reign of destruction.
If those human children can
stand and fight, so can we.
-Your bravery is so amusing.
But soon you shall taste
defeat, and I
shall devour your data.
-I think not.
-Vorpal blade!
Rah!
Huh?
Where did she go?
-Looking for someone?
-Huh?
[aggressive yell]
[sounds of struggle]
[loud crack]
-What?
[sounds of confusion]
[nasty laughter]
-Nicely done.
You cut your own
sword in half.
-Why, oh why are we bothering
with you weaklings anyway?
-Who are you calling weak?
-That'd be you, silly.
Care to do something about it?
-Dimension scissors.
-Solo roar.
[roaring]
-Missile storm.
-Right back at you,
my lovelies.
[yells of distress]
-Three down, two to go.
Who's next?
-Not so fast, lady.
-Well, well.
I've got something
special for you.
-Spiral masquerade.
[sounds of distress]
[explosion]
[yelling]
[evil laughter]
-Dragon thrower.
[blasting sounds]
[evil laughter]
-Gone, all of them gone.
This isn't good, not
good at all.
-You have to get on.
Goodbye, everyone.
-All clear.
Go, Trailmon.
[distressed sounds]
EMPERORGREYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Hey!
Why don't you pick on somebody
your own size?
-What?
-Enough is enough.
We're here to end this.
-Excellent.
Finally, a worthy foe.
So far, this has been
quite boring.
-Be careful what you wish for.
You just might get it.
And you're about to get more
than you can handle.
-You have inherited the power of
the 10 Legendary Warriors.
-Now you are the only ones who
can save the digital world.
-And that's exactly what
we plan to do.
-Ha!
You don't stand a chance.
-OK, guys.
The town's fractal code
is all broken up.
Even if they do find it, the
Royal Knights won't be able to
scan it unless they put
it back together.
-If they want to find
it, they'll have
to get through us.
-(VOICEOVER) I'm so worried.
What if someone gets hurt?
TOMMY (VOICEOVER): This
catapult is awesome.
Those guys won't know
what hit them.
ZOE (VOICEOVER): With
all of us pulling
together, this has to work.
KOICHI (VOICEOVER):
Don't worry, Koji.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
NEEMON (VOICEOVER): If we had
cherry syrup, we could make
snow cones.
-Get ready, guys.
Here they come.
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE AND
SWORDS CLASHING]
-I see you've gotten better
since last we met.
-You ain't seen nothing yet.
-Oh, I can't wait.
-Dragon's roar!
-Feral fire!
[explosion]
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE AND
SWORDS CLASHING]
-Guys, shouldn't we
fire the catapult?
-No, just hang on.
They're not close enough yet.
-I think this has gone
on long enough.
-I'm just getting warmed up.
-Ooh, I'm all aquiver.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): A
little to the left.
No, back to the right.
There!
Wait till he's out of the way.
-Right.
-Huh?
-Just where do you think
you're going?
-Ready, aim, fire!
-Fire one!
-How dare you?
-Quickly!
-Right.
-Fire two!
-Not the face!
[yelling]
[crashing noise]
-Bye, bye now.
-And hello there.
-Huh?
-I wouldn't get up
if I were you.
-Yeah?
Well, you're not me.
-EmperorGreymon.
-Well, then let me help you.
[crashing sound]
-Still not staying down.
[yelling]
-You should learn to take
advice from your elders.
-Spiral masquerade!
[sounds of struggle]
KOICHI (OFFSCREEN): Tell me
when I can fire, Tommy.
-Not yet.
I can't get a clear shot because
she won't stop moving.
-You're kidding me.
We gotta do something.
-EmperorGreymon's
in real trouble.
-What?
-We gotta help.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): I see him!
Oh, man.
He's in trouble all right.
Let her rip!
-Fire!
-Oh, no.
It melted before it got there.
-Takuya, you have
to fight back!
[evil laughter]
-Enjoying the burn?
-More than you could
ever imagine.
-What do you mean?
-I guess you forgot.
Fire is my element.
[yelling]
-Very good.
Stop, drop, and roll.
You paid attention in class.
And now--
[evil laughter]
-OK.
-It's time to end this battle
once and for all.
-Now, you guys.
Fire!
-You got it.
-[inaudible].
-[inaudible]
[yelling]
-Huh?
What?
Not again.
I remember the first
time this happened.
Dynasmon and Crusadermon
unleashed their attacks.
And Baromon tried
to protect us.
But instead--
-Is everyone all right?
Oh, dear.
They got the fractal code
knocked out of them.
KOICHI (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
Everyone's data was visible
except mine.
I was OK, I mean, relatively
speaking.
Magnagarurumon, EmperorGreymon,
and I were the
only ones left conscious to
face the Royal Knights.
And then when we wound up on
the moon, everyone was out
cold except me.
I don't get it.
It just doesn't make
any sense.
-Koji!
-Why?
Why does everyone keep getting
hurt except for me?
-You mean you don't know?
-Huh?
-Haven't you realized you're
different from the others?
-No.
What do you mean different?
-In this world, data comes
only from those with a
physical form.
You, Koichi, have no
Terribly sorry.
[nasty laughter]
-No.
Then I'm just--
-A spirit only.
-Back off!
-No!
Get back here and tell
me the truth, please!
[sounds of struggle]
-I can do this all day.
-I spy something I've
been looking for.
So if you'll excuse me.
[big crash]
-It's mine.
Impossible!
It's too slow.
Where's the rest of it?
-Well, here we are again.
Shall we dance or fight?
-Decisions, decisions.
I say fight.
-Sounds good to me, pinky.
That is if you think
you're ready.
-Please.
I was born ready for
the likes of you.
Make your move.
-After you.
DYNASMON (OFFSCREEN):
Crusadermon.
I found the fractal code.
It's here.
Help me!
-But of course.
-Come back here.
-Get off of me.
-Spiral masquerade!
-Starburst hunter!
-Excellent.
Here's another piece.
So the data is in fragments.
Then I guess I'll just have
to find them all.
-Oh, no you won't.
-Oh, yes he will.
-Hey.
You were battling me.
-Dynasmon, hurry up.
[crashing noise]
-There's another.
-Tommy, are you OK?
-Yeah, I think so.
-What happened to us?
-Where are Takuya and Koji?
-They're still fighting.
-And another.
[SOUNDS OF STRUGGLE AND
SWORDS CLASHING]
[crashing noise]
-That should be it.
Now, let's see.
This one should go right here.
And this one should
go right here.
[sounds of struggle]
-You've stolen your last piece
of data, and you'll never hurt
another innocent
Digimon again.
-One more piece after
this one.
-Dragonfire crossbow!
[yelling]
-I don't think so!
-I claim this data in the
name of Lord Lucemon.
-Not if I can help it.
Pyro dragons!
[yelling]
-Crusadermon!
-I've got it!
-She's gonna get the data!
-How right you are.
Ha ha!
[sounds of distress and fear]
-Don't worry, guys.
We've gotcha.
-Oh, how touching.
And now to take this beautiful
gift to Lord Lucemon.
[evil laughter]
-Wow.
The Autumn Leaf Fair is gone.
-Thanks to those
rotten royals.
-Well, at least we're all OK.
-Yeah, but they escaped
with the town's data.
-Its all right.
You did everything you could.
-You sure did.
-And we know where
they're going.
There's only one area left.
-If they did that last bit of
fractal code, then Lucemon
will be revived, and we
can't let that happen.
-Right.
-OK, then.
Let's go to Ophanimon's
castle.
BOKOMON (VOICEOVER): After all
this time, it comes down to
one last stand.
Can we finally defeat
the Royal Knights?
Find out on the next "Digimon,
Digital Monsters."