ZOE NARRATING: DigiDestined
hunted high and
low for their D-Tectors.
But those birdbrained Toucanmon
flew off with them.
When they tried to swim after
the birds, some Gomamon
stopped them, which is good,
since they were about to swim
into some nasty whirlpools.
So they all set sail on
a raft they built.
But wouldn't you know it?
Ranamon attacked!
She knocked Kazemon to
the ocean floor.
But there, Zoe found
her beast spirit
and evolved to Zephyrmon!
The whirlpools calmed
and the beastie
Calmaramon was defeated.
But the Toucanmon and the guys'
D-Tectors had already left.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
there's a world for us all!
Digimon!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Wow!
This is working great!
We should get to that Autumn
Leaf Fair thingy in no time.
-Let's hope so.
-And let's hope the Toucanmon
are there.
-Uhh!
-Ooh!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): How
can anyone sleep
at a time like this?
Doesn't he know we have
important things to do?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Like what?
Sweep up the raft?
Relax!
-[yawns]
Now, to make whoever has them
D-Tectors pay for making me
work so hard.
-I can't believe you
traded those
D-Tectors for that thing.
What were you thinking?
-Be quiet.
At least, I'm able to think.
Now, let's see.
Hey, I can't see anything!
It's all dark!
-I bet the old guy
swindled you.
I told you not to trade
with that sly fox.
But I guess, you never
listen to me, do you?
-What?
You say something?
-Ehh!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Man, we
are cooking along now!
-Well, maybe cooking isn't
really the right word.
-Yeah.
I can't feel my fingers.
Uh.
Ha?
-Take it.
-Yeah? You sure?
-Uh-huh.
-Grazie!
You're the best.
-Uhh.
(THINKING) Why won't
she say that to me?
Aaah.
-Ooh!
Neemon, wake up!
You can't sleep in the cold.
You'll freeze to death!
[kids gasp]
-Hey, look at that!
-Huh?
Um, what are we looking at?
-Land ahead!
[kids gasp]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): That
was way better than I
thought it'd be.
But where's that Autumn
Fair thing?
-Hm.
It should be just up ahead.
-Well, there is something
ahead.
-(TOGETHER) Ha?
-But it doesn't look
very fair!
-Everyone, hold on to something
so we don't
fall off the raft!
[group shrieking]
-Oh, oh, it's not over yet!
-Whoa!
-What is that?
-(TOGETHER) A snowman?
Oh!
[shrieks]
JP (OFFSCREEN): Now, that's
more what I was expecting.
[group groaning]
-Hey, it's warm here.
-It's warm?
Why is it warm?
-Maybe that!
-(TOGETHER) Whoa!
-Hey!
It's the fair thingy!
-Ugh, how I despise crowds.
-Even if those Toucanmon are
here, it will be like finding
the tiniest needle ever in
a million haystacks.
-So shall we split up
and get looking?
-(TOGETHER) Hm-mm.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): They're
really colorful.
And they're really
super annoying.
Have you seen them?
-Nope, sorry.
-So they've been around?
-Hm, hm-mm.
-Oh.
-And it's really important
that we find them.
-Wish we could help.
-Oh.
-Not even one?
-[sighs]
---the Digital World's future.
Oh.
-I haven't seen them.
-OK, thanks.
What if we never find them?
The Digital World is doomed.
And we'll never get
to go back home.
Hm, mm, mm.
I'm going to find them
no matter what!
Uh, a trading post!
Maybe the Toucanmon
stopped in there.
[electronic beeps]
-Anybody home?
Ooh.
Hello?
-Yeah, what?
Can't you see I'm busy here?
OPHANIMON NARRATING: Datamon
is great with any kind of
machine or electronic device.
But he's not so good
with people.
-Hm.
-And I'm the command--
-That's being busy?
-Oh!
Aw!
(ANGRILY) Yes, it is!
Come on, come on, oh!
No, no, no!
Oh, ow, aahh!
Now, I have to start
all over again! Oh, you.
[sobs]
-Hey, why don't you let me
take a shot at that?
-Do what?
You're just a human child!
-Video games are my specialty.
Um!
-OK, now, be careful
about-- oh!
You got to be.
-Hm.
-And watch out for
the-- oh, OK.
Mister, good!
So, tell me, are all human
children as good as you?
-Nope, just me.
-Hm-mm.
-It's the mother ship!
-OK, OK.
Don't panic.
Don't-- ooh, good,
yeah, OK, OK.
Come on, you can, oh!
But you can, oh, aiie,
excellent! -Ha!
-[laughs]
-Oh, yeah!
[laughs]
Hey, it looks like
I won something.
So what did I win anyway?
-Oh, that.
Oh, it's just nothing.
-So what are you going
to do with it?
-That's none of your business.
-Whoa, wait a minute!
Our D-Tectors!
-Really?
These things are called
D-Tectors, ha?
-They belong to me
and my friends.
Give it!
-You must have a cracked
transistor.
These are mine, kid.
-It was the Toucanmon.
They stole them.
Then they came here and traded
our stuff to you!
-Yeah, right.
You should write books
if you can think up
stories like that.
-It's not just a story.
It's the truth, I swear!
You have to believe me!
-Yeah, yeah.
I don't have to do anything.
Do you have any proof?
-Not really.
Wait, give me one, and
I'll spirit-evolve!
-Nice try, kid.
I give you this thing, then
you'll run right out
the door with it.
Hah!
You remind me of me when
I was younger.
-The Toucanmon really
stole them.
-Knock it off and
get out of here!
-Isn't there anything I can
do to convince you?
-Look, I'm running a business.
If you want them, you'll
have to trade for them.
-Whoa, will you give them
to me for my hat?
-No sale!
-Will you trade them
for these?
-Hmph!
Come on.
What are you trying to do?
Make me puke?
-Oh!
Wha-- what are you doing?
[static]
-I have to test these out.
Make sure they're good for the
next person to buy them.
Unlike you, I don't lie
about my stuff.
-Next person?
-Hm, this one needs fixing.
-Oh!
No, cut it out!
You're going to break it!
-Oh, yeah?
I could do what I want
with this thing.
It's mine now, kid.
-Oh!
Please, Mister!
[sobs]
[phone rings]
-Hrrrm.
All right, all right.
Don't blow a gasket.
Yeah?
ARBORMON (ON PHONE):
Hey, yourself!
Nobody's got no respect.
Youse the guy with a
Toucanmon, right?
-Ha?
ARBORMON (ON PHONE): The
Toucanmon, the Toucan--
geez, why am I talking?
Just to hear myself
speak here?
They brought in the
spirit, remember?
[toucanmon crying]
DATAMON (ON PHONE):
Oh, yeah, right.
-I'll be there in an
hour to get them.
Got it?
You make sure they're still
there, or else!
You understand?
-Yeah, sure.
I understand.
I have no idea what he's
talking about.
Oh, knock it off,
would you kid?
-Ahh!
Oh.
You broke it.
-Quit your belly-aching.
I didn't break it.
I think I broke this thing.
No, I can fix it.
I'll open up one of the other
ones to see what it's supposed to look like.
Come on.
-Will you stop!
I don't care about mine.
But don't break another one!
Oh!
[sobs]
-Look, what's with
all the brouhaha?
-I know I'm just a little kid,
and I only get in the away
most of the time.
But Takuya and JP and Koji and
Zoe, they're different.
They're going to
save the world.
But they have to have those
D-Tectors to do it!
-Hm.
I tell you what.
-What?
-I owe you for winning
the game.
I'll give you one hour to
find something to trade.
-Ha-ha!
[clock bell rings]
-Huh?
-But just an hour, got it?
Not a minute longer.
And don't you dare breathe
a word of this to anyone.
I can't have customers thinking
that I've gone soft
around the diode.
Do you know what I mean?
-Right, one hour.
-Actually, now, it's
just 58 minutes.
-Uh, you won't regret
this, I swear.
-Mm-hm.
All right.
Now, back to fixing
this thing.
Oh, of course!
I just have to find the circuit
that leads to that
relay switch.
Simple!
Eenie, meenie, miny, moe,
catch a tiger--
-[panting]
I got to hurry and find them.
Takuya! Koji!
JP!
Zoe!
Oh, just perfect.
Now, they're lost!
Well, I'll just have to
find a way to make
this work all by myself.
But I need some help to do it.
Hm.
OK, I'll do it alone.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Whoa!
That Tommy sure can run fast.
Hey, wait, where
are you going?
-No tickets!
All right!
Shove off!
-Aah!
-Urrh!
-Hey, now, what gives?
-Yeah, what's with the giving?
-No ticket, no ride, nohow!
Whoo-hoo!
-Nobody's seen them.
You have any luck?
-Nothing Those dumb birds
probably traded the D-Tectors
and left.
-Whee!
-Ha?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Another plate.
[crowd chanting "eat, eat"]
-Is that JP?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Come on.
[crowd chanting "eat, eat"]
-Excuse me.
-(TOGETHER) Ha?
-[burps] I'm finished.
-JP, what are you doing?
-I thought that maybe the
Toucanmon ate here.
And it turns out
that they did.
But then I saw that sign.
-Ha?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
"Eat 30 plates and
win an amazing prize"?
Oh, brother!
Listen, buddy, you're supposed
to be finding the D-Tectors,
not stuffing yourself!
-Yeah, but finding
is tough work.
And I had to keep
my strength up.
Plus, I thought maybe
the Toucanmon
paid with the D-Tectors.
And they're the prize.
Well, Zoe thought that.
-Zoe's here?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): More food!
Come on!
Can't you see I'm done here?
Give me the next plate!
-Zoe ate all of those?
Where does she put it all?
-Well, she is a growing girl.
-[panting]
Oh, I'll never find anything
to trade out here.
-Finally, we're here.
-Aaah!
-Ah!
Wait up!
-(TOUCANMAN TOGETHER)
We're not waiting.
We're scramming!
[crowd chants "eat, eat"]
-30 plates.
Ugh.
-Hey!
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
-I was looking for the
Toucanmon, and I saw Tommy
leave town!
-(KOJI AND TAKUYA) What?
-Just a little more, and OK!
That circuit is fixed up.
Now, I'll just transfer
the data.
Simple!
Ooh!
Hehehe!
This baby is going to sing.
-Stop!
I really mean it this time.
When I catch you, I'll put a--
-You'll never catch us!
-Ah!
Is this what you two traded
all our D-Tectors for? Isn't it?
I'm taking it!
-Where are you going?
Come back!
-I guess, I can't leave
them like this.
-Help us!
-Hm!
Then again, you did
steal our stuff.
So you're just getting
what you deserve.
-Wait!
Don't go away!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, I can't.
[panting]
Here! Grab ahold!
Give me your wing.
No!
-Thanks for the help, sucker!
[toucanman laughing]
-I saved your lives.
You can't just go.
-Just watch us.
[laughs]
-Now, I'll never get
the D-Tectors.
Hmm.
-There, at last, my masterpiece
is complete.
[laughs]
15 minutes.
I almost hope the
kid makes it.
[panting]
-Tommy?
[sighs]
Tommy!
[kids gasping]
[tommy sobs]
-Hey, what's the matter?
-[bawling]
-Eeyahh!
Knock, knock.
It always pays to be
polite, right?
-Check.
You were real polite
to my door.
Aah!
-Youse got something these
bird brains traded.
And I want it.
[clock bell rings]
-Hm?
-Hey, I'm talking to you!
Take this thing back and give
me the other things.
-Maybe.
But first I have to check
out the goods.
-Yeah, well, you better be
quick about it, or else.
-Huh?
Ahh.
Sorry, buddy.
Looks like I'm going to
have to turn down
your generous offer.
-That's better. What?
-I have another customer.
Hand it over or you'll never
have another customer.
Arbormon slide evolution!
Petaldramon!
Leaf Cyclone!
[explosion]
-That's it!
No one messes with my store!
Nano Swarm!
[snickers]
-[snickers]
-Ha?
-Leaf Cyclone!
-Uh!
-Whoa!
-Petaldramon!
-Hm!
Oho, this should be good!
-Oh.
-Oh, my.
-Hey, are you all
right, Datamon?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, it's you.
-[sobs]
I couldn't find anything
to trade.
And I tried so hard.
-Heh, you did just fine, kid.
You ever hear the expression
that truth is
the greatest treasure?
-No.
-[roars]
Ooh-whoa, oh!
-Go on, take it.
-Huh?
-You know, at first, I just
thought you were making up
stories because you wanted
these things so badly.
But you truly deserve
to have them.
-Hm!
-Here.
-Thanks, Datamon.
-But, uh, don't tell anyone
about soft, OK?
[laughs]
It's not broken.
But I did add something.
-Like what?
-What you won in the game.
It's really yours after all.
-Hm?
My beast spirit!
You are awesome, Datamon!
-[chuckles]
-(TOGETHER) Aah!
-Rrrarrhh!
-Ah.
-[roars]
-Hrrngh!
Execute!
Beast spirit evolution!
Yes!
Korikakumon!
-Aargh.
-Ooh.
-Korikakumon, Legendary
Beast Warrior of Ice.
-So it really is true.
Humans have the power to
turn into Digimon.
[both growling and grunting]
-Tommy, what in the world
are you doing?
This is no time for
reflection!
-Behind you, look out!
[crash]
-That's going to leave a mark.
-[growls]
-Avalanche Axes!
[clang]
-[grunts]
-[growls]
-[roars]
-[groans]
-[laughing]
-There's something you
don't see every day.
-He can't control his spirit.
He sure looks silly,
doesn't he?
-Not as silly as you look
trying to beat up your
friends, Mr. "Pot Calling the
Kettle Black." -[growls]
Boy, are you going
to regret that!
[roars]
Thorn Jab!
-Here, catch!
Help out your friend, guys!
-(TOGETHER ) Hm.
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
Agunimon!
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
Rrrahh!
Lobomon!
-How about we heat things
up a little?
Lobo Kendo!
-And now, Frozen Arrow Heads!
-[screams in pain]
-Molto bene!
-I'm just glad I didn't
hurt you guys when I
got my beast spirit.
-Why does everyone have
bring that up?
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE):
DigiDestined.
-Huh?
Ophanimon?
-Seraphimon turned
into a Digi-Egg.
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE):
Yes, I know.
-So what are we supposed
to do about it?
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): Before I
tell you, you must know that
this is a crucial point.
You can stop now, or face the
dangerous road ahead.
Will you accept the risk?
-(TOGETHER) Hm-mm.
-You better believe we will.
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): You must
be certain, all of you.
-I don't think I've ever
been more certain of
anything in my life.
-Me, either.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
-Hm-mm.
-So what we do now, Ophanimon?
OPHANIMON (ON DEVICE): Head
for the Rose Morning Star.
And then--
[static]
-What did you say?
Ophanimon!
-Hmm?
-What is a Rose Morning Star?
-That right there!
[group gasping]
JP (OFFSCREEN): A star?
How are we supposed
to get there?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): We're
not going to the star.
We're going to what's
beneath it.
JP (OFFSCREEN): All that way?
[group sighing]
-It looks pretty far.
We have to walk there?
[group sighing]
-Uh! Presto!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
What are those?
-These are Trailmon tickets.
Remember that eating contest?
Well, this is grand prize for
scarfing 30 plates of that
horrible food in an hour.
Do I rock or what?
[group laughing]
-Well, then come on, guys!
Let's head for that star!
-(TOGETHER) Yeah!
-Whoo-whoo.
ZOE NARRATING: For once, things
seem to be going OK.
It's usually when everything
falls apart.
Find out if they can keep it
together on the next "Digimon--
Digital Monsters."