RIKA NARRATING: Not only did
Duskmon throw BurningGreymon
around like a sack of trash,
he took the Digidestined's
attacks without even
flinching!
Later, Takuya came up with a
plan to defeat him, but that
just started an argument with
Kouji, who knew Duskmon was
too powerful to fight.
But he didn't have much choice,
since the big man
himself showed up and smacked
KendoGarurumon hard, turning
him back into Kouji.
Then things got weird.
It was like Duskmon was in
pain, and then darkness
covered everyone!
Takuya woke up alone in the
Dark Terminal, and with
DarkTrailmon offering him a
chance to go home, he took it.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future, to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a Spirit Evolution!
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Takuya, can
we really beat Duskmon?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): You know,
you worry too much, buddy.
Once we put my new plan into
action, we'll take that
laughing eyeball out
in one shot.
He won't know what hit him!
-Yeah.
That was some plan, all right.
Oh, well.
Doesn't really matter now.
I'm going home.
[screaming]
-This is it, kid.
End of the line.
KOUJI (OFFSCREEN): Huh?
Wait a minute.
This isn't home.
Huh?
Where am I?
[gasp]
-Man, I really gotta stop
landing on my head.
-It's up to you now.
Which one will you choose?
-Whoa!
-Boy, destiny sure involves
a lot of running.
-I get it.
This must be where we all left
for the Digital World.
But--
hey, what's up?
Why am I here?
-Bye, kid.
-Hey!
-[laughing]
-No!
Open up!
Please!
Let me in!
No!
Please!
[screams]
ANNOUNCER (ON PA SYSTEM):
Shibuya Station.
This is Shibuya Station.
-Hey.
-Is that some kind of animal?
-It's a kid in a costume.
-Is it trick or treat
time, Ma?
-Just don't get near him.
-Those are some weird feet.
-Looks like a goat creature.
-Oh, man, my hands!
What's going on?
-Is this some alternate
universe or something?
Wait.
It's my hometown.
It's all the same.
Well, except for me.
Ahh!
Leave me alone!
[crowd screaming]
-Mom!
Dad!
It's-- it's my house.
I made it!
-[gasp]
-Whoa.
-I'm sorry, I--
M-Michi, it's you.
-[screaming]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Wait,
I won't hurt you!
It's me, Takuya!
Don't you recognize me?
Huh?
My face!
No!
Come on, do it!
I want to be myself again!
Just turn me back!
Oh, that's great.
I'm stuck!
What do I do?
I can't go home looking like
some freaked out mutant.
-Mom, I'm back.
-Huh?
Wait a minute.
That's me!
I don't understand.
Huh?
This is-- oh, wow.
I'm going crazy.
This can't be possible.
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): But honey,
you can't be late tonight.
It's Shinya's birthday.
-And tell Dad I want
something big!
A forklift!
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Mind
your manners, Shinya.
And don't even think about
eating that cake, Takuya.
Now, honey, I know that you're
busy, but how would you feel
if the kids didn't acknowledge
your birthday?
-Man, I'm bored.
My whole life is boring.
YURIKO (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
but that time, the kids
were away at camp.
Oh, come on--
-I don't know how,
but it's true.
This is the day I left.
I've come back on the same day
I left for the Digital World.
Mom, I-I remember now.
You had to wake me up, because
I'd overslept.
As usual.
Shinya.
We used to fight all the time,
didn't we, birthday boy?
Dad.
You promised that you'd play
soccer with me next weekend.
But I left.
Why?
I could've been at home with my
family, waiting for Shinya
to blow out the candles
on his stupid cake.
I never should've gone!
-5:40?
I'll never make it!
-What if I didn't make it?
If I don't get on the train,
then everything
will go back to normal!
I'll be me again!
Takuya, you've got
a train to miss!
Don't go!
-What?
OK.
Talk about talking
to yourself.
Oh, man, look at what
time it is.
I've gotta jam!
-Oh!
-The voice said my
destiny's coming.
What could that mean?
I guess I'll find out at
the train station.
-[laughing]
Here it comes!
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
Huh?
-Dad, the ball!
-Sorry.
The phone-- that noise!
-I'll get it!
Kids these days.
-Don't go.
Don't go!
-You OK?
-What?
Oh, no!
Hey, buddy, what time is it?
-What?
Uh, a couple before 5:45.
-Huh?
Oh!
-Hey, kid, where's the fire?
-I gotta figure out a better way
to stop myself, because I
won't stop!
But how?
I remember thinking if I
didn't make it, I was
going to miss out.
Yeah, miss out on hurting
my friends.
-[growling]
-No!
[screaming]
[car horn]
-It wasn't real.
What now?
How can I stop myself if I can't
even think straight?
Don't go!
Takuya!
-Excuse me!
The train's already
on the platform!
Oh, I knew I should have asked
for more allowance!
[beeping]
-Huh?
A ticket?
Maybe this is destiny.
Wait!
My destiny!
-I'm out of time!
But I haven't gotten on
the elevator yet!
There's still a chance!
Good bye, Mom.
Hey, it's Kouji!
Wait a minute.
There's two Koujis?
Man, I'm really losing it.
He looks so much like him,
but that can't be Kouji.
If he's not, then who the
heck is that guy?
ANNOUNCER (ON PA SYSTEM):
Shibuya Station.
This is Shibuya Station.
-Huh?
Hey, wait!
-He's already at the elevator!
-Huh?
It's the other Kouji!
-K-Kouji!
-Man, I really gotta stop
landing on my head!
[crowd chattering]
-Huh?
So weird.
Were all these kids called
here the same way I was?
-It's already gone too far.
I gotta do something!
OK, here goes nothing.
-It's up to you now.
Which one will you choose?
-Hey!
-Why do you think you're
here, Takuya?
-I--
-Answer me!
I wanna know why you're here!
-Kouji.
-Whoa!
-[laughing]
[train horns]
-Guys.
Why did you guys get
on this train?
I mean, was it the message?
-Hey kid, this was the closest
train to the elevator, OK?
Now look, just leave me alone.
-Oh.
Jeez, sorry.
I'm just nervous.
But there must be a reason why
you picked this particular
train, right?
-I'm like him, it was closest
to the elevator.
-Watch this.
Hey, honey, you want
some chocolate?
-Uh.
So who are you?
-I'm--
I'm Tommy.
But I didn't want to
get on this train.
Why are kids always
picking on me?
-Whoa!
[screeching brakes]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Cherubimon
will not rest until
his warriors succeed
in destroying the
entire Digital World.
Only through using the power of
the Spirits all of you have
acquired can we stop Cherubimon,
bring peace to the
Digital World, and restore
it to its original state.
-Bokomon.
Neemon.
-Why do you think you're
here, Takuya?
Why are you here?
Answer me!
-[laughing]
-Kouji!
-Whoa.
I can't just pretend like none
of this ever happened.
Even if I did go home, I'd never
be the person I was.
-Happy birthday!
Now make a wish, Shinya!
-Huh?
And the others.
I can't leave them.
Takuya!
Run!
Get on that train!
Move it!
Go, Takuya!
Go follow your destiny,
Takuya.
Huh?
-[growling]
-No.
I won't run away!
My friends are waiting.
They need me!
And I won't let you
get in the way!
I'm not afraid!
I'm not afraid of you!
No more!
Huh?
DarkTrailmon?
-Well.
I didn't think I'd
see you again.
Thought you wanted to go home.
-I did.
I went home.
But it was the same,
and I wasn't.
I'd turned into this freak
show, because I couldn't
figure out who I was.
-I see.
-Kouji was right.
I didn't know why I was there.
But I do now.
Trailmon, you have
to take me back.
-Are you sure?
Seems to me that's what got you
here in the first place.
-Mm-hmm.
-This is a one way
ticket, kid.
I can't turn around if you
get any second thoughts.
-That's not gonna happen.
I made my decision.
-I guess you have.
All right, then.
All aboard.
-I love you, Mom and Dad.
Happy birthday, Shinya.
See you soon.
And Kouji, this time, things
will be different.
I know it's not a game now.
Hang on.
I'm coming.
I won't let you down--
any of you!
[yells]
-Sounds to me like you figured
things out there, kid.
-[yells]
-Not bad.
Not bad at all.
End of the line.
Or maybe not.
I think that's up to you.
Good luck.
-All right.
This is it.
Everything starts now.
I've got another chance, and
I'm not going to blow it!
RIKA NARRATING: Looks like
Takuya has finally grown up.
I just hope it isn't too late.
To find out, tune into the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters.