NARRATOR: When Takuya beast
spirit evolved to
BurningGreymon, he couldn't
control himself at all.
So Beetlemon and KendoGarurumon
tried to help
him, but they were
pretty useless.
If finally took a lot of
reasoning from little Tommy to
get Takuya to tame
the beast within.
Then it was off to the Forest
Terminal again.
But when the gang got stuck in
the mud, Grumblemon showed up
and grabbed Tommy.
So Takuya beast spirit evolved
and did a little
grabbing of his own.
He took Gigasmon's spirit and
returned Kumamon's to Tommy.
But Grumblemon escaped
and met up with the
evil Legendary Warriors.
Man, those are some
freaky fiends!
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned
as we work towards one
solution through a
spirit evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Hey, where do you think
you're going?
Mercurymon ain't done
with yous yet.
-I going Forest Terminal.
Must get beast spirit back
from annoying kids.
-(GIGGLING) Ooh, sounds
like fun.
-I tried to stop them.
You saw, right?
-Yes, yes.
-These be my brethren?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): I
can't believe it.
We're actually here.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): My
legs can believe it.
Oh.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
There's the sign.
Forest Terminal.
-Um but shouldn't there
be a Trailmon here?
-Yeah, really.
-Huh?
Well, maybe they're on their
way back right now.
Or, uh, you know,
they could be--
oh, man.
-Hey, who cares about
the Trailmon.
There's a restaurant here!
-Welcome, weary travelers!
-What do you have to eat?
-Ask instead what I
don't have to eat!
Step right up, friends, and
don't worry about money.
For you, the first
meal is free.
-Hey!
DERAMON (OFFSCREEN): Now there's
a man who knows what
he likes-- or doesn't
care what he eats.
Yolk surprise coming up!
Dig on in!
-Hail to the chef.
Haha!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): We must
respectfully decline your kind
offer of food.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): I can't
feel my tongue anymore.
-All right, all right.
What's the big idea?
I just can't believe all
of you are going to
turn down free food.
-That was food?
-I'm insulted!
-I'm going to be sick.
-Fine, get out of here, kid.
You're bugging me.
Go on and go to the
Forest Terminal.
They say no one's ever
returned from there.
-Yeah?
Well, we'll just take
our chances.
I doubt the Forest Terminal
will be any
worse than this food.
-Aww, come on, guys.
I was just trying to be
nice, that's all.
-Being nice has nothing
to do with cooking.
And rumors don't matter to us.
We've already been told
that we have to go
to the Forest Terminal.
-Huh?
-Attention--
go to the Forest Terminal
immediately.
-Let's go.
-(HESITANTLY) OK.
-Yeah.
-Do you really think
it's dangerous?
-I don't know.
We've come this far.
We can't turn back.
-Huh?
Hey, don't leave me!
I mean, wait up!
JP (OFFSCREEN): This
place is empty too.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
And just a little bit creepy.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Keep
your eyes peeled, guys.
JP (OFFSCREEN): For what?
All we can see is fog.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Well,
there have to
be some people here.
JP (OFFSCREEN): But what
if they're all ghosts!
[frightened groans]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
I guess we have no
choice but to keep walking.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Man, this world
sure loves its walking.
-Huh?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Great.
Now what?
[beeping sounds]
-Huh?
It's that way.
-Tommy, it's a dead end.
-Yeah.
Are you sure it wasn't
the other way?
-Huh?
Wow.
[gasps]
-And for my next trick.
-Man, I can't see anything
in this fog.
-I know.
We could be attacked.
[beeping noises]
-Hey, maybe my detector's
good for something, too.
[gasps]
-I hate it when I'm right.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): This
place is beautiful.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Doesn't
mean it's not dangerous.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): What if this
is where the person from
our D-Tector lives?
We did get a message
to come here.
-Well, should I knock?
-I still don't think
it's safe.
[beeping noises]
-Oh!
-Well, at least they're
polite, I guess.
-Yeah.
That or eager to lure
us in there.
-I say we go inside.
How bad could it be?
Sleeping Beauty used to live
in a castle in the forest.
-Yeah.
Well, so did the wicked witch.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): We'll never
find out what's in there if we don't go in.
-Hmmph.
Says the kid at the
back of the line.
-Maybe no one lives here.
-Maybe you should open up a
wishful thinking store, Tommy.
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN): Get
back, Cherubimon scum!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Uh,
isn't that Wizardmon?
-But he's a different color.
-And meaner.
-We can beat him just like
we beat Gigasmon.
-Gigasmon?
But he's one of Cherubimon's
goons.
-Yeah.
-So you're not allies
with Cherubimon?
-Are you kidding?
-Look, why don't you put
that wand down, OK?
We're all on the same side.
Isn't that obvious?
-This is what comes of
fighting too much.
Everyone seems to be an enemy.
I apologize, friends.
How did you find this place?
-We got a message that
told us all to come
to the Forest Terminal.
But there was no one there.
And when we kept walking,
we ended up
here on your doorstep.
-Hmm, a message.
Could it be?
My solitude has driven common
courtesy from me.
I apologize.
My name is Sorcermon.
Please, come in.
I have something important
to show you.
DERAMON (OFFSCREEN): Whatever
did I do wrong?
The recipe's clear--
one egg in pasta,
boiled in dirty socks.
Huh?
Aha!
Welcome, travelers!
Your first meal is free.
[growling]
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN): They've
gone to Forest Terminal.
It will be easier
than I thought.
-Where are you taking
us, anyway?
-To meet someone.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): I
bet it's a trap.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): You think
everything's a trap.
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN): Caution
is wise, friends, but only within reason.
This is no trap.
This is a prophecy.
-Wow.
-Tracks.
Fresh.
Little further.
-So where is he?
-Up there.
Allow me to introduce
our salvation--
Seraphimon.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Um, are we
supposed to know who that is?
-Seraphimon was one of the three
Celestial Digimon chosen
to rule this world.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): So what
are we supposed to do?
He's all frozen up.
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Perhaps not for long.
There is a prophecy.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): Let
your light shine as one.
-That was Lady Ophanimon!
She's the one who asked me
to watch over Seraphimon.
-Ophanimon?
She must be the voice that
told us to come here.
-It's all falling into place.
I brought you here because the
prophecy says that one day a
group of wayward humans
will free Seraphimon.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Typical.
Humans get to do everything.
When is my turn?
-How bout next week?
-Be quiet.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Just little further.
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN):
So you keep saying.
-So what did she mean?
-Hey!
I bet it has something to
do with our D-Tectors.
-Hey, guys.
Focus them up there.
-The prophecy!
Welcome back, Lord Seraphimon.
-It's good to be back,
my faithful servant.
You have done well.
-Little further.
-Will you stop that?
-Sorcermon, tell me-- there's
so little I remember.
-My lord, when your defeat
seemed imminent, Ophanimon was
able to get you to safety.
She sealed you away from danger
so you could be revived
after the trouble had passed.
-Ophanimon!
That's right.
Has she been harmed?
Why isn't she here?
-Truth is often unpleasant,
I'm afraid.
No one knows where she is.
But these humans have been
in contact with her,
so all is not lost.
-These humans?
But they're only children.
-Yes, but they're also
legendary warriors.
And if not for them, you'd still
be stuck to the ceiling.
-Legendary warriors?
Impressive.
-Hey, listen.
Just what is going on here?
We've been led all over getting
our snot kicked out,
and we don't even know
why we were brought
into this crazy world!
-Yeah!
Someone owes us some answers!
-And I think you're
that someone.
So tell us what's going on.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Um, please?
-Very well, brave ones,
I shall tell you.
-No little further.
We here now.
-What a delightful place to
destroy those kiddies.
-They won't know
what hit them.
Right, Mercurymon?
-They shall know pain.
That I promise.
-If you want answers,
you will have them.
The story begins long ago, when
human Digimon and beast
Digimon warred against
each other.
Their battle laid waste to the
Digital World, befouling what
was once beautiful.
But Lucemon appeared
and brought
an end to the fighting.
For a time, he ruled in peace.
But soon, he was corrupted
by his own power.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): My, this
story sure sounds familiar.
CHILDREN (OFFSCREEN): Bokomon!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): What?
SERAPHIMON (OFFSCREEN): The Ten
Legendary Warriors arose
to free the oppressed
and abused Digimon.
They battled valiantly, and
after a fierce struggle they
were able to defeat the
tyrannical Lucemon.
After peace was restored to the
Digital World, champions
were chosen to protect
that peace--
Cherubimon, Ophanimon,
and myself.
But as before, our time of
harmony was short-lived.
Cherubimon wanted to control the
Digital World by himself
and so attacked me.
You know the rest of the story,
thanks to Sorcermon.
Ophanimon rescued me and brought
me to safety here,
where I have slumbered and
regained my strength until I
was awakened by you,
legendary warriors.
-Luckily, you came just when
we needed Seraphimon most.
The Digital World is in a
crisis, as you can see.
-Man, the Digital World looks
like Swiss cheese.
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN): And the
future looks even more bleak.
You see, Cherubimon has sent
his minions to destroy it.
-This is even more serious
than I'd imagined.
We must find Ophanimon
at once!
-Yes, my lord.
Your combined might can surely
defeat Cherubimon.
And of course, you'll
have my help.
While you've slept, I've
felt that I have, too.
And I have dreamt only of
fighting at your side against
that evil creature.
-Dear, brave Sorcermon.
You are a true friend.
Thank you.
Your courage gives
me strength.
-I am as you taught me.
-And I must thank you
for your courage.
All would be lost were
it not for you.
But now I must ask that you
do one more favor for me.
Before the fighting begins,
go back to your own world.
You task is done, and it's too
dangerous for you to stay.
-But we're legendary warriors!
-Yeah, we can't just
walk away now.
-Huh?
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN): Good,
whole brat brigade here.
-And ready to fight!
-You better be, cause me
introduce other Digimon who
defeat you--
Ranamon.
-Charmed, I'm sure.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Arbormon.
-You're in for it now, right?
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN): And
lastly, Mercurymon.
-So these be the whelps who hast
given me so much trouble?
Pathetic.
-They'll be covered in muck.
-Verily.
It will be utter delight to
defeat thee and to hand
Seraphimon another drubbing
in Cherubimon's name.
-With so many options, I don't
know where to start.
-Enough of your meaningless
taunts.
Tell me where Ophanimon
is, now!
-Me no care about her.
Me just want beast
spirit back!
So give it!
-Why don't you come
get it, buddy?
-Yeah!
-Execute spirit evolution!
-Agunimon!
-Lobomon!
-Beetlemon!
-Kumamon!
-The legendary warriors
have returned.
-If that big dufus hadn't stolen
my spirit, I'd show him
a thing or two.
-Yeah, well did.
And now I show you
thing or three!
-You sure you don't want
to get warmed up first?
Pyro darts!
-Ooh, he's feisty!
-Howling laser!
-You might as well just shoot
at the floor, sugar.
-Thunder fist!
-Crystal breeze!
-Thanks for the overwhelmingly
underwhelming lesson in combat.
Let me show you how it's done!
Draining rain!
-Roundhouse punt!
-Oh!
-That was too easy.
-Right.
-Go get your beast
spirit, Rockhead.
Fetch!
-Be careful or you'll get
smashed next, Ranamon!
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Grumblemon, no!
You cannot do this!
-I beg your pardon?
-You shall not lead us down
the path of ruin.
I've waited a lifetime to see
peace restored to the Digital
World, and you're not going
to stop it from returning!
Crystal barrage!
-Thou art a fool!
Dark reflection!
-Ugh!
-Sorcermon!
-Worry not, my lord.
-Have at you!
-Strike of the seven stars!
Please!
I ask again that you return to
your world and leave this to me!
-There's now way we'll leave!
-Yeah!
Even if we wanted to,
we don't know how!
-I can't fight them
and keep you safe!
You must go!
-Are you kidding?
You can't fight all those
guys by yourself.
I mean, come on.
You just woke up!
-You need us!
-This foolish compassion
be his weakness.
Attack the humans and
keep him distracted.
-We should be fighting them.
-Fine by us, we fight
you good.
-Draining rain!
-Roundhouse punt!
-Strike of the seven stars!
-Dark reflection!
-Oh!
-To the victor go the spoils.
-No!
-Seraphimon turned
into a Digi-Egg!
-Oh!
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
How ironic.
Seraphimon sought to
defeat Cherubimon.
But now his Fractal Code shall
be used for our ends!
-No, it can't be!
The hope of the Digital
World is gone!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): No it's not!
Maybe we can bring him back
if we have his egg.
Right, Sorcermon?
Hey!
-Yes, we must protect that
egg at all costs!
-Oh, thou shan't get
far, trust me.
-If we can get the egg to
Ophanimon, she may be able to
revive Seraphimon.
-All right, come and get it!
-Be not stupid.
-What's the matter? You chicken?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
you big metal head.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN):
Very well.
Thy fate is sealed.
We shall take it by unpleasant,
painful, agonizing force.
SORCERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Arrogance
will be your downfall.
ARBORMON (OFFSCREEN): Wh--
what?
Oh, they got away, right?
-Them kids always do that!
-Quick! This way!
[panting]
-Well, duh!
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
We come and get you!
-Quick!
We may escape through here.
[gasping]
JP (OFFSCREEN): Wow,
a getaway Trailmon!
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Thank goodness!
Come on, let's go!
-Sorcermon, hurry up!
-I'm not coming.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): What?
-The egg is all that
matters now.
I must ensure its safety.
Now go!
There isn't much time!
-You don't stand a chance!
I
-Take care of Seraphimon!
He's our last hope.
-No!
We won't leave you!
Sorcermon!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Tommy, that
isn't helping anyone.
GRUMBLEMON (OFFSCREEN):
We too late!
Rats!
-I can't believe this is all
that's left of Seraphimon.
I'm never gonna let this go.
-That egg may be the most
important thing in the Digital
World right now.
It's its last hope.
So all of Cherubimon's
forces are going to
be gunning for it.
But no matter what happens
we got to protect it.
We can't let Sorcermon's
sacrifice be in vain!
I hate to say this, but it's
up to us now, guys.
NARRATOR: Whoa.
Talk about carrying the
weight of the world.
See if the gang can handle
it on the next "Digimon--
Digital Monsters."