RIKA NARRATING: Having survived
his weird trip to the
real world, Takuya returned
to the Digital
World a Mon on a mission.
He realized that being a Digimon
may be fun, but it
isn't a game.
It's serious, and so was the
trouble that JP, Zoe, and
Tommy were in.
They were being tickle
tortured by
Mercurymon and Ranamon.
Then, out of nowhere, Lobomon
appeared to try and save them,
but he was still too weak from
the battle with Duskmon.
When it seemed like it was all
over, a new and more powerful
Agunimon arrived, with the power
of nature as his ally.
He saved his friends, and sent
the bad guys packing.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one!
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us, let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all!
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Mercurymon, I am so angry
I could just spit!
But I won't.
After all, I'm a lady.
-Oh, really?
-I've never been
so embarrassed.
What do you mean by that, you
pontificating pinhead?
And while you're at it, why
don't you tell me why we had
to run away like fraidy cats?
We could've beaten those
little twerps!
-Ranamon, Ranamon, poor
pathetic simpleton.
Dost thou knowest Nothing
They've become aware-- aware
of the true power of nature
that dwelleth within their
Legendary Spirits.
-Huh?
You lost me.
Hey, are those snowflakes?
-I welcome thy challenge,
humans.
Follow, if you must.
-Where are you going?
You didn't answer
my questions.
-Ah, thy vanity stuffeth
thine ears, I fear.
-Can't you just speak English?
So what?
Are you gonna take
them on yourself?
I'm a Legendary Warrior, too!
Don't I get a vote?
Mercurymon!
-Farewell.
Now, Duskmon, where art thou?
Thou remain a mystery
to me still.
-Oh, great.
As if things weren't bad enough,
now we have to worry
about Duskmon?
-I don't understand.
I am not a being of mercy
and compassion.
Why do I feel anything
for this human?
-You shall be first!
-No!
Kouji!
-Kouji?
-Kouji, why?
-This Kouji disturbs
my concentration.
Who are you?
No matter.
I shall find out soon enough.
-Thank heavens you're
back together again.
So, is everybody ready to go?
-But where are we
going, Bokomon?
-You're going to follow
me and stop
asking ridiculous questions.
-Next stop, the Rose Morning
Star, right?
-And try to keep up.
-I'm the leader.
Follow me, everybody.
-Oh, well.
-One, two, three, four, follow
me as we explore!
And five and six and seven and
eight, I cannot stand an empty
plate!
-Who elected him?
Not exactly inspirational
as a leader.
-It looks like he's just
showing off to me.
-What if we don't want to
see what he's showing?
-I want a turn being
the leader.
-I don't know.
Leadership takes independence.
You ready for that?
-Hey, JP depends on chocolate,
and that didn't stop him.
-He's got a point there.
-Well, I guess it's
settled, then.
You're the next leader, Tommy.
I sure hope your marching song's
better than that dorky
one he's got.
-Oh, you're so funny.
-Whoa!
-Neemon, help!
Well, there's something new.
-Whoa!
-Do you mind?
Get off me!
-Sorry about that, Zoe.
-I really am getting tired
of falling all the time.
-I don't know how we
got here, but it
looks like we're trapped.
-Are you serious?
Ugh, there's got to
be a way out.
Feels kind of spongy.
This isn't normal rock.
-Huh?
Ai-yi-yi, dead end.
Whoa!
-Zoe, where's JP?
-I saw him go that way.
-The owner's sure got
a scary decorator.
JP!
Where are you?
-All right, who's the
punk who pushed me?
This isn't what the inside
of an eye looked
like in science class.
Guys?
Takuya?
Kouji?
Zoe?
Tommy, can you hear me?
Hey, what the heck happened
to everybody?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): It's
just you and me now.
-Huh?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
[laughing]
-Very funny.
Who are you?
Whoa!
-[growling]
D-TECTOR NARRATING: Volcamon, a
cyborg Digimon who uses his
microphone to project his
Magma Bass attack.
You'll get a really bad
vibe from this guy.
-Hey, what's your
beef with me?
-You invaded my space.
I don't have any friends,
just like you.
Poor baby.
-What?
-I enjoy being alone, but you
actually think you've got
friends.
-You don't even know me!
-I know you better than
you know yourself, JP.
-What do you mean?
-One of your so-called friends
pushed you through the portal
to this place.
They wanted to get rid of you.
-Huh?
-Who elected him?
Not exactly inspirational
as a leader.
-It looks like he's just
showing off to me.
-What if we don't want to
see what he's showing?
-I want a turn being
the leader.
VOLCAMON: Looks like little
Tommy is going to get
his turn after all.
You're conceited and selfish.
Nobody wants you around, JP.
That's why they sent you here.
-Huh?
-You know it's true,
don't you?
Why fight it?
Why don't you let me put
you out of your misery?
-You're a liar!
My friends have never
felt that way!
You're the one who's
miserable!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Beetlemon!
-You're just a waste of
space to everybody!
Tackling time!
You're only kidding yourself,
little man!
You're all by yourself here!
-I'm getting real
tired of you!
Thunder Fist!
-Life just stinks, don't it?
But I'll take care
of that for you.
Magma Bass!
Hey, at least you're
not alone!
I'll keep you company.
At least until I'm done playing
our little game.
-My head!
Stop it!
Please!
-You can't escape!
You know I'm right!
Just surrender!
You can't fight!
It's time to say good night!
Bye bye!
Later, lonely boy!
-I may have some issues,
but I think I know
who my friends are.
And you're not one of them!
Thunder Fist!
Proton Slam!
That's the name of that song.
I'm going to purify your
evil attitude, dude.
At least you won't be
lonely anymore.
Fractal Code Digitize!
-I tried to warn you!
Now you have to live with
the sad reality that
you're all alone, JP!
-No!
He was lying!
He had to be!
My friends would never just
abandon me like that.
Would they?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
I don't know.
Would they?
-Who said that?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, I think they would.
-What?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Unless
they're real friends.
But you've never had any
of those, have you?
-Oh, man, I'm losing it.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Perhaps.
But think back for a moment.
Remember your classmates
at school?
-See?
Nothing here but a plain
white handkerchief.
Observe as I take it like this,
and gently lay it across
my hand, stir in a little
magic, and ta-da!
-Wow!
-That's amazing!
-You're great, JP!
-Now, who wants to take
home a monster card?
[thunderclap]
-Oh, boy.
Weather man blew it.
-Sure wasn't expecting that.
-Man, it's really coming
down out there.
-I didn't even bring
an umbrella.
-I have one in my locker.
You want to share it with me?
-Gee, thanks.
-Hey, can I come?
I've got some more cards.
-So?
They got a little distracted.
Kids do that.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, really?
-Yes, really!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Remember what happened next?
-I'm sure someone will
walk with me.
-Later, man.
Thanks, Kenta.
-No prob, dude.
-Wait.
Huh?
Give you some chocolate
if I can walk home--
-See you.
-Under your umbrella.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): You
wanted everyone to like you,
so you tried to win their
friendship with chocolate and
magic tricks.
You have no real friends.
You know why?
Because you don't think
you deserve them.
-[screaming]
Leave me alone!
[crying]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): It's
time to face reality, JP.
You can't hide from
you anymore.
-I'm Beetlemon!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, that's a nice, strong hiding place.
-Be quiet!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
But I see you.
And so do all your so-called
friends.
Inside all that armor, you're
just a scared, lonely little
boy.
-You don't know anything!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Takuya, Zoe,
they're laughing at you.
-[yells]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
That hurt.
[laughing]
-Show yourself, you coward!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Come on, chocolate boy.
Who are you really fighting?
-Who are you?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Just a reflection of
the real you, JP.
I am your shadow.
As long as you are
alive, I exist.
-This is crazy!
-Takuya, what's the matter?
-You hear something?
-No.
More like a feeling.
JP's in trouble.
Whoa!
-Gross!
-Guess that feeling was right.
-Go away, slimey!
Back, back!
-Block buster!
Oops.
-Come on!
-Sorry, Takuya.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Agunimon!
-Lobomon!
-Kazemon!
-Kumamon!
-Wanna grab something?
Try my Pyro Punch!
-Lobo Kendo!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Crystal Freeze!
-These things probably
attacked JP, too.
-But where is he now?
-The eyeball.
-Hm?
-My guess is it's some kind
of portal, and he's
on the other side.
-I'm not beat yet!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Missed me!
Just like you missed your chance
to have real friends.
-You're wrong!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Am I?
-I don't know anymore.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe I've been fooling myself
this whole time.
Living my life like
some twisted,
sugar-coated nightmare.
Is it possible that you guys
are just part of my
self-inflicted bad dream?
Somebody, please wake me up!
What now?
Oh, this can't be good.
Whoa.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
[laughing]
Hiya, handsome.
-There you are.
Nice of you to show up.
-I've been here all the time.
I've always been with you.
I've never left your side.
-You're wrong about me.
Takuya, Zoe, Tommy, even Kouji
taught me how to be a real
friend.
-But have you chosen to be?
-You're no friend of mine, JP!
You're a fake!
-I've never liked you,
and I never will!
-You're just a big bully
and a coward!
-This isn't real!
This is just part
of my bad dream.
Come on, wake up!
-You're busted!
The game's over!
[angry chatter]
-Nobody likes you!
Nobody ever did!
Nobody like you!
-Beetlemon wants a baby!
-Enough!
Let's settle this once and
for all, you and me!
-Oh, now you want to fight?
But I am you--
your past, your present,
and your future.
What do you hope to gain?
-My life back, for starters.
If I can defeat the old me,
I can rebuild a new one!
-Sounds like fun.
Bring it on, tough guy.
Toro!
[laughs]
-Thunder Fist!
-Nice try!
Sorry, big blue, but that
attack is useless on me.
-Oh, great.
-I am your shadow, remember?
Equal and opposite.
Well, actually, you've
made me stronger.
By the way, if you destroy
me, you destroy yourself.
-I don't care!
-Proton Slam!
-[screams]
-No mercy!
Show no mercy!
-[screaming]
-Don't you hear them
out there, JP?
How could you have ever thought
they were your friends?
The truth hurts.
But in a few moments, I'll
free you from your pain,
permanently.
[crowd chanting]
-Those aren't my friends.
They're a bunch of fakes.
I believe in my friends,
and they believe in me.
And there's nothing you could
ever do to change that.
[crowd chanting]
-Then where are they?
-Give it up!
Give it up!
-Don't you think they'd be here
if they cared about you?
-You never did belong here,
or anywhere else!
-You must have done
something to them.
They'll be here, and you
can't stop that!
-What?
-JP!
Are you all right?
-Of course I am!
-Oh, now that's weird.
-What is this, some kind of
evil house of mirrors?
Huh?
JP!
-Hey, about time!
They came!
I told you they're my friends.
-They probably just want
something from you.
Whatever.
I'll dispatch them as soon
as I'm finished with you.
-Dispatch this, shadow boy!
Execute!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
MetalKabuterimon!
-Impressive.
But you forget, anything you
can do, I can do better.
Slide Evolution!
Let's party!
-Oh, man.
-Wow, there's two of them!
-Bolo Thunder!
Huh?
What are you, huts?
You blow this thing at
this range, we're
both going to go down!
-I don't care!
It's a risk I'm willing
to take to save my
friends from you!
Bye bye, bad seed!
Electron Cannon!
-JP!
-JP, no!
-Jeep, you OK?
-Speak to me!
-Did Kouji just call me Jeep?
Hey, you really are
my friends.
-Of course, you bonehead.
-Yeah, but don't tell
anybody, all right?
-I was worried about you, JP!
-I'm just happy you're
all right.
-You mean that?
-Sure.
-I'm sorry.
-Why?
-I doubted our friendship.
It was terrible.
I felt like nobody
cared about me.
-Of course we care about you.
-Thanks.
I'll never doubt our
friendship again.
You guys are like
family to me.
You're the best friends
I've ever had.
Thanks for coming.
I love you people!
-OK, now I'm uncomfortable.
-Sorry.
It's been kind of an emotional
day, you know?
I'm just glad the gang's
back together again.
-[screaming]
-Zoe!
-Where'd she go?
-[screaming]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
[laughing]
-What's happening?
-I don't know, but that's
one ugly beast.
And we're in trouble.
-[laughing]
RIKA NARRATING: Oh, brother.
They really got sucked
in this time.
And what's with all the
googly eyeballs?
I guess we'll see on the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters!