NARRATOR: On their to the Forest
Kingdom, J.P, Zoe,
Bokomon and Neemon came upon
a school for young Digimon.
There they met Tsunomon, a
little guy who didn't get
along with the other kids.
See, one day he digivolved
to Gabumon to help his
classmates, but they totally
freaked out.
So much for individuality.
Then the rain came and almost
washed away the school.
Zoe and J.P. spirit evolved
just in time.
But while they were busy,
Kapurimon got swept away.
With a little convincing from
the guys, Tsunomon digivolved
to Gabumon and saved
his friend.
After that, Kapurimon was the
most popular kid in school So
being an individual does work.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through spirit
evolution--
Digimon!
Forever united as one--
Together the battles are won--
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
there's a world for us all!
Digimon!
-I believe the Forest Kingdom
begins beyond that track.
-Sure looks big.
Hey, Bokomon, how much farther
do we have to walk to the
forest terminal?
-Don't worry.
You should only have to walk
a little bit more.
-A little bit more?
These little bits
are killing me.
Wait up!
Man, isn't it time for
a dinner break?
I'm wasting away here.
-We didn't even get
any breakfast yet.
-I think we better stop
here and make camp.
-It's been a long day
for all of us.
-Yeah, whatever.
-We're stopping?
-Does that mean I get to eat?
And lay down?
And-- eat?
Yes!
-Look what I found.
I hope it's edible.
-It's called a meat apple.
-Meat apple?
-Yes.
Each one has the flavor
of a different meat.
Quite nutritious, actually.
-Where'd you find that thing?
-It was just lying
on the ground.
There has to be a tree
somewhere nearby.
Bokomon, will you help
me find some more?
-Certainly?
-Can I come?
-All right.
-Goody!
I love meat apples!
-Well, billy for you.
-Wait for me!
-Well, I guess we'd better
gather some firewood.
-I'm not gonna have to lift
anything heavy, am I?
-Ah, yes.
Fresh young minds.
They'll have sweet
dreams tonight.
-Is something wrong?
-I just thought I heard
something flying by.
-I didn't hear anything.
Maybe it's a monster.
-Yeah.
There it is!
-Huh?
-A big tree!
-There's so many!
-It's loaded with meat apples.
Yummy!
-Am I done yet?
-Yep.
I'll take it from here.
-Apple, you're my best friend.
Blech!
Disgusting!
-You don't eat them
raw, you know.
-Why didn't you say
that before?
-I got a question.
All five of us kids now have
the spirits of legendary
warriors, right?
-Uh-huh.
-So tell me, how come even when
we combined our forces we
still couldn't beat that
stupid Grumblemon?
-Good question.
-Thunderfist!
-Nice shot, dorkus.
Huh?
Ahhh!
-At one point we seemed to
have the upper hand.
But then--
-I never find without you.
Now get rid you!
-Huh?
-Execute!
Release spirit evolution!
Gigasmon!
Quagmire twister!
-He spirit evolved into
that crazy Gigasmon.
-But he called it
beast spirit.
Just what does that mean?
Any clue?
-The fire's ready.
Bring your apples.
-Hm?
TOMMY (VOICEOVER): There
it is again.
-Come on, shorty.
Quit lagging!
-Hey, Bokomon.
Anything in your book about
a beast spirit?
-I haven't seen anything.
-If it's not too much trouble,
could you just
take another look?
-Certainly.
Let's see now.
Beast, beast, beast, beast.
I'm afraid I still don't
see anything.
Paws off, baggy.
-But I think I found
something.
This page seems to
be folded over.
Maybe there's other
stuff inside.
-Oh.
It's a miracle.
You're actually right.
This changes everything.
It seems there are two
spirits for each of
the legendary warriors.
-Huh?
-The first is the human
spirit, like Agunimon.
But the second is called
the beast spirit.
That explains where Gigasmon
came from.
But how did he summon
the beast spirit?
-I wonder what life would
be like as a beastie.
-Let's feed you to one,
and you can find
out from the inside.
Don't you realize this means
that the children may have the
power to spirit evolve again?
-Well then.
If Bokomon's right, each
of us should be able
to get a beast spirit.
-But if that's true then we're
only halfway there.
-Oh, man.
It's like starting over.
-Bokomon. Bokomon. Bokomon.
-But if get our beast spirits
maybe we can beat Grumblemon.
-Well, I'm willing
to give it a try.
Beast spirit evolution,
here we go!
-Yeah!
-Bokomon.
Bokomon.
Boko-- ow!
Is this a good idea?
-What's the matter with you?
We have to help you
find your beast
spirits as soon as possible.
After all, it may be the only
way to save the digital world.
We haven't even made it to
the Forest terminal.
We're running out of time.
These beast spirits must be
our number one priority.
-Nope.
Not good.
-What is not good?
-The meat apples.
While you're talking,
they're burning up.
-Huh?
-Mine's like a meat bun!
-This one tastes almost like
a chicken drumstick.
-I think I'm eating prime rib.
-Mm, yeah. Gingered pork.
-Mine's ossobuco!
-Hey, you're blocking
the view.
-Something is happening.
Wow. A TV.
-A bunch of 'em.
-That is pretty sweet.
-Whoa.
Tree TV.
I hope it isn't all
travel channels.
I wonder if we can
get music videos.
-Wait a minute.
That's our world.
Those scenes are
from back home.
-That's right, Zoe.
It's called the TV Forest,
a video gateway
to the human world.
-Now that's really weird.
-It's my school.
It never looked so
pretty to me.
Oh, look.
The cherry tree's blooming.
-I love cherries.
You know, come to think of
it, I love pretty much
every kind of food.
By the way, is this
pre-recorded?
-That's the park where
my mom always used to
always take me to play.
My mother.
-Huh?
-Are you serious?
-You weren't kidding.
Your mother's very
pretty, Tommy.
-Oh, Mom.
Huh?
Wait.
Where are you going?
Don't leave me!
Please!
[sobbing]
Momma!
-I bet my mom is really
worried about me.
-Cheer up, little buddy.
Go on, try my apple.
It's hot dog.
-Tommy could be your
little brother.
-Hey, Koji.
Are you falling asleep?
-Sleep?
I'm lucky I'm not
bored to death.
-Hey, bud.
What's your problem?
He needs a nap
-He's just grumpy.
Hey, J.P, maybe Tommy would
like to see you do some of
your magic.
-Magic?
Since when?
-Since I was a kid myself.
Ladies and germs, I present to
you the magic of Howie Doodat.
-Yay!
-All right!
-Observe.
Nothing up my sleeves--
KOJI (VOICEOVER):
Or in his head.
-I happen to have this beautiful
red scarf here.
But now this blue one wants
his friend back.
-Yeah!
Put 'em back!
-That wasn't my trick.
Yet.
I will put 'em together--
one more twist here--
ta-da!
My clothesline!
-Ooh.
-Yes, my friends.
But this is just
the beginning.
I will now bring them
back to normal.
-Now, how did he do that?
-Well, I guess that explains
where he got
his stage name from.
-It doesn't explain why
he's so annoying.
-Do another one!
-I don't know if
I know anymore.
In fact, I don't if I know how I
knew how I did the last one.
-Now stop that.
[laughter]
-Nightmare syndrome.
-This stinks.
I do a spectacular performance
tonight, and I still have to
watch the stupid fire.
-Stop complaining.
We drew straws and you lost,
fair and square.
-I'm just wiped out from
all the walking.
I think I need to pass
out for a while.
-Hey,
J.P. -Hm?
-I was wondering.
Are you an only child?
-Yeah.
But how could you
have known that?
-It's pretty obvious.
-So?
Big deal.
What about it?
-I didn't mean to hurt
your feelings.
I just miss my little brother.
Same age as Tommy.
It was my little brother's
birthday.
The day we came to the
digital world.
Aw, man!
I missed all the cake
and ice cream!
-Afraid it's a little bit
late for that now, bud.
-Yeah.
No big whoop.
-Huh?
Did you just see a ghost?
-I saw something.
I'm just not sure what.
But it feels like we're
being watched.
-Wha?
Um, maybe it was a squirrel
or something.
-I can't believe you didn't
feel anything just then.
-I did.
But I think it might have just
been gas from eating too many
of those meat apples, if you
know what I'm saying.
And I think you do.
-You must search for the
spirit, Koji Minamoto.
Never give up, for the
spirit awaits you.
Once you have found it,
everything will become clear.
-Everything will become clear?
I wish I knew what
everything was.
[whimpering]
-Huh?
-Wait!
Wait!
Momma!
-Tommy.
-Sorry, shorty.
You're a big boy now.
You don't need your
mommy any more.
-Momma, don't go!
-Goodbye forever, Tommy.
-No!
Stop!
-Tommy, what is it?
-I won't forgive you.
I won't forgive you.
-There's something
wrong with him.
-Hey, half-pint.
Snap out of it.
-Tommy, stop that right now.
-I will not forgive!
-Now cut it out!
This isn't funny, Tommy!
-I will never forgive
any of you.
You're going to pay for what
you've done to me.
Execute.
Spirit evolution!
Kumamon.
Crystal freeze!
[cackling]
-Keep it down.
That's one angry bear.
-Kumomon!
-Has Kumomon gone mad?
-I'm tired of you bullying me!
Crystal freeze!
-No!
-What's going on here?
-No clue.
-Maybe you could use the book?
-Maybe on your head.
-He's gone completely crazy.
-I'm really sorry, Tommy.
-Justice will be served.
Crystal freeze!
-Guess sorry wasn't
the magic word!
-You OK?
-Yeah.
-Hey, how come Takuya gets
to fall with Zoe?
-Run, you jerk!
-Crystal freeze!
-Looks like the only choice we
have is to spirit evolve and
take him out!
-I will never forgive you.
-Spirit evolve?
I won't do it.
There has to be another
way to stop him.
-Right.
-Sorry, J.P. I'm with them.
-Fine.
Well, what do you propose?
-Crystal freeze!
-Run!
Come on, Zoe!
Take my hand!
I'll protect you!
Agh!
-Sorry.
-I'm good.
-What was that?
-I know I definitely heard
something that time.
-Right.
Execute!
Spirit evolution!
Lobomon.
-Wait a minute.
I thought we all agreed
not to spirit evolve.
Who does he think
he is, anyway?
Sometimes I hate him!
-Koji must have a good reason.
Maybe he knows something
that we don't.
-Ancient spirit of light!
-There he is!
Execute!
Spirit evolution!
Agunimon!
-OK, now something is
definitely wrong.
-All I know is that they broke
the agreement and we have to
protect Tommy.
-Lobomon, don't you harm
a hair on that bear.
OK?
-Frozen tundra!
-Kumamon, this has to stop.
-Incoming!
-Stupid humans.
This is too easy.
-Rotten little warthog!
-What is he riding?
-[inaudible].
-Bakumon.
The product of a medical sleep
research computer program.
His special attack is
nightmare syndrome.
-Come back here, you
flying pork pie!
-He looked pretty nasty
for a Bakumon.
Aren't they supposed
to eat bad dreams?
-You sap.
Did it occur to you that
Cherubimon may have turned him
evil?
-But how?
-I have no idea.
Ah, he's supposed to be wearing
this power ring.
But apparently Cherubimon
has taken it away.
-Nightmare syndrome!
-What?
-These are not your friends.
Use your powers to
punish them.
-Huh?
-They're all against
you, Takuya.
Destroy them before
they destroy you.
-No, it's--
not real!
Now get out of my head!
TAKUYA (VOICEOVER): That's it.
Tommy must be having
this nightmare too.
-It's only a dream.
Bakumon has convinced him
that we're his enemy.
-Oh, no.
-Stop.
Tommy!
-My name is Kumamon, and you are
nothing but a big bully!
-No, you're wrong.
-Kumamon!
You're under the spell of
Bakumon's nightmare syndrome!
It isn't real, you
have to fight it!
-Agunimon.
You're not my enemy?
-Takuya!
-Wait! Don't do it!
-Ahhh!
It's time to end
this nightmare!
Now for some purification.
Fractal zone, digitize!
-Lobomon.
Wow, have you been fighting
somebody?
-Glad to have you back, Tommy.
-Tommy.
Don't you remember?
You just had a terrible
nightmare.
-Huh?
-That's right.
You gave us quite a scare
there, young man.
Bakumon's dream made you think
we were your enemies.
-Yeah, but it was actually
Cherubimon's fault.
-Bakumon's better now, He didn't
know what he was doing
at the time.
-I'm sorry.
From now on I promise I'll only
send you good dreams.
-Ah.
OK.
I had an adventure and I
don't even remember it!
-It's good you don't.
-Thanks, Koji.
I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
I owe you one.
-You don't owe me anything.
Besides, you're the one who
sensed something out there.
-Huh?
-I've always heard savages
rely on intuition.
-You really hate being
nice, don't you?
-I'm not sure I'll ever
understand them.
-Sweet dreams, children.
[snoring]
-Now is the way to sleep.
Oh?
-Your beast spirit awaits,
Koji Minamoto.
But first, you have some
growing to do.
-Huh?
-What?
What does she mean by that?
NARRATOR: So Koji thought
he had all the answers.
Typical.
There are only more questions
ahead, on the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters!