NARRATOR: After a wild and
watery ride on a Trailmon, our
heroes found themselves trapped
in an underground
cavern with a very
unhappy Whamon.
Unfortunately, Arbormon and
Grumblemon had figured out
where they were, and decided
to wage another attack.
Grumblemon unleashed an angry
horde of Golemon, and it
looked like the DigiDestined
were doomed!
Then Whamon blasted Grumblemon
and coughed up a spirit that
he had accidentally munched
before he was
sucked into the cave.
JP's Beast Spirit evolved
into the mighty warrior
MetalKabuterimon and wiped out
the grouchy Grumblemon once
and for all!
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music playing]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we head for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves, and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a spirit evolution!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Though us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
there's a world for us all!
Digimon!
[shouting]
-Just look at him.
How pathetic.
-I told you, he's all mouth,
no moxy, sugar.
-Methinks that his tongue doth
far outstrip his technique.
-That's what I just said,
you shiny twit.
But that's not the point.
The point is it's
up to us now.
-Thou mayest not dampen my
enthusiasm, queen of puddles.
I remain your loyal ally.
-Then why don't you prove it?
Find Arbormon.
He's thick-headed, but useful.
I don't have time for
his nonsense.
-Methinks this mere subterfuge,
my drizzly damsel.
-Mercurymon, try speaking
English.
-Shalt thou listen to make a
change, my lady, I will tell
you what you wish not to hear.
It is thine lack of a beast
spirit that doth
truly plague thy mind.
-What are you trying to say?
-I'm saying you're scared,
you murky headed nit!
You're afraid you'll end up
just like Grumblemon.
-That's ridiculous!
I think you've polished
your face one
too many times, sugar.
Of all the nerve!
How dare you compare me to that
incompetent rockhead!
-I dare because I know
it to be true.
-Your brain is rusting.
Those whiny children will
never defeat me!
The little darlings will beg
me to take their spirits
before I'm done.
-Hm.
Do as you wish, my lady.
-I always do as I wish, and he's
just plain wrong about me
being afraid.
But that metal head Mercurymon
is right about one thing.
I might as well be a silly lawn
sprinkler for all the
damage I can do without
my Beast Spirit.
But where can it be hiding?
My loyal fans have searched
everywhere.
I've searched everywhere.
Rivers, nothing.
Streams, nothing.
Ponds, nothing, nothing,
nothing.
It's really quite
embarrassing.
Honestly, even three of those
bratty babies have Beast
Spirits, and I, the queen of the
seas, the darling of the
deep, the prettiest pearl
in the ocean's
oyster, I have nothing.
I have shame and despair.
[beeping]
I haven't looked there.
This puts a whole new
spin on things.
Now to find a local
devoted fan club.
Oh, this is simply divine.
Those boys would trade their
tailfeathers for a wink.
They can search for my
Beast Spirit for me.
Oh, how I adore being adored.
It's so much nicer
than working.
See ya, buddy!
-Aloha!
-Ciao, Whamon!
-So, there he goes.
-Nice of you to point
out the obvious.
-Don't be such boys!
-My dear Zoe, that has
gotten into you?
-You can't blame a girl for
feeling good on such a
beautiful day, especially a girl
who has her Spirit back.
-And let us not forget who
has a Beast Spirit now!
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Let's
hear it for JP, the
princely beast of thunder!
JP (OFFSCREEN): And Zoe,
princess of the summer breeze.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): And
Takuya, king of
I'm gonna be sick.
-Did you hear that?
-We're standing right here
beside you, geek boy.
Of course we heard it.
-The Beast Spirit!
-Ranamon will be so happy.
-Thanks, boys.
[swooning]
-She might even come to our
island and visit us!
She'll be so happy, she might
even talk to us, with those
beautiful lips, and that
cute, cute, cute voice.
Oh!
Cute voice.
[singing]
[swooning]
-You are too cute!
We love you, Ranamon!
L-O-V-E, love, love, love you!
-Ah, what a night.
What a night!
-And just think how happy she'll
be if we give her that
Beast Spirit.
She'll come here
and sing to us.
She might even kiss us!
-Dream on, doofus.
Just how do you plan to get
the Beast Spirit away from
those kids?
-Yeah, there are a lot of them,
and they're awfully big.
Isn't there an easier
way to get a kiss?
-Chicken heart.
I got everything covered.
-You know, I can't help but
notice that it's summer, and
we're at a beach.
-I noticed that.
-Yeah.
You know what that means?
-Summer vacation!
-The waves!
-Shell hunting!
-Lots of sunshine!
-Yeah!
Put it all together, and
what do you got?
The beach, baby!
-Takuya, aren't you forgetting
something?
We're supposed to be
on a mission here.
We'd be stupid to let
our guard down.
-Come on, you gotta
lighten up, buddy.
-Hey!
-Yeah, stop being
a party pooper.
-Wait, wait, don't!
I'm not, guys.
I--
I just think that--
-Yes, you are.
You're being pooey.
-Stop it! Huh?
-It can't hurt to take
a short break.
We've earned it.
-Zoe's right.
We have earned it.
-Fine, whatever.
I'm obviously outnumbered
here.
-That's it, then.
All in favor, say I!
-Aye, aye!
-Oh!
-Oh, indeed. Look.
-Whoa.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): What's
summer vacation
without a beach house?
-This is a little
too convenient.
-I don't know about that, but
it sure looks awfully
comfortable.
-Welcome!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, goody.
It's the Toucanmon.
Gaudy looking creatures,
but very timid.
Their attack is Crazy Crest.
Sounds rather silly,
doesn't it?
-Honored guests, we welcome
you to Toucan Paradise.
-Thank you, Mr. Toucanmon.
We're honored you're honored.
-Yeah, we're honored,
but we're broke.
-Oh, please.
What's a few DigiShackles
among friends?
And it just so happens
that today,
everything is on the house.
By which I mean free.
Not served on the roof.
-We know what it means.
-Sorry! So sorry!
It was just a small joke.
Very small.
-It's OK.
-No, no, no.
We are humiliated.
There is absolutely nothing we
won't do to make it up to you.
-Oh, wow, really?
-Really, really, really,
double really!
TOUCANMON (OFFSCREEN):
A little of this.
-A smidge of that, and--
-Ladies and gentlemen--
-Your lunch is served.
-Whoa!
All right!
What are we waiting for?
-Let's dig in!
-Yeah!
Where do we start?
Delicious!
-Oh, man!
I am so enjoying these
overcooked ramen noodles with
rubbery egg!
-Mm, mm, mm.
This is the best lumpy
curry I've ever had.
-You're weird.
Is that supposed to
be a complement?
-Dude, don't you get it?
It's real food, like home, not
some kind of crazy, meat
tasting rabbit food.
-Every bit of it looks
exactly like what it
is, lumps and all!
Besides, it's a beach
house, buddy.
The food could have sand, and
bugs and stuff all over it,
and nobody would care!
-Bring on the bugs!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): And sand!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
And stuff.
Bring on the stuff!
-You ate a lot.
-I'm eating for two now.
My selfish days are over.
If I must pig out,
then so be it.
-It was wonderful!
-Don't mention it.
It was our pleasure.
-My tummy feels like a melon.
-Tommy, did you get enough?
-Mm-hm.
-Oh, enough, and more!
-Well, I guess it's
time to split.
-Wha?
-We've imposed enough
on you already.
-Go on, impose!
-Please, we're begging
you, here.
Impose, already.
-Thanks, but we're
stuffed as ticks.
-But you're growing kids.
It won't be long before
you're hungry again.
What kind of hosts would
we be if we let you
leave without supper?
-Supper?
Are you nuts?
I won't be hungry for hours.
I might never eat again!
-You say that now, but after
being in the sun--
I'm sure you will agree with
me, and might I suggest you
take advantage of our super
value summer special.
-Huh?
-What he's saying is free beach
rentals for everybody!
-Man!
-Wow!
-Man, check this out!
-Wow, look at that!
-Complimentary baskets are
available for your valuables,
so just go out and
have a good time.
Leave the worrying to us.
-Banzai!
-Now this is the life!
Hey, are you sure you don't
want to race me, Tommy?
I'll give you a 10
innertube start!
Come on!
-Naw, I'm on vacation.
-Are my ears getting burned?
-Why worry?
Your brain's already cooked.
Huh?
I don't see Zoe.
Have we lost one?
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Mm.
[giggling]
[humming]
-Hm?
Now, in this one I'd look
like a race queen.
The stripes are nice, but
white is so boring.
Well, this is kind of cool.
Super athlete!
then again, maybe not.
It's not really a fun in
the sun sort of suit.
Next!
Que bella, but not much there.
Hm, now this one's nice.
In fact, it's just perfect!
[humming]
-Hm?
Huh?
[screaming]
-Huh?
-Zoe, what's wrong?
-Are you OK?
[screaming]
-Get out, get out, get out!
[shouting]
-I am so sorry.
-So, what happened?
Why did you scream before?
-Because someone's
a peeping Tom.
-You're kidding!
-Let me at the creep.
How dare he.
-Hm.
-Hm?
-Mm-hm.
-What are you all lookin'
at me for, huh?
Huh?
-You must admit, it
looks suspicious.
After all, you are the
most likely culprit.
-Mm-hm.
-He makes a good point, JP.
Why don't you just admit it?
-Because I just didn't
do it, that's why!
-Come on, guys. it couldn't
have been JP.
He was swimming with us the
whole time, remember?
-I forgot.
-We all have the same alibi.
-Then by the process of
elimination, it was no one?
-Are you calling Zoe a liar?
-Now, of course not, JP.
It's obviously we're
not alone here.
-Of course we're not
alone, Einstein.
Did you forget the Toucanmon?
-Where'd they all go?
-Now, this is
suspicious -Oh, no!
The bird boys tricked us.
-Oh, man.
-My detector's gone.
Mine's gone, too.
This is awful.
-This goes well beyond
awful, young man.
How could you let those
Toucanmon trick you like that?
-Stop it.
They fooled all of us.
-That's right!
[awkward shouting]
BOYS (OFFSCREEN): Get out,
get out, get out!
[laughter]
-That was almost too easy.
Those silly kids never
had a chance.
We finally proved ourselves
worthy of
our ravishing Ranamon.
-(SINGING) Ah, Ranamon,
the ravishing!
-All right, hold it right
there, you thieves!
-Uh-oh.
-Just what do you mean by
Ranamon the ravishing?
Huh?
-Give our detectors back
to us right now!
-No way, no how.
These little babies are our
ticket to a date with Ranamon.
-Take it from me, you
guys are delusional.
Now give them back.
-Mm-hm.
-You can't make us.
Now, scram.
-Maybe we should scram.
-Scramming!
-Wait!
Come back here!
-This is so dumb.
-That doesn't look good.
-Oh, dear.
It's Ranamon.
-Hi, y'all.
-She's the warrior of water,
and very evil.
-Well, of course see is.
-She sure has lousy timing.
-What a pleasant surprise.
I have so looked forward
to seeing y'all again.
I'd hoped to have my Beast
Spirit to show you first, but
everything happens
for a reason.
We can't have everything.
Just be good little children
and hand over your spirits.
I'd love to stay and chat, but
frankly, you bore me to tears.
Now, how's that sound?
-Hmph!
Sounds stupid to me.
-But we don't have
our detectors.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I'll
handle her.
-Zoe.
-Don't worry, JP.
I'll take care of
her in no time.
-Goodie, goodie.
This is going to be a treat.
[muffled groans]
-Oh, man.
This was supposed to
be a vacation!
-This is very, very bad.
As long as she's near water,
her offensive power is
exponentially enhanced!
-I'm guessing that's
a bad thing?
-I just said that.
Didn't I just say that?
-I don't know.
-Water woman sure has
a nasty temper.
-Zoe, you can't!
-Look, I haven't been able
to Spirit Evolve.
I need to make up
for lost time.
-Oh, goodie, goodie!
-I've never felt this
helpless before.
-Just leave it to me!
[music playing]
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Ha!
Kazemon!
-Sugar, do you think you
can take me on alone?
-That's a silly question.
Of course I do, sugah.
-So now you're gonna mock me?
-I wouldn't dream of it.
I'd rather fight!
-Don't you want to play
with me anymore?
-Look, Ranamon!
-Over here, we're over
here, Ranamon!
I think I'm gonna faint.
TOUCANMON (OFFSCREEN):
She's so beautiful.
So sweet, so perfect.
-Enough dancing.
We have to get the Beast
Spirit to her.
-Let's hurry.
She'll be so pleased with us.
We'll give her the
Beast Spirit, and
then she'll kiss us.
-Ah.
-Whipping Waves!
-Hurricane Wing!
-Well, you're actually
pretty good at this.
-Oh, Ranamon.
That means so little
coming from you.
-You little brat.
I'm going to take you
apart wing by wing.
-Go, Ranamon, go, Ranamon,
go, Ranamon, go, go!
-Feeling a little more polite?
What's that calling to me?
Could it be?
Out of my way, brat!
-Oh, great.
What's she up to now?
-It really is my Beast Spirit.
And the little thing actually
looks happy to see me!
Beast Spirit Evolution!
Ha ha ha!
It's all over now, honey!
Too bad, I was actually
starting to
enjoy our little spat.
-What's happening?
RANAMON (OFFSCREEN): Ready
or not, here I am!
In all of my radiant beauty.
Aren't you impressed?
[groaning]
-I can see by your faces you
still need convincing.
Maybe you just need a closer
look at sweet Calmaramon.
I'm just happy to oblige!
[laughter]
-I think I'm gonna be too busy
for the Ranamon fan club from
now on.
-Yeah, me too.
TOUCANMON (OFFSCREEN):
Me three.
TOUCANMON (OFFSCREEN): And to
think, we almost had to go on
a date with her.
-That Kazemon was
kind of cute.
-Definitely cute.
-That is one ugly--
-She is not very nice, either.
-And she smells awful.
Did you notice that?
-Who do you think you are?
You can't insult Calmaramon
and get away with it!
-Whoa!
-I'm so sorry, sugar pie!
Are you not enjoying
our little dance?
Too bad!
Maybe I should turn
up the music.
-Zoe, look out!
-Ta ta, honey!
-Titanic Tempest!
[shouting]
This can't be happening!
-Uh--
-OK.
-Whoa!
Don't you know who I am?
-Um, what just happened here?
-I'm guessing that Ranamon
isn't any better at
controlling her Beast
Spirit than you lot.
-Well, then I'm guessing--
-We're OK!
-Guys, what happened
to the Toucanmon?
-Oh, no.
They're gone.
-Rats!
I forgot all about them.
-Those feathered fanboys still
have our detectors.
-The way they waddle, they
couldn't have gotten too far.
-Well, then let's go get 'em!
NARRATOR: About time these guys
caught a break, but I
wouldn't depend on it
if I were them.
Keep watching Digimon,
Digital Monsters!