NARRATOR: It's bad enough when
Mercurymon corners you in a
world of mirrors and
beats you up.
Just ask a Agunimon.
But then he uses Seraphimon's
data to turn into this big old
baddie, Shadow Seraphimon.
It looked like curtains for
Takuya for sure, but energy
from Seraphimon's Digi-Egg let
Takuya fusion evolve to
Aldamon who kicked the Fractal
Code out of Shadow Seraphimon
and Mercurymon.
Takuya returned to the others
and the Digi-egg hatched, but
inside was only Patamon.
And what good is that little
guy going to be against all
the forces of darkness?
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned,
as we work towards one
solution, through a
spirit evolution.
I am the one.
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
I am the one.
Huh!
Digimon!
-There goes Sakkakamon.
-That's a relief.
-He's just backing off.
Well, at least we got an answer
to what was inside
Seraphimon's egg.
-You're sure a cute
little fella.
-And he flies!
-My Papa-mom!
[laughing]
-Oh, isn't that adorable?
My baby thinks of me as both
his papa and momma.
-I'm hungry, papa-mom.
-Oh.
Hmmm.
Well--
-Don't look at me.
I don't even have pockets.
-We don't even have
a crust of bread.
-That's OK, I can wait.
-Oh!
-That's different.
He's so calm.
-What a good boy.
-He sure doesn't have
Bokomon's genes.
-Mmm-hmmm!
-And just what's wrong
with my genes?
-Koji, come in!
Koji!
It's no use.
Wherever he is, I can't
get through to him.
-That doesn't sound good.
-We'd better search for him.
-Hold that thought!
-Ahhh!
-It wasn't a vision.
It had to be real.
How could that boy look
just like me?
-What!
-Duskmon, why are you
running away?
Where are you going?
-What?
-Check it out!
He's twitching like he's
about to strike!
-Why is he doing that?
-I'm not sure I really
want to know.
Hurry, Patamon, get in!
-But papa-mom, I don't think
I can fit in there anymore.
You're too big.
-Oh.
-Ahhh!
-Ha he ha!
Behold, the legendary
warriors.
I must congratulate thee. 'Tis
true, thine efforts have given
me more power than even
I coulds't dream of!
-What?
-Ha ha ha!
Thunder Fist!
-Hey, what's the deal?
He's stealing my thunder!
-Yeah, that's Beetlemon's
attack!
-And now one for the ladies.
Hurricane Wave!
-Ahhhh!
-That's just not right.
-No kidding.
-Let's show him how
it's really done!
-Activate now!
Fusion evolution!
[yelling]
-Aldamon!
-Patamon?
Please tell me the rest of us
have the power to fusion
evolve too.
-Regretably, Seraphimon's power
has been all used up.
-I should have brought
batteries.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
-Yeah.
The three of us still have power
enough to take of this.
-Oh.
-Execute!
Spirit evolution!
-Ahhhh hey!
Beetlemon!
-Haaa!
Kazemon!
-Ahh oop!
Ha ha!
Kumamon!
-Hm hm hm!
My turn!
[laughing]
-Uh oh.
-Blizzard Blaster!
-He's got your attack down, too?
-How is he doing this?
-Simple.
I lured each of thee into thine
own areas to observe thee in battle.
-Oh, how valiantly thou dids't
fight against my minions.
Meanwhile, I meticulously
recorded all of the attacks
thou could muster!
Alas, not one of thee suspected
the method to my
madness, my deeper purpose.
I must admit, your efforts
surpassed even my
expectations.
The stronger the foe, the
greater the response, all in
the name of glory.
My glory!
-And now, all of thy power
can be mirrored by me.
-You planned this from
the beginning.
So that's why we had to put up
with the stench of fighting
inside of you.
You were using us!
-He made us fight so he could
copy our attacks.
-Oh, man!
You mean we had to go through
all that for him?
That stinks!
-You said it.
-I relish the thought that thine
efforts shall be the
cause of thine own undoing.
Oh, what fools these
mortals be!
Gave me thy spirits, and the
Digital World shall bow before
me!
-Hate to soak your blanket,
big mouth, but we're the
originals, and no crooked copy
cat's going to tell us when to
call it a day!
Yah!
Thunder Fist!
-What happened?
-Thunder Fist Reflection!
-What can we do?
When we attack, he returns our
attack with even more power.
-We can't give up.
Hurricane Wave!
-Hurricane Wave Reflection!
-Uh!
-Kazemon!
-I can't believe I was hurt
by my own attack.
-Most apt.
The invention returns to
plague the inventor.
-Enough!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-Atomic Inferno!
-Ahhh!
Ha ha ha!
Atomic Inferno Reflection!
Ha ha!
-Ahhh!
Uh!
-Thine attempts to attack
are futile!
The reality is thou cannot
beat me, or to be more
accurate, you cannot
beat yourselves!
-He couldn't be more right.
And every time they use
their attacks, they
lose even more energy.
And if that's not bad enough,
he returns their attacks at
double their original
strength.
I wish there was something
we could do to help them.
-I with I had a sandwich.
-Let's see how they fare when
friend becomes foe!
Ha ha ha!
Blizzard Blaster!
-Ah!
-Hurricane Wave!
Oh!
-Lightning Blitz!
-And now, for the most evolved
attack of all, from Aldamon
with love, Atomic Inferno!
-No!
Ah ha!
-Aldamon!
-To acquire thy attacks, I made
a small sacrifice, but my
human spirit was nothing
when compared to this!
-This isn't all we can do.
Time to evolve!
Slide evolution!
Zephyrmon!
-Yeah!
-Time to show you something
you haven't seen yet!
-Slide evolution!
MetalKabuterimon!
Korikakumon!
-Hurricane--
-Let me finish that
for you, darling!
Ha ha!
-Now!
-Ahh!
Oh--
but how?
-Attacking him individually
gives him time to react.
We've got to attack him
at the same time!
-Right!
-Ready?
Atomic Inferno!
-Bolo Thunder!
-Avalanche Axes!
-Hurricane Gale!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-Ah!
-Oh!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-Ah!
I fear this is the end.
-What can we do now?
He knows all our attacks.
[sakkakumon laughing]
-We've never faced an
enemy like this.
-It's no use.
We'll never win.
-Then what are we
supposed to do?
-Pull back?
-Huh?
-Let's get outta here!
-What?
-You're not serious!
-It's our only hope.
If we stay here, we're
not going to make it!
There are times when running
away is the only way to win,
and this is one of
those times.
ALDAMON (THINKING): Everyone's
losing faith.
We can't fight like this.
If we don't believe we can win,
then there's no way we
will.
-But we can't just run away.
-No way!
-Let's pull back.
-What!
-Guys, we have to
think long-term.
-But Takuya--
-How can we stop this guy
if we don't survive?
We've got to regroup and come
up with another plan.
-You're right.
-Yeah.
-Finally!
-How did he--
-I've never seen him
move so fast!
-Oh, great!
We're surrounded!
-So much for running away.
-What are we going
to do now, boss?
-Move it!
Otherwise, we're sunk!
-It's right behind us!
Jump!
[screaming]
-Here he comes!
-Great!
-Guys, this way!
-Neemon, come along.
We must follow.
-Huh?
-I wonder where this
tunnel leads to?
-Just keep moving!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-Huh?
-Thou art running to
thy own demise!
-He's gaining on us!
-Don't look back!
Run!
-'Tis no use.
No matter how quickly you may
gallop in haste, thou shalt
never outrun me!
-Huh?
Ahhhhh!
-Dead end!
Ha ha ha!
And time is up!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-He disappeared.
-It's so dark, how
can you tell?
-Ah!
[screaming]
-Ah.
He's gone again.
I can see him!
-Huh?
-Oh!
-Where's he going
to pop up next?
-Who knows?
-So dark.
-I can't see.
SAKKKUKAMON (OFFSCREEN):
I can.
-Oh!
SAKKKUKAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Ah, sweet darkness.
Let it embrace thee with its
fear and loneliness.
Yes, it controls thee now.
-I'm scared.
[music playing]
[door squeaking]
-I'm scared!
No, be brave.
But I can't!
[music playing]
-Huh?
ZOE (THINKING): Something's
here.
There's something here!
-I'm scared!
[music playing]
[thunder]
-Ah!
-Ahhhh!
-Kumamon, stop!
Stop it!
-Everybody calm down!
Just calm down!
-Whatever you're going
to do, just do it!
But turn on the lights,
will ya?
-Make it stop!
[shouting]
-Hey, what are you doing?
He's just a baby.
SAKKAKUMON (OFFSCREEN): Ring
around the rosie, a
pocketful of fears.
Oh, what's the matter?
Scared of the dark?
-Huh?
-Beetlemon, stop!
-Just because you can fusion
evolve doesn't make you the
boss here, got it?
-He's right, you need
to chill out.
-Huh?
-Splendid.
I There's nothing like discord
to depose a leader.
-We've never acted this way
towards each other before.
Why now?
-There is a black, bottomless
pit of doubt and fear in all
of your hearts.
-I not the coward here!
-You're the one who wanted
to run away.
-Well, you're the one who was
trying to freeze us all!
-Calm down, you guys!
-Self-doubt.
Jealousy.
Betrayal.
Now you will drown in the fear
of your own darkness!
-No!
-Enough!
[shouting]
-Huh?
-I'm afraid.
-I'm so scared.
-I'm--
I'm--
[shouting]
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN): Stop it!
-No more fear!
-But the dark!
-Stop saying that.
-Huh?
-With faith, we can win.
-Sorry, pal, but faith alone
ain't gonna cut it here.
-Listen to me.
There's still only one of him.
-Yeah, but that hasn't stopped
him from beating
us so far, has it?
-Close your eyes.
-What?
-I said close your eyes!
-We are not humans now.
We're Digimon.
Our senses are sharper
than when we were
in our human forms.
You have to trust the Digimon
inside of you.
-You're right.
I can feel the strength,
the power.
-That sound.
Can you hear it?
He's breathing.
I can hear Sakkakumon's
breathing.
-I hear it.
The four of us are not alone.
Our power lies in the faith that
we have in one another.
Even if you can't fusion evolve,
we can still use all
of our attacks together!
-We can use our attacks.
-All together.
-To win.
-Right.
Whenever you're finished, I
believe you have a little
something to give me.
-Oh yeah!
[sakkakumon laughing]
-Hurricane Wave!
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Uh?
Yaa!
Ah!
Gadzooks!
I don't have that attack
in my records!
-Of course you don't.
That attack's never been
used before, buddy!
-It can't be!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Thunder Fist!
Haaa!
-Ahhhh!
-Thunder Fist!
Yaaa!
-Crystal Breeze!
-Ahhhh!
-You stopped our attacks
individually, but now that
we're mixing our attacks,
you can't beat us!
You'll never steal
our spirits now.
Our attacks have changes,
so you can't copy them.
Your through, Sakkakumon!
-You're wrong!
-Don't think so!
The tables have turned here, and
now you're the one who's
afraid and left in the dark.
Try to guess what
we'll do next!
-I'll still win!
I can't lose to the
likes of you.
I am superior.
You little whelps
can't defeat me.
You will never survive
my power!
-You know what they
always say.
Never say never!
-Oh, can it!
-We're not going to run.
-And we're not afraid!
-And together, we'll destroy
you once and for all!
-You?
You will never stop me!
-The center orb.
He's never attacked
us from there!
It's always been covered up.
That must be where he
controls all the
data he's been storing.
If we could get him to stop
moving, even for just a
second, it might give me
a clear shot at it.
-I have an idea.
Can you guys hold him
still for a while?
-Sure!
-You got it!
Blizzard Blaster!
-Thunder Fist!
-Hurricane Wave!
-Nooo!
-Atomic Inferno!
Ha!
-Yaaaa!
-Time for some purification.
The final chapter to a long
and overwritten book.
Ha!
Fractal Code!
Digitize!
-We did it!
-Finally.
-We conquered our
fears and beat
him as a team [cheering]
-My last warrior, destroyed.
The time has come to
dissolve the seal.
-Once I realized I wasn't alone,
the darkness wasn't
scary.
-I know what you mean.
-Well, that's what real
friends are for.
-Speaking of friends, we've
got to find Koji.
TAKUYA (THINKING):
Where can he be?
-I lost him.
Where could he have gone?
Duskmon!
NARRATOR: So who's going to
find who first, and what's
Duskmon really all
about, anyway?
Find out on the next Digimon
Digital Monsters!