RIKA NARRATING: While Takuya was
trying to figure out how
to Spirit Evolve again, he
released this code that
actually repaired part
of the Digital World.
JP, unimpressed by the whole
experience, snuck away with
Tommy to find a way home.
This brilliant plan to bribe
the Pagumon with chocolate
backfired in a big way.
Kouji saved them with some
amazing moves, but Raremon was
too much for him.
Takuya finally managed to Spirit
Evolve to Agunimon to
fight this sewer Digimon, but
couldn't finish the job.
Thank goodness for Kouji.
He Spirit Evolved to Lobomon
and deodorized that creep.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
Digital World!
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
I am the one!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
I am the one!
Digimon!
-The wind of the Digital World
smells pretty sweet.
-If you really want to go home,
all you have to do is
hop on here.
-It's that easy?
-Neemon, a word, please?
What exactly are you
trying to do?
[interposing voices]
-I'm taking that bad boy home.
Huh?
How about it, guys?
-Uh.
You don't really want to
stay here, do you?
Ugh. Fine!
You dweebs enjoy your little
digital freak show.
Come on, Tommy, let's blow
this stupid pop stand.
-Aren't you going with him?
-I've decided I want to
stay here with you.
-Huh?
-I thought you wanted
to go home.
-Not anymore.
-Go with JP.
It's dangerous here, Tommy.
Besides, the third grade
is a formative year.
-No.
-Go home.
Hurry up now.
Take care of him, JP.
How about you, huh?
-I have a name.
-OK, Zoe.
Are you leaving?
-Why?
Would you miss me?
-I won't be responsible for
your safety, you know.
-Good one, Romeo.
I'll be fine.
-This oughta be fun.
[whistle]
-[whooping]
[coughs]
-Arrivederci!
-Nice pronunciation.
-Thank you.
-[sigh]
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-To be honest, I have
absolutely no idea.
-Me neither.
-Well, I'm not going to be
responsible for your safety.
You're on your own.
-[laughs]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Wait a minute.
Are you mocking me?
You are, aren't you?
Man, you try and be
nice to a girl.
-I hope you're planning on
helping us, Mr. Takuya.
-Hm?
-You carry with you the spirit
of Agunimon, one of the 10
Legendary Warriors.
You can defeat the Digimon
turned evil by Cherubimon.
Only you have the power
to save us!
You must help us repair the
parts of the Digital World
that have been destroyed!
-I think you need to
calm down, buddy.
-My name's Bokomon, and
I'm not your buddy.
I don't think you understand
the severity of
the situation here.
-[groan]
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Didn't
mean to yell.
But we need the data from
the Fractal Code.
It's the only way to rebuild
the Digital World.
Please, help us get the
Fractal Code back.
Save our world before it's
too late, will you?
Neemon, don't just stand there
like a cheap TV antenna!
I need your help! Say something!
-Something.
-Are you really that dense,
or do you just do
that to annoy me?
-Huh?
D-TECTOR: Attention.
Go to the Forest Terminal
immediately.
-What's a Forest Terminal?
-What is a Forest Terminal?
-[groans]
-How am I supposed to find it?
Hey.
Hey, answer me!
-The Forest Terminal is a
station located within the
realm of the Forest Kingdom.
We just follow the tracks.
They'll take us right to it.
-How far do we have
to follow them?
-Well, let's see.
It says--
it says--
uh.
All the way!
-[sigh]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): You're full
of useless information,
aren't you?
-[humming]
-[sigh]
-Neemon, is there
something wrong?
-I guess I'm a little
homesick.
-Then just go back, big baby!
-Should I stay?
Should I go?
Should I stay?
[interposing voices]
-Oh, you wishy-washy
pain in the pants.
If you get too whiny, I'll
just mail you back!
-What made you change your
mind about going home?
Hm?
-Well, I really didn't have
much going on back there
anyway, and I thought I might
be kind of fun to hang out
with you guys and get to know
you a little better.
-Ha!
Get to know Zoe, you mean.
-Hey, that is not
what I meant!
-Then why are you
all red, buddy?
-It's hot out!
I'm sunburned!
What grade are you in, anyway?
-Sixth.
Is that a problem?
-Well, I'm in seventh grade.
-Like I'm supposed to care.
-Like I care if you care.
I should've bolted from
this Digi dump
when I had the chance.
-Tommy, why didn't
you go home?
-I decided I want to
be like Takuya.
-What?
-To become a Digimon so I won't
be scared all the time.
-What about your mom and
dad waiting at home?
I bet they're worried.
-I miss my parents, but when I
come back, I won't be afraid
anymore, so they'll forgive
me for being gone.
-For such a little kid, he
sure has big problems.
-This is a fine mess.
-So what now?
-Check it out, guys!
That trail leads
to the bottom.
-Looks like a village
down there.
Maybe they can help us.
-Humans!
Human children!
Why, I oughta--
-What are they doing here?
-Well, I'll tell you,
nothing good!
We'd better enlighten
the boss!
-That's weird.
I could've sworn those lights
were coming from right here.
-Looked like that to me.
-Takuya?
-Huh?
What is that?
-Kind of pretty.
-Pretty?
Pretty, she says.
These are the marks of the
10 Legendary Warriors.
-The 10 Legendary warriors
-I've never heard of them.
-Are you serious?
The legend of the 10 Warriors is
the first thing we learned
in Digital World History.
-I must've been sick that day.
But they sure are pretty.
-Ugh!
In ancient times, there were
terrible wars between humanoid
Digimon and beast Digimon for
control of the Digital World.
One day, an angel Digimon
called Lucemon appeared.
He taught them how to resolve
their differences and live in
peace, and the fighting
stopped.
Lucemon was a wise, kind ruler,
but the peace in the
Digital World was short-lived.
Lucemon, obsessed with his
power, began to torment the
peace-loving Digimon until
they could take no more.
It was then that 10 brave
warriors rose up against him.
After a fierce battle, they
defeated Lucemon,
restoring the peace.
The legend says that one day,
the spirits of these ancient
warriors will rise again
in times of trouble
-Read it to me again.
-Mm, no.
-I know that symbol.
-It's the same one we saw
when Takuya Spirit
Evolved into Agunimon.
-And that mark next to it was
the one on Kouji's shoulder
when he turned into Lobomon.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): I wonder
if I'll be next.
Oh, I hope my Digimon's cute.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): I want to be
like the biggest, scariest
Digimon ever.
JP (OFFSCREEN): Not
likely, shorty.
I mean, there's no way we'll
all get to be Digimon.
-Huh?
We've got company.
-Why have you humans come
to our village?
You are not welcome here.
-We're on our way to the
Forest Terminal.
Sorry to disturb you.
We're just passing through.
-You're melting my heart.
-Ooh, that's a no-no.
-You mean to steal the ancient
artifact from us, don't you?
Well, you won't get
away with it!
-He's right.
The humans must be punished.
-Hey, boss!
You want us to wax him for you?
-Wait! Stop! Let me explain!
These humans have come to help
us save the Digital World, not
steal some artifact.
-But we didn't know
that at first.
-You're not helping.
This may be hard to believe,
but somehow this boy was
infused with the spirit
of one of the 10
Legendary Warriors, Agunimon.
-Did you say Agunimon?
Impossible!
-That's a hot one.
-What if it really is him?
-He's pulling our wicks!
-Well, isn't this interesting?
Please forgive our
rude behavior,
my dear young friends.
[laughs]
We are the Candlemon Tribe.
It is our sacred duty to protect
the ancient artifact.
So which of you inherited
the Spirit of
the Legendary Warrior?
-It was this one, Takuya.
-[whimpers]
-Ah.
Well, you certainly have a
brave face, young man.
On behalf of all the Candlemon
Tribe, I bid you all welcome.
Please, be our guest.
-Something doesn't
seem quite right.
-Come along now, don't dawdle.
-[chanting]
-Looks like a giant
birthday party.
-It's for you, my friends.
A welcome ceremony. Enjoy!
[chanting]
-Come closer.
Feel the warmth of the flame.
[chanting]
-Oh, look at this.
It's sleeping clover.
-It's nappy time anyway.
-I can't keep my eyes open.
-Yeah.
-Night.
-So you've claimed the spirit
of Agunimon, have you?
Bah!
We'll soon shed some
light on this!
-Let's turn up the heat on
these artifact filchers!
Get them, Candlemon!
-Yeah!
-Hey, we can't stay here.
Come on!
The river!
-Lava loogie!
-Dive in!
-I don't know how to swim.
-That was a great idea!
-I'll never complain about
my alarm clock again!
-Yeah, nice way to wake up.
Did we really have to
jump into the river?
-Takuya said we had to dive in,
or we were gonna burn up.
-Oh, yeah?
-Oh, did I disturb your
beauty sleep?
-We'll be safe as long
as we stay here.
I bet fire Digimon like
Candlemon can't get near the
water.
-Guess again, human!
Lava loogie!
-Go under!
-Find them!
Don't let them get away!
-Where'd they go?
-I don't know!
They just disappeared!
-Well, they've gotta
come up sometime!
And when they do, we'll--
-I'll distract them.
Then, on my signal, you guys
make a break for it.
-Some plan.
-Hang on a minute,
Mr. President.
I don't remember electing you
leader of this stupid club.
Right?
-Yeah.
That's right.
We're all in this together, so
any decisions we make, we make
as a team, OK?
-I really want to help,
but I'm too slow.
You guys should just
go on without me.
-That's not an option.
If I Spirit Evolve to Agunimon,
I can snuff out the
Candlemon!
-Right, Spirit Boy.
Better read your Digimon
instruction manual before you
try something dumb
like that again.
-He's right.
You shouldn't try
to fight alone.
You're not very good
at it yet.
-Here they come! Duck!
-[cackling]
-Thanks for the vote
of confidence.
Just get Tommy out
of here, OK?
-OK, let's move.
-I see one of them!
Get 'em!
-Lava loogie!
-Come on, help me out here!
-Oh, no!
My D-Tector!
-Takuya!
-We've got you now, human!
[cackling]
-What?
-Spirit Evolution time!
Execute Spirit Evolution!
Agunimon!
-[cheering]
-Well, I'll be dipped.
The brat really is Agunimon!
-Lava loogie!
-I summon the Pyro Tornado!
-[cackling]
-What?
-What's wrong?
-Fire attacks don't
work on Candlemon.
He should know that.
-Yeah, that wasn't too bright.
Come on, I'd better get
us out of this hole,
before we get waxed.
I hate ice skating.
-Be careful, Tommy.
-I'm trying.
-Wow, I didn't see
that before.
-We should be safe from those
hotheads in there.
-Please give me a Spirit.
I want to help!
-Give it up, kid.
The spirits of the Legendary
Warriors would never give
their power to a pipsqueak
like you.
Looks like it's really
up to me.
Aw, man, I wish this
came with a manual.
-Paraffin paralyzer!
-That stuff hurts!
-Ah! Agunimon!
Hang on!
-I gotcha, buddy!
Look out!
Oh no!
-I can't--
I can't move anything!
-Hang on, Takuya!
I'm coming!
-Tommy, no!
-Stop, kid!
-Lights out, you meanies!
I won't be just a little kid
in the way ever again!
-Mama mia!
-It's a Spirit!
Spirit, come to me!
D-TECTOR: It is time.
-Execute Spirit Evolution!
Kumamon!
-That's amazing!
-That's impossible!
-It's Tommy!
-Yay!
-What in blazes?
-Ah. It is.
It's Kumamon, the legendary
warrior of ice.
-Time to teach you
bullies a lesson.
Crystal freeze!
-Hey there, teddybear!
You want a playmate?
Ha-cha!
-Wizardmon.
This mysterious champion level
Digimon can make you disappear
with his Electro-squall and
Magical Game attacks.
-Crystal freeze!
-Take off, teddy!
-Kumamon!
-Looks like the great Agunimon
has a little
problem with waxy buildup!
How about a little
Magical Game?
Ta-ta!
-That was weird.
-[laughing]
Up here!
I know!
Let's play catch!
Not bad, Legendary Warrior.
But I've got plenty
up my sleeve.
Too bad you're going to
lose no matter which
Wizardmon you choose!
-Which is the real Wizardmon?
-They all look the same to me!
-Agunimon, don't you see?
All these Wizardmon are me!
We all look real,
because we are.
Just try to run.
You won't get far!
-This is just a game.
Only one is real, and I'm
going to find it!
-Every warrior must fall.
Your time is up!
Electro-squall!
-Agunimon!
Look down here!
Only one of them has a shadow!
-Thanks! Game's over!
I never did believe in magic.
Here's a trick for you.
Fractal code!
Digitize!
-Ha-cha-cha.
-Yay! Molto bene!
-Yeah, mol-- what she said!
-Ah.
Thanks, Agunimon!
-No, thank you.
You're one brave little bear.
-[laughs]
-Well, I guess this proves
that they really are the
Legendary Warriors after all.
-Yes.
I would not have believed it
if I hadn't seen it myself.
You have indeed proven
yourselves worthy of carrying
the spirits of the Legendary
Warriors,
my young human friends.
Takuya and little Tommy, you
two have truly honored the
great names of Agunimon
and Kumamon.
I salute you both.
-[cheering]
-I'm afraid I owe you
all an apology.
The truth is, we thought you
might possess the spirits of
the Legendary Warriors, but
we still had to make sure.
I'm sorry we didn't trust you.
-So then all of this
has been a test?
-Well, that pretty
much stinks.
You're lucky I don't pinch
your lights out for that.
-[laughs]
I'm so sorry.
You have every right
to be angry.
D-TECTOR: Fractal
code rendered.
-Whoa!
-Wizardmon had the code.
-Wizardmon held within him the
Fractal Code for the bridge,
which protected our village
from evil Digimon.
Young Takuya, for many
years, no one has
crossed this canyon.
But you have my official
permission to use this bridge.
Follow the tracks, and
they will lead you
to the Forest Terminal.
But it is a perilous journey.
-Uh, maybe we should think
about this, guys.
There's still time to go home.
-You're just jealous because
Tommy found his inner Digimon,
and you haven't yet.
-Why would I even
care about that?
Shorty can have it.
It's just that being here
is like working.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): We all know
how you feel about that!
JP (OFFSCREEN): Very funny.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
somebody else just beat us
across the bridge.
I wonder if he's going to the
Forest Terminal, too.
RIKA NARRATING: That could've
been a serious meltdown.
Hopefully the dream team's
on the right track now.
We'll see, on the next Digimon:
Digital Monsters.