NARRATOR: Our were desperate to
save what remained of the
digital world.
The Autumn Leaf Fair was full of
all their old friends, and
a few foes, frantically trying
to get to safety.
When the royal knights showed
up, some of the fiercest mon
around tried to take
them on, but they
didn't stand a chance.
Takuya and Koji unity of all
for battle while the others
set up a catapult for backup.
Then everyone got hit hard
enough to knock the fractal
code out of them, all except
Kiochi that is.
Crusademon said it's
because he doesn't
have a physical form.
Anyway, the fair was scanned
and those nasty knights are
out to get the only area left.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned as we
work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
I am the one--
huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one--
Together the battles are won--
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve!
When we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
We're all for one world, there's
a world for us all.
I am the one, huh!
I am the one--
Digimon!
-I'm feeling a little woozy.
-Woozy, he says.
I feel downright ill.
Are we there yet?
-I wish.
At least there's no sign of the
royal knights anywhere.
-Good.
Maybe we lost them.
-My, aren't we just the
loopy optimist?
-No more loopy.
-Hey, check it out!
-No loopy?
-Ophanimon's Castle--
finally.
-But I was having fun.
-You're such a twit.
-Just one more minor
detail and you will
be revived my lord.
-I will be most displeased
if you fail me, Dynasmon!
I've grown weary of this prison
and long to fulfill my
destiny!
-As we long for the
day you are free.
We will succeed, my lord, even
if we must risk our own
existence to do your bidding.
-Don't be ridiculous!
Our lord is right to trite me,
but those humans are no match
for us!
-As you wish, my lord, when you
are revived you will give
us the key to the human
world, won't you?
-As you wish, my dear
Crusadermon, but
do you doubt me?
How very disappointing.
[evil laughter]
-You shall have what
you desire.
-Crusadermon, you are foolish
to ask questions when you
already know the answer.
Your doubt will make you weak.
-Wow!
It's sparkly!
-Let's hope it's not just
another pretty face.
-You're right.
It doesn't look like
much of a fortress.
-It's still here.
Well, that has to count
for something.
-Now that's logical.
They just haven't found
it yet, genius.
-But I--
I--
-I gotcha.
But it doesn't really
matter does it?
If they don't know where it
is, they will soon enough.
-Right again, my boy.
-Wow!
You're starting to make
a habit of that!
-You, Koichi, have no physical
form-- terribly sorry.
[evil laughter]
-No, then--
I'm just--
-A spirit only.
-Koichi, what is it?
-Huh?
Nothing.
It's nothing, really.
[gasping]
-Wow!
-Check this out.
-Wow.
-I didn't even know there
were this many books.
-Uh-huh.
-Amazing.
-The data just has to be
somewhere in this castle.
Don't you think?
-Well yeah, but where?
[gasping]
-You are the ones sworn
to protect the digital
world, are you not?
-We are them.
Uh-- da-- we-- w--
we are they.
Uh, whatever.
Yeah, that's us!
-At last.
[gasps]
-You seem surprised.
Your adventures are
no secret to me.
You hold the spirits of the
10 legendary warriors.
-But--
how'd you know?
-All knowledge of the digital
world resides here as soon as
it is known.
-So you're, like,
the librarian?
Then you must know the key
to protecting this place.
-I'm afraid I don't.
I am Nefertimon.
I protect this castle on the
orders of Lady Ophanimon.
-Wait, I don't get it!
If you're the protector of this
place, shouldn't you know
how to do it?
-Your friend is right.
I am like a librarian.
I protect this place, but that
doesn't mean I know everything
it contains.
That would be impossible.
-Of course it would be.
Nothing is ever that
simple around here.
-Come on, guys.
Nothing worth doing is ever
simple, at least no one is
shooting at us.
We're just going to have
to find it on our own.
And I don't know about you, but
I'd rather find it before
the royal Lonuses do.
-I can't argue with
that logic.
Let's split up into
groups of two.
-Right, that's what I was
was about to say.
-Bokomon, you guys keep a look
out for the royal knights.
-We'll keep our eyes peeled.
-Really?
That sounds painful.
-Okay.
We'll head upstairs,
right Koichi?
-Huh?
Mm.
Are you okay?
You're acting kind of weird.
-Am I?
Well then, maybe
I'm just weird.
-Hmm.
-So Z, shall we check the
inner rooms together?
-Uhm, but what about me?
-All right.
How about I check the basement
with Takuya while you help
J.P. check the inner
rooms, okay?
-Okay.
-Right, so let's get going.
[moaning]
-Did I say something
wrong, J.P.?
[gasping]
[laughing]
-How could anything be wrong?
[moaning]
-I don't know how we're
supposed to
find anything here.
Everything looks the same.
-Yeah.
-Koichi.
-Huh?
Yeah.
-Come on, bro.
What's wrong?
-I told you--
nothing.
-If you say so.
I guess you are just weird.
-Koji.
-Yeah?
-Uh, nothing.
Nevermind.
[snickers]
-Koichi.
-What?
-I'm really glad I came to
this world, you know,
otherwise I might not
have met you.
Now we'll be able to see each
other all the time.
I mean, when we're back in
the human world and all.
-Yeah.
[snickers]
-Oh, man.
I don't even know
where to start.
-How about at the beginning?
[screams]
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Oh, nothing.
-I'm sorry about that, T-Boy.
-Hey, no problem.
-What?
Do you need to take a
break or something?
-No, we just got to find that
key, J.P. We just gotta!
What happens if the royal knights get her
before we find it?
-Ta-da!
[giggling]
-(SINGING) Flowers in the air
to take away your cares a--
[gasps]
-Uhm.
Guess that didn't
help much, huh?
-What?
Well, you know, you look
kind of freaked.
[sighs]
-Thanks.
-Anytime partner.
Ha!
Want to see another trick?
I can keep this up all night!
Ha!
-Hey, J.P.
-Uh, hmm?
-I'm scared.
What if we mess up?
If we can't stop him this whole
world will be destroyed
and with all of us
still in it.
I don't know.
I guess I'm still just
a scary cat.
-It takes a brave person to
admit he's scared to death.
-Are you scared?
-Are you kidding me?
[giggles]
-I am scared out of my chocolate
coated mind!
I haven't changed one bit,
but I'm still here.
-Yeah.
[screaming]
-Uh, smooth move, Takuya.
-It's like that game.
Uh, what's his name?
Anyway, I always lose.
But it doesn't usually
hurt this much.
Do you think we have to
check every book?
-Yeah, probably.
As J.P. says, nothing's
ever easy.
-Are you tired?
[yawns]
-How'd you guess?
-Gee, I don't know.
-You want to take a break?
-If I stop looking, I'll start
thinking and I really don't
want to do that right now.
[giggles]
-Yeah, we can't have you
thinking now can we?
-Well, Neemon thinks
I'm good at it.
-Yeah.
-You know, Zoe, this could
be our last battle.
We've fought well.
-It hasn't all been fighting.
It's the other things
that I'll remember.
Sure, it's way cool to be a
Digimon and kick butt and all,
but it wouldn't have been half
as much fun without you guys.
You're the first real friends
I've ever had.
I never even knew how to be a
friend and now I understand
myself a little better
and others too.
I don't think I'll ever have
trouble making friends again
and it's because I actually
like myself now.
-Well, I really like
you too, Zoe.
-Yeah.
-Like, you know,
not like, like.
Uh, oh, come on.
You know what I mean.
-Oh.
-Right?
-Right.
[humming]
-I can't believe I said that.
-Uh.
Oh.
Takuya.
[snoring]
-Well, that figures.
-Sleep tight.
-It's so quiet.
-Too quiet if you ask me.
Not that you did ask me, but.
Oh.
Please tell me you
found the key.
-I wish I could, but we
didn't find anything.
Just a whole lot of books.
-So anybody get lucky?
Nah.
-Nah, a long night with nothing
to show for it.
-Except a mess.
Nefertimon's gonna be mad.
On second thought, I
doubt she'll care.
-There's still Takuya and Zoe.
Hmm.
-So how did it go?
Did you guys find anything?
-You know, I just hate it when
I get my hopes up like that.
-I know exactly how you feel.
-Come on, guys!
We can't give up!
Are you with me, everybody?
ALL: Yeah!
[cheering]
-Koichi, my dear boy, are
you worrying about what
Crusadermon said to
you yesterday?
[gasps]
-Bokomon, promise me you
won't tell the others.
-I promise.
[cheering]
-Dynasmon, we're being bathed in
beautiful white flowers in
the dawn light.
Could there be a more
perfect way to
begin this day of destiny?
-Oh, no.
[gasping]
-What is it?
-Children, the royal
knights are coming.
[gasping]
[screaming]
-You can say that again!
-I was certain you'd run away!
-Your courage is
appealing, even
admirable but so misguided.
You remind me of this flower.
Your beauty is fragile.
ALL: Huh?
-Just as these petals scatter
in the wind, so shall you.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, maybe it will be us that
does the scattering!
-Your arrogance bores me!
Shall I call your bluff?
-From the darkness of
this fallen world, a
new order will arise.
Do you desire to go with
it when it disappears?
-Well, we desire you
to disappear!
You got that?
Let's go!
-Hmp.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm.
-Huh.
-Wind into flame!
-Ice into flame!
Thunder into light!
-Darkness into light!
[music playing]
ALL: Unity execute!
Unify spirit evolution!
[screaming]
[music playing]
[fighting]
MagnaGaruruman!
ALL: Unity execute!
Unify spirit evolution!
[screaming]
[fighting]
-Emperor Freemon!
Hmm.
-We're behind you 100 percent,
Emperor Greymon!
-You can do it, MagnaGarurumon!
-How amusing.
-Indeed, you see, we already
know where to find the key to
this area's data.
-You do-gooders who fight
against the darkness.
-You sanctify Digimon
of light.
You, Nefertimon, are the key!
[gasps]
-No!
-Silence, meddler!
[gasps]
-No wonder we couldn't
find it.
-Actually, we had
it all along.
-For Lady Ophanimon I will
protect this sacred place!
Beam of ices!
Uhh!
[gasping]
-Nefertimon!
Rosetta Stone!
[fighting]
-Gone!
-No way!
-You must destroy me, only then
can I protect this place.
-What?
-Please, I beg of you.
Destroy me and you will protect
this place forever.
-No!
-You must!
It is my duty and my honor, my
promise to Lady Ophanimon.
-Nefertimon, don't ask
us to do this!
-Let us protective this place!
-Yeah, and you protect
yourself!
Huh.
BOTH: You're going down!
-How banal.
I expected a much more elegant
expression of your intent.
[gasps]
-Spiral masquerade!
[groaning]
-Dragon fire crossbow!
-Dragon thrower!
-Ahh!
Ahh!
-We can't lose!
We just can't!
Uhh!
-If we can't beat them, at least
maybe we could take them
out with us.
[fighting]
-How judicious--
hand-to-hand combat!
-Back off you annoying
little creature!
-Now that's wishful thinking!
-We're never going
to back down!
-You will not scan this data!
We will fight you with the
last of our strength to
prevent that!
-Why do you care so much what
happens to the digital world?
[fighting]
-You're just humans!
-Yes, but we hold the spirits
of Digimon, the legendary
warrior sworn to stand
against the darkness!
-This is our world too!
-How extraordinary!
-Well, the best is yet
to come, Pinkie!
-Give me a break!
-I'd just be thrilled
to break you!
-Your attitude would be amusing
if I didn't dislike
you so thoroughly!
-I don't think too much
of you either!
-Looks like they're
holding their own!
-Yeah, but for how long?
-Hang in there guys!
The fate of the digital
world is
completely on your shoulders!
-We're with you!
-We know you can do it!
-What he said!
-We believe in you.
-Be strong.
[fighting]
-You keep getting stronger!
What is this ability of humans
to exceed their natural
limitations?
-You don't get it!
We don't believe
in limitations!
-Be that as it may, we are
destined to win, not you
arrogant creatures!
-You're wrong!
You only want to
destroy things!
How could destiny
be on your side?
-We want to bring peace to this
world, not destroy it!
We don't accept the power
of destruction!
-We might actually win!
-Yeah!
Hang in there!
[fighting]
[screaming]
-Takuya!
Koji!
[gasping]
-Nefertimon!
-No!
-You foolish creature!
What made you think you could
protect this world?
You're no better than
the humans!
-Goodbye, children.
Ahh.
-And thus it ends.
As it was foretold, a castle
adrift in snow white blossoms
will fall, and with
it the world!
-And so it is!
[explosion]
[gasping]
-It's gone.
-I can't believe it.
They destroyed the
whole world.
-Lord Lucemon is free!
-Lucemon?
-That little boy?
[gasps]
-It is done as it was to be.
I am your ordained ruler
with absolute power
over your very existence.
You will serve me as you
were born to do.
You will give me my
every desire--
even yourself.
-Well, that is not
going to happen!
What do you think this world
is, your stupid toy or
something?
-A toy?
That's exactly what it is, but
I was bored with the old one.
I think I'll create a new
digital world, a better one--
my own.
[gasps]
-You little brat!
-She's right!
You're nothing but a
spoiled little boy!
-Hmm.
-You baby!
Uh!
-Ha!
You're nothing but children
yourselves!
-Lord Lucemon, a moment.
Have you forgotten?
You promised to give us the key
to the human world if we
gave you the power to return
to this world.
-First, there are things
that must be done.
[moaning]
-I don't want to play with
you weaklings anymore.
You're no fun.
Goody good cry babies,
be gone.
Hmm.
[screaming]
ALL: Huh?
-Liebchen, grab onto me!
-A handle!
-There we go.
It wasn't exactly what
I had in mind, but
they're out of the way.
Good enough.
-I'm flying you to the moon!
-You're what?
-You didn't want to stay with
that evil child now did you?
Besides, without you the digital
world really will be
gone forever.
It breaks my heart.
The world, you must
save the world!
Please, mein kinder.
Do that for me?
-Buddy, we'll do it
for everyone.
Take us to the moon and
we'll find a way.
We have to!
-Yeah.
-Oh, dear.
I can't believe it.
They actually destroyed the
whole digital world!
You have got to keep watching
"Digimon Digital Monsters!"