BOKOMON (NARRATING):
We finally made it
to Ophanimon's castle.
There we met Nefertimon, the
protector of the palace.
Too bad she didn't know where
the key to protecting it was.
After a night of fruitless
searching, the unified kids
were forced to face those
rotten royals.
It turns out Nefertimon
was the key.
Oh, they tried their best, but
the Royal Knights were just
too much for them, and they
succeeded in scanning the
castle and reviving Lucemon.
That spoiled little brat tried
to destroy us, but thanks to
Angler, we're on our
way to the moon.
I only hope there's still
time to save our world.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): The third
moon that orbits the Digital
World is usually covered with
yellow colored sand, giving
its surface an atmosphere of
warm, golden appearance Hm.
-Yeah, this place
is a bella luna.
-Ditto me on that,
Z. It's kind of
like a slice of heaven.
-Knock it off, JP.
We're not anywhere near
heaven just yet.
-Huh?
I just meant it's nice.
-Mm-hm.
-No.
Then I'm just--
-A spirit only.
-The Digiworld's had it.
It looks in really bad shape.
-It got wiped out.
-Guess it's really over.
-No No, it's not.
-How can you say that, Takuya?
-Because I know better.
There just has to be a
way for us to turn
this whole world around.
We can't give up.
Winners never quit, and if
we quit, we'll never win.
-But Takuya, the world we did
our best to protect doesn't
even exist.
-It's not that we're quitting,
but there's nothing for us to
do here, and no way
left to do it.
-Hello.
Have you forgotten that
we're all Digimon?
-That's the spirit.
-Yeah.
-Come on!
[beeping]
Am I wrong to believe in us?
-Now, what is it?
-My lord, when can
we have the key?
-Possessing the key
to the human
world would be beauteous.
-I have heard enough.
-I humbly beseech
you, noble one.
Allow me to explain.
When you first engaged us in
your quest, you promised us
that we would ruler Earth.
But without the key, we cannot
enter it and begin our reign.
You swore that if we destroyed
the Digital World and revived
you, the key would be ours.
-I don't need you
to remind me.
I know what I said.
-Yes, but perhaps--
-Lord Lucemon.
-I plan on keeping my promise
you, but first I
must destroy them.
Now get to that moon
and do your job.
-But when 'tis done, you
will give us the key?
-How can you doubt my
word, Crusadermon?
If I didn't have the key, and if
I wasn't going to give you,
I would have already said so.
Such lack of trust will surely
poison my faith in you.
-How can you doubt our
master's intentions?
-I don't--
-Your beliefs bend with each
wind, but I will not be frozen
by your fears.
We must obey Lord Lucemon
unequivocally.
We fear nothing in serving
you, my lord.
Nothing but our own failure.
-Please forgive give
me my doubts, sire.
-Now that you are of one
mind, destroy them.
-We will.
-What are those floating
things?
-Huh?
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Whoa.
Looks like someone's taking
a bubble bath.
-Oh, goodie!
Bathtime!
-Papamon says come back!
-Wow, check it out.
[playful chirping]
-The Digi-Eggs.
-Magnifico.
They're back.
They're so cute.
-Yeah.
-Hey
-Hi.
All of these Digimon must
have just hatched.
-Yeah, I bet you're right.
-It's so great to
see you guys.
You know, sometimes you're not
really sure if your paths will
cross again, but it's put a
smile on my face to know that
we've all made it here.
-Taku!
-And you're a cute little guy.
-Yah, yah, yah.
-Wah!
-I sure have a way
with babies, huh?
-I wonder if he's hungry.
Or maybe he needs to-- ah!
-Ah, these are about to hatch!
Ah!
-My name is Lopmon.
It's nice to meet you.
And my name is Salamon.
So, tell us who you are.
-My name's Patamon.
[laughter]
-Lopmon fall down, go boom.
-It looks like time has brought
these three full circle.
Patamon is Seraphimon,
Lopmon is Cherubimon,
and Salamon is Ophanimon.
-After everything they
went through, they've
forgiven each other.
-Gee, I guess when they
were reborn, it must
have purified them.
-I don't know, Z Maybe they
became pure, and that's why
they were reborn.
-What do you think?
[humming]
-Who knows?
-I don't think it really matters
how this happened.
Just as long as they all grow
together as friends.
-Mm-hm.
-We have to make sure
that happens.
[thunder rolling]
-What can we do to bring
it all back?
-Just try.
-Yeah.
We can't give up hope.
-We need a new plan of action.
-Right.
We'll make it happen.
-Huh?
[shouting]
-They're here.
The evil ones.
-It's those bad Royal Knights.
-What will you do?
-What do you mean?
-Are you gonna stand
up to them?
Or will you run?
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
It's up to you now.
Which one will you choose?
-I'm so bored.
What is this about?
Oh, what the heck?
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
The game to determine
your future has begun.
-Yeah.
Boy, have I been in the game.
It became a more serious game
when I found who I really was.
Finding out you're not just a
kid, but a Digimon gave me all
kinds of feelings.
Feelings of power and
responsibility, but most of
all, it gave me the sense
that what I did really
could affect things.
At first it was kind of fun.
I mean, it was really exciting
to be exploring the Digital
World, discovering the
Forest Terminal.
It was like a big puzzle
trying to decide
which way to go.
But as we made our way through
the dark continent to the Rose
Morning Star, we experienced
more challenges.
As I look back on our quest, I
realize we've shared so many
adventures.
Many of my memories are
bittersweet, and some are
downright painful.
Seeing so many creatures that
were getting destroyed changed
the way I think about evil.
Evil can confuse you when you're
standing at it straight
in the face.
-You would do that?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): You hope
the face of evil can change
itself, but it won't unless
you force it to change.
-Guys, what's happening?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): As much as
evil has tried to get the best
of us, we have never
stopped trying.
Many times we've had chances
to leave the Digital World.
We could have gone back to our
safe, warm homes and our
loving families, but we always
chose to stay, to try to
change things.
Because evil in all its forms
it must be stopped.
-No!
What have you done?
-He's too strong.
I have no choice.
Zephyrote Crystals!
-We've always tried to stop
evil from running wild.
I've faced this decision before,
but I always return to
fight for what's right.
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN):
Well, I didn't
think I'd see you again.
-Trailmon, you have
to take me back.
-Are you sure?
This is a one way ticket, kid.
I can't turn around if you
get any second thoughts.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): No way.
I've made my decision.
-I guess you have.
-So why are you all staying?
-We've still got a lot of stuff
we need to take care of.
And as we watched our friends
had back to Earth, there as a
part of us that wished we
were going with them.
But there's a reason
we're still here.
We can make a difference.
After everything we've seen, and
all the things we've been
through, we're not
about to let evil
have the final victory.
-They may think we don't have
anything left, but we're not
finished yet.
-Yeah, that's right.
When we combine all of our
strength, we can't be beat.
So let's do it.
-Mm-hm.
-We have got to look at this
as the final battle.
There's no backing down.
Those royal creeps may think
we're just kids to be bullied,
but we're Digimon.
This is our world, too, and
we're not gonna let them win.
-Then let's show them.
Right now.
-Yeah!
-Wind into flame!
-Thunder into light!
-Ice into flame!
-Darkness into light!
-Unity Execute!
Unified Spirit Evolution!
[screaming]
-Unity Execute!
Unified Spirit Evolution!
[screaming]
-MagnaGarurumon!
-EmperorGreymon!
-Well, well, well.
Now allow us to show
you knights what
real courage can do!
Let's get 'em!
-I'm with ya!
-To become the supreme rulers
of the Earth, we must crush
these pests.
-Yes.
To get the key, we
must defeat them.
[laughter]
-How can you doubt my
word, Crusadermon?
Such lack of trust will surely
poison my faith in you.
-I must believe him.
[shouting]
-Let us get the upper hand.
-Oh, of course.
-Magna Missiles!
-No!
Oh, what happened?
-Those that ignore history are
condemned to repeat it, and so
you shall be defeated
again by the power
of the Royal Knights.
What?
How can this be?
No!
How can you be stronger?
[screaming]
-Crusadermon's doubts have
dissipated our power.
-Spiral Masquerade!
Fist of Athena!
-Are you tired? 'Cause
I'm not!
[screaming]
-Crusadermon!
My dear fallen comrade, we were
to rule Earth together.
You will pay for this
ruinous wound!
Breath of Wyvern!
Ha ha ha!
-Pyro Dragons!
[screaming]
-Dynasmon!
-Now I will purify you.
-No, it's mine.
Grand Cross!
-EmperorGreymon!
-MagnaGarurumon!
-Master.
-Now I'll absorb the Knights'
data and become unstoppable.
-No!
Not that!
-He's scanning them!
[evil laughter]
-Who's that?
-That's gotta be Lucemon.
And it looks like
he's evolved.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
It is Lucemon.
But now he's in his more
powerful Chaos Mode.
-I want you to understand, every
living creature in this
world is precious to me.
-That is a bold-faced lie.
-How can you think it is a
lie, dear young human?
It was difficult to put
those poor knights
out of their misery.
But for their eternal
happiness, I had to.
-You wiped them out to
take their power!
-I couldn't have them live a
life in pain, and they didn't
accept my loving
rules of life.
-So it's follow your
rules or suffer?
-You want to control everyone.
It's not right.
-Mm-hm.
-Most of you can't control
yourselves, so I'm here to
help you.
-It sounds like you don't
want us to act
or think for ourselves.
You want us to be slaves, and
to accept living in a world
run by you.
-Without a loving being to
shepherd you, this new world
order I'm creating could
become chaos.
I'm inviting all of you share
in my view of paradise.
It is frustrating to reason with
beasts like you, who only
think of themselves and never
consider that common good.
Now I ask you to join me
and share the vision I
have for all of us.
You need me, for only
I have the wisdom to
command this utopia.
-We've seen what your
evil has done here.
We don't want you.
-That's too bad.
I had hoped you'd hear me
out with an open mind.
You've made a mistake.
-You're nothing big bully.
-You're not that big,
you weirdo!
-My utopia won't have room
for upstarts like you.
You cannot survive.
To create my paradise, all you
humans and Digimon must be
exterminated.
But don't fret.
I will give you eternal
happiness.
Since you won't accept me as
your master, I've no choice
but to wipe the slate clean.
-We're not gonna let
that happen!
Dragonfire Crossbow!
-Starburst Hunter!
[laughter]
-That's impossible.
-You both look surprised.
You really thought that
would work against me?
-No!
Don't do it!
-You are foolish, but I
will show you love.
Experience my benevolent
compassion.
Paradise Lost Punch!
-Takuya!
-Takuya, get away!
-My data!
-You shall be the first.
-Takuya!
[screaming]
-No, Lucemon!
No!
-Koji!
-Help him!
-The whole place is
falling apart!
-Someone help us!
BOKOMON (NARRATING): Oh, dear.
Can the Digital World go on?
How are any of us going
to survive?
There's only one way
to find out.
Watch the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.