NARRATOR: When Cherubimon
decided to give ExVeemon the
heave ho, Aldamon and Beowolfmon
took the long-eared
ninny outside to
keep him busy.
Meanwhile, the other kids tried
everything they could to
free Ophanimon.
Then Trubimon turned into
a major klepto and stole
everybody's detectors.
Ophanimon finally broke out
of her cage and sacrificed
himself to get them back.
With the last of her strength,
she gave Takua and Koji's
detectors the ultimate
upgrade.
All the gang has to do is share
their spirits and the
unified evolution can begin.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned as we
work towards one solution
through a spirit evolution.
I am the one, huh!
I am the one--
Digimon!
Forever united as one--
Together the battles are won!
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve!
When we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all!
I am the one, huh!
I am the one--
Digimon!
-We can't feel Ophanimon!
-Use your spirits!
-Wind into flame!
-Ice into flame!
-Thunder into light!
-Darkness into light!
[music playing]
-Unity execute!
-Unified spirit evolution!
[screaming]
[music playing]
[fighting]
Emperor Greymon!
[music playing]
-Unity execute!
-Unified spirit evolution!
[screaming]
[music playing]
[grunting]
-Magna Garurumon!
-Ahh.
Another beautiful evolution.
-You guys rock!
-I'll say!
-Enjoy it while you can for
shortly all you'll enjoy is
the comfort of the grave.
Ophanimon was a fool to
sacrifice herself!
-No!
Actually Cherubimon,
you're the fool!
-What?
-You think you can control the
digital world by yourself, but
you're going to destroy
it instead!
You're so greedy that you'll
end up with nothing!
-But don't worry, we'll stop you
long before that happens!
-Pathetic meddling humans!
What could you know of
the digital world?
-Apparently more than you!
All of us can see that
your selfishness will
destroy this world!
-But with Ophanimon's power
behind us now, we'll stop you!
[grunts]
-Whenever you're ready!
-Then prepare for your doom.
No matter what power you have
gained, you are no match for
one of the celestial Digimon!
Storm of Judgement!
[groaning]
[screaming]
-Hey, guys.
That was a little too
close for comfort!
-You see, I can destroy all
of you that easily!
-We have to get the
others to safety!
-Right!
[grunts]
[roars]
[evil laughter]
-Hmm?
-Hmm.
Don't be so quick to gloat.
With your friend gone,
it will be twice as
easy to defeat you!
-All right, guys.
You should be safe up here!
[grunting]
-We're fine!
Go stop that guy!
-I'll do my best, which as
we all know, is awesome!
-Hit 'em once for me!
-Twice for me!
[screams]
-Lightening spear!
[fighting]
-What? you haven't beaten
this guy yet?
-Not quite.
[growling]
-And that's why!
-Whoa!
-Don't let him scare you!
-We're all counting
on you guys!
-We know you can do it!
BOTH: Takuya and Koji,
they're our men!
If they're can't do
it no one can!
-Trying to concentrate here!
Come on, Koji.
[gasps]
-Whoa.
-(THINKING) I should
be fighting.
I need to do something
good after all
the evil I've caused.
[gasps]
-You are more powerful than
I thought, but still--
you will perish!
Lightening spear!
[fighting]
-Actually--
perishing is your job!
Dragon fire crossbow!
[groaning]
-Magna missiles!
-Feral fire magnarockets!
[fighting]
-Ahhh!
[screaming]
[groaning]
-Did we defeat him?
-Never!
[growling]
-Good, because we're ready
to fight some more!
-You are done!
Storm of judgment!
[shivering]
-We're going to be blast into
smithereens for sure!
-Maybe not, J.P. Those attacks
are wild and unfocused like
Cherubimon fighting scared.
-I think we're actually safer
than we've ever been.
Ahh!
-Nice shooting--
unless of course you were
actually trying to hit us!
So, are you ready
to surrender?
-This is incomprehensible.
My attack should have
annihilated you!
-Face it, Cherubimon, we're
too powerful for you!
-You're too powerful?
I was ruling this world before
any of you feeble creatures
even existed!
-That's true, but not anymore!
-You don't even know our
secret weapon yet!
You're powerful, it's true.
But you're all alone.
We have the strength of our
friends on our side!
-Don't be fools!
The power you have comes only
from the spirits and from
Ophanimon's essence, nothing
more, but neither
one shall save you!
Storm of--
-Starburst hunter!
[gasping]
-Pyro dragons!
[fighting]
[shivering]
-It's coming down!
-We have to get out!
-Cherubimon, Not now!
We have to save the others!
-Right!
[moaning]
-Come on!
What are you waiting for!
-You first.
-Uh, okay.
-Come on!
-All right, I'm coming.
[moaning and screaming]
ALL: Koji!
[grunts]
-Koji.
[grunting]
-Wow!
We got out of there just
in the nick of time!
-So do you think we got him?
-No way!
It's never that easy!
-(THINKING) After all I did,
he still saved me.
-Guys, look out!
[moaning]
[coughing]
-Oh, my head.
That's the only part of
me that doesn't hurt.
Huh?
[grunting]
-Everyone all right?
-Yup.
-No one got hurt?
Well, I guess there's a first
time for everything.
-What about me?
-I'll help!
[giggling]
-Nincompoops.
-So what happened to
Cherubimon then?
-Well, I suppose you guys
really did defeat him.
-No.
ALL: Hmm?
-I know him.
There's no way he could be
defeated that easily.
-Even so, we destroyed his
hideout and I bet we did a lot
of damage to him.
He's probably off somewhere
licking his wounds.
-Thanks to Takuya and Koji.
-Not just us, it was
you guys too.
-Yeah, you helped us a lot.
Not only did you give us your
spirits, you were there
cheering us on only now
we have a problem.
ALL: Huh?
-Hey, relax guys.
I just meant that we have
to get you your
spirits back somehow.
Huh?
Aww.
Whoa.
-Hey, I got my spirits back!
-Well, I guess the spirits heard
me talking and just came
back on their own.
-Welcome back, Kazemon.
-Gee whizz.
I never thought I'd be so happy
to see something that I
can't even eat.
[laughter]
[groaning]
-Ahh, fresh meat.
-So what are we supposed
to do now?
-Make a new plan, I guess.
-Well, stop guessing
and start thinking.
-Looks to me like you
have something
on your mind, Koichi.
You want to share it?
-Uh.
-Aw, come on.
Don't be shy.
I mean, after all we're all
friends here, right?
-Mm.
-Uhm, Koichi.
-Hmm.
-So, uh, listen.
-Yeah.
-Come on, Koichi.
You can trust us.
-Well, you see--
[screaming]
-What are you yelling
for, Patamon?
-Because he's coming!
-For dinner?
-Cherubimon's coming?
-Uh, beneath us.
[moaning]
[evil laughter]
-Icedevimon, one of the nastiest
Digimon around, don't
expect any mercy from this
cold hearted creature.
-Cherubimon sent you to
finish us off, huh?
-Cherubimon?
Ha!
I wouldn't compare me to that
weakling if I were you.
-If you're not with him, what
do you want with us?
-Oh, just death and
destruction.
You don't want to know
what it says in here.
-How will I know that
until I know?
-You make my brain hurt!
Just trust me!
He's bad business.
Uh, the baddest business.
ALL: What?
-Well, if you must know, he went
on a rampage across the
digital world destroying Digimon
and eating whatever
data he could get
his hands on.
Eventually, he was captured and
since he was too powerful
for even Cherubimon to destroy,
he was sentenced to
imprisonment without end.
Are you happy now, Mr.
and Mrs. Pushy Pants?
-Ha!
-But wait a minute.
Imprisonment without end?
Sure looks like it
ended to me.
-So does the book say where
he's supposed to be
imprisoned?
-It doesn't, but I have
a sinking suspicion
that we found it.
-Well, let's unfind it.
Oh.
-So tell me, you are
humans are you not?
-Yeah, what's it to you?
-Hold your tongue
little creature.
I simply wish to express my
gratitude to those who freed
me from that tiresome prison.
-Oh.
Well, you're welcome.
[grunting]
-Ooh.
-You know, it's funny.
I didn't know humans could
evolve into Digimon.
Uh, do you have tasty data
like those others?
Yummy.
-Watch it, bub!
[grunts]
-The data of the Digimon
Cherubimon
captured was so sweet!
[screaming]
-Are you telling us that you
destroyed all those Digimon?
-You betcha, but I wonder if
your data will be sweeter.
Ahh.
-You'll never find out so long
as we have a say in it!
-And we do!
-First, I must give you all a
little gift for freeing me.
[gasps]
-My detector!
This is a thank you?
-You're powerful so I'll save
you for later that way we can
have a good fight after these
distractions are eliminated.
And let me tell you, it will be
so joyous all the pain and
the suffering, don't
you agree?
-Okay, we crossed over
into Weirdville.
-And to have the chance to taste
human data for the first
time, this will be the
most wonderfully
excruciating day ever!
Thank you so very much
for this gift!
-Listen, chump.
The pain's going to
be all yours!
-I'll second that!
-Count me in!
-Me too.
I'm not going to let you
hurt my friends!
[music playing]
ALL: Execute spirit evolution!
[screaming]
-Beetlemon!
-Kazemon!
[moaning]
-Kumamon!
[fighting]
-Thunder fist!
Ahh!
Whoa!
-Frozen flames!
-Ha!
Ha!
-Frozen tundra!
-Whoa!
Ha!
Ahh!
-Tommy!
[screaming]
-Your look of fear makes
you so much prettier.
-Icedevimon, let them
go or else!
-That's a good idea,
not bright.
[moaning]
-That's a good first step!
Now get lost creep!
-But I can't leave without
having fun with you first.
You're such unusual prey.
Now what can I do to
prolong my joy?
Aw, of course!
Trust me, you're going
to love this!
[music playing]
[moaning]
-I can't move my legs!
-Isn't it wonderful?
-Huh?
I can get you one at a time
and there is absolutely
nothing you can do about it.
Best idea I've had in years
-Crystal freeze!
-Huh?
-Shadow Lance!
Grrr!
-Very well.
If that's the way you want it.
Let us begin your beautiful
destruction.
-Come down and fight!
-I got a better idea.
You come to me if you can.
-Right.
-BOTH: Slide evolution!
-Korikakumon!
We must stop him now!
-Ha!
Ha!
-Avalanche axis!
-Ebony blast!
Grr!
-This is no fun at all.
Your attacks, they bore me.
Hmm.
Ah-ha.
-Work!
-Howdy!
[grunting]
-Put them down you
evil scalawag!
-First, some fun!
Ha!
-Grr!
-How delicious!
I just knew you were the kind
who wouldn't attack if your
friends were in danger, but
there are things I don't yet
know about you humans, such
interesting and fragile
creatures, so I propose
a little game.
[grunting]
-Let's see how much freezing
these two can stand and how
much you're willing to
let them freeze!
-Fight, you coward!
-Coward?
A coward runs from pain,
but I embrace it.
[grunting]
-So, you still want me to
fight your friends?
-You let us out of here and
we'll give you a real fight!
-Yeah, come on!
-Oh!
Oh!
You already have a fight
on your hands.
[grunting]
-Koji, no!
[moaning]
-Koji.
[grunting]
-Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Such a lovely sound.
Well, that's what you
get for trying to
protect your friends.
-Ebony blast!
-Hmm.
[growling]
-How about some pain for you?
-Ooh, delightful!
[grunting]
-Ha!
Ha, ha!
[fighting]
-Let's fight!
-No, wait.
We're just going to
be in the way.
We have to run.
-Oh, all right.
[grunting]
-It's up to you now, Kiochi!
-Are you ready?
I wouldn't want you to be the
slightest bit unprepared for
the fight that is to
come because--
it's your last!
[fighting]
-Why won't this stupid detector
unfreeze already?
-Kiochi, no!
[evil laughter]
-JagerLoweemon!
-I'm fine.
Just free the others.
-But--
-No!
Grr!
-Okay.
[evil laughter]
[fighting]
-Now for some fun of our own!
ALL: Slide evolution!
-MetalKabuterimon!
-Zephyrmon!
-You know, it's always better
to destroy many than just a
few.
-How about just one--
you!
It's time to show you the
strength that comes from true
friendship!
[fighting]
[evil laughter]
-Do you really think
cold would stop me?
[siren sounding]
-Ahh!
No way!
-Think this might stop you?
Electro cannon!
[fighting]
-It's not possible!
I'm cracking!
-You don't like it?
-Dark Master!
[growling]
[fighting]
-Slide evolution!
Glowimon, Icedevimon, your evil
data has long been in
need of this purification.
Fractal cod, digitize!
[screaming]
[grunting and panting]
-Huh?
-Well Kiochi, I gotta say,
after that fight, you are
definitely one of us!
-Yeah, welcome to the party!
-All right!
It thawed out!
-Because Icedevimon was
defeated, everything's going
back to normal.
-My pants are soggy!
-So's your head.
[grunting]
-Huh?
[sighs]
-What is that?
[evil laughter]
-I'll give you three guesses.
-I just need one!
It's not over yet, guys!
-But it soon will be for you.
NARRATOR: No way.
It's never over for
these guys!
Find out if they could come
out on top on the next
"Digimon Digital Monsters!"