BOKOMON NARRATING: Once again,
Lucemon unleashed another of
his palookas to pill for more
piles of Digiworld data, but
this time he set his sights on
the village of flame, hometown
to myself and Neemon, not
too much of a whole
bunch of other Digimon.
As the battle began, the baddy
brought in an identical
brother, and soon our heroes
were face to face with a trio
of terrible-ness.
Koji and Takuya summoned the
power of the 10 legendary
warriors and blew away
the bony brutes.
Unfortunately, the celebration
was cut short when Crusadermon
checked in and took out what
was left of the town.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
What a beautiful sight.
DYNASMON (OFFSCREEN): Especially
when scared.
[laughter]
-Lord Lucemon should be most
pleased with our progress.
His rebirth is close at hand.
-Then we'll finally be done with
those revolting children.
I can't wait to claim
their data.
-Soon.
They cannot stand against
our might.
Nothing can.
-Look at that wonderful
nothing.
-Another gift for our
lord and master.
Transmission!
-Only four areas remain.
Come, let's finish this.
-With pleasure.
-Is that all you got?
I'm not letting you
go any further.
You might as turn around now,
'cause you'll never get your
hands on the sacred jewels!
You hear?
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
Knightmon are always ready,
willing, and able to fight.
They won't hesitate to use their
Electric Slash attack.
-Electric Slash!
BEETLEMON (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
that doesn't look fair.
Lightning Blitz!
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Gotsumon!
-Huh?
It's Koji!
A hero!
I can't believe it.
Is it really you?
-It's not time for talking.
-Yeah.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Lobomon!
-Loweemon!
-Kumamon!
-Lobo Kendo!
-Wildfire Tsunami!
-Nighty night!
-Crystal Breeze!
-Shadow Lance!
-Great work, guys.
We'll protect this place,
no problem.
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Spiral Masquerade!
Beautiful, isn't it?
-The jewels!
DYNASMON (OFFSCREEN): Thanks
for reminding me.
-There are still Digimon
in there.
[screaming]
-More data for Lord Lucemon.
-But they--
those were your own men.
Don't you even care about
their destruction?
-Foolish boy.
They were simply expendable
pawns.
Nothing matters but us,
Lord Lucemon, and
his new world order.
Your useless compassion
for the weak is what's
ruining this land.
The weak taint this whole world,
tarnishing the beauty
of Digimon like myself.
DYNASMON (OFFSCREEN):
With this data
scanned, only three remain.
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN): What
do you mean, three?
-There are only three
areas left to scan.
The forests, the ice,
and the light.
The rest is already
Lord Lucemon's.
-And when the last of the data
is his, he shall awaken, and a
pure world will be born.
-No way, 'cause we're
gonna stop you.
-Hah!
Your paltry powers are
nothing again us.
-Maybe you'll fare better at
the Forest Kingdom, but I
seriously doubt it.
[laughter]
-They're gone.
GOTSUMON (OFFSCREEN):
It's all gone.
Everything.
-Gotsumon!
-You OK?
-I sure hope so.
We have to save someone.
-Huh?
-You OK, Gotsumon?
-I can't believe it.
It's all gone.
-Easy.
-Don't try to do too much.
-What do you mean?
I haven't done anything.
My whole world is gone,
and I did nothing.
-I'm sorry we couldn't
stop them.
-That's not your fault.
It's those Royal Knights.
They did it.
If it weren't for you guys, I
wouldn't be able to feel sad,
'cause I wouldn't
even be here.
Thank you, guys, for
saving my life.
But you'd better get
going now, right?
They said there were only three
worlds left to destroy.
Well, you'd better get going.
You're going to stop
them, aren't you?
-Yeah, if we can.
Now is when I usually say, of
course we'll beat them.
But look at that.
-But we have to try.
-Yeah, and I know you
too well, Takuya.
You wouldn't be able to look at
yourself in the mirror if
you didn't give it your all.
-And we'll be there
to back you up.
-Mm-hm.
-Right.
We can do it.
GOTSUMON (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
We can.
I'm going with you guys,
and you can't stop me.
-But it's really dangerous.
-Yeah, it's going to be way
worse than fighting that whole
army of Knightmon, even.
-I don't care.
What reason do I have to stay?
Let me fight with you.
-(THINKING) How would we feel
if our world was gone?
He's coming.
-You serious?
-You really think he'd
just stay behind?
And who are we to tell him no?
-Mm-hm.
-I understand just
how he feels.
I also know the pain
of having my home
destroyed, if you remember.
-Well, looks like we've got
ourselves a new teammate.
Time to hit the rails.
-Hey, you guys.
I just had a thought.
The Forest Kingdom is where
Seraphimon's castle was,
right?
-I know just what
you're thinking.
That's probably where the
Fractal Code is that we have
to protect.
-Then we'd better hurry.
KNIGHTMON (OFFSCREEN):
Electric Slash!
-Will nothing break
these doors?
Again!
-Electric Slash!
-If you want something
done, do it yourself.
-No.
-What?
-I just had the most
beautiful thought.
The door is well guarded, but
perhaps there's another way we
can get in that isn't
so well protected.
Perhaps above.
-Yes.
-You Knightmon wait here.
I'm sure those brats are bound
to show up and try to ruin
everything.
Come.
-Awesome.
Now we only have to deal
with the Knightmon.
-What's that?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
I don't know.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Of
course not, but I do.
It's a protective barrier
someone left.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): But who?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
I don't know.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Of course not.
-Oh, you're so funny,
I forgot to laugh.
-Sorry.
All right, let's do this
together, guys.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): No.
-Huh?
Why the heck not?
-Because I'm going to take care
of them all by myself.
-W--why?
-You guys are going to have
to go keep an eye
on the Royal Knights.
They can't get their hands on
that data, no matter what.
-But Koji--
-The data is all that
matters now if we're
going to save the world.
We don't have time to
argue about this.
-That's all well and good, but
how do you expect to beat all
those Knightmon by yourself?
-He won't be alone.
-Huh?
-I'll be right by his side.
-OK, fine.
Next time, buddy, can
you just tell us
without all the dramatics?
-Yeah.
Are you ready, Gotsumon?
-Let's go.
-Unity Execute!
Unified Spirit Evolution!
MagnaGarurumon!
-Wow.
And I thought he was
tough before.
-All right, gang.
Let's go.
-Yeah!
-You ready, Gotsumon?
-Yeah.
At least I hope I am.
-Very well, we are here.
What is your plan, exactly?
-Patience, please.
This type of barrier tends to be
weakest at the top, at the
juncture of its walls.
Perhaps if we hammer away
at that point, the
barrier will collapse.
-Hammer away how?
-Observe.
First of Athena!
-Dragon Thrower!
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
It's working.
Beautiful.
-Soon, the data will be ours.
[laughter]
-There they are.
We have to protect the data.
-Quick, Takuya.
You should evolve into
EmperorGreymon.
-You're right.
What's that?
-Oh, my.
-What's with the D-Tector?
-I don't know, but
it's pretty.
-Someone's calling us.
I don't know how, but it feels
like a message from a friend.
-A way in.
-I knew it.
-Wait up!
-Yeah!
-Hey, what about the
Royal Knights?
Koji said we were supposed
to keep an eye on them.
-Listen, you nincompoop.
If we get inside and get the
data before they do, then we
won't have to keep an eye
on them, will we?
-Last one in's a rotten
Digi-Egg!
-I'm always the egg.
-No fair!
MAGNAGARURUMON (OFFSCREEN):
Feral Fire!
-Rock Fist!
Rock First!
-Ha ha!
You want some more?
Magna Missiles!
-Jeez, you think you got 'em?
That was easier than
I thought.
-Huh?
Uh-oh.
-You and your big mouth.
-Wow.
-Oh, I run all the time.
-No, I mean, this place
looks familiar.
-Well, this used to be your home
when you were Seraphimon.
-Which direction?
-Well, uh--
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Which way?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Come on, buddy.
A little help?
Right!
-Dragon Thrower!
-Rock Fist, Rock Fist,
Rock Fist!
GOTSUMON (OFFSCREEN): How
can we beat them?
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN);
You can't.
-Huh?
GOTSUMON (OFFSCREEN):
Crusadermon!
-Especially not after I
get through with you.
And I can't wait to be
through with you.
But at least your trip into
oblivion will be eased by the
final vision of my beauty.
-Fine.
Let's fight.
Ready, Gotsumon?
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, goodie.
Two for the price of one.
-(THINKING) Ready?
Ready for what?
What am I gonna do
against her?
-How cute.
-Well, nothing can
stop us now.
-It's Cherubimon!
-It's the data.
-I don't know, Takuya.
Are you sure about that?
-Positive.
-Here, you see what I mean?
-So all we have to do
is protect this.
-Yeah, and I'm sure it'll
be real easy, too.
[shouting]
-It begins to break!
Ha ha!
One powerful shot should pierce
it, and one powerful
shot it shall have!
Breath of Wyvern!
Ha ha ha!
The castle can't hide the data
if the castle is gone.
And it and those children
are surely gone.
-Am I alive?
-I don't know.
It seems like I don't
know anything today.
-We should be used to being
in the dark by now.
-Yeah, but now we're
in the light.
And we're not alone.
It's Sorcermon!
-Get back.
Quick, this way.
Take care of Seraphimon.
He's our last hope.
With the last of my strength, I
have protected this castle.
But now I must leave
the rest up to you.
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Sorcermon.
-That's twice he's saved us.
We'd be gone if it
wasn't for him.
-You talk about devoted.
I mean, he was fighting evil
even after he died.
-(THINKING) I wonder if
I could be that brave?
Well, since he saved us twice
then we owe it to him to fight
twice as hard to save this world
from those evil guys.
-Why don't you start your little
fight with me, then?
What?
No pithy comeback?
-Oh, I'll give you a comeback.
-Do it.
-Let's go.
-Unity Execute!
Unified Spirit Evolution!
EmperorGreymon!
-You do not stand a chance
against me, pathetic human!
Oh, I knew this would be fun!
-This is horrible.
All I can do is watch.
He needs me!
-Fist of Athena!
-If only I were stronger,
I could help him!
-Huh?
-Meteormon!
I digivolved?
-Good timing.
-All I wanted to do was help you
fight her, and now I can.
-Uh-huh.
-Very well.
If you have help, then I
shall have help, too.
Knightmon?
-Are you ready?
-Yeah.
-Is that the best you can do?
-Not even close!
I'm just getting warmed
up, buddy!
-Galactic Blast!
-What have you done to my
beautiful Knightmon?
-Same thing we're
gonna do to you!
-You catch on quick.
But you haven't seen
anything yet!
Dragonfire Crossbow!
-Dragon Thrower!
[laughter]
-What's so funny?
You missed.
DYNASMON (OFFSCREEN): Did I?
-No!
-Fools.
Did you really think
you could win?
-Oh, no!
-They scanned the castle.
-Right you are, pebble brain.
How beautiful.
-We win again.
-Not yet, you haven't.
If you're still here,
we can stop you!
-Are you sure?
[screaming]
MAGNAGARURUMON (OFFSCREEN):
Gotsumon!
-It's a simple choice, really.
-Will you fight us or
save your friends?
-Such predictable cowards.
Come, only two areas remain.
-And then the glory of Lord
Lucemon shall be unveiled!
-What's the holdup?
Get on already.
Holy [german], get on, kiddies.
Let's go.
GOTSUMON (OFFSCREEN): Well,
I guess this is goodbye.
-Are you sure?
-Mm-hm.
Of course I am.
I don't want to be in
your way anymore.
I mean, look at me.
What good would I be to
you in this condition?
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): You were
never in the way.
-I'll be counting
on you, Koji.
We all will.
Without you guys, we wouldn't
have any hope.
BOKOMON (NARRATING):
Gotsumon's right.
I only hope this time to save
the two areas that are left.
See if they can do
it on the next
Digimon, Digital Monsters.