BOKOMON NARRATING: Visiting the
Village of Beginnings, our
heroes' expectations were
egg-ceeded by the
overabundance of babies.
The Trailmon normally hauled the
hatchlings home, but with
all the scanning going
on, they were afraid
to come out of hiding.
So the gang lent Swanmon
an hand with the
babies and the Trailmon.
Meanwhile, the Royal Knights
arrived to scan the village.
The kids were fighting a losing
battle when the data of
the four evil warriors was
activated, allowing a reunion
of the Big Ten.
Zoe convinced the Trailmon to
take the tots just in time.
But not before the
nasty Knights
made the village vanish.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
We look to the past as we head
for the future to reclaim the
Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a Spirit Evolution.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon.
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon.
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
Ha-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
BOKOMON NARRATING: Just as it
was foretold, the power of the
Ten Legendary Warriors
is alive.
Alive!
-That's wonderful in theory.
But it still didn't help
us save the Village of
Beginnings.
-Yeah, those royal windbags
swiped all the data, anyway.
I don't see where
the win is here.
-Yeah, take a look around.
-I don't know about you
guys, but I don't
feel powerful at all.
-What are you talking about?
Do you understand the
significance of the Ten
Legendary Warriors
being reunited?
No one said this was
going to be easy.
I have every confidence you'll
save the Digital World just
like in the old legend.
-How are we supposed
to do that?
-As long as we're willing to
stay together and continue to
believe, destiny will
show us the way.
-I wish destiny would show me
the way to a good hamburger.
-Now that's something
I could believe in.
-Argh!
-Ooh!
-Sometimes the echo from your
empty head is deafening.
-I want to believe, but is
my spirit strong enough?
-Well, I'm still
willing to try.
-We'll need some help.
I can still feel them, even
though I can't see them.
The other four warrior
spirits!
They stood by us before, and
they'll do it again.
If they can fight
then so can I.
-There's a point I
can't argue with.
[gasps]
[chittering]
-Oh, dear!
What are they going on about?
Enough of that!
Tell us what's wrong.
-It's the Village of Flames.
-That's my home!
Oh, dear.
Please don't tell me it's
been destroyed.
POYOMON (OFFSCREEN): No,
but it's about to be.
-What do mean?
-A scary Digimon attacked us.
-He's big and mean.
(IN UNISON) He won't stop
until it's all gone.
Please hurry, before
it's too late.
-Ugh!
-Don't worry, Papa-Mom.
I'm sure there's something
we can do.
-We have to protect
that village.
-Yeah, that forest is where
I first became a Digimon.
-Then we'd better get going.
-I'm up for sending that
Digi-thug packing.
-Well I'm ready when you are.
-One little problem.
We need a Trailmon.
-Hello, Liebchens.
[everyone exclaims]
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN): Hurry,
my Royal Knights.
I grow tired of this prison.
Hurry and set me free.
-Yes, My Lord, it won't
be long now.
-Even as we speak, your servants
are collecting some
beautiful data.
Help them!
-Yes, Master.
CRUSADERMON (OFFSCREEN):
Fools!
My patience wears thin.
But soon, I shall be
free once again!
-Mein Liebchen is making
mein tunnel.
Why do I always have to
be such a softie?
-What do we do if the Village of
Flames is gone when we get
there?
-Oh, let's not think
about that.
-I'm scared.
-We'll don't be.
We have to stay positive and
keep our heads clear.
I realize it's something you've
never done before, but
please, at least try.
Besides, I know it's
still there.
-How do you know?
-Because I can sense
these things.
Now please, stop asking
questions!
-You don't have to mean.
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN): There's
no place like home.
There's no place like home!
[chittering]
[grunting]
[scurrying]
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
We just need to have a
little conversation.
Any volunteers?
Hello?
I guess you'll do.
[laughter]
SkullSatamon, a frightening
fallen angel Digimon whose
lust for power and destruction
is only exceeded by his
loyalty to Lucemon.
He's an unnatural disaster, with
his deadly Bone Blaster.
-Where can I find the
data of this forest?
-I'm sorry, I don't know.
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN): You
lying little cabbage!
-Poison ivy!
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, not the face!
Bone Blaster!
[grunts]
-And you!
Surely a fine hare like yourself
must know where the
data for this forest
is hidden.
-No, please stop.
Don't make me tell you that!
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
You do know!
-Did I say that?
-Don't tell him!
-Maybe it's time for
rabbit stew.
-Ugh!
Please don't hurt me.
I'll cooperate, honest.
-I'm in a generous mood.
But this is your last chance.
Now tell me where the data is.
-It's in a cave below us.
I'll show you.
-Really?
And where might we find the
entrance to this mystery cave?
-He spilled the beans!
-Where is it?
Tell me.
-It's right there.
Right over there.
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Aha, ha!
Silly rabbit, I've got a
nice reward for you.
RABBIT (OFFSCREEN): Uh-oh!
TRAILMON (OFFSCREEN): I'm
so glad that's over.
I'll go hide now.
Auf Wiedersehen!
-(IN UNISON) Thanks,
very much!
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Thank you!
Ta-ta, ta-ta.
-It feels so good to
be home again!
And ever better that there's
a home to be at.
-Thank goodness the Village
of Flames has been spared!
Ha, ha!
-It's great, Papa-Mom.
I can't believe I'm
in your hometown.
It's so big, and huge, and--
and flamey, too!
Would you show us around?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
I'd be delighted.
Ah, doesn't it smell
wonderful?
-Wasn't me.
Hey, it looks like
the forest is OK.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Ah!
The green, green forest
of my youth lives on.
The majestic trees swaying
in the breeze.
The little birdies twittering.
I remember how the tiny forest
creatures would come out and
mercilessly nibble at my toes.
Ah, memories.
-It's still beautiful.
-Uh, yeah, what's left
of it, anyway.
-Well let's make sure
it stays that way!
[croaking]
-This was too easy!
Lord Lucemon will be pleased!
Oh how I love my job!
Bone Blaster!
[laughing]
-Somebody's scanning
the forest!
-Agh!
My home!
Leave it alone!
It's vanishing.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): And
disappearing too!
[laughter]
-[laughter]
Delicious!
My master will be proud!
-I haven't seen him before.
Who is that bonehead?
-According to my book,
it's a SkullSatamon.
-Did he nibble on
your toes, too?
-Here it comes, My Lord!
Yaughh!
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[crying]
-It's gone!
He destroyed the forest.
-Stop the crying and
start moving!
-Huh?
-He's not going to stop until
the whole place is gone!
You'd better get out
while you can.
-(IN UNISON) Get out
while you can!
-That scary Digimon has
a big appetite.
And if you don't hurry, you're
going to be his next meal.
-(IN UNISON) Yeah, you're going
to be his next meal.
Next!
-So do you guys have a plan?
-I plan to run!
-That's not the answer
I was hoping for.
-(IN UNISON) Crummy answer.
-The only reason we stayed
behind is because we thought
you guys could actually
do something,
but I guess we wrong!
You're just a bunch
of cowards.
-Before we give up, we should
let the humans speak.
After all, they did come
here to help us.
-(IN UNISON) No way!
Don't even bother!
-I'm not sure there's anything
they can do, Pagumon.
-Yeah, they don't
mean to mean.
Lucemon's coming soon, anyway.
It's only a matter of time.
-Hm!
We all had high hopes for you
guys when you got the spirits
of the legendary warriors.
But I guess you just couldn't
handle it, could you?
-Oh yeah!
-(IN UNISON) Yeah, he's right!
-(IN UNISON) What's
up with that?
-If we hadn't trusting you
clowns, we would have had half
a chance to save ourselves.
-You're wrong about one thing.
One of the reasons I
stayed behind is
because this is my home.
I've always lived here.
I'm going to spend my last
hours here, too!
-Going down with the ship.
-Hm?
-Very noble, Captain!
But I had another plan.
Like maybe these guys might
actually come to through.
I have a hard time believing in
anything, but this time I
trusted Bokomon.
He convinced all of us that
nothing could beat the
Legendary Warriors.
But it was too good
to be true.
It is only a legend.
-Maybe you should have
run, but running away
never solved anything!
-We did come back here
to help, you know.
If you want to give up, that's
your choice, but
it's not over yet.
We're all still willing to
fight, but we need your help.
-Please, we can do
this together.
-Huh?
-Take it from me, you'd be
surprised at how much power we
can have with a little
bit of team work.
-That's true.
He's the lazy one
of the bunch.
If he can fight, I'm
willing to try.
-(IN UNISON) Really?
-Besides, wouldn't it make you
feel good to know that you did
everything you could to
defend your home?
-I'm sorry that you feel like
we failed you, but with your
help we still have a chance to
change the history of the
Digital World.
-At this point, what
do we have to lose?
Personally, I want to make it
difficult as possible for
those data-sucking scum!
-Yeah!
For what it's worth, I'm willing
to unleash the power
of the pants!
-You really think us little guys
can make a difference?
-Definitely, as long
as you believe.
-Anything is possible.
-Whatever you decide to
do, it's OK with me.
I just want you all to know that
I'll do everything I can
to save your home.
I won't give up, I promise!
The spirit of the Ten Legendary
Warriors lives
inside each and every
one of us.
If Lucemon's goons try to take
this place, they're in for a
fight like they've never seen!
-(IN UNISON) Yeah!
Woo hoo!
[laughter]
-Ah, so brave.
They're forming a
team, are they?
Then I will too!
Time to wake up my brother!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
[laughter]
-I'm so hungry when
I first wake up.
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN):
There's plenty of delicious
data there.
[laughter]
-All right everybody,
this is it.
I'm sensing two big Digimon
approaching from the south.
-Argh!
Run!
[screams]
-Well, buddy, it looks like
you and me again!
-I'm ready anytime you are.
-Wow, they are scary!
-Uh-huh!
-Ice into flame!
-Thunder into light!
-Wind into flame!
-Darkness into light!
[electronic chirping]
-Unity execute!
Unified spirit evolution!
Agh!
[grunts]
-Enter Flamon!
[electronic chirping]
-Unity execute!
Unified spirit evolution!
Agh!
[grunts]
-MagnaGarurumon!
-(IN UNISON) Hey, hey!
-They look powerful to me.
-Well, they are!
They have the power of
all 10 Warriors.
And if you believe strongly
enough, they can use your
power, too.
-Hm!
-Huh!
[laughter]
-Nice shot, brother!
-Agh!
Run again!
[screams]
[laughter]
-Hey, Bonehead!
-Huh? what have we here?
-Well, well, well.
You must be the weaklings
Crusadermon told us about.
LILITHMON (OFFSCREEN):
So you want to fight?
Ha, ha, ha!
I love the smell of competition
in the morning.
Maybe we'll start with
a round of gulf.
Hiya!
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN): Ooh,
Nice swing, brother.
Good form!
LILITHMON (OFFSCREEN): Sorry
about the divot!
[laughter]
LILITHMON (OFFSCREEN): I see,
golf isn't your game, huh?
What's the matter?
Am I so intimidating you
can't even speak?
You're even bigger cowards
than I thought!
SKULLSATAMON (OFFSCREEN): Well,
we might as well destroy
them then, or Lucemon
will bring them back
as new Digimon anyway.
[growling]
-And you believe that?
-Of course.
Lord Lucemon would never lie.
-Really?
What did he promise you?
-Huh?
-You're nothing but a slave
to him, and that's
all you'll ever be.
That I could promise you!
[growling]
-Yeah.
I bet combined there isn't one
original thought in those
pathetic skulls of yours.
Boo!
-How dare you speak
to us like that!
[grunts]
-They're doing just what
they promised.
They're fighting to
protect our home.
-(IN UNISON) Protect our home.
Ah!
-Get back here, bony!
[laughter]
-Stop!
I'm giving you one chance to
leave this village and go back
to wherever it is
you came from.
-But the party's
just starting!
Mm!
-If that's the way you want it,
I'm going to give you the
first dance.
Dragonfire Crossbow!
-Argh!
-Feral Fire!
Hiya!
-Argh!
-(IN UNISON) Yay!
Yay!
-What do we have to do
to get through those
thick skulls of yours?
We're not going to let you
take this village.
Ugh!
Time to go back to
whatever rock you
crawled out from under.
Move it!
-Oh, we'll go.
But not until we finish
our mission.
You see, we still have
a village to scan.
-Good morning!
Catch, brother.
-What?
-Apparently, you two have been
giving my brothers a bad time.
But now that we're
all together, you
don't stand a chance.
-Ugh!
Ooh!
-I'm seeing triple.
[screams]
-We've wasted enough time.
Bone Blaster!
[laughter]
-[inaudible]
[grunts]
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Oh, my!
This isn't going very
well, is it?
[laughter]
-Hiya!
-Agh!
-Ugh, agh!
-I'm fresh out of patience,
so I'll only ask you once.
Now tell me where to find the
flame terminal's data!
-No, please!
-Don't tell him, Biyomon!
-It's time to say,
bye bye, birdie.
-It's over there.
[sighs]
-That's more like it, now.
Is this the one?
-Yes.
Please let me go!
-Thanks for your help.
As a reward, you get to
go back to your egg.
Hiya!
-I can't believe it.
Biyomon told him, and that bony
bum zapped him anyway.
-Are we going to let them
destroy our home?
We all have to rise
up and fight!
-(IN UNISON) We must rise
up and fight, and
start to show our might.
We must put an end to this
terrible blight!
-Everyone attack!
Go!
-Bone Blaster!
Agh!
[inaudible].
[laughter]
-Ooh!
-Huh, missed me, numbskull,
try again.
-We're wasting time!
Find the data.
-Yaughh!
[laughter]
-Ooh!
Ugh!
-I can't let them scan
the terminal data!
-There it is!
And it's all mine!
Lord Lucemon will be free!
-(IN UNISON) No!
Cyber Twister!
Hiya!
-Ugh!
[growling]
-(IN UNISON) Super
Thunder Strike.
-Argh!
[growling]
-(IN UNISON) Ah phew!
-Yuck! putrid punks.
Ugh!
I don't have time
for you brats.
-Run away, run away!
-Ugh!
I was going to scan you
last but there's
been a change of plans.
-Yo, ugly!
-Huh?
-Pick on someone
your own size!
-Argh!
[cheering]
-Ugh, ow.
Ugh!
-Let's show him--
- --some brotherly--
- --love.
-Ughh!
-Leave him alone!
-(IN UNISON) Come on, Flamon,
he's our man, if he can't do
it, no one can!
-Thanks guys!
Let's go!
Hiya!
-Ugh.
-Hiya!
-What are you doing?
No!
Ugh!
-Huh!
Don't ever underestimate
the power of teamwork!
Now, time to clean
up this boneyard.
Hiya!
Pyro Dragons!
[screams]
-Well, do you guys believe
in the power now?
-I believe!
-Well, I never had any doubts.
-Yay!
[cheering]
[gasp]
-It was lovely how you all came
together like that to
save your humble hamlet.
Yet the loss of the SkullSatamon
Brothers was
tragic, they're loyalty was
like a beautiful flower.
-What's that pathetic pink
psychopath up to now?
-Some day Lord Lucemon
will give new life to
this sad, sad scene.
[screaming]
[gasps]
-Goodbye, fair hamlet.
Now off you go to
Lord Lucemon.
Have a beautiful journey.
-(IN UNISON) Ooh!
-Master, your exquisite
re-awakening will
soon come to pass.
Ta-ta!
[laughter]
-Ugh!
I'm really starting to
hate that laugh.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): I can't
believe it's gone!
Our home is gone.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Yes.
-These guys are going to need
a safe place to hide.
Should we take them to
the human world?
-I don't know.
-Tukuya was right.
-Huh?
-Running is never the answer.
We have to stay here
and fight.
-Yeah.
Our home may be gone, but they
can't take away our memories.
Besides, we can always find
another place to live for a
little while.
-At least we did everything
we could.
Hey, after that battle, I'm
feeling a new sense of hope.
-Maybe these guys aren't
impossible to beat, after all.
-(IN UNISON) When we fight
together as one, we can all
help get the job done!
-Mm, hm!
-We're all in this
together now.
Those mean old meanies can do
whatever they want, but
they'll never destroy
the spirits of the
Ten Legendary Warriors.
As long as we have courage and
still believe, the spirits
will live on inside all of us!
-Not much longer!
Not much longer!
BOKOMON NARRATING: Well,
I believe that
we're in big trouble.
Sure hope there's something left
to fight for on the next
Digimon Digital Monsters.