NARRATOR (OFFSCREEN): After
Whamon dropped the gang off on
Terra Firma, they decided to
take a little vacation at
Toucanmon Paradise.
Too bad the bird boys were
rabid Ranamon fans.
The food and the free beach
gear were just a plot to
separate the boys from their
D-Tectors, so they could win
favor with the evil
warrior of water.
When Ranamon showed up,
Zoe was the only
able to spirit evolve.
Kazemon was holding her
own until Ranamon
found her beast spirit.
Calmaramon overpowered Kazemon
but couldn't control herself.
Good thing too.
Without their D-Tectors, the
boys are pretty useless.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
Look to the past as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards
one solution,
through a spirit evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
-Toucanmon!
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
Come out already!
Pretty please.
Ugh.
-Ah, who are we kidding?
We couldn't find them
if they came up and
bit us on the nose.
-Huh.
-Get it off!
Get it off!
-Where could they be?
-Toucanmon!
-They're not in my
pants, Dorkus.
You're going to big trouble
if the egg got cold.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): You know,
you really are a good mommy.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN):
Thanks, I--
oh, hush.
-How could we make
such a mistake?
-Us?
How could she turn into that?
Our sweet little Ranamon.
TOUCANMON 1 (OFFSCREEN): Sweet,
cute little Ranamon.
TOUCANMON 2 (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
[sigh]
TOUCANMON 2 (OFFSCREEN): We
nabbed those D-Tectors, and
how do we get paid back?
Hugs? Kisses?
Invites to slumber parties?
No.
She pays us back by turning
into that hideous thing.
[groans]
-So what should we
do with these?
TOUCANMON 2 (OFFSCREEN):
Let them rot.
Even if Ranamon would give us a
date for the them, who would
want to date that?
-She's probably out there
laughing at all of us.
-I hate these things.
-And I hate Ranamon.
-And I hate everything.
-I think my beak's broke.
-What were you doing?
-I had an idea.
-Not again.
-Ranamon has lots
of other fans.
We can sell these.
-Good Idea.
-Yeah.
Lets go.
-(AS A GROUP) Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
TOKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
It's no use.
We'll never find 'em.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): JP, how's
your, um, you know?
-I don't want to
talk about it.
-Let's just take a break
for a while.
-Ho.
-Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll bet you find your
D-Tector real soon.
-Huh.
What were you saying, Z?
-JP, weren't you thinking
about your D-Tector?
-Oh, uh, well, I was wondering
if you'd be like that.
-Huh?
Be like what?
-Like Calmaramon.
-Calmaramon!
Where?
-I was just wondering if you'd
be scary like that.
You know like when you
got your beast
spirit and all that.
-(GROUP) Huh.
[screaming]
-Stop that!
I can't believe you guys would
think something like that.
I'm nothing like her.
-Of course.
-Hey, say that like
you mean it.
-He's not saying you're evil or
anything, just that beast
spirits are hard to control.
-Yes, remember what happened
with Takuya?
-I'll always be a cool and
beautiful girl Digimon.
That I know.
-But how?
-Cause I'm a girl, and girls
know how to handle power when
they need to.
-Scary.
-Knock it off.
Having power does not
make you scary!
-Geez. You sure?
Hey, it's the Toucanmon.
-Where are they going?
-What's the matter?
-We're exhausted.
-You weaklings.
How can you be tired already?
We just took off for
Pete's sake.
Bunch of lame birdbrains.
-Don't be so quick to
point feathers.
You're breathing heavy too.
-I'm just copying you guys,
so you don't feel so bad.
I could keep this flapping
up all day.
But since you're tired,
we'll land.
Oh thank heavens.
I mean you guys are
lucky it's close.
Now stay close.
I don't want to have to go
looking all over the island
for you guys after we land.
Why am I still talking?
-Look.
They're landing over there.
-Right.
Don't let them get away.
We can swim over.
-I'll race you there.
-Tommy, you guys wait here.
-Takuya?
[giggling]
-What the heck is that?
-That's Gomamon.
-Well, whoever you are let
go of my foot, OK.
-Sorry, but we had
to stop you guys.
-Hi.
-Hi
-Yeah, hi.
What are these things anyway?
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): Gomamon are
cute and curious, but if
you get them mad, they won't
hesitate to attack.
Then again, what does
around here?
-How cute?
TOKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Yeah,
girls are tough.
CALMARAMON (OFFSCREEN): Well,
well, look at me.
I'm the belle of the
beast spirit ball.
There's nothing that can stand
in my beautiful way now.
Wait till Mercurymon
gets a load of--
oh my, all this beauty
sure is painful.
-Thou art a true powerhouse,
Calmaramon.
'Tis awe inspiring how
thou canst knock
thyself to the ground.
-Can it.
-Yes, thy beast spirit shall
simply go to waste if thou
cannot control it.
Tread carefully.
-Sorry, sugar.
I guess my beast spirit
has a mind of its own.
Look.
Don't get your drawers
all in a bunch.
I'm practicing with it.
Soon I'll be unbeatable.
MERCURYMON (OFFSCREEN): Thou
had better master it before
thou destroy us all.
GOMAMON (OFFSCREEN): We wouldn't
be very good friends
if we let you go out there.
The water looks so cuddly
and inviting, but
really it's very dangerous.
-Um, what do you mean by
dangerous exactly?
-Just look.
All that foam by the island is
caused by a whole bunch of
whirlpools.
TOKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Whirlpools?
GOMAMON (OFFSCREEN):
Don't worry.
We're safe here, but if you get
too close, they'll suck
you in and never spit you out.
And even if you could get past
them, you'd get slammed up
against the cliffs that surround
the only beach you
can land on.
We know all about it, because
we used to live there.
-So is there some kind
of secret way to
get there or something?
-No, I wish there were.
-You can't get home?
-That's right.
Everything used to be
so wonderful here.
Then one day, when we went out
to play and get some food,
there was a big earthquake.
That's when the whirlpools
started.
We were cut off from our island,
and we haven't been
able to get home since.
-I'd be willing to bet that the
earthquake happened when
the destruction of the
digital world began.
Oh, it seems there's no
one Cherubimon's evil
touch hasn't hurt.
-So you're saying there's no
way to get across, huh?
-Maybe we'll be able to find
some kind of flying digimon
who will take us over
to the island.
-Hey, good idea.
-Well, of course.
That should totally work.
-Thanks for your
help, you guys.
You really saved our necks.
-No problem.
-We better hurry before the
Toucanmon take off again.
-Aw.
-Zoe, what's up?
You OK?
[whining]
-Aw.
Why don't you all
come with us?
I mean, don't you want
to go back home.
-Oh, don't worry about us.
We'll be just fine.
-[sigh].
-If we swim close up to the
whirlpools, we can catch a
really good view of our friends
on the other side.
-You bet.
We get along just fine.
-Come on.
-(ALL TOGETHER) Huh!
-Are you trying to tell me
you're not even a little sad,
watching all your friends from
afar, not even being able to
talk to them?
Well, I don't buy it.
Everyone gets sad without
their friends.
-Ugh.
Yeah, we just try to ignore
that, because otherwise we get
all depressed.
-Listen, guys.
I think I have a quick
and simple
solution to your problem.
You're all going to
come with us.
-Although I appreciate the
sentiment, don't you think it
might be a tad dangerous?
-Come on, guys.
We have to try.
-We can't even help ourselves.
I mean we don't even have
our D-Tectors anymore.
What good are we?
-That's a great excuse if
you want to give up, but
I'm not going to.
Sure, it's tough, but I
believe that we can do
whatever we put our minds to.
Come on, you guys.
Let's get you back to
your friends, OK.
-After that speech, I don't
think we could say no to you
even if we wanted to.
-I hope it works.
If it doesn't, we'll
make it work.
-Zoe's right.
We can help each other out.
We'll make it together.
-Even without our D-Tectors,
I guess there's plenty
we can do as a team.
-You mean it?
Really?
-I can't swim well, and
I'm afraid of water,
but count me in.
-Hey, finding flying Digimon
is too much work anyway.
-It's decided then--
finally.
-Guys.
-Don't start crying, because
you know Tommy
will just start crying.
-Yeah, and I will
if he doesn't.
-Awesome.
Then let's get to
work, everybody.
-Heave away.
-There.
-(TOGETHER) Heave ho.
Heave ho.
-JP, what you're doing?
-To make a good boat, you
need a good plan.
-So what have you got?
Great, JP.
That should only take a
few years to build.
-Nah.
It's just like building a
model ship, only bigger.
-Yeah, right.
[maniacal laughter]
-Success at last.
I have mastered my
beast spirit.
-And only destroyed
half the lair.
-If I can do that to
rocks, think what I
can do to those kids.
-Thou makest a good point.
Now, thou hast best make
good with a broom.
-Hmm.
Slide evolution.
Be careful, or you'll find out
up close what I can do, sugar.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN):
That was hard.
JP (OFFSCREEN): You didn't
do anything.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN): Oh yeah.
-Here we go.
-Can we not rock the
boat so much?
-I can't believe you built
this without even
looking at my plans.
-This is great.
-Yeah, I'll say.
-But what about my plans?
-(GROUP) JP!
JP (OFFSCREEN): What?
-So much for fun.
-The Gomamon sure weren't
kidding, huh.
TOKUYA (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
-They said it was bad,
not horrible.
-There must be something at the
bottom of the sea that's
causing all this.
-Well, maybe we can find
it and fix it.
-(GROUP)Tidal wave!
[squealing]
-Hi there, kiddie pies.
-Oh, man!
-Great, now what do we do?
-Well, if y'all have any last
wishes, now would be the
perfect time to make them.
Don't you think?
-Don't do it, Zoe.
Don't you remember?
You were no match for
her last time.
-For Pete's sake.
Am I the only one here with
even a pinch of optimism?
-But Zoe.
-Don't "but Zoe" me.
Just figure out how to
stop the whirlpools,
while I hold her off.
Hope this works.
Execute spirit evolution.
Kazemon.
-My, you're quite a little
glutton for punishment, aren't
ya?
-Let's kickstart this fight.
Ha!
Hurricane wave.
-Honey, I could do this all day,
but I'll take pity on ya
and destroy you now.
Draining rain.
-Zoe, no!
-Zoe!
-No.
This can't happen.
I have to protect the others.
This is impossible.
I can breathe.
Huh.
I got hit so hard,
I'm seeing stars.
So beautiful.
It's my beast spirit.
-Zoe, come back!
-No, JP!
-Zoe!
-It can't be.
-What a bother.
And here I thought I'd
get a chance to test
out my beast spirit.
It's really not fair.
-You're toast, lady.
-Thanks.
But I already had
my breakfast.
Hey, maybe I could test out
my beast spirit on y'all.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
Takuya, look.
The whirlpool's going away.
-It's what?
Now, how in the world did
that happen, huh?
What is going on?
-Oh my.
Could it be?
-It could.
-It's Zoe.
-Yes, I'm back, and I brought
a little friend.
Execute beast spirit
evolution.
Zephyrmon.
-Who is that?
-That is Zephyrmon.
Behold, the legendary
warrior of wind.
-Oh my.
Why?
You're pretty.
Your beast spirit
made you pretty.
Well, of course, it's not like
you're prettier than me.
I mean that's not
even possible.
But just because you are
prettier than me
doesn't mean anything.
You got it.
Do you have adoring
fans all over the
world who worship you?
I don't think so.
-You know something for a
legendary warrior of water,
you sure give off a
lot of hot air.
-That does it.
You're going down, sugar.
Now, how should I defeat you?
Dark vapor.
You're in for it now, girlie.
That haze will melt anything.
Have your feathers started
molting yet?
Wait a minute.
How come you're not molting?
-I think it's time you learned
a little respect.
Plasma paws.
-All right.
-I'll say.
-She's controlling her spirit.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN):
She's amazing.
Isn't she, JP?
JP!
-Ahh. Boy howdy.
-Right. That's it.
No more pussyfooting around.
Ranamon.
Slide evolution.
Calmaramon.
Let the party begin.
-Zoe, get away.
-You won't be so pretty when
I get through with you,
sweetheart.
Acid ink.
That's what'll happen
to your friends.
Ready, boys?
Oh, what's the matter,
little girl?
Did I burn you all up?
I'm just too good.
-That witch.
-It's awful.
We can't do anything.
-Stop it.
Let her go, you scum queen.
-Yeah, you ugly fish head.
-What?
What did you say?
-You heard him.
If we call her names and
distract her, maybe Zephyrmon
can escape.
-OK.
Hey, you slimy dateless
wonder.
-You big coward.
[shouting]
-Can it.
Oh, you are so dead.
-Hurricane gale.
That's for picking
on my friends.
-And go tell your friends, there
will be more of that if
they mess with us.
-Now, you're going to get it.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): That's
the scariest thing yet.
-Be quiet.
You brats are in for a heaping
helping of pain.
Titanic tempest.
-Ooh.
I am going to enjoy this.
-I let you off easy this time.
JP (OFFSCREEN): What was that?
ZEPHYRMON (OFFSCREEN): I guess
someone can't control her
beast spirit yet.
Now, let's get everybody
back to that island.
[cheering]
-They're sure happy.
BOKOMON (OFFSCREEN): And it's
all thanks to you, Zoe.
If you didn't have the courage
to stand up to Ranamon, none
of this would be possible.
-Thanks.
-My pleasure.
-Hey, Zoe.
How were you able to control
your beast spirit so fast?
-Well, just luck, I guess.
-Not because you're a girl.
-Yeah, maybe.
But I won't tell.
A girl has to have secrets.
[kissing noise]
-You feel as sick as
I do right now?
-No, I'm sicker.
-Guys.
-Me too.
-Knock it off.
-We just wanted to
thank you all.
If it weren't for you, we would
never have seen our
friends again.
-You should be thanking Zoe.
-Yeah, she's the one
who did everything.
-Aww.
You guys helped me more
than you know.
-Uh.
Cut it out.
-Hey, we helped too.
Where's ours, huh?
-OK.
-Hey, did you guys see
the Toucanmon?
-They're gone.
-Huh.
-They all left for the
autumn leaf fair.
-The what?
-It's a trader's market on the
continent north of here.
-Then let's go.
-But how?
JP (OFFSCREEN): Why is
nothing ever easy?
NARRATOR (OFFSCREEN): And it's
a safe bet that it's just
going to get harder, guys.
To find out what's going on at
the fair tune in to the next
"Digimon Digital Monsters."