BOKOMON (NARRATING): After
Lucemon destroyed the last
moon, we were all left floating
on this ridiculous
rock, and vulnerable to every
passing magma attack.
Neemon tricked me into telling
Koichi's secret.
Luckily, everyone was distracted
when Lucemon opened
a window into the real world.
Our brave children Spirit
Evolved to stop him, but
Lucemon revealed that
he had the power to
combine light and darkness.
As has prepared to send our
dear friends to oblivion,
Koichi gave up his Spirits
of Darkness to Koji.
Lucemon scanned him, but then
Takuya and Koji united their
ancient spirits to become
Susanoomon.
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Look to the past as
we heard for the future to
reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve!
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon!
[shouting]
[screaming]
-Ancient Spirits unite!
Susanoomon!
[gasping]
-And just who are you?
-I am Susanoomon, inheritor
of the spirits of the 10
legendary warriors.
-Susanoomon?
Well, I bid you welcome.
Allow me to inform you that
all those who live in the
Digital World must follow me.
If you serve me, you
shall live forever.
If, however, you have your own
ideas, I cannot allow that.
To exist, obey.
-We know that you stand
for evil and tyranny.
You want to destroy
the Digital World.
-I only wish to bring order
to this world of chaos.
But that will never happen with
the Digital World in its
present state.
To begin it anew, I must
destroy it utterly.
-We won't let that happen.
-So, you think you can defy me
and live to get away with it?
Paradise Lost Punch!
-What furious fisticuffs!
It's deja vu again.
-Time to pay!
-Your Paradise Lost Punch won't
work on us anymore.
All right, guys!
-Susanoomon rocks!
-You will not survive.
-That's where you're wrong.
What?
-I served my time.
And learned this.
Oh, yes.
I was imprisoned in
the dark area.
For far too long!
The hatred!
The fearless [inaudible]!
As I waited to be freed,
I added to my powers.
I'm beyond the Lucemon
I was before.
-Be careful, Susanoomon.
-I really must congratulate
you.
You hold the spirits of the
10 legendary warriors.
Too bad I can't allow a being
with all that power to exist
in my world.
So goodbye!
[screaming]
-If you had chosen to obey
me, you might have lived.
All the power you possess
must be broken down.
-No, Susanoomon!
[evil laughter]
-Guys, get out of there!
-Even with all the Ancient
Spirits combined, is this all
the strength we have?
-Koji, listen.
I want you to promise
me something.
When you go back to the
real world, I want you
to visit our mom.
Will you do that?
-Our mom.
-My brother, I can't tell
you what it means to
me to have met you.
I have no regrets, no regrets.
-Koichi!
Neither do I.
-Can we still do this?
Is it really possible for us
to save the Digital World?
-I don't think we'd all still
be here if there wasn't
something we could
do about it.
-What?
What can we do?
-Protect our world.
That's all I ask.
-We promised you we would,
no matter what it took.
-We have to find a way.
[evil laughter]
LUCEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Excellent.
-Susanoomon's gone!
-Behold the punishment for those
who dare to defy me.
Hm?
They're alive?
But this is not possible!
No one can survive my Ultimate
Sacrifice attack.
This simply cannot be!
-Well, they did survive
your attack.
The only way they could was by
separating their own spirits
from the 10 Ancient Spirits.
-It can't be done.
It's against the
laws of nature!
-I'm back!
Now it's your turn
to be afraid.
Very afraid.
-Koichi, you are gonna love
what's about to happen.
Ready.
Celestial Blade!
[shouting]
-No.
No!
[screaming]
-Those pesky children
won't give up.
I was so close to my goal.
-Lucemon, you are full of
hatred and bitterness.
Your evil must be destroyed.
Your spirit will be renewed,
and all your
evilness will vanish.
Now with this energy, you
will be purified!
Fractal Code Digitize.
-No!
[gasping]
-Lucemon's gone.
-Yeah.
We did it, guys.
-It-- it really happened.
Susanoomon was able
to take him down.
-This is fantastico!
-Outstanding.
And Koichi, I'll keep
my promise to you.
-Oh, Neemon, they fought the
unthinkable and accomplished
the unimaginable.
-It's just like you said.
Yippee!
-Great job.
-That's right.
-Uh-huh.
-So, I wonder what'll happen.
-Huh?
-Hey, what's happening?
-What's it doing?
-It's rising up like
a loaf of bread!
-It's growing.
This can't be good.
It looks evil.
-I thought Lucemon
had been scanned.
That means his data's
been purified.
So why's this Digi-Egg
acting so weird?
-Oh, no.
No that!
-What?
-When Susanoomon scanned
Lucemon, he may have only been
able to scan the data that was
good, which means all his evil
data still exists.
And I'd say it's
growing again.
-Then if your suspicions
are right--
-He's been stripped
of all goodness
and is now evil incarnate.
His reign of terror will
be unstoppable.
-But I used to like the rain.
-Whoa.
He looks like a dragon
to the 10th power.
[roaring]
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
Unbelievable.
NEEMON (OFFSCREEN):
Where's he going?
TAKUYA (OFFSCREEN):
He's trying to go
to the human world.
TOMMY (OFFSCREEN): Oh, no!
-We've got to stop him.
-But how can we?
-I have no idea.
-But you know everythign,
Bokomon.
-Neemon, calm down.
We've got to follow him.
-Well, then let's evolve.
-Execute now!
Fusion Evolution!
[screaming]
-Aldamon!
-Execute!
Fusion Evolution!
BeoWolfmon!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Beetlemon!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Kumamon!
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Kazemon!
-All Digimon are behind you.
You can do it!
Our world depends on it.
-He's faster than I thought.
But if he thinks we're gonna
let him make trouble in the
human world, then he's wrong.
We're not gonna let some
overgrown evil lizard take
over the earth and
run our lives.
No way!
I've gotta protect my family
and stop this creep.
-I can't let it stop me from
keeping my promise.
I gave my word to Koichi that I
would visit my mom and bring
her flowers, and let her know
just how important she is to
both of us.
She deserves all my respect.
-I'm doing this for
my friends.
And thanks to this adventure,
I know what
friendship really means.
It's not about chocolate
or magic tricks.
it's about caring.
I'm not afraid of protecting
my friends.
That's what real friends do.
-I know who I am now.
And I'm gonna surround myself
with new friends.
That lonely girl who couldn't
open up to anyone doesn't
exist anymore.
I'm a new person, and I
want to help everyone.
-I've learned not to be
a crybaby or a coward.
My big brother always tried
to protect me, but now he
doesn't have to.
I can't wait to show him
how much I've changed.
We've got to win , so
we can all go home.
-We have to work as a team.
We're all totally committed
to do whatever it
takes to stop Lucemon.
-As humans.
-And as Digimon.
-We are here to protect--
-All of the digital world.
-And the human world as well.
-We have to succeed!
[roaring]
-It's gonna be a beautiful
sunset.
-I don't know.
To me, the sky looks
kind of bizarre.
-What's this?
You must choose to follow
me or be destroyed?
[growling]
[computer sounds]
-What is going on?
[growling]
-We've got to catch
up with him!
[gasping]
WOMAN (OFFSCREEN): You
must choose to
follow me or be destroyed?
Huh?
-So, where are we, anyway?
-I can't believe it.
[gasping]
ALDAMON (OFFSCREEN):
It can't be!
-No!
-Huh?
-We're back in the Shibuya
train station.
And if Lucemon isn't here, then
he must be up above us.
KAZEMON (OFFSCREEN): Then he's
trying to get above ground.
-We've got to move.
[roaring]
-There he is!
I'll stop him!
Atomic Inferno!
A direct hit!
Wait a second.
-How about a little
Cleansing Light?
-Let's attack together.
-Got it!
-Hurricane Gale!
-Blizzard Blaster!
-Lightning Blitz!
-Well, that should do it.
[gasping]
-He keeps healing himself.
-Our attacks don't work.
-Tide of Despair.
[roaring]
[screaming]
LUCEMON (OFFSCREEN):
You must choose to
follow me or be destroyed.
BOKOMON (NARRATING): Looks like
our plans to rescue the
human world and the
Digital World are
about to go up in smoke.
Find out on the next Digimon,
Digital Monsters.