NARRATOR: You'd think after
handing Cherubimon a heaping
helping of defeat everything
would be fine, right?
Wrong.
The gang was soon attacked by
that frozen freak IceDevimon,
who only wanted to toy
with them before
gobbling up their data.
He froze Koji and Takuya's
D-Tectors then trapped the
others in ice so he could pick
them off one by one.
JagerLoweemon fought IceDevimon,
but Korikakumon
freed the others and luckily
they were able to stop the
evil dude from chilling
and purify his data.
But then Cherubimon came back.
Don't these guys ever
get a break?
Digimon.
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the digital world.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other we live by
the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one
solution, to a spirit evolution.
Digimon.
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digimon through us let
your spirit evolve.
If we're all one world there's
a world for us all.
If we're all for one world
there's a world for us all.
Digimon.
-Wow!
Look at all those pretty,
floaty thingies.
-Sorry to burst your blissful
bubble of imbecility, but
those are not thingies.
-Oh yeah?
Then what are they?
Hm?
-Well, um, I don't know.
But sea thingies do not glow.
-Oh, OK.
-Whatever it is, it sure is
sucking up a lot of data.
-Whoa.
-Oh, boy.
Now what?
Cherubimon--
he's definitely up to
something up there.
I can feel it.
-I don't know about the rest
of you, but I've had just
about enough of that guy.
-Apparently the space and
gravity data is being affected
by some sort of energy wall.
-Or by those glowing thingies.
-Oh, Neemon.
Would you please stop it with
your thingy thingy.
-I think it's time
to finish this.
How about it?
Are you with me?
-Uh huh.
I guess we have to do
something, right?
-Definitely.
And you and I are the only
ones who can do it.
-I bet Bokomon and I could do
it if I only had the nerve.
-I bet Neemon and I could do
it if he only had a brain.
-Well, all righty then.
-Win this battle and you could
save the digital world.
-Yeah, we really could, huh?
-You bet.
-Well, I'm game if you are.
You don't mind staying behind?
-Aw, come on.
Why would we mind?
After all, you're the ones who
have to fight Cherubimon.
EmporerGreymon and
MagnaGarurumon are the only
ones strong enough.
But don't worry.
We'll be here rooting for you.
-Wow, I'm touched.
-I'm touched.
Touch this.
Just remember, pally.
If you lose, you'll have
to answer to me.
-Right.
-Relax, J.P. We got everything
under control.
-Yeah.
I'm glad to hear it men.
And we'll all celebrate
once you've won.
-Yeah, when you defeat
Cherubimon I'm going to cook a
big yummy dinner for everybody
-I want to contribute
something.
I know!
When you win you can
take me on a date.
-What?
-Yeah and I'm going to give you
both a great big kiss on
the cheek.
-That's just wrong.
-I'm going to knit you both
matching waistbands to look
exactly like mine.
-Bokomon you really shouldn't.
-But I--
-Before you go, there's
something I need to tell you.
-Mm hm?
-You can do this.
-Yeah.
-I believe in you brother.
-OK.
Well then.
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
How about it?
-Hm.
Oh yeah.
Now let's go make
some history.
-Then go already.
I've got some rooting to do.
-We're coming for
you, Cherubimon.
-I don't know what's going to
happen up there, but I do know
we'll need you guys to
believe in us with
everything you've got.
You up for that?
-Definitely.
-Let's bring peace back
to this world.
-This could be our
last battle.
I'm proud to be fighting
it with you, Takuya.
-I guess we'd better
win then, huh?
-Yeah.
-Go get 'em, guys.
We'll be here waiting for you.
-Unity execute.
Unified spirit evolution.
EmporerGreymon.
-Unity execute.
Unified spirit evolution.
MagnaGarurumon.
-Are you ready?
-Mm hm.
-Let's do it.
-Don't mess up, guys.
Hey, but no pressure.
-Get 'em!
Get 'em!
-Stay tough!
We believe in you.
-Right fast!
-Right hurry.
I'm hungry.
-Come back safely.
Oh, dear.
Just come back.
-The compression of the data
is working perfectly.
[evil laughter]
-The human children have been
a source of great irritation
but oddly, because
of them it seems
you're that much sweeter.
-I think he knows we're here.
-Mm hm.
I feel him.
[evil laughter]
-So you've come back to play.
You may have lived a little
longer had you not.
Take a look.
Do you know what this is?
Well, then let me
enlighten you.
This orb contains all of the
data I have collected from the
digital world.
-But why?
-Yeah.
What exactly do you plan
to do with that?
-Make it a part of me.
-Great.
What does that mean?
-He's insane.
-Yes.
Perhaps I am.
But once I've assimilated this
compressed data, I will be
invincible.
It is done.
And now I shall relieve you
of the legendary spirits.
-I don't think so.
Not as long as I'm breathing.
Mega missile.
Magna rockets.
-Missed again.
-Whoa.
Calm down.
Did you really think it
would be that easy?
-You're right.
We need to get focused here.
-Yeah.
-What are those lights?
-The beginning of a very
battle, I'm afraid.
-Storm of judgment.
Ah, very well.
Lightning spear.
-Is that the best you've got?
He's pretty quick.
I'll drive him this way.
Back me up.
-I'll be ready.
-Hey, ugly.
Wanna dance?
Sorry, you're not getting
away this time.
-For someone with so much
courage, you are a little
short on brains.
I was merely testing you.
-Test over.
Time to teach you a lesson.
Gotta get closer.
More power!
I need more power.
-I know.
Gotcha!
-No!
You had me.
-Almost ready.
Just a little bit more.
Dragon fire crossbow.
[screams]
-I hope that worked.
[groans]
-What?
-Valiant effort.
Impressive strategy.
Oh, but did I mention
that I'm invincible?
-That's impossible.
-Not when you possess as
much data as I do.
Thank you.
That was quite refreshing.
-His body--
it's regenerating!
-Even stronger.
And you will be my
first victims.
[roars]
-He's huge.
And he looks mad.
-Tell me, are you afraid now?
-No way.
I don't care how big you are.
-You don't scare me either.
-That will change.
Watch out.
The sky is falling.
Let's swing.
Get ready.
I'm about to rock your world.
-Nice trick.
But you've got to do
better than that.
-Perhaps you'll like this one.
[groans]
-Are castles supposed
to do that?
-No.
-What's happening?
-Just a little demonstration
to show you who's still in
charge around here.
Now, to finish the job.
Frozen spears.
[groans]
-Aha.
Maybe one more.
-Terminal judgment.
-We're not done yet.
No way!
-Where am I?
-In the middle of our date.
-Uh our what?
-Silly boy.
Don't you remember?
I promised I would go out on
a date with you if you won.
I'm sorry I'm so boring.
-But you're not.
I mean, I guess I'm
just really tired.
-Well, that of quite a battle.
Maybe you should sleep
some more.
-OK.
-Leave me alone!
I risked my hiney
out there, too.
How come Takuya got to
go out on a date?
-Looks like Koji's got his
hands full out there.
But I suppose after what you
guys have been through, he
should be able to
handle anything.
-Yeah, but I got to say, I'd
much rather be doing what I'm
doing than doing what
he's doing.
Guess I will take that nap.
[gasps]
-What?
Oh no.
We're still here.
It was just a dream.
We're not done yet.
MagnaGarurumon, wake up.
[groans]
-Amazing.
You're still alive.
-You're telling me.
Can you still fight?
-Yeah.
I think so.
-No rush.
Perhaps I should enjoy
my new powers.
You're such willing playmates.
-Look!
He's moving.
Oh no!
I think they're in trouble.
-Oh.
-Don't worry.
They'll be all right.
But we all have to
believe in them.
-Z's right.
We can't give up on them yet.
I believe.
-Me too.
-Oh!
-Fools!
Why do you resist
the inevitable?
Give me your spirits.
-He's too strong.
-Forehead.
-What?
-It's his forehead.
Beams of light seem to shoot
out from it every time he's
about to launch an attack.
It's got to the a source
of his power.
-So what we do?
Our attacks are useless
from a distance.
We've got to strike
at close range.
If we can find a way to release
the compressed data
stored in his forehead, he'll
have a sudden loss of energy.
Then we can take him out.
-OK.
But how are we supposed
to get that close?
-I fly in first and distract him
while you come in behind
me and go straight
for the forehead.
-Why should you go first?
My armor's stronger
than yours.
-And what am I supposed to
do once I get there?
In case you didn't notice,
my attacks were useless.
The only way to get him
is with your sword.
Once we're up there, it's
all going to be on you.
So what do you say?
Think you can handle it?
-Well, sure.
No problem.
-Atta boy.
-I'm tired of waiting.
Good bye.
Come seal your fate.
[roars]
-Bring it on.
I can take anything
you've got.
-1,000 spears.
-Hang in there, Koji.
Almost there.
I can do this.
-Lightning blast.
-No Takuya!
-Koji!
-Go get him, buddy.
[screams]
-Give up your spirit.
I'm going to take it, anyway.
-You're not taking anything
ever again!
-What makes you think
you can stop me?
You're all alone.
1,000 spears!
-I'm not alone.
I can feel them.
The spirits of all my
friends are with me.
That is the source
of my power.
As long as they believe,
nothing can stop me.
-No!
-You're done Cherubimon.
It's time to restore the peace
of the digital world!
-No!
Stay back!
Get away from me.
-I hope Takuya believes
in himself as much as
we believe in him.
-Let's finish this.
Good bye, Cherubimon.
I don't know if all that evil
can fit in my D-Tector.
If anyone needs purification,
this guy does.
Fractal code digitize.
-See ya soon, Cherubimon.
-Hey, you OK?
-Did we get him?
-Oh yeah.
-Well, then I'm fine.
-Koji.
-I hope they survived that.
-Takuya.
-Koji.
-Hey!
-Oh yeah!
Oh yeah.
-Cherubimon.
You pitiful fool.
You failed me.
No matter.
As long as I have the data you
collected, my resurrection
will soon be complete.
Rise up, my royal knights.
It is now up to you.
NARRATOR: Oh, great.
There's somebody worse than
that creep Cherubimon?
This ought to be good.
On the next Digimon
Digital Monsters.