NARRATOR: Mirror, mirror
on the wall, who's the
fairest of them all?
Well, you'd better say Ranamon,
or she'll sick her
Honeybeemon goons on you
like she did on Zoe.
Luckily, the Honeybeemon weren't
so hot at getting Zoe.
They even became her friends.
But Ranamon got Zoe to eat a
poisoned apple and tried to
convince her that no
one liked her.
They ended in a real knock
down, drag out fight, and
Ranamon was finally defeated!
Zoe and her new friends met up
with Tommy and the others, but
Takuya and Koji were still
trapped in their own worlds.
And who knows when, or if
they'll be able to get out?
THEME SONG: Digimon!
[theme music]
THEME SONG: We look to the past
as we head for the future
to reclaim the Digital World.
With faith in ourselves and
trust in each other, we live
by the lessons we've learned.
As we work towards one solution
through a Spirit Evolution.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
Forever united as one.
Together the battles are won.
Digmon!
Through us let your
spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Hi-ya-moo-ah!
Huh!
Digimon!
-Koji.
-I believe I just saw
Koji up there.
-I believe in Santa Claus,
but I know I saw Koji.
-Ugh, please ignore him.
-Let's get up there.
-Mhmm.
-I'm ready.
-Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
-Kazemon!
-Beetlemon!
-Kumamon!
-You can do it.
-Hang in there, Koji.
We're coming!
-Brace yourself for impact.
-Oh dear.
I believe we need
to rethink this.
-I believe in flying Duskmon.
-Oh?
-What now?
-No idea.
-He made it in.
-Unfortunately, Taki and
Koji don't know that.
We've got to warn them.
-No kidding.
But how are we supposed
to do that?
It's not like we can just pick
up a phone and call him.
-Hm.
I wonder.
Maybe we can.
Maybe there's a way to use the
D-Tector to contact them.
(THINKING) I wish this thing
came with instructions.
-Koji!
Zoe?
J.P.!
Tommy!
Aw, man.
Where is everybody?
I wish I could talk to them.
[buzzing]
-There's something new.
Huh?
ZOE: Takuya, can you hear me?
I can't believe it.
Zoe, is that you?
-No way!
I mean, yeah!
10-4, copy that, loud and
clear good buddy.
TAKUYA: Ha.
-Wow.
TAKUYA: Where'd you learn
to talk like that?
Wait, never mind.
Where are you?
Are you alone too?
-I'm outside with J.P., Tommy,
Bokomon, and Neemon.
But, listen.
You're in danger, Takuya.
You're inside Sakkakumon.
TAKUYA: Sakkaku-wha?
-Sakkakumon.
Mercurymon Beast Spirit
Evolved into a hideous
creature, and you, young man,
are deep inside it.
-That explains the smell.
-This isn't funny.
We gotta get him out.
-Sakkakumon is a
multidimensional being, so
please, stay alert.
Portals to the outside sometimes
appear once you've
won the battle.
Yeah, we all managed to escape,
but now that we're
outside, it seems like it's
impossible to get back in
there to help you and Koji.
TAKUYA: Man.
Well, have you contacted Koji?
-No, but we're about to.
-Koji, come in.
-Talk to me.
-Duskmon just went inside.
I think he's after Koji.
Please, be careful.
-Thanks.
Hang on, Koji!
I'm on my way.
DUSKMON (OFFSCREEN): Koji.
Who are you?
-Duskmon!
-I can't wait any longer.
I need to know.
What is our connection?
Why do I feel like I know you?
And why did you come
to this world?
Give me your memories.
Now!
-Hi, looking for a present
for someone?
It's for your mother, right?
-Kinda.
-I'm not a which or anything.
I just like to guess
that stuff.
Do you want some help?
-Uh, yeah.
-Oh, I love my job.
All right, let's find something
really pretty.
-Argh!
-Let me guess. Birthday?
No, anniversary!
-Their anniversary's today.
How'd you know that?
-I don't know.
It's my own little game.
So, what, about 10
or 15 years?
-Actually, it's three years.
-Three years.
How wonderful for them.
Well, wait a minute.
You must be at least 12.
Why have your parents only been
married for three years,
huh?
-Um, well.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): Koji.
Are you there?
KOJI (OFFSCREEN):
What is this?
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): This
is part of a game.
A test to determine
your future.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): My future?
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): Yes.
Are you willing to play Koji?
Very good.
Now, you must get to the Shibuya
Station by 6:00.
Take the elevator
to the basement.
What?
But I--
I have to go to my--
-Hey, flowers are ready.
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): I'll pick
them up later, OK?
-But--
All right.
Bye!
-What am I doing here?
How can this determine
my future?
-Argh.
-What is it?
What is this horrible
human emotion?
-Koji!
This sadness.
Overwhelming.
-Let me guess, you're looking
for something for
your mother, right?
-Their anniversary's today.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN):
Koji, are you there?
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Actually,
it's three years--
three years.
-Why am I even affected?
Why should I care about
him or his parents?
What is this connection?
-Get out of my head, Duskmon.
Leave my memories alone.
-Silence!
-Ah!
[knocking]
-Koji?
KOJI (OFFSCREEN): Yeah?
-Coming in.
Your mom's photo.
I haven't seen that
in a long time.
Son, I know it's been hard since
your mom died, but you
need to accept your stepmom.
-Ugh.
But she's not my mom.
She'll never be.
I don't need a mother anymore.
Well, can you at least try to
be nice to her for my sake?
-Ah!
-Ugh.
I don't want this burning.
This is his struggle.
I don't want to feel
this pain anymore.
I've got to put an
end to this, now.
-(THINKING) Why is he
doing this to me?
I don't understand.
-Am I still stuck
in Sakkakumon?
Whoa, bet I can't say that
five times fast.
-Frozen Fury!
-Whoa!
-That's what I call
a cold reception.
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
IceLeomon, the proud and
mighty king of the cold.
His chilling attacks will stop
anyone in their tracks.
-Frozen Fury!
-I don't have time to play
with this nasty kitty.
Koji needs my help and I won't
let you stand in my way!
Execute!
Spirit Evolution!
Agunimon!
He's dazed.
It looks like he's under the
spell of Sukkakumon.
Aw, man.
And I thought this place
couldn't get any worse.
[shouting]
-Duskmon.
You hesitate.
You alone posses the
spirit of darkness.
Do you realize its full power?
Mercy cannot exist.
Remove this obstacle at once.
-That's not what you really
want, Duskmon.
-Ignore him.
Listen to the darkness
in your heart.
Destroy this human and
fulfill your destiny.
-I will cover this world
in darkness.
-I can't let that happen.
Execute.
Spirit Evolution!
Lobomon!
Lobo Kendo!
-Get him, Lobomon.
-Take that creep apart!
J.P. (OFFSCREEN):
All right, Z!
-Come on, Agunimon.
Hang in there!
-Oh, he's struggling.
-Which Agunimon or Lobomon?
They're both fighting.
-Neither of them.
I'm actually referring
to Seraphimon's egg.
Oh dear.
I'm feeling faint.
-I know you don't really
want to fight me.
You're being controlled.
-Your feeble plea for
mercy won't work.
-(THINKING) He doesn't get it.
I guess I have no
other choice.
-(THINKING) The smug fool.
No one controls IceLeomon.
-I think it's time to melt
your frozen heart.
Pyro Punch!
-Blizzard Breath!
-Missed me, oh master
of darkness.
-Is that all you've got?
Fight me.
-Howling Laser!
-Very pretty, but I'm afraid
you'll have to do a lot better
than that to defeat me.
-I intend to.
-Pyro Torch!
Pyro Tornado!
Let's bring you in
from the cold.
Goodbye, Kitty.
It's time to get purified.
Fractal code digitize!
It's the outside.
I'm out of here!
-Now that we're outside, it
seems like it's impossible to
get back in there.
-(THINKING) Koji.
Can't leave yet.
-Slide Evolution!
Lupine Laser!
-Bad doggy.
I'll give you something
to howl about.
Lunar Plasma!
-You're gonna be the one
howling this time.
Howling Star!
[yelling]
-Oh, it's coming.
I feel it.
My baby's coming.
Somebody.
[groaning]
-You're scaring me.
-Neemon, I'm the one
having the baby.
-Uh, what are we supposed
to do to help him?
-It's a first for me.
-Why's it happening now?
I'm too young for this.
ZOE (OFFSCREEN): Oh no.
The light went out in
Agunimon's area!
-Bokomon, this really isn't
a very good time.
-It's not up to me.
Instead of standing there
like a lump of sap,
maybe you could help.
-Koji!
-Anything else you'd
like to try?
-Got to do something.
I know it's not supposed
to end like this.
OPHANIMON (OFFSCREEN): This
is part of a game.
A test to determine
your future.
-I can't let Duskmon win.
I just can't.
Not yet.
-It's time to say goodbye.
Any final thoughts?
-I'm sorry, Dad.
It hurt so much when mom died.
I guess I'm not over it.
-Well, can you at least try to
be nice to her for my sake?
-I tried to do it.
I'll pick them up later, OK?
I'll go back for
those flowers.
It's not their fault.
-No, stop it.
-I've been meaning to
tell you something.
I'm sorry.
These are for you, mom.
-Enough!
-I'm sorry!
[groaning]
-Oh?
-What's happening?
-Please be careful, baby.
-What was that?
What is this hideous
force of light?
-A brand new power source.
That's my spirit of Lobomon,
and KendoGarurumon.
I feel them.
My humand and beat spirits
have come together.
Execute!
Fusion Evolution!
BeoWolfmon.
-[italian].
-It's Koji.
-His two spirits have
come together!
-He's pretty.
-Actually, combined, they
become BeoWolfmon.
-Hold up.
Just how did you find out
his name is BeoWolfmon?
-That's a silly question.
What else will you call him?
-Uh.
[sniffing]
Uh.
-Go get him, BeoWolfmon.
-Um, where's the baby?
-I underestimated you.
But I don't understand.
You're miserable, Koji.
What do you have to fight for?
-I have some unfinished
business to attend.
Maybe you're so far gone that
you've given up on those you
care about, but I've been given
a second chance, and I'm
gonna take it!
-Koji!
-Who is that?
-Oh man.
I'm too late!
Koji, no!
-Now where are they going?
J.P. (OFFSCREEN): Koji!
-My dear sweet baby.
-He came to me.
Does that mean I'm
his uncle now?
-Duskmon.
Let the darkness embrace you.
That is where you belong.
Cover this pathetic world in
darkness, and it shall become
your kingdom forever!
-Yes, master.
My kingdom awaits.
-I have to find out.
(THINKING) Somewhere deep inside
that dark heart is just
a kid in pain, like me.
How are we connected?
Who is this Duskmon?
NARRATOR: Argh.
I can't take this anymore.
Now I gotta know.
Maybe we'll all find
out on the next
Digimon, Digital Monsters.