NARRATOR: While Crusadermon
and Dynasmon continued
gobbling up the digital world,
the DigiDestined ran into
trouble with lame brain
robber, Saggitarimon.
Luckily, four kids appeared
with Angermon
and drove them off.
Good news, except that two
of them were bullies
who picked on Tommy.
And they just got mad when they
were told to go back to
the real world.
Even worse, Saggitarimon
returned with a whole mess of
Centarumon.
Tommy saved one of the bullies,
and the new kids
realized it was time
to go home.
But even that didn't work out,
because the Royal Knight
showed up and carried
them off.
What else could go wrong?
THEME SONG: Digimon.
Look to the past, as we head for
the future to reclaim the
digital world.
The faith in ourselves and
trust in each other.
We live by the lessons we've
learned, as we work towards
one solution to a spirit
evolution.
Digimon, forever
united as one.
Digimon, together the
battles are won.
Digimon, through us let
your spirit evolve.
If we're all for one world,
there's a world for us all.
Digimon
[screaming]
-Tommy.
-We'll find you.
-That's great.
-Wow, they're gone.
-Ooh.
-We can all see that.
-Let's move.
-I wouldn't do that.
-Yeah, tracking them down
might be dangerous even.
-Hey, Trailmon.
-You might as well
just forget 'em.
-But they're our friends.
-They'll probably send you
a postcard someday.
-What?
[grunting]
-You're doing great, Tommy.
You just keep hanging
onto that net.
-Thanks, I've got a good grip.
Huh?
Wow, I've never seen
a tree that big.
-Oh, it's like Jack
and the beanstalk.
-Are those buildings?
[screaming]
-Beanstalk Village.
-Bingo.
What would you call a village
with a humongous beanstalk
growing up right in the middle
of it, Bean Town?
-That's a beanstalk?
Is there a mean giant too?
-Oh, J.P., it goes
into the clouds.
-Whoa.
-Well, this isn't in the book.
-It's tall.
-All right, Trailmon, who wants
to be the lucky one to
take us to Beanstalk Village?
-What?
-Huh?
-Ah.
-I got to do laundry.
-I got a horn buffing
appointment in Breezy Village.
-I'm not going there.
-Come on, help us out.
-That's just great.
Now what?
-Huh?
[snoring]
-Sounds like he's counting
some sheep.
-Or buffalo.
-Well, whatever he's counting,
he's our last chance.
-Rise and shine.
All aboard for Beanstalk
Village.
[sigh]
-Here, jigga, jiggle, jigga.
[sneeze]
[groaning]
-Hey, what was that about?
-Huh?
-Wake up, I'm trying to get
some shut eye here.
-I just love that you're
so outspoken.
You think a big, take charge
Trailmon like you could help
me out?
-Why, sure, you could
just call me Wormy.
[sighing]
-Actually, we all could
use your help.
We need a ride to Beanstalk
Village.
-No, you practically scare my
wheels off yelling at me, and
now you expect me to
give you a lift?
-Well, that sure would
be nice of you.
-Listen, I never been there, and
besides, I need more rest.
[yawn]
Nap time, and don't wake me.
Goodnight.
-A moment, Mr. Worm.
Your plate says otherwise.
-You're the Beanstalk
Village express.
My guess is you were still a
little sleepy and just forgot
where you were going, right?
[grumble]
[rattling]
-What a giver.
-He's all heart.
[screaming]
[groaning]
-That beanstalk's familiar.
-We're in Beanstalk Village.
-You've been here?
[gasp]
-What's happened?
NARRATOR: Mamemon, a small
ball like robot Digimon.
They are friendly, but if
threatened, they pack a wallop
with their smiley bomb attack.
-He's been hurt.
-They must have been attacked
or something.
[grunt]
-You two did this.
Only creeps like you would
do something this low.
-They brought it
on themselves.
They wouldn't tell us
where the hey is.
-Huh, what key?
-You know what I'm
talking about.
Now out with it.
Give us the key or you will
suffer the consequences.
-Everybody needs a relaxing
scrub now and then, and you,
Mr. Worm, are no exception.
Bet you've never had anyone
fully detail you.
You look great.
-You're looking so shiny, we
might need sunglasses.
-Think of all the compliments
you'll get
in Beanstalk Village.
-Rub a dub, duba duba
doo doo day.
-Hey, are you hungry?
I've got a chocolate
bar we could split.
-La.
[humming]
-I'm betting that chocolate
bar seals the deal for our
ride, right, eh?
-You're wrong.
-Huh, how come?
-It's too far.
-Why, you lazy train.
-That's it, I'm out of here.
[screaming]
-Come on, you guys, get on.
[horn]
-J.P, run.
Now jump.
[cheers]
[horn]
[sigh]
-Well, that worked out.
-Sure did, we got lucky.
[panting]
-I call it skill.
Huh?
-Did everyone make it?
-Yup, amazing, considering
how fast Worm took off.
-At least now he's
calmed down.
[screaming]
[grunting]
-You can enjoy your stay
in there until
you feel like talking.
-Great, how do we
get out of here?
-I don't know, but I do those
two creeps work for Lucemon.
-What's that key he's
asking about?
-Yeah.
-Oh, Katuharu.
-Who's that?
[gasp]
[chattering]
-Mamemon.
-Looks like they've
been beaten up.
-So tell us just what happened
here, Elder one.
-It's a long story, but what's
important is the Royal Knights
think you humans know where
the key is hidden.
-Where'd they get that idea?
-And just what is
this key anyway?
-To understand, I must share
with you a saying we Mamemon
have known for years.
The light dwells in the great
beanstalk, promising abundance
to the village once
the key is found.
We Mamemon had never taken root
anywhere until we decided
to make a home here.
Our life was hard.
We had little left when you
humans first passed through.
Meeting you and your
friends took away
all our heavy hearts.
Your smiles reminded us that
we should be kind to those
that are strange to us.
And to celebrate our friendship,
we planted the
last bean we Mamemon had.
It grew into our magnificent
life giving beanstalk.
-Huh?
-That bean became this
huge beanstalk?
-No way.
-You mean it?
-Oh, yes, our lives were filled
with joy and abundance,
all thanks to you humans.
Then the Royal Knights arrived
and began turning the digital
world into data and taking
over our land.
But the beanstalks roots have
spread into the land, so the
data is locked and safe.
The beanstalk you planted
is keeping us alive.
Without the key, its data
cannot be scanned.
The Royal Knights must believe
you humans have the key or
know where it is hidden.
Oh, I forgot to tell you the
second part of the saying.
Once the key is found,
the land will
once again sleep peaceful.
I'd say the Royal Knights know
about our saying and want to
prevent it.
-Now I understand why they
want that key so bad.
-So how are we going to find
the key before they do.
[groan]
-Well, first, we got to
figure a way out.
[sigh]
-Oh, man.
-I'm kind of tired.
Sleepy bye nappy time.
-Well, I'm tired of your
attitude, Worm boy.
Hm.
-Attitude shmatitude.
If there was tracks,
I'd be more than
willing to take you across.
Huh?
-Now, that's a plan.
Good plan.
[laughter]
-Huh, what's going on?
[chattering]
-Whatever you're doing,
it's not funny.
[chattering]
-Good job.
-Hold on.
If you tear up that rail, then
how am I going to get back
where I belong?
-We need this to repair
the track ahead.
-And now you can't run away.
-Sit tight.
-This'll just take a sec.
[grunting]
-OK, next one.
-How's it coming, J.P.?
-Have it for you in a
sec, Z.
-Got it.
[cheering]
-Uva, you may.
-Hey, human.
-What, Worm?
-Tell me, why are you guys so
hot to get to Beanstalk
Village anyways?
-We got to save our other
friends who got snatched up by
the Royal Knights.
They were heading towards
Beanstalk Village.
-And they have an even
bigger task,
saving the digital world.
Without the help of these brave
humans, our world would
already be gone.
-What a useless cause.
-What?
-You can't fight that.
Sooner or later, those Royal
Knights will turn
everything into data.
Stuff's disappeared every day.
The land I run on is starting
to look like Swiss cheese.
My friends--
I tell you, my boiler starts
burning whenever I think of
all my buddies that are gone
down for the count.
Let's face it, your friends
have probably
already been scanned.
You might as well
just pack it in.
[sigh]
-Huh?
Takuya.
-Hey, didn't you hear me?
Give it up.
-I'm not ever going
to give up.
Tommy, Katsuharu and the others
are waiting for us to
rescue them.
I'm not going to
let them down.
If we just keep believing in
ourselves and going forward,
we will win.
We'll do whatever it takes to
save this world, right?
-Uh huh.
-Yeah, you bet.
-That's right.
-I mean, let's face it.
The digital world is kind
of like our second home.
-Yeah.
-You call this place home?
And you guys really believe
you can save it?
You humans got a lot of
moxie, but how can
you save this place?
-I don't have a set plan, but if
we humans join up with all
you Digimon, I know
we can do it.
And before you know it, you'll
be back to racing around a
digital world that's in
once piece again.
-When you put it that
way, well, that
sounds kind of great.
Guess we'd better make tracks.
-Hey.
-You're going to take
us all the way?
-How about shodding me up
before we head out.
-Not likely.
-Mamemon.
[cheering]
-[inaudible].
Let's move.
[screaming]
-Elder.
[grunt]
-You silly prune, you don't
posses the strength
to escape from us.
-Let him go.
-He hasn't hurt you.
[groaning]
-You need to us where
the key is first.
[sighing]
-My servants, oh Royal
Knights, give me
what I need, data.
Give me more data.
-He is calling.
Lord Lucemon is calling to us.
-Then let's be quick about it.
-Elder.
-Let him go now.
-No, that would be unwise.
-It is simple.
You tell us where the key
is, we let him go.
-Even if we did know where it
was, we wouldn't tell you
jerks.
-And I don't care what
happens to me.
-We don't care what happens
to you either.
-Elder one.
[grunting]
-Execute.
-Tommy.
-You are an impertinent child.
-Huh?
[train horn]
-Oh yeah.
Now Worm's on our side.
That'll make this ride smooth.
[gasping]
-I didn't see this trouble
coming, did you?
-We should have taken a plane.
-This is why I didn't want to
go to Beanstalk Village.
It's one of the roughest routes
in the whole digital
world.
-That might explain why
the other Trailmon
wouldn't give us a ride.
[screaming]
-Pedal to the metal time.
-For the last time, I ask
you, where is the key?
-First let Elder one go.
-Why do you care
about Digimon.
Certainly I have value, but
common Digimon are just data.
-They're not just data.
They have feelings.
They feel hunger, fear,
happiness and sadness, just
like the rest of us.
When we met, they had hardly any
food, but they shared it
with us like we were
their family.
To us, the Mamemon
are true friends.
And I will do whatever it takes
to make sure you leave
them alone.
-Me too.
-Let him go.
-Yes, please, let
go of Elder one.
Release him now.
-Katsuharu, enough.
[laughing]
-What's going on?
-It's your human Digicode.
It's quite beautiful.
If I scan it, me thinks you'll
become a Digiegg, just like
Digimon do.
-Scan what?
Digiegg?
-Don't do it.
-No matter.
You're about to disappear.
-Katsuharu.
[horn]
[grunting]
-Katsuharu, Tommy.
-We're all OK.
Can you get this off?
-Sure I can.
Smiley bomb.
-Great.
Hey, thanks a lot, guy.
-What a fun choo choo.
-Whoa whoa.
-My back is bent
like a pretzel.
-Tommy, are you OK?
-Yup.
[screaming]
-Takuya, Koji, you've
got to do it.
-Ice into wind.
-Thunder into light.
-Wind into flame.
-Darkness into light.
-Digi execute.
Unified spirit evolution.
[screaming]
[grunting]
-EmperorGreymon.
-Digi execute.
Unified spirit evolution.
[screaming]
-MagnaGarurumon.
-How amusing.
You two insist on being
thrashed by us again?
-This time your impudence
will be rewarded more
appropriately.
We will not show
you any mercy.
[grunt]
-Pyro Dragons.
Dragon thrower.
[explosion]
-Magna rocket.
[laughing]
-Barrel fire, magna missiles.
[gunshots]
-Tommy, hurry, let's get
these Mamemon on Worm.
-Right.
-Come on, Mamemon, get on.
-Move quickly.
-Thank you.
-Spiral masquerade.
[grunt]
-And check, you pathetic pawn.
-Koichi.
-No, let him go.
-Stop, don't you hurt him.
-What?
I see.
You can't attack because you
wish to protect this human.
[scream]
-Koichi.
[grunting]
-Ah ah, if I were you, I'd be
more worried about myself.
-Release him, you witch.
-How dare you.
[grunting]
-Get her, come on, guy.
Don't let her get
the best of you.
She's just a big weirdo.
-Your slings and arrows fall
short, for I am beauty
personified, compared to
you homely humans.
-Wow, take a bow.
-Yeah, she's all that.
-Remember, the light dwells in
the great beanstalk, promising
abundance to the village,
once the key is found.
Together, we will win.
[cheering]
[grunting]
-Thanks a lot, Koji.
-Why, sure, anytime, brother.
-Ah, brotherly love is grand.
-I think her helmet's
on too tight.
[grunting]
-I am rather enjoying this.
-Enough dawdling.
We can't keep Lord
Lucemon waiting.
-Then let us finish this.
-Fist of Athena.
-Dragon thrower.
[grunt]
-Heads up, EmperorGreymon.
[grunting]
-Takuya, Koji.
[hum]
[grunting]
-The time has come.
-Your demise will be glorious.
-Royal Knights, stop.
The key you seek is at the
top of the beanstalk.
It is a golden pod.
And when you take it
from there, the
luck will be undone.
-Elder one.
-Whoa.
[grunt]
-Once the key is found, the
land will once again sleep
peacefully.
[sighing]
-Wondrous the data has been
colored by the beauty of
friendship.
-Go now, quickly.
[horn]
-Lord Lucemon will surely be
pleased with all this data.
-To the dark area and
Lord Lucemon.
Transmission.
-It's completely gone.
-The beanstalk and
your village too.
-It's sad.
-Katsuharu, now you and your
friends must leave this world.
-Not without taking
you Mamemon.
We'll find you a
place to live.
-We will not leave the
digital world.
This place is our home.
Our village was destroyed, but
we can always find another
place to build.
But if we were to lose dear
friends like you, that would
truly be a tragedy.
We can always plant another
bean and nurture its
possibilities.
Who knows?
This one might even grow as big
as the one you planted for
us, Katsuharu.
-Why are all of you
staying here?
-Well, we've still got a
lot of stuff we need to
take care of here.
-Hey, Tommy, why don't you
come back with us?
-Mm-mm.
I want to stay right here
to help save this place.
We have lots of Digimon friends
just like you do, and
we can't let them down.
-We're counting on you.
-Thanks.
-Well, good luck.
-Yeah, we're going back home.
-Hey.
-Be careful, you guys.
Tommy, your turn.
[screaming]
-Give me a shove this time.
[giggling]
[horn]
-The earthbound express
is hitting the rails.
[horn]
[laughing]
-See ya.
[cheering]
-Now we're even, Tommy.
-Bye.
-Well, what do you know?
A happy ending.
But Tommy and the gang still
have a lot of work to do.
See if they can get it
done on the next
Digimon Digital Monsters.