[NARRATOR] Long, long ago,
when the world was darker,
the sky lit by fewer stars,
the gods began to tire
of the dice game
that would determine
who among them
would hold dominion
over the world.
And so, they created
many worlds,
and beings to populate them:
humans and elves,
dwarves and lizardmen.
These new creatures
began adventuring.
Sometimes they were rewarded.
Other times they ended up dead.
[PRIESTESS]
Incredible.
[PRIEST] My compliments.
Was that some form of magic?
No, it's just that once
you've mastered a technique,
It can seem as though
you've cast a spell.
Yes, well, next time I'll show
you what a dwarf can do.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
One, two.
[ARCHER]
Huh?
What are you doing?
My arrow killed them.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] They're
highly sensitive to smells.
Especially the scents of women,
children, and elves.
Ugh! No way! You keep
that filth away from me.
You get used to it.
[whimpering]
-[ARCHER screams]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER grunts]
[sword clanging]
[PRIEST]
Interesting designs.
I believe this might
have been a shrine once.
It looks like some kind
of battle took place here
during the Age of the Gods.
This could have been used
as a fortress.
Whatever the case,
it was built by humans.
[PRIEST]
And after it was abandoned,
the goblins made it their home.
What a terrible jest.
Speaking of terrible.
Eww!
This is so disgusting!
Um, it does wash off
with water, mostly.
I'm not gonna forget
about this when we get back!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Understood.
I'm used to living underground,
but being down here
feels wrong somehow.
[ARCHER] I think
we're walking in a spiral.
[PRIESTESS] I wonder
what's in the center.
[ARCHER]
Wait, stop.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What's wrong? An alarm?
I think so.
I only spotted it
because the marks are new.
Conniving monsters.
These ruins could be
full of traps.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] That's strange.
-What's the matter?
-There are no totems.
-Huh?
Um, that means, there aren't
any goblin shamans here.
Great.
This'll be a lot easier
without any spells
flying around.
[PRIEST]
Apologies, but that's not so.
The lack of shamans
is disconcerting to him.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Correct.
Ordinary goblins shouldn't be
able to set traps like this.
[SHAMAN] You think someone
could be leading them?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
We should assume so.
I have heard many tales
of the large nests
you bravely destroyed
in the past, Sir Goblin Slayer.
What are your
preferred methods?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Smoke them out,
then crush them one-by-one.
Set them on fire,
drown them in the river.
There are many options,
but those won't work now.
-Are there tracks?
-It's hard to tell in here.
The rock floor is too smooth.
[SHAMAN]
Let's see.
Their hideout is
down the left hallway.
-[PRIESTESS] How can you tell?
-The subtle wear on the stone.
It looks like they travel
from the left side to the right
and then back again,
or they head from their hideout
to the entrance.
[PRIEST] What do you suggest,
Sir Goblin Slayer?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
We go this way.
[ARCHER]
Did you not hear him say
their hideout's
in the other direction?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
But then we'd be too late.
[armor jangling]
[gagging]
What an awful stench.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Breathe through your nose.
You'll get used to it.
[thudding]
[flies buzzing]
[ARCHER]
What is this place?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
A goblin waste heap.
[ARCHER]
You don't mean...?
[gasps]
♪
[vomits]
-What in the name of the gods?
-Poor miserable soul.
-Please, you have to...
-She's still alive!
-Quick, a miracle!
-Right!
[gasps] What?
What is it, Goblin Slayer?
-You must kill.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I understand.
♪
Wait! Please stop!
We can still save her!
-[ARCHER] Don't!
-You must kill this monster!
[growls]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Three.
I don't know what
you all were expecting,
but I only came here
to slay goblins.
Kill them all,
every last one of them.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I will.
[PRIEST] O horns and claws
of our father, Iguanodon,
thy four limbs become two legs
and walk upon this earth!
[air whooshes]
A miracle from my ancestors,
the dragontooth warrior.
Send this with him.
It should explain everything.
[PRIEST]
Hmm.
[clomping]
Make haste.
My conjured messenger
should safely deliver her
to the elves in the forest.
[sobbing]
What the hell is going on?
Can you imagine
what she's been through?
[sighs]
Hmm?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I found something.
[PRIESTESS]
Is it another scroll?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
A map of the ruins.
It was in this rucksack.
The elf must have been using it.
There's large chamber
to the left.
They're likely using it
as their main camp.
-So, you didn't believe me?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I did.
But the more information
we have, the better.
You take this, ranger.
Let's go.
[PRIESTESS]
Hey! Give her a second.
[ARCHER]
It's fine.
[sniffles]
We have to move quickly,
and stop them.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That's right.
The goblins
must be put to death.
[arrow whizzes, thuds]
♪
[sighs]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] How many spells
do we have left?
[PRIESTESS] I only used Heal,
so I can pray for two miracles.
I have three remaining myself.
But a dragontooth warrior
requires catalysts.
I will only be able to use that
particular miracle once more.
And this old dwarf
can cast about four or five.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Got it.
Would you like some water?
Yes, thank you.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Show some moderation.
Only a sip, a full belly
will slow your movements.
She needs something to drink.
Can't you be a little more--
There's no need to act tough.
If you're up to this, come.
If you're not, go back.
It's that simple.
[ARCHER] Don't be ridiculous.
I'm a ranger.
Who's going to scout and find
all the traps if I leave you?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] We'd just have
to make do with the four of us.
Ugh, you idiot!
There's no way I'm going back!
Not after what they did
to that elf.
My home isn't very far
from here, what if they had...?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see. Then let's begin.
[SHAMAN] Keep your wits
about you, long ears.
Stealth is our greatest ally
against the beasts.
Did you know that dwarves
consider goblins
our mortal enemies as well?
We'll make them pay
for what they did to her.
I won't leave here
until they're all dead.
I hate taking advice
from dwarves, but you're right.
Sorry for that just now.
I'll refocus.
[chuckles]
It sounds like your head's
back on your shoulders.
[gasps]
[wind blowing]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Well?
-It's just as it looks.
-There are many.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Not a problem.
[PRIEST] Sir Goblin Slayer,
do you have a plan?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I do.
[moans]
[yawns]
[grunts]
Drink deep
and sing loudly spirits.
Shout, dance,
and sleep like the dead.
Show me the dreams
of fire wine!
[gasps, chokes]
[jangling]
[PRIESTESS] Hear me,
O merciful Earth Mother.
Grant us the peace
to accept all things,
and bless us
with your solitude!
[muttering]
[choking]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Stupor and silence.
By combining those two magics,
the goblins will fall asleep
before any sort of alarm
can be raised.
And then, the three of us
will slay them up close,
one at a time.
[ARCHER grunting]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[ARCHER shudders]
Too slick.
[ARCHER] I see.
He's using their weapons.
[grunting]
Has he really been doing this
by himself this entire time?
[gasps]
Huh?
♪
-[rumbling]
-[all] Huh?
-[thudding footsteps]
-[air whooshing]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[ARCHER]
An ogre!
I thought those dirty goblins
were awfully quiet.
They don't even
make good foot soldiers.
You people seem more prepared
than that elf from before.
But you're wrong if you think
you can step foot
in my fortress and live.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Oh. So, you're not a goblin?
Are you being serious?
He's an ogre.
-You've heard of them!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] No.
Bastard. You mock me.
I, who have been
granted an army
by one of the demon lord's
generals.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I know there are powerful
monsters in the world.
But I'm afraid
I've never heard of you.
[roars]
[gasping]
Then I'll show you my power,
so that you may die knowing it.
Carbunculus crescant!
He's casting a fireball!
-[ARCHER] Scatter!
-[SHAMAN] It's enormous!
Where do you propose we go?
[PRIESTESS] Hear me,
O merciful Earth Mother.
Please protect us, the weak,
with your divine light
and the sacred power
of nature!
-Iacta!
-Protection!
[grunting]
O, Earth Mother...
Please protect us, the weak,
with your divine light
and the sacred power
of nature once more.
Protection!
[growls]
-[rumbling]
-[PRIESTESS whimpering]
[whimpering]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You saved us.
-We can handle him.
-Foolish little archer.
You'll suffer far more than
the other elf ever dreamed of.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Create
a warrior. We need numbers.
As you wish, Sir Goblin Slayer.
O horns and claws
of our father, Iguanodon,
thy four limbs become two legs
and walk upon this earth!
O sickle wings
of the velociraptor.
Slice, fly, and hunt!
-I request backup!
-You got it!
Time to work,
you crafty gnomes.
Mash grains of sand together
to form mighty rock!
Measly little dwarf!
[grunts, groans]
You damn cave dwellers
are too slow.
We have our own way of fighting.
Observe, long ears.
Stone Blast!
[growls]
[grunts]
Did you think you could beat me
by throwing a few pebbles?
[grunts]
Now, Sir Goblin Slayer!
Is that your best attack?
-Orcbolg, no!
-I don't think he's moving!
Do not mistake me
for a mere goblin.
-[grunts]
-[sizzling]
You shall each pay dearly
for this humiliation.
First, I shall break
each of your limbs,
then I'll make sport
of the females in front of you.
[PRIEST] You will not defeat us,
Ogre. I swear it!
[growls]
Please attend to him,
Priestess.
Goblin Slayer!
Please, can you hear me?
[growls] Out of the way,
overgrown lizard.
Sir Mage and Lady Ranger,
now's your chance.
Hurry up with another spell,
dwarf!
I'm working on it!
You insolent bug,
stop your incessant buzzing!
[grunts, screams]
[grunts]
Have another Stone Blast!
Your attacks are useless.
[roars]
Come on, speak to me!
[GOBLIN SLAYER grunting]
I can't see well.
What's happening?
Everyone's still
fighting the ogre.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Good.
I need a healing potion
and a stamina potion.
-Of course!
-Thanks.
[GOBLIN SLAYER grunting]
-Take them.
-[thunderous boom]
[groans]
-[glass shatters]
-Huh?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER gulping]
-[glass shatters]
Let's do this.
Where's my bag?
It's right here.
What do you need?
-Thanks. Stay back.
-Be careful!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'll be reckless
if it means I win.
But there are usually
other ways to ensure success.
Watch out! You're injured!
I have a plan. Stand aside.
All right. Kill him!
My faith is with you,
beard cutter.
Take him down!
We find ourselves in dire
need of your assistance.
[OGRE] I looks as though
the human weakling
has used up the last
of her miracles.
Carbunculus crescant.
No wait!
Fear not.
If she manages to survive this,
I'll allow her to live
for a little while.
She'll be my plaything,
and then my food.
I need someone to spawn
more goblins for me now.
[growling]
-Iacta!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] You're a fool.
[rumbling]
[grunts]
Huh?
[wind blowing]
[groans]
[vomits]
♪
But how? What did you do?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
This is a gate scroll.
I linked it
to the bottom of the sea.
What just happened?
Was that just seawater?
[PRIEST] The water at that depth
is under incredible pressure.
It must have been unleashed
swiftly, like a blade.
To think, he used
a transfer scroll as a weapon.
Such magic allows you
to escape in an instant.
It's often used
by adventurers in peril.
But certainly not as a form
of attack like this.
[WITCH]
The thing is, dear.
Your friend asked a strange
favor of me once upon a time.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I was going to use that scroll
to destroy a nest.
-Oh, well.
-[OGRE groaning]
Now, then,
what were you called again?
Not that it matters.
You're insane.
You would use such power
against mere goblins?
-[grunts]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
Because goblins are
far more troublesome than you.
[OGRE groaning]
[MALE ELF]
You have our gratitude.
We received your letter
and the girl,
then came as soon
as were able.
How many more goblins
are left inside at this point?
Well, anyway,
we're going to go scout
for any survivors now.
Please try to rest in the back
on the way into town.
-Priestess.
-What is it?
Does Orcbolg always do
insane stunts like that?
Yes. That's just
who he is, I think.
Well, then...
[PRIESTESS] But despite
how rash he can seem,
he's always quite aware
of his actions.
He also isn't obligated
to teach me anything,
and yet every quest he does.
I see.
[snoring]
-We should sleep.
-[PRIESTESS] Yes.
♪
Yeah.
No, I still don't like him,
even if he did save us
from that ogre.
I thought adventures
were supposed to be fun.
There's joy in experiencing
the unknown
and discovering new wonders.
We should feel happy
or accomplished,
proud of what we've done.
But that's not what I'm
feeling in the slightest.
Someday, I'll take him
on an actual adventure.
-[trudging footsteps]
-[cows mooing]
[gasps]
Welcome home.