[birds chirping]
-[soup boiling]
-[COWGIRL humming cheerily]
[sips]
Oh. Huh?
Good morning!
It'll be just a minute.
Breakfast is almost ready.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Run.
-Huh?
Okay. You're kidding.
You are, right?
Come on.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
There were tracks.
♪
Goblins.
All right, so you'll
just fight them off, then.
-Won't you?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I can't.
[gasps]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] In a cave,
I would win against them,
even if their numbers
were a hundred strong.
No matter what,
I'd be victorious.
But...
there were at least
ten sets of scout footprints,
which means this horde
definitely has a leader.
Not a hob or a shaman, no.
Judging from their numbers,
it must be...
something much stronger.
A Goblin Lord.
[soup boiling, sizzling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] The attack
will come tonight or tomorrow.
We don't have time
to ask the military for help.
Based on the tracks,
it's a horde of more
than a hundred goblins.
[COWGIRL]
So many. That's terrifying.
But why here? Why the farm?
What do they want with it?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Most likely
they'd use it as a stronghold
to launch an attack on the town.
I'm not a platinum-ranked
adventurer.
I'm not a hero.
I don't see how we can
possibly muster enough people
to face more than a hundred
monsters in an open field.
I'm not strong enough.
I can't do it.
[gasps]
That's why you want me to go.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
-I'll live, if I run now?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes.
Okay.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] You've decided?
-[COWGIRL] Yeah.
[sighs]
I'm sorry,
but I'm not going to run away,
because you're going
to stay behind. Right?
You always do that,
go silent when you're at a loss.
It's cute.
[chuckles]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
They won't just kill you.
Yes. I know that.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I've seen it, what they do.
Yes.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Don't think that you'll survive.
Yes, you might live,
but you'll be dead inside.
♪
So you need to run!
[COWGIRL]
I told you, I'm staying!
I can't...
I can't go through that again!
I won't just run away
knowing you're going to lose
your home a second time.
And, besides,
maybe we'd escape,
but the farm,
it'd be completely destroyed.
Even if we came back,
well, there would be nothing.
You know?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I see.
-Yeah. I really am sorry.
I know I'm being stubborn,
not to mention foolish.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Don't look at me like that.
[whimpering]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'll do everything I can.
-Everything.
-Okay!
[sobbing]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
"You have to protect those
who are smaller than you."
[UNCLE]
Hey.
You ought to at least say
goodbye when you're leaving.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You're right. I'm sorry.
[UNCLE]
She's a good girl, you know?
Despite everything,
she's grown up so well.
Keep her safe. You got it?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'll try my best, sir.
[UNCLE] Sometimes I wish
you would just lie.
[doors creak]
-[VILLAGERS chattering]
-[GUILD GIRL gasps]
Uh...
Well, look who it is.
Figured you'd crawled off
and died somewhere.
You just gonna
stand there or what?
[ARCHER]
Huh?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I apologize, but hear me out.
I have a request.
The Goblin Slayer has a request?
Isn't he a solo
adventurer, though?
[ADVENTURER] Nah. I hear
he's been going out on quests
-with a party lately.
-Really, him?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] A horde of
goblins has been scouting a farm
on the outskirts of town.
I don't know
how many there are,
but they'll probably
attack tonight.
Something about goblins.
Big surprise, huh?
[ADVENTURER] What's the big deal
about a horde of goblins?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Judging by
the footprints the scouts left,
they're led by a Goblin Lord,
which means there's at least
a hundred of them.
-[SPEARMAN gasping]
-[GUILDSMAN A] A hundred?
-That many?
-He's gotta be kidding.
-[GUILDSMAN B] There's no way.
-[GUILDSMAN C] It's impossible.
[GUILDSMAN D]
What's going on?
-You lost, too?
-Yeah.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Lords are
a mutated class of goblins
that excel in leadership.
-Think of them as the top rank.
-That sounds bad.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
And the horde that it's leading
will be here soon.
There's no time.
I could handle them in a cave,
but I can't kill them
out in the open, alone.
Please,
I'm asking for your help.
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
-What should we do?
-Don't know.
-What do you think?
-Some goblins need killing.
That's his thing,
so he should do it.
[GUILDSMAN]
You can count me out.
[GUILDSWOMAN] I'm not going near
those disgusting creatures.
[grunts, growls]
[SPEARMAN]
Hey!
Listen. I don't think you
understand how this works.
This guild hall
is for adventurers,
and everyone here falls
under that banner.
Which means we don't
do anything as a favor.
So put up a quest
and offer up a reward.
-That right?
-[GUILD MEMBERS] Yeah!
-[GUILDSMAN A] Yeah!
[GUILDSMAN B]
We're adventurers!
[gasps] What the hell is wrong
with these people?
[SHAMAN]
Simmer down, Long-ears.
No need to stir the pot
and complicate things.
I understand
this boils your blood,
-but don't act rashly.
-Let me go!
[gasps]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes, you're right.
So, what are you offering?
What's the elimination
of 100 goblins worth to you?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Everything.
-Uh?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'll offer
everything I have as a reward.
[SPEARMAN]
And what does that entail?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All of my belongings,
and everything
within my discretion.
My equipment, my assets,
my knowledge, my time, and--
Even your life?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes, if that's what's necessary.
And would you take your life
if I asked that of you?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No. I can't do that.
Why?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Because if I did,
it would hurt someone important.
I was told I can't let
that happen.
So I suppose, my life isn't
within my discretion.
[groans, sighs]
[SPEARMAN] I really have no clue
what's going on
under that beat-up old
helmet of yours,
but it's fairly obvious
you're serious about this.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes, extremely serious.
Well, damn it all to hell.
[chuckles]
I wouldn't ask you to off
yourself anyway, you dimwit.
A strong drink will suffice!
Come on, that's an amazing deal.
A man of my prestige agreed
to slay no small number
of goblins for you!
Where's your gratitude?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Of course. Forgive me.
-Thank you.
-Uh... All right, that's enough.
Just thank me after
we've tallied up our kills.
-[ARCHER] I'm in!
-[CROWD gasping]
I'll slay some goblins
with you, gladly!
But I'm asking for something
in return from you as well.
Once all this is over,
promise that you'll come
with us on a real adventure!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I swear it.
[SHAMAN]
My price is a bit steeper
than just one drink,
Beard-cutter.
I'm going to need
a whole barrel!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] All right.
Then you'll have it.
I'd also like to join
our elven friend
on this grand adventure,
if you'll have me.
I wouldn't dream of going
without my party.
By that logic,
I can assume
I shall also be included
in your numbers.
Though I don't mind
helping out a comrade in need,
if I were to ask for some
small token of reward...
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Cheese?
That, and one more item
would be appropriate.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Ice cream?
-Oh! That's perfect.
A reward even
the gods would envy.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
They don't belong to me,
but they are made at the farm.
If wiping out the subterranean
scourge would also protect
that exquisite ambrosia,
count me in.
Well now, that makes five--
[WITCH]
There were five. I'll be six.
Brilliant Inflammarae.
Seems your flame
has drawn more moths to it,
but will they burn their wings?
[GUILD GIRL panting]
Listen up, everyone!
I have an announcement!
The guild's offering
a quest as well!
There is now a reward
of one gold coin
for every goblin slain!
-How's that for incentive?
-[GUILDSMAN A] Seriously?
[GUILDSMAN B]
A gold coin for every goblin?
That's great!
[MANAGER]
You're sure we can do this?
[CHIEF] Well, it is based
on intel from a silver rank,
so it's not a problem.
And besides,
with that kind of passion,
how could we say no?
Just keep an accurate count.
[sighs]
Suppose I've got no choice.
You're going too?
It's not like I'm doing a favor
for Goblin Slayer, mind you,
but denying the reward
would be foolish.
Really?
There's no need to lie about it.
I know the reason.
You're doing this
because he was the one
who slayed the goblins
that attacked your hometown.
[groans]
Damn it! That's not so.
I'm doing this strictly to gain
some gold coins
and nothing more!
It furthers my goal
of becoming a Paladin.
I can't refuse anyone
in need of help.
You hear that? If they're going
to join the fight,
-then I guess I am as well.
-And I'm going too.
Looks like we're all
in this together, then.
-So, uh...
-What's wrong?
Just that I haven't ever slain
any goblins before.
Well, it is pretty dangerous.
But I'm thinking that now would
be the perfect time to start.
You're right.
We do owe him after all.
[ADVENTURER] Okay. We became
adventurers at the same time,
so it seems fate
has decided for me.
[GUILDSMAN] To be honest,
I think I'd actually miss
all his talk
about goblins around here.
[GUILDSMAN B]
Yeah, the truth is,
he's really pretty popular
in the ol' guild hall.
[GUILDSMAN B] The one thing
worse than having him around
would be if he wasn't here
to drive us crazy.
I gotta say,
a quest this bizarre is way too
interesting for me to resist.
That's great!
Even though we're not
in your party or close friends,
we're all adventurers.
It's what we live for!
[ALL]
The adventurers will handle it!
[cheering]
You don't need to fill out
any paperwork right now,
just give us the tally
when you return.
[giggles]
-Wonderful, isn't it?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yeah.
You realize, I'll be coming
with you too, right?
[GOBLIN SLAYER chuckles]
Yeah.
[crickets chirring]
♪
[growling, grunting]
-[chattering excitedly]
-[low growling]
[GOBLINS growling]
[growling, roaring]
[GOBLIN LORD bellows]
[GOBLINS cheering]
[roars]
[growling]
♪
[canary twittering]
[DRUID]
Everything will be fine.
I needed to hear that.
-[squawking]
-Huh? Over there!
-[birds fluttering, squawking]
-[animals screeching]
[ADVENTURERS growling]
-[plants rustling]
-[GOBLINS muttering]
I hope you're ready for this.
[gasps, grunts]
[GOBLINS cackling]
[shuddering]
[growling, cackling]
[growling]
[cackling]
[gasps]
[bodies thudding]
[warbling]
-Fall into Stupor.
-Go to sleep.
[SHAMAN]
Sleep, you filthy goblins!
[ADVENTURER]
Now!
Don't bother with the goblins!
[GOBLINS gasping]
Just grab the captives
and get 'em outta here!
Hurry! Fall back! Now!
[ARCHER] Using human shields?
Despicable.
They deserve
every arrow they get.
[grunting]
We've brought
all the women to safety!
[ARCHER] I've taken care of all
the spell-casters within sight.
[GUILDSMAN]
Good work!
[lantern clattering]
[voices murmuring]
Yeah! Now!
Time to earn your gold, boys!
-Attack!
-[ADVENTURERS shouting]
I look at these goblins,
and all I see is an easy payday!
[grunting]
[SPEARMAN] Damn! I can hardly
believe how many there are!
[grunting]
A real pain in the ass.
This is why even Goblin Slayer
couldn't do it on his own!
[blades slicing]
We knew it wouldn't be easy.
That definitely got
my juices flowin'!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[BOTH scream]
I'm sure you'd be fine
out on your own,
but if you're close, I can use
-my Deflect Missiles spell.
-Hmm.
[growling]
[distant screaming]
[LIGHT SWORDSMAN]
They're pushing hard.
Yeah. I should've gone
out there with them.
Wait. Do you see that?
[wolves growling]
Those are the goblin riders,
just like he said.
[inhales]
[whistling]
On guard! That means
the riders are coming!
Get ready!
[grunts]
All right everybody,
you know what to do!
Remember, we're going to need
to form two lines,
with the men in the back
filling the gaps in the front.
Have your weapons out
and stay alert!
They're coming in low, so draw
them in as close as you can!
-Not yet!
-[growls]
[SPEARMAN]
Keep waiting!
[wolves growling]
Get ready!
Here we go!
[shouting]
[growls]
♪
[ADVENTURERS groaning]
Back-line troops!
Let's move in!
[shouting]
There. Here it comes.
[gasps]
Oh. It's dead.
[sighs]
-[blade clanks]
-[grunts]
Ha-yah!
Get your head out of the clouds
and into the fight!
You want your gold, don't ya?
[gasps]
[APPRENTICE CLERIC]
Are you hurt?
No.
My armor saved me.
Thank God.
[HEAVY SWORDSMAN]
Pretty easy money, huh?
Yeah, but without his strategy,
you might be singing
a very different tune right now.
[HEAVY SWORDSMAN scoffs]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Set ambushes.
It's a tool they use often,
but they won't
expect it from others.
They'll be leading
with meat shields.
We'll cast sleeping spells
and when they fall,
that's when we rescue
the hostages.
Just leave the sleeping
goblins on the ground.
We don't want them to wake up.
A bigger horde like this will
have riders on trained wolves.
There'll probably be
20 or 30 of them.
We can take most of them
out with spear walls.
Those of us
not holding up the wall
will kill the survivors.
You can use weapons or spells,
whatever it takes.
We'll need to kill
their spell-casters
as soon as possible.
[GOBLIN LORD shouts orders]
[roaring]
Underneath all that
tarnished metal,
there really is a silver rank.
You went and ran too
far away from the group,
you stupid goblin!
-[screaming]
-[chuckling]
Hey, find any stragglers
over there--
[whimpering]
-[screaming]
-What was that?
Something's flying this way,
watch your heads!
[BOTH gasp]
-[thuds, squelches]
-[gasps]
[gasps]
[pounding footsteps]
[GREENHORN WARRIOR screams]
[growling]
[growls]
Looks like we've got some hobs!
-[HEAVY SWORDSMAN] No.
-[SOLDIERS gasp]
[HEAVY SWORDSMAN]
That's a big boy.
A goblin champion.
[SPEARMAN]
Make that two of 'em.
[roars]
[HEAVY SWORDSMAN]
Nice.
I was getting a little bored
with all the small-frys.
I may actually break a sweat
taking these guys down.
Are you asking for help?
I don't know, how can I fight,
and count up
all these goblin heads
-I've collected so far?
-I'm sure you'll find the time.
-Step back, okay?
-[WITCH] As you wish.
Those heads look heavy.
We may actually be
doing the beasts a favor
by taking them
off their shoulders.
This has turned into
a veteran's battlefield.
If you doubt your skills,
get out of the way!
[blades tinging]
-[roaring]
-[shouting]
Crazy.
[WITCH]
May I have some water?
-Yes, right away.
-Thank you, dear.
Are you sure
that they don't need you
out there on the battlefield?
[WITCH] I am,
to be quite honest.
He's far more used
to dispatching these brutes
-than normal goblins.
-Wait a sec.
Does anybody know where Goblin
Slayer might have run off to?
Of course. Think,
ask yourself who he is.
[ARCHER]
Yes.
It's not that tough
to figure out.
[GOBLIN LORD panting]
[growls]
[ARCHER] Obviously,
he went to slay some goblins.
[growls]
[dice clatter]