[wind howling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Master, what should I do today?
[BURGLAR]
What should you do?
What kind of question is that,
you little idiot?
[grunts]
You got hit,
so now you hit back.
Destroy the goblins!
Those filthy critters
are smarter than they look.
Think you'll be able
to kill them, boy?
-I will.
-[BURGLAR laughs]
This from the useless
little wretch who just watched
while the goblins made his
darling sister their plaything.
Why didn't you attack
the goblins and make them stop?
Why didn't you take
your sister and run?
-[grunts]
-[rock clatters]
You were powerless,
so you chose to do nothing.
Did you think
it would be different
if you became stronger?
Because it won't, maggot!
Even if you do gain
a little power,
it'll just be for show.
Here one moment
and gone the next!
It's your actions,
not your strength
that will lead you to victory.
Yes, boy.
The moment you make the decision
to do something and act on it,
you win.
-[flame whooshes]
-[gasps]
What you need is luck,
wisdom, and courage.
First decide whether or not
you're going to do something,
and then do it!
-Yes, master.
-[BURGLAR] Look above you.
I'm going to give you a riddle.
If you don't want to die,
answer quickly.
-Yes, master.
-[BURGLAR] Very good.
More just than the gods,
more vicious
than the evil deities,
the rich need me,
the poor need me not! What am I?
Better not get it wrong.
You'll be crushed if you do!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] It's nothing.
The answer is nothing!
[BURGLAR]
Correct! Time for another!
He may appear before you
at any time and in any place.
He will utter not a word,
and from his grasp
there can be no escape.
He is beside you even now.
Give up?
I know what the answer is.
It's Death!
Yes. Well done.
Finally, answer me this.
What am I carrying in my pocket?
[gasps]
Your answer?
[wind howling]
[birds chirping]
[groans]
Hmm?
[snoring softly]
[SWORD MAIDEN]
It appears you are awake.
Tell me.
How did you find the experience,
sharing a bed with me and her?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Fine, I guess.
So I benefited from
the Miracle of Resurrection
by sleeping next to a virgin.
I see. So you've heard
about it before then.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes. I have.
[SWORD MAIDEN] Although, sadly,
unlike this young priestess,
I cannot be considered
pure anymore.
Was it goblins?
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Yes. It was about ten years ago.
I was captured
by a group of them.
[cries] I'm sorry.
This is hard to talk about.
Should I tell you
what they did to me,
after they took me
to their cave?
-I already know.
-I cried like a child,
screaming "It hurts! It hurts!"
over and over again.
I can still see, you know,
just a little.
It's blurry, but I can make out
the shape of your body.
Like a shadow,
that's how I perceive the world.
Suggestions of forms,
outlines of people
who seem like they might
slip away at any moment.
We're such weak creatures,
aren't we?
We humans.
I try not to let it show,
but I'm frightened.
Isn't that strange?
[chuckles]
I'm the Sword Maiden
and yet, I'm terrified.
I spend night after night
trembling with fear
and feeling
absolutely helpless.
Because this is the world
we live in.
No matter how much help we have,
it's never enough.
Though, I'm sure, no one else
would understand.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Really?
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Huh?
"Really?" he says.
[chuckles]
Is something funny?
You don't see
the absurdity of it?
I'm an archbishop,
the woman who defeated
the Demon Lord.
And yet I'm scared to death
of wretched little creatures
like goblins.
Please.
Will you help?
I don't know who else to ask.
[footsteps recede]
[door creaks open, closes]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER sighs]
-[PRIESTESS groans]
Huh? [shrieks]
I... I...
You didn't see anything,
did you?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah. Don't worry.
You don't have any scars.
[groans]
[PRIESTESS] What about you?
Your wounds were serious.
-Are they healed now?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
-[PRIESTESS] Goblin Slayer.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What?
Are you...
maybe pushing yourself too hard?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Why do you ask that?
It's just, well,
you seem different somehow.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No. Nothing has changed.
Okay. If you say so, I guess.
-[ARCHER] Here we are!
-Huh?
Good morning!
We heard you two were awake.
How are you?
Better?
Seems they healed up
well enough.
Those were some pretty
nasty wounds, though.
A close call.
Thank goodness the resurrection
was performed in time.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Hmm. Are all of you okay?
[ARCHER]
You're worried. How touching.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
How's the canary?
The bird is just fine.
Honestly, you were
much closer to dying
than any of the rest of us were.
Right? And this poor girl,
"Oh, no! Goblin Slayer!"
Blubbering.
She was a real mess.
What are you doing?
You promised
you wouldn't tell him that!
[ARCHER]
He needs to know these things.
Well, with the two of you
feeling better,
we should be able to continue
our exploration of the sewers.
Uh... Or perhaps
it would be better
to tend to our equipment
before proceeding.
Don't be ridiculous.
Obviously the first
order of business
-is filling our stomachs.
-Ah, yes, how thoughtless of me.
[laughter]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Wait. You mean
none of you have eaten yet?
That's right. We had a promise,
don't you remember?
After the battle, we'd all sit
down and enjoy a meal together.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Hmm?
And it's important to always
keep your promises.
Don't you think?
[singing]
[patrons chattering]
[SHAMAN] Ha-ha! I'm not sure
how much my belly can hold,
but I'm going to do my best!
[PRIEST]
There is nothing quite like
the simple joy of sharing
a meal with your companions.
[ARCHER]
You two see to your equipment
and get a little more rest.
We'll head back underground and
continue scouting the sewers.
-[PRIESTESS] Uh, but--
-With the shape your gear's in,
you'd be a liability down there.
We can't risk it.
I guess you're right. Thanks.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Thanks.
[villagers chattering]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Want me to carry that?
No, it's fine. I've got it.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
[PRIESTESS]
The others will be okay
down there without us, right?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
And, um, you feel fine?
No pain?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
Good.
Don't push yourself too hard.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
What's wrong?
[PRIESTESS] "What's wrong?"
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong is you seem
incapable of answering me
-with anything other than yeah!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I see.
-And not just today.
[PRIESTESS]
You say that all the time, too!
[GOBLIN SLAYER sighs]
I... I'll try to stop.
See that you do.
[giggles]
So, earlier you mentioned
there were some errands
you wanted to run?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yeah.
-[grumbles]
I'm going to look at weapons
and armor since mine
since mine were damaged
in the battle.
What are you going to do?
My chain mail got torn,
so I was hoping I'd be able
to find an armorer in town
who could repair it for me.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It'd be faster to replace it.
[PRIESTESS]
Maybe, but I'd rather not.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Why's that?
-Well, it's special.
You know what, this chain mail
is the first thing
you ever complimented me on.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
I guess you're right.
[BLACKSMITH]
This has a huge hole in it.
You'd be better off
buyin' a new one.
No. Please, sir. I'd really
prefer to have it repaired.
Yeah, Yeah.
You're the customer.
[coughs]
Mm-hmm!
Maybe I should do
a fitting, too.
Huh?
No! No, thank you!
-Mmm-- [grunts]
-[bag thuds]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I need these repaired.
[BLACKSMITH] Whoa.
A silver rank?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] It's leather
armor and a round shield.
I need it done
as soon as possible,
along with that chain mail.
Um, sure, but for a rush job,
the fee will be a bit higher.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] That's fine.
-[coins clink]
Oh! That ought to do,
thank you, sir.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'm going
to look at your swords.
This one.
It's a bit long,
but I'll shorten it myself
with your whetstone.
I'd choose another, sir.
Killing goblins is the only
thing that's sword's good for.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'll be using it
to kill goblins.
Uh...
[MERCHANT]
Fruit for the little one?
-[bell ringing]
-Hey, kids.
Who wants some tasty ice cream?
Nice and cold!
Get your ice cream here!
-[laughing]
-[PRIESTESS] Ice cream?
-I wonder what that is.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'm not sure.
But considering how many kids
are gathered around that stall,
it's likely something sweet.
[PRIESTESS]
Hmm?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Go ahead.
-Oh, really? Thank you so much!
[giggles]
[kids chattering excitedly]
-[boy] Look!
-[girl] Oh, it's sprinkles!
[gasps] Amazing!
It's so cold and sweet.
I've never had anything like it!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] It's good?
-Yes! Wonderful!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
Hmm...
So it's a type
of frozen dessert.
I've never seen
a spell like this.
How is it accomplished?
[MERCHANT] Well, it's
pretty fascinating, actually.
A scientist found
that adding a certain mixture
-freezes it right up.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Huh.
[MERCHANT]
So that got me thinking.
What would happen
if I froze up some milk?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see. That was very helpful.
Give me one. Keep the change.
[MERCHANT gasps]
Thank you, sir!
-[PRIESTESS chuckles]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What?
Nothing.
I've just always wondered
where you learned
all of those random facts.
Guess now I know.
[water trickling]
[PRIESTESS]
It's strange, isn't it?
No one here has any idea
that goblins are running around
right under their feet.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
[PRIESTESS] Though there were
those attacks in the city.
I'm sure plenty of people
were scared after that.
You know?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
When I was young,
there was a time when I thought
if I took a single step,
the ground would open up
beneath me and I would die.
It got so bad that eventually,
I was scared to walk at all.
Such a thing isn't impossible,
but it's not something
anyone ever worries about.
That was strange to me.
Plenty of people
laughed at me for it.
But eventually, I realized
I still have to walk,
no matter how scared I am.
Is that something
you still believe?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes. It is.
Even now, years later,
I'm still terrified.
I am thankful
that you're helping me.
But you know
you're not required to.
Hmm?
I told you, I'm going to do
whatever it is I want to do.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Did you?
-Don't tell me you forgot.
You know,
you are absolutely hopeless.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER chuckles] Sorry.
-I didn't ask for an apology.
[GOBLIN SLAYER laughs]
Sorry.
[PRIESTESS]
I sort of understand, though.
We can't help the things
we're scared of.
-[yelps]
-That's cold!
[sighs]
[gulps]
[whimpers]
We should probably be
on our way. Shall we head back?
[SPEARMAN]
There you are, Goblin Slayer!
You've got some nerve
summoning us here with a letter.
You're lucky I didn't
mention it to the Guild Girl.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Mention what?
-That you keep going on
overnight trips
with another woman.
[WITCH]
Calm yourself.
Remember, it was I
who was summoned, not you.
-Um... Hello.
-[WITCH] You seem well.
That makes me happy.
Yes! I'm fine.
We had some business
near this town,
so he came too.
Now...
-go on.
-Woman!
[grunts] There.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Thanks. This will do.
[SPEARMAN]
I'm not a delivery boy, damn it.
I'm not doing
any more errands for you.
[WITCH]
But why did you send for this?
You could have
bought it here. No?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I needed something very fine.
Nothing in this town would work.
I see.
Just what are you gonna use
this for anyway?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What else?
-Huh?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
To slay goblins.
♪
[UNCLE] He didn't
come back today, either.
-[COWGIRL] No.
-How many nights has it been?
Well, he did say
he had to go to faraway town.
I'm sure there's a reason
he's still there.
[UNCLE sighs]
He keeps going on quests
to slay goblins
without giving himself
time to rest.
Eventually,
that relentless drive of his
is going to be fatal.
-[COWGIRL] He'll be back.
-Huh?
He'll return, no matter what.
This is
a very important place,
both to him and to me.
-[UNCLE] Hmm...
-We'll see him again,
and I want to be here
when he gets back,
so he knows
I was waiting for him.
Beard-cutter,
you're armed to the teeth today.
But your whole look could use
a little more style, you know.
[PRIESTESS]
You could be right.
You know what,
we could get some feathers,
and stick a few of the plumes
in your helmet.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Not interested.
-By the way,
why aren't you carrying
a torch like usual?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
An open flame would be dangerous
for what I want to try.
So, what's this trouble
you mentioned?
[PRIEST]
Mm.
-Behold.
-[growling]
[PRIESTESS]
Wha-What is that foul thing?
[ARCHER] No idea. I guess
a giant, floating eyeball?
[PRIEST] As far as I can tell,
it is a creature of chaos.
[PRIESTESS] A creature
who must not be named.
It's a sort of cursed beast,
isn't it?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Who cares what's it's called.
Giant Eyeball is fine.
Even when faced
with a monstrosity,
you remain the same.
As you might imagine,
the creature is quite dangerous.
[clatters]
[roars]
[PRIEST] This evil eye can use
the power of Disintegrate.
It can cast Dispel as well,
which means that a single glare
would destroy
any dragontooth warrior
that I summon.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Disintegrate and Dispel?
That's troublesome.
[PRIESTESS] It looks like
it won't attack us
or even see us as long
as we don't enter the room.
That means,
I can still cast a Miracle,
as long as I stay
out here to do it.
[SHAMAN] But if we get close,
we'll be in its sights.
We'll have no time
to finish spells
before those
deadly beams hit us.
I'm at a loss.
We might as well be
twiddling our thumbs out here.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] No.
There's something I want to try.
Just remember, you promised
you wouldn't use
any water, fire, or poison.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I haven't forgotten.
Our location is well
outside of town now, right?
As much as we walked, yes,
we should be
a good distance away.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Then this
shouldn't be a problem.
[growling]
That's right, look at me!
[panting]
[SHAMAN] Drink deep
and sing loudly spirits.
Shout, dance,
and sleep like the dead.
Show me the dreams
of fire wine!
The monster is harmless
if its eyelids are closed.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right.
[ARCHER]
Orcbolg! What is that?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Flour, don't breathe it in.
My spell isn't going
to last much longer!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Shoot an arrow.
Hit any part of it.
Then immediately
cast Protection.
This relies on you.
-If you fail, we die.
-Got it!
Hear me,
O merciful Earth Mother.
Please protect us, the weak,
with your divine light
and the sacred power of nature!
Protection!
[SHAMAN]
Powder in an enclosed space.
-Don't tell me he's--
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Cover your ears
and keep your mouths open.
[grunting]
-[SHAMAN] Get down!
-[GIANT EYEBALL roars]
[PRIESTESS grunting]
[GIANT EYEBALL roars]
[debris clattering]
[thuds]
[SHAMAN]
You actually did it.
Sir Goblin Slayer,
might you explain what happened?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
When the coal miner told me
about the canary,
he mentioned something else.
When there's a lot of fine
powder in a confined space,
and then a spark,
it will catch fire and explode.
Such an attack
is a hassle to prepare.
There's the risk
that it will ignite too early.
Meaning it's usually
an impractical trick
to combat goblins.
Wait, you just rigged
an explosion!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes, but I didn't use water
fire, or poison.
I don't think that's
actually the problem here.
Know what? Never mind,
just forget about it.
But, um, what were
you going to do
if the flour
didn't actually explode?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] We'd shoot
an arrow from the hall
and then retreat until it let
its guard down again.
Then repeat this attack
until it died, finally.
I get it, so I'd be the one
stuck with all the work, then.
And we all know that
if you were to keep
running that scrawny body
of yours back and forth,
then you'd eventually
just disappear into thin air!
And when it's so obvious you're
the one who needs the exercise.
[SHAMAN]
What's that, now?
My plumpness defines me
as a dwarf!
[ARCHER] Get any fatter and
we can roll you down the hall!
[SHAMAN]
Bah!
[PRIEST]
Now that we're safe,
this is what's rather curious.
[dice clatter]