Ex.
[MANAGER] How are
the promotion exams going?
So far so good. We've got
one today and one tomorrow.
[gasps]
This applicant.
She's the one who's been working
with Goblin Slayer lately.
Remind me
who this Goblin Slayer is?
-Oh. That guy.
-Yes, that guy.
[MANAGER]
Forget I said anything.
[COWGIRL grunting]
-Good morning! Finally awake?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
-Everything okay?
-No sign of goblin activity.
That's not what I mean,
actually. I'm talking about you.
You collapsed as soon as you
got home from that quest.
I'm worried you're pushing
yourself too hard.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I rested for days.
Only three.
You need more than that.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It was just exhaustion.
Nothing to worry about.
Although, I was told
that my refusal
to take care of myself
is a problem.
By that priestess girl?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No, another adventurer.
Oh! So you're going out
with more people now?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Just once so far.
[COWGIRL] So far?
That makes it sound like
you plan on working
with them again.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Does it?
-Mm-hmm.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
[villagers chattering]
[footsteps echoing]
[sqeaking]
[shrieking]
[grunts]
-Kill it already!
-I'm trying, okay?
-[shrieking]
-[grunts]
Ouch. Are you all right?
It didn't get me.
I'll need this.
[grunting]
I can't get it to come out!
[rat hisses, roars]
Not good. What
do we do now? I can't--
Chief of Justice,
Lord of the Sword,
Ward of the Scale,
may your forces manifest!
Holy Smite!
[screeches]
-[sighs]
-It must be nice.
Miracles from the gods
make things a lot easier.
You know it's not that simple.
They only answer
my wishes once a day,
so the rest of the time, I'm--
[insects chittering]
[CLERIC screams]
Quick!
We need to run!
[gnawing, crunching]
[GUILD GIRL] You weren't able
to complete the quest,
so there's no reward.
I'm sorry.
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am.
And I think you'll probably
want to find somewhere
to wash up as soon as you can.
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am.
[WARRIOR] I've got to find a way
to get my sword back.
You're right.
Giant rats and insects aside,
it would be a waste
to leave it down in the sewer.
Well, yeah. But how am I
supposed to fight
those things without a sword?
-Do you have any money?
-I'm flat broke.
-Then what are we going to do?
-Get a loan maybe?
Going into debt's
not what we need right now.
Not money.
I thought I would see
if someone would let me
borrow their spare weapon.
-Who, exactly?
-No clue.
I'll go get this signed
while you finish up.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right.
Orcbolg?
What are you doing?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Unloading cargo.
That was quite a beating
you took. You all right?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I am.
I was distressed to hear that
you were asleep for three days.
You appear to be back
on your feet now, though.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes.
Please forgive me,
but there is a favor
I'd like ask of you, if I may.
-You see... How can I put this?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Just say it.
I wondered if you have any more
of that particular item?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What item?
-Scaly, here, wants cheese.
-He's been whining non-stop.
-I swear, for three solid days,
he's done nothing
but talk about cheese.
Will this do?
-[moaning]
-You can pay the guild for it.
[PRIEST]
Yes, certainly.
Thank you very much,
Sir Goblin Slayer!
-[ARCHER] So, Orcbolg.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What is it now?
Well, it's just...
I don't know if you've heard,
but we took on a new quest
surveying some ruins.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I see.
-So, um, you know,
it's possible we'll ask
for your help or something.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'll think about it.
[laughs]
You do that.
We'll be going now.
Why must you always
make things so complicated?
Just come right out
and ask him to join us.
-[ARCHER grunts] Shut up, dwarf!
-Oh!
I will shoot you!
Nectar!
-All done, thank you.
-Great! Have a nice day.
[SPEARMAN]
Lost your weapon, huh?
Yeah, that's not good.
I'd like to go back and
retrieve it, but I'm unarmed.
I was hoping somebody might have
a spare I could borrow.
Hey, look. I've got
plenty of spare weapons,
so I could lend you one and all.
But you're not strong enough
to wield them.
Weapons are tricky.
If you use one
that's not a good match,
you could get into
all sorts of trouble, yes?
Right. I know that.
I'm sorry.
Dumb question, I guess.
[WITCH]
Just a moment.
-[gasps]
-It's no sword,
but I believe this may help.
[WARRIOR]
A candle?
[WITCH]
Yes, indeed.
It's very useful
for finding things.
Ah. [gasps]
[giggles]
A marvelous item.
You see it grows hot when you
get close to what you seek.
I suppose, you could
sell it for cash
instead of using it,
if you want.
Oh, wow, that's really
generous of you.
-Thank you very much.
-Don't mention it, dear.
It's no trouble.
I'm simply happy to help.
All right, then.
Time to head out.
Well, I guess
I'll see you back home.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Okay.
I need some repairs.
[BLACKSMITH]
Aah! Again?
You're always
destroyin' my work.
You need to learn to be careful.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I am careful.
You ought to learn
about sarcasm, too.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'd like you
to procure a scroll, as well.
[BLACKSMITH]
Scrolls are hard to come by,
not to mention expensive.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Cost isn't an issue.
If some adventurer comes around
here lookin' to sell one,
then I'll buy it,
but I wouldn't go
gettin' your hopes up.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I understand. That's fine.
[PRIESTESS]
Goblin Slayer!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'm running into everyone today.
[PRIESTESS] I wanted to show
you something. Look!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
So you're obsidian-ranked now.
That's right! I had
my promotion exam yesterday.
I wasn't certain
that I'd get it,
but apparently, fighting an ogre
really gave me an edge.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see. Congratulations.
It's thanks to you.
Without all your help, I never
would've gotten this far.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I didn't do anything.
Of course you did.
You saved me
the first time we met.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Maybe.
The rest of your party
didn't make it, though.
I know. Still,
if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have
survived, either.
But I did, and I wanted
to thank you properly.
I can't tell you
how grateful I am.
And now, I'm going to
go to the temple
and tell Mother Superior
about my promotion!
Nope, not a chance.
I just lost my own sword,
so I have to use a loaner.
The boss would kill me if I
let somebody else borrow it.
Wow, you too?
What happened to it?
He had an unfortunate
encounter with a giant slug.
Those things are disgusting.
A giant slug, huh?
That's gross!
[CLERIC]
We're porcelain-ranked.
Those two are both silvers.
You can't compare us to them.
-[whines]
-[sighs]
You said you guys
were out hunting rats?
That's right.
My sword got stuck in one.
Look at that. I'm so jealous.
I want a two-handed blade.
-Like that great sword he has.
-[CLERIC] Don't be an idiot.
You'd collapse just trying
to hold that thing.
Not to mention,
it costs M-O-N-E-Y.
[whines]
Aw. You broke
the poor guy's heart.
You know,
if you talk to the guild,
they might be able to help.
[CLERIC] You think
they'd lend him a weapon?
[DRUID] No, I meant ask
how to slay those rats.
They could have some
useful suggestions.
[CLERIC] It can't really be
that easy, can it?
[voices chattering]
Oh!
Goblin Slayer!
-Pardon me.
-Oh, yes?
Uh...
[GUILD GIRL]
You're asking me for information
on how to slay giant rats?
Sorry, I'm afraid
it doesn't work that way.
We leave these sorts of things
for adventurers to handle
precisely because they're
so difficult to deal with.
-We're desperate, here.
-Anything at all would help.
Please, we're begging you!
Well, you may have already
thought of this,
but you could try
strengthening your defense
-with chain mail or other armor.
-Except we don't have any money.
You know, if it's advice
you're looking for,
perhaps another adventurer
would be the best person to ask.
-Huh?
-Uh...
[WARRIOR]
You mean, Goblin Slayer?
[GUILD GIRL]
Is that a problem?
-I don't think he'd help us.
-Yeah, um,
we've said some pretty rude
stuff about him before, so.
I wouldn't worry.
I'm not sure he even notices
that sort of thing.
[CLERIC]
He won't get mad?
[GUILD GIRL]
No. You'll be fine.
[voices chattering]
-[CLERIC] Excuse me.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] What is it?
We wanted to ask you something.
If you lose your sword,
what's the best way
to fight enemies?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Steal one from a goblin.
Okay, but we're
not fighting goblins.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Oh.
Have you ever used any weapon
other than a sword?
No.
And we don't have
any money, either.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] In that case,
how about a club?
-[WARRIOR] A club?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yeah.
Throw, stab, break, shatter.
There are plenty of ways to kill
a goblin besides using a blade.
Would it work on rats
and bugs, too?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Probably.
I'm sure being hit with one
would at least hurt them.
Plus, clubs don't get
nicked like swords do,
so the maintenance is easier.
Easier. A club, huh?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That's what I would do.
What do you mean
the observer can't come?
I guess there was
an incident on a quest.
Do you know someone else
who can do it?
Well, actually. I might.
[GUILD GIRL]
Goblin Slayer!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Are there goblins?
Not today.
But I was just-- No, wait!
Please don't leave!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] But you said
there were no goblins.
Yes, that's true.
And I know they're
your specialty, but...
does absolutely everything
have to involve,
you know... goblins?
[sighs]
[door creaks closed]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Keep it short.
-I will!
You see, I've found myself
a bit understaffed.
I was hoping you might fill in
for an observer
who can't make it today.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] An observer?
For a promotion exam?
[water lapping]
[CLERIC] I just think about
finding the sword,
and the candle's
supposed to react, right?
-Is it?
-Uh...
I think it feels warmer when
I point it in this direction.
Which means
my sword's that way!
[BOTH gasp]
[rats growling, crunching]
[WARRIOR]
Found them.
[hisses]
-[screeching]
-[grunts]
Bastard!
-[shouts]
-[rat grunts]
-Die! Die! Die!
-[rat squealing]
[rat screeching]
-Where's the other?
-It's gone.
So, what do you think
of the club?
Well, it's effective, at least.
A handful of good whacks
was enough to kill the rat.
Plus, it suits you
better than a sword.
Oh, shut up.
Uh...
[giggles]
All right, then,
if you're ready,
we will now begin
the promotion exam.
Yeah! I'm absolutely ready.
I say we skip past sapphire
and emerald
and go right to ruby.
No, scratch that. Just promote
me straight to bronze!
I'm sorry.
That's not how this works.
The leather armor
and boots you're wearing,
-those are new, right?
-Yep. They sure are.
Did you notice
the quality of the boots?
Not only are they well-made,
I had them altered
to fit me perfectly.
I find it interesting
that you're so much better
off than your peers,
considering the same quests
are available to everyone.
Oh, no, wait. I can explain.
It's just. I, um...
I was running kind
of low on funds,
so I had my family send me
some money, that's all.
-A lie.
-[gasps]
On the name of
the Supreme God, I swear,
what this man just uttered
was false, a lie.
[RHEA SCOUT]
Sense Lie!
The ability to see
through lies.
Damn it.
Curse these seekers!
Apparently, you just acquired
new gear in a raid at the ruins.
Oh! I think I understand
what happened.
While the others thought
you were scouting,
you found a treasure chest,
which you kept for yourself
until you could sell
the contents.
No, please. It's not as bad
as it looks, I swear!
I'm sorry!
[GUILD GIRL]
Absolutely unacceptable.
This sort of thing
is exactly what's led
to the widespread prejudice
against other rheas and scouts.
But since this is
your first offense,
demoting you to porcelain
and banning you
from adventuring in this town
should be sufficient.
Whoa! Hold on a second!
That's ridiculous!
You're not seriously
gonna kick me out
just for keeping
one little treasure chest
to myself, are you?
[gasps]
Are you some sort of imbecile?
An adventurer who would betray
the trust of his party
doesn't deserve the title.
You are hereby demoted on the
grounds of falsifying a reward.
You won't be removed from town,
but you may no longer work here.
Huh?
Don't go getting
any foolish ideas.
Hey, Goblin Slayer,
don't let them do this to me!
You've been out on quests,
you know what it's like.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Me? I'm just here to observe.
Nothing more and nothing less.
But you're one of us,
you're an adventurer, too.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes. Just like the people
you tricked and stole from.
[RHEA SCOUT]
Damn it!
-[RHEA SCOUT grunting]
-[screaming]
[grunting]
[running footsteps]
You'll regret this!
That isn't likely.
[flame whooshes]
-[gasps] That hurt!
-What's wrong?
The candle,
it's getting hotter
by the second.
[WARRIOR]
Good!
That means we're getting
closer to my sword.
[whooshes]
-Watch out!
-[gasps]
[CLERIC]
Careful!
-[chittering]
-[screaming]
[WARRIOR]
This way!
-How's the candle?
-It's still really hot.
Don't tell me it's inside
one of those things?
-What should we do?
-Get to the surface?
They'd just catch up to us
while we climbed the ladder!
We could jump into the water.
Sure, if we want
to get the plague!
[WARRIOR]
In that case...
[shrieks]
[insects chittering]
-Give me the lantern.
-What? Why?
Quick, use a miracle!
[chittering]
[shouts]
Now!
Chief of Justice,
Lord of the Sword,
Ward of the Scale,
may your forces manifest!
Now. Holy Smite!
[screeching]
[shouting]
-[grunting]
-[screeching]
[whimpering]
[yelling]
[panting]
[CLERIC]
Is it still alive?
-[club clatters]
-[CLERIC shrieks]
You stay there.
I've got this.
You've got something of mine
and I bet it doesn't
taste very good,
so... give it back!
[GUILD GIRL sighs]
That was scary.
Thank you so much
for your help, Goblin Slayer.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I didn't do anything.
Just being here helped.
I had some pretty bad
experiences
back when I was training
in the capital.
The place was full of men
who couldn't open their mouths
without a lewd remark
falling out,
like they had nothing better
to do than harass me.
I know what you mean.
The capital
was overrun with them.
And more often than not,
I would have to deal
with that type of thing
all on my own.
So, having someone I trust act
as an observer is wonderful.
I felt so much safer
knowing you were there.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Really?
-[GUILD GIRL] Yes, absolutely!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Are we done now? I'd like to go.
[GUILD GIRL]
Oh, of course.
If you go to the front desk,
they should give you
your compensation.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right.
Um. Please wait!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What is it?
Well, um...
It's just...
Good work today?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah, you too.
[GUILD GIRL sighs]
You did so well.
But still, I doubt we've heard
the last of that rhea.
[GUILD GIRL] There aren't enough
adventurers these days,
and what he did wasn't
necessarily illegal.
I hope he accepts his demotion
and takes on quests elsewhere
instead of giving up
and becoming a true criminal.
[MANAGER] Well, adventurers'
morality runs the gamut.
They can be anywhere from
lawful good to chaotic evil.
[GUILD GIRL] And as long
as they remain adventurers,
that's their choice to make.
-Thank you for everything.
-No thanks needed.
I was just doing my duty as
a priestess of the Supreme God.
It was my pleasure.
Do you suppose the God of Law
would think I handled
the situation correctly?
You know, it's funny,
but most of the time,
people don't understand justice.
It's pretty common nowadays.
[clears throat]
Justice is not about
striking down evil,
but making people aware
that evil exists.
Wow, what a beautiful way
of thinking about it.
It's easy enough to say,
harder to do.
Unless you're
the Sword Maiden, of course.
She's great.
She was one of the adventurers
who defeated the Demon Lord.
The Sword Maiden, a servant
of the all-powerful Supreme God.
I admire her so much.
All I have to do is see
through other people's lies.
It's not hard.
You still have work left?
I need to get started on the
paperwork for that demotion.
So, the guy in the helmet's
the one you like?
What are you talking about?
All right, fine.
So what if he is?
[MANAGER chuckles]
[MANAGER]
You always did have a soft spot
for the strong, silent ones.
[SPEARMAN]
To the brave adventurer
and the heroic recovery
of his lost sword!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[GUILD GIRL]
Adventurers tend to be
noisy and difficult
to deal with.
I've always wished more of them
were the stoic type.
But I think it's possible
he's a little too stoic.
[MANAGER] You seem to have
a lot on your plate.
I should let you get to work.
[GUILD GIRL] Yes. Time to get
my head out of the clouds.
-There are things to do.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'm back.
[gasping]
What are you--?
Um... Goblin Slayer!
What are you doing here?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What else?
I'm going to slay some goblins.
That quest listing,
it arrived on a parcel carriage
that had travelled
a great distance.
And it's specifically
asking for Goblin Slayer?
But who could it be from?
[dice clattering]