[water dripping]
-[stone door scraping open]
-[whimpering]
-[flames whoosh]
-[whimpers]
[chains clank]
-[male shouts]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[PRIESTESS]
I want to be an adventurer.
-[WOMAN] Good morning!
-[MAN] Everyone off your horses.
(villagers chattering)
[GUILD GIRL] And do you know
how to read and write?
I do. Those were skills
taught at the temple.
Perfect. Then please fill
this form out for me.
[MAN] How'd it go
with that manticore at the pass?
[WOMAN]
Eh, you know, it wasn't too bad.
[MAN 2] I hear the capital's
the place to go
if you're lookin'
to make some coin.
Apparently,
a demon lord showed up.
[MAN 3]
How strong are we talkin'?
Figure I could handle
a low-level one myself.
[laughter]
Okay, you're 15 years old.
And it says you've trained
to be a priestess?
That's right.
And now that I'm an adult,
I want to become an adventurer
and help out
as many people as I can.
Here. This will serve
as your guild identification.
Now, there are ten ranks
for adventurers.
Platinum is the highest rank,
following that is gold.
However, the highest-ranked
people you'll encounter
out in the field
are the silvers.
If you'll look at your tag,
you'll see it indicates
that you're a porcelain,
which is the lowest-ranked
among our adventurers.
This tells people
that I'm a beginner?
Correct, and should anything
go wrong on a quest,
it can also be a means
of identifying you.
-Hold on to it.
-Right!
Well, that's it
for your registration.
This board is
where quests are posted.
You're welcome to look
through them
for one that's suitable
for your rank.
Another option
would be joining
-a veteran adventurer's party--
-Hey.
We're gonna go on a quest,
do you wanna come with?
Yeah, she said
you're a priestess, right?
My adventuring party's
missing a healer,
but we've got
an urgent quest to tackle
and are looking to add
somebody with the right skills
and training
as soon as possible.
Will you come along with us?
I don't know.
What kind of quest is it?
Goblin slaying!
You're gonna go after goblins?
Sure are.
They attacked a village,
and as if stealing supplies and
livestock weren't bad enough,
they kidnapped
a few of the local girls too.
We need to rescue them
as soon as we can.
[GUILD GIRL] Um, you're all
porcelain-ranked, aren't you?
This'll be quite the challenge.
I'm sure if you wait,
there will be other adventurers
willing to take on the quest.
Oh, please.
The four of us can handle
a bunch of filthy goblins,
no problem.
-Can't we?
-Mm-hmm.
You in, Priestess?
Come on and make up
your mind already.
Okay, I'll go with you,
if you really think
I'll be able to help.
All right! We can finally go
on an adventure!
-Welcome aboard!
-Yeah! Great to have you!
[laughter]
[WARRIOR] Those goblins don't
stand a chance now!
[WIZARD]
Don't get too excited.
[FIGHTER] If things start to get
ugly, just leave it to me.
[crows cawing]
Oh. Uh...
[chuckles nervously]
Oh... Mm.
[crows cawing]
Um, is this a good idea?
I mean, just barging in?
Maybe we should head back
outside and plan some more.
Really? Now's when you decide
to back out of this?
[laughs] You don't need to worry
about anything.
Goblins are nothing.
They're the size of little
children and just as stupid.
They're basically the weakest
monster you can fight.
I even kicked a couple out of
my village once, all by myself.
I wouldn't be bragging
about that if I were you.
[WARRIOR] Ha! I'm sure we'll
be able to handle anything,
and after this quest
we're going to go kill a dragon!
[WIZARD] You're getting
ahead of yourself.
But, yeah, we'll
eventually get there.
One day, I'm gonna be
a famous dragon slayer!
-[grunting]
-[laughing]
Even if that idiot
can't cut them all down,
I'll kill them
with my bare hands.
I've got you covered.
Besides, she's a wizard
who graduated
from the Sages's Academy
in the capital.
-[PRIESTESS gasps]
-Hmm?
[harrumphs]
[WARRIOR] Okay. Less talking,
more exploring. Let's go.
Did any of you bring
potions along just in case?
-[WARRIOR] Nope.
-Huh?
We didn't have the time
or the money
to do much shopping
before we left.
Rescuing those
kidnapped girls takes priority.
Plus, we've got you to help.
You can heal us if we happen
to get hurt, right?
Well, I can pray
to the goddess
and ask for the miracles
of healing and light if need be,
but there are limits.
I can only use them
three times, so...
-Hold up!
-Huh?
[WARRIOR]
What the heck is this?
[FIGHTER] There was one
at the entrance, too.
[WARRIOR]
I know.
Hear me,
oh merciful Earth Mother.
Please offer us
your loving protection.
-Light the darkness.
-Come on, we're falling behind.
The other two ran up ahead and
I don't want to miss anything.
Right, I'm sorry.
[panting]
[distant clatter]
Jeez, what's the matter now?
It's just, I thought
I heard something.
[WIZARD]
Like what?
I'm not sure,
but it was behind us.
That's impossible,
we just came from the entrance
and didn't see anyone
along the way.
It's probably only
your imagination.
-[clatters]
-Huh?
-[growling]
-[gasping]
The goblins!
[goblins growling]
[whimpering]
-Huh?
-[growling]
Sagitta inflammarae... radius!
-[growls]
-[gasps]
-Firebolt!
-[goblin screams]
Hey, I got one!
Sagitta inflammarae radius!
-[growling]
-[whimpering]
No, don't!
Give that back!
-[growls]
-[gasps]
[growls]
-[grunting]
-[growling]
Get away from her, monsters!
[groans]
[screaming]
[WARRIOR grunts]
[yelling]
How dare you hurt her!
You're dead!
-Get over here!
-[whimpering]
[grunts]
Take that!
Hurry and perform
a healing miracle.
Of course! Hear me,
oh merciful Earth Mother.
Please lay your blessed hands
upon this child's wounds!
Heal her!
[grunting]
Monsters! I'll kill you all!
Stop swinging that thing around.
I can't get close!
You stay back there and protect
the rest of our group.
I'll take care
of these bastards!
What's the matter, you scared?
[screaming]
[yelling]
[grunting]
Die!
-[growling]
-Huh?
You're the next one down!
[sword tinging]
-[goblins roaring]
-[sword clangs]
[WARRIOR screaming]
-[whimpers]
-[squelching]
-[WARRIOR screaming]
-[gasping]
I don't understand.
I used healing on her,
but she's not getting better.
Take her and get out of here.
-But what about you?
-I can still fight!
[grunts]
[gasps, growls]
[cackling]
[FIGHTER grunting]
[yells]
[growling]
[grunting]
Let go... my leg!
[whimpering]
[crying]
[goblins cackling]
-[goblins growling]
-[FIGHTER screaming]
[whimpering]
Go. Take her.
Just forget about me and run.
[goblin grunts]
[cackling]
-[gasps]
-[whimpers]
[FIGHTER screaming]
[screaming continuing]
I'm so sorry.
-[staff clatters]
-[PRIESTESS gasps]
Forgive me!
Are you okay?
[groans, gags]
Why didn't you get better?
-[knife whirs, thuds]
-[screams]
[whimpering]
-[goblin grunts]
-[kick thuds]
[goblin grunting]
[goblins grunting excitedly]
[whimpering] Hear me,
oh merciful Earth Mother.
[sniffing]
[cackling]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[cackling continuing]
[GOBLINS]
Huh?
[heavy footfalls echoing]
[flames whoosh]
[shouts]
♪
[GOBLINS]
Huh?
[grunts]
[armor clanks]
[growls]
[goblin screaming]
[grunts]
Huh?
♪
[groans, screams]
-[flesh sizzling]
-[goblin screaming]
[body thuds]
That's one.
[goblin gasps, screams]
-[squelches]
-[groans]
[blood swooshing]
[PRIESTESS whimpering]
-[gasps]
-And that's two.
Who are you,
and where did you come from?
[whimpers, gasps]
♪
I am the Goblin Slayer.
Goblin Slayer?
[gasps]
Huh?
-Silver.
-Are you a rookie?
Yes. I am.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You can still talk. Good sign.
[whimpers]
[screaming]
Drink this.
It will help with the pain.
Thanks, but...
she needs it much more.
[gagging]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] No point.
-[gasps] Huh?
-She's poisoned.
-Aren't you too?
I have an antidote,
but it's too late for her.
-[gagging]
-[footsteps approach]
-[weakly] Kill... me.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] As you wish.
-[squelches]
-[gags]
[groans softly]
[breath shudders]
We might've been able to get her
out of here and save her!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
She would have suffered more.
Drink.
[gulps]
[coughs]
[gasps]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Is there a big one with them?
Yes, I think I saw one.
-He was strong.
-That was a hobgoblin.
They must have recruited one
as a guard.
I'm going to kill this horde.
-What will you do?
-I'll go, too. With you.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do you know spells?
I can perform the miracles
of Healing and Holy Light.
-How often?
-Only three times.
So, I can cast
two more spells in here.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right.
[squelching]
[whimpers]
Huh?
What are you doing to him?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] We have to get
rid of our scents.
[gasps]
-Get used to the smell of blood.
-I'll try.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Eight, nine.
♪
[gasps]
[sobs]
♪
[GOBLIN SLAYER] This is too long
to swing in a cave.
♪
I don't get it.
How did this happen?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Let me guess.
They attacked you from behind.
That's right.
[gasps]
But earlier,
how did we miss this
when we walked by?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It's a dark cave.
If all you have is a torch,
this entrance would just look
like a shadow on the wall.
And that's what
you were looking at.
♪
[GOBLIN SLAYER] It's a common
mistake for rookies.
♪
[GOBLIN SLAYER] These creatures,
they're not bright,
but they're not fools, either.
And this horde is being
led by a shaman.
-[PRIESTESS] A shaman?
-A powerful spell-caster.
-How many of you came here?
-There were four of us.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
The last one must be a woman.
Looks like they
dragged her in deeper.
We have to go save her!
[clattering]
[goblins growling]
[goblin grunts]
[grunts]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Ten.
Do you have an ability that
lets you see in the darkness?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Of course not.
I've just practiced.
The trick is to aim
where their necks should be.
That's insane.
How much have you trained?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
A lot.
You're leaving the sword?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
There's too much blood on it.
That was a scout.
We should go this way.
-Follow me.
-Right. Yes, sir.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Use Holy Light from here.
Once you're done, run back
towards the entrance.
-Okay.
-[growls] Do it!
♪
[breathes deeply]
Hear me,
oh merciful Earth Mother.
Protect us and bless us
with Holy Light!
[gasps]
[growling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Six goblins,
plus a hob, and a shaman.
[chanting spell]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
He dies first!
-Fall back!
-Okay!
[goblins roaring]
[panting]
-[growling]
-[panting]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
The light, again!
Oh merciful Earth Mother,
protect us as we go forward,
and bless us with Holy Light!
[roars]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Eleven.
[hobgoblin screams]
There will be others
coming for us,
but I'm all out of spells.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I know.
[goblins growling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
See ya.
Twelve. Thirteen.
[goblins screaming]
[coughs]
What was that?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Gasoline
I bought from an alchemist.
Wasn't very effective
for what I paid.
But the girls,
what if they get burned too?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] There were only
three goblin corpses,
the flames won't spread too far.
-They'll be fine.
-Are you going in there again?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No.
[goblins growling]
-[squelching]
-They probably think we ran.
They'll have no idea
I'm waiting out here for them.
[growling]
[foosteps echoing]
[gasps]
[breath shuddering]
You're gonna be okay.
It's safe.
They won't hurt you again.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Shaman.
-You can't fool me.
-[roars]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Eighteen.
These high-level ones are tough.
[debris clattering]
[PRIESTESS]
A secret door?
[crying, whimpering voices]
-[PRIESTESS] Children.
-They multiply quickly.
If this nest had been
left much longer,
there might've been a horde
of 50 waiting for us down here.
We were lucky.
-Are you going to kill them?
-Of course I am.
These animals hold on
to grudges for life.
The survivors in the nest
would learn from the mistakes
of the dead and adapt.
There isn't a single reason
to show them mercy.
But what if there
was a good goblin?
-They might exist.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Maybe.
If you looked hard,
you might be able to find one.
But in the end,
the only good goblins
are the ones who never show
their faces to the light of day.
[goblin children screaming]
[PRIESTESS sobbing]
[screaming continuing]
[screaming fades]
[PRIESTESS crying]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That makes 22.
[crying continuing]
♪
[PRIESTESS] Apparently, this is
a common occurrence.
A goblin horde attacks a village
and kidnaps any girls they find.
Rookie adventurers think slaying
them will be an easy quest,
only to end up being
slaughtered themselves.
If the girls are rescued,
they're traumatized from
being treated as playthings,
and usually end up
joining temples.
Sometimes
an adventurer survives,
but gives up the life.
Just disappears.
Tragedies like this happen all
too often in this harsh world.
But does it really
have to be this way?
I don't know the answer.
In the end, there are only
two things I'm certain of.
[doors creak]
The first is that,
despite what happened,
I'm still an adventurer.
And the second...
[gasps]
It's good to see you,
Goblin Slayer.
Um, I went and bought some armor
like you told me to.
It's chain mail.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That'll work.
Are you taking a quest?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'm killing goblins.
Are you coming?
Yes!
[rocks clattering]