[PRIEST] Now that we're safe,
this is what's rather curious.
It's possible this is
an object of worship.
Whatever the case, we should
take much care when touching it.
I agree,
but we should investigate.
[voice in mirror gasps]
-Huh?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Get ready.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Goblins.
[PRIESTESS]
What are we seeing?
[PRIEST] I believe this is
the goblins' home.
[ARCHER, gasps] Over there!
That's the boat we saw!
No wonder that thing
was guarding this.
The mirror must be
how the goblins
are getting into the sewer.
Ah, so then this must be
an ancient artifact
that's capable
of producing a gate.
A magical mirror that can invoke
long-forgotten spells.
I can't begin to imagine
what a valuable find this is.
If that's true, it means
someone's been
summoning the goblins.
And then supplying them
with weapons
and allowing them to live here.
Not to mention employing
that foul creature
to protect the gate.
An unexpected turn of events.
What should we do now
that we know, Goblin Slayer?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
So, it was goblins.
-[distant roar]
-[gasps]
-[sighs]
The explosion must have shaken
the depths of these ruins.
[ARCHER shudders]
[GOBLINS murmuring, panting]
♪
If this is the place
the goblins are using
as a portal between worlds,
then they must know
to protect it.
Which means now
they're all running this way
to kill the intruders.
Can't we catch a break?
Ugh! I'm over this already.
Goblin Slayer?
♪
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Remember,
"What is in my pocket?"
♪
Don't worry.
This won't be a problem.
[GOBLINS murmuring, growling]
[PRIEST growls]
[thuds]
[GOBLIN CHAMPION roars]
Hmm?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Can you fight?
-[ARCHER gasps]
Of course.
Worry about yourself.
Don't get knocked into a wall
like you did last time.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That's not my plan.
We have completed all of your
suggested preparations,
Sir Goblin Slayer.
The defenses are pretty
thrown together though.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It will do. Are you finished?
Yes. I've gathered all I can.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Good. How many
spells does our party have?
Well, uh,
I only have one remaining.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Don't cast it
until the moment I ask you to.
-All right.
-[PRIEST] I have two left.
If I do not summon
a dragontooth warrior to aid us,
I'll be able to use three.
But I assume you'd like
another fighter.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Correct. Give it a shield.
Have it protect the girl.
Understood.
And would you like me
to attend to the ancient mirror?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes.
[whooshing]
Pretty sure I could
muster two more spells.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] We'll need them
to finish the fight.
[SHAMAN chuckles]
Then I guess I'll assist you
until the time comes for me
to work my wonders.
[ARCHER] All things considered,
we're pretty lucky.
Three spellcasters
make for good odds.
Huh.
Even Long-ears has it in her
not be bratty
when it comes down to it.
Hold your tongue.
I'm never bratty,
you walking barrel!
[laughs]
[muttering, growling]
So, what am I supposed
to do in this fight?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Lure in
as many of them as you can.
Get them close,
then take them out.
Why am I always stuck
with the most dangerous job?
Oh, well.
Here they come.
[growling, muttering]
With these numbers, we won't
have to worry much about aiming.
[whooshing]
[BOTH groan]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] One.
-Beard-cutter, keep on slinging.
I'll make sure
you're well supplied.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That's my plan. There.
Two. Three.
Eight.
The swarm is too large.
[growling]
-And too many got through!
-Watch out on the right!
-I see them.
-Three from the left.
-Four in the middle!
-[ARCHER] Yeah, yeah.
[gasps]
[groans]
[arrow clatters]
-[PRIESTESS shrieks]
-[arrow clatters]
Aww! Well, aren't you
an adorable skeleton?
Uh, that isn't the word I'd use.
You bring me honor
by praising him.
Confound it!
How is this mirror attached?
It refuses to budge.
[inhales]
O hear me, proud
and strange Brontosaurus.
Give me the strength
of 10,000!
[shouting]
[growls]
-[roars]
-It's that huge one!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I'll handle him.
Don't leave the altar.
-[SHAMAN] You got it.
-[GOBLIN screams]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
[ARCHER]
Mm-mm.
[gasps]
Got him!
I need arrows, quick!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Huh?
[GOBLIN growls]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Pass them.
-Right away.
-Thanks.
-[SHAMAN] Mm.
[PRIESTESS]
Look out!
[SHAMAN grunts]
-You done, Scaly?
-Only a few moments more.
-I'll help you.
-[PRIEST] I'm grateful.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do you still need more time?
[GOBLIN CHAMPION roars]
I'm getting really
tired of this guy.
[growls]
-Huh?
-[GOBLIN champion roars]
-Orcbolg, wait!
[GOBLIN screams]
[SHAMAN] He's purposely luring
it into the goblin mob!
[ARCHER]
You truly are unbelievable!
Come on, Long-ears,
can't you shoot any faster?
[ARCHER]
Quiet, Dwarf.
I could if I had
better quality arrows.
[SHAMAN] Why don't you
just throw some rocks?
[ARCHER]
I'm not a barbarian!
Just one more push should do it!
[grunting]
[PRIEST shouts]
-[rumbling]
-[PRIESTESS shrieks]
The mirror is down!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Face it toward
the ceiling, and get underneath!
Right away!
[footsteps thudding]
[GOBLIN CHAMPION roars]
He's coming!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Dwarf, cast
a spell, towards the ceiling!
Up? All right.
Time to work, you crafty gnomes.
Mash grains of sand together
to form mighty rock!
-Orcbolg, quickly!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Thanks.
-What do we do now?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Use Holy Light!
Okay. Hear me,
O merciful Earth Mother.
Protect us and bless us
with Holy Light!
[growls]
-[SHAMAN] Stone Blast!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Bring it down!
Spin your buckets,
crafty gnomes!
Turn upside down
and spill to the ground.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] And that...
-Falling Control!
-[glass shattering]
-[rocks clattering]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
...makes 53!
[wind blowing]
[debris clattering]
[ARCHER groans]
[gasps]
-We're okay.
-[ARCHER panting]
[ARCHER] No thanks to
Mr. Strategic Genius over there.
Was that your plan, Orcbolg?
[PRIESTESS]
It was a little scary.
-That's all you have to say?
-I guess, I mean,
I think I'm getting used
to this adventuring thing.
-[whines] This isn't normal.
-[PRIEST] My heavens.
We had the gate mirror
to protect us, thankfully.
It absorbed most of the debris
and falling rubble,
though it did prove
to be rather heavy.
Yes. You held most of the weight
back there, Scaly.
I almost feel bad for
the unsuspecting creatures
on the other side.
I wonder if this is how people
traveled long distances
in the olden times.
Eh, Beard-cutter?
What do you think?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I don't know.
-We're very lucky
we weren't underneath
the city when we did that.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
If we had been,
I would have thought
of another plan.
-So...
-What is it?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] No fire, water,
poison or explosions.
True.
Do you want a little reward?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What?
-[ARCHER grunts]
-[PRIESTESS shrieks]
-[ARCHER scoffs]
-Are you okay down there?
[wind blowing]
[waterfall splashing]
-[rustling]
-[gasps]
I'm happy
you've returned safely.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I have a question.
Yes? What would you like to ask?
If it's within my power
to answer you, I will do so.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You knew what was down there.
-Didn't you?
-[SWORD MAIDEN gasps]
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Yes. You're exactly right.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
[SWORD MAIDEN]
But how did you figure that out?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I didn't.
I planned to ask everyone who's
in a position to know the truth
until I was satisfied.
Oh.
Well, then,
I gave myself away.
Perhaps in the future, I will
learn to be less forthcoming.
It is somewhat flattering
you'd ask me first.
I assume you had your reasons.
May I ask why you suspected me?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Several reasons.
The white beast.
What was it called?
[SWORD MAIDEN]
The alligator?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes, that's the one.
I don't believe it was
an accident we encountered it.
[SWORD MAIDEN] You're suggesting
someone controls it?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It tried to chase us away, yes.
But it also attacked
the goblins.
Listen to you.
Are you observant
or simply paranoid?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Well, despite
how elaborate the ruins are,
you provided no precise maps.
And there are
no rat-killing quests.
In fact,
adventurers avoid the sewers.
But something was
patrolling down there.
You seem rather knowledgeable
about our adventurers.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I did my research.
[SWORD MAIDEN sighs]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Back to the point:
I knew something had to be
guarding the sewers.
That creature...
it's your familiar.
Shameful, isn't it?
That the messenger
of the Supreme God
should protect the city,
and the city alone.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You must have known.
Killing women, ripping out
entrails on the street,
and then leaving
the corpses behind--
that's not what goblins
usually do.
Indeed.
[SWORD MAIDEN] They bring
their prey back to the nest,
so they can toy with them.
Death is not something
that comes quickly.
The minions of the Demon Lord
were doing
their master's bidding.
They were plotting to do
something with the mirror.
But now their lord...
no longer exists.
Thanks to a hero
in an entirely different place,
and in another time.
And yet, if goblins
were to attack me here,
I would surely break.
I would not fight, only weep.
I knew they were moving
under the city.
And I'd heard that
the Evil Sect was to blame.
They long for revenge.
I could face that,
but not goblins.
But, then, who could I tell?
I'm the Sword Maiden after all.
How could I ask for protection
from mere goblins?
No one would take me seriously.
So, what now?
What will you do with me?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Nothing.
-[gasps]
Because you're not a goblin.
[SWORD MAIDEN] Is that why
you're not going to ask
for my motives?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] If you want
to talk, I'll listen.
I longed for understanding.
[wind whooshing]
I wanted people to know my fear,
and that the world is a painful,
terrifying place.
They need to know
what to be afraid of
and that no one is safe.
There is much malevolence and
such atrocities in this world.
But in the end,
no one gave a second thought
to the goblins.
You may have the gate mirror
if you like.
Just tell me you understand.
Of all the people
on this planet, surely you do.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I got rid of the mirror.
[gasps]
That was an ancient relic,
a priceless treasure
worth a fortune.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Best to get rid of it
before other goblins learn
how to use it.
We encased the mirror
in concrete
and sank it in the canal.
It'll make a good bed for...
whatever you call
that white beast.
[SWORD MAIDEN gasps]
[laughs softly]
Naturally,
you never cease to amaze me.
I dare say
you may be unstoppable.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Perhaps.
[SWORD MAIDEN] Please,
may I ask you one more thing?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I can't promise an answer.
Has anything changed
since you started
slaying goblins?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Like what?
If the hero is able
to slay the Demon Lord,
we know the world
can be kept safe from harm.
But if the 15-year-old girl
who was attacked by goblins
is still looking for deliverance
after all these years,
no one even notices.
No matter how many goblins
are slain in this land,
the terror is still alive in me.
I want to know
how to change that.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I don't know
that you need to.
[gasps]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You said you went through
something horrible.
That's right.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I've seen what they do,
-from start to finish.
-That means--
[GOBLIN SLAYER] But I can't give
you a solution.
[SWORD MAIDEN] So you can't
offer me salvation?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No.
But...
if any more goblins appear,
call for me.
I'll kill them for you.
[gasps]
[sobbing]
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Even if they're in my dreams?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
[SWORD MAIDEN]
You promise? You'll come?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
Because I'm the Goblin Slayer.
[gasps]
Thank you.
I... This is... I'm sorry.
[sobs]
Goblin Slayer...
I cherish you.
♪
-[footsteps approach]
-Hmm?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'm done.
[PRIESTESS] Thank you
for reporting back to her.
[wagon clattering]
[groans, sighs]
Well, that was a fun one.
You were crying
like a newborn babe
when the goblins surrounded you.
-Or did you forget that part?
-[ARCHER] Let me have this!
We took out their portal,
survived and won!
Plus, we even got
a decent reward.
Yes. I can't help but feel that
the gate mirror went to waste
when we threw it
into the canal.
However, we gathered
vital information
and destroyed a heresy.
Our deeds were quite valorous.
I'm satisfied with our work.
Well, I've got no complaints
as long as I can use this
to buy
a delicious feast soon.
Predictable.
All dwarfs care about is food.
[PRIESTESS giggles]
Huh?
-[wagon clattering]
-[grunting]
-[canary singing]
-Huh?
Things turned out
all right, huh?
Good work, Goblin Slayer.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I was thinking.
-Really?
You should have told me
that you weren't asleep
in the first place.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I just woke up.
Well, how was
I supposed to know?
You're always wearing a helmet.
- [GOBLIN SLAYER] I see.
-[giggles]
[gulping, sighs]
When we get back,
there's something
I'd like to make.
A new kind of weapon,
I'm guessing.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Ice cream.
-[PRIESTESS laughs]
An iced cream?
Would it be too much
of a bother for me
to join you
in this frozen treat?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] If you want.
It's made with milk.
-[PRIEST] Oh! Sweet nectar!
-[thumping]
[gasps]
[PRIESTESS] Sorry about that!
We're fine back here.
[SHAMAN]
Come now, Beard-cutter.
You should rely upon this dwarf
for all culinary matters.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Is that so?
-I'm an expert.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Then I will.
-[chuckles]
[SHAMAN]
So, how is it made?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Like this, I believe.
Sir Goblin Slayer,
if you need to spin something,
I believe a stool
that uses a pedal
to rotate a bowl
would be effective.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see. Makes sense.
I want to help make it too!
After all, I plan
on eating a lot of it.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sure.
Oh?
[GROUP chuckling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What about you?
[gasps]
I guess I'll taste it. Why not?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Don't kick me
if it turns out bad.
[ARCHER grumbles]
[ARCHER]
You're still sore about that?
Just give me
some stupid ice cream!
I won't hurt you.
Satisfied?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
[dice clatter]