[COW GIRL]
Hey!
I’m gonna go into the city.
One of the cows
on my uncle’s farm
is giving birth
and I wanna be there.
I’m going all by myself!
After that,
I even get to go shopping!
I can’t wait to see what they
have at all the stores!
My mom even gave me money
to buy something!
I wonder what all
I should get.
Is there anything you want me
to look for?
I’d love to buy you a gift--
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No.
Oh, are you sure?
There’s gotta be--
I just told you
I don’t want anything.
You don’t have to be mean
about it.
I just wanted to do
something special.
Since you’ve never been
to the city before.
‘Cause that’s what friends do.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Shut up.
Just go to the city or whatever
it is you’re doing.
Why are you so angry?
-I’m not angry.
-Yes, you are!
-Calm down.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Sis.
The two of you
shouldn’t be fighting.
[GOBLIN SLAYER ] We weren’t.
We were only talking.
-Right?
-Sure. That’s right.
[OLDER SIS]
You’re sure you’re okay?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah, it’s nothing.
[OLDER SIS]
All right then.
If you say so.
[COW GIRL MOM] Please take
good care of her for me.
[COW GIRL UNCLE]
I will.
How long are you
going to pout for?
I thought you were looking
forward to going into the city.
[COW GIRL]
Yeah, but...
I wanted to go with him.
Or, if he couldn’t come,
I wanted to buy him something.
But then he got really angry.
And for no reason, either.
[COW GIRL UNCLE] I’m sure
the boy wanted to come as well.
Think of how he must feel.
Did you two make up?
If not, you should
when you get back.
[COW GIRL] I wanted us
to not be fighting.
I wanted to apologize.
But, sometimes it can be hard
to say you’re sorry.
[COW GIRL]
Even now.
It’s not easy.
[yawns]
Hey, there!
Morning!
I see you’re up early again.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
[COW GIRL]
The weather’s so nice today.
The sun feels great on my skin.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
Do you know if my uncle
is awake already?
-I don’t know.
-Oh, well.
If he isn’t around by now, then
I’m sure he will be pretty soon.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
S’pose so.
You must be hungry.
I’ll go start on breakfast.
We can eat together.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sounds good.
[COW GIRL]
It’s the same thing every day.
Goblins usually move around
at night
and return to their nests
in the morning.
So, at dawn, he checks
our land to see
if he can find
any footprints.
Goblins always scout the area
they plan to attack,
so any disturbance is
a warning of trouble.
If he sees any sort of tracks,
then we’ll know to be
extra careful for a while.
He always checks the fence, too.
Just to see if there are any
parts that have come loose
or been damaged
since the day before.
‘Cause, of course,
that’s a bad sign.
If anything is broken,
he makes the repairs himself.
He keeps our farm
and everyone in it safe.
Our valiant guardian.
It’s been this way
for five years,
since he first
came to stay with us.
His daily routine.
And, here you go!
[COW GIRL UNCLE]
Smells good, as usual.
-Thank you.
-Eat it while it’s still hot!
Huh?
[GOBLIN SLAYER slurps]
Taste good?
I hope you like it.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
-[slurping]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Here.
Rent money.
It’s heavy this month.
Being an adventurer must
be pretty lucrative.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sometimes.
I’ve had a lot of work lately.
[COW GIRL UNCLE]
Apparently.
Right, so, will you be
going out again today?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes. I’m visiting the guild.
They’ve got plenty of work.
Not surprised.
Well, don’t push yourself
too hard.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I won’t.
Hey!
I need to make a few deliveries.
I should go with you!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
If you’d like.
Well, in that case,
I’ll go get the wagon
ready for you.
[COW GIRL] Don’t worry, Uncle.
We’ll be fine.
I know how overprotective
you can be.
I’ve got this.
I’m a lot stronger than I look,
you know.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do you need help?
I’m fine.
It’s not that hard.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Okay.
-[COW GIRL] Thank you, though.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It’s nothing.
So, how have things been lately?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Too many goblins.
Really?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
An unusual amount.
-You must be busy.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yeah.
You have been going
out more, much more.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah.
Having lots of work
is a good thing.
-You make more coin.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] No. It’s bad.
What do you mean?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] It’s better
when there are no goblins.
[COW GIRL]
Right. Of course.
[MAYOR]
Please, you gotta help me.
Those goblin critters
came to my village.
If somethin’ don’t happen,
they’ll eat my cows
an’ burn my fields to ashes!
So you need an exterminator.
No problem.
I’ll just need your completed
form and payment.
Yes.
Of course, ma’am.
Here you are.
Seems like everything
is in order.
I’ll just have to count out your
payment to confirm the quest.
Two. Four. Eight. Ten.
Twelve.
Great.
Looks like it’s all here.
So rest assured an adventurer
will come out to your farm
to take care
of the problem soon.
Is it really true those
little monsters treat women
like their playthings,
and then eat ‘em up afterwards?
Well, yes, there have been cases
reported of that happening.
[GUILD GIRL sighs heavily]
Another goblin quest?
That makes three already.
What’s the pay?
Welp.
Hope they don’t want someone
with experience.
‘Cause that’s pretty pathetic.
[GUILD GIRL]
No, he'll still take it.
Money’s not an issue to him.
Thanks for the prompt delivery.
[COW GIRL]
No problem!
It was my pleasure.
I need to get a signature over
at the reception desk.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right.
Get this.
There was this troll, right,
a huge sucker.
But I was able to
dodge his attacks.
Got ‘em with my spear
before he knew what hit him.
[GUILD GIRL]
Oh, wow. Nicely done, sir.
I’m well-aware that trolls
are powerful foes
and that I should
be impressed by this.
I took down a troll with nothing
but my bravery and a spear.
I’m not bragging,
it’s just true.
Uh-huh. If you’re feeling tired,
I’d recommend this.
Our new stamina potions
are best-sellers here.
I’ll take whatever
you’re selling.
[gasps]
Ah! The Goblin Slayer?
[MALE ADVENTURER]
That’s him?
[ELF] He’s the weirdo who only
takes goblin-related missions.
That big idiot gives
silver-ranks like us a bad name.
If all he hunts is goblins,
I doubt he could
handle anything bigger.
I’m surprised
they even ranked him up.
Just ignore that guy.
Our paths’ll never cross.
I know!
What a slob.
I’ve never seen
such filthy armor before.
[ROOKIE MAGE]
Even our equipment
is better than
what he’s carrying.
[ROOKIE CLERIC WARRIOR]
Don’t be so judgmental.
He must still be a rookie,
just like us.
I’d feel bad if he heard you.
[thud]
Good morning, everyone.
Who’s ready to see all
the available quests today?
[ALL]
Yes, finally!
Come on!
I want to slay a dragon.
Heroic feats like that are the
fastest way to gain experience.
There’s no way.
You don’t got the equipment.
How ‘bout you just stick
to taking out bandits.
That usually pays well, too.
Man, look at these awful
porcelain-ranked quests.
They hardly pay anything.
And I don’t wanna have
to clean ditches.
You can’t be too picky
when you’re just starting out.
Oh, hey.
What about that one there.
Goblins are easy, right?
Sounds like a good rookie
quest for us.
[APPRENTICE CLERIC]
No way.
You heard what the Guild Girl
told us.
We should start with the sewers
and work our way up.
Move, kids, let the real
adventurers through.
You idiot.
Don’t push.
The big quest is ours,
little spearman.
Look somewhere else.
That’s no way to talk to the
greatest warrior in the room.
[chuckles]
[GUILD GIRL]
Please, settle down, everyone.
There’s no reason to fight
amongst yourselves.
[COW GIRL] He’s not even gonna
go look at the quests?
He did say
there’s no reason to rush,
since none of
the other adventurers
like killing goblins.
Sir.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Hello.
About what I was saying
to you a few days ago.
I still don’t think
it’s a very good idea
to use flammable liquids,
especially if it’s in a cave.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Your thinking is flawed.
What would you prefer: that we
just let the goblins live?
[PRIESTESS]
Well, no, of course not,
but think of the consequences.
What if you caused
an avalanche or a cave in?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] The goblins
are a bigger problem.
[PRIESTESS] I know they are,
but every cause has an effect,
and we’ve got
to consider the risks.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I see.
Please at least try
to find another way.
[COW GIRL]
He said he’d formed a party
with someone
about a month ago,
but I didn’t think
it’d be with a girl.
And, also,
when we’re covering up
our scents,
can we use something
besides blood?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No. What times of day
do we usually attack goblins?
Um, early morning,
or early evening.
[giggles]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Tell me why.
Because early evening for
goblins is early morning for us.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Correct.
So, their afternoons are
the middle of our nights.
That’s when they’re
most guarded.
Next, what are the steps
to approaching them?
[PRIESTESS]
Uh, well, if possible,
we’ll smoke them out with fire.
That’ll throw off
their defenses.
Plus, it’s dangerous
inside their nests.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That’s right.
The only reasons
we would ever enter a nest are:
if there’s no other way,
or we’re certain
we can kill them all.
Well done.
Oh, good morning Goblin Slayer,
it’s so nice to see you.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Are there
any quests that involve goblins?
[GUILD GIRL]
Ah, yes, of course.
We have three goblin quests.
There’s a swarm in
the western river village.
And a small nest
in the southern forest.
And then, an old mountain fort
that’s been claimed by goblins.
That one will be really tough.
It’s a castle
that’s been fortified.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
They’ve settled there?
Yes. And there’s been
a few casualties.
The younger sister of the person
who requested help
was kidnapped.
No one’s heard
from the adventurer
who went into the castle
to find her.
He’s completely disappeared.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It’s too late for them.
But I can kill the goblins.
That will prevent further deaths
at their hands.
[GUILD GIRL] We’ll be counting
on your success, then.
I wish you the best of luck.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
One last question.
Did anyone else
take goblin-slaying quests?
[GUILD GIRL] Yes, a party
of rookies went off on one.
They’re headed
to the river village.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What was their party like?
Um...
One warrior, a wizard,
and a priest.
Each porcelain-ranked.
Like I said,
they were all pretty new.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Not a bad balance.
[PRIESTESS] If it’s the three
I heard earlier,
they’re in way over their heads.
Even my party had four members.
Yes, I did try
to explain that to them.
They’re going to die.
We have to stop them
from going there.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do as you please.
I’m going to destroy
the mountain castle.
You’re going to abandon them?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] If you believe
you can save that group,
feel free to try.
[PRIESTESS] But that would mean
you’d have to face
this horde of goblins
on your own.
That’s far too dangerous!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That wouldn’t be anything new.
I’m just saying this seems
way too risky.
Honestly.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Are you coming?
Of course!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I’m going out.
Oh. Okay.
Please be careful.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Get home safely.
[door opens]
[COW GIRL]
I waited for him,
but he didn’t
come back that night.
Or the next one.
All I could do was wonder
what he was doing,
and if he would return.
You’re going to have a hard
time tomorrow
if you stay up too late.
I know.
Just a little while longer.
Then I’ll head to bed.
[wind blowing]
[evil laughter]
[growling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Think about
how it would feel.
If your home was suddenly
attacked by monsters,
without any warning.
Picture it.
They show up out of nowhere,
and before you know it,
they’re obliterating
your village.
They burn and destroy
whatever they want.
They kill your friends.
And your family.
Then they plunder what’s left.
[blood splatters]
Now, imagine if your
older sister was attacked.
She’d be tortured, forced to
endure unspeakable things,
and then finally, killed.
Let’s say you witnessed
all of this firsthand.
Holding your breath
in a hiding spot.
Waiting to die.
[sobbing]
[GOBLIN SLAYER] There’s no way
you’d forgive them.
You would take up weapons
and devote your entire life
to getting revenge.
You’d hunt the monsters
down one by one.
You’d kill obsessively, your
hands always smelling of blood.
[ROOKIE MAGE]
Look, we made it.
[ROOKIE SWORDSMAN]
Finally.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Some days, you’d be successful,
and on others, you would fail.
You’d try to figure
out the best way
to kill them
the next time.
This would be the only thing
that occupied your mind.
You’d test every idea you came
up with, no matter how absurd.
And against your better nature.
You’d start to enjoy it.
[growling]
A naive person might suggest
you let the children live.
But she’s not thinking about
how they’ll grow up
to attack the villages,
stealing women and livestock
to survive.
You’ll watch young,
aspiring adventurers.
Those with new porcelain ranks,
who will think,
“I chased away a goblin
that came to my village once.
They’re weak.
easy to deal with.”
These rookies won’t realize
that the goblin
they proudly chased away
was likely an injured Wanderer
whose horde has been destroyed.
Still, this gives the young
adventurer false confidence.
Meanwhile, goblins that survive
an attack gain experience.
They become Wanderers
and grow stronger.
Eventually, the Wanderers
become bodyguards,
or leaders of new nests.
In a way,
I am, in turn,
a monster to them.
I know you’re worried,
but you need to remember,
that the only reason
I allow him to stay here
is because he pays us so well.
He may have been your
childhood friend back then,
but he’s not that boy anymore.
-[metal clinks]
-Huh?
[COW GIRL UNCLE]
Look, the truth is...
He’s completely lost it.
You know that, but you
choose to ignore it.
I understand.
But I’m still going to wait.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That makes five.
[snarling, growling]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
They’re on their way.
Right. I’ll start.
Hear me, o merciful
Earth Mother.
Please protect us,
the weak,
with your divine light
and the sacred power of nature!
Protection!
[grunting]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That’s quite a useful
new miracle you’ve been granted.
Six dead.
The rest will most likely
burn inside.
Yes. It just seems wrong to use
the miracle
the Earth Mother bestowed
upon me in this way.
To do harm to other
living beings.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
They might have a back door
or another escape route.
Stay on guard.
I can’t believe that’s what
you’re thinking about right now.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Imagination is a weapon.
Those who lack it
are the first to die.
[PRIESTESS] Just like the ones
who take quests
without considering
the consequences.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Precisely.
[PRIESTESS]
Great Earth Mother.
Why did you bestow
this miracle upon me?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] Now we don’t
have to extinguish the fire.
When it dies out,
we’ll hunt down those
who survived the blaze.
We can’t let
any of them live.
Not everyone may appreciate
what you do,
but you save so many lives
by hunting
those disgusting monsters.
I hope you’re as proud
of yourself as I am.
Not just anyone can become
a silver-ranked adventurer.
[grunts]
[screeches]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Just as I suspected.
I’m not what they expect
of a silver rank.
Morning!
Thanks for your patience,
everyone.
I’ll now be posting all the
available quests for today!
[MAN]
Time to make some coin.
-[door opens]
-Huh?
Hmm?
[COW GIRL]
Welcome back.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Thanks.
How about something to eat?
I can get a quick lunch ready.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sure.
[COW GIRL] I’ll make this one
extra delicious for you.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Great.
The Goblin Slayer swung his
blade fierce wretchedness
and now would purify.
Goblin corpses he cut through
as their heads flew high.
O, courageous warrior
with a sword
that’s tempered
in perfect silver.
Never will the blade
betray its purpose or its way.
Wielded by a master
who will wander for always.
And finally, the goblin
king’s reign comes to an end.
Relieved to be free,
the beautiful maiden
leans in for a kiss.
However, he is
the Goblin Slayer.
Sworn to wander,
spilling monsters’ blood,
never to settle down.
The princess reached out
but found only air.
Following destiny
the Goblin Slayer
left without looking back.
[song ends]
That’s “The Stronghold
Up in Flames”
from “Goblin Slayer: The Brave
Warrior from the Frontier.”
-Thus ends our tale for now.
-[applause]
[WOMAN]
Sir.
That adventurer you were
singing about.
Does he really exist?
Why, yes.
Of course he does.
You’ll find him living
in the frontier city
which is about two
or three days’ ride to the west.
[WOMAN]
Thanks.
[gasps]
So we’ve found Orcbolg.