[NARRATOR] Long, long ago,
when the world was darker
and the sky lit by fewer stars,
the gods of light, order,
and destiny
and the gods of darkness,
chaos, and chance
vied to see which side
would be granted dominion
over the world.
Their struggle was played out
not in battle
but with the roll of the dice.
Their game continued for ages.
The gods rolled the dice over
and over and over again,
until they grew weary
and tired of their contest.
-Oh, wow. Look at her!
-Down boy.
Right. I'm sorry.
It looks like she's a high elf.
They're direct blood descendants
of the fairies.
Those ears,
just look how long they are.
Much longer than other elves.
-Where can I find Orcbolg?
-Oak? Like the tree?
No. Orc, as in "Orc."
Orcbolg.
I heard that he was here.
Are you referring
to an adventurer?
You fool. We're in the realm
of the humans now.
Your fancy long-ears talk
isn't going to help.
Oh? Then what exactly
should I call him?
His proper name, of course:
Beard-Cutter.
Sorry, there's no one here
by that name, either.
There isn't?
You dwarves have
as much imagination
as the rocks you work.
Always convinced you're
the ones who are right.
Ha! And what do you know
of the world?
With a heart as small
as your chest is flat.
At least I'm not barrel-shaped
like your dwarf women.
-I think you mean voluptuous!
-Now, please.
-Uh...
-If your quarreling isn't over,
I beg of you,
kindly go elsewhere
and spare the rest of us.
If my companions have
caused you trouble,
-I apologize.
-It's fine. I'm used to it.
[GUILD GIRL] Still, this is
quite an odd party:
A high elf traveling
with her ancestral foe, a dwarf,
and a member of the rarely
glimpsed lizardman race.
Plus, they're all silver-ranked.
As my comrades have said,
the one we seek is known
by the names Orcbolg
and Beard-Cutter.
Sadly, the human tongue is not
my specialty, but translated...
I believe he is known
as the Goblin Slayer.
-[GUILD GIRL] Oh! Goblin Slay--
-Hmm?
-[footsteps approach]
-[armor clinking]
Wait! Hold on!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] We're done.
-That's wonderful!
-Welcome back, Goblin Slayer!
-[gasping]
Our quest was successful!
I'm glad to see
you're both safe.
Well, more or less.
You were talking about goblins.
Where are they?
Um, well... ask them.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Are you goblins?
Of course we're not.
But are you Orcbolg?
‘Cause you certainly
don't look it.
Why would I?
I've never been called that.
Sir Goblin Slayer, if we might
have a moment of your time,
there is something we would like
to discuss with you.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Fine.
-In that case,
we do have some meeting rooms
available for use upstairs.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Let's go.
Um, should I come
along with you?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
You need rest.
Don't worry.
We'll have him back soon.
[patrons chattering]
[sighs]
-Um, priestess?
-Yes?
Look, why don't you join us?
You're porcelain-ranked,
too, right?
Oh. It's very kind
of you to offer,
but I'm already
working with some--
Yes, the brooding one
who never removes his helmet.
We know that, but something
seems off about him.
He's silver-ranked,
but all he ever wants to do
is kill goblins.
Silvers would usually go
for bigger prey than that.
[CLERIC] I've heard that he's
just dragging beginners
around to use as goblin bait.
-That's not true!
-Now, now.
You're not spreading
rumors, are you?
[WARRIOR] I'm just trying
to warn her about him.
[WITCH]
How noble. You go on.
I'll take it from here. Okay?
Now, dear. Tell me,
You're travelling with
the helmed one, is that true?
It is, ma'am,
when he allows it.
(chuckles)
[WITCH]
When he allows it, hmm?
That man,
he seems like a handful.
Rather dense, too, yes?
Inflammarae.
That's a powerful word
to throw around.
You think I'm wasting
a spell, hmm?
The thing is, dear, your friend
asked a strange favor of me
-once upon a time.
-(gasps)
You're imagining something
naughty, aren't you?
No. I'm not.
Apparently,
he required assistance
with a certain scroll.
It's hard,
travelling with a man
like that, is it not?
A bit.
It's taking everything I have
just to keep up with him.
And all I do is
cause him trouble.
And naturally, there's the fact
that he's a bit crazy, yes?
(coughs)
He's good, of course.
His only interest is
in slaying goblins,
but he's been honing his blade
for years now, you know?
There's no denying that he helps
to make the world a safer place,
much more so than those
of lesser skill
-who go after greater prey.
-(sneezes)
However, that being said,
it wouldn't hurt to hunt
something different
every once in a while.
The world is full of monsters.
Take the capital-- it's
positively overrun these days.
Demons.
If you want to help, you can.
Join those other two.
Why not?
There's more than one choice.
I could, but, it's just...
Little one, I'm sorry. I am.
There are so many paths. Yes?
And no clear answer, truly.
It's difficult, life.
Still, if you are going
to accompany him,
take my advice,
and know your own mind.
Know my own mind?
[ARCHER] Are you truly an
adventurer of the silver rank?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
The guild thinks so.
Then the guild must be wrong.
You look weak, and your
equipment is so shabby.
What do you know?
Before you speak, long-ears,
take a closer look.
That leather armor makes
for easier movement,
and the chain mail
and helmet provide protection
against blades
and blows to the head.
His sword and shield
may be small,
but they're also easy
to maneuver in tight spaces.
Well, it certainly
wouldn't kill you
to keep your equipment clean.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It's a precaution to cover
the smell of metal.
Those bastards have keen noses.
Listen, you may be a high elf,
but you're still
an inexperienced whelp
who's out wandering the world
because she got bored
and doesn't have the sense
to listen to her elders.
I'm 2,000 years old.
And you're how old?
[SHAMAN]
One hundred and seven.
[giggles] Oh, my!
Is that all?
-You look older, much older.
-[grumbles]
Those wrinkles!
Poor man.
[groans] That's more than enough
talk about age.
It shames those of us
with shorter lifespans.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
What's your business with me?
I'm sure you've heard by now
about the growing number
of demons in the capital.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] No.
-Leading them is a demon king.
He's been resurrected.
Now, he's gathering forces
because he wants
to take over the world.
-I see.
-That's why we came.
We need somebody
with your skills--
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Ask someone else.
I have no interest
in anything but goblins.
Don't you understand?
I'm saying hordes of demons
are going to attack!
Do you realize the entire world
is at stake here?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes.
But before the demons
destroy the world,
the goblins will destroy
the villages.
They can't be spared simply
because the world is in danger.
-How dare you!
-Easy!
Think about why we're here.
We didn't track him down
to ask for his help
dealing with the demons
themselves, remember?
Sir Goblin Slayer, we've come
to ask for your aid
with an infestation of goblins.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All right. Then, I accept.
Where are they?
How many?
How big is their nest?
Do they have a shaman or a hob?
What's with this guy?
[SHAMAN cackles]
As my companion has mentioned,
in the wake of
the demon king's resurrection,
an army of his minions
has gathered
and is preparing
to make its move.
So the chieftains of my kind,
the kings of men,
and the elders of the elves
and dwarves
have decided
to hold a conference.
[SHAMAN]
And we're the adventurers
who've been hired to act
as their representatives.
Eventually, a great battle
is going to be fought.
Although I'm sure you don't
care about that.
The goblins we mentioned
to you earlier
are currently becoming
more active on elven lands,
making a real nuisance
of themselves.
Have any champions or lords
emerged among them?
Champions? And lords?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Goblin heroes or kings,
basically equal to
platinum-ranked adventurers.
I'm afraid I cannot answer that.
However, our search has turned
up one enormous nest.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
And as usual,
the military won't deploy
for goblins.
The human kings may see us
as allies,
but they don't see us
as equals.
If we brought our soldiers
into this,
they would think
we were plotting something.
Which is why they sent us
adventurers.
But we still require a human
with goblin-slaying prowess.
So, out of everyone else,
we've chosen you, Orcbolg.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do you have a map?
[PRIEST]
Right here.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Ruins?
-[PRIEST] We believe so.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Numbers?
-[PRIEST] We only know
that there are many.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'll leave immediately.
You can decide how much
you want to pay me.
What the...?
Is he planning to go alone?
-[patrons chattering]
-Hmm... Yeah.
-You look lonely, milady.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Goblins.
Well, your meeting
didn't take very long.
From the sound of it, they came
to offer you a mission?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] That lizardman
will give you the details.
I'm heading out.
I'd like my pay
for that last quest.
[GUILD GIRL] Oh, but you
haven't made your report yet.
I suppose I could make
an exception for you.
Just who does this rust bucket
think he is?
Come, now. No pouting.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I've got
my share. Give this to her.
Wait. Are you going alone?
-The girl...
-She should rest.
[PRIESTESS]
Goblin Slayer!
So, what did they want?
-Is it a quest?
-Yes. Slaying goblins.
[PRIESTESS]
Then I'll get ready immediately!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No. I'll go on my own.
[PRIESTESS]
That's not fair!
We could've...
at least discussed it.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
We are, now.
Um, so, then,
this is a discussion?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Isn't it?
[sighs]
It doesn't really qualify
as a discussion
if the other person
doesn't have a say.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It doesn't?
I'm going with you.
You aren't going to leave
me behind.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Do as you wish.
Yes! I plan to.
[giggles]
[SHAMAN] Teaming up with a man
like that can't be easy.
If she can manage that,
I wonder what else she can do.
[PRIEST] If I were to put in
the quest and not go with him,
I wouldn't be able
to face my ancestors.
[ARCHER]
This Orcbolg is a strange
and incomprehensible being
Just what I left
the forest to see.
Now, wait up, boys.
Don't you know that you're
supposed to respect your elders?
[ARCHER] So, why did
you all become adventurers?
[SHAMAN]
Me?
For the exquisite cuisine,
obviously.
For you.
Well, what about you?
I've always longed to see
the outside world.
-This is delicious!
-I'm talking here!
I'm so glad you find it
to your liking.
What kind of animal
is this from?
That is the meat
of a swamp creature.
-Eww.
-Mmm!
A rabbit like you couldn't
possibly understand
the pleasure of biting
into a steaming hunk
of freshly roasted flesh.
There's hot soup, too.
Would you like some?
Yes, thank you.
(slurping)
Ah! Mmm!
It tastes wonderful!
I hope to raise my status
by rooting out heresy
-so I may become a dragon.
-[PRIESTESS] Huh?
[PRIEST] That's the reason
I became an adventurer.
Oh, right.
Huh?
[ALL]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Goblins.
[ARCHER] Yeah, I think
we all had that one
pretty much figured out.
Thanks.
That soup was delicious,
it's only fair I give you
something in return.
[rustling]
Elven traveling rations.
We're not supposed
to give them to others,
but this is a special occasion.
-So good!
-I'm glad you like it.
All right, then, I suppose I'll
have to offer something too.
-Huh?
-[clears throat]
Fire wine, a dwarven brew made
deep in our cellars.
Fire wine?
Surely someone
of your advanced age
and considerable maturity
has had a tipple or two before.
Don't you mock me, cave dweller.
Of course I have!
[gasps]
Would a sip of water
help, maybe?
-[groans]
-[cackles]
Go on, Beard-Cutter,
have a swig.
[SHAMAN]
Not bad, eh, kid?
[ARCHER groans]
Come on, just take it off
for a few minutes.
Why do you need it
when you're eating, anyway?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] So that I'm not
knocked unconscious
in the event of an ambush.
Yeah, she's going to feel
that in the morning.
[groans]
[ARCHER] It's your turn
to share something with us!
Hello?
Did you fall asleep in there?
[ARCHER giggles]
[PRIESTESS] He's quiet because
he's thinking about something.
[SHAMAN]
How can you tell?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Will this do?
[PRIEST]
Whatever is that?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Cheese. It's made
from fermented cow
or goat's milk, then hardened.
Hold on. You've never heard
of cheese before, Scaley?
My people hunt beasts
rather than raise them,
so products like this one
are unknown to our society.
Mmm!
And give it here.
I'll cut it for you real good.
[fire crackling]
[SHAMAN]
Oh! This is a fine cheese.
Hmm...
Oh.
[growls, roars]
Nectar! This is surely
the nectar of the gods!
Lovely.
Pairs well with the wine.
Mmm!
It's so sweet,
almost like a banana.
Is this from the cows
on that farm?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It is.
-It's wonderful.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Good.
-Don't touch that.
-[gasps]
It's dangerous.
-Aw. I just wanted a peek.
-Not a good idea.
[ARCHER]
That's a magic scroll, right?
I've never seen one before.
Such scrolls contain
powerful, ancient spells,
magic that is now lost to us.
They require
no expertise to wield.
Once unrolled, even a child
could use the spell within.
Indeed, and they can contain
any variety of spells,
and each one can be used
only once.
Most parties rely
on their own magic
and sell these things
off to collectors
and researchers for profit.
[WITCH] Apparently,
he required assistance
with a certain scroll.
Well, fine.
But at least tell me
what kind of spell
you've got there.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] No.
What if the goblins capture you
and you tell them what's in it?
I'm beginning to think you don't
like me very much at all.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'm not particular.
It's no use, just leave
the man alone.
Really. He's far more stubborn
than I am.
He is Beard-Cutter after all.
-He's Orcbolg after all.
-He's Sir Goblin Slayer,
-after all.
-(overlapping chatter)
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It's just Goblin Slayer.
-[chattering continues]
-[giggles]
-That's nonsense!
-[chattering excitedly]
[PRIEST] There is something
that's been on my mind.
Does anyone truly know
where goblins come from?
I was taught
that they originated
in a kingdom
deep underground.
When I was young,
we were told
that when someone misbehaves
or makes a mistake,
-a goblin appears.
-What's that mean?
People just say it
to make children obey.
They're less likely to act up
if they think
it'll create a goblin.
That's horrible!
And it means,
if we left long-ears
to her own devices,
we'd be neck-deep
in the creatures by now.
[growls]
Watch your mouth, dwarf!
Or tomorrow,
I'll give you a demonstration
of my skills with a bow!
How scary!
My beard's all aquiver!
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] I heard...
-[others] Hmm?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I heard they came from the moon.
The moon? As in,
one of the two above us now?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yes.
The green moon, that's where
the goblins originated,
their green home.
[ARCHER] Does that mean
shooting stars are goblins?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I'm not sure.
But that moon has no trees,
grass or water.
It's a desolate place,
and that makes them angry.
They envy us because we have
what they don't,
and so they come here.
Which is why if you ever become
jealous of someone,
you become like
a goblin yourself.
[PRIESTESS]
Who told you all of this?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
My older sister.
-You have an older sister?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Had.
I had an older sister.
[ARCHER] Just so I'm certain
I understand,
you really think
they're from the moon?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All I know for sure,
is that my sister
never made mistakes.
[crackling]
Oh.
I think he passed out.
Oh. Seems like the drink
finally kicked in.
[PRIESTESS]
I'm not surprised.
He did have quite a bit of it.
It would be wise
for us to sleep.
If we're tired tomorrow, we run
the risk of making mistakes.
We'll take turns as lookouts.
[cows mooing]
That's a good girl.
Time to go home.
Don't dally.
[COWGIRL]
Still gone.
♪
[berates in foreign language]
[yawns]
If you miss, this is going to be
much more difficult.
Quiet, you.
Where the hell are you aiming?
♪
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Let's go.
♪