[laughter]
[FEMALE HERO]
Just what do you think
you’re doing?
Yeah.
I’ve been saving that line
for a special occasion.
Whatd’you think?
I think a surprise attack
is more effective
if it’s actually a surprise.
Announcing your presence
can be helpful, though.
In this case, it drew their
attention away from the captive.
How did you know the location
of our secret meeting place?
I had a hunch.
Ugh!
We know about the evil plans you
and your sect have concocted.
Don’t even think
about trying to escape.
This ends now!
Wait! That holy sword!
No! It can’t be!
The Hero has arrived!
[MAN]
And just like that, it was over.
The Hero appeared out of nowhere
and defeated
the Demon Lord’s minions
with her unbeatable holy sword!
[FEMALE DRUID]
Isn't it incredible?
Apparently, the Hero's a girl!
-She must be quite a warrior!
-[MAn] No fair!
I wanna go on an adventure
with the Hero!
-You wouldn’t last two seconds.
-What?
[SPEARMAN]
Well, she’s obviously
not good enough to take down
all of them on her own.
Or else the rest of us
would be out of a job.
[SPEARMAN gulps]
[WITCH] Is somebody feeling
a little threatened?
Oh--
Orcbolg!
The Hero’s quest was successful!
That doesn’t matter.
It’s time to slay some goblins.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
It's time to slay some goblins.
The location is Water Town.
The reward is one bag
of gold each.
It’s up to you if you want
to come or not.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER scoffs]
Seriously?
This is something I’ve already
suspected for a while,
but now
I’m completely convinced.
You’re going to drive me crazy
if you continue to surprise me
with every move you make.
So, listen up!
We’ve been over this before.
It’s not a discussion unless
everybody involved has a say.
But I am giving you a say.
You’re not!
Whatever we choose,
the outcome is the same.
[GOBLIN SLAYER groans]
If we decided
not to go with you,
you’d go by yourself, right?
Of course.
Hm.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
So she’s right.
This isn’t a discussion.
[DWARF SHAMAN] Still,
the fact that Beard-cutter
is even mentioning
it to us
means he’s getting
a little better.
-Maybe.
-Indeed.
I believe this is a sign
of real progress.
-[LIZARDMAN PRIEST chews]
-[DWARF SHAMAN sighs]
Sweet nectar!
[PRIESTESS sighs]
All right.
I’ve decided.
I’ll go with you.
You don’t know how many goblins
you might face.
The more spellcasters you have,
the likelier the quest
is to succeed.
Oh, very well, then.
Our travelling expenses seem
to be more or less in order.
I suppose we could go.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Once we’re done
slaying these goblins,
you’ll go on another
adventure with us.
What do you say, Orcbolg?
Do we have a deal?
Sure.
That’s fine.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
And remember,
there will be no water torture.
-Got it?
-Or setting them on fire.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Or poisoning them.
No poison?
[PRIESTESS and HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Absolutely not!
Very well.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER gasps]
[BOTH]
He actually agreed!
[BOTH giggle]
[birds chirping]
[horse running, distant]
Not far, you can
see it from here.
So big!
[PRIESTESS]
That’s Water Town?
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
It looks just like I remember.
The waterways are a means
of transportation,
and keep the town well supplied
with food and other wares.
[PRIESTESS]
What kind of food do people
around here like to eat?
Hmm, all sorts
of things, really.
They’ve got access
to many ingredients,
but lamb liver stewed
with wine and fried fish
are local favorites.
Apparently, the wheat here
is very coarse,
so it makes great batter.
You seem quite knowledgeable
about the region,
Sir Goblin Slayer.
Someone I know told me about it
when I mentioned
I was coming here.
Do you mean your friend,
from the farm?
Yes.
Wow, so this is
the Temple of Law.
Just like I imagined!
Look, Goblin Slayer!
-It’s amazing!
-Is it?
[PRIESTESS groans]
So, this is where we’re meeting?
Yes, our client
should be inside.
Is the person who sent us
the quest a priest
of the Supreme God?
No, the Archbishop
-of the Supreme God.
-[PRIESTESS gasps]
Um, the Archbishop, really?
[BOTH]
Hmm?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Let’s go.
[PRIESTESS gulps]
[PRIESTESS]
He means...the Sword Maiden.
The arbiter of the law
all across the western frontier.
The Archbishop beloved
by the Supreme God.
She was one of the adventurers
who defeated the Demon Lord
ten years ago.
She’s gold-ranked,
the second-highest tier.
She isn’t a hero
from some old story.
She was born of the people,
and became a legend
in her own right.
[PRIESTESS]
Is that her?
It is.
The Sword Maiden
Hello?
Oh, my. Visitors.
I’m here for the goblins.
[PRIESTESS]
Uhh...!
I’m sorry, excuse him!
Thank you very much
for seeing us.
I can’t tell you what an honor
it is to meet you.
We have a brave warrior,
and a sweet priestess.
And you are?
Fellow adventurers who have
had the privilege
to fight beside them.
Though we were not summoned,
we’d be happy
to offer assistance.
Well met, stalwart adventurers.
I welcome you from the bottom
of my heart.
So...where are the goblins?
[PRIESTESS groans]
[SWORD MAIDEN]
It happened about a month ago.
We sent one of the acolyte girls
from the temple
out on an errand late at night.
Her corpse was discovered
in an alleyway the next morning.
The reports said it looked
as though
she was sliced apart
while still alive.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Still alive?
-So it happened right there?
-[SWORD MAIDEN] Mm-hmm.
Did the goblins eat parts of her
or was she only murdered?
[HIGH ELF ARCHER sighs]
Just let her talk.
Continue.
That attack was
just the beginning.
I had the city guard
extend their patrols,
but our crime rate
rapidly increased.
Women assaulted.
Children kidnapped.
And all, apparently, the work
of cutthroats or thieves.
But after one such attack was
interrupted by an adventurer,
a shocking discovery was made.
The corpse of
the small would-be assassin
wasn’t human.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
A goblin?
Goblins, huh?
And more than a few of the nasty
things by the sound of it.
How do you think that many of
them have gotten into the town?
Surely they would have
been stopped
if they’d tried to enter
through the gates.
[DWARF SHAMAN] Maybe they
tunneled up from underground,
or used the waterways.
Seems like a lot of casualties
if they were just
passing through.
Goblins always make their nests
beneath the surface,
do they not?
This town was built on top
of an old settlement,
so there are probably some ruins
below the newer construction.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] If I were them,
I would settle there.
They aren’t bright creatures,
but they’re not total fools.
There you go again.
You’re always thinking
like a goblin.
Of course I am.
If I didn’t know
how they thought,
I wouldn’t be very good
at fighting them.
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Like you,
we concluded that they
were living under the city,
and sent out a quest for the
Water Town adventurers, but...
[PRIESTESS]
What happened to them?
Oh...
-I see.
-And that was when I heard
-[PRIESTESS gasps]
-the ballad of the brave
and honorable Goblin Slayer,
the hero of the frontier.
What ballad?
You mean you didn’t know?
You’ve been
immortalized in song.
Meeting you in person
was pretty disappointing.
That’s not my problem.
Come now, Sir Goblin Slayer.
Tales of bravery survive thanks
to the bards who sing of them.
Why does that matter?
Do you truly not understand
how these things work?
The more that word of your deeds
spreads throughout the land,
the more requests
you’ll get to do the goblin
slaying you love so much.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Hmm...
I beg of you.
Kind sir, will you please save
Water Town from these creatures
and their depravity?
Your town may already be lost,
but I’ll kill some goblins.
Goblin Slayer!
Can’t you be
a little more tactful?!
It’s the truth.
[PRIESTESS]
And that’s exactly why you
should be more sensitive!
Shall we head to the sewers,
then, Sir Goblin Slayer?
Yes.
We’ll need to be careful
and thorough.
It would be annoying
if one of them got away.
And remember, no using water,
fire, or poison!
-I know.
-Hm.
Forgive me for asking,
but why have you not ordered
the city guard
to eradicate them for you?
Admittedly, there is much
I do not know about
this town and its ways,
but surely that would fall
under their jurisdiction.
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Well...
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Were you told there was no point
in mobilizing the military
against mere goblins?
Mm-hmm.
I suppose you can’t really
blame them.
There are still plenty of demons
running around the capital,
after all.
With the military spread thin,
goblin slaying is a job
for us adventurers.
The difficulties that arise
from money and politics
in human society
never cease to amaze me.
Enough of this.
How do we get underground?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Well?
Oh of course.
I do beg your pardon, sir.
[SWORD MAIDEN]
I believe that your best option
will be to access the sewers
by going down the well
behind this temple.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Is this map accurate?
Mostly.
It’s an old sketch dating back
to when the temple
was first built.
But still, the waterways
should be intact there.
If there is damage,
it won’t be too severe.
All right.
You navigate.
I’m happy to.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Let’s go.
-There’s no time to waste.
-Right.
That’s Orcbolg, always getting
straight to the point.
[sighs]
[SWORD MAIDEN]
Miss...
Archbishop?
Perhaps it isn’t my place
to ask this, but...
are you not frightened of what
you might encounter down there?
Well...
we’ll be facing an unknown
number of goblins
in their own territory.
So, yes.
But still.
[gasps]
[PRIESTESS] I’m sure that
together, we can handle it.
[GOBLINS chatter, grumble]
[shield bashed]
[GOBLIN]
Ahh-- ahh!
[splash]
I believe
that should be the last
of this particular group.
No...
that’s the last of them.
This many goblins living
right under a city...
it’s enough to make
your skin crawl.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
About what I’d expect.
[DWARF SHAMAN]
Huh?
[HIGH ELF ARCHER] I’m not
going to do what Orcbolg does.
This will be a long fight.
I don’t want to have to resort
to using the goblin
made arrows halfway through.
They’re terribly crude.
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Are they?
-Yeah, they are!
[DWARF SHAMAN]
This is the fifth time
we’ve been attacked
today alone.
Who knows how many goblins
are actually down here?
This place is crawling
with the filthy things.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
I’m starting to think
we’ll be down here forever.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Don’t worry.
These walls are made of stone.
They’re unlikely to ambush us
through them.
[PRIESTESS] I can’t stand
the thought of another ambush.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sorry.
At least with all the refuse
down here,
we don’t need to worry
about masking our scents.
Please don’t remind me
of such a terrible memory.
Hm--
[DWARF SHAMAN]
What is it, long-ears?
Something feels off,
but I’m not sure what.
And I hear water...up there?
[rain patters]
[PRIESTESS]
Hold on...is that rain?
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
We’re underground.
How can it be raining?
[DWARF SHAMAN]
The obvious answer is that
it’s raining on the surface.
It must be making its way
down here
through the canals
and the sewers.
What are your thoughts,
Beard-cutter?
It will be bad if our light
source was extinguished.
What’s the matter,
Goblin Slayer?
Did you see something?
Be on your guard.
We’re about to have company.
Here, you’ll need this!
[PRIESTESS exhales]
[DWARF SHAMAN groans]
[water rushing]
♪
No!
-[gasps]
-A boat?
[shouts]
-[GOBLINS grunting]
-[arrows whizzing]
Hear me, O merciful
Earth Mother.
Please protect us, the weak,
with your divine light
and the sacred power
of nature!
Protection!
I can’t hold this long.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
What do you want to do?
What else?
The same as always.
[crack]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
All goblins must die.
That’s one.
Hey, now.
Leave the long-distance
targets to me.
Show off.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] How many
spells do you have left?
Loads of ‘em.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Good.
Then use Tunnel, dig a hole.
You know there’s a
whole town above us?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Not up.
Dig down.
Make a hole in the waterway
and let the water run out.
[DWARF SHAMAN] If we mess
around too much down here,
the sewers could overflow.
But it’s not water torture,
fire, or poison.
Do something else!
I’m going to lose the shield!
If you have another
transfer scroll,
then you might want
to consider using it now.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Unfortunately, I don’t.
I’m going to throw this as soon
as Protection goes down.
Once I do,
use the miracle again.
Solidify our defense.
[PRIESTESS]
Yes, right!
If you wouldn’t mind waiting
just a moment, please.
Now...I call upon you,
ancestors:
O sickle wings
of the velociraptor,
slice, fly, and hunt.
[LIZARDMAN PRIEST]
I believe that blade
will be to your liking.
But please avoid throwing it.
I’ll do my best.
Just a...little...longer.
-[ding]
-[GOBLIN] Ugh!
[GOBLIN gasps]
[GOBLINS pained screaming]
What the...?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
We’re jumping.
Five.
Now, O great and fearsome
dragon,
behold your descendant
in battle!
-[GOBLIN grunts]
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Nine...ten...
they’re wearing armor. It’s
easier just to knock them off
-the boat.
-Excellent idea!
[GOBLINS]
Whoaa!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Sixteen.
With these numbers,
we may be in trouble.
[GOBLIN growls]
Eyes open or eyes closed,
a high elf’s arrow
never misses its mark.
Here.
Ugh.
And here I was hoping
not to use these things.
[PRIESTESS]
Protection!
Ahh!
Thanks for that!
I’ll keep their strikes
from reaching us,
so the rest of you can
concentrate on your attacks.
Okay!
Time to work,
you crafty gnomes.
Mash grains of sand together
to form mighty rock.
[grunts]
[DWARF SHAMAN]
Beard-cutter! Scaly!
Get back here!
Stone Blast!
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Another battle over.
What next?
Personally,
I’d like to rest a little while.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
No, we need to keep moving.
Yes, I agree.
That skirmish was
anything but quiet.
Even with the rain
masking some of the noise,
we may well have alerted
other denizens of this place
to our presence here.
[GIANT GATOR growls]
-What?
-A goblin?
[thundering chomp]
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
That’s not a goblin.
Thank you for clearing that up!
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Time to get out of here!
I wasn’t expecting
a swamp dragon!
Swamp dragon,
Or an alligator!
Hey, Scaly,
isn’t that thing
a relative of yours?
Talk to it!
It pains me to say this,
but I have had no contact
with any of my family
since I left home.
[ALL gasp]
Ahh!
Uh-- ahh!
[LIZARDMAN PRIEST] And even
if I had, I can assure you,
that violent creature is
no relative of mine, Sir Mage.
Well, I guess this is one way
to get around.
[GOBLIN SLAYER panting]
Try to steady your breathing.
I’m fine, you don’t need
to carry me!
[GOBLIN SLAYER] You have
one miracle left, don’t you?
I can’t have you fainting here.
I say we feed the dwarf to that
monster and make our escape.
It’ll definitely get
food poisoning!
You just try it!
[gasps]
There’s something up
ahead of us.
At least one goblin ship,
possibly a lot more.
Who knows?
[PREISTESS]
So, what should we do?
There is a way.
I don’t know what kind of
crazy plan
you’ve got in your head this
time, but remember the rules!
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
We’ll go with your idea.
[GOBLINS chatter, grumbling]
[GOBLIN SHAMAN growls]
[GOBLINS cheer]
[GOBLIN SHAMAN chuckles]
[GIANT GATOR roars]
[GOBLINS scream]
[PRIESTESS] Hear me, O merciful
Earth Mother.
Protect us and bless us
with Holy Light.
I get it.
You had her use Holy Light
on the swamp dragon’s tail,
and that lured the goblins
straight into its path.
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I was told not
to use water, fire or poison.
My options were a bit limited.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
They may not be smart,
but I can’t believe
that’s all it took to fool them.
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
The goblins learned to associate
light with groups of adventurers
because we always travel by it.
[HIGH ELF ARCHER]
Really?
[GOBLIN SLAYER] I’m not sure
when they figured it out,
but it’s commonly
known among them now.
Their kind are nothing
more than scavengers.
They’d never think of building
anything on their own.
Again, they aren’t
bright creatures,
but they’re not total fools.
They learn how to use
items quickly.
If they were shown a boat,
it wouldn’t take them
long to learn to use it.
Well, aren’t you
Mister Knowledgeable?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
I’ve studied them.
This is why I make sure never to
give the goblins any new ideas.
I kill them instead.
You think...somebody showed them
how to use the boats...
intentionally?
-[GOBLIN SLAYER] Yes.
-[PRIESTESS] But...
isn’t it also possible
they had a goblin shaman
who figured it out for them?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Could be.
But if their numbers increased
naturally down there,
why didn’t they know
about the...
what was that thing
called again?
[PRIESTESS] The, um,
swamp dragon, you mean?
[GOBLIN SLAYER]
Yeah, that.
The goblins didn’t
know about it.
If they had, I don’t think they
would’ve dared to use boats.
They’re cowards by nature.
[LIZARDMAN PRIEST]
What exactly are you suggesting,
Sir Goblin Slayer?
The goblin population here
isn’t the result of them
multiplying naturally.
Someone...or something
orchestrated this infestation.
[growling]
[dice rolling]