(Digital jingle)
(thunder claps)
(digital jingle)
- [Hackmon] The one born from the vast darkness
is a burning flame.
A rising moon which wipes away the memory
of daylight, the searing embrace of a dark power,
dancing madly in a crazed storm.
However, in time, even this storm shall pass.
In its wake, joy and prosperity will vanquish despair,
and the darkness will fade into the light.
(somber orchestral music)
- [Joe] If King Drasil gets his way,
I think we all know what's going to happen.
The human world is going to be swallowed
by the digital world.
(growling)
(forlorn orchestral music)
(loud rumbling)
- Hold on tight.
(dramatic piano music)
(loud crash)
- Tai?
(woeful piano music)
Where are you, big brother?
The two of us, we've always been together.
Sometimes you got bored.
Sometimes I got angry.
Lots of times we had fun.
But you were always right there.
(alarm beeping)
You awake?
Of course not.
Hello, world to Tai Kamiya, wake up.
Let's go, rise and shine.
- [T.K.] Kari, Kari?
(Patamon whimpers)
- What is it, T.K.?
- You all right?
- Mm-hmm.
(Patamon whimpers)
- Just thinking about Tai.
Where'd he go?
- (gasps) Look at that, guys.
It just keeps getting closer.
(all gasp)
- I can see our school.
- Can they see us?
- Distortions everywhere.
- [Joe] What do you make of this, Izzy?
- The line separating the human and the digital world
is starting to disappear.
(grunts)
- Couldn't that be a good thing though?
We wouldn't need a portal to go to your world anymore.
- I can go see Joe anytime.
- It's not that simple.
If this keeps up, there won't be
a human world for any of us to visit.
- I guess Homeostasis isn't going to stop
King Drasil from reshaping both worlds.
- [Matt] (grunts) There's no way I'm going
to let that happen.
- But what can we do?
We can't even control Meicoomon anymore,
now that she's combined with Ophanimon
and her Dark Mode.
She's grown more powerful than ever.
Homeostasis wants only stability and harmony.
That's it's only purpose.
- That's what they always say.
- So how are we gonna save Meicoomon.
(explosion)
(all gasp)
- Is that pink lava a portal, Izzy?
- Not only that, it connects directly
to the human world.
And it's within walking distance.
What do you say, Matt?
Should we go home?
(dramatic piano music)
- Yes.
- [Tentomon] Walking distance is far.
- [Biyomon] Yeah, only because we don't
have legs.
- [Tentomon] But dancing looks like fun.
- Not as fun as flying.
When Tai through me in the air,
ah, that was so much fun.
- [Palmon] I remember that.
I wanna fly.
Throw me, Mimi.
- [Koromon] When Tai comes back,
he'll make us all fly.
- [Tentomon] Maybe we should talk about another topic.
How about food, food's good.
- [Koromon] Ah food would be good.
That would make this walking distance much shorter.
What have you got?
- [Tentmon] I've got nothing.
- [Koromon] Well why do you wanna talk about it?
That's not nice.
- It's okay, you know?
- Hmm?
- I know you don't want to leave.
Let the rest of us handle things
back in the human world for awhile.
You wanna stay and look for Tai, don't ya?
- Well, yeah.
I'd like to stay here, but I can't.
Our world needs to be saved too.
- Hmm, it still doesn't seem real, does it?
What happened to everyone.
First Meicoomon.
Then Gatomon.
And poor Mr. Nishijima was just trying to help Tai.
It's like a bad dream.
- I keep thinking Tai's gonna come around
the corner any minute.
And really tick me off.
- Yeah, I wish.
Just between us, can I ask you something?
- Sure.
As long as it's got nothing to do with ghosts.
But maybe we should get going before everybody
starts won--
- What happens if Tai's really gone?
(Matt groans)
I mean, it kinda looks like he's gone.
I know that doesn't sound remotely possible,
but the last time we saw him, he fell into
a big crack.
And when it closed back up, he was gone.
And I'm worried about Kari.
She lost her brother and her Digi partner
got turned into a giant flying feathered monster.
(sighs) All right, I'm done.
And now you tell me there's no point
in getting all emotional and we just
have to buckle up and keep going.
- Exactly.
- That's good advice.
- [Biyomon] Sora!
- Over here, Biyomon.
- (gasps) What did you do?
- Hey, hey, everything's okay.
- You've been crying.
Was he singing one of his songs to you?
They're awful and they don't even rhyme.
- How would you know?
- You sing in your sleep.
- [Whines] Oh Tai, I'm leaving now.
Come find me again, in your world.
- [Professor] Thank you all for coming.
As you know, recent Digimon attacks
have resulted in power outages and caused
digital devices to fail.
Reports of hostile Digimon wreaking havoc
on critical infrastructure continues to pour in
from every corner of the world
with no end in sight.
These incidents are proof that our world
is being systematically invaded by the digital world
and we must act at once.
We had hoped the military forces would not
have to enter the cities, but it's clear that
we are now past that point.
Meiko, call me as soon as you get back.
Where is my daughter?
- [Hackman] Your efforts are in vain.
The situation is beyond the power of humans
to control.
- [Professor] What do you mean by that?
What's going on?
- The attempt by Homeostasis to eliminate
the Libra has failed.
(Professor gasps)
(loud rumbling)
During the battle, the Libra combined
with Ophanimon Falldown Mode, this was not expected.
The result was the creation of the Digimon
known as Ordinemon.
The worlds harmony is now utterly lost.
- And Meiko, did the children get out safely?
- No one was sacrificed.
Homeostasis does not wish that.
We must act before events spin further
out of control.
The time has come to execute the fallback option,
our plan of last resort.
- What does that mean?
- If we do not stop Ordinemon,
the human world as you know it
is finished and nothing will remain of mankind.
It's possible that the fallback option itself
will destroy your world.
But if we do nothing, then we remove
any doubt about what will happen.
Let us hope it's not already too late.
(sinister ambience)
(professor groans)
- Well, we're here.
- What's been going on?
- [Man Over Intercom] All citizens
are ordered to clear the streets and public
areas until further notice.
A state of emergency has been declared.
Repeat, all citizens are to clear city streets
and public areas and to remain indoors
until further notice.
- [Izzy] At least that thing that Meicoomon
turned into hasn't shown up in the city yet.
- There's nothing about it on the news?
- There would be, if it was here.
- That's for sure.
- So now what?
We saw it disappear into a distortion.
- Yeah, we did, what do you think, Izzy?
- [(Zzy] Unfortunately, as much as we don't
want it in this world, we have to assume
it'll come here.
It's a very powerful Digimon.
- [Kari] This is all...
My fault.
- [All] Huh?
- Tai is gone.
- Kari, no, no.
Don't talk like that.
- What if he is?
Then what?
Where's my brother?
(sorrowful piano music)
Please come back, Tai, please.
(Kari sobs)
- Mimi, when you cry, I cry, too.
(Palmon crying)
- Come back, Tai.
- She fainted.
- Don't let her fall.
- [Sora] Her forehead's so hot.
She has a fever.
- But she was okay when we got here.
- It's all the stress.
It got to her.
- I guess you can say that every bad thing
that's happened is my fault.
Ever since Meicoomon went crazy,
it seems like nothing's gone right for us.
- That's not true.
Remember that time we had cake?
- Yeah, chocolate.
- Lots of things have gone right
for us since then, Meiko.
But the future is what's important now.
Not the past.
I think she'll be fine if we just
get her off her feet.
Come on, lie down for a bit, Kari.
(Kari moans)
(gentle piano music)
- [Matt] Tai or no Tai, we'll be okay.
- [T.K.] I hope you're right about that, Matt.
- Uh, Joe.
- What's up?
- Koromon's acting weird.
- [Joe] Maybe he swallowed a bug.
- Bugs don't taste that bad.
- [Mimi] Oh, you poor thing.
You don't sound good at all, Koromon.
What's wrong?
- Maybe he's just super hungry
after all those battles.
- You know what they say about feeding
a Digimon with an empty stomach.
A gold banana is quite restorative
and tastes better when someone else
makes it for you.
- I love that saying.
Let's order in.
(Digimon's cheering)
- We have to eat two digi bars.
(Gomamon laughing)
- [Gomamon] Pepperoni for me, Joe.
- [Joe] Good to see some things are still
the same as ever.
(Meiko chuckles)
- Of all the things that have happened
to us, Tai, this one might be the worst.
I don't remember when the odds were ever
this tough before.
Why did you have to disappear on us now, Tai?
How can I do this when I'm all alone?
(Matt groans)
- Why would you ever think
that you're alone, Matt?
I'm with you.
- Gabumon?
- Tentomon was right, I ate and I grew, (laughing).
(Matt laughs)
So listen, it seems like you're having
some trouble dealing with stuff now that
Tai's not here.
- You heard that?
- But as they say, your Digimon partner
has all the answers.
- They really say that?
- Nah, I just made it up.
But it sounds like a real answer
so it must be true, (laughing).
(Matt laughs)
Everything's going to be okay, Matt.
You're gonna be a great leader
and you're not alone.
You'll never be alone as long as
you have me around.
(Matt sighs)
You know you can count on me.
I'll stay by your side no matter
how bad things get.
- Thanks, Gabumon.
- Even if that Ordinemon blows up
the whole city, or if you mess up
and get us all deleted.
- Huh?
- Or if you get confused and we get lost
and go through a distortion, only,
it's the wrong one and we all end up
floating around in space forever.
- That's not gonna happen.
- (sighs) And when you get married,
I'll watch your kids.
And when you get old, I'll go for walks
with you, I'll do anything for you.
I'll even save the world.
- Thank you, Gabumon.
Thank you for everything.
(gentle piano music)
- [Gabuman] Tai is still in your heart, Matt.
- [Matt] I know that.
I think about him all the time.
I think I understand what he was trying
to tell me now.
I just didn't want to hear it back then.
What's going on in your head?
This isn't like you.
The old you would've taken action.
- I don't know what to do.
It's not like when we were kids.
(gentle piano music)
These days it feels like I see more but,
I understand less.
Is fighting the answer?
It might seem right at the time...
But maybe it's not.
(gentle piano music)
I still believe we're the only ones
who can fix this.
I'm just worried, what if we make it worse?
- (scoffs) Oh spare me, look.
- What?
- Quit trying to run away from it.
I finally realized how much I depended on him.
It's terrifying to lose something irreplaceable.
I know that now.
Now that Tai's gone.
- You have to stop thinking that way, Matt.
You're just making it harder on yourself.
You know you're the only one who can
step up and take over for Tai.
And you know that's what he would want.
So, do it for him.
(Matt crying)
it's all right, don't cry.
- [Matt] You're making me cry.
(Matt crying)
Hmm?
What are you doing?
- [All] Hmm?
- [Tentomon] Uh nothing really.
We were just out for a walk and you know.
(Digimon chattering)
- [Matt] A walk, huh?
And your walk just happened to bring you all
right to that window at the same time?
- [Tentomon] Well, it is a very nice window.
- Maybe it's time for a digi-spanking.
(Digimon yelping)
(groans) Knuckleheads.
- Matt? - Hmm?
- [Gabumon] Something's happening.
- Distortion.
- [Gabumon] That's right, you have Tai's goggles.
Put them on.
- Here it goes.
(sighs)
(crackling)
(rumbling)
(Matt whimpers)
(menacing music)
No way.
(loud whooshing)
(swooshing)
(sinister music)
(screeching)
Meicoomon's just reappeared!
- Everyone evacuate the area at once.
Everybody out!
- [Officer] The police cannot patrol down here, stay here.
- [Japanator] Chopper later to group.
Follow me and fly low. - Roger that.
(loud crash)
(intense music)
(eerie screeching)
(spooky ambience)
(thunderous footsteps)
- (maniacal laughter) I can't believe
those fools have created this monster.
It's fantastic.
They're doing my job for me.
All I have to do now is stand back and watch.
Do it, Ordinemon, destroy it.
Destroy it all!
Burn this rotten, useless world sown.
Destroy these humans and everything
they've created.
(maniacal laughter) And in from its flames
and ashes, a new world shall arise.
A new world ruled by King Drasil, hee-hee-hee.
- Citizens are reminded to stay indoors
and to monitor this channel for further news bulletins.
(sizzling)
- Has anybody heard from Tai yet?
- Not yet, nothing.
- Same here, I can't contact Meiko.
(loud thud)
(citizens screaming and crying)
- Things seem bad, but we have to trust our kids
and know they'll find a way out of it.
- Mm hmm, that's the only thing we can do.
They're all survivors.
I have faith in them.
- Dance, my horrible monster.
Just keep on dancing (maniacal laughter).
Destroy everything, Ordinemon!
(eerie ambience)
(foreboding music)
(sizzling)
- [Japanator] Stay on my six, we're going in.
- [Pilot] Right behind ya, Japanator.
(female yelling and crying)
- [Officer] Keep moving!
Keep moving!
Don't panic, people.
- [Meiko] Is that really Meicoomon?
- [Joe] How are we supposed to stop that?
- I was going to volunteer to go talk to her,
but now that I see her, maybe not.
- Swallowing Ophanimon has made her
a little more intense.
The situation has gotten quite dangerous.
- Oh Mei, now what?
(loud whirling and thuds)
(sinister music)
- Let's go, Gabumon.
- Roger that.
(upbeat inspiring music)
- [All] Gomamon, Tentomon, Biyomon, Palmon, Gabumon
digivolve to...
(upbeat dance music)
(singing in foreign language)
- Garurumon!
- Togemon!
- Birdramon!
- Kabuterimon!
- Ikkakumon!
(singing in foreign language)
- [All] Digivolve to...
- WereGarurumon!
- MegaKabuterimon!
- Lilimon!
- Garudamon!
- Zudomon, let's go.
(singing in foreign language)
(laughing)
- What do you want?
- I see you still prefer to wear
that disguise, edging your bets
just in case your little plan falls through.
- Yeah, this war is as good as over.
What are you doing here anyway?
Come to eat some popcorn and watch
the whole human world's last pathetic performance?
- [Hackmon] It's too early to predict what will happen.
- [King Drasil] You guys won't like the ending.
- [Hackmon] Homeostasis wishes for harmony and stability
in the world.
(King Drasil laughs)
- [King Drasil] Now this is getting bold.
I think you need a new catchphrase.
I mean, come on, you're destroying everything anyway,
just like we would.
- Harmony and stability are the opposites
of what you seek.
You seek only destruction and pain and fear.
(King Drasil laughs maniacally)
- You crack me up.
You hide behind philosophy but you have
no loyalty.
It's not a half bad strategy.
Oh no, our owner's being destroyed (laughing).
- [Hackmon] Ordinemon stopped its rampaging
when it's partners appeared.
Perhaps it still has some shadow
of a conscience left.
- So she's taking a quick break.
She'll be back to destroying in a minute.
Just admit it, Homeostasis has tried and failed.
(sizzling)
No one can save this world now.
All hail its final destruction
and the rise of King Drasil.
(upbeat inspiring music)
- [Lilimon] After her, everyone.
(loud roaring)
(growling)
(singing in foreign language)
- No effect.
- [Joe] We're gonna need to crank it up
to the next level, you guys.
Let's go!
- MegaKabuterimon digivolve to...
- Lilimon digivolve to...
- Zudomon digivolve to...
- Garudamon digivolve to...
- WereGarurumon digivolve to...
(singing in foreign language)
- MetalGarurumon.
- HerculesKabuterimon.
- Phoenixmon.
- Rosemon.
- Vikemon, arctic blizzard.
- Garuru Tomahawk.
- Star-Light Explosion.
- Forbidden Temptation.
- Giga Blaster.
(blasts and crackling)
- Still nothing.
- Incredible.
Now what?
(screeching pulsations)
(loud explosion)
(roaring)
(Digimon whimpering)
- Our best shot didn't even make a dent.
- What if we can't stop this?
- Oh Meicoomon, what happened to you?
- I can't just stand here and do nothing.
- It's too dangerous.
- You do not lack for courage, digidestined.
- [Matt] Who are you?
- A messenger sent by Homeostasis .
Fear not, I am here as a friend.
- [Several] Mm hmm.
- Hackmon and it's mega form makes it...
(dramatic thump)
Jesmon!
(all gasping)
- Huh?
(whirls and zaps)
(small explosion)
- (grunting) That was you.
- [Hackmon] Yes.
- (groans) you're not our friend.
You're the reason Tai isn't with us anymore.
- Take it easy.
(Mimi whimpers)
- King Drasil had predicted that the Libra
would destroy the real world.
If he was correct, then the key to destroying
both the real world and the digital world
must surely be what the Libra has now become.
- Ordinemon.
- [Hackmon] It is now far stronger than all of you.
But it cannot even control its own enormous power.
And it has no plan of direction.
It wanders aimlessly, destroying without purpose.
(Meiko whimpers)
In response, Homeostasis has implemented
its plan of last resort.
We cannot allow King Drasil to continue.
- What is this plan of last resort?
- It involves rebooting the real world.
(all gasp)
- Is that even possible? - A reboot?
We already did that.
- [Hackmon] The reboot you initiated
was only of the digital world.
The programming code of that world
and the real world are vastly different.
But the distortions transferred data
between the two and have caused damage
to the real worlds code.
The very structure of its basic code
has been rewritten.
According to my calculations, it will take
only 94 seconds to rewrite all code
and then the real world will transform back
into the Quantum Sea.
- The Quantum Sea?
- We must prevent that from happening,
for the survival of your world.
- So the first reboot wasn't enough?
- (gasps) Does that mean our Digimon will lose
their memories again?
- No, this time we can avoid that
by using the backup memory we made for them
after the last reboot.
The trouble is, a total reboots gonna reset
every single computer and electronic device, too.
It's digital Armageddon.
- [Hackmon] Issues relating to the everyday tools
of human beings are unimportant.
We are talking about the question of whether or not
humans in the real world will survive at all.
The reboot is the last hope for humanity.
- We have to save it by destroying it?
Will it even be our world anymore?
(solemn music)
(Kari whimpers)
- Oh, Kari, I wish there was something
I could do to help you.
So this guy thinks our planets hard drive
needs to be wiped clean?
Isn't that a little extreme?
- What would Tai do?
Would he believe him?
(several gasp)
- Well I'm sure of this, what Tai would be
focused on would be saving people.
And he'd work as hard as he could
to minimize any damage.
He'd find a way.
- Sounds great, what do you think, Izzy?
- I think it's crazy.
Think about the electrical grid
and power plants and the gas lines
and the water supply and transportation
and even medical services.
Rebooting the real world would mean
shutting down every one of those things
all at the same time.
And Hackmon says all that's unimportant.
There's gotta be another solution.
And I'm gonna find it before this reboot happens.
- He has a point.
- Just the same, the reboot will begin
when Homeostasis decrees, but I do agree.
Ordinemon should not be allowed to further
damage this world.
Could you lure it away toward the ocean?
- (gasps) But, but how?
- Sorry, Meiko, but Hackmon is right.
Meicoomon or whatever she's called
is destroying everything and we have to stop her.
Look, you have the best shot as her partner.
Try to lead her away from the city.
- Well, wish me luck.
All right then.
(eerie rumbling)
- Gather around you guys.
We brought you some food, so dig in.
- There's nothing like food to cheer you up.
- (laughs) Tummy so happy.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my eyes were bigger than my thorax.
(slurping)
- Why do you eat so much, Agumon?
- Because eating is the funnest thing there is.
Plus I've got to be strong for when Tai
comes back.
(Mimi gasps)
(Agumon smacking)
- I hope you're right.
- I'm always right about food.
I wish I was as illogically positive as you are.
I'm so afraid we'll never see Gatomon
and Meicoomon again.
How do you do it?
Do you know some sort of secret to happiness?
- Mm hmm, my secret is eating.
(melancholy piano music)
- [Izzy] Oh, another dead end.
I have to keep looking.
If I could just figure out how to prevent
the reboot from happening.
I've gotta find something.
(computer buzzes)
(gasps) Anything.
(intercom chiming)
- Hey, Izzy, can I come and join you?
- [Izzy] Sure Tentomon, come on out.
(gulping)
- You sure took off in a hurry.
Is stopping Hackmon's plan that important?
- [Izzy] I feel like if I don't,
it's gonna mean the end of the human world.
Then again, maybe not.
You guys got rebooted and you're fine.
- Wait, I got rebootified?
Are you sure?
That sounds like the kind of thing
that would definitely leave a bruise.
- It's true, you just forgot.
That's the problem with rebooting.
Your memory can get wiped out.
That's why I don't wanna do it again.
(mellow piano music)
(groaning)
(sighs)
- [Mr. Nishijima] Who's there?
Is that you, Tai?
- Mr. Nishijima, where are you?
I hear you but I can't see anything.
- [Mr. Nishijima] Over here.
- Over where?
(gasps)
- You're all right.
I'm so glad.
- But, you're hurt.
- [Mr. Nishijima] Yes, I wasn't as quick
as you, obviously, (groans).
- Don't try to stand.
- Where are we?
- Well, we're still in the digital world,
but I don't know where.
(digital whining)
(Tai gasps)
I knew it.
This isn't random.
Someone brought us here.
But why?
(gasps)
(eerie piano music)
Impossible, it's them.
It's Davis and Ken and it's all of them.
Are they alive?
- [Mr. Nishijima] I think so.
It looks like they're in suspended animation.
In fact, there's something else you need to know.
I couldn't tell you before.
- Huh?
- Davis, Ken, Yolei and Cody, the four of them
went missing a long time ago and I always wondered
what happened to them.
But then that intel was classified top secret.
Even their names were made confidential.
And all related information was kept under seal.
- Who gave the order to do that?
- It was Director Himekawa.
I didn't know it at the time but she was
cooperating with King Drasil.
So when these four learned about him
and what he was planning, she made them disappear.
In our last battle together, Himekawa's partner,
Tapirmon was sacrificed.
That loss broke something in Hime.
I think that's why she wanted to reboot
the digital world.
She thought it would bring Tapirmon back.
Nothing else really mattered to her.
- [Tai] Did it work?
- I don't know.
I don't even know if Hime is still alive.
Having a partner Digimon can save a person
or if things go wrong, it can drive them mad.
If only I'd seen where Himekawa was heading,
maybe things wouldn't have turned out this way.
Sometimes your best friends somehow become your enemies.
That's when the decisions get tough.
That's when we do things we never thought
we would be capable of.
(Tai gasps)
- Please kill her.
Just do it.
(Tai groans)
- [Dark Gennai] Beware when fighting monsters,
that you do not become a monster yourself.
If you gaze long enough into the abyss,
the abyss will gaze back into you.
Sounds like that was written about you.
(finger snaps)
- [Tai] Wait, what are you doing?
(alarm beeps)
- [Dark Gennai] Just a little program modification.
- [Dr. Tapirmon] He's turned off their life support.
- [Dark Gennai] Yes, they don't have long now.
But you can save them by transporting them
to the real world, if you hurry.
Because in a few minutes, this whole place
is gonna blow, kaboom!
(Tai gasps)
We've even prepared extra slots for you.
Wasn't that merciful of King Drasil?
But wait, what's this?
I only see one.
How can we make such a fatal error, (crying)?
(maniacal laughter)
I guess only one of you gets to go.
(sinister laughter)
I've been waiting for this day for a long time.
A chance to finally show you how pathetic
and powerless you humans really are.
By yourselves you can't do anything.
Without Digimon, you're worthless.
How does it feel to realize that?
On your own, you're nothing but clowns.
The digidestined are a joke.
(laughs maniacally)
(Dr. Nishijima grimaces)
You really should be ashamed of yourselves,
you wannabes, (laughs).
- Are you trying to stop it?
- Yes, I've gotta kill the program.
There has to be a way to override the sequence.
(computer beeps)
(Tai grunts)
(dramatic instrumental music)
Mr. Nishijima, see if you can find
the root directory on that computer.
- [Mr. Nishijima] Right.
Hey, Tai, I think I found a way to override
the transport and stop the self destruct sequence.
Go look at the controls inside the last cryo chamber.
The empty one.
- Okay.
(frantic instrumental music)
- Mr. Nishijima] Step all the way inside.
(door slams shut)
(Tai gasps)
- [Female Computer Voice] Transport system activated.
- Hey, Mr. Nishijima.
Something went wrong.
I'm trapped.
- [Mr. Nishijima] I'm sorry, Tai.
But if only one of us can go back
to the human world, it has to be you.
It has to be.
(alarms buzzing)
- Open the door.
Let me out of here.
We still have time to figure it out.
(grunting) Come on.
- [Mr. Nishijima] There's nothing here to figure out, Tai.
But you need to figure out what's happening
back home and make things right.
You kids are the only ones who can do it.
(tai grunting)
You just have to do the very thing
that you guys taught me to do.
To never give up.
To believe that no matter how bad
things get, there's always hope.
I think I understand that now.
Always hope.
I have to stay, you have to go.
- I can't.
- [Mr. Nishijima] Yes, you can, Tai.
You have to help your friends.
You kids are the future.
Your generation will write the next chapter.
Maybe for our entire world.
Maybe for the digital world, too.
So, dream big.
I believe in you.
(woeful music)
(loud blast)
(chopper blades whirring)
- [Pilot] Jet calling Delta.
You have friendly inbound on the bridge,
300 yards out to the east, over.
- [Delta] Roger that, chopper two.
We have visual, over.
Transport, you are clear on approach.
Checkpoint, Delta, out.
- Mei Mei, this is really brave of you.
- Thanks for stepping up.
- Well, I'm the right choice.
- Plus we're here to help you.
- You can count on it.
- You say that but I'm a little scared
we'll get swallowed up like Gatomon did.
(Digimon whimpering)
- Mm hmm, there's gotta be something
we can do.
I want Gatomon and Meicoomon back.
(Digimon whimpering)
- [Meiko] Oh no, look at the lights.
The city's entire electrical grid
is on its last legs.
It can't take much more of this.
Well, at least it'll be morning soon.
- But we don't have very much time.
Meiko, go ask Hackmon what he wants you to do.
- Should I go try to talk to her?
- No, that is not necessary.
All you have to do to lead her away
from the city is to walk away.
Ordinemon will go wherever you go.
- [Meiko] What makes you think that's still true?
The Meicoomon I knew is gone.
How do you know that creature up there
even recognizes me after all these changes?
- [Hackmon] Homeostasis believes the bonds
between Digimon and their partners are unbreakable.
They can survive any transformation.
(Meiko grunts)
- Assuming Homeostasis really is on our side.
I have my doubts.
- Homeostasis strives only for harmony and stability.
It does not take sides.
- Yeah, but what's that really mean?
Cause in that big battle, you certainly took sides.
You digivolved into Jesmon and tried
to destroy Meicoomon.
I'm sorry, I guess I don't have any right
to question what you're doing when it was my fault
for creating this whole problem in the first place.
- No need to apologize.
You are an innocent victim in this situation.
We involved you for our own reasons.
Personally, the reboot is not the course
of action I would choose.
(Meiko whimpers)
(ominous music)
- Poor Mei.
(rumbling)
- [Joe] Oh, check it out, guys.
She's on the move again.
- Maybe Meiko can save her.
- Almost doesn't matter.
- What do you mean?
- Even if she stops, our world
is still in trouble. (Joe and Mimi gasps)
Homeostasis is obviously determined
to go through with the reboot.
- Yeah, and they think it's okay.
They know the results will be catastrophic,
but they don't seem to care.
- It's not their home.
King Drasil, Homeostasis , neither of them cares
about saving our world.
We're on our own. (all groan)
- If Ordinemon doesn't change back,
then what's going to happen to Meicoomon and Gatomon?
- But she's gotta change back.
- I know I'll be fine.
(mobile rings)
- It's Izzy.
What's up?
- [Izzy] Matt, you're not going to believe this.
Davis and Ken Yolei and Cody just came back
from the digital world.
- Are you kidding me? - Huh?
- [Izzy] I don't have all the details yet,
so I don't know who found them
or how they got out of there,
but they're here.
They're in a hospital and apparently
they're all right.
Can you believe it?
They've been in the digital world the whole time.
- That's crazy.
Okay, keep us posted.
(Kari moaning)
(Patamon chattering)
(Patamon yelps)
- You're awake.
Here, have some water.
- [Kari] Thank You.
- [T.K.] How are you feeling?
- Huh?
Like I might as well disappear again.
- Don't say that!
I'll always bring you back.
I wanna help you but you have to talk to me.
Don't let the sadness win.
(Kari groans)
Trust me, Kari, it's okay.
I'll always be here for you. (Patamon whimpers)
Always.
- You're touching, I didn't see anything,
I swear, I wasn't even in the same room.
(eerie rumbling)
(Kari gasps)
Ah, what's that?
(all gasping)
- [Kari] Gatomon is still in there somewhere.
(rumbling)
I have to go.
I have to do something.
- Meicoomon, come here.
(waves crashing)
(eerie music)
(rumbling)
(Meicoomon screeching)
(roaring pulsations)
(all grunting)
(Meicoomon screeching)
- [King Drasil] Ah yes, Ordinemon.
Bring down all your friends to join
our lovely party.
(growling)
(squawking)
Together we will destroy this world completely.
Let the humans weep and wail as they watch
everything they have built burn to ashes.
(King Drasil laughs maniacally)
All hail King Drasil.
(ominous music)
(tinkling)
(intense music)
- Meicoomon, Gatomon, are you still in there?
Have all the memories of your partners been erased?
- Meicoomon!
- Please remember!
(Meicoomon roaring)
- I'm sure our friends are still there somewhere,
deep inside.
- Yeah.
- But if it comes right down to it,
we may have to fight them.
- Yeah, I know.
- Are you with me?
- But I can't digivolve.
I need time.
- That's okay, because there's still
a lot of things you can do.
There are some things we Digimon can do
that no one else can.
- [Agumon] You're right, and it's time we went into action.
- [All] Hmm.
- Matt will make the right decision.
We just have to make sure that when he does, we're ready.
- [Both] Hmm.
- Meicoomon and Gatomon are still our friends,
this is not gonna be easy.
- [Soldier] Should we strike, sir, or give it more time?
- Time's up, send the men.
- [Strike Force Soldier] Strike Force Delta here,
what are your orders?
(energetic music)
Target acquired, all gunships, fire when ready.
(soldier screaming)
I've got a clean shot, here goes nothing.
(Meicoomon roaring)
(soldier screaming)
- [Control] Chopper force, do not close engage target.
Artillery units, you are clear to fire.
Choppers, minimum distance, 300 yards.
Stand off and fire rockets.
(artillery firing)
(explosions)
(artillery fire)
(Intense battle music)
- Stop it!
- Why are they shooting at her?
- How are we ever gonna rescue her now?
(rockets exploding)
(digidestined gasping)
All that firepower, and it didn't even slow her down.
(upbeat battle music)
- [Soldier] This is Chopper three,
something's happening over here.
(soldier screaming)
- Gabumon, let's go.
- You got it.
- Gomamon.
- I'm on it.
- Palmon.
- I'm good.
- Biyomon, you ready?
- Let's do this.
(upbeat music)
- [All] Digivolve to...
(upbeat battle music)
(singing in foreign language)
- Togemon!
- Birdramon!
- Garurumon!
- Ikkakumon!
(singing in foreign language)
- Weregarurumon!
(roaring)
Digivolve to...
(singing in foreign language)
(rapid gunfire)
(explosions)
- [Soldier] Chopper force, retreat.
(roaring)
(singing in foreign language)
(both panting)
(growling(
- It's time, you good?
- Yeah.
(singing in foreign language)
- Patamon, digivolve to...
Angemon!
(singing in foreign language)
Angemon, digivolve to...
MagnaAngemon!
(zapping and explosions)
(growling)
- There's so many of them.
- How is MagnaAngemon supposed to
fight all of that?
(MagnaAngemon grunting)
(MagnaAngemon yelling)
(King Drasil laughing)
- I guess he's not, does that answer your question?
- (sighs) You again.
(King Drasil laughing)
- If only you could see your faces.
I'm glad to run into you, because I wanted to thank you.
So nice of you to make my job easier.
In fact, I have Kari to thank for all of this.
You're the one who was so determined
to stop Homeostasis from destroying Meicoomon
that you kept your brother, Tai, from acting,
and that solved my biggest problem.
- Lay off!
- So, now you see how not being able
to control your emotions can lead
to serious problems.
You freed me up to destroy your entire world,
and that's exactly what I'm going to do.
Wait for it.
Almost.
He's here!
(grunting)
(screaming)
- MagnaAngemon, no!
- Oh man, is that all you got?
I was hoping you could play at a much higher level.
- Please, no!
(growling)
(explosions)
(footsteps approach)
(eerie ambience)
- [Meicoomon] Meiko.
- [Kari] It's showing me Meiko's memories, but why?
(Kari gasps)
(Meicoomon crying)
- Gatomon.
- It'll be all right.
(Meicoomon gasps)
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm just here to give you a message, Kari.
- What message, Gatomon?
(kari gasps)
Gatomon, what's happened to you?
- This isn't about me.
- Don't leave.
- The bad things that have happened have been
too much for Meicoomon.
She's a gentle soul, and she suffered so much,
more than any of us.
She needs your help to end this.
(Meicoomon crying)
She doesn't want to be scared anymore.
Listen to me, okay?
All the light you will need is inside Meicoomon.
- Gatomon.
(Kari gasps)
- [T.K.] Good, you're awake.
- Did I miss anything?
- [T.K.] Just some more end of the world
as we know it stuff.
- [Kari] I saw Gatomon in some place filled with data,
and she gave me a message.
- What did she say?
- All the light you will need is inside Meicoomon.
I don't remember anything else.
What do you think she was trying to tell me, T.K.?
- Coming from Kari, it's probably some kind of prophecy.
It sounds like one.
Any idea what it means.
- [T.K.] Nope.
- She definitely has some strange powers.
All the light you will need.
(Izzy gasps)
Hold on a sec.
(alarm chirping)
I just got an alarm and some kind of countdown
on my screen, I think the reboots
about to start.
- Can't you just hit the snooze button?
- Time to bug out, Tentomon.
- Hey, that's my line.
(roaring)
- I've got you, WereGarurumon.
- [Mimi] Get her, Togemon.
(Togemon yelling)
- Go!
(WereGarurumon growling)
(grunting)
(intense battle music)
(WereGarurumon growling)
- Get in there!
Go, Ikkakumon.
(Togemon yelling)
- Firing needle spray!
Take that, you overgrown mermaid.
- [Birdramon] Multi fire missiles.
I've got you, Togemon.
(explosion)
(grunting)
(yelling)
(Meicoomon roaring)
(groaning)
(crackling)
(loud thud)
(all groaning and moaning)
- This is a disaster, nothing we do
has any effect on her.
(artillery firing)
(explosions)
(Ordinemon roaring)
(forlorn music)
(squawking)
- I've got you, Togemon.
(fiery explosion)
(forlorn music)
(Mimi gasps)
(multiple explosions)
(large explosion)
(electricity crackling)
- [Kari] No, you have to stop this, Meicoomon, please.
There's gotta be something we can do.
- Hang on, my friend.
(groaning)
- Everything about this is wrong.
If Tai were here, what would he do?
- [Hackmon] It's beyond your control.
The reboot has begun.
All suffering will soon end.
Homeostasis will make certain of that.
- Shut up!
Stop telling us how great this reboot is.
Homeostasis has done nothing to help
us since this whole thing started.
We're gonna save the world our way, without you.
(phone ringing)
All right, Izzy, what do you got?
- [Izzy] I'm glad you guys made it.
Meiko, let me borrow your digi device for a sec.
- [Meiko] Okay.
- Just as I thought.
I've been trying to figure out the meaning
of Kari's message.
All the light you will need is inside Meicoomon.
- And what did you come up with?
- Well, remember after the reboot
of the digital world, how Meicoomon
was the only one of our Digimon
who didn't lose her memory?
It really puzzled me.
I knew what the reboot could do,
so I had tried to back up all our Digimon's
memories just in case.
I noticed some of Meicoomon's code
was mixed into Tentomon's.
At the time, I just figured a digital
glitch has caused it during battle,
but later, I found some of her data
in all of the Digimon.
I just ran a complete diagnostic
on Meiko's digi device, cross referencing
every network and system and digital channel
that I'm aware of.
Take a look at this.
This shows Meicoomon's carrying
a massive amount of memory data
from herself and from all of our Digimon.
- All?
Did you just say all?
- So, their memories can get downloaded
again somehow?
Are Patamon's memories in there too?
- All there.
- You know, I miss Meicoomon.
I like her a lot.
- Could it be?
- Hi.
- [Izzy] It might explain why meicoomon was able
to grow so powerful so quickly.
She had all our Digimon's data.
- Must have been crowded in there.
- [Izzy] I found something else in here too.
I'm positive this folder must be special.
It's the only one that's password protected.
For the sake of argument, let's assume
that fear is what causes Meicoomon to change.
Remember when we first met her?
She was child-like and bonded to Meiko.
I believe the code containing
her gentle spirit and good memories
was corrupted and replaced by frightening
dark data instead.
If Meicoomon's original data is in that
folder, I can use it to restore the memories
she had before fear made her violent,
her memories of Meiko.
- Well, get to it.
I don't want to experience the mother
of all reboots.
- That's the best choice we've got.
Nothing else has worked.
Let's give it a try, Izzy.
- But we don't know the password.
We don't even know whose password
it is in the first place.
- Actually we do.
It's Meicoomon's password.
We need you to think hard, Meiko.
What password would Meicoomon use?
- I have no idea.
(background explosions)
(artillery gunfire)
(zapping)
(loud explosion)
- Did she has a favorite saying?
Did you have any special nicknames for her?
- Nicknames.
- Why don't we try your name? - [Izzy] M-E-I-K-O.
(beeping)
Okay, that's not it.
Try again.
(beeping)
Mei?
Nope, it's not any of the variations of Meiko's name.
- [Mimi] Think of some word that meant a lot to her.
- Come on, Meiko, we're running out of time.
- Just think back to when you first met.
Maybe there was something you said
that she would have remembered.
Do you recall anything like that?
(gentle piano music)
(Meiko gasps)
(Meicoomon roaring)
- [Soldier] This is chopper nine.
The creatures are everywhere,
they're coming right at us.
- What was the password?
- I had forgotten, but it was the first
word I had taught Meicoomon,
and the first thing I said to her.
Because she had just agreed to be my partner.
Thank you.
We're so lucky we met all of you.
What do you say to our new friends, Meicoomon?
Dandan.
- Dandan.
- Huh?
Say what?
- That's thank you in Meicoomon speak.
- [Mimi] You tried to pull one over on us.
- [Matt] It's not Meicoomon speak.
It's your dialect.
- [Izzy] You guys, it's working.
All the data's being transferred.
- [Soldier] Model five report,
what's going on down there?
(soft music)
(gasping)
All units, hold your fire.
I repeat, hold your fire.
(mellow piano music)
- What is all this?
Is that Tai?
I remember.
I remember it all now.
Tai.
My partner.
- It's all coming back.
Matt and I went through so much together,
and it was so hard to say goodbye.
So hard.
- [Gabumon] Being with you always made me so happy, Joe,
even though you didn't always understand why.
- Oh, T.K., even when I was infected,
you stayed with me the whole time.
I remember now.
- Sora, look at us, we were great friends, weren't we?
Now I know why you were being so kind to me.
Can you ever forgive me for being so mean?
- It's amazing.
We spent so much time together, Izzy.
And you worked so hard to get us here.
I hope our stories are safe inside your big brain.
- I can't believe how lovely all these memories are, Mimi.
We're perfect together.
We're going to be partners forever.
- [Matt] Look, it's MetalGarurumon.
- [Joe] There's Vikemon.
- [Kari] And Rosemon.
- [Mimi] Is that Pheonixmon?
- [T.K.] There goes Seraphimon.
- [Izzy] I see HerculesKabuterimon.
They all digivolved to mega level and are flying
to Ordinemon.
- (gasps) Kari, I see you.
I'm coming back to you.
(grunting)
Kari!
- It's Gatomon.
- [Gatomon] What on Earth is happening,
what is this?
(ominous music)
(static and explosions)
(Meicoomon whimpering)
This was not expected.
The awakening of old memories within the Libra
has also given it new powers.
(all gasping)
(mellow orchestral music)
- She has all her memories again, right?
So, why isn't she turning back into Meicoomon?
- Maybe it's gonna take a little more time
for her to change.
- [Izzy] It's not her size that's slowing it down,
it's the size of all the data that's being restored.
Years of memories created before the reboot
are being recovered and coming back
to our Digimon, as well as to her, to Ordinemon.
Gatomon and Meicoomon's data will probably
be the last piles to be recovered.
- This is truly the power of the Digidestined.
It's unbelievable.
- [Izzy] Hackmon, stop the reboot.
The data isn't completely restored yet.
We just need a couple more minutes.
If we're successful, the reboot won't be necessary.
(intense music)
- [Gatomon] Kari, help, it's pulling me back in.
- Gatomon.
(Gatomon yelling)
- No way.
- [Izzy] Ordinemon is trying to restore harmony
and stability.
(Meicoomon roaring)
- [T.K.] Less than two minutes until the reboot.
Are we gonna make it?
- I hope so.
Ordinemon is heading for that portal.
If she goes through it, we'll never
see Gatomon or Meicoomon again.
(Meicoomon roaring)
- Don't go, don't leave me.
(zapping)
- [T.K.] Something stopped her.
- [Matt] Jesmon.
(whooshing)
(all gasping)
(groaning)
(Gatomon groaning)
- Gatomon!
I'm coming, hang on.
I'm right here.
You're safe now.
- Of course I am, I've got nine lives.
(all chuckling)
- I guess Homeostasis came through,
with only 11 seconds to go, the reboot countdown
finally stopped.
- Then we made it.
- What a relief, I was sweating.
- So we're back to normal again?
- No, we're not done.
- [Kari] She's, she's still Ordinemon.
Why didn't she turn back into Meicoomon?
- It should have happened already.
- All the data's there.
there must be something blocking
the memories from integrating into her fractal code.
What's this?
(squawking)
Losing all those memories freed up a lot of space.
- What's so bad about that?
- Someone is uploading new files to Ordinemon.
It's King Drasil.
- [King Drasil} (Laughs) That's right.
Say goodbye to your world and gaze upon the glory
of King Drasil's paradise.
(ominous music)
- (gasps) What did she ever to do deserve this?
Stop, stop making her suffer.
(intense music)
(rustling)
(groaning)
Meicoomon, no!
- [Matt] Run, Meiko.
- I gotta help her.
- [T.K.] Hey, Agumon.
(Meiko whimpering)
(singing in foreign language)
- I'm so happy to see you again.
I've missed you.
- You're late.
- Yeah, sorry.
But I'm here now.
Let's end this.
- Yeah, you got it, tai.
(singing in foreign language)
Agumon, digivolve to...
(roaring)
Greymon!
(singing in foreign language)
Greymon, digivolve to...
MetalGreymon!
Metalgreymon, digivolve to...
WarGreymon!
(singing in foreign language)
WarGreymon, digivolve to...
Omnimon!
- Tai, don't attack Meicoomon, she's one of us.
- Oh, Kari.
- Don't do it.
Everyone has both good and evil inside.
I just know the good part of Meicoomon
is still alive.
You've got to find a way to make her
remember who she is.
Save her.
- I hope you never change.
You might hate me for doing this,
but this is how it has to end.
(swooshing)
(zapping)
- We're no longer the Digidestined kids.
Our destiny is ours to decide now.
No matter how painful, we have to save our own future.
- Tai, if you destroy Meicoomon, I'll never forgive you.
But you're still my brother, and if you think
this is the only way, then I'll battle alongside you.
- In that case, I'll join the fight too.
(upbeat battle music)
- Gatomon, digivolve to...
Angewomon!
Angewoman, digivolve to...
Magnadramon!
(upbeat battle music)
(zapping)
(explosions)
(groans)
(yelling)
- Fire tornado!
(explosions)
- What does it mean?
Please be merciful.
- [Izzy] Look, Omnimon's gathering the power
of all our Digimon.
(majestic music)
- [all] Whoa.
- [Kari] Check it out.
- [Meiko] Look at that.
(zapping)
(majestic music)
- [Joe] Pro...
- [Izzy] Digious.
(high energy music)
(Meicoomon yelling)
- [Tai] It's almost over.
- [Matt] Yeah.
(Meicoomon yelling)
(sizzling)
(roaring)
- Yeah!
(zaps)
(yelling)
- Oh, Meicoomon, I can't save you.
- [Meicoomon] Meiko.
I'm here.
- You're alive.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, I understand.
- Dandan.
(Meiko crying)
Don't cry, Meiko, it's all right.
(Meicoomon laughing)
(Meiko crying)
(sorrowful music)
(waves crashing)
- [Meiko] Dandan, Meicoomon.
- Oh well, it was fun while it lasted.
Such beautiful destruction.
(laughing)
But there's always tomorrow, right?
You can find a little child inside everyone.
A little child is ready to play.
Oh well, Daemon could be next,
or even Diaboromon.
(Meiko sighs)
- [Gabumon] Matt.
- [Gatomon] Kari. - Well look whose back.
- [Mimi] Tentomon.
- I think I'm hungry.
- [Patamon] No more fighting, right, T.K.?
- [Mimi] Let's all go home.
- [T.K.] Hi, Meiko.
I can't believe it's been three months
since you left and went back to Totori.
The city was really a mess, as you know.
All the damage is taking a long time to fix.
But life is slowly getting back to normal around here.
We heard Homeostasis finally shut down King Drasil.
The other Digidestined kids who came
back from the digital world are fine,
but the people around here still don't
trust Digimon very much.
Izzy's working on a system that will
let us go between the human world
and the digital world without
using any type of digi devices.
Amazing, huh?
I hope we can all go to the digital world
together someday.
That would be great.
Until then, please take care of yourself.
- Tai's going to cram school?
- Yeah, Kari told me about it the other day.
He changed his college plans. - Really?
- He said it was because of something
that Mr. Nishijima told him,
how we have to create our own futures.
- Well, that's one hell of a homework assignment.
- What future do I want?
Hmm.
- If we really get to choose, then I'll
head out to space.
- Sora, I like your new hairstyle.
- Really?
Thanks.
- Huh, is it different?
- Brother, you are hopeless.
- hey, they all came together.
Yay!
(giggling)
- [Matt] Well, you gonna call or what?
And don't say anything stupid.
(phone ringing)
- [Meiko] Tai, is that you?
- [Tai] Uh, yeah.
- [Meiko] How have you been?
- [Tai] Fine, everybody's fine.
- It's been a long time since we talked.
- Yeah.
- [Meiko] It's good to hear from you.
- Good to be heard.
Did the box come?
- Yes, it got here today.
That was so nice of you.
I certainly wasn't expecting you guys to each
send me a Christmas present.
Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- [Sora] What's with the silence?
- Come on, get to the point.
- I knew we should have given him notes.
- Tai.
- Okay, okay.
Listen, Meiko, I know we all went through a lot together.
I think about it all the time.
No matter what--
- [Sora] Keep going.
(shushing)
- [Tai] What I'm trying to say is, no matter what, uh...
- Oh come on.
No matter what happens, we'll be friends forever.
You think she heard me?
- [Meiko] Oh, Agumon, I'd know that voice anywhere.
- [Tai] Maybe in the future we should
let Agumon handle the phone calls,
because he kind of wrapped up the way everybody
here feels about you, Meiko.
- Aww.
- So heart wrenching.
- [Meiko] Thanks, dandan.
- [Sora] Look, it's snowing.
- [Palmon] So pretty.
- [Mimi] Can I talk to Mei Mei, next?
- [Sora] No, me first.
- [Joe] Hey, what about me?
- [Matt] Hand over that phone.
- [Kari] No way.
- [Biyomon] Good luck.
- [Gomamon] I never get to talk, not a word
this whole episode.
- [Joe] Gomamon.
- [Tai] You guys.