The math exam's last problem.
Half of our grade was weeded out before getting this far.
The other half had absolutely no time to spare.
And was so exhausted they
didn't have the energy to solve it.
The only students still standing with any chance
of earning full marks in the few minutes left...
were these two.
What was it Nagisa always used to say?
You're so talented, Karma.
How is there such a gap between the both of us?
Guess some people are just geniuses, huh?
Easy for you to say.
If you ask me,
it's not all that cut n' dry who the real genius is here.
Talent is usually an invisible trait.
More often than not, it's the
result of work other people don't see.
Take Sugino.
He can fit in easily with anyone, anywhere.
Or Okuda, who can totally lose herself
in something she's passionate about.
Even Terasaka, who dives right
in without a second thought.
From where I'm standing, we're in the same boat.
Everybody has something,
some hidden special ability they take for granted.
We're all geniuses.
We all have a talent.
Still...
The issue at hand is whether or not I can filter
the answer to this problem through the lens of my own.
C'mon, man...
Snap out of it, you don't have time for this.
Atoms.
Body-centered cubic units...
Extraneous details.
Stay focused.
Broken down to essentials, the problem is simple.
Solve for the volume of your specific domain,
in a box, surrounded by enemies.
When both sides are evenly matched,
their attacks meet in the middle.
Of course, from there inward is my domain!
That's one enemy down! Ha!
Nice try.
But I'm afraid you won't be
encroaching on my turf anytime soon.
Eight enemies total, surrounding the cube's perimeter.
If I determine the volume of the
eight areas I've effectively sealed off,
and subtract that from the volume of the cube,
I'm left with A-Zero, my specific domain!
Once I've locked down this space, I'll have the answer.
Come on, come on!
Ruling my own domain.
Nice overall theme for my goal in life!
A different sort of ruler than my father.
He's obsessed.
The man only cares about proving his "rational"
approach to education superior to all others.
His method may break a person's spirit,
but it won't educate them.
It's time to set the record straight,
give him a piece of my mind! I have to take control!
That...
is my responsibility as your son!
There it is!
The volume of one of the sealed-off areas is an
aggregate of one hexagonal and three triangular pyramids!
Hang on a minute...
This problem doesn't even call for difficult math.
The whole thing's divided out
into this one itty-bitty little cube...
and if it's supposedly an atomic crystal...
Yeah,
everything on the outside is just more of the same.
Which means...
The world doesn't end here.
From where I'm standing,
everyone has their own talent.
Their own specific domain.
We are all in the same boat.
I just couldn't see it before.
All I could see from inside this box
were fragments of the bigger picture.
I have my area, they have theirs.
We all do.
That's how this works.
How it's always worked.
Everyone's the same size,
the same distance apart.
And if we're all cut from the same box,
those eight contiguous boxes can be
broken up into the same proportion.
Each person's individual fragment
accounts for one-eighth of the whole.
So what it boils down to is: This box contains
one whole me and one-eighth of eight other people.
In other words,
inside this cube, the ratio of me to
the other eight fragments is one-to-one.
Simple!
And if it's one-to-one inside the box,
the volume of the area I can call my own
is up to one-half of the cube!
Voila! That's my specific domain!
Piece of cake.
They taught us this stuff in primary school.
No need for long, drawn-out equations.
No need for big, complicated diagrams.
Nope.
You just have to adjust for the fact
there's a world outside yourself.
Pencils down!
Time's up, son. The test is over.
Just one more line.
Damn it! I knew the answer!
And like that,
the tidal wave of our end-of-term exams broke.
Alright-y, class!
Let's all have a look at your compiled exam papers.
Did those crucial second blades manage
to pierce their intended targets, I wonder?
No splitting hairs over a point or two, understood?
The only thing we're concerned with right now is whether
these scores secured a place for you in the top 50.
Unless I'm mistaken, the main campus ought to be
posting the results for all to see as we speak.
So I see no reason we can't do the same in E-Class...
You... you're kidding me...
I'm forty-sixth?!
Isn't Terasaka dead last even in here, though?
If he came in forty-sixth, then that must mean...
Is this for real?
We did it!
And we beat out the Big Five for the top spots!
Go us!
Karma! Dude, you got first place!
Feels pretty good, doesn't it?
Earning the highest rank on
such an unforgiving battlefield.
Whatever. I guess so, yeah.
It appears your contest with Asano the
perfectionist came to a head on that last,
and I must say, particularly thorny, math problem.
Yeah, about that.
Not sure I could say exactly why, but...
If I hadn't spent the past year with you guys,
I don't think I could have solved it.
That's the kind of problem it was.
Tough haul gettin' to this point, though, huh?
Yeah! I don't believe it!
And, well, all wanted this so badly!
We actually beat A-Class.
Almost sounds too good to be true.
We're back on track for the top tier schools!
The ladies'll be throwin' themselves at our feet!
Way to go us, right?
Yeah! Chicks everywhere!
Feels like a final episode.
Wait a sec! It's not over!
Uh. What's with that look, man?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, it's just that, so much
has happened since I came here.
I'm really glad I got kicked down.
Aw, why you gotta be all depressing, huh?
Besides, why make an ugly face
when this clown has it covered?
What does that mean?!
Terasaka! Easy, you're choking him!
Whaddya think?
What do I think?
I think I can get into my dream school now.
What are you gonna study? Architecture, right?
Yeah. I'm angling for a high school
that's big on engineering and science.
Hm.
Ha! Man, those A-Class dillweeds.
What I wouldn't give to see the
looks on their faces right now!
Bet'cha anything they never thought
in a million years they'd lose to us!
Now, to be fair, on their part A-Class
performed quite well on the first half of the exams.
But as the questions grew increasingly
difficult on the second half,
more and more students found
themselves running out of steam.
Yeah, well, that's what they get.
Whoever you are, nobody's bloodlust holds out that long.
Even after intensive assassination drills.
It's next to impossible staying in
that frame of mind for an entire day.
If you expect to boost your system on bloodlust,
cramming isn't the way to go.
You have to nurture it over time, slow and steady.
How'd this happen?
How'd we lose after everything we put ourselves through?
Your study methods worked against you.
You were set up to lose.
That's what it comes to.
Not that my scores are anything to brag about, either...
Rest assured, I'll put this frustration to work.
Come high school, I'll be on top again,
doing my damnedest to blaze a trail for the rest of you.
Just... All I ask is for your support.
Asano...
You mean that?
Intriguing.
Strong words for someone who's lost
the fight on which he staked his future.
Principal Asano.
All we may count on in life is the unknown,
what seems arbitrary can in
fact be what costs you everything.
One can't be sure until the battle is over.
This, you see, is why I insist on always playing to win.
I have an obligation to prepare
my students for the unknown.
Between now and graduation, you have much to learn.
Principal Asano, sir?
Hm?
All due respect, it's clear to us...
that your methods
aren't going to help us beat E-Class.
Defeat made them stronger.
Asano's taken that lesson to heart.
We're no match for them, sir...
Their strength is just too... what's the word?
Adaptable.
Forgive us, sir.
We fell short of our goal.
If you think it's appropriate,
transfer us down to E-Class.
I think there's a lot to learn
from their way of doing things.
Well, Principal?
What do you have to say to that?
Asano!
Are you all right?!
Your face looks like it's glitching out.
Uh-oh.
Don't tell my I'm finally seeing your fatherly side?
Excuse us, sir. We have to be going.
Well, boys and girls!
You've officially qualified to
be transferred out of E-Class.
Anyone here ready to leave the mountain?
Yeah. You'd like that, wouldn't you?
I don't think so, we've found our second blades.
This is where things get serious!
If you know a place better suited
to assassination, we're all ears!
Gluttons for punishment, I see.
I suppose, then, as your reward
I ought to divulge my most notable weakness...
Huh?
Ah! Our building!
Evacuate the premises, please.
Principal Asano!
The Board reached a unanimous decision.
The old campus building is to be demolished today.
Oh, don't worry.
You'll be moved to an affiliate
school slated to open next year.
We need students to performance-test
their newest facilities.
Wait, you're farming us out somewhere?!
It's not all that bad.
Let us call it a social experiment.
The building is state-of-the-art,
with closed-circuit surveillance cameras
and escape-proof architecture.
It's similar to a prison.
The culmination of my educational philosophy.
But, you can't move us right now!
We won't go!
We're graduating from this campus!
I see you'll spare nothing to see your methods vindicated.
Correct.
Oh, and incidentally,
your services will no longer be required.
Mm.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
This is the part where I terminate you.
Whoa! He just got slapped with walking papers!
I don't believe it.
The man actually played the forbidden ace-in-the-hole!
Ah! This is wrongful dismissal!
The Octopus is ridiculously
susceptible to this mode of attack.
Do super creatures have a legal right to protest?
Now don't go jumping to conclusions...
Actually, this is no more than a
clever means of distracting you.
When I said "terminate," I meant it literally.
I'm here to kill you.
Eh?
You see, Koro-sensei...
You don't fit with my vision.
He can't be serious.
Look, man, we know you're a big Machiavelli and all that,
but I'd tread carefully in your shoes.
The Octopus is clever.
Hold off on the demolition for now, if you would please...
I have unfinished business inside.
Where the hell'd that notice of dismissal come from?
This is crazy. What is he thinking?
Now, then, Koro-sensei.
I assume you don't wish to be fired?
And furthermore that you wish to preserve this classroom?
Well, what would you say to a little wager?
What's he getting at?
I've prepared five subjects' worth of exam questions,
and five live grenades.
Four contain anti-Sensei projectiles.
That is, they are fatal to you.
One is fatal to humans.
All five grenades are identical in appearance and smell,
and designed so that once their pins are pulled
they will explode the instant their handles are raised.
I've pulled the pins,
and carefully placed the grenades between
random pages of each test booklet, handles down.
You must open each book and solve the
problem in the top right-hand corner.
But, that'll push the handles to the up position!
That's correct.
Your teacher will almost certainly
be hit with an explosion.
Furthermore,
he can't move until the problem has been solved.
The first four books
are yours and yours alone to open and solve.
I will be taking the remainder for myself.
Kill me, or force me to withdraw,
and victory belongs unquestionably to you.
You and the E-Class students will be allowed to stay here.
Agreed? Terasaka, look sharp.
Use the appropriate formula
to find Koro-sensei's odds of winning.
Why do I have to solve something so messed up?
An anti-Sensei grenade won't kill you...
The real one will, naturally,
but we'd have to save it for the end, so let's see.
Four-fifths
times three-fourths
times two-thirds
times one-half equals one-fifth.
So... 20%.
Well done!
Yeah, but hold on:
The Octopus sits through four explosions
before you even take a turn!
This game is rigged! You can just bow
out if you don't like the way it's going.
Dunno about you, but I call that unfair!
Young man.
Hm?
Life is unfair. It's chock full with injustice.
Especially if you're not fortunate enough
to be one of the strong.
Don't you see?
This is why I teach the true meaning of strength.
So, then. Shall we proceed?
Show me how serious you really are
about your chosen profession, Koro-sensei.
In fact, if I were you,
I wouldn't waste a single moment.
Yes, of course.
Let's jump right in.
He threatens dismissal,
devises a game that's clearly in his favor.
And there's no way out.
Mathematically, the odds of it succeeding
are better than anything we've tried.
The most important blade is strength...
This man is an assassin.
Open, solve the problem, and close.
Move quickly enough and the grenade won't go off.
Speed is your specialty.
This should be walk in the park, yes?
Uh, yes! Excellent point!
Planar calculations!
Oh, th-this couldn't be easier!
A-All you gotta to do is borrow from the tens
and get three with four left over,
or, ah, actually I believe it's three or thereabouts.
I know how you are with puzzles.
You get flustered; Your processing speed declines.
This trap is almost too perfect.
Koro-sensei...
We'll call the first one a hit... Bravo.
Only three more to go and you'll have won the game.
Now, please move on to the next
problem before you've regenerated.
This is B.S.!
No way can he survive three more of those explosions!
He's seriously gonna be taken out!
And the setup is so friggin' simple!
You see my point?
The weak have to rely on assassination,
whereas the strong may kill at their leisure,
when and however they please.
Soon, I will plant institutions across the nation
that drive home this truth.
The Ministry of Defense has been generous.
Between them and the bounty,
I'll build affiliate schools all over the world.
It's always about education with him.
Come now, Koro-sensei.
Validate my ideology.
Be the cornerstone of my vision.
Surprise!
Tell us, Kunudon!
That festival was a real white-knuckler!
Ah, but it looks like those E-Class losers
are down for the count for the count at last!
That's all she wrote!
Ha, ha, ha, ha! Hey there Losers!
Just desserts! Yay!
Oh, Mr. Principal!
What brings you into the studio?
Notice of dismissal!
I'm being... moved.
To E-Class?
Hooray for unemployment!
Woohoo!