End-of-term exams were over.
Victory was total,
but no sooner had we gotten the
results than the principal showed up,
Koro-sensei's walking papers in hand.
The man challenged his rival to a one-sided game.
Come now, Koro-sensei.
Validate my ideology and be the cornerstone of my vision.
Mm?
Alright-y, then!
Open, solved, and closed!
Fortunately, I just so happen to remember more or less
which questions are on what page
in this particular series of books.
Math was the only trouble spot.
That one's been loaned out to a student
for so long I'd forgotten.
You know these books backwards and forwards?
A rather remarkable coincidence.
Oh, not just these.
I've committed all of Japan's test materials to memory.
You say no moving out of the blast radius
until the given problem is solved?
Very well.
That little caveat is nothing to a passionate educator.
I'm sorry, sir.
You sincerely thought you'd gotten the better of me, huh?
My, my.
A-Class' crushing defeat must have you in a tizzy.
I'm afraid this one-dimensional stratagem
may wind up getting the better of you.
There we have it. The last book.
Your turn, I believe.
What does it feel like,
staring your own demise in the face?
They say one's life flashes before one's eyes.
What do you see, Principal?
What's flickering by in that exemplary brain?
Sir?
Mr. Asano?
Two monsters, teaching at the same school.
One to atone for his strength.
The other to atone for his weakness.
A noble effort, Ikeda.
Maybe next time. Hey.
A deal's a deal. So, study and behave yourself today.
Uh. Aw, dang! No fair, sir.
You're totally a superhuman or something.
Hey, Mr. Asano?
Why does a beast like you start a cram school
in an abandoned shack like this?
I'd have thought you'd graduated from some big college
with loads of credentials and stuff.
No offense, sir, but it seems
like a waste of talent to me.
Not to mention how far we all gotta hike.
Come now, Nagai.
Nothing is for naught in this world of ours.
This mountain is wonderfully scenic.
And the hike is good exercise.
What about funds?
Bet this place is in the red.
Don't worry, Mori my dear.
My stock portfolio more than makes up for the deficit.
I don't mean to brag, but I'm
something of a financial wiz.
As you can see, this month I'm happily in the black.
He's superhuman!
So why does someone so awesome
get into teaching in the first place?
If you wanna make us that awesome,
you've got your work cut out for you.
Don't overthink it.
All I ask is you try to be good students.
Remember, the bar is set differently for everyone.
But your enthusiasm is an asset, Ikeda.
As is Mori's cleverness.
And of course Nagai's diligence.
You see?
Each of you has your very own strength, but you're right.
I do have my work cut out for me:
To properly teach you,
I'm going to need to have all
your strengths combined and more.
The private cram school was off to a promising start.
Three students of my inaugural term were ideal.
In the peace and quiet of the mountain, I
could shape their minds to my heart's content.
A model education. My dream come true.
Ow!
Aw c'mon, don't be a baby. I gave you a heads-up.
Next time move. What're you, a snail?
Uh. We just got out.
Really? Why're you so rowdy?
Whatever. Basketball stars can't just study!
Gimme a break. I've got tons of pent-up energy!
You don't say? A basketball star?
Heh. Fine dream.
How 'bout you and I play a little one-on-one?
U-Uh. Yeah, right!
Like I could win against a superhuman!
Good point.
I have one or two abilities
you haven't cultivated in yourself just yet, huh?
Interesting.
Your classmates could just as well say the same about you.
I, uh, sorry, Nagai.
Oh, it's cool.
Everyone has faults.
We all have to grow into our strength, but also
come to understand how it affects those around us.
I put everything I had into my daily lesson plans.
In just one year the students
were coming along brilliantly.
What's this?
A Kunugi oak-leaf tie clip! Neat, huh?
We pooled our allowances together to buy it.
Pro'ly peanuts compared to what you make
off your stock portfolio.
Now, now.
Just because it's grown a thousand percent...
Wow. You seriously could've kept that to yourself.
I... I'll cherish this.
Ha, ha. Hey, you got us into our first-pick schools!
Yeah! No way we could've done it without you!
When I grow up, sir.
D'you, mind if I come and visit some time?
How time flies.
They'd grown into such wonderful students.
Parents saw my track record.
Soon, children enrolled from all over.
Three short years later, my
little cram school was booming.
Ah! How long has it been?
Ikeda! Great to hear from you!
Long time no see!
Things are going good for you, huh?
Can't complain. What can I do for you?
Oh, nothin' really.
I just wanted to catch up and see how you were doin'.
That's very kind. Thank you.
Uh, ah, what about you?
Not out there causing trouble, I hope?
Ha! No sir!
I'm just a regular Samaritan now, thanks to you!
Anyway, you sound busy. I should let you go.
Let's do dinner sometime! Your treat, of course.
Later!
I have business in that neck of the woods next week.
Perhaps I'll stop by.
They said it was a suicide.
Some horrible older boy on his team
drove him to it, apparently.
Used to beat him up, and take his money.
Poor thing couldn't take it anymore.
That's awful!
And he'd been such a sweet boy since junior high.
Still, though.
I mean, you'd think the young
man would stand up for himself.
What on earth have I been teaching these children?
How to be good students? What was I thinking?
Does dying make you a good student?
I have an obligation to make them strong,
or this will have been for nothing.
But then, what is strength?
Until I have the answer, I have no right to teach.
From there, things changed quickly.
I learned all sorts of strengths.
I sweet-talked the men who drove my student to suicide,
put them on the road toward a
disastrous gambling addiction.
That's how I fine-tuned my brainwashing techniques.
Soon, I opened another school,
and the old campus building that symbolized my weakness
would stand as a lesson to others.
Strong. I wanted to make them strong.
Strong young men and women who could survive,
sacrificing others if need be.
To that end,
I would need more funding, more staff.
If it could serve my goal, I would use it.
All to educate, to breed true strength.
Yet here I stand,
abandoned by the strong and the weak alike.
The only thing before me, certain death.
What will it be, Principal?
Will you open the last book, or fold?
You may be an exceptional human being, sir,
but taking a grenade blast won't end well for you.
This was your idea, 'case you forgot!
But hey it's no big deal, just gracefully admit defeat.
And just so you're aware, fire Koro-sensei all
you want, it doesn't make any difference to us.
Don't get us wrong,
it'll be sad to leave this place behind.
But whatever comes, we're going right along with him.
That's right!
Even if we gotta run away from home, or hole up in a cave!
We'll keep this class going.
It's not over until March!
Why have I indulged them this far?
E-Class has been a thorn in my side all year.
Such presumptuous, bald-faced defiance. Such a stain.
Koro-sensei.
Eh?
You may well destroy the Earth.
Even so, as far as my educational philosophy,
it would make absolutely no difference whatsoever.
Whether now, or in March,
death will come for us all in the end.
Strength won't matter.
My students won't suffer alone, and, in a way,
my vision will have been fulfilled.
Somebody forgot about my molt.
Your once-a-month trick?
And why precisely would you not use it on yourself?
Because I was saving it for you, silly man.
I suspected if I won, odds were fairly good
you'd think nothing of blowing yourself to bits.
But, how could you be so sure of what I'd do?
Because, we have a lot in common.
We're both stubborn education fiends,
willing to forfeit our lives
for the privilege of molding young minds.
I hope you won't mind,
but I took the liberty of speaking
to your old cram school students.
I wanted to get their impressions of you as a teacher.
Imagine my surprise upon learning that the
idea of teaching you exemplified 12 years ago
is identical to mine.
Though as far as students are concerned, I've been lucky.
E-Class is a marvelous proving ground.
There are a fair number of students, you see,
and they all share the same predicament.
These boys and girls work as a team,
unafraid to ask for help or to hold each other up.
And if I may point out,
credit for conceiving of and implementing
this class, goes first and foremost to you.
There you have it. Don't you see, sir?
You've been abiding by the same
vision you began with all along.
Incidentally, I'm the only thing this knife can kill.
The taking of human life plays no part in our approach.
You and I are one and the same, Principal.
We don't teach killing, we teach life.
So why not stay true to ourselves
and continue down this road?
Playing outdoors is fine, Ikeda.
Playing hooky? I don't think so.
Heh. I'm an athlete. I can't be cooped up.
Right? Gimme a break!
I propose a game.
Once every school day.
You have my permission to try and attack me.
Manage to get a hit and I'll
let you skip class for that day.
You serious?! You'd really let me do that?!
Sure.
You gotta deal, sir!
If I hit ya, I get to ditch! No take-backs.
You have to see it through!
My philosophy's always been right on the nose.
Students have to be strong.
My successes over the past 12 years prove this.
And, I suppose, so long you
acknowledge its proper function,
I see no reason why you and E-Class
can't remain here as you are.
Still too proud to admit defeat, I see.
Oh, and do mind if pop by and try my
hand at killing you once in a while?
Be my guest.
Always happy to oblige a worthy rival.
That pristine facade is crumbling.
You've lost. I can tell by your face.
Something I can help you with, Asano?
No, no. Just thought I'd come by to cheer you up.
That and show you my wounded face.
Perhaps some monetary compensation
would help ease the pain a bit?
Ha, ha. Feel free to take me to court.
Though of course, don't expect to win.
You'll never win against me, Asano.
No matter how strong you think you've become.
And what makes you so certain of that?
Because I don't intend to ever stop growing.
As a teacher. Or as a father.
So, yeah. About that reward?
Um? Oh, yes!
In return for ranking in the top 50,
I promised to share a critical weakness.
Well, children,
I have in fact very little power. I'm designed for speed.
When at a perfect standstill,
one of my tentacles can be
held down even by a single person.
Hey, wait, if eight of us teamed-up on you all at once...
You're saying we could essentially paralyze you, right?
Man, if we had known that sooner,
this would have been easy as pie!
This is bunk!
You only told us 'cause you knew it'd be impossible!
Not having any luck?
The trick is to pretend you're
hand-fishing for slime eels.
A drama festival?!
But we're about to take high school entrance exams.
I know, I know.
I did complain to the student council.
Asano fired back, though.
What's the problem?
Memorizing lines and stage directions
quickly is good mental exercise.
It's part of the curriculum.
Besides, you'll figure something out.
You always do.
At least he gave us respect.
You could be the leading lady, Nagisa!
Just, y'know, throwin' it out there.
Why do I get a bad feeling about this?
What about Kayano?
Huh?
The preschoolers adored you.
You had 'em on the edge of their seats.
Um, I don't know if that...
That ain't gonna play in junior high.
People need to identify with the
main character, and you're too short.
Shut up!
I'd rather be in charge of handling props anyway.
Uh...
Right.
So then for our main crew, Mimura will direct,
and Hazam will write, naturally.
Mm?
Thoughts on our leads?
You know, I'm available.
You're supposed to be a state secret!
This is our play! No adults allowed!
But I have the makings of a phenomenal lead!
What if this is my one and only shot?
You can't deny me the limelight!
All right, then. I have a play.
One where you can be the lead without upstaging us.
Everybody's happy.
Great. Sounds like plan.
Let's put on a show the likes of which
those main campus chumps have never seen!
Okay. E-Class goes on next.
Heh. I say we eat loudly and
sneer through the entire performance!
A peach.
Uh...
The greatest medical minds are baffled,
but by some strange miracle there's a baby growing inside.
Upon hearing this, the old man's eyes lit up.
"Excellent," he thought.
"This peach will bring riches!"
What a stroke of luck! A miracle indeed!
People will pay good money to see this peach! They'll
come from far and wide! I'll be richer than any king!
Mm?
Divorce papers.
The old woman had been thinking
of leaving him for some time.
His greed, choice of words, and complete
disregard for child welfare decided her.
At long last, she's had enough of his selfish nature.
The marriage was over.
For good.
The rift between them was as wide as the river
in which she'd washed his clothes for over
30 years without thanks or acknowledgement.
The atmosphere at home had become as dry and as
suffocating as the smoke from a mountain wildfire.
The peach rightfully belongs to me.
I am the head of this household, do you understand woman?!
I'll decide how to divide our property!
Uh?!
Lawyers.
We'll be representing your wife from here on out.
Any and all communication
must be handled through our office directly.
Regarding the miracle peach.
Since this marriage has technically
been on the rocks for over a decade,
we're well past the mandated
cut-off date for carving up your combined assets.
Oh, and fair warning: Our client
is seeking reparations for emotional distress.
For 30 years she'd born her husband's cruelty,
his disinterest.
Not only had he consistently
failed to bring home the bacon,
the old woman possessed incontrovertible
evidence of his infidelity.
In court, he wouldn't have a prayer.
In desperation he hired a band of thugs to strong-arm her.
But, being incompetent, they were hauled off by police.
The old woman shed her misery and started over.
She gave the miracle peach pride
of place in her lovely new home.
Life was sweet, as it had been in her youth.
Happiness and serenity surrounded her.
Hooray!
A dog, a monkey, and a pheasant.
An unlikely trio, trained to attack human beings,
devouring their food with the abandon of
wild animals, in thrall to their wicked master.
All-consuming greed had driven
the old man to unspeakable evil.
Perhaps the fabled demon-haunted island of
Onigashima is none other than the human heart?
The miracle peach will bear its child very soon.
Will it, too, be prey to demons?
Uh...
Great. My appetite's ruined!
Say what you will about my writing style,
words leave an unmistakable mark.
I did it! I transported them!
What the hell did I just sit through?
He has my school in his grip,
as surely as if his very tentacles
were wrapped around the campus.
Even so, carefree though they seem,
E-Class won't get a fairy tale sort of ending.
The Ministry of Defense has big plans, and yet,
based on my experience of such things,
the only person qualified to
predict what may happen next, is me.
I can't help but wonder, Koro-sensei.
Can one be a teacher amidst the coming storm?
Surprise!
Not needed, Kunudon!
Now that he's served his purpose,
Kunigigaoka's beloved mascot
has been transferred to E-Class.
Huh? Hey! What are you lookin' at?
Yeah, that's right: I used to be somebody!
Yay for unemployment!
Bye-bye, Kunadon!