November: Maturity month.
Everyone's really started thinking for themselves.
Which is good.
Because we only have four months
left to assassinate Koro-sensei.
Is the Octopus for real?
He's giving you kids career counseling now?
Wow, look at you!
In a normal outfit!
Yeah.
Thought I'd go for cheap and plain.
Just tryin' to fit in to your
regular old world, that's all.
Oh, come on.
Don't tell me all of a sudden you wanna see more skin?
No, leaving more to the
imagination is somehow even sexier.
You've really grown as a person!
Uh.
Uh! Nakamura! Did you write this?!
That's my future you're messing with!
Sorry, sweetheart, men's work just doesn't suit you.
Hey, Nagisa.
Huh?
Which would you prefer,
Thailand or Morocco after graduation?
I'm kinda partial to Thailand myself.
Why do I get the feeling
everyone's dead-set on neutering me?
Careers? Seriously?
Why're we talking about this stuff when
the Earth's on the verge of being destroyed?
Hm. What do I wanna be?
A bureaucrat, eh?
Interesting choice.
If I may say so, administrative duties seem rather, um,
restrained for someone of your temperament.
Well, remember the last quake?
How the politicians were completely useless?
I won't disagree with you on that.
The country should've been paralyzed, but it wasn't.
Everything kept functioning.
Who do we have to thank?
Behind every talking head at a podium
is some bureaucrat pulling the strings.
That's what real power's all about.
Does that make sense?
You know, I take it back, that's a good fit for you.
Take my advice, Terasaka.
Don't be a politician.
Huh?
I mean, sure: People love seeing a big-mouthed,
impulsive idiot on the ballot, don't get me wrong.
It's just that making you a puppet'd be way too easy.
Huh.
You're delusional, man. Like I'd be somebody's puppet!
Who the hell said I wanna be a politician?
Nakamura.
You aspire to be a diplomat?
Oh, to aim so far above one's modest beginnings.
You don't have to put it like that, sir.
Believe it or not, back in primary
school they said I was a certifiable genius.
In first grade,
I actually tested at a sixth-grade level.
I always placed in the top of my class.
The thing is... it really sucked.
I just wanted to be normal.
Not caring about grades, goofing off with your friends:
That's normal.
So, when I made it to Kunugigaoka, I played dumb.
After a while it wasn't an act.
Then I saw how disappointed my parents were,
and the importance of what I'd thrown away really hit me.
I still wanted to joke around, but
I knew I needed to apply myself, too.
This class is the best of both worlds.
What I mean is... Thank you.
Aw...
Miss Irina! Miss Irina!
Can I hear more of the story, please?
To look at them,
you wouldn't believe anyone's thinking all that hard.
But they are.
Uh-oh.
Miss Irina's top.
The tag's still on.
She's not used to buying stuff off the rack.
You think maybe we should tell her?
I'll take care of it.
Believe me, I earned that car.
Putting the moves on the CEO of a tech company
is challenging to say the least.
Oh, yes.
For one thing, the hours are atrocious...
if Karasuma hadn't forbidden
me to drive the damn thing here.
He says I won it by defrauding a man.
"I'm Karasuma and I hate fun!"
Okey-dokey. Last but not least.
So, have you decided on a prospective career,
Nagisa m'boy?
Sir, I... I think, well, uh.
I think I have a talent for killing people.
I'm pretty sure I could get to
where I do what the Reaper does.
We all know I don't have any other strengths.
So, I mean, what else can I reasonably shoot for, right?
Koro-sensei, should I...
Should I become an assassin?
Please, sir. What path should I follow?
'Cause I don't know.
You're a sensible young man, Nagisa.
And a good student.
I'm sure you would've weighed the risks of
becoming an assassin before coming to me with this.
For the record, you have a gift for the work.
No one who's seen you in action could doubt that.
Whether facing an otherworldly monster,
an unhinged teacher, or an evil genius, you prevail.
Your attacks are thought-out,
well-timed, and without fear.
All indispensable qualities for a master killer.
That said, of course.
While you are courageous, there's a tinge of desperation.
Uh!
You never give your safety, or dignity,
a second thought. You strike without fear
because you feel you have nothing to lose.
To what end should your talents be put to use?
More importantly, for whom?
Reexamine those questions more closely.
We'll talk again after you've
done a bit more soul searching.
I give you my word,
if you still wish to be an assassin,
I'll support that decision wholeheartedly.
Whoa! You beat it? Even the secret boss?
Not my first time.
I had to play it twice before I got enough experience.
Oh, I see, I'll start over. Cool!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Nagisa. Have a seat, please.
Sure, mom. What's up?
Not your grades, certainly.
Fifty-fourth on midterms?
The cutoff for being permitted back
onto the regular campus is fiftieth place.
I'm disappointed, but don't lose hope.
Tanaka's older brother was once sixtieth.
Of course, this was three years ago
now, but he managed to bounce back.
The school made an exception for him on
account of his family's rather generous donation.
The same gesture should work for us.
Whatever gets you out of that dreadful E-Class.
The sooner the better.
I'll be scheduling an appointment with Mr. Ono of
D Class very soon and I expect you to come with me.
No, wait! You... you can't!
Please! You gotta let me stay where I am for right now!
I know you don't like it, but honestly,
I'm bringing my grades up, and it's a lot of fun!
Look, I'll go to whatever college you want, I swear!
But for junior high I really, really...
Uh-oh.
She's in one of her moods, not good.
Here it comes.
Shut that filthy, ungrateful mouth!
I did not raise my son to be
driftwood, do you understand me?
Do want to live the rest of
your life in the shadow of failure?
You have no idea what it's like!
I work and slave to spare you the fate of
your poor mother and this is that thanks I get!
Do you think money grows on trees?!
You think I just pulled this donation out of thin air?!
Well I've got news for you!
I put myself through hell to secure your future!
Who do you think you are?!
There's no talking to her when she's like this.
It's my fault for not bringing
this up when she was in a better mood.
I'm sorry, mom.
I was being selfish. I wasn't thinking.
Dad doesn't have the stomach for confrontation.
This is why he walked out on us.
Now, then.
You listen to me.
You're a child.
You have no earthly idea how
to make your way through life.
But mother knows all the twists and turns.
I won't let you end up like your father and I.
See, I have it all planned out, just trust me.
The long-term goal is to get you into Keisetsu University.
One of the top schools in the country.
Mom didn't make the cut.
It's a great Alma mater.
Big companies take notice.
In the real world, it's not what you know,
it's who you know: School ties are everything.
A Keisetsu graduate could even have a shot at
working for an elite corporation like Hishimaru!
They're a famous company, who didn't hire her.
Have I ever told you how badly I wanted a little girl?
Only about a million times.
Your grandparents discouraged me from being too feminine.
It was always studying and hard work.
That's why Hishimaru didn't want me.
They're all about looks.
I promised myself if I had a daughter,
she'd get to wear are the frilly
things I was never allowed to.
Ah!
See how nice this looks with your beautiful, long hair?
Yeah. Looks great.
Except I'm a boy.
It's chilling how determined she is.
I don't think I'll ever be able to get out from under her.
Koro-sensei saw right through me.
I'm not, and never will be, the hero of my own life.
Not even close. It's her RPG.
I'm just her new play through.
Oh, and by the way.
Just so you know, I'll be dropping by the school
tomorrow to meet with your teacher for a transfer.
Huh?!
That's a little out of the blue, mom!
I think he might be busy!
It's for the best, Nagisa dear.
Now, if I were you, I'd say goodbye to my E-Class friends.
She's gone dark again.
Nothing I say will make any difference.
I see.
Your mother seems to be rather single-minded.
Yeah, I know. What do I do now?
She won't listen to a word I say.
Mr. Karasuma's out of town on business.
I can't ask one of his subordinates
to meet with her on his behalf.
I'm just... I can't.
I'm not ready to leave E-Class yet.
Now, now.
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'm a super being capable of
destroying the planet, after all.
A simple parent-teacher meeting
should be a walk in a park!
Uh... I'm not so sure about that.
Wow, seriously? Your mom?
She's one tough cookie.
Koro-sensei seems pretty sure he can handle her, but...
I see no reason I couldn't play your teacher.
Uh?
Problem is, officially it's Mr. Karasuma.
His name's on file.
If our parents talk to each other it won't add up.
Mm. Yeah. Good call.
Ha, ha, ha. There's a simple solution.
Yours truly becomes Tadaomi Karasuma.
Koro-sensei?
Ha!
Why, no!
I'm Karasuma!
Worst cosplay ever!
Did you draw lines on your face with a marker?!
It's a furrowed brow to accentuate his bleak worldview.
Details!
Why do your arms look like summer sausages?!
These are Karasuma's bulging muscles!
You look ridiculous!
All I can do at this point is pray.
With any luck, mom will fall for the charade.
Please just let me stay in E-Class.
That's Nagisa's mom?
She's a knockout.
More like she'll knock you out.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Ms.Shiota, Nagisa's mother.
Yes, yes. Please, have a seat.
Good to see you.
Trekking up the mountain is
quite a journey, you must be tired.
Might I offer you a refreshing beverage?
I...
I guess it's kinda convincing?
If I may say so, madam, you're quite stunning.
I see where Nagisa gets his looks.
Why, thank you!
You know, if only this one had been born a girl,
I'd have groomed her to be my ideal!
Not quite sure I follow you.
Well, you see.
I wasn't allowed to wear my hair long and a
girl is ever so much prettier with flowing locks.
Oh, Nagisa, what I wouldn't give
to have had lovely, full-bodied hair.
I was so mad when he started tying it back
for school this year. But it looked so good,
I just had to let it slide as
long as he wouldn't cut it off.
Ah.
But we're here to discuss his future.
We can't afford to discourage them at this age.
They're far too impressionable, in my experience.
You're familiar with Kei U?
They've accepted several graduates
from Kunugigaoka High School.
I'd very much like Nagisa to go one day,
but I'm afraid being so far off track
in Junior High will hurt his chances.
So I've come here, with all due respect,
to talk about what we can do to get him out of E-Class.
And I trust you spoke with Nagisa on the matter?
Oh, he's too young to understand what's
at stake, believe me. And at any rate,
it's my job as a parent to steer him
clear of the mistakes I made at his age.
Mom. I, don't...
Hush up now, sweetheart, the adults are talking.
Uh.
Yes, well...
I believe I'm starting to get a clearer picture
of how Nagisa became the person he is today.
Huh?
Ugh!
Yes. Indeed. I, Tadaomi Karasuma,
wear a toupee!
High schools, colleges, and hairstyles.
Ma'am, forgive me for saying so,
are decidedly not a parent's prerogative!
I'm sorry.
Nagisa must be permitted to live his own life.
You'll get nowhere foisting your complexes onto him.
Ms. Shiota. Let me be perfectly clear.
Unless Nagisa so desires,
he will not be allowed to leave E-Class.
Uh.
What's the hell is your problem?!
Since when does a teacher talks like that to a parent?!
How dare you?!
"Foisting my complexes onto him"?!
If you think I'll sit by...
Whoa.
Holy crap!
That is one seriously pissed of lady right there!
Of course! That explains your attitude
at home lately, this bald idiot's been giving you ideas!
Well, watch this!
When I'm done with you, your eyes will be wide open!
Koro-sensei.
Hm.
That was a bit more tactless than I'd planned.
Still, though...
There's a lesson to be learned here.
You need to communicate your
intentions more clearly from now on,
speak your mind.
It's not that easy.
Mom won't listen to anything I say.
She only sees me as her second play through.
It's not as though you're powerless.
If assassination is your forte, what can't you do?
The first round of your own RPG started
here in this classroom, remember that.
My first. My first round.
Looks great, thanks.
Sorry for earlier, darling.
I ought not have blown up at your teacher like that.
It's just that I'm so invested.
Yeah.
Well, anyway.
I've been doing quite a bit of thinking today.
And I've decided I simply will not have someone who
thinks they know better than me interfering with my life.
Period.
All obstacles must be removed.
It's time I gave you a new outlook on life.
Nagisa.
Wha... What the...?
Mom?
This is where it all started going downhill.
When you started disobeying me.
This place turned into a monster.
Burn it to the ground.
With your own hands.
Get your life back on track.
Mom, please. What're you doing?
Calm down!
Mother knows best, honey. Listen to me.
Burn it down and the guilt will keep you from
being able to face any of these people again.
Plus, with the building gone, the main campus
will have no choice but to take you back in, yes?
No! I don't want to!
I brought you into this world, Nagisa!
I scraped to send you to cram school, then private school!
You have no idea what it cost me!
I do everything for you!
Every night dinner's on the table,
no matter how exhausted I am from work!
Does E-Class do that for you?!
I made you who you are! You owe me!
You will do what I tell you!
She's wrong.
But she's right.
How do I tell her, what do I say?
You need to communicate your intentions
more clearly from now on, speak your mind.
Mom, listen. I...
How 'bout you quit shrieking, you old bag.
Sit back and enjoy the show like a good girl, hm?
That bloodlust. He's an assassin!
Actually, it's you who's in my way.
It's Wednesday night.
He comes here to watch his favorite
TV shows on the Autonomous Artillery.
He'll shoot through here at the speed of sound,
and when he does, I'll split his
head open with my whip and kill him.
Kill? Oh, dear.
I have to call the police...!
Wouldn't do that if I were you.
The bounty's void if I kill the kid,
but nothing in the rules says I
can't take out a whiney old hag.
Okay. She's afraid.
Which probably means the assassin has his guard down.
Mom.
I've spent my whole life learning how to read you.
It's given me a very specific set of skills.
Maybe not the ones you'd prefer me to have,
but they come in very handy.
Especially in E-Class.
The first round of your own RPG started
here in this classroom, remember that.
Mom. Believe it or not,
I'm giving this class everything I've got.
Before I graduate, I'll get results.
And when I do,
I'm cutting my hair,
and paying back every scrap you've spent on me.
If you can't find it in your heart to forgive me...
What is this?
Then I'll graduate again,
from you.
Mom.
I'm grateful that you had me.
Grateful that you raised me.
It may be asking a lot,
but if you can just be happy that you have a child.
That, all things considered, turned out relatively okay,
that's all I need to be happy.
Who are you, Nagisa?
What in the world have you done?
Certain unsavory types have made
this their after hours hangout,
I recommend you give the area a wide berth at night.
Koro-sensei.
Just for the record,
you just vowed to kill me before March.
No takesies-backsies!
You heard all that, huh?
Now, then, ma'am.
Nagisa has quite a bit of growing left to do, I agree.
What he needs more than anything is a loving mother.
Don't take his stubbornness so personally.
Every little birdie needs to leave the
nest at some point, that's the way of things.
My baby is...
pulling away. He's leaving me.
Mom, no!
It's all right.
The adrenaline rush got the best of her.
Why don't I take the two of you back to her car?
I'll drive you home.
So tell me, Nagisa.
If you did manage to assassinate me,
would you marshal your talent toward
becoming a full-fledged professional?
Good question.
I don't know.
Probably not.
I mean, when we're talking about talent.
It's not like it's only for one thing or the other.
I'd be good at killing,
but I'd be good at protecting people, too.
But definitely not by being an assassin.
Way too dangerous for me.
I'd rather find a career that wouldn't worry my folks.
No rush. You have plenty of time.
Ah, and keep in mind:
With your parents, communication is key.
Right.
Ugh! Come on, there's no cross traffic!
How long does it take to get a green light?!
And what's all this?
I'm making breakfast from now on.
So, uh, you can take it easy in the mornings now.
I'll start taking out the trash, too.
And hey, I promise to get into a high
school every bit as good as Kunugigaoka!
Just please, mom.
Let me stay in E.
If that's what you want, fine.
I really couldn't care less.
Ha!
I'm an assassin!
Holding my head high till graduation!