Merry Christmas!
What a magical Christmas Eve!
And in February, no less! How festive!
Happy New Year!
Out with the old and in with the new!
That's right, boys and girls!
Throw yourself into study and, of course, assassination,
with renewed vigor!
Now...
time to laze the day away.
Where's he going with all this?
Oh, I think I'm starting to get the picture.
You're trying to cram all the good times you missed out on
over the Winter Break into February, is that what this is?
Precisely!
Our only Winter Break together,
and not one of you came to visit.
'Course, I knew you were worried about me
and trying your hardest to find a solution,
which is why it didn't seem proper
to invite anyone over, but still.
Seems kinda weird to be all bummed
out about it now, don't'cha think, sir?
Water under the bridge, as far as I'm concerned!
We'll simply reclaim the time we
lost by having all the fun at once!
Koro-sensei's living life to the fullest,
as frantically as ever.
Still. It's February.
March is just around the corner.
We've got to face the future.
Figure out where we're going before we say goodbye.
Thirty-two days. That's all the time we have left.
Koro-sensei deadline is practically here.
Future plans, huh?
Okay, what high school you goin' to?
I was thinkin' someplace lower level
so I can have a little bit of elbowroom.
Well, we've definitely got
fundamentals down through senior year.
High school can be about fine-tuning
what Koro-sensei's taught us.
That's one way to look at it, sure.
I don't know about you, but I'm gonna push myself.
"It takes a pristine academic record
to make it in Communications these days."
So I'm told, at least.
Wah-wah!
So, Karma, what're your sights set on?
Hmm...
I figure I'll just stay at Kunugigaoka.
You're gonna subject yourself to
the entrance exam all over again?
Wow, seems kinda low profile.
With your grades you could get into any school you want.
Put yourself in the shoes of the kids on Main Campus.
The guy they thought was exiled is suddenly back,
looming head and shoulders above 'em all.
What could be sweeter than sailing by on an ocean
of humiliated faces for three whole years, right?
That's a winning personality you've got.
And besides, there are tons of decent schools out there
if all you care about is your transcript.
But do any of 'em boast an arch nemesis worthy of me?
I'm inclined to say no.
Have fun while you can.
Broader ambitions can come later.
What I want out of life right now
is a good academic battle, or three.
That's so you.
And? What's your high school of
choice, Nagisa? You picked one?
Mh-hm.
Just like Kayano. Sugino. Everyone.
It's almost time to part ways.
Each of us going wherever the future leads.
Believe it or not,
my top pick is Keisetsu University's high school.
It's crazy hard, but hands down the best shortcut
for getting into the college Mom hopes I'll go to.
After that? I don't know.
I have certain skills. There's no question of that.
Trouble is... what I'm good at
puts me out of step with others.
Seems like everyone knows where they're going but me.
Hey. Yoo-hoo!
How many times I gotta tell you? I'm finished!
Ha, ha. Oh, sorry about that.
Come on, snap out of it already!
You're supposed to be giving me the
academic chops to march back into school!
I thought the idea was to enroll this
term, not when I'm like old n' crusty!
Hey, don't worry, we'll get you there.
Just, dial it back a teensy bit.
Huh...
You're worried about your own future, aren't you?
Junior high kids sure have it rough.
I have no earthly idea what I wanna be.
Uh?
You have options?
Apart from the obvious choice of profession, I mean.
Your path seems pretty clear to me.
What've we been doing this entire time?
You're gonna be a teacher, silly.
A what?
Of course, if you're not feelin' it, I understand...
It took her saying it for me to realize.
A teacher. Someone with the power to change lives.
Suppose a kid gets saved by a doctor.
Naturally, he grows up wanting to be one.
A kid sees an assassin wielding his blade,
and from then on, it's all he can think about.
Or maybe,
a kid sees a teacher molding young minds.
Yeah, but...
Um, what is that?
Uh?
Someone's family, I guess?
Go! Go! Nagisa!
Go, go Nagisa! Go, go Nagisa! Woo! Yay!
Okay, then. Um, is that an actual mob of giants?
Ugh. I do not appreciate those
weirdos hogging the send-off ceremony.
Koro-sensei, what in the heck do you think you're doing?!
I'm cheering you on, of course!
You didn't suppose I'd let my prize
student's big moment slip by unnoticed!
Oh dear! Look at the time!
I've got to drop by and cheer on Kimura!
And Kanzaki! And Chiba! And Hayami! And Hara!
Uh!
You got this! Up, up and away!
I'll never be a teacher like him, that's for sure.
The last career counseling session is at
the end of February, after our entrance exams.
I've got until then to make
up my mind one way or the other.
For now, though, I'll focus on
the target right in front of me.
Okay, I'll just ask. What's wrong with you, Okajima?
Uh. What, with me? Nothing!
Is it because of the chocolates? Please.
I-I have absolutely no idea what you're talking about!
You're sick.
Uh! It's Valentine's Day!
I'm just excited is all!
And don't worry. I'm not gonna eat
any of that cheap-o crap you give out!
Excuse me? What is that supposed to mean?
What do we have here?
And who's the lucky fella you're giving these to?
What are you talking about? They're just a formality!
Why do you have to go there?
Everybody likes chocolate. They could be for anyone!
Right.
And by "anyone" I assume you mean this little stud muffin?
It's true, it's true...
Weird. Her acting chops are usually more spot on.
Not even Koro-sensei wised up to
her before it was almost too late.
It was that kiss.
Ever since Nagisa laid one on her,
the girl's been a bona fide hot mess.
Heh. If we bring the two of 'em together...
we can tease two love birds with one stone!
We've got a shiny new plaything!
His self-esteem isn't exactly the highest.
Poor guy can't imagine the opposite
sex wanting anything to do with him.
It's why he's avoiding you.
See, in his mind, that smooch is
something you're pissed as hell about.
That's just how he is.
Till you say otherwise, that's what he'll think.
I know, it's just...
I mean, I've played being in love dozens
of times, but this is totally different.
I have no real-life experience crushing on a classmate.
Like, what am I supposed to say
when I give the chocolates to him?
Ah. Want us to do some recon?
Maybe a little covert training would be in order?
Absolutely! Absolutely!
I'm, uh, glad you like them.
See, in this case the receiver is overjoyed.
But observe how the giver is
rather a bit on the cool side.
Total formality.
His "overjoyed" face is terrifying.
Impressive.
Your shots are just as accurate
when using chocolate ammunition.
Here's the rest. You've more than earned it.
Good call.
I respect you. Let's keep it that way.
Sure.
See? Now there's a couple that's
always on target. Gotta love that skill.
I can't imitate that.
I can't even tell if she meant it.
Gentlemen, I await your answers with baited breath.
To each of you, a love letter.
I put a lot of myself into these.
Yourself? More like an ancient curse!
She beat me to the punch.
I had Okuda cook me up a batch I planned
on leaving in Teresaka's shoe locker.
Here's your Valentine's Day cyanide!
What is wrong with you?! That's
not what chocolate is for at all!
Whoa!
All these for me? Is this for real?
I thought you might like to share
them with your brother and sister.
Nothing fancy, just bulk stuff from a wholesale store.
Took me four hours to ride there and back.
Uh.
But how'd you even...? When did you study?
It's not a big deal.
After all, I have days before the entrance exams.
I'm going to state school.
That makes you and me both, doesn't it?
Guess so. Hope we can get in.
Right?
See?
Everyone has his or her distinct approach to this stuff.
Best policy is to say what you
have to say in your own words.
You should just be yourself.
Yeah. I guess so. Thank you, guys.
Only problem I see?
Hm?
Privacy.
With the Octo-perv on watch, there basically is none.
Oh, you can just leave that to me.
Kayano, I do hope you brought the you-know-what.
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Oughta put Koro-sensei on lockdown
long enough for you to get the job done.
Don't worry about him.
Concentrate on giving Nagisa those chocolates.
Right.
Where are my Valentine's chocolates? I
know I got something! Nagisa, help me look!
Some joker probably thought it'd be
funny to hide them on the mountain!
Huh?
Kayano?
What's wrong? Why're you so quiet?
Oh, God. My heart's beating so fast!
How do I do this?
Do I look all right? What do I say?
Uh, hey, Nagisa.
Where're you headed after graduation?
Honestly, I know the career path I wanna follow,
I'm just not real sure that
it's something I'm cut out for.
He wants to be a teacher.
It's obvious he looks up to Koro-sensei.
Not for the reasons most of us do,
but because Koro-sensei has a knack
for bringing out the best in people.
When Nagisa talks to him at the end
of the month about a future career,
he'll ask about education.
Huh?
What's Koro-sensei doing up there?
He's fixated, whatever it is.
Of course he's out of range.
Why would I think he'd leave himself so open to attack?
Oh.
That look. I love it when he stares dead ahead like that.
He's so intense.
Not that long ago, revenge was my whole life.
I should've been crushed when my plan failed,
but I wasn't
because it was Nagisa who stopped me.
He's the kindest soul I've ever known.
Sure, he's an assassin,
but his bloodlust filled the hole in my heart.
What do I say to that face?
What words do I use?
Nagisa.
As a thank you.
These chocolates are yours. For always being by my side.
Here.
Are you sure?
Yep!
Okay, then.
Mission accomplished. Job well done.
Move along. See you tomorrow, okay?
Hope you get in the school you're aiming for!
Yeah, thanks.
There he goes. Staring dead ahead.
It's not right for me to get
in his way, he needs to focus.
But I can thank him without complicating things.
I'll use the sharpest blade in my repertoire.
My acting ability.
Imagine being able to cast your feelings
aside at the moment of truth like that.
Wow, there's no question she's Miss Yukimura's sister.
No kidding, right? So noble.
Well damn, now I feel guilty
thinking about trying to steal from her.
Come again?
Uh, never mind. I didn't say anything. So, yeah.
Hm?
What exactly has Koro-sensei so enthralled?
Ah. I had Kayano leave a note and
some chocolates somewhere obvious,
with a special photo of course.
You dog.
If I'd known it was gonna work this
well, I'd have used as bait long before now.
A four-star Valentine's Day dinner?
What's in it for you?
I'm told you menfolk tend to give
back three times as much on White Day.
Seems like an honorable tradition to me.
Of course, I can't imagine how
you could possibly measure up.
Ah... We'll see, won't we?
I'm out.
Don't be like that! At least stay through the meal!
That wasn't meant as a jab at your manhood, I swear!
You don't know what I went through to get reservations!
I'm surprised a place like this would
let someone like you cross the threshold.
Here, from Hinano.
She asked if I'd mind passing it on.
You're at school so seldom these days.
When I see an opening, that man is mine!
Poor girl.
She seems to have gotten it in
her head that we're a thing now.
Hm. Bet the boys are brokenhearted.
I got a veritable boatload of chocolates, even for me.
I'm sure a few kids thought it
might be their last Valentine's Day.
Can't blame 'em for going overboard.
So, what's goin' on in your world lately?
How's the "big plan?"?
The kids think if they can keep the Octopus
from blowing up, everything'll work out.
Of course, we know better, don't we?
That's why we're in a private room at a place she trusts.
I should've known.
Maybe.
I have been meaning to talk to you, actually.
I've been relegated to providing
E-Class with proprietary guidance,
so I'm kept out of the loop.
They'll likely only brief me at the 11th hour.
But... something is in the works.
The government is moving forward
with a secret assassination project.
There's no doubt.
Seeing it again like this, I'm stunned.
But do you think it can eliminate him?
You may take my word for it, gentlemen.
The question with this weapon isn't whether it is capable,
but rather how efficiently and smoothly it can do the job.
A first-rate mind and a first-rate figure!
I must say, seeing one of my teachers
so enamored with a questionable photograph
does not strictly inspire confidence.
Mr. Principal, sir, wherever did you come from?
I find your work ethic wanting.
There will be a corresponding pay cut.
I beg your mercy!
Miss Yukimura, I believe.
It's a pity we lost such talent.
Her passion for teaching was matched only by her vitality.
Given a few more years,
she would've become an outstanding educator.
Indeed.
Oh, by the way,
I understand there's an excellent
chance of your life being spared.
If you do survive this, would you indulge me?
I want you to continue teaching E-Class next year.
Truthfully, I find your fixed expression and singular
anatomy to be rather, well, suited to the position.
I'm flattered, sir.
You judge fellow educators purely on aptitude,
unmoved by sentiment or the shadow of their past.
To be offered a job by such a man
is the best mark one could hope for.
Alas, I decided it's best for this
year to be my last at the blackboard.
What will you do?
Anyone's guess, really.
I have a mind to circumnavigate the globe in a sailboat.
May I just say how delightful it's been
having you as an archrival through all this.
Your dedication is nothing short of inspiring.
The feeling is mutual.
I don't suppose you're open to bribery?
Uh?
In the grand design,
I rule this institution from on high
while the Miss Yukimuras of
the world support it from below.
The perfect expression of my educational philosophy.
What's that boy of yours up to these days?
Ah.
Arranging the pecking order for high school, I suspect.
He'll have the whole system under
his thumb by the end of freshman year.
A truly remarkable young man.
Well, we're not quite there yet.
He still has a few lessons to learn.
Can I be honest with you?
I'm not so sure it'd be such a bad
thing if the world were destroyed.
For the kids, anyway.
They'll never get over it if they can't kill him.
They'll be haunted by that
failure the rest of their lives.
And they'd resent having their thunder stolen
by some big shot, government-sponsored mercenary,
or whatever the Powers That Be are cooking up.
But think about it.
Imagine those kids watching their teacher die,
the Octopus writhing in agony at
the hands of one of their classmates.
They're screwed either way.
The trauma will follow them to the grave.
However this turns out, we're talking years of therapy.
Being part of something like this just
twists you in a way you can never undo. Ever.
Irina.
Uh?
Once this business is said and done, you should quit.
You're just not built for it.
Excuse me?
Can't you see? Your feelings run too deep.
Over the past year they've taken the wheel.
If you're this worried about your students being affected,
what might another job down the road put you through?
Sure. You can dismiss the life
I've made for myself. Why not?
It's easy to pass judgment from the nosebleed section.
But here on the ground, I'm a killer.
There's no going back from that.
No place in the sun waiting for me
to shed the past and reinvent myself.
Everything we experience is a
tool for clearing one's path.
That's the most important thing I've learned on this job.
What those kids taught me.
I understand your concern,
but they have resilience down to an art form.
Whatever they face, however horrible,
they know how to let it nourish them.
Irina, why don't you come work for us?
Huh?
You have skill, an impressive
range of professional experience.
As far as we're concerned, your past is just that.
With us, you'll save more people than you've killed.
And if you want, every morning,
you can pray for your victims at the shrine.
Something to consider.
What do you mean a shrine?
You are aware that I identify as Christian, right?
And why stay where I hardly know anyone?
I don't think you understand.
There's no church anywhere near my house, sorry.
Uhhh...
What?!
Wait a minute!
Are you saying what I think you're saying?!
Probably.
Wah! A man and a woman can't live together out of wedlock!
What will people think?!
Suit yourself, then.
Ah!
No! It's fine!
It's the 21st century! It's a different world!
Wait for me!