Stop it, Kayano!
This is insane!
If you think I care...
you're wrong.
When my mind's fixed on something, I just keep rolling!
This is the real Kayano, not the character.
She's been in boss-battle mode for maybe 15 seconds
and already the tentacles have
gotten a foothold on her brain.
If she's that far gone, it's too late.
Whether she gets her revenge on Koro-sensei or not,
another few minutes of this...
she's dead.
Kayano...
Kill you! Murderer!
Kill you! Kill you!
Koro-sensei...
Please...
Save me...
Die! Die! Die! Die!
You hear me?! You're going to die!
But if he does, he won't be the only one...
We have to do something, guys.
What, we just stand here while her
life's being eaten away like this?!
Children!
Koro-sensei?!
Just a face now?
Sorry. Partial clone.
I'm afraid Kayano's attacks aren't
leaving me a lot of wiggle room.
Believe me, it's all I can do
to project an afterimage of this.
It's kinda cool, actually.
Her tentacles must be removed ASAP!
They're putting out this infernal
heat at tremendous cost to her body!
She's so bent on killing me, she's lost all reason!
If we don't act quickly, they'll sap
her life force and kill the poor girl!
Trouble is, so long as her
bloodlust equals that of the tentacles,
they'll be rooted into her nervous
system, impossible to extract!
Talking her down isn't an option as it was with Itona.
We simply don't have the time!
So... what do we do?
The only thing we can.
I'll have to pull 'em out as we fight.
I'll have to let her hit my most vulnerable spot...
The area beneath my tie.
My heart.
Should she completely destroy it, death is certain.
But if she feels as though she's done me in,
her tentacles will be satisfied, for a moment.
One of you must exploit that tiny window of
opportunity to make Kayano forget her bloodlust.
Forget it? How?
By any means necessary.
Whatever it takes to get her mind off assassination!
Alas, it's the only thing I can't do.
If her intended target were to try anything
funny, her bloodlust would only intensify.
Quell it, however, and the
tentacles' bond will temporarily break.
Their grip on Kayano's nervous
system will be loosened just enough
to make extraction possible without major damage.
Yeah, but she'd...
I mean, the tentacles would be on
your heart the whole time, right?
Wouldn't you die before we could get them off of her?
I might be able to postpone the moment
of death long enough to regenerate,
but optimistically the odds are 50-50.
Then no!
Don't despair!
The possibility of E Class not being allowed to
graduate is far worse than the prospect of my demise.
But... Ugh! Really?
He wants them to jump into the fray?
These kids aren't magicians!
What does he expect them to do against that?
Mimura!
Give us some air guitar.
What?
Come on, man! Show her your mad skills!
But she's gonna go after me!
Just do it!
That's ridiculous!
The clap stunner?
No. Her mental frequency's too out of whack.
I'd never find an opening. At best, she'd just ignore me.
Knives? Guns? Out of the question.
We don't want to hurt her.
There has to be something.
What've we all been doing with ourselves the past year?
We're supposed to be trained
assassins, experts in this kind of stuff!
Hold on, there's that one killer move.
Die! Die! Die!
Die!
Gotcha!
I made a promise to your sister.
Forgive me. I'm not letting you out of my grasp.
Nagisa...
What're you doing?
I won't let you say it, Kayano.
That this was all an act.
We've made too many memories.
Been through too much together.
I won't let you say the only thing you cared about...
was revenge.
Will this do? Please say yes.
Well done, Nagisa!
They'll come out with ease!
Is she...
Is she all right? Is this over now?
I think so. Probably.
The important thing is that she get plenty of rest.
Whew, now that was a kiss!
Look at you, goin' all Prince Charming! Way to go, Nagisa!
Don't make it a thing. I was distracting
her from her bloodlust, that's all.
I'll apologize to her when she wakes up, so...
Fifteen hits on a ten second kiss
is noting to write home about honey.
I'm disappointed...
"Fifteen hits"?
If you're gonna kiss, get in
there like there's no tomorrow.
Go big or go home.
You could've pulled off a minimum of 40 hits.
Huh... my upper limit's around 25...
Why do you guys make me want to hate this place?
It's a red letter day if I get to 20.
Koro-sensei!
I'm fine...
It'll just take a little while
for my heart to fully recover.
I realize you're waiting for an explanation, but please...
Indulge me with your patience a bit longer.
Stop playing the deathbed angle.
You've clearly recouped enough to dodge.
It's Shiro.
Pathetic little twit.
For someone so willing to sacrifice
themselves for the sake of retribution.
You'd think she'd have managed something
a little more on the nose than this.
Quite the monster, aren't you?
How many would-be assassins have you
sent away empty-handed in the past year?
Well... There are still at
least two you haven't deflected.
And I will be the last.
Yes, the one from whom you stole everything.
To whom, in the end, you will give your life.
Ah. So it is you.
I thought I recognized that twisted genius.
This, boys and girls, is Yanagisawa.
Come, 2.0.
March is upon us
and with it, a perfect end to an accursed life.
What's with that guy?
What happened?
Ah, Kayano. Thank goodness.
Are you, uh... You okay?
Mm-hmm...
So you're back?
At first, I was driven by bloodlust.
But, the more time I spent with Koro-sensei,
the less and less it seemed to matter.
I started to think, "What's his story?
What about him don't I know?
Should I hold off killing him
till I get the whole picture?"
But about that time, the tentacles took control.
They refused to let me wait.
I'm so stupid...
Assassination's been about self-discovery for you,
while I've spent the past year
secretly obsessed with revenge.
Kayano.
It's 'cause of you I quit feeling
self-conscious about my hair.
The first time we met, you pretty much
called it out and look at me now, right?
And like you said, Koro-sensei's name...
You're the one who gave it to him, remember?
Maybe you were just playing a role. Okay, fine.
Doesn't mean it wasn't a part of you or
that our friendship was based on a lie.
We all wear masks from time to time.
We're all different on the inside than on the out.
It's still the real you.
Here's the deal:
Koro-sensei owes us an explanation as a class.
None of us expects him to be a saint.
We know he doesn't always do the right thing.
But as a class, let's hear his story.
Okay...
And thanks...
It's nice to finally be real...
Don't worry, sir.
What's done is done.
As long as you tell us the truth, we'll accept it.
Thank you.
I'd hoped to never revisit this chapter of my life.
And yet... I have little choice.
Your trust is vital to me...
I would never do anything to break it.
Never jeopardize our bond.
Last summer, on the island,
Mr. Karasuma said of Miss Irina, if you'll recall:
"There's a lot more to a good
assassin than meets the eye."
Those words are especially relevant here.
You see, children, this class
represents my first go as a teacher.
But, all things considered, I think it's fair
to assert I've more than risen to the challenge.
After all, I am a gifted improviser.
Then... you mean...
Yes.
Until two years ago, I was the
assassin known as the Reaper.
And that's not all.
Whether you kill me or not, come March, I'm doomed.
Either I go alone... or I take the Earth with me.
That's the only aspect of your
future assassinating me can change.
We wanted his story.
He delivered.
These were his memories of being human.
Born in darkness,
he grew to disdain the light.
Weaned on soul-crushing poverty,
a child of the slums, he knew
only ugliness and degradation.
Life taught him that he could only rely on three things:
Skill, money, and death.
Naturally, the assassin's path beckoned.
Those stronger than himself, he killed with knowledge.
Those more knowing, he killed with strength.
Those gifted with both, he killed with surpassing charm.
When the number of his victims reached a thousand,
fittingly, rumor christened him the Reaper.
Watch how you handle this one.
Assume he can kill you regardless
of setting or apparent disadvantage.
Of course, it's hard to imagine a more
disadvantageous setting for him than this.
They don't come more clear-headed or hard-boiled.
There's no next-of-kin to complain if he dies.
The perfect guinea pig for our
experiment if ever there was one.
How lucky we are to have found him.
Listen closely, guinea pig.
You may have been the Reaper out
there, in here, you're a specimen.
Your daily routine is going to be very unpleasant.
Wow! That's a shock!
You don't look like a ruthless killer.
Someone drew the short straw.
Look, ma'am. I won't do anything.
Can't you just get me out of here please?
Sorry. It's just that I've developed
an intense allergy to being murdered.
I like her. She can be useful.
There's only one thing that bothers me.
What's with the shirt?!
I'm Aguri Yukimura. It's a pleasure to meet you.
ATPase. Rebalance phase.
Give him 40 units of SOD inhibitor.
Yes, sir.
They're wide open.
But killing them now would be... premature.
Hmm?
Ah!
Excellent work today.
Take a little while to relax.
I'll check your vitals in a few.
Nice shirt.
It's even dorkier than the last one.
Huh?! Oh, come on!
I'm just trying to add a little color to your life!
I thought you'd appreciate it!
To be honest, it grinds my gears.
Wish I'd known that before I fell in love with this brand.
Ugh. I guess my students aren't
the only ones who think it's lame.
Students?
Aguri!
Is there any reason a simple data check takes so long?!
I-I'm sorry, Kotaro, we were just...
If your dolt of a father weren't
one of my core subcontractors,
it'd be you on the other side of the glass!
You owe me!
I let you slide on the connubial
duties, but here, I expect professionalism!
See you tomorrow, guinea pig.
It's going to be a busy day.
The chief ambition of Yanagisawa's
research was to generate organic antimatter.
To that end, he would stop at nothing.
He spliced the particle acceleration cycle
necessary for antimatter into the life cycle of a cell,
effectively priming the cell's engine
and infusing it with astonishing power.
Hey, Yanagisawa?
There's no feeling in my hands or feet.
And I'm chilled to the bone.
"Mister" Yanagisawa!
Ugh. And peripheral neuropathy is par for the course.
I recommend we take him off the alkaloid, sir.
If I can subtly manipulate the process myself,
I'll boost the likelihood of success.
Destructive powers beyond all measure will be mine.
Wow! Lots to get to on the checklist today!
Best get started if I don't wanna get smacked around.
I take it that's a frequent worry for you.
Oh, yeah.
Can't let the sense get knocked out of me.
There'd be nothing to pass on to my class.
Your class?
Aguri! Damn it, woman!
Why must you try my patience?!
I-I was just getting started, dear!
Put those clerical skills to use!
Or have I overestimated your
capacity for basic grunt work?
You have one job! Learn to do it!
Huh?
What did you do?
Mister Reaper, you...
He's just immobilized, ma'am.
Relax. You have a classroom to think about, right?
After three months in that dreadful place,
the teacher and the killer were as
open with each other as old friends.
Quadratic equations?
Might I suggest you dress them up a little?
Never go too easy on college prep school students.
Huh?
The mercenary giving career advice to the educator?
You know, I'm starting to think you're
better suited to my teaching gig than me.
Ah, well, I could definitely play
the part if the job called for it.
But, uh... I'm not cut out for the real thing.
Huh...?
Believe it or not, I had a protégé once. He betrayed me.
How do you think I wound up in this place?
Uh-oh.
It looks as though you'll be passing
on more than just your skill set.
Don't worry, though.
Your name will live in infamy through a thousand faces.
Goodbye, sir. It's been fun.
A shame you never really knew me.
Maybe another time.
How could I be so blind?
I cultivated his abilities.
Gauged his progress in minute detail.
He wanted to be seen.
Huh?
He wanted your approval.
Everything he did was just to get your attention.
Believe me.
But I watched the boy like a hawk.
Everyone wants attention.
That's the key to winning them over.
Break time's over, guinea pig.
Back to work.
On the table, please.
We have some tests to run.
The changes our subject's body
is undergoing are unprecedented.
I hate to think of the havoc he'll
cause when he decides he's had enough.
Oh, if he tries to escape, taking Aguri
hostage will be the linchpin of his strategy.
Come now. You didn't suppose I gave her
this job out of the goodness of my heart?
She's a pawn. A sacrificial lamb to gauge his mileage.
This is the reaction we anticipated.
It's all right. He'll be fine.
She was part of the experiment.
The Reaper was turning into something altogether inhuman.
She suspected as much.
But didn't wish to burden her superiors with questions.
Great job again today.
Take a second to catch your
breath and I'll take your vitals.
I'll stick around so we can visit for a while.
She looked straight ahead and smiled.
Sweet and lighthearted as ever.
Of course...
Everyone wants attention, approval.
Sounds lovely.
You bring the exam questions?
The legendary killer who'd never shown himself to anyone,
at last understood the joy of being seen.
The seasons changed.
A new school year began.
A fresh batch of students gathered
under the roof of Kunugigaoka's Class 3-E.
Little did they know,
in only two week's time,
the moon would become a permanent crescent.