Itona's tried to kill Koro-sensei a total of three times.
It took some convincing,
but in the end he finally joined our class.
And so, about a week later...
Well that just about does it, boys and girls.
See you tomorrow.
Payday today, at long last, so I'll be treating
myself to some mouthwatering Shanghai crab.
Yi, er, san, GO!
You could treat us to some.
Is it me or has our workload gotten
crazy hard now that it's second term?
Yeah, well you can't exactly blame
Koro-sensei for trying to get our grades up.
Guess not.
It's just that it's been
forever since I picked up a chick.
Hey, Itona. Are you stickin' around?
What'cha working on there?
What's it look like I'm doing?
I'm building a remote-control tank.
How come?
The Octopus. He made me cram all day yesterday.
Stressed me out.
Focus on the material, please. Next question.
I'm pissed. So I'm gonna use this to kill him.
It's like the idiot said. What's his name? Terasaka.
If I fail a hundred times, so be it. Who cares?
Only gotta kill the task master once.
Good way of lookin' at it.
Wow, this stuff, it's, like, stupid high tech.
I mean, is it even for real?
Kudos.
This puppy's using modified camera phone parts.
Wow, Itona.
You came up with all these tweaks yourself?
It's not really a big deal.
I picked up electronics workin' for my old man.
Anybody could do this stuff. Except Terasaka.
What a change.
Compared to how he was when he had tentacles, I mean.
Still has a sharp tongue, though.
Wow.
Are you kidding me?
That thing barely even makes a sound.
When it moves or when it shoots.
I used electrical parts instead of gears.
Noise cancellation is paramount.
The camera feed is linked to the controller.
I've got it lined up with the sights on the main gun.
Wow. Cloak and dagger!
Okay, suppose you could sneak up on him.
Where're you gonna aim?
Where else? That's right.
I'll let you guys in on a little secret, you see.
Koro-sensei has a single weak spot.
This is news to me.
His heart.
It's located directly behind that necktie.
If we hit it, we can take him out in one shot.
No doubt he's telling the others
about my heart this very moment.
Clever child that he is.
Assassination promises to be a good deal
more fun now that Itona's thrown into the mix.
I'm thinking this could work.
Yeah. All right.
Let's give 'er a test drive.
Get a feel for how she handles.
It is better to test it now than
watch it break when we need it.
Let's make it happen!
See ya later, Professor Bitch.
Bye! Have a good one!
Straight home, ladies. No detours, understood?
Yes, ma'am.
Cool. Snack run?
Um, yeah!
Wait. Didn't you just say...?
Do ya see anything?
Not a lot. Ugh, this camera totally sucks.
Its field of vision is way too narrow!
So? It's not the end of the world.
We'll fit it with a bigger one.
But that would increase the weight, compromise mobility.
Target acquisition would be more difficult.
In that case.
We'll just install a fisheye
lens on the camera we already have.
Takebayashi!
If we write a program
that can correct image distortion in the data feed,
even a relatively small lens
can give us a wide field of view.
That's good.
Right. Fisheye lens with a big viewing angle.
I've got it taken care of.
Ritsu.
Hello!
Can you build an image correction program for us?
Of course!
I have no idea what you're
using it for, but I'm on the job!
Takebayashi, you're a genius.
We need to be able to record.
Absolutely.
We'll wanna analyze the upgrades as effectively as we can.
Weren't we all just put off by an underwear thief?
In the name of assassination,
onward...! Uh, Prototype Zero!
I'll flip it over!
Yeah, sure. Thanks, man!
There's not much in the way of
a suspension system, apparently.
Leave it to me.
I know a thing or two about drive mechanics and metalwork.
Doesn't the paint job on the
chassis stand out like a sore thumb?
That's combat camouflage.
Unless we want our target
seeing the tank from a mile away,
we need it to blend in with the school.
I got this.
Classroom camouflage. Consider it done.
We should chart out the territory at RC scale.
In the name of better maneuvering...
I'll draw us a detailed map.
They, uh,
really get into it when smut's on the line, huh?
It's kinda creepy.
S'up?
Transmission's ready. I finished it last night.
Oh.
And I made us all breakfast.
Hey. Think it'll stand out now?
This is great and all, guys, but, uh,
you do get that this is for an assassination plan, right?
Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say, President Poverty. Sure.
Okay! Let's give this sucker a proper
field test before all the girls show up!
Yeah!
Funny how nobody's tardy on a day like today.
Ritsu won't boot up until precisely eight o'clock.
You see, I didn't want her to see what we were doing.
Oh. Yeah.
Step aside! I wanna take a shot!
Turns out there was no reason to
worry whether Itona would fit in with us.
He did better than most, actually.
Smut, killing, making stuff.
Talk about hitting all the right buttons.
All of a sudden, he was the center of attention.
Itona. This thing should have a codename.
Seems only fair it should come from you.
I'll give it some thought.
The tentacles once asked me
what kind of person I wanted to be.
I told them I wanted to be strong.
Soon, that was all I could think about.
My mind raced with images of fighting, winning.
Over time, you can spin even the
weakest material into good, strong thread.
"Itona" means "becoming thread," you know. Remember that.
How did I forget my roots?
It's in my name.
Aw, dammit! It crashed.
Watch what you're doin', Terasaka.
Shut up! It's not my fault...
"Becoming thread."
This is where I'm finally gonna live up to it.
It's a monster!
Pull out!
No, fire!
Crap! The main gun's not strong enough!
It's okay. We'll tweak that, too!
Well, damn. Outdone by a squirrelly little weasel.
Next time, we need to designate who's what.
Which means, first off, we need a gunner. Chiba?
Yeah. Sure.
It's all right. Screw-ups are a part of the process.
We all agree Itona One was a dud.
So, we'll just keep spinning till it's gets stronger.
I might fail a hundred times.
But I'll be sure to kill him
before it's all said and done.
You've got my back, right, guys?
'Course we do!
Nothing binds like bloodlust.
I think this is going to be fun!
Okay! Back to the drawing board, men!
We put our heads together, this
baby'll be lookin' up skirts by March!
When did that become the goal?
Uh, what's all this I hear about skirts?
Kataoka, it's not what you think!
We were talking about the kind of skirts you put on cars!
Yeah, sure.
Boys suck.
Uh-huh. And who's big idea was this?
Itona, perhaps you'd care to tell me?
Okajima.
What?
Ah! Good morning, everybody!
Oh, hey, Okajima, about that program you
wanted for correcting fisheye lens distortion,
I finally have it ready.
Hang on. It wasn't me, all right? Tell 'em!
Tell 'em what? Don't try to pull me into this, ya perv.
You have got to be kidding me!
Guys, we really oughta 'fess up.
Whether you do or don't,
it's clear you're all involved in this disgusting scheme!
Boys make me wanna puke!
What's going on in here?
Why don't we just call it a crime of passion.
So it's true. Boys really do only think about one thing.
Karma, I'm gonna ditch class today.
Where's a good spot to go?
Wow, so you can talk. Follow me.
Hey! Where you goin'? Hold on!
Apparently, Itona's a cooler customer than we thought.
Huh. So that's what "Itona" means in kanji.
Well, I think it's awesome!
Yeah!
"Becoming thread." Pretty cool.
It is what it is. Lots of kids
in the class have weird names.
Hang on a sec!
"Justice"? I thought your name was "Masayoshi."
Yeah, if you write it out in kanji,
but my parents insist on saying "Justice."
Koro-sensei's just nice enough to say it my way.
When they called you at opening ceremonies,
I got nervous hearing them yell "Justice."
Yeah, no kidding.
I know. And when they do it again at closing
ceremonies, it'll be even more public humiliation.
Kimura's parents are both in law enforcement.
Apparently they're very passionate
about the fact that they're cops.
When I was a kid, I'd complain about having a weird name,
but mom and dad would just get all upset at me.
They didn't put a whole lotta
thought into the kind of hell
they were setting me up for
once I started going to school.
You can't expect parents to
have your best interests at heart.
Does a cute name like "Kirara"
go with this face? Seriously?
My name makes me sound like a sparkly princess.
I-I... yeah.
My mom lives in her own little fantasy world.
When the least little thing threatens to break
the illusion, she goes into full-blown hysterics.
You have any idea what it's like
growing up in a house like that?
Well it doesn't make living up to a
ridiculously adorable name any easier.
Getting' saddled with a weird name?
How do you poor bastards manage to cope?
What? Oh, c'mon.
What's not to love about being named Karma?
Both of my parents have pretty bizarre
taste, and I guess I inherited that from 'em.
Come to think of it,
I'm far from satisfied with my name.
Hang on, I thought you liked being called Koro-sensei.
Kayano gave you that name, didn't she?
It's because I like it that I'm not satisfied.
There happen to be two people in this very room
who refuse to address me accordingly.
At best, Mr. Karasuma talks to me using nothing but,
"Hey. Hey, you."
What are we, a middle-aged couple?
We're adults.
We don't say things like "Koro-sensei"
because it makes us sound like idiots.
Here's a thought.
We could call each other by specially chosen code names,
couldn't we?
Are you serious?
Yeah!
I mean, codenames are actually kind of appropriate
for this classroom.
The assassins we met on the island all had one, remember?
They used them to keep their real names a secret.
Personally, I think it made them sound
really polished and professional.
Yes, of course. That's an excellent idea!
Here's what we'll do, then.
Write down a suggested codename
for each of your classmates and place them in the box.
We'll call each other by whatever codenames I draw out.
Sounds like fun, but won't we
have to do separate drawings?
I'm writing down the first thing that pops in my head.
Also, I should mention this.
For the rest of the day, real names are forbidden!
What?
Baseball Geek. Come in, Baseball Geek!
Can we confirm that the target's on the move?
Sorry, Lanky Artist, that'd be a negative.
Codename Da Densest is still hiding
out there somewhere in the pine trees.
President Poverty's team will come up
from the rear and chase him toward the swamp.
When he's out in the open,
Hot-n'-Cold Sniper will take the shot.
All right. Let's do this!
Congratulations!
You just let your target slip away from the scene.
Shape up, Womanizing Scumbag!
I told you! Always hold your gun at firing height!
I'm not letting you get away!
Director Mushroom! Mistress Kanzaki! Fluffy Stag Beetle!
He's headed your way!
Don't worry, we've got him!
He pulled a fast one!
Home Plate! Loofah! Picture-Book Graduate!
I'm on it!
That's right, keep those eyes on the ground.
Nicely done, Pseudo-Takaoka.
Don't get comfortable!
Scoring a hit on me doesn't mean anything.
It certainly doesn't mean you can get helped!
Poison Specs! Forever Flat!
If I can see your positions, I can dodge your shots!
He spotted us. Dignified Didact, take over!
All right!
English Lass, Gender! You two get a move on!
Roger, that!
Nice shooting.
They didn't give away their position.
That has to be thanks to Dignified Didact's leadership.
Keep your distance back there. Wait for your chance.
Terminal Perv and This Manga is
Amazing aren't too bad, either.
Semi-Senioritis has blocked the escape route.
It's all on you now, Dating Sim Emo Character.
Dating Sim Emo Character!
I told you, a sniper has to assume
his target is always on high alert!
I know, but the one taking you down...
is Justice!
How'd it go?
Using those codenames felt pretty great, huh?
Actually, it was kinda painful.
"Scrunchies and Boobs"? Really?
Try being called "Amazing Ape" all day.
Ah, yes. Well, I see.
Could someone explain what "Box o' Moe" means?
Uh, isn't it pretty obvious?
Excuse me, sir?
My codename was just the same thing as my real one.
Correct.
Because I knew what you'd be doing in P.E.
Given your agility,
it was all but certain you'd have a special role to play.
And considering the moves you showcased out there
this afternoon, I'd say "Justice" fits perfectly.
You bet it does!
Now, now. Rest assured, Kimura my boy.
If you don't like it, requesting a name change is
simply a matter of filling out the right paperwork.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You should bear in mind, however.
If you wind up being the one to actually assassinate me,
I'm certain people are going to
be quite gracious about your name.
"Justice indeed," they'll say.
"Wow, what else do you call the
man who saved the entire world, eh?'
Honestly there's very little significance
to the names our parents give us.
We don't choose what we're called,
but we can choose what people come to associate with it.
Names don't make us who we are.
They're merely part of what we
leave behind as we walk through life.
Footprints in the sand.
That said, cherish them.
If nothing else, for their potential.
"Justice," for example.
Why not hold on to that until after the assassination?
What do you say?
Hmm...
Yeah! I think I will.
Now then!
Since everyone got to use their codename today,
it's only fair that I divulge my own.
From this point forward, kindly refer to me as follows:
"Prince of the Fateful Eternal Wind."
Why do you get to pick one that's all fancy-schmancy?
And wipe that smug look off your face!
Aw, c'mon! Just for one day, then! Please?
And for the rest of the day,
Koro-sensei was referred to by a very different name.
"The Octopus of the Idiotic Perverted Chicken!"
Octopus?!
Well, that was fun.
The codename thing was a blast!
Maybe he'll let us do it again sometime.
Hope so. Right, Picture-Book Graduate?
Shut your face, Baseball Geek.
Call the burn unit!
My codename doesn't even make sense.
Yeah! And while we're at it,
who's brilliant idea was "Forever Flat?"
Like that means anything!
So it was you.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, I could go for a bowl of
that disgusting ramen. Let's go.
Not cool, man.
He's fittin' in with Terasaka's group pretty well.
Sure looks like it.
And so time marched on,
all of us determined to give
Second Term everything we had.
Of course, being E-Class, it was more or less a
given that the good times wouldn't last forever.
Dare I ask how things are coming along?
Of course, I trust you realize any response short of
"exceptionally well" would be unacceptable for A-Class.
Things are going exceptionally well.
Any student who lags behind gets left behind. Period.
I have no patience for slackers.
None. I rule with an iron fist.
And when it comes to midterms, the bar has been raised.
That is encouraging.
However, it appears you are still the
subject of much derision among the student body.
Letting E-Class get the better of you in the First Term.
It's not a stain that washes out.
Let people say what they like. I'll crush them!
Will you now?
At its most basic, this institution
is divided into two groups: The weak and the strong.
Which group you belong to is, on
principle, of no consequence to me.
That being said,
allow me to offer you a little guidance.
True leadership requires an aptitude for winning.
And on top of that...
to triumph, a leader must first consider the
where and when, and the how soon will follow.
Should a loophole present itself,
it is to be exploited mercilessly.
Good word, "aptitude."
Something without which you haven't a
prayer in the world of besting me, Asano.
Very well.
Then my aptitude will be on
full display, Mr. Principal, sir.