I'm not even sure it's possible.
But instead of killing Koro-sensei,
I think we should try to save him.
Save him?
By like, finding a way to keep him
from self-detonating come March, or what?
Where do we start?
Well, I don't know. Yet.
But...
Totally! I'm game!
Koro-sensei's way too good of a
bug-hunting buddy to let explode!
Kurahashi...
Thank you for bringing it up.
If you hadn't said something, I would've.
Saving him's the least we can do.
So you're on board?
Seems appropriate.
It is what this class has been leading to.
Damn right. I'm in!
Far as I'm concerned, it's a whole new challenge!
Like a new show, sort of.
I really don't wanna live with the guilt.
I mean we're obligated to at least give it a shot.
Guys, you...
Thank goodness...
They feel the same way I do.
I really hate to be the one who spoils the mood...
but I'm against it.
Huh?
We're assassins. He's the target.
That's our bond.
Koro-sensei said so himself.
I don't know about you, but I cherish that bond.
Think about it.
Not killing him would defeat the purpose.
Nakamura, I...
You're against it?
We get wantin' to save him and all.
But how do we know it's even doable?
Well, I...
You act like you're the only
one who's been thinkin' about this.
Also, what happens if the clock runs out on
us before we find a way? Did you consider that?
Seriously. You want the Octopus's last thought to
be. "Damn, my students are a bunch of half-asses"?
No! But...
We owe it to him!
Always the talented ones, huh?
Figuring whatever the odds, in
the end, things will always work out.
Wow. Listen to you.
Getting a tad full of yourself there, chief.
Granted, you're the most gifted one in our class.
But seriously.
We should just up and scrap the whole assassination plan?
What about the underdogs?
Those of us who work ourselves sick just to squeak by
on what little talent we have. How're we supposed to feel?
You're like a hot chick tellin' her homely
friends there's no point trying to find a man.
'Course you don't have a problem with
changing the rules. You've already won the game.
That... That's not what I'm trying to say...
Besides... I'm not the gifted one. Between
you and me, you're the better assassin.
Okay, hearing you talk like
that just pisses me off even more.
You know what your problem is, Nagisa?
You've got no respect for how hard
this is for everyone who isn't you.
Whoa, whoa! Where is this coming
from?! I'm just telling you how I feel!
Do you have an axe to grind
with Koro-sensei or something?!
He took us to the movies! He's made learning fun!
That's my point! Why do you think he bothered?! Huh?!
He didn't want us to end up like a bunch
of whiney, half-assed jerks! And look at you!
Assassinating him is what this entire class is
based on. You're just trying to find a loophole!
You wanna undermine what Koro-sensei's done?
Or do you have the mind and the body of a ten-year-old?
Ah. What's with that look?
Aw, the itty-bitty mouse wanna roar?
Feel like he could take on a lion?
No, I...
Got somethin' to say?
Kick my ass for once and you can say whatever you like.
Oh, don't be shy. What're you
afraid of? Let's settle this like men.
C'mon! Ha!
A flying triangle hold!
I am not... a whiney, half-assed jerk!
Well, all right then. When did Nagisa learn that move?
Um...
He's still no match for Karma in hand-to-hand combat.
You little...!
Knock it off!
What the hell are the two of you trying to prove?!
Okay! I don't think I can hold him back!
Damn it, Karma! Will you chill out already?
A good old-fashioned schoolyard fight?
Outstanding!
However, you're the Assassination Classroom!
This is how we settle our differences!
What kind of mediator are you?!
Oh, these are just red and blue paintballs.
Red for those who feel I must be liquidated.
Blue for those who beg to differ.
Before we begin, I want each of you to state
his or her position clearly and choose a color.
Then, after battling it out on the
mountainside like civilized human beings,
the winning team's opinion prevails.
Absolutely no grudges allowed!
Seem fair?
For the record...
Whatever the outcome, I'll respect your decision,
provided you defend it with everything you have.
You are all a family.
I can't abide for my students
to be at odds with each other.
If you truly care about me, promise what
we've built here won't crumble into discord.
Well, guys?
Right. Let's do it.
To kill or not to kill.
'Kay, then. So, guess I'll choose a side.
Me, too.
The insta-kill shot's almost there.
We've put a lot of work into it.
And, as for who, or what, got us this far...
I'm sure he'd want to see us take it all the way.
We keep our eyes on the target.
Chiba... Hayami, you...
My mind's made up.
I've already tried to assassinate him once,
and I regret it.
I want Koro-sensei to live as long as possible.
My sister felt the same way;
Must run in the family or something.
No more death.
He's entitled to our protection.
Having a thing for assassins runs in the family, too...
The power of science is limitless!
If it can sow destruction, then
surely it can find a way to save!
Right. And it's not as though hope is slim,
we can do anything together. I know we can.
Sorry, but us hands-on types?
We kinda see this assassination as our big final project.
If Koro-sensei's gonna die anyway,
showing him our masterpiece
will be his going away present.
Justice is a tricky concept for a kid like me,
you're the one who taught me to respect it.
My choice is clear: Gotta live up to my name.
I suppose I'm selfish.
I want him to keep giving us good advice.
Save the planet or save our teacher?
Blah, blah, blah. We're just goin' around in circles.
I'm more of a cut-to-the-chase kind of gal.
If you can't be true to your own feelings, what
hope is there in life? I want him to live, that's that.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
We're simple guys at heart, the two of us.
We wanna save him 'cause we wanna save him, y'know?
Right?
Sure. As long as I can still be
sensitive to everyone else's needs.
I'm a simple guy. I joined this class to kill him.
I've learned a lot. Even made a few friends.
Coming up with ways to kill him has been fun.
So, yeah. More of that, please.
It may be my prime directive, but after
several attempts to assassinate Koro-sensei,
I'm at a loss. The protocol has changed.
I've thought about this, and I've come to the conclusion
that the target's death would
be an immeasurable loss to us.
The right course of action is unclear.
My current specs are unable to make
an informed decision on the matter.
So in the spirit of cooperation, I'll remain neutral.
Not gonna lie... I was in the no-kill camp.
But hearing everyone's thoughts... now I'm not so sure.
I have a question.
If we do this, does killing
you necessarily mean we hate you?
Of course not, Okano.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
It's when you're killing me that I feel the most loved.
Well, in that case, Nagisa, I'm sorry.
Pretty sure my feelings are more
in line with where these guys stand.
Guess it was a little arrogant of me
to think I spoke for the whole class.
Aw, man.
This is gonna be one hell of a showdown, huh?
Uh, hey, I've been kinda wondering about something.
So Nagisa and Karma...
They've been friends for a while, yeah?
Oh, sure, been in the same
class since they were First Years.
They hang out all the time.
Huh. But look how they act.
There's always this polite distance.
You can hear it in the way they talk sometimes.
Like they don't really feel comfortable with each other.
All right.
Looks like everyone's picked a side.
The object is to the steal the opposing team's flag,
or to wipe them out entirely. It's my job to referee.
I'll be watching from midpoint.
If I see zombies or any other
illegal moves, I'll call 'em.
Don't worry. For all intents and purposes,
I'm blind to your respective positions, got it?
Even if the pro-kill team wins this thing,
odds are an assassination at this stage won't succeed.
These kids are just too conflicted
to go through with it. Who wouldn't be?
Here we go. Are you ready?
Let the intra-class assassination survival game...
Begin!
Right out of the gate?!
Ugh!
Shot just as we were getting into position!
It's hard to establish a BB's trajectory beyond 50 meters.
Chiba and Hayami's super
long-distance sniper shot is incredible!
Holy crap.
The killing machines you've made out of those two!
Indeed.
Though, as you'll see, they're far from the only ones.
Nice job: Keep your sights trained on the enemy.
You're kidding me! Wow. Did not see that one coming!
I should've known.
Kanzaki: Undisputed champion of the online war game.
Started playing to help with
assassination and got where I mastered it.
What?!
I'm glad I did. The hours it took really paid off.
Yukiko. She's been keepin' a low profile.
Hasn't she, though?
And her battle style is so classical!
A frontal breakthrough on this field is quite difficult.
Normally, the best strategy would be to
circle around and attack from the outside.
And yet...
Oh, that's right.
You cut your teeth on a virtual battlefield, didn't you?
Trouble is, once I realize you're
making a beeline for a key position,
all I have to do is be patient and wait for you to jump.
Red Team, it's Karma. I'll be taking the lead.
Mimura, there's a highpoint to
Mr. Karasuma's right. You should have a visual.
Go for it.
Copy that.
Make sure no one sees you.
Terasaka and the other stooges, I
want you on defense at Face Rock.
We're screwed if they make it
past there, so play it tight.
Man, why are we always pawns?
Shut your hole!
Ah! Very well done out there!
I was careless.
We were only two minutes in and I got killed...
By Karma's orders, most likely.
Incredible.
The red-headed one's so organized.
What else does he have up his sleeve?
Karma, I'm at the highpoint.
Perfect.
You should have a clear view of the enemies' movements.
Anyone shows up, give me their positions
and I'll order our team to mobilize.
Mimura always blends in. Makes him ideal for covert ops.
Plus he's got a producer's eye for the field,
which translates into a real knack for reconnaissance.
Not that anyone else in class has ever noticed.
I see Sugino and Fuwa, I think.
Forest, right flank.
Nice. Keep it up.
Hazama, this is your cue to advance.
Where'd she even come from?!
Stop being one with the shadows, dang it!
Rat bastard used me as a decoy.
You'll be paying for that, Karma.
Why move Hazama into such a compromising position?
He had to have known she'd be hopelessly outnumbered.
Well, Hazama is a terrible fighter, but
she did manage to take down two enemies.
Not least of which was Sugino, the close-combat superstar.
Their ranks are in shambles.
Now's the time for a surprise attack.
Okano?
On it!
Oh no!
I lost the Battle of the Hinas. I'm sorry...
Ha! Well done! You've been holding out on us!
I'm gonna assume you didn't
pick these moves up in gym class!
I'm an actor, I take training for a role very seriously!
Now that I don't have to mask
the pain of having tentacles,
I can actually focus!
Aw, crap...
Koro-sensei... I'll keep you safe!
I'm impressed.
But I sure wish we could've
seen this side of you before now.
You weren't the only one working hard in secret.
We've all been training. Honing our skills.
However this business ends up,
we'll face it together as a class.
No masks. No more secret agendas.
Sound good?
Okay, then. We'll see you later!
Oh-ho, hey! Remind me to get your autograph.
Ee-hee-yeah-ha!
Let's keep up the momentum and tag someone else!
You sure? But Karma's orders were to hit and run!
Yo, look! It's Hara and she's wide open!
Tonight's rations belong to me!
Uh-oh! Ha! Little homemade trap of mine.
Mama is fierce.
An unarmed girl alone in the woods
must seem like a pretty easy mark.
I suppose looks can be deceiving, huh?
Hey, no butt-cutting, pervert!
Stupid idiot got ahead of himself. Seriously, why
the hell can't people just do what I tell them to?
Yeah, it's a tragedy.
Well, looks like it's time for
your lieutenant to finish this off.
Isn't that why you left the stooges over there?
Not bad. You get me.
Have fun.
Ah-ha! Over there!
Ugh, I figured our formation was leaked.
Mimura can see us!
As of now, both sides are down by half.
Okay, I think it's time we start
focusing on flag-capturing tactics.
Strategic maneuvering is key.
We were bound to get here eventually.
It's why we took out Kataoka and Takebayashi first.
To deprive the enemy camp of options.
To that end, Hayami's lookout
position was absolutely crucial.
Couldn't have done it without her.
I'm gonna need you stand guard, Itona.
Chiba can shoot farther and hit the target more often,
but her balance and kinetic vision are way better.
Give her an active battlefield
like this, and she really shines.
She's not gonna be an easy one.
Gotta go in carefully.
We could try attacking from the opposite side,
but then we'd have to break through
Terasaka's defensive line, and he's too solid.
And the area around their flag
is well within Hayami's range.
We've no choice but to take Hayami out first.
Hayami, Itona, they'll be coming in droves any second now.
Do whatever you can to slow 'em down.
If you can take 'em out, take 'em out.
Roger.
Nakamura, when the fight starts, I
want you to step in and finish it.
Gotcha.
That means we're counting on you, Meat Wall!
Excuse me?!
Shut up. Everyone else'll be occupied with Rinka.
I'm gonna rush in while you play the part of my shield.
Once you three are dead, I'll
have time to capture the flag.
Good strategy, right? Of course it is.
So we're being sacrificed, then?
That is some serious ruthlessness.
Duh! We have to do whatever it takes.
I wanna win this... so we can kill Koro-sensei.
I know what this is.
You wanted us all to think you
were stupid, so you did stupid stuff.
But be honest, you joined the pro-kill
camp because you feel you have a sense of duty.
In reality, out of everyone here you're
the one who takes things the most seriously.
The plan's as ready as it's ever going to be I suppose.
There's just one hitch: Nagisa.
Not even Mimura can figure out where he is.
Okay, guys. Forget about defense.
Take out Hayami and Itona no matter what!
Tag those two, and Karma's the only one guarding the flag.
Let's settle this now!
All right...
Let's get over there, guys!
Surround them from the left!
Isogai's in the lead.
If I can take him down, we'll have this game in the bag!
I sincerely hate conflict,
and never once have I managed to
shoot anywhere near as good as Rinka.
But this isn't for me. It's for Koro-sensei!
Yada...?
I got her!
And I'm out, too...
Cool, huh?
I had a feeling I was more of a knife guy, y'know?
I mean, there's no way I'm worth a damn with a gun.
Son of a...
Did they get you?!
It doesn't matter. The flag's unguarded either way.
It's time.
Nakamura, get in there now.
Yes, sir!
From behind at point-blank range...?
Like a bolt of lightning out of the clear blue sky!
Where in the world has he been hiding?!