[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
the true objective of Doctor
Myuu's evil experiments
was discovered.
The fiendish physician had
been gathering life force
for the creation of Baby--
the ultimate mutant machine.
But thanks to Trunks and Giru,
the Neo-Mutant seemed
to have perished
in it's embryonic state.
[DR. MYUU] The Galaxy
is yours for the taking!
Live Baby! Please!
Your my only baby! My only...
Don't leave me.
Please don't leave me.
[NARRATOR]
Defying premature death,
Baby entered the world
with a vengeance!
Trunks! Pan! Now!
My Baby. Every time I hear
that it makes my insides
boil so much I want to explode.
You are nothing but
a simple machine mutant.
For it was I who
programmed you to gather the
energy needed for
my resurrection.
And it was I who gave you
the plans for creating Luud
and the other machine mutants!
Yet, you had no idea,
you feeble shell of a machine!
Your time on
this planet is over!
[NARRATOR] A true monster was
born and it had Goku, Pan,
and Trunks in it sights!
My time is just beginning.
I know three
disgusting creatures
who have to die today...
They won't be expecting me.
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
All right! Good work, Giru.
It looks brand new again!
[PAN] I don't think
it ever looked this shiny
before we left!
It really is pretty.
[TRUNKS]
Nice work, Giru!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
I sure am glad
that Giru is around.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru. Giru good!
Dragon Balls, here we come!
I know this is your home Giru,
but when your home stinks,
it's best to just
find another one!
You're okay about
that, aren't you?
[GIRU]
Absolutely! Giru, Giru.
Great! Now let's go get
the Dragon Balls back!
Yeah!
[TRUNKS]
Good riddance, Planet M2!
[ALL]
Whoa!
[PAN] What do you think you're
doing, Trunks! This isn't funny!
It's not me!
You defective piece
of scrap metal!
Why did we ever let you lay
a finger on our spaceship?!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
No, it's not that!
Something's holding us!
[TRUNKS]
Impossible!
[GOKU]
Rilldo!
[PAN]
This guy just won't quit!
Imbeciles! No one makes it
off my planet in one piece!
You wanna bet?!
Wake up, Rilldo!
Don't you get it?
Myuu doesn't care about you!
He thinks you're inferior!
He'll exterminate you, as well!
[RILLDO] Me? The greatest
mutant robot! Inferior?
He's snapped! If we don't
take him out, we're going down!
[TRUNKS]
Get ready, Goku!
Now!
[battle crys]
Curse you!
[shrieks]
[PAN] Grandpa! Would
you kindly remove your foot
from my posterior!
I'd be happy to.
But someone's gonna have
to move their knee first.
Trunks!
Okay, no fooling
around you guys.
We don't have much time left!
We have to get the Dragon Balls
or Earth will be gone forever.
We would be done...
...if a certain robot
hadn't messed up our plans!
Grandpa? What's the matter
with your stomach? Are you sick?
[GOKU] Worse than that...
I'm starving!
Didn't you hear what Trunks just
said? We need to get serious!
[stomach growls]
Sure. But can we eat first?
[GOKU] Uhh! I think
I'm dying, you guys!
[PAN]
Don't be such a wimp!
[GOKU] Come on, Pan!
You know how I get
when my stomach is empty!
[PAN]
Poor Grandma.
[GOKU]
What's wrong with Grandma?
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!...
[TRUNKS] It looks
like we're in business!
[GIRU] Dragon Ball dead ahead!
On screen now!
[GIRU]
Magnifying image!
[GIRU] Dragon Ball on board!
Dragon Ball on board!
[PAN] Look at
all of those holes!
It must have been
pummeled by meteorites!
[TRUNKS]
I don't think so!
It looks like those holes were
made from the inside out!
[GOKU] Think there's
anything to eat in there?
[GIRU] Danger! Danger! Gravity
pulls ship in. Into star!
10 minutes! 10 minutes!
Are you sure about that Giru?
That star's kind of small!
[GIRU] Gravity seventy times
greater than Earth!
Giru be crushed!
Let's move! If we're not
out of here in ten minutes,
we'll lose our ship
and the Dragon Ball!
Look at you,
Mr. Dying of Starvation!
So now you're all
ready to go? Huh?
{GOKU] No problem
boarding this ship!
[TRUNKS] Not with
these new renovations.
The hull has been
completely demolished.
[PAN] What do you think
happened here, you guys?
[TRUNKS] I don't know,
but whatever it was
it had some serious power!
[PAN] There's not a soul around!
This is really creepy!
[GIRU] Dragon Ball ahead!
Dragon Ball ahead!
[GOKU]
Come on, you guys!
[PAN]
Wait for me!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[PAN] Hmm!
It's not so bad in here!
Looks like the artificial
atmosphere is still intact!
[GOKU]
Super!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Dragon Ball
this way! Dragon Ball inside!
[TRUNKS] Goku! Would you
like to do the honors?
[GOKU]
I'd be happy to!
Ha!
[TRUNKS] Pan! Wait!
It could be a trap!
[PAN] Nonsense!
Don't be so paranoid!
See, Trunks!
Nothing to it! Voila!
[TRUNKS]
Mmm!
[GOKU]
What's the matter, Trunks?
I don't know! It's just
that finding a Dragon Ball
has never been
this easy before!
Come on! Lighten up!
It's probably just
my good karma!
[GOKU]
Pan? What is it?
Someone's in here!
[GOKU] I don't sense anything!
Do you, Trunks?
No!
Well, something moved! I saw it!
Someone might still be alive...
...and I'm gonna find 'em!
Griu, how much
time do we have left?!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru!
Five minutes! Danger!
Go on back to the ship,
you guys! I'll meet you there!
Someone's still
alive on this crate
and my conscience won't let
me leave until I find 'em!
[TRUNKS]
Pan! Wait!
[GOKU]
She's just like ChiChi!
Once her mind's made up,
there's no stopping her!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
Error! Error! Calculation error!
Two minutes remaining!
[TRUNKS] That's one
serious miscalculation!
[GOKU]
Pan's still in there!
[PAN] Hello! Come out,
whoever you are!
I know you're here! I saw you!
Holy smoke! Are those
legs or skyscrapers?
Hey, I know I'm intruding
but I'm just trying to help!
Let's be friends! Okay?
My name's Pan. What's yours?
[screams]
What's going on you guys?
Giru got his calculations wrong!
We have less than two minutes!
Way to go, Giru!
[GIRU]
Giru. Giru.
Danger! Danger!
Sorry, tinhead...
but we've got to go!
[laughs]
Just too easy!
I don't think that robot
had enough fire power
to damage this big
of a ship that bad!
I was thinking the same thing.
But if he didn't
do it, then who did?
You guys think too much!
We can sit and wonder about it
or we can get
the heck out of here!
[GIRU] Life form reading
detected! Very weak! This way!
[PAN]
I did see someone!
[PAN] There he is!
H-He's not dead. Is he?
[TRUNKS] I don't know.
I hope not.
He's alive!
The sole survivor!
[GIRU] Danger!
One minute left! Ship doomed!
We've got a lot of
ground to cover!
Trunks, pick him
up and let's go!
--Hurry!
--Right!
[glass shattering]
[GIRU] Thirty seconds remain!
Twenty nine seconds!
Twenty-eight seconds! Twent--
Shut up!
Hey, you guys?! This thing's
not moving! What's wrong?
[TRUNKS]
It's not the bikes!
We're not moving because
we're being pulled in
by the star's gravity!
It's overpowering us!
Forget that!
That's full throttle!
[PAN] Grandpa! Trunks!
This isn't working!
[TRUNKS] We've only got a couple
of minutes worth of power
before these things
give out on us!
We don't have that long!
Ditch the bikes, now!
[PAN]
Oh, no!
Don't give up Pan! Push!
[PAN]
I'm trying Grandpa!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
Nice shot!
Grab hold!
[TRUNKS]
Pan! Take my hand!
[PAN]
Grandpa! We're slowing down!
At this rate the ship
will be pulled in, too!
I've got an idea! Afterburners!
Trunks! Giru! Pan! You guys
hold on as tight as you can!
I'm going to try
giving us a boost!
[GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Haa!
[PAN] The poor, little guy's
really struggling!
I don't think he's
going to make it
if we don't get him some help!
[TRUNKS]
Yeah, I think you're right.
But finding a planet
with medical facilities
is the problem.
Giru! Distress call!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[GIRU] Mayday! Mayday!
Vessel seeking port!
Need emergency
medical attention!
Please respond! Please respond!
Just hang on.
[GIRU] Incoming transmission!
Incoming transmission!
[MAN]
Planet Vidal here!
We are standing by
with medical attention!
Transmitting coordinates now!
Fantastic!
That's great!
Hey! Ask him what
kind of food they have!
Ah! What was that for?
[PA] The red zone is for
loading and unloading
of emergency vehicles only.
No parking is allowed
in the red zone.
[DOCTOR] Nurse, have
you seen my stethascope?
[NURSE] Doctor, I need 50ccs
of Synsadrine, stat!
[HEAD NURSE] Here's the test
results you asked for, Doctor.
[SURGEON] Nurse, where's
that chart I asked for?
[ASSISTANT] Doctor, here's
the chart you requested.
[RECEPTIONIST] Okay, if you
have a seat in lobby,
we'll be with you
in just a minute.
[HEAD DOCTOR] Orderly, can you
take this up to the lab?
[ORDERLY] Excuse me doctor,
you're needed in Exam Room 3.
[PAN]
All we can do now is hope.
[waiting room chatter]
[NURSE] Okay, I just need you to
fill out this insurance form...
[family bouncing in unison]
[DOCTOR] Are you the ones
who brought the boy in?
Yes! How is he? Is he okay?
His condition was quite serious,
and he could have died but,
our facility is number
one in the galaxy
and he will make
a full recovery.
Thank you so much!
What a relief! Eh, Goku?
Huh? Where'd he go?
What's wrong, Grandpa?
Look, doctors give shots!
I hate shots!
So I avoid doctors!
[laughing]
[GOKU] They won't be laughing
when they get the needle!
[NURSE] Oh, my stars!
It must be broken!
I've never seen
readings like this before!
They're off the chart!
Just what are you doing?!
Please, get back to bed!
You have to have your rest!
[NURSE] If you don't get back in
bed right this second,
I'm calling the doctor!
[mischievous laugh]
[BLACK HAIRED DOCTOR]
What? I'm serious!
[screams]
[BLACK HAIRED DOCTOR]
Get some orderlies in here!
On the double!
[woman screams]
Now what?
[ORDERLY]
What happened?
[RED HEADED NURSE]
I don't know!
We've got massive equipment
failures in Intensive Care!
Oh, no, you guys!
That's where the boy is!
[PA]
Emergency in ICU One!
[NARRATOR] Trouble has
erupted on Planet Vidal!
Just who is the mysterious boy
that Goku, Trunks,
and Pan rescued?
And what does he intend to do?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next GT!