[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
[SS4 GOKU]
Now, laugh at this!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Ha!
[NARRATOR] Goku, using all
the energy he could muster,
unleashed an Ultimate
Kamehameha Wave on Baby,
his fiercest attack yet!
[SS4 GOKU] Your overconfidence
will be your undoing.
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[NARRATOR] Having withstood
Goku's attack with ease,
Baby armed himself with
the Super Gallic Gun
to wreak havoc on
the now winded Saiyan!
[SS4 GOKU] Are you willing
to sink that low, Baby?
[BABY]
Super Gallic Gun!
Baby! You haven't
seen the last of me!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY] Oh-ho! That's
going to leave a bruise!
He's lost all control. If he
makes an attack like that again,
the force of the earth's
explosion will send debris
and shockwaves smashing
into the Tuffle planet,
destroying it, too.
But then he'd kill himself!
[NARRATOR] With every
passing minute, the fate
of the Tuffle planet and all
it's Earth-born inhabitants
grows more and more bleak,
as it hangs in the balance
of Baby's own sanity!
Is this the final day
of the human race,
or will Goku be
able to stop it?
[KIBITO]
Goku! Goku, wake up!
[SUGORO]
What's he waiting for?
Oh, this is not
looking good.
[BABY]
If that's all he's got,
then that putrid monkey
will be done for in no time!
[CROWD clamoring]
Baby! Finish that Saiyan
once and for all!
[ALL] Baby! Finish that
Saiyan once and for all!
Baby! Finish that Saiyan
once and for all!
Lord Baby! Rip his head
off while your at it.
[SS4 GOKU]
Come on already.
Those Kamehameha waves
should have kicked in by now!
[BABY]
Your time has come, Saiyan!
Any last words
you'd like to share?
[BABY BULMA screams]
[BABY]
Nooooo!
[CROWD screaming]
[BABY] Who in the world
could have attacked me?
It couldn't have
been the Saiyan.
He was lying face down in
the dirt the whole time.
Unless... Of course!
Now. Laugh at this!
Ka... Me...
Ha!
[BABY] It figures he
has a delayed attack.
I guess he needs
his dirty tricks
to have any chance against me.
[SS4 GOKU] Looks like you
weren't expecting that one,
were you, Baby?
You should try to
be more perceptive.
[BABY] The only thing I'm
going to do is kill you
as quickly and
painfully as possible.
So let's cut to the chase and
do what we came here to do!
You know, I've heard enough.
You're having trouble
standing on your own feet,
much less fighting me.
[BABY]
You're hallucinating then.
There's enough
fight in this body
to last me for weeks on end!
Think so? Try me.
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[KIBITO]
I can't believe
they knocked each
other out, Ancestor.
I mean, what an
amazing fight so far!
Okay! Now's our chance!
[ALL gasp]
What exactly do
you have in mind?
Listen up. It's very important
that you focus right now.
Yes, because focusing
is the key to
channeling enough energy
to revive Goku's power.
[OLD KAI]
No, dummy.
You don't have nearly
enough power to revive Goku
since he's a Super Saiyan Four.
You would need to match his
power to even attempt it!
But--
[OLD KAI] Why don't you start by
reviving Trunks or Gohan first?
What in the world are
you talking about?
Don't you know? Trunks has
been taken over by Baby,
so reviving him would
only be helping the enemy.
It doesn't make sense.
That's why you'll need
the Sacred Water.
Sacred Wa--
That's right!
The Sacred water
at the Lookout!
Why didn't I think
of that earlier?
Well, if it's a secret,
how do you know about it?
No, not 'Secret Water,'
Sacred Water!
[KIBITO] Sacred Water is
a legendary liquid
with enormous healing powers.
When splashed on a person,
it purifies and removes
all toxins from the body.
Oh... Then I won't tell anyone.
That's great! And I vow to do
whatever it takes to
obtain the sacred water,
and begin soaking every infected
being with it's cleansing power.
Then why don't you fetch
some, Mr. Know-It-All!
Yes. Yes, of course. I'll be
back right away. Wish me luck.
[OLD KAI] It's about time
he got going, eh?
He can be such a
burden at times.
That was quick.
Sorry about this but,
where do I go to find
the Sacred Water again?
Kibito, where has your mind
been for all these years?
Do you really not know?!
I'm sorry, Ancestor.
It's by the throne in the
temple at Kami's Lookout!
Now get moving!
Right away, sir!
[OLD KAI sighs]
[KIBITO yelps]
[KIBITO]
Whoa, that was a close call.
It looks like Popo and Dende
are still under Baby's control.
I need to be
extremely careful!
[KIBITO gasps]
Look at me. Even though
I may be a Kai Spirit,
I'm sneaking around like
a petty cat burglar!
[KIBITO] There's the throne that
Old Kai was talking about!
And there's the Sacred Water!
There's not as much as
I thought there would be!
Looks like I hit the jackpot!
There's plenty here
to cure everyone!
Tastes normal!
There's so many
of these barrels.
How does Old Kai expect
me to carry them away?
And how can I be
sure that all of this
is even the right stuff?
[BABY DENDE]
Why are you running around here
like some kind of
cat burglar, Kibito?
Surely you're not thinking
of using this Sacred Water
against the wishes of Baby,
because those who try
such a foolish things
meet with a grim fate.
Well, you see...
[BABY DENDE]
Even though you're a Kai,
we cannot allow this
to go any further.
Prepare to defend yourself!
[KIBITO grunting]
[KIBITO panting]
Hey, what are you doing?!
Take this!
And this!
Cut it out!
Why isn't any of this
water working on them?
If I mess this up,
Old Kai will kill me!
[BABY DENDE cackling]
[KIBITO panting]
End of the line Kibito Kai.
[BABY POPO] Oh!
[KIBITO grunts]
[BABY POPO yells]
[BABY POPO gurgling]
This must be it.
What's happening
to you, Popo! Popo!
Ah! Here!
[BABY DENDE gasps]
[BABY DENDE groaning]
Don't worry guys. This is
for your own good. Trust me.
[BOTH groaning]
What happened?
Hey, you're back to normal!
Kibito, why are you here?
Okay, I found the Sacred Water.
Now I need to find Trunks.
Make sure it's on tight.
Now, Trunks.
There he is!
Gotta go guys. See ya later!
Are you as lost as I am?
Yeah.
Listen up, Trunks. You've got
to drink this! Come on! Wake up!
Drink! You only
need a little bit.
[TRUNKS groaning]
Is that you Kibito Kai?
Don't you worry, Trunks.
You're back to your old self.
Yeah, but where am I?
[TRUNKS] Okay, you want me to go
down there and take out Baby,
or at least keep him
busy for awhile.
How much time do you need?
Well, as much as you can.
And while you're doing that,
I'll start using this
water on everyone else,
starting with Gohan.
Great! Sounds like a plan.
[KIBITO]
I have faith in you Trunks.
Back to work.
[BABY BULMA groaning]
[BABY BULMA]
Oh No!
Lord Baby!
What's happend here?
The only way to revive him is
with the Blutz Wave Amplifier!
I just hope it works as well
as last time. It has too!
The antennae are in place.
We're ready to go.
Now is your chance.
Baby, you must stand up!
This may be the last time
I get the amplifier running!
[BABY BULMA]
Initiate... and fire!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[BABY BULMA]
I think it's working!
Please stand up, Baby! Stand up!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY BULMA grunts, cackles]
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[BABY]
How can this be?
I'm filling up with
power, growing stronger.
You've really outdone
yourself, Bulma!
Lord Baby! These are
pure Blutz Waves.
You will receive
all of the energy
while the Saiyan receives none!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[ALL gasp]
Oh no! Those appear to be the
same waves of energy as before.
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY] Yes! Excellent work, my
dear! I'm stronger than ever!
[BABY cackling]
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[TRUNKS groans]
Where... Where did
that come from?
[KIBITO]
What is that?
I hope it's not too late.
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[SS4 GOKU] I see you're
feeling better now, Baby.
It's funny. Did you know
that when you're sleeping,
like just now. You snore
like a little baby?
[BABY] So, you still have enough
strength to actually speak,
do you?
[SS4 GOKU] Well, while you
were laid out unconscious
on the ground, I decided to take
a little nap until you woke up.
And may I say
that this has been
one of my most
rewarding battles ever.
Which makes my achieving Super
Saiyan 4 all the more worth it.
[BABY] Oh, is that so? This must
be your inner peace taking over
to make the transition into
death that much easier!
I will enjoy this!
[SUGORO] Wow! Goku is the most
amazing guy I've ever seen!
He looks like he'll be able
to hold off Baby forever now!
Don't you think so, Old Kai?
Don't you? Hm?
Unfortunately, Goku
is only playing a bluff.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Goku is bluffing?
Yes, he's probably
completely drained of
his power at this point.
He may be able to get off
one Kamehameha wave,
but only at normal power.
Uh oh, that's not good.
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[BABY] I had more than enough
chances to kill you earlier,
but each time
I underestimated you.
Now I'm running
on hatred alone,
and nothing will stop me from
dropping you at death's door!
Baby, there's no need for you
to blame me for your mistakes.
[SS4 GOKU]
Okay, enough bluffing Goku.
I practically have
no power left
and my legs feel like
they're made of jelly.
If my body can't handle
what I need to do,
then I'll have to force him
to make his own mistakes.
That may be my only
option at this point.
[BABY]
Well?
Are you ready to finish this
battle once and for all, Saiyan?
[SS4 GOKU] Actually, I'm looking
forward to continuing this.
Allow me to
demonstrate some more
of my new Super Saiyan
powers for you!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[NARRATOR] Now that Baby
has recovered his energy
to full power, Goku is facing
his toughest predicament yet,
as his own powers have
drained almost completely.
But Old Kai and Kibito Kai
have set the wheels in motion
by beginning to take back
some of the key Saiyans
currently controlled by Baby!
Can Kibito Kai work fast enough
to organize the counter-attack
of newly revived Saiyans?
Although Goku's bluff
is working for now,
how long will he
be able to hold it?
And will that buy enough
time for Kibito Kai?
Don't miss the
exciting conclusion
on the next Dragon Ball GT!