[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball GT,
Goku battled Baby, who had
taken over Vegeta's body.
Even Goku's own sons
were against him.
They, too, were being controlled
by the deranged parasite.
But just as it looked
like help had arrived,
Goku found out
that even Trunks
was fully ensnared by
Baby's web of control.
Trunks!
Come on!
You've been friends forever!
Seeking to destroy Goku,
Baby called forth
all of the hatred
that his people had
for the Saiyans,
who had destroyed
their race long ago!
Let it go! Find a way
to rebuild peacefully!
Oh, no! You have a debt to pay!
Revenge Death Ball!
Battered and unable to move,
Goku could only watch as the
dark energy descended upon him!
Then, poof!
Buu can't feel Goku anymore!
Goku!
I don't believe it!
Goku's fate unfolds,
right now on GT.
[HERCULE giggles]
Fresh air and sunshine!
I feel as free as a bird!
[HERCULE gasps]
What's Pan doing down there?
Is she hurt?
[HERCULE yells]
[PAN crying]
Grandpa, why?
Why did you die? I need you!
[BABY evily laughs]
The Black Star
Dragon Balls, Master!
Let us wash down the
sweet taste of revenge
by sipping from
this cup of power.
My friends, what the
Saiyans have destroyed,
we will rebuild! This is it!
[BABY laughs maniacally]
Shenron! Come forth!
Look. It's nighttime.
[HERCULE gasps]
But it's still early.
Oh, no! Dra-Dragon!
It's Shenron!
I've heard Grandpa's stories
but I've never seen
him with my own eyes!
Incredible!
[SHENRON growls]
Why have you summoned me?
We meet at last, Shenron!
I hope that one day soon
my power exceeds your own!
Make your wish!
Very well! My home world was
destroyed! The Saiyans did it!
Now, Shenron! Restore it!
Right here in Earth's orbit!
I command you!
So be it!
[BABY laughs maniacally]
A new Planet Vegeta!
How magnificent!
Let it be known as
the Tuffle Planet!
Your wish has
been granted! Farewell!
[PAN panting]
We just got the balls back
to Earth and now this!
We did all that
work for nothing!
[BUU and HERCULE panting]
[PAN] I'm sorry
beautiful Mother Earth.
I hate to tell you this,
but in one year
you're going to explode!
[HERCULE gasps]
Unless we gather all the balls
again in one year's time.
[PAN thinks] But how?
I can't do it alone!
[HERCULE] The Earth is
going to explode! We're doomed!
Hey! Quiet! Buu doesn't
think Pan should hear that!
You're right, Buu.
I'm the adult here.
I need to act bravely,
like everything's okay,
even if we are all doomed.
Pan? Don't cry, sweetheart.
Everything's going to be okay.
I promise, honey.
Grandpa.
Hm?
[MAN] Just when I get
jazzed about having someone
new to play with,
I see it's only a little boy!
Hey, where am I?
Am I dead or what?
Oh, no!
You're not dead! Yet!
Who are you, Mister?
What? You mean you haven't
heard of moi? My name's Sugoro!
Su-goro?
Good! Now then child,
who are you?
Who me? Uhh... Hey!
I'm no child! The name is Goku!
You're not a child, huh? Okay!
Have it your way, big man!
We'll play by your rules,
until you die! How's that sound?
[SUGORO laughs]
Ha, ha, ha! Look! Nobody's
dying around here! You got that?
Of course not! That's
what I like-- an optimist!
You very well might win!
You seem like a lucky fellow!
Do you feel lucky?
I hope so!
Because if you lose the game,
you lose everything!
[GOKU] But I don't
have anything to lose!
[SUGORO] Oh, yes you do!
Your life!
If you lose the game,
you lose your life!
What? Are you crazy?
Hey! Come back here! I'm not
going to play your silly game!
Tell me how to get
out of here right now!
Oof!
There's only one way
out of Sugoroku Space
and that's to beat me!
Come on! It's gonna be a blast!
[SUGORO] It's just
a simple game of chance!
It's so easy that a child
could understand it!
Besides, my lucky streak
is bound to end sometime!
I've won my last
32,547,000 games.
You have? That's a whole
lot of games. I don't know.
Well, if it was easy,
it wouldn't really
be fun, would it?
You seem like a guy
who likes a challenge!
That's true! Let me
think it over for a while!
[GOKU humming]
It does sound
interesting! Why not?
Besides, I have to!
You said it's the only way out!
But you'd better keep
your word! If I lose, I die!
I get it! But if I win,
I go free and clear!
Eh, ehh! Yes!
That's the deal all right!
[SUGORO] Now then,
the rules are simple.
You role the dice, you get to
advance that number of spaces.
Whoever reaches the end
first wins, but no cheating!
Don't worry about that!
I never cheat!
Well that's a good
thing kid! Trust me!
Because if you cheat,
you die!
Okay! I go first!
Four! One, two, three, four!
Well, what are you waiting for?
It's your turn!
[GOKU giggles]
Six! See ya later!
Go back five spaces!
Oh, yeah! I think
I forgot to mention!
Some spaces have directions!
You can get sent
forward or backward,
depending on the
space! Okay! My turn!
Three! One, two... three!
[trumpets sound]
Lucky Chance!
Roll three more dice
and advance by that number!
[GOKU groans]
Great!
[SUGORO giggles]
Wow! I must be extremely
lucky today! Ha, haa!
Yeah, maybe too lucky!
Come on! That's it! Bite!
Ancestor!
Idiot! You let him get away!
How could you!
I'm sorry ancestor!
I couldn't help it!
He slipped right
out of my hands!
He would have been so delicious!
Huh? Pardon me, Sir, but
who are you talking about?
The fish.
Oh, I misunderstood!
I meant Goku!
Baby was attacking him
with a powerful, dark energy!
I snatched him up just
in the nick of time!
But the repercussions
of that blast
were far more severe
than I realized!
Just as I was making my
inter-dimensional shift,
I was caught in the shockwave!
Goku fell into a different
dimension, into Sugoroku Space!
I lost him.
Oh, dear! Not only that,
you lost him in Sugoroku Space,
the one place we can't help him!
My powers don't work there!
They're useless in that realm!
He's going to have to find
a way out on his own somehow!
Do you know what
the odds of that are?
This must be the biggest
bungle a Kai has made
since I let myself get
trapped in the Z Sword!
[GOKU] Three, four,
five, and stop!
Now what's up?
And the answer is: You!
Answer a riddle
correctly to proceed!
Hey! What's going on? Stop
this crazy thing! Let me down!
You lucky dog!
This is my favorite part!
The riddle will be easy
since you're a child!
I'm not a child!
I told you that already!
And the first question is...
Hey! Wait! This isn't fair!
I'm no good at riddles!
Listen up!
What can run, but not walk?
What? What do you mean!
Me? Is the answer "Me"?
U-Uh! Sorry! Wrong! The
correct answer is: Water.
Water can run but not walk.
I get it.
They're like trick questions.
Answer wrong and
the hole gets bigger!
Careful, Goku! If it gets
too big, you'll fall in!
Trust me! That's not good!
What's down there?
[SUGORO] That's it! Take a look!
Deep, deep, down!
Question two!
No! I'm not good at this!
[BABY] This is it!
Capsule Corporation's
Doom's Day Transport!
Yes! Rise, my masterpiece!
A fitting gift for the Tuffles!
The Transport is
clear for take-off!
Baby! I'm at
your service, Master!
Well done!
Excellent! It's perfectly
suited for our needs!
Trunks! What--
Let him go, Pan. Please.
He's my best friend, Gramps!
I know, honey. I know.
What has a bottom at it's top?
Aaah! Krillin!
No! The correct
answer is: A leg!
A leg has a bottom at its top!
[GOKU sputtering]
All right, then!
Question Number Three!
Who always rides in a taxi,
but never pays?
Oh! Vegeta!
Nope! Wrong again!
The answer is: the taxi driver!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
Why can't I fly?
Oh, dear. Flying's
against the rules.
I really should have told him.
He didn't last long at all.
How disappointing.
I should have known better
than to play with a child.
It's just not fun!
[GOKU]
I'm not a child!
[SUGORO gasps]
How is this possible?
This has never happened before!
Are you sure you're alive?
Oh, yeah, I'm sure! Still here!
Then it's my turn!
C'mon, six!
I said six!
Whoo-hoo! Another six!
Your turn, Goku!
Hmm?
Super Challenge!
Player must not cry!
Now what? What's that
supposed to mean?
Why can't I land
on a normal spot?
Oh, boy! Super Challenge!
Goku, if you cry, you die!
If you pass the challenge by
not crying you get to play on!
Great! No more riddles!
What a relief! I like this one!
You do?
Yeah, it's simple!
I never cry! Ever!
Then you should do very well!
Show 'em what you're
made of, Goku!
Woo-hoo!
What are these?
Onions? Eww, Yuk!
Uhhh!
You stinky onions!
You can't make me cry!
I won't let you! I won't!
How can you resist?
This is overwhelming!
Yowza! Now for the second
part of the Super Challenge!
The inner-psyche-slam!
Where have you been?
Chi Chi!
You're sick!
Do you hear me? Sick!
I've had it!
You're always gone!
You never earn a Zeni,
and all you do is train!
Chi Chi! What are
you doing with that?
You know how I hate shots!
Now hold still!
Are those tears I see?
I'm not crying! I'm not crying!
See! Dry as a bone!
Oh, come on! Where'd they go?
Hmm!
Hey! I landed on
the hospitality space!
[SUGORO laughs]
You're not doing
so bad yourself I see!
Go back five spaces!
What?
Advance four spaces!
Go back three!
Move ahead two!
Go back one space!
This is crazy! No matter what
I do I end up on the same spot!
[SUGORO] What? Don't tell me
you're still down on Lava Lane!
Hey! Why are bad things
happening to me, and not to you?
I noticed that!
Just lucky I guess!
Oh, Sugoro! Have you
no shame? Cheating a child!
Goku! Another six!
This is amazing!
Your luck's bound to
run out sometime, Sugoro!
You've been burned! Lose a turn!
[NARRATOR]
As Goku tries to survive
the living board game
of Sugoroku Space,
Baby's plans to populate
the new Tuffle Planet
are well under way!
Prisoners in their own bodies,
the captive souls of Earth
are unable to resist
the Tuffles' mighty grip!
Just look at it, my dear!
Isn't it lovely?
After all those years of
struggling against extinction,
of walking the fine line
between life and oblivion,
the Tuffles have conquered
at last! We are whole again!
And now we will spread until
the entire Universe is ours!
[BABY laughs maniacally]
[NARRATOR]
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next episode
of Dragon Ball GT!