[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
Vegeta's body was shrinking so
Baby decided to abandon ship!
The parasite was
making his escape
and heading deep into space!
But Goku had the evil
Tuffle in his sights!
[SS4 GOKU]
Me... Ha... Me... Ha!
[NARRATOR]
Goku's beam found its mark,
and the threat of Baby
disappeared forever!
Like from a giant
fountain above,
the Sacred Water flowed
down on the Earth and
liberated its people
from the foul hatchlings
nesting in their bodies.
[KRILLIN]
How did I get here?
[NARRATOR]
Free at last, it seemed like
the nightmare was over! But
more danger lay just ahead.
[GOKU]
What? But we brought
the Black Star balls back to
Earth, Mister Popo! Remember?
[NARRATOR] Almost a year
has passed since Baby used
the Black Star Dragon Balls to
wish for the new Tuffle planet.
Now, only two weeks remain
until the Earth explodes!
How can we get the
Dragon Balls in two weeks
when it took us a year before?
There's no way!
[PAN]
If everything went perfectly,
we might be able to get
it done in six months!
But two weeks? It'd take
us that long to get one!
Yeah, you're right. We wouldn't
have a chance, would we?
[PAN]
What are we gonna do, Grandpa?!
We can't just wait to die!
[PAN] I don't like
this! I'm scared!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[WOMAN A] Why are we
having so many earthquakes?
The Earthquakes are
getting bigger and bigger.
[VEGETA] This is all that
degenerate Baby's fault!
First he steals my
body and now this!
If he wasn't dead already,
I'd do the honors myself!
We need a plan!
[HERCULE whimpering]
I'm too young to die!
Gramps!
[TRUNKS] Goku! Our
communications network
is back on-line! We can talk
to the Tuffle Planet now!
Great!
Alright!
Hello! Are you just gonna
leave us up here or what?!
Hi, Bulma. You're
back to normal I see.
You all have a lot of explaining
to do! What's going on?
How did this planet get here?
[GOHAN]
Excuse me.
We've treated everyone here
with the Sacred Water, Dad,
and they're all back to normal!
You can send a ship up now,
we're ready for transport!
I wish I could, but I can't.
[CHI CHI]
How dare you!
Move it Gohan.
Goku! You're plotting something!
You don't want us to come back!
No! That's not it
at all! I promise!
[CHI CHI] I'm too old for
you now, is that it?
You've found a pretty young
girl your age, haven't you?
Chi Chi, you know
that's not true.
I just don't want you
coming back to Earth
because it's going to
blow up in two weeks.
What do you mean?
You brought the Dragon Balls
back to Earth a long time ago!
Yes that's true, but
Baby used them again.
And that was almost a whole
year ago. So, we failed.
What are we gonna do?
[VEGETA]
I can answer that! It's simple!
We migrate to planet Tuffle!
Of course!
We can just use Baby's base
of operations as our refuge!
Yeah, but how can we move
them all in two weeks?
[VEGETA] Kakarot, are you able
to do the Instant Transmission
in your current state?
No, but if I transform,
it'll be a cinch!
Super Saiyan Four will do it!
Super Saiyan Four
will do it, huh?
Go ahead Kakarot,
rub it in why don't you!
And Trunks, we'll need you too.
Can you get the big ship
fired up and ready to go?
Sure! No problem!
Okay Kakarot, that's our plan.
[VEGETA] We'll take as many
as we can on the spaceship,
but your going to have
to transport the rest.
Wow, Vegeta! You're
on a roll! Big time!
In the old days,
we got used to moving
from planet to planet
in large numbers!
Came with the trade!
[GOKU]
Even with Instant Transmission,
I won't be able to move all
of those people in time!
Can you help us, Kibito Kai?
[KIBITO]
I'd be happy to, Goku.
I think we're forgetting
about one thing though,
the people themselves.
They're skeptical. It will be
hard to convince them to leave.
You're right.
No one's going to believe that
the Earth is going to
blow up in two weeks.
That sounds crazy.
Yep. It's going to be pretty
hard for them to swallow.
[GOKU] Yeah, remember
when Vegeta asked them
to give me their
energy to beat Buu?
They wouldn't listen to
anyone but Mr. Satan!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL]
Yes! That's it!
[HERCULE]
Me? Okay, I'll try.
In less than two weeks,
the Earth will no
longer be here!
It will be destroyed by
a cataclysmic explosion!
[MAN A]
How could that be possible?
[MAN B]
That's a bunch of bologna!
Some of you don't
believe what I'm saying!
And that's understandable!
But the Earth is
going to blow up
whether you believe it
or not! It can't be helped!
[TRUNKS] Look at that. They
flock to him like little sheep.
They all look up to him!
Ever since he defeated
Cell, they just love him!
Goku, don't tell me
you believe that story
about him beating Cell, too!
Gramps could be such a
great man... if he didn't lie.
[HERCULE]
Starting right now,
I will be offering
transportation
to anyone who wants to take it.
To the planet that you
see above us in the sky!
My helpers will be wearing
badges like this one!
Please listen to them!
They will lead you and your
children to safe passage!
Gosh! What do you think?
Mr. Satan wouldn't steer us
wrong. I'm doing what he says.
[MOB screaming]
[WOMAN B]
Save us, Mr. Satan!
Awesome! The Champ is
totally on top of it!
Yeah! What a guy!
[MOB]
All right! Yeah!
We love you, Mr. Satan!
[HERCULE]
I am the greatest.
[PAN]
I don't know how he does it.
[GOKU laughing]
[MOB cheering]
[FATHER]
Come on!
[SON]
Where are we going, Dad?
[FATHER]
We're taking a little vacation!
[HERCULE]
Yeah!
Here you go! Here's your badge!
[VEGETA]
Yeah, right.
[GOTEN]
They come in different colors!
Now everyone, grab
your neighbor's hand!
You'll have to grab someone
else's. Mine are taken.
If you get left behind, make
sure you bring the luggage!
You two have some nerve!
I get more respect
from total strangers!
Kibito Kai, we're all set.
Great! Hold on tight!
Alright! Are we ready?!
[MOB cheering]
Thanks for having faith
in me, your highness!
[HERCULE]
I promise, you won't regret it!
Mmmm!
[GOTEN]
This is not the time
to be playing video games,
you guys! Don't you get it?
Look, the Earth is
really going to explode!
If you stay here,
you're all going to die!
No dice! Not dying!
You're the only one
in danger of dying here!
[ALL groaning]
[PUNK 7 groaning]
Put 'em in with the luggage!
[GOTEN laughing]
[DANNY'S FATHER] Alright,
ya little yobbos! Get moving!
You're all gonna
be space piggies!
[DANNY'S MOTHER]
Oh, no you don't!
Danny! Get over here
and tend to these hogs!
[DANNY laughing]
I'm being attacked, Mum!
[SS4 GOKU] Hi, everyone!
It's nice to see you again!
If you'll all join hands,
this will just take a second!
Here we go!
[BULMA] Ladies and Gentlemen,
another wave of ships
is approaching! If you are still
missing family members,
please report to
the docking bay!
[REPORTER]
The emergency evacuation
of the doomed planet Earth
continues across the globe!
Millions have made the
journey to planet Tuffle,
but many more still remain
unsure of their fate,
or the lives of
their loved ones.
[PEOPLE yelling]
[PAN]
Please! Remain calm!
[SS4 GOKU] It's not easy
being the little guy, is it?
There you go! Yeah! That's it!
Keep it coming, guys!
Huh?
[SS4 GOKU]
Well, well, well!
What are we going
to do with you two?
Alright! You win!
First class it is!
Wait! Don't leave us! Please!
Hurry up! Let's go!
[PAN] Forget what I said
about remaining calm.
We really need to get a move on!
Hey! Get the led out, people!
What are you doing?
[GOTEN] Me? I'm loading up
the pigs! Give me a hand!
[DANNY laughing]
[WOOFER yipping]
Oy! Woofer! Come back!
Where are you going?
Has everyone made it?
Four more left!
This is going to be close!
[TRUNKS] Goku! Climb aboard!
We're out of time!
[SS4 GOKU] You go ahead!
We've got a few stragglers!
I'll catch up!
Hurry up! We're leaving
with or without you!
No worries!
[DRUNK MAN groaning]
[COUPLE yelping]
Hi, everyone! Do you
have room for two more?
We did it, Grandpa!
Thanks to you!
Your the greatest!
[DANNY'S MOTHER] Stay still
or I'll lose my place! 16, 17.
Well I'll be, all here.
[BOTH sigh]
[BOTH]
Danny!
Woofer, where'd they go?
They wouldn't have just
left us, would they?
[DANNY yelping]
[WOOFER yipping]
[DANNY]
Help me!
Hello! Little boy,
are you out there?
[VOICE]
Over here!
[SS4 GOKU gasping]
Piccolo, it's you!
But why are you still here?
[PICCOLO]
Just enjoying the solitude!
And looking out for stragglers
like this little guy!
That's just like you.
But we'd better get going.
There's no time left.
She's gonna blow.
What happened?
Goku?
It's not working, Piccolo.
My tank's empty.
I'm all out of energy.
Man, some rescue, huh?
Now we're stuck here.
I'm sorry, Piccolo. I failed.
[PICCOLO] I hear what you're
saying, but I don't believe it!
How could you fail? You're Goku!
You can do anything.
But Piccolo.
[PICCOLO]
But nothing!
You can do it, Goku!
Believe in yourself!
[GOKU yells]
Danny!
[DANNY]
Mommy! Daddy!
[WOOFER yipping]
[BOTH sobbing]
How sweet.
[GOKU laughing]
We did it, Piccolo!
[GOKU]
No! Piccolo!
[PICCOLO]
Gohan, can you hear me?
Is that you, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO]
Yes, it's me. I'm still here.
I have a bit of a
situation on my hands.
[GOHAN] Don't tell me
you're still on Earth!
The last ship already took off!
[PICCOLO] Yes, I know.
I was helping someone out
when it left.
What? Call my dad!
He can come and get you!
[PICCOLO]
Your dad's out of energy, Gohan.
I could call Lord Kai, but I've
decided to ride this one out.
The Black Star Balls
are too dangerous.
Look what they're
doing to the Earth.
If I die they'll turn to stone,
and this will
never happen again.
I don't want you to die!
It's okay, Gohan.
I know now that it was
meant to be this way.
Sometimes we have to look beyond
what we want and do what's best.
But Piccolo?
Come now, it's all right.
This is the path
that I've chosen.
Let's talk about something
else. Like how you've matured.
[PICCOLO] You've become a
truly great warrior, Gohan
and yet you've remained humble.
You've shown me
that power is nothing
if not guided by love.
Watching you grow has
helped me grow, Gohan.
That's why I'm here.
[PICCOLO]
It's begun.
Goodbye, my friend!
[PICCOLO yelling]
[ALL gasping, yelling]
Oh, no! Piccolo!
Piccolo, don't leave us!
Piccolo!
[NARRATOR]
Soon after Piccolo's passing,
a wish was made to Porunga,
which restored the Earth to its
rightful place in the heavens.
[BULMA]
I can't believe
out of all the pretty young
girls on this planet,
Baby picked me to be his Queen!
Gosh, it's flattering
when you think about it!
[PAN] I finished, Grandma!
What do you want me to do now?
[BULMA] Well, it looks
like some big shot
from corporate headquarters
is coming to our party.
[DRIVER]
Shall I wait here for you, sir?
No, that will be all.
Hey, Pan!
Trunks? Is that you?
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
Giru!
[GIRU]
Pan!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Giru missed Pan! Giru
loves Pan very, very much!
I missed you so much, Giru!
[GOKU laughing]
Well, how's it been having
a child for a husband?
Oh, the same.
Even when Goku was an adult
it was still like living
with a little child.
[GOKU]
Gohan?
I miss him, Dad.
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Gohan! Hey! We're here!
[ROSHI]
Let's party!
[GOKU] Hi, everyone!
Come on in! Let's eat!
[NARRATOR] At last it was
a time for celebration!
Baby's nightmarish reign had
all but faded from memory,
and things on Earth were
back to normal once again!
Or were they?