[NARRATOR] On the last GT,
Omega Shenron revealed
that he had the powers
of all the Shadow Dragons
at his disposal!
Finding himself outmatched,
Goku was forced to resort
to desperate measures.
Let go, you coward!
No! Dad's converting
his life force into energy!
He's making a bomb
out of his body!
At Vegeta's behest,
Goku abandoned his plan.
The Saiyan Prince had
something different in mind.
Using Blutz Waves
as a catalyst,
Vegeta intended to transform,
first into a giant ape,
then into a Super Saiyan 4,
the summit of Saiyan power!
Although he found success,
two Super Saiyan 4's
wouldn't be enough!
Goku was still preparing
to die for the cause!
You know I wouldn't
suggest joining bodies
with you unless it
was our only hope.
Witness the ultimate
Saiyan fusion today on GT!
Did I hear Vegeta say Fusion?
Yeah, but will it work?
Sure! Why not?
Trunks and I were able to
do it as Super Saiyan 3's!
What's the difference?
Yes, of course.
What a great idea!
Father!
Whoa! Hey!
What's all the fuss about?
What in the world is fusion?
Well, here goes!
Let's do it!
Before he decides to attack!
Mmm!
Whatever they're planning,
it won't work.
I'll make sure of that!
Father! Goku! What are
you two waiting for?
Go for it!
And just what were
you planning to do?
Keep your dirty hands
off of my son, you bully!
Mother!
How dare you!
Shooting a defenseless lady!
If I could fly I'd come up there
and show you a thing or two!
Gohan! Goten!
Goten! This is it!
This is our last chance!
If he stops them from
doing Fusion, we're history!
I'll do whatever it takes!
Will somebody please
tell me what Fusion is?!
Gohan! That's it!
You annoying little pests!
What's going on through
that head of yours?
Kakarot! Are we going
to use Fusion or not?!
Have you lost your mind?!
What are you doing?!
Just soaking it all in.
This is great.
Watching our sons
fight together.
It doesn't get any
better than this.
Yeah, great. Come on.
This going to be special.
I can feel it.
Oh, no you don't!
Sorry! No Dragons allowed!
[TRUNKS yells]
Get out of my way!
Fu... sion!
Fusion...
--HA!
What's this?!
Huh?
Where are the other two?!
The Saiyans? They're here.
I am they. We are one.
Unfortunately for you, Omega.
Wow! He never
even touched him!
How awesome!
Grandpa and Vegeta have joined
their bodies like Siamese Twins!
Not exactly.
They're not two separate beings
that are attached together.
They're one being.
That's what Fusion is, Pan!
Two beings become one!
That is so cool!
I'd like to give
it a shot myself.
The Fusion I mean.
I wanna give it a shot.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I'd like to try it too someday.
Not someday, I mean right now
if one of you guys is up for it.
What do you say, guys?
We could help your dads
with that kind of power!
Well, how about it, Gohan?
Trunks! What about you?
Sorry, it wouldn't work.
To do Fusion you have to have
the exact same power levels.
You need to let
your body heal first.
Stupid fools!
Now I can kill
you both at once!
Heh. Three hard punches, and
all you've got is a bloody nose.
I have to admit, I'm impressed.
You stupid monkey.
What do you mean three?
I'll slow 'em down so you
can count 'em this time.
You shouldn't be
able to do that!
They're taking control!
It's too good to be true!
What did you expect?
Nobody can mess
with our husbands
when they work together!
Go, Grandpa! Go, Vegeta!
Let him have it! Yeah!
[OMEGA thinks]
How could this be happening?
I am Omega Shenron,
the all-powerful dragon!
Now it's your turn!
I guess it was still your turn.
Hello? Are you napping?
'Cause I could have sworn you
said something about hitting me!
Shut up!
Who do you think you are?!
You may have
increased your power,
but it's not enough to overcome
the power of the Shadow Dragons!
[GOGETA growls]
[OMEGA yells]
Father! No!
Grandpa!
[OMEGA laughs]
That's power!
Beautiful!
I don't care who he is,
but hits like that'll
cause serious damage!
[GOGETA grimaces]
Feeling a little
bit sore, are we?
Not really!
Actually your little
treatment took care of a crick
in my neck that's
been bothering me!
[OMEGA growls]
I hate you.
Hey Dragon. I hope this
isn't too much to ask,
but could you do
my back side now?
Rrrrgh! Cocky little chimp!
How dare you make
light of Omega Shenron!
[OMEGA growls]
I've had enough.
It's time to unleash my
most devastating attack!
[OMEGA grimaces]
[OMEGA gasps]
Not even you can
survive this one, Omega!
It has enough power to
extinguish every cell
in your body.
Haaaaaa!!
[OMEGA whimpers]
[GOGETA taunts]
[GOGETA laughs]
[OMEGA]
Why you...!
[OMEGA growls]
[GOGETA laughs]
I crack myself up!
[OMEGA growls]
I've had enough!
You have?!
Nobody makes a
mockery out of me!
I have the power to
destroy you now, Omega,
but there's something
you can do to avoid that.
What is it?
Promise never to
hurt anyone again!
You're insane!
There's only one promise
I'm going to make!
On my honor, I promise to kill
you at all costs! Aaaah!!
[HERCULE]
Somebody! Please...
...do something!
He's pulling it
inside his body!
No! He's condensing it!
This is the sum of all
history's dark deeds!
Humanity itself
has given me life
and armed me with this power,
and I intend to use it!
Negative Karma Ball!
Trunks! Goten! Let's move!
It's no use.
There's no point in running.
If that blast hits, the entire
planet will be ripped apart.
We'll all die anyway.
Ancestor! You're not
going to believe this!
There's been a
change in the Earth!
You've got to see this!
I'm like Goku.
I don't like to work on
an empty stomach, you see.
Not yet! You'll ruin it!
You'll have to wait!
Show some restraint, Ancestor!
Watch the crystal ball!
The negative energy enveloping
the Earth has been lifted!
It's gone!
Oh...
Do you notice anything
different, Omega Shenron?
Does the world seem a
little brighter to you?
Brighter? What do you mean?
Before I kicked your Negative
Karma Ball into outer space,
I changed it.
When I made contact
with the Ball,
I flooded it with
my own life force
and transformed the negative
energy into positive energy.
When I kicked it away,
it was no longer your weapon.
It was my weapon!
You! You're despicable!
Are you saying that you
changed the Karma Ball
into positive energy and
used my own weapon to destroy
the negative energy that
was covering the Earth?!
Hey! Check out
the big brain on Omega!
I couldn't have said
it better myself!
Rrrrgh! Why you...
There's only one
thing left undone!
Big Bang Kamehameha!!
[OMEGA yells]
[GOGETA grunts]
The Dragon Balls!
They did it, yeah!
Thank goodness!
No! Please! Not again!
I haven't dropped
dead yet, Saiyan!
Omega lives on!
That was an impressive feat!
But your power's been
severely crippled!
One more blast like that
and you're history and
you know it, dragon!
Big Bang...
Ka... Me... Ha...
I'm me! We're us again!
Surely a half an hour hasn't
passed yet, has it?!
No! It's been ten minutes!
Fifteen minutes at the most!
What the heck happened,
Kakarot?!
Uh...
Oh, hey!
I know!
Since we're at Super Saiyan 4
we use a lot more power,
which means the length of time
we stay fused is shortened!
See! It all makes sense!
I knew there was an explanation!
You idiotic fool!
Shouldn't we have known
about that beforehand?!
Hey! It's not my fault!
I can't have
all the answers!
Darn! We were there!
Just one more blast!
[OMEGA laughs]
Too bad, you had me!
But fate has turned
the tables once again!
Now it's your turn
to face the terror!
Don't be so sure!
Look at you!
You're hardly even
worth my time!
In your current state, I can
defeat you all by myself!
You both presume too much!
Shadow Dragons' Power...
...Unite!
Yes! That's it!
That's mine!
I like to keep
the four star ball
to remind me of my grandfather!
I won't let you
have this one, dragon!