[EIS] I'll give you anything.
Don't hurt me!
And now,
I'll finish him!
No!
I'll finish it!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball GT...
Taking away my
sight still leaves me
with four very sharp senses.
[NARRATOR] After being
blinded by Eis Shenron,
Goku struck back
and put an end
to the devious dragon's
plans of domination.
But no matter what he tried,
his eyesight would not return.
[NUOVA] I will not challenge
you again until you can see.
Seek me out then.
[NARRATOR] But when it seemed
Goku was safe for the moment,
a new evil made
his presence known.
Nuova!
It's a pitiful dragon that
gives allowances to a monkey.
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Ha!
[SYN] You certainly
did it all right, Goku,
but none of it
seemed to hurt me.
What you're
learning right now,
is that you are simply
not strong enough.
Something's wrong...
[NARRATOR] As Goku's
confusion swells, Syn Shenron,
the final Shadow Dragon,
is confident in his ability
to strip victory away
while Goku is at
his most vulnerable.
Will Goku be able to
triumph in this final hour?
Find out today on
Dragon Ball GT!
It's too bad...
But the comfort
you've always felt
at being called the strongest
fighter in the galaxy
will come to an end today.
No more will the word "Saiyan"
mean anything but failure.
[SYN laughs]
[GOKU grimaces]
Too much time and energy
has been wasted on you
to bother with anymore.
Good-bye, Goku.
[GOKU's heart beating slowly]
[GOTEN]
Father!
[SYN] Ah, the
reinforcements are here.
That's a pretty harsh way
to rescue someone, Majuub.
But thanks!
Sorry, Goten. I didn't
have time to think it out.
Goten and Majuub...?
Well, here I am rushing
to save the day...
And it turns out Majuub seems to
have everything under control.
But still, you made
the effort to be here.
Hey Dad, are you
gonna be okay?
Gohan? And Trunks too?
You all came?
Papa! You're here!
Pan, don't bother them now.
[HERCULE]
They got work to do.
Can't I hug my own dad?
Mama, what are you doing here?
We came to watch Goku fight and
to help him out if he needs it.
We figured that the world has
to have gone completely mad
if the Dragon Balls
have turned against us.
And if that's the case,
I'm gonna spend every
second with my family
and support them
as best I can.
We're behind you every
step of the way, Goku.
Now go make things right!
You're all here so
we can fight together.
I appreciate it,
but understand...
Even if we attack
him as a group,
he's still too powerful.
Yeah, we know that.
Huh?
You always taught me that
a great fighter knows the odds,
and the odds here are that even
if we all fight as a unit,
we still don't stand a
chance of beating him.
But, you're here.
We are, but you're the only
one who can beat this guy, Dad.
Come on, you can't tell
me you're not used
to hearing that
one by now.
We came here so you could
use all of our strengths.
You have to borrow
our Saiyan powers.
Thank you, guys.
[SYN laughs]
[SYN]
And the cavalry arrives
muttering nonsense
to their hero.
Have any of you taken a look
at that decrepit creature?
Does he really look like
the savior of Earth?
Do you actually think
that lending him your
strength will help?
I sure do.
My father was the galaxy's
greatest fighter,
and he was doing it long
before you were even born.
You're history.
You know, we're all here
because we believe in you.
You can do this, father.
Well, I'm not a Shenron,
so I can't make you guys
any guarantees about this,
but I promise I'll do my best.
And if I'm going
to stick to that,
I'll have to take the
absolute maximum power
you guys can give me.
[GOKU grimaces]
Well, well...
What a hero!
As interesting as it
would be to fight you
with your newfound
strength intact.
I think I've already given
you and your buddies
enough time to recover.
Look out!
[ALL yell in surprise]
[SYN growls]
Trunks, no!
[SYN]
There go your friends...
I have to say,
I'm not very impressed with
the way they don't fight back.
So, Goku... You ready?
Gohan!
Papa!
[GOHAN whimpers]
It's strange, you Super
Saiyans aren't that super...
How disappointing!
Gohan, hold on!
Stay back!
I've come to
kill all of you
and yet you stand
together in a bunch...
You're making this too easy!
I took out four Saiyans
with one blast...
How many will it
take for you, Goku?
I don't think I've ever seen you
move that quickly before, Dad.
The little bit of power
I absorbed from you earlier
really helped my
instant transmission.
Wow, Syn! I never thought
I'd see you look so confused.
I guess your confidence
is melting away.
Hardly, I know you're bluffing.
You've only gathered
just enough power
to make it look like
you're ready to fight.
Then what do you
say we find out?
[GOKU yells]
Dad, your power
is amazing!
Yeah, but I still need
you guys to give me more.
This won't be
enough to beat him.
That's crazy, Dad...
If you had any more
power inside your body,
it might just kill you.
I've gotta take that chance.
I already know that none
of my earlier attacks
have worked at all,
so I'm going to
have to find a way
to fight this dragon
as a stronger being.
And the only way
I can think of to do that
is to take even more
power from all of you
and push my physical self
to its absolute limit.
I say we do it.
It certainly wouldn't
be the first time
he's had to push himself
into doing something crazy.
It'll be the last.
Just hold it right
there for one second...
[GOHAN, TRUNKS,
and GOTEN yelling]
[GOKU grimaces]
Dad, this is
getting dangerous!
It's... it's all right!
No! You can't!
Listen to me.
If you don't give me your full
power we're all going to die!
[SYN] Power-up time
is over, boys.
It's time to finish the game.
I'll take on all of
you, and still win.
You'll only fight one of us,
because after what
I've got for you,
I make you one promise...
You won't be able
to tell up from down!
Not only can I still
tell up from down,
but I'm lucid enough to notice
that you're starting to sweat.
I sense your fear!
You stupid insect.
Waste of my time, let's go!
Great, you again!
I'm giving you all
the time I can.
Come on, Goku, power up!
[yelling]
[growling]
Die!
I'm sorry, Goku, I failed.
Have a nice landing.
That was the weakest first line
of defense I've ever seen.
Which one of you is up next?
[GOKU roars]
[SYN gasps]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU roars]
Unbelievable...
What's going on?
With the extra energy Goku's
new Super Saiyan 4 power level
has skyrocketed past
his earlier level!
Now, this is the kind of power
I'd be running
away from... if I were you.
Ha, a terrible bluff...
You look exactly
as you did earlier.
Why don't we try fighting?
You can come over
and see for yourself.
My pleasure!
What do you think?
That's it!
It's useless...
Even though I'm blind
my body compensates
for it in amazing ways.
I can feel every
one of your moves
before you even make them.
We'll see.
[GOKU]
I told you it was useless.
No you don't!
Syn, these times were
dark enough without you.
It's time you went away.
I can outrun this!
No matter where you go,
I'll always be able
to seek out your evil
like a bird senses its prey.
[clock chiming]
[SYN laughs]
This is where your blindness is
going to work to my advantage.
Can you sense the
evil of this clock?
No, because it has no
evil for you to sense.
So I bet you can't
see what happens next.
That's a little childish.
Tear him apart!
[GOKU grimaces]
Sorry, Syn.
It was a good theory.
But I can see everything
just as if my eyes worked.
But that's impossible.
Now Syn, please
apologize to Nuova...
...when you see him!
Ka... Me...
Ha...
Me...
Ha!
He did it!
That's my man!
--All right!
--Nice one.
[ALL cheering]
[CHICHI] Goku, you
did an excellent job.
You've made your
wife very proud.
[GOHAN] You've made
us all proud, Dad.
[GOKU]
Well, I certainly couldn't have
done it without you guys.
Quit being so modest Grandpa!
Like I haven't been hit enough.
[EVERYONE laughs]
But what ever happened
to the Dragon Balls?
They were scattered again,
but only around here.
If we look we should find them.
What do you know, our luck
is finally returning!
You're not getting away
from me that easily.
Wait! That doesn't seem right.
I thought you were dead.
How could you hold
up against that?
I move as fast as you, Goku,
but I'm disappointed in myself
for underestimating
your skill...
A mistake that I do not
intend on making again.
If you want this,
then come and get it!
He ate it!
How could he just eat
the Dragon Ball?!
He's gonna eat 'em all!
Now, look at me!
Do you see?
This is my true form!
The form I use to stand at
the pinnacle of dragon power!
[SYN yelling]
No! He's got all of
the Dragon Balls!
His power's unreal!
I don't think we've ever faced
anyone this strong before.
Behold! The body of
Syn Shenron has absorbed
the abilities of all six
of the Shadow Dragons
to create a dragon of one body
that fights with
the power of seven.
What? All seven
of you are one?!
[NARRATOR]
After the bizarre technique
of swallowing the
other six Dragon Balls,
Syn Shenron is no more.
He stands reborn
as Omega Shenron,
with the abilities of
all of the Shadow Dragons.
If Syn was unstoppable,
how will Goku survive this new,
even more powerful threat?
Find out on the next GT!