[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
Goku, Trunks, and Pan
were attacked by a swarm
of carnivorous Mouma,
the only native life found
on the Asteroid Beehey!
But the giant beasts proved to
be no match for these Saiyans.
Soon thereafter they encountered
the Para Para Brothers,
whose extremely bizarre
"dance and attack" strategy
only worked for a short time.
Pan and Giru tried
to locate the Dragon Ball
hidden on the Para Para ship.
Not only were
they unsuccessful,
they were trapped on board
and launched
into unknown territory!
[PAN] Giru, can you
read this language?
[GIRU] Destination: Planet Luud.
Departure: Imminent.
Launch sequence initiated.
Will Goku and Trunks
regroup in time
to track them down
and save them?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball GT!
Atmosphere re-entry
process complete.
Now deactivating heat shields.
Caution: Restoring gravity
control in 3, 2, 1...
Giru. Giru. Giru head hurt!
Why didn't you tell me the
gravity was coming back on?!
Giru. Giru.
You're impossible.
Oh, no... This is
not a good situation.
We're in the wrong place
and nowhere near Grandpa.
Alright...
Giru.
Look, we both know
we don't get along.
So why don't we just put
aside our differences...
...and work as a team!
Pan. Pan. Danger! Danger!
"Danger-Danger"?
I'll show you danger!
"Danger" is what happens
to stupid little robots
who don't do what I tell them to
do, when I tell them to do it!
I'm all you've got out here,
buster, so you better shape up!
Got it?!
Of all the people to
get stranded with, why him?
Calm giru. Giru calm.
I don't understand
any of this...
It's just a bunch of
switches, lights and knobs...
Who am I kidding?
There's no way I'll be able
to fly this ship out of here!
Giru!
You sit right here, Giru...
Since you're a robot and all,
I figure you'll know
much more than I do
about how to pilot
this behemoth.
Giru... Doesn't know.
Don't give me that baloney!
You could at least try to look
at the controls and help out...
Either that, or I pound
you into scrap metal!
Searching.... Button identified!
Really?
That's the right button?
See! That wasn't so hard
now, was it, Giru?!
We're outta here!
Wrong button. Giru...
Boy... I hope Pan's okay...
Wherever she is.
Yeah... Me too.
Alright guys, listen up!
Tell me where your
spaceship went, right now!
I... I wish I knew!
Don't lie to me!
Okay, guys... Get ready.
Let's do this in E minor.
Aawww... Yeah!
One... two...
One two three four...
Don't think you can
deceive us like that again!
Now tell me!
Where did Pan go?!
One two. One two.
I just don't know.
I just don't know anything about
setting the ship's auto-pilot
to return straight back
to our home Planet Luud.
Son Para!
Here we go!
This looks like a door!
Giru giru giru!
What did I do to deserve this?
Giru! Why are you always
causing trouble?! Ya jerk!
Giru Giru.
Where are we, Giru?
Unknown... Location unknown.
Consuming now.
Helpful as always, Giru!
These ships look like
the one we were in....
Of course! This must be where
the Para Para Brothers are from!
Don't do that, Giru...
You almost scared me!
Discovery! Discovery!
Dragon Ball located!
What did you just say?!
Yeah, you're right.
There really is a Dragon Ball...
But I wonder what it's
doing all the way out here.
Duh! It makes total sense!
It's the Dragon Ball the
Para Para Brothers stole!
Of course...
They must have dropped
off the Dragon Ball here
before they went to Beehey!
That explains why
you and I couldn't find it
anywhere on
their ship... So...
According to this right here,
the Dragon Ball should be...
...down this way.
What is that?
Looks like a shrine or something
Danger!
What's wrong with you, Giru?
You've been acting up all day!
No! Danger! No!
Danger! Danger!
Danger!
Gee, for a shrine... this place
is a tad on the ugly side.
What do you
think you're doing?!
Fine... I'm going
after the Dragon Ball!
What? You're gonna let
a little girl like me
walk into certain
doom all by myself?
Danger! Danger!
How can you be so sure
there's danger in there?!
You haven't even been inside!
Danger! Danger! Danger! Danger!
Danger! Danger! Danger! Da-
Great! So tell me what it
is I need to watch for!
Danger! Caution! Caution!
Shut up, Giru! I can't
take it anymore...
I'll just have to find
it without your help!
Pan?
Danger, Pan! Danger! Danger!
Enyaka Yakayaka
Luud Rama Lama Sama...
What are those voices?
Enyaka Yakayaka
Luud Rama Lama Sama...
Looks like the door is locked.
Not scared, Pan... Not scared!
Now, my faithful believers...
The rebirth of our savior,
Lord Luud, is at hand.
You all must give
him your strength,
for it will be the source of
power in his resurrection!
Okay... Now I'm scared!
It's our Dragon Ball!
Not so fast, kid!
You're not goin' anywhere!
Well, we're here.
So this is Planet Luud, huh?
There's something eerie
about this place.
Come on, let's go guys!
Hey! Quit playing
around up there!
You're gonna pull your teeth
straight out of your jaw!
Nice one!
Why'd'ya hafta go
and electrocute us?!
I just hope that the great and
wonderful Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy
hasn't seen us tied up
and crying like this!
Whatever he does to us,
it's gonna hurt so bad!
Giru giru giru giru...
Whoa!
Giru!
So it looks like
you're doing okay!
Pan pan pan pan pan pan!
What about Pan? Is she
in trouble or something?
Pan in danger! Pan in danger!
What's going on here?!
Hey, you! Over here!
You must be the boss!
Didn't your mother
ever teach you
what good manners
are all about?
It's not right to steal
other people's property!
Who would dare to--?
You have no idea how hard I
worked to get this Dragon Ball
from the people
of Planet Gelbo...
And you had
the nerve to take it!
How pathetic for a grown man
having to steal
from a little girl!
Oh, I know who you are.
Why don't you cough up
the other Dragon Ball
you have in your possession
before I start to get angry.
Uh, what Dragon Ball?
I can see through
your lies, little girl!
Now hand over the
four-star Dragon Ball!
Who do you think you are?
I am the famous
Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy.
I serve him, our great Deity
of Destruction, Lord Luud.
He will be resurrected with
the power of his followers
and your precious Dragon Balls!
For when Lord Luud is reborn,
he will destroy
the non-believers
in this unruly Universe,
and we, as his emissaries,
will rule over all!
Now hand over
the Dragon Ball, little girl.
I don't have the slightest clue
what you were just
babbling about!
But I do know that this is
the Dragon Ball I came for,
so I'll be leaving
now... Okay? Bye bye!
Hey! Stop!
You're not going anywhere!
What the--?
That's what you get for
not obeying my orders.
What's wrong with me?
I can't move my arms or
legs! I'm frozen still!
Oh, Grandpa, where are you?!
It looks like this girl didn't
have the Dragon Ball after all.
Oh, well. I'm sure
I can still use her.
Lord Luud, you will enjoy this
little girl's Saiyan power.
Eenyaka-Yaka-yaka--
All right, now I'm
starting to get worried...
I'm still not sensing
Pan's energy anywhere!
Hey, Pan! Where are you?!
Why are you fools all tied up?
Cardinal Mutchy Mutchy!
Have you three
failed me once again?
Uh... You see...
We uh, brought back
the, uhhh, you know...
The Dragon Ball!
We have it here!
So do you expect me to
say you did a good job?
Because you haven't!
What the--?!
Danger! Danger!
Now wait! Those guys
were on your side, right?
So why would you
do that to them?
What do you mean why?
I just did them a favor by
fusing them with Lord Luud.
They'll be of much better
service to him now,
rather than dancing
and prancing around
like a bunch of
show-tune obsessed idiots!
Lord Luud?
The Para Para
Brothers did exactly
what I sent them out to do,
which was to bring
you Saiyans to me.
So if you want to
live to see tomorrow,
you'll give me what I want!
I don't think so!
Now hand over the Dragon
Ball you stole from us!
You're making Lord
Luud very angry,
so give him what he wants!
No way!
You'll never get it!
Oh, is that so?
You leave me no choice.
I'll just pry it from
your cold dead hands!
You wish!
What's that?!
Hey! Why don't
you try fighting fair!
Fair? I don't even know what
that word means, you brat!
You're a quick one, aren't you?!
Goku!
It's gonna take a lot more
than a gun to stop me!
Lord Luud teaches us how to win
a battle by any means necessary.
And that's exactly what
I plan on doing to you!
I won't stop until you're dead!
Giru! Danger ahead! Big danger!
Run away giru!
You both know it's
worthless to fight now!
My Leon here will take care
of you two in no time,
so surrender or die!
Trunks! Grandpa!
It's me, Pan! Help me!
Giru run away! Giru run away!
Giru, I'm over here!
Come save me!
Oh, you better hope I
don't come out of this,
because if I do,
you are going to pay!
Run away! Run.... Giru?
Yes, Giru! It's me! It's Pan!
Signs of life present.
Signs of life present... Pan!
Right! You're right
Giru, it is me!
No!
Major malfunction.
Hey, you all right?
I'm fine... Sorry about being
off guard back there...
W-What?
I must admit that
you two have some skill.
But don't pat yourselves
on the back for taking out
Cardinal Mutchy-Mutchy,
for he's only a part of me!
He... He must have
a cloaking device!
Now that's funny!
Tell you what, I'll save you the
tension and show my true form!
We... should've seen
that one coming!
Yeah, no kidding! What are you?!
You may call me Mutchy...
Lord Luud's right hand man!
The mysterious
Cardinal Mutchy-Mutchy
has revealed his true form.
And this tentacled threat
is all that stands in the way
of recovering the Dragon Balls
and saving Pan from
a fate worse than death!
The plot thickens on
the next Dragon Ball GT!