[NARRATOR]
On the last episode of GT...
Goku decided to take on the
entire Sigma Force by himself!
But, armed with the
data that Giru provided,
the mutant-bots were
forewarned of his every move!
Meanwhile, back at the ship,
Pan awoke to some bad news!
Giru came and took
the Dragon Balls!
No way! That little jerk!
[BIT]
Bizu!
[RIBET]
Ribet!
[NEZI]
Nezi!
[NARRATOR]
When the three became one,
Goku was suddenly
matched with an adversary
that was bigger, stronger,
and faster than before!
[MEGA-NEZI]
Killer Driller Attack!
[NARRATOR]
But when push came to shove,
Goku showed that he had
plenty of reserves left!
Had the young Saiyan
been sandbagging?
[GOKU grunting]
[MEGA-NEZI yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Apparently so.
[MEGA-NEZI] That power!
Explain how you did that!
Your energy tripled just then!
Oh, you think so?
Well, I hate to break
the news to you guys,
but that was just
the tip of the iceberg!
[GOKU grunts]
[MEGA-NEZI]
Curse you!
Okay!
[GOKU, MEGA-NEZI grunting]
[GOKU]
Ha... Me... Ha!
[MEGA-NEZI]
No!
[NARRATOR] But just as
the Sigma Force Cannon
fell into the scrap heap, a new
threat emerged on the horizon!
[TRUNKS] It's coming this way,
Pan! Stay here! Please!
Right! I see! Get 'em Trunks!
[TRUNKS grunting]
What a colossal energy!
And it's closing in fast!
Oh, no! Those Sigma Force guys
must have hurt my Grandpa!
No! Look! Let's not
assume the worst!
Goku can take care of himself!
Get ready, Pan!
It's him!
Huh?
Hey!
Grandpa!
[GOKU]
We're in hot water, Trunks!
Something huge
is on the way!
Right! I think I've been
sensing it for some time now!
[PAN] Grandpa! The
Dragon Balls are gone!
They took them from the ship!
Hm... I figured as much!
That Giru! Every time I think
of him I want to scream!
It's here!
[ALL gasp]
[PAN whimpering]
I'm scared, you guys!
[TRUNKS]
Be strong, Pan!
[RILLDO]
I must say that I'm impressed!
A mere child defeating
my Sigma Force!
If I hadn't watched it with my
own eyes, I wouldn't believe it!
[PAN] Look! You better go
back where you came from
or you're next!
Pan! Not now! Let Grandpa
handle this! He's powerful!
Even more powerful
than Majin Buu!
It's exciting to
think about it!
Don't you think you should take
this a little more seriously?
Focus!
[RILLDO cackles]
[PAN gasps]
[PAN]
That face! I know you!
You're General Rilldo!
That's him, guys!
He gave Giru a medal
for betraying us!
He's the big cheese!
[RILLDO chuckling] I see
my reputation precedes me!
You're right! I am
General Rilldo! It's true!
And I rule here.
It was low of Giru to betray
friends that cared for him!
But it was even lower of
you to order him to do it!
You creep!
Pan! No!
[PAN yelling]
[GOKU, TRUNKS gasp]
[RILLDO groans]
[PAN yells]
That was...
That was, uh, great!
Yeah! Well, uh, she is your
granddaughter all right!
Well! Whatd'ya think?
Not too bad, aye?
I can get the job done!
Maybe you two should stop
treating me like
a child so much!
Ha, ha, ha! I guess so! You're
a lot stronger than I realized!
Now, as for you Mister General
with the stinky attitude!
If you don't want
to suffer anymore,
then I suggest you apologize
and give us back
our Dragon Balls!
And I mean this minute!
[RILLDO]
I'm afraid I can't do that!
[RILLDO grunting]
[RILLDO] You see, the
Dragon Balls don't belong to me!
They belong to Doctor Myuu,
who is their sole proprietor.
They are an integral
part of his grand plan
to conquer the galaxy!
The galaxy? What?
Why would he do that?
[RILLDO] Why did you
decide to start walking
rather than continue to crawl?
And then, why did you
venture into space
rather than continue to walk?
Progress, my little friend!
Natural evolution!
Just as the inferior
beings of this planet
were replaced by
our robot mutants,
so too does forward
progress dictate
that this must happen
throughout the galaxy!
Doctor Myuu is the grand
conductor of this orchestration!
And there is nothing
you can do to stop him!
The strong must flourish
and the weak must perish!
All right! We'll play
by your rules then!
But don't be
surprised if you find
we're not as weak as you think!
[RILLDO] Hmph! An amusing
theory to say the least!
[RILLDO grunting]
[PAN whimpering]
Look out!
[PAN grunts]
[TRUNKS yelling]
[PAN]
Trunks! No!
[PAN] Oh, my gosh!
Trunks! What happened?
He's gone.
You beast! You bring
him back here right now!
[PAN grunting]
Silly nuisance!
[PAN groaning]
[RILLDO cackling]
[RILLDO] Your friend
is being transmitted
as one of Doctor
Myuu's guinea pigs!
Think of it as an honor!
What? What do you mean by that?
Being transmitted?
[GOKU]
I think I understand!
It's something like
Instant Transmission!
But where? Where
did you send him?!
If you must know...
that tower behind me!
[RILLDO] From there he will be
transmitted to Doctor Myuu's lab
where he will be
dissected and studied!
Oh no, he won't! Not as long
as there's breath in this body!
Trunks! Hold on! I'm comin'!
You first! Then I'll take
care of that little brat!
You belong to us!
[GOKU grunting]
[RILLDO yelling]
Woo, boy! One strike
and you're out!
You're fast! But not if
I disable your movements!
The old-fashioned way!
Fine by me! But I think it's
only fair that I warn you first!
[GOKU] I've been trained
in the art of self-defense!
[RILLDO]
So have I, my friend! So have I!
[PAN] It looks a lot bigger up
close! He could be anywhere!
Well, here goes nothing!
[COMPUTER]
Alert! Alert! Security breach!
Intruder! Intruder!
[alarms blaring]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
[RILLDO, GOKU grunting]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU yelling]
[ROBOT LEADER]
Intruder description:
Organic, female, bi-ped!
Seek and destroy!
This must be the
welcoming committee!
[PAN yelling]
[ROBOTS groaning]
[PAN grunting]
[PAN]
Hmph!
[ROBOT 1]
Danger! Danger!
You! Tell me! Where's
my friend being held?
[RILLDO, GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] Are we really
through here, General,
or are you playing possum?
[RILLDO grunting]
Ah... Hey! What in
the world was that?
A flying punch?
Ow! Ow! Come on!
I have many special talents!
In fact, behind you,
there comes another one!
[GOKU yelping]
[RILLDO]
Mm!
[RILLDO cackling]
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU yelling]
[RILLDO groaning]
When our scientists
are done with you,
you're going to make an
extraordinary mutant robot!
[GOKU] You mean they'd turn
me into a robot like Giru?
[RILLDO] Not quite! You'll
probably look a little like me!
[GOKU]
Ew! Thanks, but no thanks!
My wife already has a
problem with the way I am!
If I came home looking like you,
she'd have a heart attack!
[RILLDO yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
[GIRU]
Giru! Begin transmission!
[ROBOT ASSISTANT]
Affirmative T-20-O-6!
Initiating transmission
sequence!
Beginning molecular
destabilization.
[PAN gasping]
How horrible!
[PAN] Oh, no! Please! Not again!
Trunks! Wait! Don't leave me!
One minute too late! I
don't believe it! Trunks!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru!
Oh! It's you!
[GIRU] Pan too late!
Trunks transmit already!
No duh! How could you just
stand there and let it happen?!
[GIRU]
Pan! Alert! Danger! Danger!
For you maybe!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[COMPUTER] Initiating
Coercive Removal System.
Hey! Get back here, you twerp!
[PAN shrieking]
[PAN] Whoa! How bizarre!
I got spit out?
[MYUU cackling]
[MYUU] What a splendid
piece of artwork!
Organic reliefs
are my favorite!
Such expression! Such emotion!
And captured so beautifully!
You can almost feel the
pain and disillusionment
etched on his face!
You pitiful creature!
Smile! Soon, you will
be a mutant like me!
Fool! Your aim
is pathetic! What?
[RILLDO yelling]
[RILLDO screaming]
[RILLDO]
Tricky runt! Where did he go?
[GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Ha!
[RILLDO screaming]
Is it over?
Hm! Nope! I guess
not! Hello, General!
[RILLDO] I'm really starting
to dislike you, kid!
Not bad! You mutants have
some pretty tough skin!
I'm impressed!
It's a shame! You
could do such good!
[RILLDO growling]
I am what I am!
Hey!
[GOKU yelping]
New and improved! And
they're factory inspected!
DNA Replicants!
[GOKU laughing]
Is death funny?
No, it's not! But I have
no intention of dying!
[GOKU yelling]
[RILLDO groaning]
[RILLDO coughing, groaning]
[RILLDO] Your power has
increased 100 fold!
So it's true! I was
right! Shame on you!
You've been bluffing
the whole time!
Holding back your true power!
A deceitful practice!
Yes! It is! So let's stop
playing games with one another!
[GOKU]
Why don't you drop the act
and show me your true power now?
[RILLDO] I see! I never
was good at acting weak!
[RILLDO yelling]
Whoa! Not good! That's
much more than I expected!
[RILLDO yelling]
[RILLDO]
Meta-Rilldo!
[GOKU] Uh, oh! I don't
like the feel of this!
[RILLDO] Heh, heh, heh, heh!
Ah! Yes! What a rush!
I'd almost forgotten what it
feels like! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
It's impossible for
a race like yours
to survive against our
mutant civilization!
Why not? Enlighten me.
You got me interested.
[RILLDO] You can not beat
us because you are a race
of individuals, each with
his own selfish motives.
We live for one purpose alone.
Our energies are focused,
yours are scattered.
We cooperate with one
another. You do not!
Your race is inferior
and it must die!
[RILLDO yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned for
scenes from the next GT!