[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT...
Goku broke free of the ice trap
set for him by Frieza and
Cell in the bowels of Hell.
But knowing that the
ice would only work
on those who were already dead,
Goku quickly turned the
tables on his enemies.
[GOKU] You'd think these guys
would've learned their lesson
after all this time.
We are but one...
[NARRATOR] Despite the
great victory underground,
the surface told
a different story.
The two Android 17s had finally
merged into one perfect being.
And the terror that this
Super Android 17 possessed
would send crippling
blows to the Saiyans
in one of their darkest hours.
[VEGETA]
This one's mine!
[VEGETA groans]
[MAJUUB yelling]
[GOHAN]
Ka, me, ha, me...
...Ha!
[GOTEN]
He did it!
[NARRATOR] Earth's heroes
quickly gathered to face
this new challenge, but the
powerful Super Android 17
shrugged off even
their strongest attacks.
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
It's flattering to see the kind
of show you put on for your
most dangerous enemies,
but ultimately it's meaningless.
Let me show you want I mean.
Flash Bomb!
[GOKU] If things continue
like this up there,
without my help, those guys
will be wiped out in no time.
[PICCOLO]
That's why I'm here.
I came down to
help get you out,
so you can get
back to fighting.
[GOKU] They let you
come all the way to Hell
just so you could help me?
[NARRATOR]  Can Piccolo
help Goku escape in time
to stop Super 17's rampage
before the Earth is destroyed?
[PICCOLO]
The powers of a Nammekian
have many uncharted avenues.
[NARRATOR]
Piccolo's plan is revealed today
on Dragon Ball GT!
Can you really get me
out of here, Piccolo?
I hope you have a plan,
because I know I don't.
Of course I do.
I always have a plan.
Dende, can you hear me?
Dende? What can he do?
[PICCOLO]
Dende!
[DENDE]
What? Did you hear that?
I can hear you loud
and clear, Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] I will be sending
an energy beam from Hell.
Listen to me, Dende.
You'll have to send me
an equal amount of energy.
This is the only
way it'll work.
Do you have any idea
what he's talking about?
It's easy! All we
have to do is send
a highly direct stream
of energy to each other.
[PICCOLO] My understanding
of the situation
is that the two Android 17s
created that giant
hole in the sky,
when they converged their powers
together between the two worlds.
If we can emulate what they did,
we will open up a gate
between Hell and the Lookout,
allowing Goku enough time
to escape back to Earth.
I never thought we'd be
replicating the
tactics of an enemy,
but if it works
then I'm all for it.
Alright Piccolo.
I'm ready when you are.
Hey, I know I'm not an
expert on this or anything,
but are you guys planning
on doing some type of fusion?
Yes, but it's a fusion
of the minds, Goku.
Okay, Dende! Let's begin.
We'll start by
synchronizing our timing.
Ready.
One...
And two...
Three!
Let's kick up the
intensity and try it again!
Ready when you are!
[PICCOLO]
One...
[DENDE]
Two, and three!
It's no good. Our
timing is too far off!
Let's do it once more, Dende!
Well I guess it's gonna
take Piccolo a little longer
to get me out of here
than I had expected.
I just wish there was something
interesting to do down here
so time could pass
a little quicker.
[PICCOLO] Three! Come on,
Dende! It's still not working!
[GOKU] Oh gosh, is there a
restaurant around or something
'cause my stomach is killing me!
If I don't get some food soon,
I'm gonna be in bad shape.
Hey, you guys have
anything to eat down here?
I'm getting really hungry!
[PICCOLO]
No! We almost had it there!
Yeah!
[GOTEN yelling]
[TRUNKS]
Goten!
You're gonna pay
for that, you jerk!
[TRUNKS groaning]
[MAJUUB]
Oh no! Trunks!
You're all pathetic.
Super 17, stop horsing
around and finish the job!
[MAJUUB gasps]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
Hey! Don't underestimate me!
I can't take it. Hurry up
and get back here, Grandpa!
He's making Vegeta look
like a defenseless, child.
Piccolo, haven't you
figured that out yet?
If you don't hurry, there
won't be anyone left to save!
Shut up! Please Goku,
I can't concentrate.
Dende, we need to coordinate
the movements of our hands
and keep them in sync.
Come on, once more.
Now, one, two...
[DENDE]
...three!
What are we doing wrong?
It didn't take long for
these losers to get creamed
and sent back to Hell.
Well, I can't remember
seeing surface walkers fight
with such ferocity
and intelligence.
And don't forget that you are
in line with all those losers.
Well that may be the case,
but at least I wasn't
beaten by a girl.
Greetings.
If you are in line
for the bus to Hell,
please have
your ticket ready.
I'll be up to my neck
in paperwork for weeks.
I can't believe
this is such a mess!
I'm not done with
you yet, android!
[VEGETA yelling]
So, you've decided
to go blonde again.
That's still not going
make a difference.
Enough already!
It's time to show you why
you should fear a Saiyan!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA]
I've got you now!
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA groaning]
Oh man! Come on, Vegeta!
You've just got to hold him
off a little bit longer.
[GOBLIN A]
Ah, excuse me, sir.
I brought you your meal, sir,
and please be careful. It's hot.
[GOKU]
That's fantastic!
I can't believe how good
the service is here.
It smells great! What is
it, soup or something?
[GOKU yelping]
Shut up!
[PICCOLO] How can you expect me
to get you out of here, Goku,
if you keep on making
such a loud racket!
I'm sorry Piccolo, but a
bunch of tiny little skulls
jumped out of my soup!
[PICCOLO growling]
Uh, I'm really sorry I
broke your concentration.
I won't let it happen again.
[DENDE]
Piccolo! Let's keep this going!
I'm starting to get
the hang of it,
so let's not waste any time!
Good thinking.
[GOKU sighs]
[stomach growling]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO]
One... Two!
[DENDE]
Three!
We came so close that time!
The timing!
We just need to be
more precise than that,
but we're very close Dende.
Keep focusing and we'll get it.
[GOKU]
Hey, Piccolo.
What is it?
Why don't you try using a chant
to get your timing correct?
It worked for me
and Pan one time.
What do you mean, a chant?
Like... Pepper pot!
Pickle pot! Purple pot!
[PICCOLO]
You are an idiot!
[GOKU] Wait, I'm being
serious here. Trust me.
It may sound silly,
but it's been proven to work
very well in the past.
Dende, you get that?
Yes. Ready when you are.
Pepper pot!
Pickle pot!
[PICCOLO] Purple pot!
[DENDE] Purple pot!
[BOTH yelling]
Okay, Dende! Continue
holding the energy beam,
and slowly spread
your arms apart
so we can expand the
opening and lock it into place.
Right!
Dende, hold it together.
You've got to keep it open!
[GOKU] Alright! It looks
like it's working!
[PICCOLO]
Dende, excellent job.
[GOKU] Thank you, Piccolo.
I owe you big for this!
What are you waiting for?
Aren't you coming, too?
Trust me, I'd love
to come with you.
But unfortunately, I can't move
any of my muscles even an inch.
If I move my arms
in any direction,
the hole will close up
and we'll both be stuck.
I won't be able to hold
it open much longer.
So, you're gonna have to
stay in Hell for good?
That's okay, it was part of
the plan from the beginning.
It's no big deal.
[PICCOLO groaning]
[DENDE groaning]
Quick! Hurry up, Goku!
I can't hold it much longer!
[PICCOLO] Come on Goku,
get out of here. Now!
Okay I'm going,
but I will pay you back
for this. I promise.
Thanks, just get going!
[GOKU] I can't thank you enough,
Piccolo! I'll see you soon.
[GOKU]
Thanks Dende!
[PICCOLO sighs]
[ASSISTANT BLACK] Hey guys, look
who decided pay us a visit!
[NAPPA] What the heck does he
think he's doing down here?
Well, as long as I'm
stuck in this dump,
I might as well get
in some target practice.
[VEGETA groaning]
Oh Gramps, I can't
watch this anymore!
Let go of me!
I can take him! I know I can!
Listen to what you're
saying, Pan! It's crazy!
You know you don't stand a
chance against him by yourself!
[DR. MYUU]
Who would have thought that
the Prince of all Saiyans would
fight like such an amateur!
It's downright
embarrassing to watch!
[VEGETA groaning]
Now then, it's time
to end this comedy show!
Put the fool to sleep
for good, my loyal android.
It feels like he
paralyzed my body.
What is wrong with me today?
Surely I have more
power left than this!
[DR. MYUU] Now, now.
Don't criticize yourself
like that, Vegeta.
You tried your best,
and that's what's important.
[DR. GERO groans]
[PAN]
Tell him to stop that android
from attacking, right now!
Why, you little brat!
I've heard every
word you've said,
including the orders
to kill Vegeta!
Now if you don't tell
Super Android 17 to stand down,
I'll make you wish
you were back in Hell!
[DR. GERO] Stop messing around,
little girl! Why don't you
go find some dolls to play with
before you get yourself hurt!
Come on. Give up before
I really get angry!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru!
[PAN]
That's not a toy, Doctor!
So tell that no good
android to stop!
Okay, I'll do it!
17, halt your attack!
Do not attack Vegeta!
That's an order!
[DR. GERO]
What does he think he's doing?
Don't... don't you dare
do it, 17! I am your maker!
[DR. MYUU cackling]
You actually think
you are in control?
Are you blind?
I re-programmed 17 to
only obey orders from me.
I thought for sure
you would have noticed,
but you're too stupid for that.
What? So you've been
against me the whole time?
Myuu, you dirty traitor!
[DR. MYUU] Your ambition
to conquer the Earth
is inadequate at best.
As long as this Super
Android 17 is around,
conquering the entire galaxy is
not some dream! It's a reality!
17 can no longer
be considered
a simple artificial human
being with immense powers.
He has been reborn by me,
as the Ultimate Machine Mutant!
So you're going to betray
me again, my Number 17?
Wait a minute! He's about
to shoot that at us!
Do it!
[DR. GERO]
No! Not like this!
[HERCULE grunting]
Oh Pan, are you alright?
Please let my
granddaughter be okay!
Tch.
I'll never understand these
Earthlings with their emotions.
Let's clear out the rest of
this planet's threat to us,
even though it is quite small.
I'll start with
this pathetic louse
before he gets a chance
to embarrass himself again.
That's good, and with
Goku out of the picture,
we have nothing to worry about.
You may proceed as planned.
Huh? Did he say Goku?
[VEGETA] How dare
you mention that name
to The Prince of Saiyans!
[VEGETA yelling]
I am the leader and sole
protector of the planet Earth!
And that Kakarot is a clown
who only knows his stomach
and his own stupidity!
I came to do this job, and I'm
not leaving until I finish it!
[DR. MYUU]
You've aged so much, Vegeta.
And the limitations of your
flesh are no match for us!
It disgusts me to listen
to the Prince of Saiyans
say he'll protect the Earth.
Your race is of no use,
and you've lost the pride
you once stood for!
Saiyan blood still
courses through my veins,
and I call the Earth my home!
[GOKU groaning]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
How did you...
Vegeta, don't worry.
I'll handle the rest of them.
Nonsense! 17 is
more than capable
of sending you back to
where you came from!
Ha! No thanks! I've spent
more than enough time in Hell.
Besides, the food
there was terrible!
Stop babbling!
This specimen of mine will
make quick work of you,
just like your
pathetic friends before!
I wouldn't be
so confident, Dr. Myuu!
You failed with Baby,
and you'll fail again.
[NARRATOR]
Goku has returned,
and now stands as
the prime contender
to defeat Super Android 17.
Can the Saiyan put a stop
to this mass destruction...
[DR. MYUU]
Attack, 17! Attack!
[NARRATOR] ...or does Dr. Myuu
have more tricks up his sleeve?
Don't miss the next explosive
episode of Dragon Ball GT!