[NARRATOR] With the threat
of Super Android 17 gone,
Goku attempted to summon
Shenron to restore order.
To his surprise the creature
that emerged was not Shenron,
but the terrible
Black Smoke Dragon!
It is known that the mighty
Shenron will grant a wish
to whomever gathers
the Dragon Balls
and summons him
from his slumber.
But even though
these wishes were used
mostly for the
good of humanity,
the Dragon Balls also
had a terrible secret.
[NARRATOR] Shortly after Goku
reluctantly allowed Pan
to join in the hunt for
the seven Shadow Dragons,
the duo found
themselves face to face
with the toxic dragon of
pollution, Haze Shenron.
[GOKU] I wouldn't be
laughing if I were you.
[NARRATOR] Haze Shenron
wasted no time flexing
his putrid muscle as the battle
for the Two-Star Dragon Ball
became more dire with
each passing moment.
With unexpected and timely help
from their mechanical
friend, Giru,
the Saiyans safely secured
the first Dragon Ball.
The Shadow Dragon
hunt continues now!
Oh yeah! That's great!
[PAN]
It actually tastes good?
Have some.
You'll feel a lot better.
No matter how thirsty I am,
I can't drink from the
same pond as a horse.
[PAN] Anyway, this right
here is all I need
to keep me happy for a while.
[PAN]
Grandpa, I have a question.
[PAN] The two-starred ball
turned back to normal
when we beat Haze Shenron.
So Earth should be getting
back to normal too, right?
Which means that since there
are seven Dragon Balls in all,
one, two, three, four, five--
if we topple six dragons,
Earth will return to
its original state!
Good! It looks like you've
really done your homework!
I wanted to make sure
there weren't too many,
but taking on six dragons
one at a time will be easy.
You always want to do
everything yourself.
Why won't you let me help?
In fact, you go home
ahead of us, Grandpa.
Giru and I can
take it from here.
[GIRU] Danger for Giru!
Danger for Giru and Pan!
Danger level increasing!
Giru, Giru, Giru...
[BULMA] Come on, everyone.
Try cheering up a bit.
Goku's fixed worse
problems than this before.
[VIDEL sighs]
Thanks, Bulma.
I've had it with those two
always running off at the
first sign of adventure.
I'm so sick of
worrying all the time.
Please Goku, we're
all counting on you.
[beeping]
[PAN]
Come on Giru, are we there yet?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball ahead.
Dragon Ball ahead.
One kilometer north. Giru.
[GOKU]
Right there! In that town.
I need something to drink.
I'm thirsty.
We're stopping here.
Okay, I get it, we'll land!
[PAN] Grandpa, the light's
red! You can't walk!
This place looks abandoned,
like everyone just
picked up and left.
[PAN]
Now, let's see? Which one?
Uh, lemon!
Is it broken?
You dumb machine. I put the
money in! Now where's my juice?
I can't really tell. Which way
is the Dragon Ball from here?
[GIRU] Dragon Ball north, 34
meters. West, four meters--
[PAN]
Aaah!
What is it, Pan?
Grandpa, look at that.
It's disgusting. Whatever it is.
[PAN groans]
Ah! What is happening?
It's sucking up electricity.
One day not too long ago,
that blob appeared,
and then it started to suck
up all the energy in town.
[OLD LADY]
It's disturbing.
Everyone in town just
picked up and moved out.
Here. If you're as
thirsty as I think,
then this should hit the spot.
Thank you so much.
We're the last ones here.
All the other
townsfolk have gone.
And I suggest that the
three of you do the same.
We'll leave soon. We just
have something to find first.
[beeping]
[PAN whimpers]
[PAN yells]
Don't you come near me!
These goo things
are really nasty!
I don't know.
I think they're kinda cute
looking, like a jellyfish.
[GIRU] Dragon Ball approaching!
Dragon Ball approaching! Giru.
[RAGE SHENRON] I've been
anticipating your arrival, Goku.
My name is Rage Shenron,
and I want to congratulate you
on the defeat of Haze Shenron,
even though he is
easily the weakest
among the Shadow Dragons.
Oh, yeah? How about you?
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
You really need to ask?
With the abilities I wield,
you'll come to know me
as the most densely powerful
of all the seven dragons.
Okay. I hate to be the one
to tell you this, but...
...you don't look it.
But Grandpa, my mother
always told me this saying
when I was a kid: Never
judge a book by its cover.
[RAGE SHENRON cackling] Your
granddaughter is very smart.
You should listen to her.
I call the electric slime!
[PAN, GOKU grunting]
[RAGE SHENRON] It's a different
kind of enemy, isn't it?
It has no face,
no stomach, no limbs,
and you have no idea where
to attack it to make it stop!
[PAN groans]
[GOKU groans]
Surprised, are we?
Pan, are you going to be okay?
Yeah, my whole body's
just a little numb.
So, you're not going to
make this easy on me!
[RAGE SHENRON]
Electric Slime, Body-Build!
[BOTH gasping]
So is there anything else
your mom used to tell you
that might come in handy?
She said big things
come in small packages.
[RAGE SHENRON] Goku, certainly
you remember the time, long ago,
when Vegeta and Nappa
traveled to Earth.
They were going
to stage an attack.
And you were quite fearful
of their coming, remember?
[RAGE SHENRON]
So fearful, in fact,
that you used the Dragon Balls
to bring yourself back to life.
But the side effect of
overusing the Dragon Balls
is an outpouring
of negative energy.
It was the negative
energy of that day
that brought me into existence.
Oh really? That makes us kinda
like brothers then, doesn't it?
Yes. And just like brothers,
the biggest will
always win the fight.
And now Goku, you will die!
Dragon Thunder Clap!
[PAN gasps]
No, Grandpa!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru! Electricity scary!
Electricity short circuit
Giru! No short circuit!
Giru, Giru, Giru...
[GOKU]
Okay. That's the last straw.
Why won't you stay down?!
Dragon Thunder Clap!
Thunder Clap!
[GOKU yelling]
It's like punching
a bowl of jelly!
Now that you're closer,
no way this won't hurt!
[GOKU groaning]
[RAGE SHENRON]
Oh, no you don't, young one!
[PAN gasps]
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
Your bark's bigger
than your bite!
[SS4 GOKU]
You're about to find out.
[RAGE SHENRON shrieks]
So, we've made one of our
little transformations, I see.
You changed first, Rage.
I just evened the playing field.
[RAGE SHENRON]
Dragon Thunder Clap!
Well, I was kind of cold.
Thanks for warming me up.
[RAGE SHENRON]
What?!
Get him, Grandpa!
SS4 GOKU] Sorry, Rage.
But a whole lot of people
are counting on me, and they
don't have much time left.
There are still five other
dragons I have to finish off
when I'm done here.
So, I'm afraid
I'll have to conclude
our quality time together.
[RAGE SHENRON gasps]
[RAGE SHENRON]
You don't have it in you.
I'll show you exactly
what I have in me!
[RAGE SHENRON screams]
[RAGE SHENRON]
It seems you can take a hit,
but you certainly
can't dish it out.
What? He couldn't have
stood up to that attack.
That electric slime is amazing.
That's impossible.
[RAGE SHENRON] I didn't
stand up to your attack.
I'm just holding on
to it for a moment.
But I'll be happy
to give to back!
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
You have no idea who
you're messing with, Goku!
You're no more damaging
to me than a sunburn!
Uh... It's kinda embarrassing
to be hit with my own attack.
I gotta give you some credit.
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
But you know what the
best part about this is?
It's when I show you that
I've been holding out on you.
Here goes!
[RAGE SHENRON] I've accessed the
planet's electricity reserves!
Now, it's is all mine!
No way! If he keeps growing,
he'll just step on us!
[PAN yelling]
Pan, no! Don't!
You don't stand a chance!
Haven't you learned?
Your puny blasts
will do nothing!
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
Mine! Mine! It's all mine!
I think he's telling the truth.
[BOTH yelp]
[PAN] At least he
can't get any bigger!
[PAN]
Grandpa!
[PAN screams]
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
Serves the two of you right!
This is it, Goku!
[GOKU screaming]
[PAN screaming]
[RAGE SHENRON cackling]
I wonder how much
they can stand.
I'll increase the
voltage to 50%.
[GOKU screaming]
[PAN screaming]
No, Pan. At this rate
we'll be toast in no time.
Yes, you're starting to see.
Even half of my power is too
much for you two to handle,
but we can still up the voltage!
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU] My body is so numb.
I can't feel a thing.
This could be it. For all I
know, I might already be dead.
[GOKU grunts]
[RAGE SHENRON gasps]
No! No rain! Not now!
No! I'll be ruined!
Electric slime, find cover
before you short circuit!
And hurry up! Our very lives
depend upon this battle!
Come on. You've got
to wake up. Pan?
Hi Grandpa.
[RAGE SHENRON] Electric slime,
if you don't hurry up,
we'll explode!
Look at what's happening to him.
I bet those little explosions
will turn into something
bigger real quick.
His whole being
thrives on electricity,
and with the rain pounding him,
the only thing he can
do is short circuit.
It's the perfect
time to attack him.
You can finish him off
while he's at his weakest!
No, I think we've
already won here.
No matter what I do,
this is definitely going
to be the end for him.
[RAGE SHENRON screaming]
He made the mistake of letting
his obsession with power
get the best of him.
At that enormous size,
he couldn't take
shelter from the rain.
He must have been
pretty conceited
to think that no one
could ever beat him.
It's kind of sad.
[RAGE SHENRON screaming]
I would say that our little
quarrel is over, wouldn't you?
Yes, I'm done.
Well, that's very
big of you, Rage.
This Dragon Ball
now belongs to you.
You've earned it.
[RAGE SHENRON cackles]
What a naïve
little girl you are!
Pan, get out of there! Fast!
[GOKU]
Ka, me, ha, me... Ha!
[RAGE SHENRON screaming]
[PAN sighs]
[GOKU sighs]
[PAN] Thanks, Grandpa!
You saved me again!
[GOKU]
Anytime.
[PAN laughing]
[NARRATOR]
With Rage Shenron defeated,
Goku and Pan claim their prize--
the Five-Star Dragon Ball.
As the skies clear
for our heroes,
they must make their way
back on to the trail
of the remaining
Shadow Dragons.
[GIRU] Giru lost. Destruction
everywhere. No Pan, no Goku.
Giru not alone?
[NARRATOR] But as they prepare
to set out on their journey,
there are forces at work
to stop these two
heroes in their tracks.
What evil stands in their way?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next riveting episode
of Dragon Ball GT!