[NARRATOR] The battle between
Meta-Rilldo and Goku rages on.
The Space-Time trans-what?
[SCHOLAR BOT] The Space-Time
Transmission Machine on the top
floor runs all systems,
including Coersive Removal.
That means it's got to be
the Space-Time Machine
that sent Trunks
to Dr. Myuu's place.
I've got to
find that machine!
[SCHOLAR BOT]
But, it's dangerous!
[NARRATOR] Then Meta-Rilldo
underwent further transformation
and proved himself to be
a master of metamorphosis!
[RILLDO] Have you put it
together yet, Saiyan?
The mighty Meta-Rilldo is
not just a superior fighter,
but part of this
very planet itself.
I thought so.
[GOKU]
There!
You've got abilities, but
you haven't quite mastered them.
If I were judging you off
appearance, I'd call you a liar.
And it seems that you've
already forgotten
the most important
point of all.
[RILLDO] You can
fight me all you want...
...but until you rid this planet
of all the metal covering it,
I will always have a
body to bring to the battle.
Now, this is the part
where you hand yourself
and the other Saiyan
over to Dr. Myuu.
[RILLDO]
I wonder if this kid
has anything else
hidden up his sleeve?
[GOKU] This guy's gotta have
a weak spot somewhere.
[battle crys]
[crash]
[exsperated breathing]
[RILLDO] Where are you,
you Saiyan brat?
It's useless to hide from me!
Now come out!
[girl screams]
Take this!
This is pretty funny
from down here, Rilldo!
You look just like
the monster on the screen!
Is he your twin brother?!
Yummy! That is good!
[RILLDO] I'm getting tired of
playing around with you, boy.
But I'm just getting warmed up!
You little brat!
That's good!
[GOKU]
Hey! I'm over here!
This way, shiny!
[RILLDO] So, shall you hide like
a coward or fight like a Saiyan?
Or are they one and
the same? Show yourself!
[PAN]
Grandpa!
I found the rest of
the Dragon Balls,
but Dr. Myuu has
taken Trunks hostage!
Pan! Stay where you are!
[screams]
[RILLDO]
Give me the Dragon Balls!
[PAN]
Grandpa!
Pan, no!
[PAN]
Wha, what's happening?
[evil chuckle]
[GIRU] Success!
Giru, Giru. Success!
Set the Space-Time
Transmission machine.
Yes sir. Right away sir!
[GIRU] Dr. Myuu very
impressed, very happy!
Hurry up with
the next transmission!
[GIRU]
Yes, sir. Yes, sir!
Giru silent. Watch mouth.
[RILLDO] Perfect!
No one can stop us now.
[DR. MYUU] Have the other two
been delivered yet?
[PEON ROBOT] Yes Doctor. They're
still warm from the machine.
Oh. Three Saiyan's and
a Dragon Ball. Wunderbar!
Let's start right away on
the molecular restructuring!
[DR. MYUU]
Now let's see...
[maniacal laughter]
I can actually feel the
intensity of their Saiyan power.
[DR. MYUU] I have waited
ages for this moment!
Begin the molecular
restructuring operation. Now!
[chuckling]
[DR. MYUU]
Ah, T-Twenty-O-Six.
Good timing
my little robotic friend.
I was just about to start
cooking up the Saiyans.
[GIRU]
Bad news! Giru.
[DR. MYUU] Very soon
the true value of their power
will become clear.
Achtung! Since you've done
such an excellent job for me,
I will allow you to view
this momentous occasion,
the catapult for
every day to come!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Move it Rusty!
[GIRU] Which is
the main off switch?
[DR. MYUU] What?
What are you doing?
[GIRU]
Giru just helping, sir.
[DR. MYUU]
Why you insolent bot!
[screaming]
[ROBOT]
Don't worry. We'll save you.
[GIRU]
Giru succeed! Giru succeed!
[Giru laughs]
[GIRU] My friends are safe!
Giru succeed!
Stop! Stop that! Do you
hear me T-Twenty-O-Six?!
How dare you betray me
when I am your creator!
[GIRU] Betray? Giru, Goku,
Pan, Trunks, friends.
[GIRU]
All good friends.
Wha-- What?
[GIRU] Dr. Myuu, no friend of
Giru. No friend. Enemy.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru.
This...
This can't be.
You've been working
for them the whole time!
Ahh! Ouch, my head!
[GIRU]
Pan! Pan!
Oh, my whole body
feels as stiff as a board.
Giru, what took you so long
to get us out of there?
Do you have
any idea what it's like
to be encased in
metal for that long,
and not be able to breathe or
move your arms and legs?
[GIRU] Giru is metal. All metal!
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
[PAN]
I don't care what you say,
because I'm gonna
tear you apart!
[GIRU]
No! N-No!
[running footsteps]
[DR. MYUU]
Ahh, excellent work! Top notch!
Not Trunks!
Don't move!
The life of your Saiyan
friend here is in my hand,
so stay back!
[DR. MYUU]
If this tablet is broken,
you can expect your friend to
never regain his original form.
Guard, contact General Rilldo
and have him report to
this location at once!
[ROBOT]
Yes, sir.
[GIRU]
No, no!
[ROBOT]
Get out of my way!
[GIRU]
Can't let you past here.
[ROBOT]
Back off!
[GIRU]
Nope.
[DR. MYUU]
Give that back!
[ROBOT]
Hold it right there!
Out of my way!
[ROBOT]
Got it!
--Stop!
--Catch!
[ROBOT]
Got it!
Be careful Pan!
[ROBOT]
I am getting tired of you.
[ROBOT] Got it!
Got it! Don't got it!
No!
Ah!
[screams]
[ROBOT]
Oh no! Oh no!
[quivering]
That wasn't supposed to happen!
I can't believe he's dead!
What have you fools done?!
[hysterical crying]
[TRUNKS]
I'm all right!
Pan!
[TRUNKS]
I'm up here! See?
Trunks!
[GIRU]
Trunks late! Late, late!
I know that Giru,
but you more than anybody
should know how busy I was.
So there was a plan after all!
[groans]
Oh, did you know the whole time?
I was hoping that we'd have a
much better chance at succeeding
if you two were in the
dark about the whole plan.
Well, I wasn't
really sure at first.
But then when you were turned
into metal by General Rilldo,
something just didn't ring true
about that. That's when I knew.
Ahh, very good.
[PAN]
Hey, wait just one minute.
What in the world
is going on here?
Why is it that I'm the only one
confused about
what just happened?
We're just saying that Giru is
one sneaky fellow, right buddy?
Giru?
[GIRU]
Giru sneaky.
Well, you see Pan, everything
that happened up to now
was planned by Giru and me.
Wha--?!
[GIRU] Metal Trunks a fake. Giru
made. Giru made. Giru, Giru.
[GIRU] Giru protect
Dragon Balls. Giru, Giru...
[GIRU] Giru sorry, Pan!
Giru sorry!
Oh Giru, I'm so glad you're with
us and not some rotten traitor!
Get them!
[GOKU]
Watch out!
I know you're hiding something
behind this door, Doc.
And seeing as
you're outnumbered,
why don't you just give up?
Goku! Pan! Giru! Why don't the
three of you come on up here?
I think our Dr. Myuu
has a little secret
he'd like to reveal to us!
A secret?
[DR. MYUU]
Ahhh! Stop!
Please don't open that!
[NARRATOR] Giru has
proven his true loyalties
by helping his friends foil
Dr. Myuu's evil scheme.
But there is
little time to celebrate
as the mad doctor's most
sinister secret of all
is about to be revealed!
What could this secret be?
And how can it be so important
that even Trunks would be forced
to trick his own friends
just to seek it out?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball GT!