What?! That's not Shenron!
[NARRATOR]
After Goku and his friends
defeated the evil Dr. Myuu,
Earth was bombarded with
devastating natural phenomenon
that threatened to wipe
out the entire planet.
It was learned that the
over-use of the Dragon Balls
caused a build up
of negative energy.
Not only did this
negative energy cause
the near-destruction
of the Earth,
but it also caused the
Dragon Balls to crack
and release the seven Shadow
Dragons upon the world.
[PAN]
The Dragon Balls! They're gone!
What are we gonna do now?
Goku and Pan set out on a quest
to find the Shadow Dragons
and battle each one for
their Dragon Ball.
All in the hopes that in
gathering the balls again,
they will be purified and
ready for one final wish--
that the Earth return
to her normal state.
Find out which Shadow
Dragon is going down next,
today on Dragon Ball GT!
[beeping]
[PAN] Giru, are you sure
there's a Dragon Ball here?
It's awful quiet.
[GIRU] No mistake! No mistake!
Giru's precise. Giru, Giru.
Uh-oh. Signal lost, signal lost.
[PAN]
What do you mean, "signal lost"?
You just had it!
[GIRU] Not enough energy.
Battery low. Battery very low.
[PAN groans]
[GIRU]
Need food, Giru need food!
I don't get you, Giru!
How can you be hungry?
You're just a pile
of rusty circuits!
[PAN screaming]
[VILLAGERS clamoring]
Hey, quick! Get the cart!
We need to grab as much mackeral
as we can and get to the market!
[PAN] These people are freaking
out. And they stink! Bad!
Grandpa, where are you?
This is incredible!
I've never seen so many fish!
The smell is making me sick.
[VILLAGER B] If we made fish our
currency, we'd be millionaires!
[COLM'S FATHER chuckling]
As far as I'm concerned,
Princess Oto
is our savior.
If she weren't around, we'd have
to catch the fish ourselves!
[VILLAGERS clamoring]
[COLM]
Listen to yourselves, everyone!
How can you expect
a little princess
to make all those fish
fall from the sky?
Don't you think that's strange?
Something awfully wrong is
goin' on 'round here, Dad.
Look, Colm. Stop makin' me
look like a fool, would ya?
Don't ya have friends
to play with? Huh?
All of my friends'
dads are fishermen
and they're unemployed now!
My friends can't even play ball
because they have to make
money for their families!
[COLM'S DAD growls]
I'm sick of hearin' it!
Wait, Dad!
[COLM'S DAD grunts]
What's wrong with you?
You shouldn't throw things
at your own children!
And just what would you
know about it? I don't know
who you are, kid, but you
better get home to your mama!
Hey! Wait a minute, I'm no kid!
[COLM'S DAD groans]
All right everybody, we're
gonna have a fish fry party!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[COLM] Ever since Princess Oto
appeared out of nowhere,
the fishing business has
vanished from our village.
Now small children
are being put to work,
while their parents act like
brainless servants
to the Princess.
[GOKU humming]
Who is this Princess Oto?
I don't know. That's just
what everybody else calls her.
And now the adults party
all day and night,
like they have no
responsibilities.
The kids don't deserve that.
[VILLAGERS laughing, yelling]
Every day, more fish fall
from the sky than we can handle.
And all the leftover fish
ends up rotting in the streets
and polluting the village.
[GOKU humming, munching]
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru!
[GOKU muffled grunting]
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
[GIRU munching]
[COLM]
To make matters worse,
all the seagulls have either
died or suffered bad injuries.
It's just not fair.
Many have broken
wings or twisted beaks
as if something, or
someone, is hurting them.
[PAN screams]
[COLM]
Are you okay?
I'm okay. But what is that?
[COLM] Those are the birds
I was talking about.
I've tried to
treat their injuries
but they've been
spooked by somethin'.
It was hard enough
gainin' their trust.
I hope they'll be
strong enough to fly
before the seasons
change! I hope.
The poor things! They must have
seen something really scary.
[GIRU] Dragon Ball detected!
Dragon Ball detected!
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU muffled gasp]
[GIRU] Dragon Ball! Dragon Ball!
Giru! Giru! Giru!
[COLM gasps]
[COLM] It's Princess Oto!
The one I was telling you about!
[GOKU]
That's no Princess!
[COLM'S FATHER] Hey look
everybody! It's fish time again!
[VILLAGER C] Princess Oto's back
again! I love that bonny lass!
[PAN]
Hey wait! Come back here!
[VILLAGERS] She's back!
The princess is back!
[GOKU] Your Princess is not
what you think she is.
What do you know
about it, boy-o?
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[COLM] Fa-Father!
[GOKU gasps]
[COLM'S FATHER, VILLAGER C yell]
Now do you see
what I was saying?
She may seem like a pretty
Princess with gifts,
but she's actually a very
evil and dangerous dragon
born out of Shenron himself!
[VILLAGERS clamoring]
[COLM'S FATHER screaming]
Dad! What's wrong?
You must be the creep
that has our Dragon Ball.
[PRINCESS OTO huffs]
I can't believe a little boy
could talk like that!
[PRINCESS OTO] You may
call me Oceanus Shenron,
commander of the
water and the air!
[GOKU] That may be.
But you exist
only because we overused
the Dragon Balls. Right?
Of course!
So, which
time was it?
I hardly think
that matters now!
But it does matter.
Because you wouldn't even be
here if it weren't for us!
In a way, we
gave you life,
so you owe it to us to
tell us what wish it was!
That stupid pig...
[GOKU gasps]
It was the pair
of underwear!
Did she say underwear?
[GOKU] Oh yeah,
I remember.
Oolong did that. It was
our very first wish!
And it was a
funny one, too!
I'm very aware of the stupid,
inane wish that gave me life
but don't even
think for a second
that you can laugh at me and
not suffer the consequences!
[GOKU laughing]
That really was a stupid wish!
Okay, that's enough.
It's really not that funny.
And with that, Goku,
I will enjoy burying you
with my own two hands.
Now die!
Air-Shattering Energy Balls!
[GOKU]
Move, Pan!
[COLM]
What's that?!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU yelping]
[PAN yelling]
[PRINCESS OTO chuckling]
[GOKU gasps]
That felt like
punching a steel wall!
[PAN]
Was that a force field?
[PRINCESS OTO chuckling]
[PAN panting]
How about this?
[PAN]
Ha!
It didn't work!
Okay... Leave it to me!
[PRINCESS OTO huffs]
What idiots!
Ka, me, ha, me... Ha!
[COLM whimpers]
[COLM gasps]
What the-- I'm flying!
[PAN chuckles]
So, you can deflect
my kamehameha waves?
You should be really proud!
Keep on laughing,
it'll be your undoing.
Now, Mighty Hurricane Fury!
[PAN gasping]
[GOKU gasps]
[PAN gasps]
Be careful!
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU]
I know your secret now!
Grandpa, that's not cool!
What's wrong, Pan?
Funny... I seem
to agree with her.
[PAN] Now, what was it you
were gonna say earlier?
Oh yeah, I was gonna say...
...I really don't mind
being naked at all.
Not that!
I was talking about the secret
you found on Princess Oto!
Oh yeah! That's right.
[GOKU]
I've been studying your moves
and I know your secret is
in the way you spin around!
[PRINCESS OTO chuckling]
Aren't you a bright
little stinker!
Seems you've figured
me out already.
But...
...I control the ocean and
the wind that moves it.
Nothing can stop
my force of nature!
[COLM]
Oh, look out! It's a monster!
Wait a minute!
Did you just put on a mask, or
is that actually how you look?
I hope it's just a disguise!
Heh. While I'm on the subject,
I'll tell you one more thing.
No one who has ever
seen my true face,
has ever lived to
tell anyone about it.
You better be ready to fight!
Pan! Get Colm out of here.
[PAN]
Right!
[GOKU yelling]
Wha-What's the--
You know, I really
like your technique!
It's so much fun!
I could do this all day!
How pompous!
[BOTH grunting]
This is quite fun actually!
I feel like I'm fighting a tiny,
pip-squeak version of myself!
[BOTH grunting]
What do you say we
pick up the pace a bit?
[BOTH grunting]
You may be able to
imitate my techniques,
but can you keep
up with my speed?
How about this?!
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU] Now that is
some amazing power!
I didn't even see it coming!
[PRINCESS OTO] You shouldn't
be so clumsy, Goku!
You might hurt yourself.
[GOKU] The air pressure is so
strong that I can't even move!
I need to stop the
air from spinning
to have a chance for an attack!
Whirlwind Spin!
It looks like I'm
the winner again!
[GOKU] Don't be so sure!
I've survived worse than this!
He'll make it!
[COLM]
My seagull!
The bird!
It's flying!
You can do it!
[GOKU] I need to avoid
her wind altogether!
Maybe I can get a trophy
for beating up a Saiyan!
[PRINCESS OTO yelping]
No way! Colm,
hold on to my back
and whatever you
do, don't let go!
Get out of my way!
Thank you so much, birdie!
I think you just showed us
the trick to beating her!
A Whirlwind Spin!
[GOKU]
Is that the only trick you know?
[PAN] It's the same as
the eye of a hurricane.
At the center, the
airspeed is almost zero
and easy to fly through!
Today your death will be
my reward, young one!
[GOKU]
No it won't!
Hang in there, Grandpa!
What do you think you're doing?
Pan!
I know what I'm doing.
Let's see, if you go, Ka...
[PAN]
Me...
Ha...
Ha!
What!? No! Deflect!
Deflect! Deflect!
[PRINCESS OTO screaming]
That was great, Pan!
Sorry Princess,
but giving up my life
is simply not an option
for me right now!
Ka... Me...
[GOKU]
Ha... Me...
Ha!
No! They can't win!
[OCEANUS SHENRON screaming]
[PAN] Grandpa, did you
see me? I did it! I did it!
Wow! That was
really impressive, Pan!
Your very first Kamehameha wave.
I wanted to try it
all by myself, Grandpa.
It was perfect form, wasn't it?
[PAN] 'Cause when I do
something, I do it with style!
What? What's so funny?
[COLM'S FATHER]
I really don't know what to say.
Words can't express
the gratitude and thanks
we have for you two.
We will work harder than ever
before from now on. We promise.
Daddy, can we go out
fishin' sometime this week?
[COLM'S FATHER] Of course we
can, son. Of course we can.
Look!
[ALL gasp]
[seagulls squaking]
Got it.
See you, Colm.
Wait a sec!
Next time, will you teach
me how to fly like you?
Come over to Mount Paoz.
I'll teach you there anytime!
I will.
You better! Because
I'll be waiting for you!
[GOKU] Bye!
[PAN] Giru! Giru!
[NARRATOR] And with that,
Goku and Pan collected
their third Dragon Ball.
But they can't let
themselves relax for too long.
Four evil dragons still
stand in their way.
The hunt continues on
the next Dragon Ball GT!