[NARRATOR]
Previously on GT...
the hunt for the seven Shadow
Dragons was in full swing.
[RAGE SHENRON]
This Dragon Ball is yours!
[NARRATOR] And as each
dragon fell, the Dragon Ball
that it possessed was
restored to normal.
[GOKU]
Ha... Me... Ha!
[NARRATOR] With the defeat
of Oceanus Shenron,
and the recovery of the
Six-Star Dragon Ball,
Goku found himself matched up
with his deadliest rival yet!
[NATURON SHENRON]
Not quite. You call that
an Ultimate Kamehameha?
Guess you're not as
strong as I thought.
[GOKU yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Naturon Shenron was right.
He had called Goku's bluff.
The Super Saiyan
was holding back!
He didn't have the heart to
attack with all of his might
or Pan would be destroyed!
[NATURON SHENRON] I can't
believe this is happening to me.
[NARRATOR] But Goku finally
found the opportunity
he was looking for!
[SS4 GOKU]
Gotcha!
No!
[NARRATOR] With Pan no
longer inside of him,
Naturon Shenron returned
to his true form,
and Goku was free to
attack him in earnest!
After a brush with death,
Goku managed to outwit
another Shadow Dragon!
But with only
four dragons gone,
three are still left
roaming the Earth!
[beeping]
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
Dragon Ball detected!
Dragon Ball nearby!
[PAN]
Alright already!
Will you please stop saying the
same things over and over again!
You're driving me crazy!
You're obviously letting the
heat get to your head, Giru!
Now pull yourself together!
Or has the heat
fried your circuits?
[GIRU]
No, Giru fully operational!
Dragon Ball nearby!
Dragon Ball here!
[GOKU groaning] I don't know
about you guys but I'm starving.
I don't think I've ever
been this hungry before.
[PAN groans]
I can take being hungry.
But this heat is unbearable!
[PAN gasps]
Why's the Sun so
bright all of a sudden?
It's been covered up by a haze
ever since the
dragons got loose!
I don't know.
Maybe since four of
the Dragon Balls are fixed
there's not as much
negative energy
and the Earth is starting to
get back to normal again.
[PAN]
What a mess this is.
Any luck, Grandpa?
[GOKU]
Not yet.
[PAN]
Hm?
Hey, the sun just got bigger.
[GOKU]
That's just an illusion.
The heat must really
be getting to you, Pan.
You're seeing things.
The sun can't get bigger, silly.
Can it jump across the sky?!
Hm?
Just try that again,
you monster!
NUOVA SHENRON cackles]
[NUOVA SHENRON] You people
create your own monsters.
Just like you created me.
I am Nuova Shenron, the
invincible Four-Star Dragon!
You're a dragon?
You don't look like the others,
and I don't see a
Dragon Ball anywhere!
[NUOVA SHENRON chuckles]
[NUOVA SHENRON] Maybe you
should look a little closer!
All right! Cough it up, Pal.
Or we're gonna have
to take it by force!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
Go ahead and try!
You won't be happy
with the results!
[PAN]
You have no idea
who you're dealing
with here, do you?
We've already tangled with
four of you Shadow Dragons
and they're all dead!
So I'd be more than a little
concerned if I were you!
The odds aren't
exactly in your favor!
Cut it out, Pan!
You're underestimating
your opponent!
This dragon's stronger
than the others!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[GOKU] Besides, we're
not here to fight!
We're here to save the Earth.
I hear you, Grandpa!
And that's what I'm going
to do! Save Mother Earth!
That's not what I meant!
[PAN grunting]
[NUOVA SHENRON cackling]
Put her down! Right now!
[GOKU grunting]
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Wake up, Pan! Please! Wake up!
Giru! Giru! Giru!
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I've been
awaiting your arrival, Goku!
Now we are free to play
the ultimate game of survival
without any distractions!
I see. Well, I'd rather
settle this without fighting.
But if I have to, I will!
[NUOVA SHENRON] Let me make
it simple! You have to!
[GOKU] He's definitely not
lacking in confidence.
[NUOVA SHENRON] When the statue
above us hits the ground,
that will be the
signal to start!
[GOKU] Fair enough. By the way,
which wish were you formed from?
[NUOVA SHENRON]
I was born when your first
true rival, King Piccolo,
wished for his youth and
got his full powers back.
[GOKU grunts]
[NUOVA SHENRON growls]
[GOKU yelping]
I didn't even touch him and
my hand still caught on fire!
[GOKU yelping]
[NUOVA SHENRON] Did I forget to
mention that I have the ability
to raise my body temperature to
even higher levels than the Sun?
What? Yes! You did!
[GOKU]
Where did he go?
Why can't I see my shadow?
[GOKU grunting]
[NUOVA SHENRON] I do hope he's
enjoying my Sun Gun Attack.
[NUOVA SHENRON] You can't
dodge me forever, Goku!
[GOKU panting, yelping]
[NUOVA SHENRON]
You silly, ignorant Saiyan!
There are no walls that can
protect you from Nuova Shenron!
If I punch him, my
hands will burn off
and if I kick him,
I won't have any toes left.
What a defense.
I'll have to be careful.
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU panting]
This is bad! I need some food!
[GOKU]
Oh, man! Not good.
Please go away.
His power level is mountains
above those other dragons.
This is the wrong time for my
body to go on a hunger strike.
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU]
Whoa! A punching inferno!
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU] My only hope is
to use energy waves,
but how can I do that if
I'm all out of power?
[NUOVA SHENRON]
You're mine, Goku!
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU]
What?
Ow! Running away is more
painful than fighting!
[GOKU]
Ha!
Ha, ha! Come in. It's open.
[NUOVA SHENRON] What a pity.
I didn't expect the game
to end so abruptly!
[GOKU] Alright, my body's
actually responding!
Let's see how far
I can push it!
Bull's-eye! Dead on!
He never moved!
Uh, oh!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU]
Hot!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru! Giru!
Pan sweet when she's sleeping.
Not mean to Giru. Very nice.
Giru love Pan.
Oh, no! Pan! Please wake up!
Danger! Danger!
Giru!
Pan, wake up! Dan-Danger!
Not safe! Not... safe...
Yes, sleep peacefully.
Eis Shenron will
make you a nice tomb.
[NUOVA SHENRON gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU]
Over here!
[NUOVA SHENRON groans]
[NUOVA SHENRON growling]
[GOKU] Where could he have gone?
There's nowhere to hide.
Unless he went
down the sewer too.
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU]
I can't win at this rate.
There's got to be a way
to cool this guy down!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Alright, you wanna
fight? Follow me!
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Oh, no! What am
I going to do now?!
[GOKU] He's too hot to
fight in close quarters!
He'll have the
advantage down here!
There's got to be
another way out!
[GOKU]
I've got two choices.
I can stay here and die or
I can jump through there!
But can I make it?
Yes!
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU] Ow! I landed right on
the burned spot! That hurts!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
Isn't it about time
we put an end to things, Goku?
[NUOVA SHENRON yelling]
[GOKU grunts]
That blast of his...
It's just light energy
gathered from the Sun!
But it gets focused and
magnified when he shoots it
through that lens
and it becomes lethal!
[GOKU groaning]
[NUOVA SHENRON]
So you got a small taste
of my Nuova Death Ray!
Yeah, converting the Sun's
energy is pretty ingenious!
And you never run out that way!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
You're correct!
The Sun gives me an
endless supply of energy!
Allow me to demonstrate
it's deadly potential!
Nuova Death Ray!
[GOKU]
Solar Flare!
[NUOVA SHENRON groaning]
Come on. Someone
of your strength
being knocked out
by a Solar Flare?
I don't think so, Nuova Shenron!
I'm not buying it!
[NUOVA SHENRON]
You don't disappoint, do you?
Alright then! No more games!
[NUOVA SHENRON yelling]
[NUOVA SHENRON growling]
Impressive. So this is
your true form I take it?
Yes! You have drawn me
out of my shell so to speak.
What you see before you is
my ultimate fighting form.
And now that I've raised
the stakes, it's your turn.
It's time to ante up or fold!
Fold? No chance of that.
I'll see you and I'll raise you!
[GOKU yelling]
So, Super Saiyan Four,
you've come out. Let's play.
Look! I can't allow
you to turn this planet
into a desert wasteland,
Nuova Shenron!
It's not right!
The game is over!
[NARRATOR]
Goku has laid down the law,
but can he take the heat?
Having started the battle
exhausted and
depleted of energy,
how long can he push
himself to the limit
before he runs out
of gas completely?
Don't miss the next GT!