Too much time and energy
has been wasted on you
to bother with anymore.
Goodbye!
[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
a helpless, blinded,
and beaten Goku
was snatched out of
the jaws of death
by Goten in the nick of time!
Even though he had
lost his eyesight,
Goku was still
the only one
with a chance of
beating Syn Shenron!
So Majuub came to the fore,
hoping to hold off the
evil dragon long enough
for Goku to recuperate!
You know, we're here because
we all have faith in you.
In a desparate move,
Goku took on even more energy
than the natural limits
of his body should allow!
[GOKU]
When you see him!
[NARRATOR]
Unable to see Syn Shenron,
Goku had to rely
on his other senses!
But he still managed
to score a direct hit
on the powerful
One-Star Dragon!
He did it!
That's my man!
Nice one!
Now, look at me,
do you see?
This is my true form!
The form I use to stand at
the pinnacle of dragon power!
His power's unreal...
I don't think we've ever faced
anyone this strong before.
[NARRATOR] After ingesting
the Dragon Balls,
the ultimate evil dragon,
Omega Shenron was born.
Blind and battle weary,
how will Goku withstand the
might of all seven dragons?!
[SYN laughs]
Gohan, use your senses!
Whose power is greater?
Your Dad's or the dragon's?
I can't say, Mom!
It's hard to tell!
But this really isn't
the best time to ask!
[GOKU growls]
[EVERYONE yells]
Enough! If you want to
fight, Omega, fight me!
Of course, I want to fight!
And I have no choice
but to fight you!
There's nobody else around!
What?!
Gohan! Trunks! Pan!
Are you all right?!
Chi Chi! Goten! Videl!
Can you hear me?!
I want you to see this!
Allow me to be your eyes!
I've built a fine cemetery!
There is parched, lifeless
ground for a grave!
And broken buildings in the
background for a headstone!
Now all we need
is a dead body.
And I can assure you that
after all this is over,
I'll give you
a nice burial.
You misunderstand me!
This is your grave, for your
funeral, and your burial!
We'll just have
to see about that!
Go ahead!
Grind it in!
What? Nuova Shenron! How?
You like that?
Well I have many more gifts!
I'm all the Shadow
Dragons wrapped in one!
[GOKU thinks]
Darn, frozen again!
[SYN] Guess your body didn't
remember that from last time!
How 'bout this one?
A Whirlwind Spin!
[SYN roars]
Mighty Hurricane Fury!
[GOKU yells]
Dragon Thunder Clap!
Time to break out the shovel!
Oh please, show
me something new!
Come on! You're just
tickling my feet! Let's go!
[groaning]
[GOHAN grimacing]
Goten! No!
You'll only get
in his way, Goten!
You're gonna have
to trust him!
But, he's hurt!
[glass shatters]
What a pity. He's dead.
The fun's over.
[GOKU pants]
You can never kill me, Omega!
[OMEGA growls]
[GOKU groans]
Is that so?
[GOKU grunts]
I kill whomever I please.
Well, Goku, are we done?
[GOKU grimaces]
[GOKU]
Oh, man!
I hate to say it, but you've
seen better days, Goku.
[GOKU thinks]
My eyes! I can see!
Prepare yourself, this is
the day you die, Goku!
[GOKU chuckles]
If I had a zeni for
each time I heard that...
You know you're not the first
one to try that line on me,
but you just might be the last!
Ha! You're too blind and
beaten to sense where I am!
Hey! Hey! Over here!
Listen to my voice!
Go ahead! Take your
best shot! Right here!
[GOKU growls]
Well, if you insist,
I think I will!
But how?!
You were finished!
No more!
You're mine!
Dragon Fist!
Yeah, Dad!
Get him, Goku!
All right, Grandpa!
[GOKU growls]
[SYN yells]
Got him!
Yeah!
[ChiChi cheers]
Goku! You did it!
You did it!
You're the real Champion!
I mean no one can beat you!
You are the greatest!
Oh, my goodness!
A public confession!
We'd better get
that on tape!
[EVERYONE laughs]
What's that?
It's him, Grandpa! Look!
That's just what Rage
Shenron did! Remember?
Oh, no.
Ah! That was quite a
painful technique indeed!
But, it will take more than
that to be rid of Omega Shenron!
This is bad! I don't
know what else to do!
That was my best attack!
[OMEGA laughs]
You're not laughing
anymore are you?
Fools, did you really think
you could overcome the power
of the Shadow Dragons?
Run!
[EVERYONE yelling]
I will not quit! Ever!
Come now! You're done!
Finished!
Why do you persist?
Stop torturing yourself.
Death will bring relief.
Really? Then it's you
who'll taste relief!
Mmm! You just don't
know when to quit,
do you monkey man?!
Why you insolent...
Let...
...go!
No chance. Not until
I show you a technique
that my friend Vegeta
used against Majin Buu!
Huh?
[OMEGA] What technique?
Your hands are tied!
You can't attack me
unless you let go!
What?! What are you doing?!
[BOTH grunting]
No! Dad's converting his
life force into energy!
He's making a bomb
out of his body!
What do you mean?
I mean he intends
to blow himself up
and take that dragon with him!
Is he crazy?!
No! Mom!
[GOKU thinks] If this
doesn't work, then I'm sorry!
But I have to do it!
I have to try!
You maniac!
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
Vegeta!
[VEGETA] Don't be stupid!
It won't work!
You'll only succeed
in killing yourself
and then where will we be?
Vegeta!
It's about to get
intense, Kakarot.
No offense, but it's
been intense all along!
This dragon is in a league
of his own. You have no idea.
Yeah, I know he's great,
but is he strong enough to
take on two Super Saiyan 4's?
Two?
You heard me. I have a plan
to reach Super Saiyan 4.
[GOKU gasps]
[VEGETA thinkis]
Where is that woman?
How can she be late
at a time like this?
Ah, speak of the devil!
[GOKU] What in the world
is she driving?
[VEGETA]
Blutz Wave Emission equipment.
[GOKU]
Huh?
[VEGETA] What were
you doing? Taking a nap?
You've got some nerve!
It would take anyone else
years to build this, you jerk!
Why don't you pipe
down and get busy!
Super Saiyan 4 or not!
He doesn't scare me!
Not one bit!
Blutz Waves? What for?
[VEGETA yelling]
What's happening?
He's transforming!
Vegeta's turning
into a giant ape!
This could turn out bad.
[VEGETA roars]
Bulma, what are you doing?
Cut it out!
If Vegeta loses control, he
could blow up the entire planet!
Look! Our only
hope is for Vegeta
to become a Super Saiyan 4!
If Goku was able to do it,
he should be able to do it, too!
But there's no guarantee!
It's too risky!
It's sink or swim, Gohan!
If this doesn't work,
we'll all die anyway!
But...
Listen! Above all,
I'm Vegeta's Princess!
Bulma...
[VEGETA roars]
That's it, he's lost it!
Father!
[VEGETA roars]
What the...?!
This is trouble.
[VEGETA roars]
Vegeta, no! Please! It's me!
[GOKU yells]
[OMEGA chuckles]
So! Is this your
secret weapon?
A giant monkey too ignorant
to know who the enemy is?
Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
Ka... ka... rot...
I am the Prince of all Saiyans!
I could never allow my
reason to be overpowered
by the primal mind!
Awesome, Vegeta!
You're really something!
What?
[PAN] This is what Grandpa
did when he first transformed!
All right.
He's doing it!
That's it, dad!
Just a little bit further!
It's working! I knew it!
At long last, I've ascended.
Well done. You amaze me.
Wow! He's really cute!
Gosh, he's even better
looking than Goku!
Excuse me!
You're kidding, right?
Goku's far better looking!
What?! No way!
You're crazy!
I'm crazy?!
Well you're blind!
Ladies! Why squabble?
You're looking at the blue
ribbon face right here!
--Get over yourself!
Uh, okay!
Quit stalling!
[OMEGA growls]
[BOTH yell]
Whoa! I gotta learn
how to do that.
It's almost as if the Earth is
quivering because it's scared!
Do you really think one more
weakling will make a difference?
Well, then. Shall we?
Kakarot, if we
attack now, we'll die.
Are you serious?
Search your feelings.
You know it as well as I.
It is true.
Well it wouldn't
be the first time,
but I have to
die again, I'm ready.
No, there's no need.
When there's Fusion!
You know I wouldn't suggest
joining bodies with you
unless it was
our only hope.
Our last hope.
[NARRATOR] After preventing
Goku from needlessly
sacrificing his own life,
Vegeta has come up
with a plan for victory!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!