[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
urgent preparations
were being made
for an expedition
into outer space
to recover the
Black Star Dragon Balls!
Hi, Mama! Papa told me
I should come help you!
Not right now...
I still don't understand!
Why do we have to go with him?
[NARRATOR] Vegeta appointed
himself head recruiter
and rounded up a
flight crew for Goku.
Main power link...
Check!
[BULMA]
All systems are go for launch.
[NARRATOR] While giving the ship
a quick once over,
Goku and Trunks found
an unexpected stowaway!
Hi!
Hi, there Pan!
What's going on?
Oh, no? Then let's
get serious! Blast off!
[NARRATOR] And so the
galaxy-wide search
for the Black Star
Dragon Balls began--
a few minutes
earlier than intended
and with a slightly
different crew!
[NARRATOR] Before the
smoke had even cleared,
a troubling discovery was made.
A small part has fallen
off of the spaceship.
[NARRATOR] Will the loss of this
part be a minor incovenience...
[BULMA]
Hmm?
[NARRATOR]
...or a recipe for disaster?
[TRUNKS] Pan, this isn't funny!
Give it back right now!
[PAN] No way! You want it?
Come and get it!
[laughs tauntingly]
Pan! Give me that
override key this instant!
Why? So you can take me
back to my boring life on Earth?
Forget it!
Pan, this mission's way too
dangerous for a child. Please.
Like I care!
[giggles]
Trunks?
Now! Give me back that key!
You're going home, Pan!
Hand it over! Now!
[giggles]
Well! Your move!
[sighs]
[TRUNKS] A year of this and
I'll be a basket case!
[birds chirping]
[yawns]
[CHICHI] Well, let's see...
I do laundry once a week.
So if I do laundry
51 more times,
they should just be getting
home while I'm folding.
[computer beeps]
Come on... How many
parts are on this ship?
It's got to belong somewhere.
[CHICHI]
Bring our granddaughter back
safe and sound, Goku. Please.
[PAN] Move your big,
fat behind, Grandpa!
Coming through! Let's go! Move!
--Move! Move! Move!
--Hey!
[GOKU]
What are you doing with that?
[PAN]
Cleaning! Whatd'ya think?
Hey! I already took a shower!
There! That oughta do it! All
done! Now it's your turn, guys!
Huh?
You don't expect me to
do everything, do you?
Trunks, you can do
the laundry! How's that?
What? Me? Do laundry?!
Sure! Why not? And Grandpa,
you can be the head dishwasher!
Well, maybe we should wait
until you get more experience
before we make
you head dishwasher!
Yeah, when I try doing dishes,
I end up breaking them.
Ah, man...
I don't know why Grandma puts up
with you! All you have to do is
take your time and be careful!
Trunks...isn't that right?
Yes, of course.
But maybe we shouldn't be
assigning chores just yet, Pan.
We share the housework
equally and that's that!
[both groan]
[explosion]
Something must have
hit us, you guys!
[unintelligible stammering]
What is that thing?
[GOKU] It looked
like part of the ship!
[mortified utterings]
[computer beeps]
[BULMA] Bingo!
A perfect match! Finally!
And the mystery part is...
[screams]
No! Of all the parts,
why that one?!
Get your seat belts on!
We're going in for
an emergency landing!
Emergency landing?
What's happening?!
One of our
stabilizer jets fell off!
[both scream]
If we don't land soon, things
are going to get really bad!!
How bad? What do you mean?
The ship will be torn apart!
Why did you tell me that?
I'm just a kid!
You should have lied!
What's wrong with you?!
If we die, everyone
on Earth will die, too!
Will you shut up! What kind
of adults are you, anyway?!
[PAN]
I want my Mommy!
Pan, it's okay!
We'll make it! I promise!
We're going to be all right!
No! It's too late! We're doomed!
[alarm beeping]
That's the one! Goku!
Make sure that you and Pan are
strapped in! Are you ready?
Yeah, sure! No sweat!
I don't want to die!
Nobody's going to die here!
We're just going to crash land!
Are you nuts? People
die in crash landings!
No one dies today! Here we go!
[TRUNKS]
Hold on, guys!
[alarm beeping]
[thunderous impact]
[screaming]
[crash]
[enormous sighs]
[MERCHANT] Quality goods at
cheap prices! Why hesitate?
Put your charge
card on the plate!
If you don't buy,
your children will cry!
Wow!
--Ahh! Look at all that food!
--Fresh fruit! Fresh veggies!
--This is great!
--Get them here!
Maybe we should get
a place to stay here tonight
and repair the ship tomorrow.
Sounds good to me!
[rumbling]
[chattering]
Oh, no! A stampede!
They look extraordinarily
appealing! Yes?!
Absolutely dazzling!
One could easily mistake
them for royalty! No?!
Most definitely!
Some of my toe rings could
add excitement to your feet!
That's your opinion!
So, maybe we should just
spend the night somewhere else.
No way! This place is awesome!
Uh, we just came here to get
some parts for our spaceship.
Do you have stuff like that?
Imecka is your
one-stop shopping planet!
Look! You need parts
for your spacecraft!
--No, no! Here!
--No?! Over here!
I'll just charge it
to your account!
--Ten thousand Gametz here!
--Two thousand for the fruit!
--Five thousand for this!
--One million Gametz!
I hope you chose well, because
there are no returns here!
What? You're kidding!
Welcome to Imecka.
[TRUNKS]
Do you see any salesmen?
[PAN]
Not yet. So far so good.
[MAID] Call the porter!
New guests have arrived!
Call the porter!
[GOKU]
That's pretty cool!
[PAND AND TRUNKS]
Sshhh!
Looks like we're clear.
[HOTEL CLERK]
You seem disappointed
with our accommodations!
You'll have to excuse us.
We just had a very
trying experience.
Oh, it's very peaceful here!
Great! Then we'd like
to get a room, please!
Yes! But of course!
[HOTEL CLERK] Fitting a
room is like fitting a shoe!
Can you believe this thing cost
two hundred and fifty Gametz?!
And they practically
forced it on me!
Yeah, but at least
the food was good!
Aahhh!
That's what this is about!
You've been taken in
by our street merchants!
Haven't you, Sir?
Yeah, they did
a number on us all right!
And like naïve tourists,
we fell right into their trap!
Well, now that
you're in our hands,
you can relax and enjoy Imecka!
Our porter will
take you to your room!
[PORTER]
Allow me!
Let me get that!
[screams]
I'm not a bag! I'm a
person, you stupid robot!
[GOKU] Put me down!
What kind of robot are you?
[PORTER]
I am a Porterbot 3000,
programmed to retrieve
and deliver luggage
in a prompt
and courteous manner.
[GOKU] Yeah, well,
you must have a screw loose
because I'm not luggage!
[PORTER] This is
where you will be staying.
I hope you enjoy
your honeymoon.
Hmm?
[sigh of disbelief]
[double beep]
It looks like a palace!
[PORTER]
The Bridal Suite is equipped
with our gold star amenities
package for your comfort!
It's almost too nice.
You can put our
luggage down now!
[PORTER] We hope you enjoy your
stay! Please insert gratuity!
[GOKU] Uhh, Trunks... I think he
wants us to give him some money.
I guess he's programmed for
more than carrying luggage.
[PORTER] Thank you,
Sir or Ma'am! Welcome to Imecka!
Please ring the front desk
if I can be of any
further assistance! Enjoy!
[relieved breath]
I'm going to go
soak in a nice hot bath!
I hope they have some food
around here. I'm starving.
[NEWS REPORTER] People from
all over Imecka flocked to the
royal palace today to get a
glimpse of Lord Don Kee himself.
Once a week,
Don Kee grants an audience
to the citizens of his kingdom.
[WOMAN]
Don Kee!
[CITIZENS]
Don Kee!!
[mass cheering]
Well, so much for democracy.
It looks like a dictatorship.
[PAN] You guys! There's
something wrong with the shower!
I can't turn the water off!
It just keeps on running!
[TRUNKS]
Just a sec! I'm coming!
[metal clank]
What in the world?!
[GOKU] Trunks! Pan!
I found the fridge!
This is too good to be true!
I hit the jackpot!
The food won't stop coming out!
Something's strange
about this hotel!
They have a meter on
the shower like a taxi-cab!
[groans]
[PAN] The number keeps
getting higher and higher!
It's already past
seven thousand!
[ticking]
Strange...
What's that noise?
[ticking]
[TRUNKS]
You've got to be kidding me!
There are money-meters
everywhere! This is insane!
We're being charged
for everything!
Even for watching TV!
[horrified gasps]
[ding...ding...ding...]
[TRUNKS]
They're robbing us blind!
They even have the nerve
to charge us for looking
at the decorations!
[TRUNKS] I've never skipped
a check before, but let's go!
Ahhh! Just a second, you guys!
Goku! Come on!
Well, we picked one heck of
a planet to crash land on,
didn't we?
I don't know about this trip.
Nothing seems to be going right.
We did kind of
get off to a bad start.
Are you insinuating that
this is all my fault?!
Well, we were still checking the
ship when you pushed the button.
You're the one who let those
bunglers make a wish on
the Black Star Balls right under
your nose! It's your fault!
I guess you're right.
It is my fault.
Oh, no you don't! I know what
you're trying to do, Grandpa!
You're trying to act like you're
the one to blame! Aren't you?!
Well you can stop acting!
Because you really are to blame!
No sense in
staying out in the rain!
We might as well
head back to the ship
and spend the night there.
[PAN] I am not walking
all the way back to the ship
in the rain.
I am way too tired.
And hungry! And cold!
[whiny cry]
--Are you okay?
Hi! My name is Pan!
Nice to meet you.
--Good evening, folks!
Good evening.
[FUTOVA] We've never actually
met any aliens before.
I hope you're enjoying
your stay on Imecka!
It's a nice place, but
the people are strange.
It seems all they care
about is making money!
I've never met a greedier
bunch of scammers before!
Pan! Please!
No, let her speak her mind!
Your child's honesty is
refreshing, isn't it?
Yes! And I'm ashamed to
admit that she's right.
You people are nice. Why is
everyone else so money hungry?
Our leader-Don Kee's to blame.
Lord Don Kee!
[siren]
Are they coming here?
I think so.
[siren approaches]
[REPO-ROBOT]
Nobody move!
The lease has expired
on this dwelling place!
Rent is now due!
[REPO-ROBOT] Produce the funds
needed to renew your lease
or we will proceed to
repossess this dwelling!
[flabbergasted disbelief]
Your time to renew has expired.
Future rental inquiries must
be made at the palace.
[REPO-ROBOT] We will now
dismantle and repossess!
Hey, is this all right?
They're taking everything.
You won't have a home
left for your children.
It can't be helped. My income
has been insufficient lately
to afford
the luxury of a dwelling.
Prices have been at a premium
ever since Lord Don Kee
became our King.
I saw him on TV.
[FUTOVA]
That's him.
Long ago things were affordable,
and we had no trouble
providing for our families. But
now we are all deeply in debt.
Our futures are sold
before we live them.
But we still have our reasons.
Our reasons for pressing on,
regardless of what
humiliation we must endure.
[FUTOVA]
I seem to have lost my roof.
[sympathetic horror]
More embarrassing
are the low practices
my people have resorted to.
But don't judge them. Truly,
they're only trying to survive.
It's hard to maintain integrity
in the face of adversity.
Only a few of us have managed.
But it usually means
losing one's house--
a tough pill to swallow.
That's why many of us
have become swindlers.
That's so sad.
How terrible.
[REPO-ROBOT] Your dwelling has
been reclaimed by Lord Don Kee!
Repo-robots, move out!
[GOKU]
I'm no lawyer,
but I think I know how
we can get your house back!
You're a very brave child.
But I'm afraid the use of
force is out of the question.
[FUTOVA]
Don Kee is too powerful.
If we were to offer any
physical resistance,
the Don would send out his
army and ravage us all.
We have enough
hardships already.
We don't want to add bloodshed
of our loved ones to
the weight of our burden.
[WIFE]
But thank you for your concern.
You are very caring people.
I hope those nice people
can find a way to get
their problems sorted out.
Yeah, I do, too.
I don't feel right. I wish there
were something we could do
to help those people
get their house back.
Yeah, it's hard,
but every planet has
its share of problems.
If we tried to solve
them all ourselves,
it would take a lifetime.
And besides, if we don't find
the Dragon Balls in a year,
the Earth is going to have
far more serious
problems than high rent.
Hey, maybe there's a Dragon Ball
on this planet! You never know!
We haven't checked! Have we?
[TRUNKS] No, but I can
tell you there's not.
[PAN]
How do you know?! Check!
[TRUNKS]
If you insist.
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru...!
[GIRU]
Hmmm...
[slurps]
[gasps]
Without that radar our
whole mission is history!
[GIRU] Need energy!
Energy needed to function!
Daa, Daa, Daa, Daaaaa!
Giru! Now fully operational!
Why you! That's ours!
Give it back to us right now!
[GIRU] Not capable! Giru! Device
integrated into system!
Giru! Giru!
That's our Dragon Radar!
If we lose that, we can kiss
Earth and our families goodbye!
[GIRU] Already integrated!
Kiss goodbye!
What?!
--Giru! Giru...!
--Oh, no! Look!
[loud motor]
Hey! Come back here with that!
[GIRU] Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru!
Ahh! Man!
Darn! You get back here,
you little runt!
--Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
--Give me that!
--Giru! Giru! Giru!
--Oh, no you don't!
Pan! Heads up! Three o'clock!
[GIRU] Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru...!
--I got it!
[crash]
[GOKU]
Hey, guys!
Is this what you're looking for?
[GIRU] Giru.
Giru. Giru. Giru.
[PAN]
And there goes our ship.
They've got some nerve.
[TRUNKS] Unbelievable. This
just isn't our planet, guys.
That's all there is to it.
[NARRATOR] With the Dragon Radar
in the belly of a robot,
and their spaceship
disappearing over the horizon,
Trunks, Goku, and Pan
have a difficult road ahead.
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next GT!