Now that was embarrassing!
[NARRATOR]
On the last Dragon Ball GT!
[BABY] That's exactly
what I'm looking for,
the peak of your Saiyan power.
Ka...
Me...
Ha... Me... Ha!
[NARRATOR] After pushing
Goten to the peak of his power,
Baby used the moment to
infiltrate the Saiyan's body.
Then Baby started attacking,
using Goten's body
like a puppet.
[BABY] Now this is what I've
come to expect of Saiyan power.
This is the kind of
ability and control I need!
[NARRATOR] Baby has torn through
two Saiyans in one day.
But in the far reaches of space,
Goku, Trunks, and Pan are
wrapping up their journey.
However Goku cannot
shake his gut feeling.
[PAN] Soon, we'll be able
to go home, save the earth,
and live out our
lives as heroes.
It's not the Dragon Balls
I'm worried about.
Even though this
is the first time
you've been shopping
with me in a while,
we made quite a haul.
Don't you mean you
made quite a haul?
And I ended up
paying for everything.
Yeah, but that's
what dads are for.
You're just like your mother.
So you decided to take my
advice and shave. Good!
[VEGETA grunts]
Hey hot stuff, lookin' good!
[BULLA]
Thanks. It's a new outfit.
How 'bout you and your outfit
dump that geezer
and ride with us?
[BOYS] What was that?
What's your problem?
[BOYS whimpering]
[BOYS screaming]
[BOYS gasping]
Sorry, fellas! My dad's
got a bit of a temper
and he can get kind of grumpy
when he has to take me shopping.
But he knew you were kidding
about the 'geezer' comment!
Teenagers.
[CHI CHI]
Goten? Can you hear me?
[GOTEN groaning]
[BULMA]
He's got quite a fever!
What happened? He's never
been sick before...
He's never even had a cold.
[BABY GOHAN]
Vegeta...
Where are you going, Gohan?
[BABY GOHAN]
Out.
But we don't know what's
wrong with your brother.
She's right. We need
you to get a doctor.
We need you to help out your
little brother right now.
And then, he'll be better
and we can all
go out for dinner.
Hey, Gohan. Wait a second.
You've been acting weird.
What's your problem?
Let go!
[ALL gasping]
You're very close... Vegeta.
[CHI CHI sobbing]
Every time my husband
is away from home,
the only thing the kids can
think of are themselves!
Ah, Goku, what is
taking you so long?!
[GOKU sneezing]
Wow. It's really
cold in here.
Well, when we stopped
to buy jackets,
because Giru's radar said that
the Dragon Ball was on a planet
with a temperature of
272 degrees below zero,
you should have spent your money
on a jacket instead of food.
It's amazing that you're not
frozen like an icicle, Grandpa.
[GOKU laughing]
I'm fine. It's my eating
habits that keep me healthy.
[GOKU sneezes]
[TRUNKS groans]
[PAN] Grandpa, cover your
mouth when you sneeze!
[GOKU]
I'm sorry, but--
Achoo!
[PAN] That is sick! Will you at
least try and blow your nose?
Yes. Gohan's
Super Saiyan power
feels better than the last.
[BABY GOHAN chuckling]
The only one left is Vegeta.
[BULLA]
Mom is going to be so surprised
when she sees who
took me shopping.
I'm gonna have to
put on a fashion show
to show her all of my wonderful
new clothes you bought me!
[BULLA yelping]
Ow... Dad what are you doing?
You could really hurt someone
if you stop like that
without warning them first.
Gohan... why's he here?
[BULLA] Something about
Gohan doesn't look right.
Almost like he's here
to fight someone.
I think he is.
[BABY GOHAN yelling]
[BABY]
Just as I was hoping for!
Vegeta slipped past
one of Gohan's attacks
like it was nothing.
So, who are you?
Can't you tell,
Dad? It's Gohan.
You can spot him by
his nerdy clothes.
[BULLA]
But left his glasses at home.
Maybe that's why he
ruined all my new stuff!
[BULLA gasps]
Now, I'm mad at you!
And the last thing you want on
your case is a blue haired girl
who's shopping you've destroyed.
What is your problem?
All you're doing is standing
there like a silent idiot.
Normally, when nice people do
bad things they apologize.
[BABY] That must be
the Saiyan's daughter.
It would explain the attitude.
[BULLA screams]
Ow! Are you trying to kill me?!
[VEGETA]
Go home!
But, Dad?
[VEGETA] Do it, Bulla! I have
some business I need to handle.
[BULLA]
What about you?
I'll be fine. Now, stop
arguing and go home!
Fine, I'll leave.
But he better have enough money
to replace what he ruined!
Jerk, thinks he's so great.
[BABY]
Finally, the mightiest warrior.
Now, where's Gohan?
I know you're not him.
He's much faster.
Well... It's sad that
you've forgotten so much
after such a short time.
But that just goes to show you
no matter how much a
monkey evolves it's...
...still a monkey.
How is... your father?
What?
[BABY GOHAN] You're a fool,
just like your daddy.
It's predictable.
[BABY GOHAN]
Vegeta...
[VEGETA chuckling]
Finally, one of the
Tuffles returns...
You almost had me concerned.
Almost.
So, you finally
get it, monkeyboy.
Yes, I am a proud Tuffle
and I can finally take revenge
on you worthless Saiyans!
[BABY GOHAN yelling]
[GOTEN groaning]
[CHI CHI]
Goten, are you awake?
Oh, thank goodness!
You really had me worried.
Where's Valese?
The last thing that I remember
I was on a date with Valese
and there was this guy.
He had this weird voice and he
was telling me to fight for him.
You had a really
high fever, dear,
but you're doing
much better now!
[GOTEN]
Mother, that hurts.
I, could use a big glass of
ice water. I'm really thirsty.
Whatever you need,
dear. Anything else?
Maybe just not so
much on the hugging.
[GOTEN sighs]
[GOTEN groaning]
[GOTEN cackling]
[CHI CHI]
Goten, are you okay?
[BABY GOTEN]
I'm fine. I'm going out.
[CHI CHI]
What are you talking about?
You're in no shape
to be running around.
You need to get some rest!
[BABY GOTEN]
I'm leaving.
[CHI CHI]
You can't go!
You need to rest, please...
Back off!
Goten!
[CHI CHI sobbing]
Why are all of my
children delinquents?!
[BABY] Stay right where you
are, Saiyan. I'm on my way.
[BABY GOHAN yelling]
[BABY GOHAN]
Huh?
Poor Tuffle. Running
into vengeance
without a day of
training under your belt.
[BABY GOHAN] The training
I present here is Gohan's.
It should be sufficient.
[VEGETA groaning]
[BABY GOHAN cackling]
[BABY GOHAN yelling]
[VEGETA groaning]
Well, well... His body moves
in a very interesting way.
It's very fluid, but
not without structure.
[BABY GOHAN] And its
destructive force is unrivaled.
I can finally
appease my ancestors.
We Tuffles have waited
centuries for this day.
The time has come to
steal your body, Vegeta!
Enough games!
You're nothing but a loser,
like your ancestors.
King Vegeta threw your
people out for one reason--
Because they were unworthy!
[BABY GOHAN cackling]
Your monkey brain really
doesn't understand.
Our fight is not a
question of what you think.
It's a simple
matter of the math.
You're outnumbered, Vegeta.
Just because you're
inside a Saiyan body
doesn't mean I'm outnumbered.
Ha! But that means, to kill
one you must kill the other.
What a predicament.
If you raise your power high
enough to rid the world of evil,
you kill your
Saiyan friend's son.
[VEGETA]
And what makes you think
I have a problem with that?
[BABY GOHAN gasps]
[BOTH yell]
[VEGETA yelling]
Yes! That's it...
That's him...
That's just like Vegeta.
Raising his power every step,
never wanting to be equaled.
[VEGETA] How do you plan
on finishing me off?
You've done such a
great job beating me down.
[BABY GOHAN chuckling]
[GOTEN]
Hey, Vegeta!
I've come to the rescue!
[VEGETA] Don't butt in,
Goten. This is my catch.
You hear me?!
Wow. You're in a bad
mood today, aren't ya?
[GOTEN]
Wait.
You're not seriously going to
fight with my brother, are you?
We're brothers then.
Sounds about right.
Fly away, boy!
That's how it's gonna be!
I told you I was
coming to the rescue.
Sorry if you
thought I meant yours.
[BABY GOHAN laughing]
Nice job there, Goten.
Thank you.
Goten, not you, too?!
[BABY GOHAN chuckling]
[VEGETA yelping]
[VEGETA growling]
[BABY GOTEN]
Give up now, Vegeta.
You're fighting two Saiyans
and we're brothers.
Neither your strength
nor your ego
can come close to this power.
A smart fighter would take
this chance and go home.
[VEGETA]
We'll see about that.
[VEGETA yelling]
That's it, Vegeta. Get angry!
Push all of that hatred you
have built up inside you
to the surface and
reveal my victory!
[VEGETA yelling]
[BABY]
Now!
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA]
Ha! I'm the imbecile?
[BABY]
Yes, you are.
[VEGETA gasps]
Where are you? Show your
face, you filthy coward!
[BABY] I'm everywhere you
are, now. Inside you.
You're where?!
You would probably
call me a parasite,
but it's far more
complicated than that.
You see, I also control
you... You're my puppet...
You became a Tuffle without
ever knowing a thing.
You think you can control
me, you disgusting--
[BABY] Oh, I do control you.
Go ahead, try to move your body.
This is destiny.
This is the revenge
the Tuffles have sought
from the Saiyans for so long.
[BABY] My ancestral home
planet was actually
a peaceful and wealthy society
with a highly developed
scientific community.
It was you barbaric,
evil Saiyans who destroyed it,
burning through our
planet's resources
like they were dry wheat.
So you were kicked off your
own planet by the Saiyans.
[BABY] The unrefined killer
instinct in the Saiyans
rose to a deafening pitch
as the Tuffles were slain
all over their own
planet like insects.
And the being responsible
for this genocide was
none other than your
father, King Vegeta,
who, in his greatest
moment of arrogance,
renamed the planet
after himself.
Having been
pushed out of society,
we took what remaining
scientific knowledge we had
and used it to create
a genetically superior
parasitic organism.
Then our King Tuffle
combined his own DNA
with the genes
of the parasites,
and scattered
his creation across
the vast reaches of space.
And now some of us have made
it back to exact our revenge.
[VEGETA] That's you, not me!
You cannot control me!
I won't let you!
[BABY]
Unfortunately, foolish one,
that is no longer an option.
Once I'm in your blood,
my cells spread
immediately to the brain
for better control.
Right, Goten?
Right.
And when they reach your brain,
[BABY] your body starts
trembling uncontrollably,
just like right now.
Soon, you'll
understand everything.
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] You monster! I'll
show you what a Saiyan can do--
Go ahead. Show us.
[BABY] Now that I have all
of the Saiyan power I need,
I will start to spread my cells
through every living
being on this planet.
And when I'm finished here,
I will move on to the
rest of the universe.
All the while with
you, your friends
and your family as
my puppet slaves!
[BABY] I've won the fight
with the bully of the galaxy.
My ancestors would be so proud.
Now, the son of the man
who killed my people
will forever be part of me.
My plan to make Tuffles
of this entire planet
is finally in place.
But Vegeta...
Since it was your father who
pushed my people to this...
...I'll make sure to
kill you when I'm done.
[beeping]
Okay, guys, when we're
done, I need a jacket...
...or maybe a pelt.
Or maybe a microwave?
Put me on the stove.
[PAN] Where is it,
Giru?! If we don't hurry,
Grandpa's brain will freeze
right along with his body.
[GOKU yells]
[PAN]
Oh, no! Grandpa!
Goku!
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru!
Look what I found in the snow!
[BOTH laughing]
[PAN]
Yes!
[TRUNKS] You did it, Goku!
I can't believe it!
[GOKU]
Finally, we can go home!
And the first
thing I'm gonna do
is have some of Chi-Chi's
best homemade noodles!
Oh-yeah!
[NARRATOR]
Little do our heroes know that
while they plan a
glorious homecoming,
their near-forgotten enemy,
Baby has already initiated
his plan to turn all of
planet earth into Tuffles.
Will these three
find their way home
in time to save it from an
entirely different threat?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball GT!