[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
the mechanized juggernaut Luud
pushed the team to
the cusp of their abilities,
bending them nearly
to their breaking point.
[GOKU grunts]
[PAN inaudible]
[NARRATOR] And while
Goku found himself
in a rather tight situation,
Pan and Trunks were
able to devise a plan
that would free
all of those trapped
in the belly of Lord Luud.
[PAN shouts]
[LUUD groaning]
[BOTH shouting]
[LUUD moaning]
[ALL cheering]
[LUUD groaning]
[NARRATOR] While everyone
celebrated victory over
their giant captor,
danger continued
to simmer in the shadows.
What now lies blocking their
path towards the Dragon Balls?
What other tricks has
Dr. Myuu hidden up his sleeve?
Find out now on Dragon Ball GT!
[ship humming]
[food sizzling]
I think it needs
just a bit more garlic.
Hey, get your filthy hands out
of there! It's not ready yet!
[GIRU] Giru cannot analyze
the composition of this matter.
[GIRU] Structural similarities
to fertilizer detected.
Oh what do you know?
A stupid robot
insulting my cooking!
You don't even have
any taste buds, Giru!
[GIRU] Sorry Pan. Giru
only want to help. Giru.
[PAN grunts]
[PAN] Well, you should
learn that sometimes
it's best to keep
your mouth shut,
and that includes not
opening it to steal food.
What kind of robot
needs to eat, anyway?
[GIRU whimpering]
I wonder what
Dr. Myuu's like anyway?
Don't worry, Goku. I'm sure that
we'll find that out soon enough.
But I'll tell you
what I do know.
If we don't find
a way to stop him,
then he's going to destroy
the entire universe, okay?!
You don't have to yell.
[GIRU] Does not compute.
Giru only give advice. Giru.
Giru, Giru, Giru.
I do not need
any advice from you.
[TRUNKS] I've been thinking,
ever since we left Planet Gelbo,
Dr. Myuu and his minions have
anticipated our every move.
He probably expects us
to come right to him.
Maybe we should
stop back by Earth first.
Go back to Earth?
We could drop off Pan,
so she's safe, and bring Goten!
His power would help!
[PAN]
But I don't wanna go back.
Uh, Pan...
[GIRU groaning] Poultry egg not
constructed for throwing.
[PAN] Do you want to
take me home, Grandpa?
I'm staying out of this one.
Grandpa!
I'm sorry Pan, but you can't
go on this mission with us.
It's for your safety.
You understand this, don't you?
We don't want you hurt.
I can take care of myself.
[GIRU]
No.
Pan, wait.
[GIRU]
Giru go too.
Giru.
[ship humming]
[PAN] I know I could help,
if they'd take me with them.
Pan leaking. Giru.
I don't need your
tissue or your pity!
[GIRU whimpering]
Giru, Giru, Giru.
Please, please not hit Giru.
Giru, Giru.
Sorry. You're right. There's
no use taking it out on you.
[ship humming]
[GIRU]
But Pan still leaking.
Dragon Ball located.
[GIRU] Coordinates Green
Sector 2814! Giru!
I'll show 'em.
They'll let me stay,
if I find a Dragon Ball.
[GIRU humming]
Dragon Ball, Dragon Ball,
Giru find the Dragon Ball.
Giru, Giru, Giru! Giru!
[PAN nervous sigh]
[TRUNKS]
Oh, it's hot!
I'm melting.
How well does the air
conditioner work on the ship?
[TRUNKS]
I don't know. Let's go check.
Giru.
[GIRU]
D-d-d-d-d-danger! Giru, Giru.
Just our luck.
[PAN screams]
[GOKU, TRUNKS grunt]
[PAN whimpering]
Take this!
[PAN sniffling]
Next time you show up,
we won't go so easy on you.
[TRUNKS groans]
Hey, Goku!
[TRUNKS] I know you had a fun
time with that snake thing,
but it seriously damaged
our cooling system.
We'll have to
replenish the water tanks.
Water? We picked the wrong
planet to run out of that!
No joke!
But we can't just
leave the ship here
to get swallowed
by sand monsters.
Great! You go find water,
and I'll watch
for that creature.
[PAN groaning]
I can't take this heat.
When can we leave?
Is the ship fixed?
Watch out.
I was just trying to help you.
[TRUNKS]
I can handle this.
Just go play inside the
ship where it's safe.
Go play? Is that
all you think I can do?
I can help too, you know.
[GOKU] Hey, Pan!
Don't get in Trunks' way.
He's got work to do.
[PAN] What do you mean,
get in the way?!
[GOKU] If you're going to play,
play somewhere out of the way.
[PAN]
I can't believe this.
[GIRU]
Pan, what happened?
[pans clattering]
[GIRU]
Pan leave? Where?
That's none of your business.
Don't follow me.
[GIRU]
Pan?
Pan, don't go.
I'll show them that
I'm good for more than
just playing around
like a little girl.
But it's so hot. It makes it
hard to fly on this planet.
I'm going to find the
Dragon Ball all by myself!
[water sloshing]
[PAN]
Hey! Get back here!
[PAN yelping]
Giru.
Where are you off to, Giru?
[GIRU]
Giru worried, look for Pan.
Where's he going?
[PAN groaning]
I can't walk anymore.
I want to go back.
But wait. Which way is back?
[PAN whimpering]
I'm so lost.
Giru, Giru, Giru...
[GIRU] Don't worry Pan.
Giru come for you.
Giru.
Near miss. Danger. Danger.
Hostile creatures active.
Danger level rising. Must
save Pan. Danger level rising.
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
W-Water...
Please, I need water.
[DOLLTAKI] Dr. Myuu,
excuse the interruption,
but I, Dolltaki, have returned
with the most excellent of news
to report to you this day.
I'm sure that upon hearing it
you won't begrudge me
a minute of your time.
I hurried here to report that
those beings you discovered
are in possession
of a most amazing power.
If their power were
to be harnessed
and used to our benefit,
it would represent a force
far greater than that of Luud.
And I believe the
best means of doing so,
would be for me to use my
amazing powers of persuasion
to bring them over to
our side, and if we--
We require no more assistance
from you, Dolltaki.
General Rilldo.
Wh-why are you here?
I mean, where is Dr. Myuu?
That is no longer
of any concern to you.
[DOLLTAKI gasps] Well then,
I'll just be on my way.
[RILLDO]
Dolltaki!
Dr. Myuu did send you a message.
Drop dead.
My assignment is now
completed Dr. Myuu.
[RILLDO]
I await your further orders.
[DR. MYUU] I see you've wasted
no time, as usual General.
[RILLDO]
Thank you sir.
[DR. MYUU]
Now watch the monitor.
[DR. MYUU] You must obtain
the Dragon Ball from these boys.
And I wish for them to be
brought to me alive as well.
Do you understand?
They are in possession
of amazing power
that should be quite useful
to me in my research.
That is why they must
be brought to me alive.
I expect you to be a bit
more delicate than normal
in your operations, General.
Be careful, for these
are no mere boys.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru...
Pan in danger! Temperature 112
degrees Fahrenheit. Giru!
[GIRU whimpering]
Giru.
Giru?
Pan!
Canteen detected! Must be close!
Hang on Pan. Giru to the rescue!
Giru. Trail ends here.
[GOKU groaning]
[TRUNKS grunting]
Goku, would you mind playing
a little further from the ship?
Guess I should have asked him
to stop playing altogether.
Hey Pan, I got him. Wow.
This guy's crazy looking.
You should come check him out.
Hey Pan.
Pan, where are you?
[PAN groaning]
[PAN whimpering]
I really liked that umbrella.
I guess I'll buy another.
[PAN groaning]
Trunks, Grandpa, please help me.
[GIRU]
Danger! Danger! Pan, danger!
Giru?
Giru, did you come to save me?
[GIRU grunting]
Giru.
[GIRU whimpering]
Giru, Giru, Giru.
Giru, I'm sorry I picked on you.
[GIRU groaning]
Don't worry Pan. Giru.
Thank you... Giru.
[PAN]
Where am I?
Mama! Papa! Gramps!
Trunks! Grandpa!
I'm sorry... that I ran away.
[PAN grunting]
[PAN]
Giru.
[GIRU]
Pan needs water, drink.
Giru, did you do that?
[GIRU] Giru discovered Dragon
Ball as well. Recovery complete.
[PAN] Giru!
[GIRU whimpering]
[PAN] Oh, I'm so sorry for
ever being mean to you.
[PAN sniffling]
[GIRU sighs]
[GOKU]
Hey, Pan!
Was that Grandpa? Grandpa!
[GOKU laughing]
[PAN] I sure got myself
into a big mess.
[TRUNKS] I think you handled
yourself rather well.
I mean it!
You managed to find us
a Dragon Ball and an oasis.
[PAN]
But Giru did that.
[TRUNKS]
Without you though, Pan,
we would've never come
to this part of the desert.
Right, Giru?
[GIRU]
Right Trunks.
Pan, listen. I hope you can
forgive me for suggesting
that we take you back
to Earth and drop you off.
You're just as much a part
of this team as anyone.
Does that mean I can stay
with you and Grandpa?
Well of course, because
the four of us are a team,
and a team is reduced to nothing
without all of its players.
[GIRU]
Yeah!
[PAN whimpering]
[GOKU laughing]
[PAN, TRUNKS shouting]
Grandpa! That's it!
You're gonna get it!
[TRUNKS laughing]
Turned out to be a pretty
good day, after all.
Objectives complete.
Plus Pan friend now. Giru safe.
[PAN]
I'm have your toe, Grandpa.
[GOKU]
Can't catch me!
[PAN]
Just you wait.
[ALL laughing]
[NARRATOR] Goku and his team
strengthened their alliance
in the face of great danger
on the desert planet.
And they even managed
to find a Dragon Ball
among the endlessly
shifting sands of the dunes.
But the weary warriors
can't let their guard down,
for the evil Dr. Myuu
has not given up,
and his creation,
the indomitable General Rilldo,
is bearing down on
the group with great speed.
Will our heroes be able
to evade his iron grip?
Find out on
the next Dragon Ball GT.