[NARRATOR] It was the day of
the dragon on the last GT,
as seven evil dragons made
off with the Dragon Balls!
[PAN] They're gone!
What are we gonna do? No!
[NARRATOR]
Before they had time to act,
Old Kai delivered
an urgent warning.
[OLD KAI]
Now you listen here!
[OLD KAI] I'm afraid you don't
have much time to act, Goku.
That dragon is attacking the
nerve centers of the globe.
If you don't intervene soon,
the destruction of
the Earth is inevitable!
[NARRATOR] The race was on! Goku
tried to set off on his own,
but much to his dismay,
Pan conned her way
into joining him!
[GIRU]
Dragon Ball nearby! Giru!
[NARRATOR] The two-star ball
was indeed nearby...
[HAZE SHENRON]
Now your lives belong to me!
[NARRATOR]
...in the form of Haze Shenron,
the Dragon of Pollution!
[HAZE SHENRON] You creep!
Do you know who I am?
You'll die for that!
[NARRATOR]
It soon became apparent
that Haze Shenron
did not possess
any awesome physical strength!
Will this be an easy
victory for Pan and Goku,
or does Haze know something
that our heroes don't?
[PAN]
Grandpa, tell me.
Is this the terrible,
evil dragon? Please say no.
Well, he's definitely
different than the one we saw.
[HAZE SHENRON] Kicking a
Shadow Dragon in the head
is not a wise thing to do!
I know all about you, Goku!
And a power such as yours
is no match for the
great Haze Shenron!
Uh, Sir, with all due respect,
you don't seem
that strong to me.
Oh, is that so?
Well, I've been watching you
for many years, and frankly,
you don't know what you're
getting yourself into!
We don't?
What's this we stuff?
I wasn't talking to you,
you silly little girl!
Big, bad Pan!
Don't hurt me, please!
I'll never laugh at
your bandana again!
What are you gonna do?
Dress me up like a baby doll?
He's mine, Grandpa! Stay back!
[PAN yelling]
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
[HAZE SHENRON growling]
So, that was the great
Haze Shenron, huh?
Don't you remember?
Please, don't hurt me,
Pan! Please!
You'd better mean it
when you beg me for mercy!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
So, you think the
battle's over, do ya?
[PAN]
Well, that's up to you!
I can keep kicking you around
or you can just hand over the
Dragon Ball and call it quits!
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
You can't scare me with
your overgrown belly!
Pan! Be careful!
He could be more
dangerous than he looks!
[PAN yelling]
[PAN gasps]
Don't be deceived by his
current power level, Pan!
I think he's getting ready
to undergo some sort
of transformation!
There's no way a Shadow Dragon
could be this weak!
[PAN] So, he's just been
playing games with us?
[GOKU]
I'd be willing to bet on it!
Well, get on with it!
What are you waiting for?
[PAN] I'll take you any
which way you please,
so stop wasting my
time and transform!
I want to see your true power
and nothing less, Haze Shenron!
I'm ready!
What? You're ready? Come on!
I am!
[GOKU]
Pan, be careful.
[GIRU] Pan! Danger!
Danger! Energy increase!
Some dragons transform...
...but not me.
[GOKU laughing]
Well uh, I guess you learn
something new every day.
It's not funny, Grandpa!
You said he was
gonna transform
and I thought you were
the dragon expert.
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
[GOKU] Sorry, Pan,
my bad! I had no idea!
Oh, Grandpa, you're hopeless!
You think everything's funny.
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[HAZE SHENRON]
So what if I can't transform!
That doesn't matter!
Transformation is a cheap trick
that cowards use when
they're desperate!
True warriors like me
have no need for gimmicks!
Wow! Amazing! A true warrior!
[PAN grunting]
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
[PAN]
Take this Mr. True Warrior!
Oh man, I don't think I've
ever seen her like this before.
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
[PAN]
That'll teach him some manners!
Maybe he'll think twice about
making light of a
young girl on a mission!
Well, where do we go
from here, Haze Shenron?
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
[PAN] Why don't you be a
good dragon and hand over
the Dragon Ball so I don't
have to get ugly again!
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
Why should I stop now,
just when the fight's
about to get interesting?
Hey, that's strange.
For someone as weak as him,
he sure took a good beating.
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
I don't know, Giru.
I'm having a real hard
time figuring this guy out!
[PAN] Look! Just give
us the Dragon Ball!
You'll be saving yourself
a whole lot of pain!
Is that so?
[HAZE SHENRON yells]
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[HAZE SHENRON gasps]
[PAN]
Looking for someone?
[PAN yells]
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
Huh? Maybe he's not
that strong after all.
Well, I guess that
takes care of that!
Yeah, I guess so.
He sure was peculiar.
[GOKU] Well, you've got
to give him credit,
he's not very strong, but
he's definitely determined.
Alright! That's it!
Hand over the Dragon Ball or
you're really gonna get it!
I wasn't born yesterday!
Actually, I was born today,
but I still know why you
want the Dragon Balls!
Yeah?
It's simple!
You want to wish for the things
you obviously don't have!
[HAZE SHENRON]
Good taste! Clothes that fit!
A little height!
Man, you just don't know when
to quit! Well, I've had enough!
[PAN grunting]
[HAZE SHENRON groaning]
How dare you,
you giant tub of lard!
Take that! Take that!
Uh... I'm worried, Giru. Look.
Something's just not right.
[GIRU]
Yes! Not right!
[PAN yells]
[HAZE SHENRON groans]
[PAN panting]
Well then, did I knock
some sense into ya,
or do you want more?
[GOKU]
He's perfectly composed,
like that beating didn't
affect him at all.
But Pan's too proud to
see it. She's already tired.
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
So, that's it, huh?
You do want more!
All right, then!
Have it your way!
[PAN yelling]
[PAN grunting]
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
You're really
asking for it, Dragon!
[GOKU]
It's no good!
He just keeps getting
stronger and stronger!
[GOKU]
Pan! No! It's not working!
Oh, it's working!
He's making me so mad
that I'm gonna beat him
to a fat, green, pulp!
Put 'em up, dragon!
[GOKU gasps]
No way!
What do you mean?
This is how it always works!
I, the star,
take a good beating,
and then I muster
uncommon strength and win!
[HAZE SHENRON grunts]
[PAN groans]
Pan!
He dodged me!
I don't believe it!
Believe it! No one defeats
the great Haze Shenron!
Round and round you go!
Where you land, nobody knows!
[PAN, GOKU screaming]
[PAN, GOKU groaning]
[HAZE SHENRON grunts]
It's a heavy burden for two
children to face Haze Shenron!
Oh, yeah? Not as heavy
as you think, Haze!
[PAN]
Now where'd he go?
[PAN] Let go of me right
now! Do you hear me?
Put me down this
instant! Let go!
Oh, gosh! What's wrong with me?
Pan! Hold on!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[HAZE SHENRON] Don't worry, Haze
Shenron is not a cruel dragon!
I can't stand to see suffering!
I'm going to end this quickly!
I'll just eat you up!
[PAN] Huh? No, don't you dare!
I don't want to be eaten!
That's disgusting!
Let go of me right now!
No! Stop!
How weird! That's
never happened before!
Whoa! What's going on?
[HAZE SHENRON]
It's no use! You can't power up!
[GOKU]
What d'ya mean?
[HAZE SHENRON] Look! Look at my
beautiful lake! Isn't it lovely?
[GOKU sniffs]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU] How gross! It smells
like rotten lunch!
This is really disgusting!
Don't be bashful!
I know it's inviting!
Take a dip if you like!
[HAZE SHENRON] I poisoned
it myself! It's my gift!
And it's a gift
that keeps giving!
The vapors from the
lake poison the air,
and then the air poisons
the trees and vegetation!
It's a beautiful synergy
of death and destruction!
There is no more life in
the air to draw energy from!
You two are like
the fish in the lake!
Now I get it! Your energy
hasn't increased a bit!
You're not getting any stronger!
We're getting weaker!
Ah! Yes, now you understand the
secret of my power! Very astute!
[GOKU] Hey! That's no way
to fight! It's not fair!
[HAZE SHENRON] You're the
one who created me, Goku!
So deal with it!
What are you talking about?
That's a big, fat lie!
My Grandpa never even
met you until today!
There's no way!
Goku, do you remember your dear
sweet childhood friend, Upa?
Huh? Upa?
[HAZE SHENRON]
Ah, yes. You remember.
His father was killed
by Mercenary Tao.
[GOKU]
Eternal Dragon! I have a wish!
[HAZE SHENRON] You took pity
on Upa and you summoned
my predecessor, the
mighty Eternal Dragon!
When the dragon granted your
wish and restored Bora to life,
a vast amount of negative energy
was introduced into the world
and concealed inside
the Two Star Ball.
You had no idea that this
energy existed, but I did.
I was born from it!
Oh, no! If what you say is true,
then I really am responsible
for bringing you into the world!
Don't look so horrified, Goku!
You should be honored!
[BOTH groaning]
Being this weak really hurts!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[GOKU] I wouldn't be
laughing if I were you!
I'll figure out a
way to beat you!
I am not going to let
you poison the Earth!
Why not? Humankind is doing that
on its own anyway, isn't it?
I'm only going to
speed up the process
and kill the Earth
more efficiently!
[HAZE SHENRON] Polluting the
planet is my sole reason to be.
My poison is unstoppable!
It spreads like a disease,
sucking the life
out of creation!
Let it live, so
that all may perish!
[BOTH groaning]
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
What do you think of
Haze Shenron now?
[HAZE SHENRON]
Do you still think I'm weak?
Definitely! Your evil deeds are
the poison that makes you weak!
Well, a philosopher!
What d'ya know!
Perhaps you'll better
understand the depth of my power
at the bottom of the lake!
[PAN]
Hey! Cut it out!
Don't you dare put us
in that nasty lake!
[HAZE SHENRON] Don't worry, you
won't have to put up with it
for very long!
The acid and pollution
are so bad in here
that you'll be stripped to your
bones in a matter of minutes!
No! I don't want to
die in that filth!
Grandpa, do something!
Be strong, Pan!
We can't allow ourselves to lose
hope or we won't have a chance!
[HAZE SHENRON] Hope! Do you
see any hope in that lake?
Don't be a fool!
You're finished!
[PAN]
No!
[GIRU] Direct hit!
Direct hit! Giru! Giru!
Giru!
I'm still here.
[GIRU] Uh, oh! Zero damage!
Zero damage! Giru!
[HAZE SHINRON] You're not
affected by my pollution
because you're a machine!
So before we fight I
have to ask you one thing!
[GIRU groans]
Giru!
I wouldn't be too worried
about him if I were you!
I'd be worried about myself!
[PAN screams]
Pan! No!
[HAZE SHINRON]
So long! It's been fun!
[PAN] Grandpa! You said not to
lose hope. I'm trying real hard.
Mom, Dad, I need you!
Trunks, Uncle Goten, please!
Even Gramps would be a
big help at this point!
Why is this happening to me?
Where are you, Grandpa?
I know you're down
here somewhere.
I'm scared! I love everyone
so much! I'm not ready to die!
I'm moving!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
Giru! Giru!
[GIRU] Zero pollution.
No poison. Water clean.
[PAN coughing]
[GIRU]
Pan cough. Is Pan okay?
[PAN]
You have no idea how okay I am!
Giru, Grandpa! Go find
my grandpa! Hurry!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
Losers! Serves you right!
[HAZE SHENRON]
You had the nerve to call
the great Haze Shenron weak!
But who's weak now? You're
nothing but pond scum!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[GOKU coughing]
[PAN] Grandpa, I'm trying
to speak telepathically.
Can you hear me?
Hi, Grandpa!
[GOKU]
Pan! Giru!
This is weird. The lake was
pitch black when he threw us in.
Why is the water so clean?
And how are we breathing?
[PAN]
I'm not sure.
[GIRU] Living water! Giru
find magic living water!
[PAN] An underground spring.
That's why the water's so clear.
Let's blast it.
[GOKU]
Let's what?
[PAN]
If we blast it here,
the spring will flood
the lake with fresh water!
[GOKU]
It's worth a shot!
[PAN] Go for it, Grandpa.
I hope this works.
Ha!
[HAZE SHENRON cackling]
[HAZE SHENRON]
Their meat is falling off
their bones by now!
No more little pests!
Now nothing can stop me
from spreading my poison
across the Earth!
I have to admit, Haze Shenron,
you're a genius!
What? Something's moving?
That's impossible!
Everything's dead down there!
[HAZE SHENRON] Fresh water?
No! How can this be?
[GOKU]
Hey, dragon!
But, you should be dead!
It seems there was a little
life left in your lake!
That's right!
Fresh spring water, Haze!
Without it, we would
have been dead,
just like you're
going to be now!
[GOKU yelling]
[PAN yelling]
[HAZE SHENRON whimpering]
[BOTH]
Ha!
[HAZE SHENRON screaming]
[GOKU]
I think that did it! Alright!
[GOKU] Pan, look! The sky's
turning back to normal again!
[PAN] Awesome! Maybe the Dragon
Ball will go back to normal too!
Or maybe not.
[GOKU]
No, wait a second! Look!
[BOTH laughing]
No! Not the lake!
Well, have a nice swim.
What? Why do I have to go?
Why? Get real. Because!
I'm not going in that filthy,
stinking water again!
[GOKU] Hey! I was down
in that lake too,
and I don't want to go
back any more than you!
Well that's too bad!
I guess we'll just leave
the Dragon Ball here then
'cause I'm not going!
Me neither!
You dropped it!
[GIRU]
Giru!
Giru! Giru!
[BOTH]
Giru.
[PAN]
He's got the Dragon Ball!
Way to go, Giru!
You're incredible!
[GIRU]
Giru! Giru!
Wow, Giru! You're
braver than Grandpa!
Thanks.
[PAN] It's healthy and shiny
again! One down and six to go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR] With the Two Star
Ball in their possession,
things are looking
a little brighter!
But with six evil
dragons on the loose,
the fate of the Earth is
still in the balance!
What strange powers do
these dark dragons possess?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!