[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
The sinister robot Baby
moved from victim to victim
as he continued his
search for the Saiyans.
Sound good? I'd like to use
it to defeat your father.
Hey, what's so funny?
I must have missed something.
[NARRATOR]
With Goten before him,
Baby's first true battle
with a Saiyan is at hand.
Can Goten put up
the kind of fight
it will take to stop
this evil entity
from taking over
his body as well?
Find out right now
on Dragon Ball GT!
Hm... Ok, so you're tough.
But I'd hardly call
you a great fighter.
What?!
[cellphone ringing]
Hello, this is Goten...
I'm kinda busy right now.
Goten it's me.
You're not hurt are you?
Oh... Valese, it's you.
No, I'm fine. Haven't
even broken a sweat yet.
It's really not as bad as
it might look from down there.
If you wanna hang
around for a few minutes
while I wrap this up,
I'd love to finish our date.
Goten, look out!
He's coming right for you!
What? Oh--
[VALESE]
Get out of there!
[BABY thinking]
Hmph... Saiyan power.
This one isn't even half
as strong as I expected.
That's embarrassing!
You should really try harder
to back up your mouth.
Goten, are you there?!
That was so cool. I never
expected that from you.
It runs in the family...
You know, the whole idea
of protecting the innocent.
Yeah... That's my boy!
Spoken like a true
champ, Goten!
You sure have learned
a lot from me!
Goten, did he get you?!
Uh, no. It's just a scratch.
Nothing to worry about.
I'll talk to you in a bit, okay?
Now that was embarrassing...
You'll pay for that!
[GOTEN yells]
[BABY] Yes, that's exactly
what I'm looking for--
the peak of your Saiyan power.
Wow... What's happening to him?
He looks like a beautiful angel.
I think I'm in love.
Hiya! Hiya! Hiya! Hiya!
And that's that.
[BABY] Is that as high as your
puny Saiyan powers can reach?
[GOTEN]
Ka...
Me... Ha...
Me...
[BABY]
That's it...
Just release this
one blast of energy,
and your physical
power will top out.
And at that moment
the chance for me to transfer
to your body will be at hand.
Ha!!
Now!
[BABY as GOTEN]
This energy feels so rich.
Finally, the Saiyan power
I've been aching for is mine!
I may have failed with Trunks,
but today I've
grasped my destiny!
[BABY as GOTEN yells]
Wow... That was cool.
Uh, did you see
what happened?
Goten, you're okay!
Anybody see where
that baby-doll-looking
freak ran off to?
This... is the best date ever.
[BABY as GOTEN growls]
Oh... she' s yours.
Obviously, you're a
strong enough young man
that we don't have
to call off our date
for a little scratch, right?
There you go... So, what do you
say we get something to eat?
Are you okay?
[BABY as GOTEN thinking]
This is amazing.
Through the eyes of Goten,
I can see everything in
this world so clearly.
Ah, there are
Saiyans in West City.
But more importantly...
Who is the strongest
of them all?
Vegeta.
Yeah... That was
one heck of a job...
Hey, don't be mad at me 'cause
I was holding onto your girl.
I was just hiding behind her
'cause I was a little scared.
Let me, scratch that.
Wow, what a temper... Maybe
my training was too aggressive.
Wait, where are you going?
What about me?
He... doesn't seem like himself.
Of course not.
Now, he's mysterious...
It weighs heavy on his soul
that he had to destroy
another creature.
Vegeta...
If I acquire his Saiyan power
then my strength will surpass
both Trunks and Goku.
Soon the universe will bow
when they hear the name Baby!
Dragon Ball detected...
[TRUNKS] Looks like the Dragon
Ball is somewhere in this lake.
[PAN]
How deep is it?
[GOKU] Just leave
the swimming part up to me.
[ALL yell]
[TRUNKS]
The reaction is emanating
from inside that lizard!
[PAN] You've gotta
be kidding me!
[GOKU grunting]
Grandpa, get down!
[GOKU grimacing]
That should do it.
[TRUNKS] Ah, Goku
are you crazy?!
[PAN] Give me back my grandpa,
you creep! Spit him out!
Spit, like this, bleh! Spit!
[DRAGON roars]
[DRAGON yells]
[GOKU laughs]
[air whooshes out]
[DRAGON whimpers]
And I present to you
the sixth Dragon Ball!
[PAN] I'm really sorry.
My grandpa didn't
mean to hurt you.
I hope that
bandage works.
I liked it when
he was bigger.
Grandpa...
[ALL laughing]
[DRAGON crying]
One... more... Yes!
That's right...
Just one more to go!
Why are you looking
so glum, Grandpa?
Soon, we'll be able to
go home, save the earth,
and live out our
days as heroes.
I'm not worried
about the Dragon Balls.
It's... Baby...
I was positive he would come
after us but he hasn't...
I'm wondering if we
really got rid of him
or if he's hiding somewhere
while we get comfortable.
You're right.
There's an eerie feeling here,
like the calm that always
comes right before the storm.
Stop worrying... He put up
his best fight, but we won.
It's that simple.
But maybe too simple.
Imbalance...
There is a disturbance
in the earth's spirit.
[CHICHI]
He's late!
He's too late!
[BULMA] Relax, ChiChi.
He's just on a date, isn't he?
[VALESE] Yeah... But she prances
around like she's so innocent...
I'm not stupid. I know exactly
what kind of girl that is.
Goten is an adult now.
Maybe you should let him be one.
[phone ringing]
Bulma speaking.
A visitor in the front lobby?
Okay, we'll send someone
right down. ChiChi--
Now where did
she run off to so fast?
[CHICHI]
Goten, Goten, Goten...
Uh... Mother?
Oh, it's you, Gohan.
Hello Bulma.
Well... look who
stopped by for a visit!
Dad called me not too long ago.
I need an aspirin.
There was some kind of
a fight in West City.
And it appears Goten got
dragged into it somehow.
[CHICHI spits out water]
[CHICHI coughs]
Did somebody hurt my Goten?
[VIDEL] It was
just a scratch.
Gohan... I want you
to find your brother
and bring him back to me.
I swear, I warned him about
going out with that girl!
Hey... don't get
so worked up...
I'm sure Goten will
call you when he can...
So... Which room can
I drop my things in?
You go ahead and pick
whichever room you like best.
Doesn't anybody
care about my son?
Are you alright?
Goten?
You... You're home!
I'm so glad you're okay!
[BABY as GOTEN thinking] This
must be the one he calls mother.
So you did get
hurt out there!
Get away from me!
Then... are you hungry?
Vegeta...
Tell me where Vegeta is.
[BABY as GOTEN thinking]
So the mother is a fighter, too.
How dare you walk in
here and act like that?
You show some respect...
Do you hear me?!
[BABY as GOTEN thinking] What
an overwhelming personality.
She may be physically
weaker than the others,
but in Goten's mind she is
more important than anything.
Perhaps her powers are
hidden deep inside her.
Are you listening? You answer
me when I'm talking to you!
Perhaps it is best for me
to abide by the customs of
this planet until I find Vegeta.
So where is Vegeta?
Tell me now.
[CHICHI]
What is wrong with you?!
Didn't I teach
you any manners?
Will someone please
tell me where he is?
Well...
You know Vegeta...
He runs off all the time
without telling anyone
where he's going...
Why don't you just wait
around for him to show up?
[BABY as GOTEN thinking]
Oh, just perfect.
[GOHAN] Goten, you're back.
How'd it go?
[BABY as GOTEN thinking]
Who is this?
I sense more power in
him than in Goten.
Perhaps I should transfer
myself over to his body
so I can better acquire Vegeta.
What's wrong?
Did your date not go off
as well as you wanted it to?
What did you do that for?
Well...
You're the one who walked in
and started making fun of me!
Can't you take it?
I can take it. Even though
you're acting like a baby.
Shut up!
You two are together
five seconds
and you're fighting again!
Can't my house have some peace
and quiet just for once?
Take it outside!
Fine... Let's go then.
I'm ready when you are.
I hope they don't
hurt each other.
This kind of sibling rivalry
just proves their
love for each other.
Gohan... are you sure
your brother is okay?
He gets like this.
Would you mind holding this for
me? I won't be gone too long.
I'll be waiting.
Goten... Follow me!
My mother can overreact some,
which is why I didn't
say anything earlier...
So what have you
done with my brother?
You Saiyans are perceptive
little snots, aren't you?
Wait... The force of
that was much too weak.
I wonder if he's holding
some of his power back.
[GOHAN]
Tell me who you are!
[BABY as GOTEN] This "Gohan"
has the kind of body
that can stand up
to brutal attacks.
That is exactly
the type of vessel I need.
I can't stay here
and fight this guy.
That's Goten's body,
but some kind of being
has gotten inside
and possessed him.
So if I attack him and win, then
I'll be killing my own brother.
Ready?!
Wow, I did it--
There's something
different about this Saiyan.
Does he know somehow
that I wait for the moment
that they power-up
before I make my move?
Is that why he's
waiting to attack?
I have to stop this.
But how do I save Goten?
Or is he simply a coward?
I can't fight him... I have
to... think of something...
He's dead set on hiding
that Saiyan power of his
until I dig it out.
Which is precisely
what I intend to do.
Come on, Gohan... You...
...need to show me what a true
Saiyan warrior is capable of--
No! Goten, stop him...
He'll kill us all!
[BABY as GOTEN yells]
Listen to me Goten!
He'll destroy everything!
[BABY as GOTEN screams]
Finally, the power
I've been waiting for...
Now this is what I've come
to expect of Saiyan power.
This is the kind of
ability and control I need!
You're a parasite...
You've lived off of my friends'
bodies long enough....
Show yourself.
The Namekian, Piccolo.
One of the most brilliant
fighters in the galaxy...
I would say you're the perfect
candidate on which I can...
...try out my new skills.
What do you say?
Fine.
Ka... Me... Ha... Me... Ha!!
[[BABY as GOTEN yells]
This is becoming
disappointingly easy.
Two Saiyans and
one Namekian down.
Now all I have to do is
find the one and only Vegeta.
That is where the true power is.
[NARRATOR] With Goten and
Piccolo out of commission,
Baby continues
his hunt for Vegeta.
Can the Saiyan Prince
stop the powerful
mutant's escalating terror,
or will he be the next to fall?
Find out on
the next Dragon Ball GT!