[NARRATOR] In the face of Omega
Shenron's overwhelming power,
it appeared that Goku
had finally fallen
at the hands of
the last Shadow Dragon.
But from under this
blanket of despair,
a miracle suddenly
revealed itself.
Hey wait!
I thought I killed you!
[GOKU] Everybody!
Give me all of your energy!
Impossible, how did he do that?
This is it!
No, No! Hold on!
[GOKU yells]
[OMEGA SHENRON gasps]
[NARRATOR] Following Goku's
defeat of Omega Shenron,
the Eternal Dragon himself
appeared of his own free will.
What reasons does Shenron
have for this sudden visit?
Find out now, on the final
episode of Dragon Ball GT!
[SHENRON growls]
So Shenron appears before us
without being summoned?
That's never happened before.
I mean, I've never heard of him
doing this kind of thing.
Yeah, and doesn't the sky
usually cloud up and turn dark?
[SHENRON]
Now, arise, Goku.
Goku, you're alive!
Shenron? You're here?
So, all of the Shadow
Dragons are gone.
Yes. But do you know why they
ever had to appear at all?
Kind of...
The Dragon Balls were overused.
Following the barrage of
enemies from your past,
a final wish was made
causing the balls to crack
under the pressure of
their negative energy.
The Dragon Balls
were intended to be
a thing of extraordinary
magic and power.
Something to be revered, not
for the ease of their method,
but for the dream of
never having to use them.
I am afraid now
I must separate myself
and all of Earth from the
Dragon Balls for a long time.
I gotcha, but I was wondering
if, for old times sake,
you wouldn't mind listening
to just one more
little request I have.
One last time.
After the hole to
hell was opened,
the Earth had
no time to recover
before the Shadow Dragons
started destroying even more.
So many people have died.
If this is
anyone's fault, it's mine.
I take full responsibility.
I just wish that
the people of the world
didn't have to die for nothing.
The fight was never
theirs to win or lose,
but they all lost anyway.
[HERCULE whimpers]
This, your final wish,
is granted.
Pan!
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
Giru hey!
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru...!
Pan, danger. Pan, danger.
Giru like Pan and danger.
Thank you, Shenron.
[SHENRON] The time has come.
I must say goodbye.
Do you mean you're
leaving us for good now?
Are you coming along, Goku?
Should have known
it would end this way.
Wait, Kakkarot!
Where are you going?
You're going to train, alone!
They're in your hands now.
Goodbye, everyone!
Goku, you're crazy.
You don't even know
where he's taking you!
It's been a long ride,
a lot of years.
I must have only been sixteen
when I first went looking
for the Dragon Balls
and stumbled into Goku.
The decades have
certainly seemed to fly by.
I'm gonna miss that guy.
Hey Shenron...
Before we get on our way,
there's a couple of guys
I'd like to stop in and see.
I love it when I get
someone else's mail.
I don't have to pay for these.
Keeping those magazines
is the same thing
as stealing, ya know.
I don't see that keeping
you from reading them!
[yells]
I heard some turtles like me
can live a thousand years.
So, why're you
telling me this?
You're not even
close to that old.
I'm just trying to
change the subject.
Hey, look! It's Goku!
Yeah, right.
That would be funny.
Isn't he dead?
No, really, it's him!
I think the old man has
finally lost his mind.
Hey, guys!
Goku, you're alive!
I'd thought you'd
been killed for sure!
Or was I the one killed
and brought back to life?
[GOKU laughs]
You along with the rest
of the people on Earth.
It's so great to see you
guys again, I missed you.
You missed me? Aww...
So, you're still a kid, huh?
Yeah, but I won't mind it
when I'm an adult again.
The three of us here together
reminds me of old times.
Brings back a lot
of fun memories.
I remember we
had a bet one time.
We were supposed to
find a rock like this one
with a turtle on its back
and bring it back here.
Oh yeah, and the loser
had to go without dinner.
That's the worst way
to lose for me.
You and Master Roshi are
the only people I know
who haven't changed one bit
in all the years that
we've been friends.
I guess some people
never get old.
Unfortunately,
I'm not one of them.
Then let's fight.
I bet that will make
you feel young again.
Oh, yeah, right.
I'm old and you're still a kid.
It's hardly even.
You're gonna say no?
Okay, just don't
make me look too stupid.
Those boys'll never change.
You're old,
but you're still fast...
...and you still
pack quite a punch.
Nah, you're the better fighter.
I just have you beaten
hands down in good looks.
Huh? Goku?
Goku, where did you run off to?
Hey! Where'd you go?!
Tell Shenron thanks
for the Dragon Balls, Goku.
And I hope your journey
brings you back home someday.
Which one can I eat first?
[yelling]
They have a saying on Earth.
They say that the weakest
dogs bark the loudest.
Wow, thank you Mr. Green!
[cheering]
Why are you here?
[GOKU] You did real
well with that guy!
I asked what
you are doing here?!
Please tell me you
haven't died again.
Do you have any idea
what I had to go through
to send you back to Earth?
What are you doing?
I just came to say goodbye.
Well then, so be it.
You've always been there
for me when I've needed help.
You'll always be one
of my best friends.
Someday, you'll get out
of here, Piccolo. I promise.
What?
Farewell, old friend.
Hey, Goku! Are you gonna be
home by dinner time tonight?
Well, I had planned on making
a nice dinner just for him,
but I guess it's
take out food now.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm sure he'll come back
if you're gonna cook dinner.
Just what were you planning
on making, by the way?
[CHICHI] Tonight we're
having roasted Paoz shish kabob
with horncrammy taters!
[GOHAN] Alright!
That's my favorite!
Well, I guess it's time
we got going too.
Take care, everyone.
I'm heading back home.
Hey, Ma. Come on!
I'll help you get dinner
started back at the house!
Dad, why don't you come over
to our house for dinner tonight?
We'd love to have you.
[HERCULE]
That sounds wonderful.
What's up, Pan?
I'm just wondering...
Is what Shenron said true?
Are we ever gonna see
the Dragon Balls again?
It's up to us to make sure
we don't ever need them again.
So from now on, we're gonna have
to focus all of our energy
on preventing problems
rather than relying on
the Dragon Balls to solve them.
Once we are capable of that,
I have no doubt in my mind
that the Dragon Balls
will appear once again.
Smart thinking, Trunks!
I bet you're right!
Alright then.
We better get home!
It's about time!
Wait a sec...
These look like the same
clothes Grandpa was wearing
before he went off with Shenron.
They are.
Take good care of those, Pan.
I'll miss you.
You know, Shenron,
I've never been this tired.
[SHENRON roars]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Today at the World
Martial Arts Tournament
you will witness the final
bout in the junior division!
Let's go!
Oh yeah!
First, Goku Jr.!
I know what you're all thinking!
He's a dead ringer for the Goku
in the statue perched above us!
Your assumptions
happen to be correct!
Goku Jr. is the
great-great-grandchild
of the Legendary Goku,
who fought in this very
arena many years ago!
And in the audience,
we are proud to welcome Pan,
who is herself the Grandchild
of the World's Hero, Mr. Satan!
Mrs. Pan, what is
he talking about?
Is what he said really true?
It's true. Are you surprised?
Well, yeah!
Of course I'm surprised!
You're related to Mr. Satan,
the world's hero?!
And you're related to Goku, too?
I have more crazy relatives than
I'll ever know what to do with,
and they're all heroes.
[GOKU JR exhales]
Focus... Focus... Focus.
[VEGETA] Ew!
What are you wearing, rags?
They're not rags, Vegeta!
They happen to be the fighting
clothes of my great ancestor!
They're just
a bit aged, that's all!
[PAN thinking] Whoa!
That kid looks just like Vegeta!
This is turning into
a quite a little reunion!
Excuse me.
You're Goku Jr.'s mother, right?
Because he's about
to fight my son.
Aren't you a little old?
What's wrong with being old?
And I'm not his mother,
you nitwit! I'm his grandmother!
Sorry about that.
It makes sense though.
I can't wait to
watch this battle!
It'll be a good fight, but I'm
certain my Vegeta will win it.
[phone ringing]
Madame President.
The meeting is about to start.
We need you back immediately.
Not right now! My son
just walked into the ring.
[PAN thinking]
It looks like Bulma's work
with the Capsule Corporation
is still paying off
after all these years.
It's so funny how
things have turned out.
Makes life quite interesting!
Goku! Show that kid
what you're made of!
Come on now, give him
one for Grandma Pan!
[drums beating]
[ANNOUNCER]
Let the match...
...begin!
[gong dings]
That's amazing!
Look at those kids go!
[PAN thinking] I wouldn't expect
anything less from these two.
They are the descendents
of Goku and Vegeta!
It's just like the old days!
[VEGETA yells]
You put up quite a good
fight there, weirdo!
I didn't think I was gonna
have a chance to do this thing!
Well, if that's how
you want to play it!
Hey, that's pretty cool there!
I didn't know we could
both become blonde!
Ha ha! This is gonna
be a good match, huh?
You ready?
Yeah!
Woohoo! Alright!
Get him, punch him!
Knock him down!
Nice hit! One more!
Grandpa?
Let me through, please!
Coming through...
Excuse me, pardon me.
[PAN th inking]
Pan, you old goat.
You must be seeing things again!
[NARRATOR] With the
earth finally at peace,
Goku, the savior of
the planet takes his leave
to await the day when
he is needed once again.
Not quite!
Wait.
Stop, I'm gonna fall over!
Oh, man.
That's gonna leave a mark.
Well, hello there, kids!
What did you just say?
Are you Chi Chi?
Yes I am, but who are you?
Wow. The moon
is really big tonight!
[roars]
What are you?
You two showed up just in time!
Is that pleasant
odor I smell fish?
My break'tis!
Hi! I'm Goku.
He's Goku.
Help me!
Release it Gohan,
release everything!
Now die, Saiyan!
[NARRATOR] He was always
friendly and cheerful...
What's up?
Hey, Goku!
A true gentleman
and a loving father...
Come here, buddy!
Daddy!
And now we end the story
of the Dragon Balls
with the hope that
the Earth will never again
see the kind of darkness
that brought it close to
extinction so many times.
But if that day comes,
there is one who will
step out of the shadows
and fight in the name of
all that is good and true.
[GOKU laughing]
'Til we meet again, guys!