[PAN]
I'm gonna find the Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
Pan headed into the
scorching desert on her own,
angry at Goku and Trunks
for treating her like a child.
But this blisteringly
hot planet would have
its own surprises
in store for Pan.
[PAN groaning]
[NARRATOR] And just as all hope
seemed to fade for the Sayian
a savior from the sky
came to her rescue.
Don't worry Pan! Giru!
Thank you... Giru.
[GIRU]
Pan needs water. Drink.
[PAN grunting]
[PAN]
Giru.
[NARRATOR]
Thanks to his persistence,
it was Giru who rescued
Pan from certain death.
And with another Dragon Ball
in their possession,
our heroes are one step
closer to victory.
But there are forces at work
that may put a stop
to their adventures.
[DR. MYUU] You must obtain
the Dragon Ball from these boys.
And I wish for them to
be brought to me alive.
Do you understand?
I expect you to be
a bit more delicate
than normal, General.
But be careful,
for these are no mere boys.
[ship humming]
[PAN grunting]
Oh, great.
It's another enemy fleet.
I won't let 'em
take me this time.
[PAN]
Fire the laser cannon!
I got 'em!
[computer beeping]
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru. Giru.
[PAN whimpering]
[computer beeping]
[PAN]
No! I'm crashing!
[PAN yelping]
[game music humming]
[PAN] Fine!
[GIRU] I win!
[PAN] Gloat about it,
see if I care!
Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru! Giru!
One more round!
[GIRU]
Okay.
Would you let it go?
There's no way you
can beat him, Pan.
Yes, I--
Uh...
[TRUNKS] Giru, can you stop
fighting and show me the radar?
Giru! Giru, Giru, Giru.
Giru. Giru. Giru. Giru.
[TRUNKS] Looks like we're just
about on top of the next one.
Thank you.
[PAN] Let's go, Giru.
Time for the next round.
Giru, Giru, Giru! Giru.
[TRUNKS] So, which one
of you is winning so far?
[game music humming]
Is that's fifty... to zero?
I've tried to tell her
before, she can't win.
She's playing
against a computer.
[TRUNKS nervous laughter]
[GIRU] Giru, Giru.
[PAN] When I say I'm
gonna do something,
that means I'm gonna do it!
Now, get over here!
[TRUNKS groaning]
[TRUNKS]
When you're dealing with
an ultra-competitive
person like Pan,
you should really let
her win once in a while.
But make sure she
doesn't know you let her.
[GIRU] Why let a person win
what they do not deserve?
So, she'll stop
screaming at everyone.
It's getting pretty annoying
hearing it all day long.
[GIRU] Giru will try.
But Pan is very bad at game.
[game music humming]
[PAN] All right! I'm gonna
get you this time!
[buttons beeping, clicking]
[computer beeping]
[PAN yelps]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[PAN yelling]
[TRUNKS nervous laughter]
[game music humming]
[GIRU]
Pan, danger! Danger!
[PAN] You rotten little
[GIRU] Danger! Danger!
[PAN] trash compactor!
Get back here right now!
[GIRU]
Pan, Danger!
[PAN]
Stop, Giru!
[PAN] You have to play the game
with me one more time!
You can't just win and
run away like that!
I want another round!
[TRUNKS groans]
[TRUNKS] It never ends
no matter what I try.
[PAN]
You can't escape from me!
I've got you right
where I want you!
[PAN yelps]
[GIRU groans]
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru.
[PAN gasps]
[GIRU] Giru, Giru, Giru,
Giru, Giru. Giru, Giru, Giru...
Giru, Giru, Giru!
[PAN] I really hope
I didn't break him.
[GIRU sputtering]
[ship humming]
Giru Giru, Giru.
[PAN]
Hm?
Giru want to return.
[PAN gasps]
That is Giru's home planet.
[PAN]
Your home?
Correct. Pan! Danger, danger!
Pan, danger. Danger,
danger, danger.
Danger, danger, danger, danger.
[ship humming]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[PAN grunting]
[GIRU]
Home.
[TRUNKS] We're going back to the
planet we passed yesterday?
It's Giru's home.
[GIRU]
Giru born on that planet.
That's weird. I thought
robots were made, not born.
We can't go there.
Remember, Dr. Myuu is after
the Dragon Balls as well.
It's too dangerous
for us to stop.
We need to just keep
moving on to the next planet.
Come on, it won't take long.
Just one day won't kill us.
Pretty please!
[TRUNKS grunts]
So, you're telling me, that if
that was Earth over there,
and you hadn't been home in
who knows how long,
you wouldn't want
to stop and say hi
[PAN] to your friends and
family? [GIRU] Giru, Giru.
And while we're there,
we could get more food.
Fine. You've got a point.
But we're staying for
one day only. Got it?
[PAN]
Yeah!
[PAN laughing]
[GIRU]
Return.
Any new developments?
[ROBOT] The spacecraft
radically changed directions
within the past six hours.
The data states that they are
headed back toward planet M2.
It seems our little
T-20-O-6 has
finally worked
his magic on them.
His success will make him
a hero to our planet.
[DR. MYUU]
General?
[RILLDO]
Yes, sir, Dr. Myuu.
[DR. MYUU]
Do you have any news
on our friends with
the Dragon Balls?
Sir, we will have them in our
custody by the end of the day.
[DR. MYUU]
Very good, General.
I want the three of them
captured alive.
Their living tissue is
precious to my experiments.
I expect you to make this
clear to your M2 Commandos.
Sir?
Your team has a history
of what I would call...
...questionable tactics.
You understand my concern.
Of course Doctor,
but you flatter me
with such compliments.
[BOTH cackling]
[GOKU yawns]
[PAN] Please, Giru,
would you calm down a bit?
[TRUNKS] Be careful, I don't see
a single person down there.
[PAN] Well, duh.
We're in the the forest.
I bet there are tons of people
in that city over there!
[cracking]
[GOKU yelling]
All I did was try to take
a bite of this apple,
but it's as hard as a rock!
Well, Grandpa,
that's what you get
for acting like a monkey
the second you hop off the ship.
[TRUNKS grunting]
Uh... This apple
is made of metal.
Cool.
Wow! This would look great
in my bedroom at home.
[GIRU]
Thank you, Pan.
[GIRU munching]
Giru's energy replenished!
Giru, Giru, Giru.
Giru, Giru, Giru...
Giru?
[GIRU sputtering]
[TRUNKS]
Did he short circuit?
[GIRU sputtering]
Hey! Don't scare us like
that you crazy little bot.
[GOKU]
Sorry, I had to punch you, Giru.
The fruit is good.
[beeping]
This is very strange.
[PAN]
Where did everybody go?
This place is creepy, like the
aftermath of a war or something.
[GOKU] So, were you really
born on this planet, Giru?
[GIRU] All that you
see was Giru's home.
[GOKU]
Hello? Is anybody here?
[sirens blaring]
[ALL gasp]
[PAN]
What's going on here?
[GOKU whimpering]
[ROBOTS clamoring]
[GOKU]
What are they?
[PAN] You screamed for them,
Grandpa, why don't you ask them?
But I don't know
how to speak robot.
[ROBOTS clamoring
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru.
They all look
just like you, Giru.
[ROBOT]
Does not compute.
That is T-20-O-6, returned
from his great mission.
[ROBOTS clamoring]
[ROBOT] You deserve great praise
for your achievement, T-20-O-6.
General Rilldo will
be extremely pleased.
[ROBOTS] T-20-O-! T-20-O-6!
[GIRU] Uh-oh.
Wait. Do you know these guys?
[GIRU]
Uh... Giru not know these bots.
But, they all recognize you.
They keep calling you by
the production number
you told us when we found you.
Giru is confused as well.
[ROBOT] T-20-O-6, you are
to be commended...
What glory. What fame!
[PAN]
You sure you don't know them?
[GIRU]
Giru... does not know.
But you said this was
your home planet.
You don't recognize
any of them?
[GIRU]
Giru does not know. Giru.
[GOKU]
Where are you going?
Do you know where we
can find some food?
I'd love to have some
enchiladas and blueberry
pie if you can find it.
And if not that,
I'll settle for
a triple cheeseburger
with barbeque sauce!
Please! Just find a restaurant!
[GIRU]
Giru back soon. Back soon!
Could I get some fries
to go with my burger?
[PAN] Hey, Giru,
make it a nice restaurant!
I guess I shouldn't
get my hopes up.
[ROBOT]
It is an honor to see T-20-O-6.
T-20-O-6 is great!
[ROBOTS clamoring]
[GIRU]
Thank you. Thank you.
Giru.
[RILLDO] T-20-O-6,
prepare for transmission.
[GIRU]
T-20-O-6 ready, General Rilldo.
That was an incredible strategy.
Infiltrate their team,
get them to trust you, and have
them land their ship here.
Brilliant. Even worthy of
a medal of honor, I believe.
[GIRU]
Thank you, sir.
[PAN] Hmmm.
What's taking Giru so long?
[TRUNKS] Yeah, I wonder
if everything's okay?
[GOKU]
Well, why wouldn't it be?
[TRUNKS]
I'm not sure,
but something about
Giru has seemed off
since we got to
this weird planet.
[GIRU]
Pan! Goku! Trunks!
Up here, up here!
Well, it's about time.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru, Giru!
[PAN] Cheeseburgers,
fries, blueberry pies!
I'm so hungry
I could eat a house.
You know Giru,
this apple is yours
as soon as you
find us some food.
[GIRU]
Thank you, Pan. Thank you.
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, Goku. Your stomach again?
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL grunt]
[NEZI] Thank you, T-20-O-6,
for all the trouble you took
in getting these three
to us promptly.
[GIRU]
Giru, Giru, Giru...
They called you
by your number.
Guess you don't
know them either?
Watch yourselves.
There's something
different about these guys.
Their power is awesome,
but they're giving off
strange energy patterns.
[NEZI] It seems the little
Saiyan's receptive capabilities
are as advanced as our own.
Interesting.
[BIZU] It is quite clear why
Dr. Myuu wants them so badly.
[NAT] It's for the
Dragon Ball, the Dragon Ball.
[RIBET cackling]
[NEZI] And now let's give them
a sample of our power.
[GOKU grunts]
[PAN grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[PAN groaning]
So, I was right about you.
It's been a long time
since I've seen a display
of strength like that.
You can call me Goku.
What are your names?
[NEZI]
You can call us the Sigma Force!
[ALL cackling]
And we are the least
of your problems.
What are you doing?
That's my friend
you've got! Put him down!
[RIBET]
You cannot be serious.
T-20-O-6 is a very valued
member of the Planet M2.
[NEZI] And now it is time for
you to see the General.
You don't really expect us
to believe that, do you?
[TRUNKS yelling]
[PAN gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[PAN whimpering]
[GOKU, TRUNKS groaning]
[PAN grunts]
Pan! Get outta here!
[BOTH yelping]
[NAT]
Wait right there!
I... I feel weird.
It's sleeping gas.
Goku, hold your... breath.
[NAT] You're quick, but
my fists are quicker!
[PAN yelling]
[PAN grunts]
[GIRU]
Leave her alone.
[NAT]
Do not interfere.
[GIRU] Pan cannot
escape this planet.
The Guard Bots will find her.
The other two
are most important.
They are in possession of the
Dragon Ball the General wants.
Giru! What are
you talking about?
[GIRU] The General will be
happy about the Dragon Ball.
[NEZI]
Point well taken.
To the General!
You're one of them?
You've deceived us all
along! You traitor!
I was such an idiot
to ever believe him.
[NARRATOR]
Giru has betrayed everyone.
After weeks of gaining their
trust, Giru has put his friends
in the hands of General Rilldo,
What does the General
have in store for them?
Find out on
the next Dragon Ball GT!