[BABY]
How can this be?
I'm filling up with power,
growing stronger.
[NARRATOR]
On the last GT,
thanks to Bulma's
scientific genius,
the immobilized Baby
was rejuvenated
when his body was bombarded
with Blutz Waves,
the energy that transforms
Saiyans into Giant Apes!
[SS4 GOKU]
Okay, enough bluffing, Goku.
I practically
have no power left
and my legs feel like
they're made of jelly.
If my body can't handle
what I need to do,
then I'll have to force him
to make his own mistakes.
That may be my only
option at this point.
[NARRATOR]
Completely incapacitated,
Goku stands before a mountain
of sheer muscle and power!
With nothing protecting him
from Baby except his wits,
Goku's life could
end at any second!
But like a true
hero, he stands tall,
ready to confront his fate!
[BABY] What's wrong, Saiyan?
Why aren't you attacking?
[SS4 GOKU] Just savoring
the moment, Baby!
Painting a picture! And I
couldn't help but notice that
you look a lot
bigger than before!
[BABY]
In that case...
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY]
What's this?
[BABY cackling]
Fool! I'm not going
to fall for that!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[SS4 GOKU panting]
[BABY] So, you weren't
bluffing after all!
You really are out of energy!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[BABY]
The great Super Saiyan Four,
lying there as helpless
as a little infant!
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
He's killing him.
[GOKU screaming, groaning]
[BABY GORILLA growling]
[PAN]
Oh, no! Grandpa!
Pan! Are you crazy?! That
beast'll kill you in a second!
I don't care! Let go of me!
If Grandpa dies, what's
the point of living?
[PAN grunts]
[HERCULE gasps]
Pan, come back!
[SS4 GOKU]
I'm not scared of you! Go ahead!
Do what you have to do!
Oh, man. It'll take a
miracle to pull this off.
[BABY]
Enough! Stop whispering! Die!
[PAN]
Stop!
[SS4 GOKU]
Pan! Get out of there!
And do what, Grandpa? Watch
you die? I can't! No, I refuse!
I don't understand why
your doing all this, Baby!
It's not right!
[PAN] My dad never
hurt you! Or my mom!
My family and friends had
nothing to do with your
planet being destroyed!
It was the Saiyans!
Not us! Please! Just stop! I
won't let you hurt my, Grandpa!
[BABY] And just how are
you going to stop me,
you silly little insect?
I can't stand
what you are, Baby!
All you do is hate! And hurt!
Pan! Please! Get away!
You took my parents away
and I want them back!
[PAN yelling]
No, Pan! Run away!
[PAN]
I hate you!
[PAN groaning]
[HERCULE gasping]
Baby!
[BABY GORILLA growling]
One inch closer and I'll blast
you so hard my last attack...
...will feel like a tickle.
Leave her out of this.
This is where the battle is!
[BABY]
You're bluffing!
I'll bet you're using
all of the energy you have
just to stand up!
Do your worst.
Baby, this is your last
warning! Stay away! Or die!
This ends now!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Grandpa!
Ha!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[SS4 GOKU] It looks like that
miracle came just in time.
[TRUNKS]
Boy, did that feel good!
I've felt a little
pent up lately!
[BABY] Fool! I'm your Master!
What have you done?
You're not my Master!
You controlled my body
like a puppet! Nothing more!
[BABY] We were going to
unite the Universe!
No more individuals
fighting one another!
Everyone would be of one mind!
[TRUNKS]
People have to choose that!
You can't achieve it by
taking away their free will!
[TRUNKS shouting]
That's not enough, Trunks!
You can't beat him in
that state! Don't do it!
[TRUNKS grunting]
[TRUNKS yelling]
[BABY] Have you no respect for
your father's body, Trunks?
Huh?
[TRUNKS groaning]
Why did you say that
about my father?
[BABY]
Don't you recognize him?
This is your father's
body transformed!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[BABY cackling]
[BABY] Now you see our full
potential! Don't you son?
Don't worry, Trunks!
It's really me!
Gohan, thank goodness.
[BABY]
Who's responsible for this?
You are! You took our
bodies and our free will
and now we've got them back!
It was only a matter of time!
You have to steal power from
others because you're weak!
Please, tell me that
I'm not dreaming!
[KIBITO] Hi, Pan! Let's move
to a safer place. Okay?
[SS4 GOKU]
Hey, you guys.
[PAN]
Papa, it's really you!
I'm glad to see you
on your feet, Goku!
Thanks, Kibito Kai!
I should have known
you were responsible
for bringing my
family back to me!
You're the best!
You've been through
enough already, Dad!
We'll take it from here.
Hey, Trunks!
How about some Fusion?
Sure!
[GOHAN] Yeah, that's our best
bet! Let's go for it!
[ALL]
Right!
It won't work!
[GOTEN] It has to work,
Dad! It's the only way!
We'll do Fusion. Then can
all attack him together!
[SS4 GOKU] I've already fought
him. I know how strong he is!
Even if you two do Fusion and
we attack him in a group,
he'd still defeat us!
We wouldn't even
have a slim chance!
[BABY] You cowards!
Stop your whispering
and come forward and fight!
It doesn't matter what you plan,
you're all going to die!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
So what, then? We can't win
so we're just gonna sit here
like helpless lambs and
let him slaughter us?!
That's not what
I'm saying, Goten!
There is one way
that we can beat him.
But Fusion would
just get us killed!
I have to fight
him alone to win!
You'll each have to
give me your energy!
Just like you gave
it to Baby before!
If it worked for him...
...it can work for us!
[SS4 GOKU]
Exactly, Pan!
Super Saiyan Four
is our strongest hand!
It has to be me!
And I have to win!
Yes, sir! You can do it,
Grandpa! I know you can!
You should have seen him
fully powered, you guys!
[PAN] Grandpa had that giant
monkey on the ground!
But then Bulma
used this huge tower
to send out all these waves--
He's coming!
[BABY]
The little brat's right!
I cannot let him
power up again!
[GOHAN]
Look out!
[GOHAN] Trunks! Goten! We
need to give him the slip
so we can give Dad our energy!
[BOTH]
Right!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[GOTEN]
Behind you!
[TRUNKS]
Look out!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
This isn't good! He's
keeping them all on the run!
They don't even have time
to gather around Goku,
let alone give
him their energy!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
Thanks, son.
Gohan! Close your eyes! Quick!
Solar Flare!
[BABY]
I can't see! What have you done?
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
Hurry! We don't have much time!
[BABY]
Saiyan Scum! You're going to pay
for that trick with your lives!
He's mad!
[PAN]
It's over, isn't it?
[BABY] Behold! Witness
the glorious extinction
of the Saiyan race!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[BABY]
What's happening to me?
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
[BABY]
I can't take it anymore!
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
[MAJUUB yelling]
Hey it's Majuub! I'm sensing
his energy signal! He's alive!
[TRUNKS]
Look!
[GOTEN]
What's happening?
[MAJUUB yelling]
No one beats me with
my own technique!!
[MAJUUB yelling]
[BABY] This pain is unbearable!
It's that kid! It has to be!
But how?! He was a
piece of chocolate.
[MAJUUB yelling]
How do you like your
chocolate surprise now, Baby!
You should really be a lot more
careful about what you eat!
[SS4 GOKU] Awesome! He knew
he could reverse the spell!
He got swallowed on purpose!
[BABY]
You little scoundrel! You knew!
You tricked me into eating you!
Isn't that how
you operate, Baby?
You lay your eggs in people and
attack them from the inside!
[BABY]
Curse you!
[MAJUUB groaning]
[MAJUUB yelling]
Goku! What are you waiting for?!
I can't keep this
up much longer!
This is our last chance!
[KIBITO]
Goku! He's doing this for you!
Now I get it!
Thanks, Majuub! Nice work!
When this is over,
we'll have another sparring
session together!
[SS4 GOKU]
Let's do it, guys!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[PAN]
Wait for me!
Pan, come back!
What are you doin'?!
She just wants to help!
Let her go!
But she's just a little girl!
Not a Super Saiyan!
That's true! But she certainly
has the heart of a Super Saiyan!
[BABY GORILLA groaning]
[SS4 GOKU] You're doing
great! I can feel it working!
[BABY]
Get out of me! Get out!
[MAJUUB yelling, groaning]
[BABY GORILLA roaring]
It's no good! I can't
hold it anymore! Goku!
[KIBITO]
Oh, no!
[BABY cackling]
[HERCULE]
Goku! The monkey's on the loose!
Majuub has been spit out, Goku!
Baby's free!
There's no more time!
Let's do this!
Dad! Are you ready yet?
Hold tight, guys! He'll
tell us when he's ready!
Almost there!
Just a little more!
[BABY] That's it! Stay still
and die like sitting ducks!
Super Gallic Gun!
We were...
We were so close!
Where'd she go?
Pan, where are you?!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY]
I can't believe those idiots!
[BABY GORILLA cackling]
[BABY] They couldn't have
made it easier on me!
All five of them, standing
there like a giant bulls-eye!
Fools! How could
they fight so grandly
just to botch it up
like that at the end?
Oh, no! Please! Not my Pan!
Where are you?
Pan, come out of here.
[HERCULE]
Oh no! I'm all alone!
You know I can't
live without you.
You were everything to me, Pan!
How dare you hurt
my Granddaughter,
you ugly brute! Come on!
I ain't scared of you!
You're just a big,
fat bully! Let's go!
[SS4 GOKU] Easy there, Champ!
Better let me handle this one!
[HERCULE]
Goku?!
I-Is that really you?!
[BABY] It can't be! Where
did that voice come from?
[BABY] It should be over!
I had you! What happened?!
She's alive!
Thank goodness!
Curse you!
[HERCULE] You did it, Goku!
You saved our Granddaughter!
Thank you so much!
[HERCULE]
Hi, Pan!
Hi, Gramps. Are we dead?
No, Pan! We're still alive!
Alive and well! Thanks to Goku!
[SS4 GOKU] You're a real
hero now, Mr. Satan!
You should be proud of yourself!
[HERCULE]
I should? Really?
You stood up to
Baby without fear,
without any regard
for your own life!
And that's what it's all about!
I really did, didn't I?
I don't believe it.
So that's what a fully powered
Super Saiyan Four is like!
Wow! Dad's power,
it's incredible!
This goes way beyond anything
I ever thought possible!
There's no way to describe it!
[SS4 GOKU] I couldn't have
reached this without
each one of you! You
all made sacrifices!
And now it's my turn!
The killing stops here!
All you see is the light shining
through the cracks around
the edges of the door, Baby!
And you just don't think
that little bit of light
can overcome your dark plans!
But what you can't see
is what's behind the door!
That's what I am!
[BABY] I don't care
what you are!
Your flesh can bleed and
your bones can be broken!
Funny! I have no
wish to destroy you!
It's your own desires
that make it necessary!
[BABY] Why you insolent,
presumptuous rat!
[BABY GORILLA, SS4 GOKU yelling]
[NARRATOR]
In a twist of cosmic irony,
Goku must confront
the same nefarious power
that his ancestors destroyed
countless lives with.
Is there anything Goku can do
to put the sins of the Saiyans
to bed once and for all?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball GT.
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka, me, ha, me, ha!