[NARRATOR] On the last GT, the
challenge was laid down by Goku
and taken up by Don Kee's
hired assassin, Ledgic.
A victory for Goku meant
the trio from Earth
could resume their journey.
A loss--
and their mission was over.
Kaaaa! Meeee!
Haaa! Meee! Haaaaa!!
[NARRATOR] At last the forces
of darkness were overcome
and the spaceship was repaired
and readied for flight.
But the Dragon Radar
was still questionable.
It looks like the Dragon
Radar is still in tact!
That's just great.
If the radar's part of him, then
we have to take him with us!
[NARRATOR] And so the crew of
three became four
and a course was set for
the nearest Dragon Ball.
The space voyagers are
finally back on track,
but valuable time has
been lost on Imecka.
The uncertain future of the
earth is still in their hands,
and the clock is ticking.
Hey, uh... What's your name?
Or do you even have a name?
[GIRU] Giru Giru Giru.
My name is T-Twenty-O-Six!
Wow. T-Twenty-O-Six, huh?
Well, that's certainly unusual.
That's probably his
production number, Goku...
Maybe we could brainstorm
and think of a name for him.
[GIRU] Giru!
Giru! Giru! Giru!
[GIRU] Dragonball detected!
Dragonball detected!
There'd better be for your sake!
If you led us all the way out
here on a wild goose chase,
you're finished!
You got that, pal?
[GIRU]
Giru.
Pan, for his safety and yours,
you'd better sit down...
We're about to
enter the atmosphere.
[TRUNKS] We're through.
That wasn't so bad.
Hey! Nice handling! How about
we see what this thing can do!
[GOKU]
Yeah!
[PAN]
Careful, Trunks!
[GIRU] Atmosphere inhabitable.
Will sustain organic life.
We'll land beyond those rocks.
[impact]
[reverberation]
Can you try landing this thing
a little softer next time?!
You almost gave me whiplash!
[GIRU]
Giru.
Sorry about that...
Except for the crash,
this is the first time
I've landed this ship.
[groans]
Let's see what
kind of food they have!
[ship creaking]
Trunks! What's the deal?!
But I didn't do anything.
[further creaking]
Uhh! What's going on...?
It feels like an
earthquake! Look!
[PAN] The rocks are moving!
That can't be good, can it?
[TRUNKS] No!
That's definitely not good!
[roars]
[waves breaking]
That... was too close!
[PAN] I really hope that wasn't
a sign of things to come.
[GOKU]
Hey!
[TRUNKS]
How did you get out there?
Nevermind! You're not gonna to
believe this place! Come on!
Why does he get to fly?!
I'm going too!
How am I gonna put up with
those two for a whole year?!
[GIRU]
Giru.
[chuckling]
Oh, man, this is fun!
And it sure beats walking!
Hey there, Grandpa. So?
What do you think?
I look just like
a bug, don't I?!
Yeah, I guess.
[groans]
Well, would it be more
realistic if I bit you?!
[PAN] They're...
so... beautiful!
Hey! Wait for me!
[TRUNKS] There you are!
What are you guys doing?
We need to be looking for
the Dragon Ball! Not playing!
[laughs]
Pan! Let's go!
She left with the butterflies.
She'll be fine.
Let's go get the Dragon Ball
and meet her back here.
Are you sure?
[GOKU]
I'm positive! Come on!
I hope he knows what he's doing.
[laughing]
[PAN] I could do this forever!
This is so much fun!
Wow! Cool flower! Hey!
What do we have here?
Delicious!
A flower for a bed!
This is the life!
[sighs]
What is that sound?
[buzzing]
[uncertain whimpering]
This isn't what you think!
I'm not a bug! I'm a girl!
[GIRU] Dragon Ball detected!
Straight ahead! Giru, giru!
[laughs]
[chomps]
[GIRU]
Down there!
[TRUNKS]
Yeah! I see it!
[GIRU]
Giru!
[TRUNKS] Goku! We found
the four-star ball!
That would have hurt.
Did you guys
get the Dragon Ball?
Not exactly.
Oh, I see. How 'bout
I lift and you grab it?
[screeching]
[GOKU]
That was close!
[TRUNKS]
Yeah, no kidding!
We're just lucky he was in
the mood for something sweet.
[disappointed groan]
What happened?! It's gone!
[TRUNKS]
I-I don't know!
[GOKU]
Ball in apple.
[screeching]
Let's go get him!
[resounding thuds]
[TRUNKS]
Whoa!
Whoa! He's huge!
[screeching]
[delightful groan]
[wings flapping]
[resounding thuds]
[TRUNKS] We have to get the ball
back before he eats that apple!
[scream]
--Huh?
--Pan!
She'll be okay. We'd better
get the Dragon Balls first.
Hey! That's the wrong way!
I'm going for Pan! We can find
the Ball again using the radar!
But if we lose her,
we're cooked!
I guess he's right.
But if he eats that
apple, we're in trouble.
[PAN] Let go of me!
Put me down right now!
[PAN] What is this place?
Where are you taking me?
Why are you
looking at me like that?
[thud]
This must be their hive.
[PAN] And just what do they plan
on doing with me now?!
Those bees don't know who
they're dealing with!
If they try to get
fresh with me
I'll blast this place
to smithereens!
Yikes. The walls are alive.
[PAN]
These must be their eggs.
There are hundreds of them
and they're all about to hatch.
And each one...
has a nasty larva inside.
[terrified scream]
[screams]
Uh...huh?
[bee murmurs]
[delighted laugh]
Oh, how adorable!
Pan! Where are you?!
Pan!
Goku, I've found her!
[blow lands]
[shoots]
[GOKU]
I can't see!
[blow lands]
[thud]
[disgusted groans]
[TRUNKS]
Pan! Are you okay?!
Huh?
Oh, boy!
Trunks? Is she okay?
Well, she's a little shaken up.
But she'll be just fine.
[GOKU] That's not Pan!
She's too quiet to be Pan!
[buzzing]
For me?
Oh, hey. That's a really
good batch, guys!
[buzzing]
More honey. Gee, thanks.
Hey. Wait a second...
They're bringing me honey
because they think
I'm their queen.
Well I'm not ready for
that kinda responsibility!
I'm outta here!
[buzzing]
Ah!
Can't you guys
take no for an answer?!
Bees have no class!
[laughs cheerfully]
Wow! Everything's big!
[PAN]
Leave me alone!
[screeching]
[PAN]
Ow!! That hurt!
[GOKU]
I know!
Who's that? My replacement?
No. She's just a bee that we
helped who had lost her way.
She's been through a lot.
She's still a little weak.
[buzzing]
[GOKU] What's going on?
They're surrounding us!
And they mean business!
I know what's going on!
[PAN] I'm not your Queen, you
buzzing boneheads!
She's your Queen!
[GOKU] Imagine that.
Mistaking Pan for their Queen.
That's something else, alright.
It's called being
clueless, Grandpa!
I don't know...
Having a countless number
of personal attendants
does have its advantages, Pan.
I'll never eat honey again!
But Pan, to them honey is worth
more than diamonds and gold!
I guess you're right. How sweet.
That's strange...
Five readings.
What?! Give me that!
Great! Now I'm not
getting any signal at all!
[GIRU]
Giru! Not broken.
[GIRU] Radar not malfunctioning.
Energy too low.
Ahh! So that's it!
I should have known!
[crickets chirp]
[dragonfly buzzes]
Well... On a planet
without any industry,
we're going to be hard pressed
to find any metal
for Giru to eat.
A lot of good he is! Conking out
at an important time like this!
[GIRU]
Giru.
Hey. Wow!
Someone's cooking fish!
[stomach growls]
My stomach's empty too!
Let's eat!
Now, who would be cooking
fish way out here? Come on!
[TRUNKS]
I know who!
A giant lives out here!
We saw him earlier!
Awesome! It must
be a huge fish!
Maybe we can sneak
a little nibble!
I saw him too. He's huge. He
might sneak a nibble out of us.
Over there, Trunks!
[fire crackling]
[GOKU] Whoa! And I thought
I caught big fish!
[TRUNKS]
Goku! He's coming!
He reminds me
a little bit of you, Goku.
[wings flapping]
All right, step lightly.
Operation Apple is underway!
Let's go get that Dragon Ball!
[PAN] I was expecting the Giant
to be really mean and scary,
but he actually seems
kind of gentle. Don't you think?
Sssshh! He may seem gentle,
but that might change
if he finds us!
[PAN] Don't worry.
Everything's going to be fine.
[GOKU] Aaah!
He's eating all the fish!
I need to get some
before it's all gone!
[TRUNKS] Goku!
Get back here! Are you crazy?!
[GOKU]
But I'm starving!
[TRUNKS] Ssshh! Come on! Let's
get the Dragon Ball first!
Then you can eat all you want!
We'll catch our own fish!
[GOKU] All right!
Now you're talking!
Look! Right there!
The apple on top!
[PAN] Wow!
This must be our lucky day!
--Yeah!
--Great!
I'll go get it!
Whoa!
[chomps]
[scream]
Did he just...?
I'm afraid so! This is bad!
[chuckles]
Nobody said getting the Dragon
Balls was going to be easy!
I cannot... believe this.
[straining]
[toilet flushes]
[screams]
Absolutely no way.
If that's what it takes
to save the planet, then
I just don't care anymore!
You're the one who wanted to
come on this mission.
You volunteered.
I know! How about we go hunt
down another Dragon Ball
and come back for
this one later. You know...
give things here time to
work themselves out naturally?
[strained groan]
What's wrong with him?
It's like he's being
attacked or something!
[thunderous stomping]
[screams]
Hey! What's the matter?
Are you okay? Hello!
[pained screaming]
Hey! There's the Dragon Ball!
[crash]
Goku!
[GOKU] He never swallowed it!
It's in his mouth!
The Dragon Ball's
stuck in his tooth!
[PAN]
Look out!
Okay... Now!
[battlecry]
Grandpa! Are you
out of your mind?!
[straining]
Trunks, I can't hold this much
longer! Get the Dragon Ball!
No way am I going in there!
Yes! No! Too late!
I hate to do this!
Kaaaa... Meeee...
Haaaa... Meeee...
[GOKU]
Haaaaa!!
Alright! I did it!
Well, guys...
we got our first ball!
That is a foul smelling cavity!
[pained screaming]
Taah-daah!
Yes! At this rate,
a year's plenty of time!
Good thing I was here,
right guys?
Hey, sorry about that!
You had something in your
tooth that we needed.
Yeah!!
Here you go!
That was a really bad cavity
you had there, Giant! Bye!
Make sure you brush your
teeth after every meal!
[laughs]
The Four Star Ball!
It's... gorgeous!
That's right...
This is your first time to see a
Dragon Ball up close, isn't it?
Mm-hmm! And it's all
thanks to this little guy!
You really pulled through.
Keep up the good work.
[GIRU]
Giru!
Hey, why don't
we call him Giru?
He seems pretty fond of that!
Giru? I doubt he'd
object to that,
it does seem to be
his favorite word!
Well then! It's all settled!
Your new name is Giru!
How's that sound?
[GIRU] Good!
Giru giru giru...!
[NARRATOR] With the
Four Star Ball in the bag,
spirits are high.
But what challenges await
the adventurers from Earth
as they continue to
search the galaxy
for the Black Star
Dragon Balls?