[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
Piccolo used Dende's help
to attempt an incredibly
difficult technique
that would open a rift
between Hell and Earth.
And while Goku was concerned
only with the rumble
in his belly,
Super Android 17
was tearing through
the ranks of the Saiyans,
still fighting on Earth.
As the hopes for a safe
Earth began to fade,
Piccolo and Dende
finally cracked open
the gateway between
the two worlds.
[GOKU]
Okay, I'm going.
But I will pay you back
for this, I promise.
I'll see you soon.
Saiyan blood still
courses through my veins,
and I call the Earth my home!
Kakarot...
Vegeta, don't worry.
I'll handle the rest of them.
Nonsense! Super 17 is more
than capable of sending you
back to where you came from!
I wouldn't be
so confident, Myuu!
You failed with Baby
and you'll fail again!
[NARRATOR] Has Goku
returned to Earth in time
to stop the evil doctor
and his killer android?
Find out right now
on Dragon Ball GT!
[HERCULE sobbing]
This is all my fault.
If I hadn't endowed you with
all my martial arts knowledge,
this would've never happened.
I'm sorry. He's too strong.
The two of us didn't stand a
chance against a guy like him.
Poor Pan.
Goku, show that scum any mercy
and you'll have to deal with me!
Well, you've made
quite a mess, 17.
[GOKU] What do you say
you show your face
so I can start
cleaning up, now!
[DR. MYUU] If your living
body didn't like Hell,
then perhaps you
should return dead!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 groaning]
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
Heh!
Super Flash Bomb!
[GOKU growls]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 gasps]
[GOKU grunting]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 groaning]
Hands off.
[GOKU gasps]
You can imagine
my disappointment.
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
Seeing through your techniques
gets kind of old.
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU screams]
[DR. MYUU]
Magnificent! Truly magnificent!
It seems the
trustworthy Dr. Gero
really came through on his end!
But it will be my
own personal additions
that will make Super 17
a true work of art!
[GOKU] You think you've got
me figured out, don't you?
Believe me, you've got no
idea what I'm capable of!
[GOKU yells]
How 'bout that?!
I'll bet you didn't see that
one coming, did ya, big guy?
[GOKU]
You want some more, 17?
'Cause I can keep
this up all day.
All these attacks and he still
hasn't taken any damage!
[GOKU]
I gotta say, that's impressive.
[DR. MYUU] That's right.
Just keep on trying, you runt.
I've had enough!
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Ha!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU] Still think you've
got me figured out?
Let's see you come
back from that one.
How's this?
[GOKU gasps]
[SUPER ANDROID 17] You should
try being more direct!
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU]
This android is doing more
than just reading my techniques.
He took every one of
my best attacks head-on
without getting so
much as a scratch.
If anything, he keeps
getting stronger and faster!
Enough of your stalling!
You and I both know quite well
that last attack was not
enough to destroy you!
[GOKU yelling]
He's completely
changed! But how?!
[SS4 GOKU] Maybe you should
pick on someone your own size.
I'd say Super Saiyan Four...
should be a challenge.
Super Saiyan F-Four?!
[SS4 GOKU] That's right! You may
have anticipated my attacks
so far, but you have no idea
what I'm capable of now!
And what you don't
know could hurt you!
[VIDEL humming]
[BULMA] Goku is always so hard
to find when you need him,
maybe we should
buy him a cell phone.
[BULLA] Do you think that Dad
and the others are alright?
They sure have
been gone a while.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHI CHI]
Just because Goku's not around,
doesn't mean we can't fight!
You see this?
This is my broom stick!
If this thing scared
my kids so well,
it should work wonders
on the bad guys!
[CHI CHI grunting]
Chi Chi, are you alright?
[VIDEL]
Chi Chi's right, Bulma!
As long as there's
evil in the world,
it is our job as Earthlings...
...to defend our home!
[VIDEL]
But more importantly...
...I'm just glad the uniform
still looks so good on me.
All right, Videl! It's our turn!
Right! Let's go!
Hey wait, you two! Where are
you going? What about me?
Man, now this one...
I gotta see.
Come on, Mom! Let's go watch!
[BULMA]
Bulla, this isn't funny!
[SS4 GOKU yelling]
[SS4 GOKU grunting]
[DR. MYUU chuckling]
[DR. MYUU] This is exceeding
my goals a hundred fold!
It will be far
too late by the time
Goku realizes 17's
true advantage!
Very soon, my Super 17
will finish Goku
and give me the sweetest revenge
the Universe has ever known!
[DR. MYUU]
17's power is increasing
with every energy
attack Goku delivers.
He might as well just hand over
all of his power at once
and be done with it.
My creation has surpassed
all other fighters
and this time
I've made no mistakes.
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunting]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
[SS4 GOKU]
Something's not right.
He's not even trying to
avoid my energy blasts.
It's as if he's actually
trying to get hit!
No way!
[DR. MYUU] It seems as though
he's finally figured out
Super 17's little secret.
Oh well, it's of no
concern at this point.
He's handed over too much power
to an already
unbeatable android!
I can't tell which
is more enjoyable,
my brilliant mind or
the sweet smell of victory!
[DR. MYUU cackling]
Where'd he go?
All right! Now I'm mad!
[DR. MYUU]
He's still alive!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
[GOKU yelling]
It didn't work?
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
How much can he take?
[SUPER ANDROID 17
panting, laughing]
Ha!
[DR. MYUU]
Remarkable!
[SS4 GOKU] So, that's it,
huh? You've been feeding off
all of my attacks just like your
old counterpart, Android 19!
You know, guys like
you should learn to fight
with your own power!
If you had really
figured it out,
then why would you have
kept on attacking?
Are you really that dumb?
Wait and see! Someone
as brilliant as you
should know that I don't
give up without a fight!
I'll show you personally
what I'm capable of!
[DR. MYUU cackling]
I wish I could say
you had me worried.
I wasn't sure how
his body would respond
to absorbing that much
power all at once.
It seems that he is capable
of more than I even predicted.
My dream to construct
the ultimate machine mutant
has finally arrived.
[DR. MYUU] And now my dream has
become your worst nightmare!
Ha! Quit your daydreaming!
I honestly don't care
how strong you say he is!
Both of you are about to get
the wake up call of your lives!
So please, spare me
the small talk!
All right Super 17! I grow
tired of this macho banter.
Give the rotten
Saiyan what he wants!
Let's try this again!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 grunting]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
[SS4 GOKU groans]
That hurt!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
You missed!
[SS4 GOKU]
Ka... me... ha... me...
Wait a second! This won't work!
Any energy I use will
just make him stronger.
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
Come on! Is that
the best you can do?
No.
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU gasps]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
[SS4 GOKU groans]
[SS4 GOKU]
Stop this one.
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
[GOKU grunting]
[SS4 GOKU groaning]
It's crazy, like he
knows exactly where
I'm going to appear,
before I even get there!
I'm sure that on a
more inferior opponent
that special move of
yours works rather well.
It's just one of the
perks of being an android
that I can sense the
vibrations in the atmosphere
at the point of your reentry.
He's too strong.
[NARRATOR] With Super 17 knowing
where Goku will strike next,
things look bleak for
the Earth's mightiest hero.
[SS4 GOKU] From the looks of
whatever he's got brewing,
I know I'm gonna have
to get up and fight back.
I guess I should
come up with a plan.
I just can't lie
here and wait to die.
Giving up already?
[NARRATOR] Can Goku find the
strength to defend himself?
Or has the Super Saiyan Four
finally entered a battle
he can't finish?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball GT!