Show your face right now!
Finish him!
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball GT...
it was Super Saiyan
verses Super Android
as Goku fought 17
in a battle that would
decide the fate of the Earth
and the Galaxy beyond!
Goku powered up to
Super Saiyan Four
to deal with
the Android threat.
But Super 17 seemed immune to
every attack thrown at him.
Goku realized too late
that 17 was actually
absorbing the attacks.
And using that power
against the Saiyans.
The epic battle
concludes today on GT.
[VIDEL] Keep your eyes peeled,
Chi Chi! We're getting close!
[CHI CHI yelping]
Videl, a little lower!
[CHI CHI] Right now! There's no
need to be flying this high!
[VIDEL]
Right!
[CHI CHI yelping]
Are you crazy?!
What are you doing?
But you told me to go down.
[CHI CHI]
Not that fast, you idiot!
[BULLA]
Chi Chi must be really brave!
I don't know if I'd
trust Videl's flying
after all these years!
Trust me! She's yelling
so loud right now
that she could swallow a bird!
Huh?
[BULMA]
This is awful.
[BULMA] Oh, no! That entire city
is practically under water!
[BULMA] The whole planet
is going haywire!
Flesh and blood organisms,
so delicate and frail.
I'd ask for my money
back if I were you!
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
Now for the final touch!
[SS4 GOKU]
What is that?
Electro Eclipse Bomb!
[SS4 GOKU] Everyone's counting
on me! I can't give up!
What? How? You were done for!
He must have been bluffing
if he has that much power!
[SS4 GOKU]
Heh, heh! That wasn't too smart!
It was a nice attack, but it
provided me the perfect cover!
Now you can't attack me as
long as I have you in this hold!
Give it up, 17!
Yes, but I think
you're forgetting something!
You can't attack him either!
It's a stalemate!
Huh? Unless!
Unless I'm willing
to die with him!
You wouldn't dare! Would you?
[SS4 GOKU] I sure would!
Don't get me wrong,
I'm no fan of dying,
but if that's the only way to
stop you from hurting people,
I'll do it!
[DR. MYUU grunting]
[SUPER ANDROID 17]
Let go of me! Are you crazy?
[SS4 GOKU]
What's the matter?
You only want to play the game
if you're winning! Is that it?
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
17, I won't let
you kill anymore!
[BOTH grunting]
[DR. MYUU gasping]
No!
[DR. MYUU screaming]
[HERCULE yelping]
[HERCULE]
Holy smoke! What's happening?
[HERCULE grunting]
Now you've done it, you clown!
[CHI CHI]
No! My pot!
[BULMA gasps]
[BULLA, BULMA yelp]
[BULMA] That was Chi Chi's pot!
[GOKU groaning]
[DR. MYUU] I-I don't believe
it. Everything, ruined.
It was all for nothing.
Could it be over?
[GOKU]
Nope. Definitely not.
He's alive!
[DR. MYUU] You did it, 17!
You're number one!
Goku played his best
card and you trumped him!
You didn't make the
grade as a Kamikaze!
I guess you can
blame me for that
because the shield I put up
kept you alive as well!
I should thank you.
But I wish we were both
in the next dimension!
I can make half of
your wish come true!
[GOKU chuckles]
Half, huh? I guess I'm
in no position to bargain.
Huh, I can't even move my pinky.
So moving my whole body is
definitely out of the question.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
[SUPER ANDROID 17] Trust me,
this time I won't miss.
Sorry, I let everyone
down. I tried.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
[DR. MYUU]
We finally beat the great Goku!
Prepare yourself, Goku!
It end's now!
[EIGHTEEN]
Hold it right there, 17!
Eighteen? What are you doing
here? Get out of the way.
[GOKU] Eighteen, please. I don't
want you to get hurt.
How dare you!
I'll never forgive this!
I will avenge my
husband's death!
What? Krillin's dead?
[EIGHTEEN] I can't even look
at you anymore! You sicken me!
You're half of what
you were before!
Now how do you figure
that one, Eighteen?
I'm twice as strong now!
Strength is
one thing, 17!
But character is another!
[EIGHTEEN] The 17 I knew
wasn't a cold blooded killer.
At one time you were
programmed to destroy Goku,
but you never took pleasure
in killing innocent people!
You even managed to
overcome the programming!
You were so strong
and independent
that you refused
to be controlled!
But now look at you!
If you want to kill Goku
and me, go right ahead!
But you know full well that
I have a bomb in my chest!
So if you take me down,
your going with me.
[GOKU]
What's Eighteen talking about?
[GOKU] Doesn't she
remember what happened?
We had Shenron remove
that bomb a long time ago.
It was after
Gohan defeated Cell.
Wait a second! Now I get it!
17 doesn't know that!
She's bluffing him!
[EIGHTEEN]
So, go ahead! Blow us all up!
[GOKU] Wow! What a great actor!
She's really believable!
What are you waiting
for, you coward?
Are you scared to die or what?
If you're gonna do it,
get it over with! Come on!
[EIGHTEEN]
Go ahead, 17, do it! Why not?
Destroy the one person that
actually cares about you!
I don't respect you anymore
anyway! Weak-minded fool!
You can't even make
your own decisions!
Some Doctor has to
tell you what to do!
What a buffoon you've
turned out to be!
Hey, take it easy Eighteen!
He's struggling inside.
If you push him
too hard he'll snap!
[DR. MYUU] What are you
waiting for, you fool?
Can't you see that she's
trying to manipulate you?
That little bomb can't
cause any serious damage!
Don't be scared of something
that can't hurt you!
I'm not scared of
anything, Doctor Myuu!
That's the spirit!
Now finish the job!
[DR. MYUU]
Show Goku who you really are.
And show that android reject
that you can't be
manipulated or controlled!
You're right, Doctor!
Nobody controls me!
[DR. MYUU screaming]
Now, let's see who the
real coward is, Eighteen!
At least you saw
through that Doctor!
There might be some hope left
for you after all, 17.
It's a shame we have to fight!
[EIGHTEEN grunts]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 grunting]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 cackling]
[EIGHTEEN grunting]
[GOKU]
Eighteen! It's not working!
He's absorbing your power.
You can't beat him!
I have to at least try!
He killed Krillin, Goku!
[GOKU]
I understand!
But your energy blasts are
only making him stronger!
[EIGHTEEN] I can't stop now!
When I stop, I die!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 yelling]
[GOKU] He's not absorbing the
blasts! He's shielding himself!
That means he can be hit!
He must have to stay
in that one posture
for the absorption to work!
He's vulnerable!
This is our chance!
Fire, Eighteen! Don't stop!
I have a plan! Keep it up!
[EIGHTEEN yells]
[GOKU yelling]
[SUPER ANDROID 17 laughing]
Yes, that's it!
Give it everything you've got,
Eighteen! Let it all out!
I'll just sit here
gathering energy
so I can destroy you
when you're finished!
Maybe not!
[EIGHTEEN yelling]
[GOKU]
This is for Krillin!
What?
[GOKU yelling]
Super Dragon Fist!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 groaning]
You wretch!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Fool! Haven't you learned yet?
It will only make me stronger!
I don't think so!
Ha!
[SUPER ANDROID 17 groaning]
Yes! We did it, Krillin!
[GOKU groaning]
[TRUNKS weakly]
Father?
[VEGETA]
Rest, son. It's over.
Kakarot, you've done it.
How could he do it, Goku?
I'm his twin sister.
How could he kill my
husband like that?
That wasn't really
your brother, Eighteen.
He was in there somewhere,
but 17 wasn't the one
calling the shots.
They were controlling
him somehow.
But, you know, I think he
was trying hard to help you.
Huh?
There was no need to
start powering up.
All he had to do was keep
absorbing your energy!
Yes! I sensed him then!
[EIGHTEEN] He forced that
monster into making a mistake
that could cost him the battle!
He was showing us where
his weakness was! Wasn't he?
[GOKU] I'd like to think so.
He did have some control.
Otherwise, he would have
never turned on Doctor Myuu.
There was definitely
a struggle going on,
and I think your brother won.
Thank you, Goku. You don't
know how much that means to me!
[EIGHTEEN]
Krillin.
I'll bet he's celebrating!
Laughing himself silly
because you won!
[GOKU] You know that,
don't you? That he's happy!
Well?
Mm-hm!
[CHI CHI]
Where is he?! Let me at 'im!
No android is going
to bully us around!
[CHI CHI, VIDEL panting]
We've come to subdue the
wicked and punish the evildoers!
Yeah, what she said!
Sorry you got all dressed up!
But Eighteen and I already
took care of business!
[CHI CHI]
Well, that's good.
A little disappointing maybe,
but I'm sure it's
all for the best.
[GOKU laughing]
[BULMA]
Goku! We've got big problems!
Old volcanoes are
starting to erupt!
Earthquakes are being
reported around the globe!
The flooding's so bad that
whole cities are going under!
That inter-dimensional
doorway they opened up
must have upset the
natural balance!
[CHI CHI] Then we have to
gather up the Dragon Balls
and wish things back to normal!
[GOKU]
Yeah, good idea.
We can use them to wish
Krillin back, too.
[EIGHTEEN] Thank you, Goku.
I give Krillin a hard time,
but I do love him.
I miss him.
Then it's settled!
Let the official hunt for
the Dragon Balls begin!
[NARRATOR] Now that Super
Android 17 had been defeated,
it was time to make reparations!
King Yemma took care of
returning all the
escapees to Hell.
Trunks went to work
on the Dragon Radar
and restored Giru
to life as well!
And with the old Dragon Ball
hunting team back together,
they began to scour the globe
for the seven magic balls!
Everything was going
according to plan,
until the team located
their first Dragon Ball.
and made an unusual discovery.
[PAN]
Oh, no! Grandpa! Trunks!
You're not gonna
believe this! Look!
[NARRATOR]
And so it was with all seven!
Not just one, but
every single Dragon Ball
was inexplicably cracked!
The Dragon Balls even
sound different than usual.
I don't know, guys.
This is freaky.
Maybe they... Maybe they're
too dangerous to be using.
Grandma, our hearts
are in the right place,
so we'll be alright.
It's ill will that makes
the Dragon Balls dangerous.
Let's go ahead and
give them a try. Okay?
And then maybe Shenron can
tell us what's going on.
Hey! Maybe our wish will do it!
Whatever's causing
the disruptions on Earth
might have cracked
the Dragon Balls as well!
Maybe wishing the Earth back
to normal will mend the balls!
[TRUNKS]
It's worth a shot!
[GOKU]
Okay! Arise, Shenron!
[GOKU] Wow, the sky isn't
changing at all, is it?
[GOHAN] 'Fraid not! That's
about as normal as it gets.
Well gosh, maybe you didn't
say it loud enough, Goku.
Try it again.
Arise, Shenron!
Alright!
You can do it, Shenron!
[PAN]
What's happening?
[TRUNKS] I don't know, but
I think we made a mistake!
Whoa! I'm sensing
an enormous power!
[GOKU]
It's evil, whatever it is!
Wait! That's not, Shenron!
[NARRATOR] As the foul
black smoke issues forth
from the broken Dragon Balls,
a Dragon that has
never been seen before
looms ominously
over the planet!
What does his evil
presence signify?
What horrible danger has
been unleashed on the Earth?
[GOKU] What are you
doing here? Who are you?
[NARRATOR]
Find out on the next GT.