[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball GT,
the evil monstrosity
Luud was resurrected
by channeling the life energy
of his believers.
As this robotic giant began his
attack against Goku and Trunks,
the Saiyans had to resort
to some fancy footwork
to escape his crushing blows.
[GOKU yelping]
[BOTH groaning]
[BOTH yelping]
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] Trunks and Goku
seemed to be evenly matched
against Luud's might,
with neither side able
to deliver the final blow.
But the mysterious Dr. Myuu
had a plan to tip
the scales in Luud's favor.
With the additional
life energies
of both Pan and Dolltaki,
Luud is now more
powerful than ever.
[DR. MYUU cackling]
No!
[NARRATOR]
Will Dr. Myuu's plan succeed?
Or will our heroes finally
bring an end to Luud's reign?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball GT!
[GOKU]
Pan!
[LUUD growling]
[GOKU gasping]
I think we might
be in trouble here.
[LUUD growling]
That's unreal!
[DR. MYUU cackling]
I've finally done it!
[DR. MYUU cackling] You can
see the horror in their eyes!
They don't have a chance!
[LUUD growling]
Goku, we have to
formulate a plan!
My cute little Panny...
Aren't you just a doll?
[DOLLTAKI kissing sounds]
[PAN shrieking]
Where am I?
[PAN gasps]
Oh no!
Don't tell me I've been
swallowed by that stupid
robotic Luud thing.
[DOLLTAKI]
Pan!
My sweet Pan!
[PAN shrieking]
Pan? What did I do?
[PAN shreiking]
[DOLLTAKI groaning]
[BELIEVER A]
Huh? What's this?
[BELIEVER B]
Was I asleep?
[DOLLTAKI yelping] You're not
my sweet Pan! You're a ruffian!
My sweet Pan would never
strike me like that!
You're an evil barbarian!
Barbarian? After
what you did to me?
[DOLLTAKI groaning] I can't
believe this. You've changed.
[BELIEVERS murmuring]
[BON PARA]
Wait! Are we just floating here?
[PAN] I hate you! I hate you!
[DOLLTAKI moaning]
And now you get
what's coming to you!
Not in the face!
[DOLLTAKI shireking]
[BELIEVERS shrieking]
Do you see what happens when you
don't listen to your elders?
Ignorant child!
[DOLLTAKI shrieks]
[DOLLTAKI coughs]
[BELIEVER A]
Who's the guy with the hair?
[BELIEVER B]
That's gonna leave a mark!
[BELIEVER C]
It's Dolltaki! Get him!
[BELIEVERS murmuring]
[DOLLTAKI whimpering]
Stop and think about this!
If you people kill me,
you won't know how
to get out of here!
And then we'll all be trapped
in the belly of
this thing forever!
[BELIEVERS murmuring]
So, there is a way to escape.
[PAN] Well, spit it out!
How do we get out of here?
I... uh... I don't...
They're gonna kill me. I'm done.
[BELIEVER A]
Answer her, "Master"!
Yes, of course.
[BELIEVERS clamoring]
[PAN]
Now, now! Calm down!
All right.
Who wants out of here?
[BELIEVER]
Uh... I do!
--I could go.
--Okay.
That was pathetic. I said,
who wants out of here?!
[BELIEVERS]
We do!
Good! Just leave
everything to me!
[BELIEVERS cheering]
[LUUD growling]
[GOKU, TRUNKS yelling]
[LUUD roaring]
[DOLLTAKI] If I tell
them how to get out,
then they'll learn the
secret, and Dr. Myuu
will kill me for sure. But if
I don't show them the way,
then I'll die in here!
Redeem yourself, Dolltaki.
How do we get out?
I'm sorry Pan,
but I just cannot tell you!
I see. Don't worry.
We have ways of making you talk.
[DOLLTAKI gasps]
Para Para brothers, You're on!
Do your thing!
What are you going to do?
Please, don't hurt me!
♪ Bon Para!
Don Para! Son Para! ♪
♪ Just shake it! ♪
Shake that tushie!
Why am I moving? I can't stop!
♪ Kick it left
and left and left! ♪
♪ Kick it right
and right and right! ♪
--Left! Left!
--♪ Left and left and left! ♪
--♪ Kick it right
and right and right! ♪
♪ Left! Left! ♪
♪ Now it's time to
smile! And sing! ♪
♪ Bonpara-para, Bonpappa! ♪
♪ Bonpara-para, Bonpappa. ♪
♪ Tell us now creep.
What's your name? ♪
♪ Why, yes. My name
s Dolltaki. ♪
♪ Now tell us what's
your claime to fame? ♪
♪ I turn girls to dolls
and act real cocky! ♪
♪ Time for us to go,
so tell us where to aim! ♪
♪ That red cell... Yeah. ♪
Uh-oh.
[PAN]
Ah-hah!
So, that's it, huh?
Luud is bionic. Dr. Myuu took
a single cell from his own body
and began Luud's creation
with a mutation...
[DOLLTAKI]
...a mutation of his own design.
[water bubbling]
[DR. MYUU cackling]
[DOLLTAKI] Luud's entire being
is built around that one cell.
If you destroy it, you
destroy the infrastructure,
and by that, bring down
the entire creature for good.
Then you will be set free.
Well, at least we have a plan.
Huh?
[GOKU groaning]
[PAN]
Grandpa!
[inaudible]
[GOKU groaning]
[PAN shouts]
[LUUD groaning]
[GOKU groaning]
Good. At least it looks like
we're on the right track.
[DOLLTAKI]
See? I helped you.
Now, will you please
not hurt me?
[DOLLTAKI yelling]
Wait! I'm afraid that one
energy blast from the inside
is not enough to finish him!
What are you saying?
It's true! You can't
destroy the cell
unless it's attacked from the
inside and out, simultaneously!
[PAN] You couldn't have
mentioned that earlier?
[PAN] Grandpa! Trunks!
Please hear me!
You have to shoot
at Luud's heart!
Hurry!
[GOKU grunting]
[LUUD roaring]
[PAN]
I can't believe this.
I know exactly what to do,
and they just can't hear me.
Hey, Dolltaki!
[DOLLTAKI gasps]
You find us another way out...
...or find a way
to talk to Grandpa!
Either way you're gonna come up
with a better plan than this!
[DOLLTAKI] Don't you
think someone like me
would have brought down
Luud a long time ago,
if I knew a good
way to do it?
You're useless!
Ahh! We're gonna spend the
rest of our lives in here!
[BON PARA]
Uh... Pan?
What now?
I could use telepathy
and talk to your friend outside.
You can do what? Why did you
keep this quiet until now?
[BOTH]
Well, you're kind of scary.
That's okay. I know my prowess
can be intimidating sometimes.
Yes! Telepathy is perfect!
Now, get to work!
You've got people
counting on you.
Oh, Pan!
Listen. I scratched your back,
now it's your turn
to scratch mine, right?
[PAN shouts]
[DOLLTAKI groaning]
[PAN]
Yeah, yeah. I'll let you go.
But I can't speak
for everyone else.
She's so very evil.
All right, now!
Paras, would you mind
telling my grandpa
what to do and where to shoot?
♪ It's time... ♪
♪ For us... ♪
♪ To save... ♪
[ALL]
♪ The day... ♪
Um... That's real nice,
but do you have to sing?
♪ To use telepathy... ♪
♪ We have to sing... ♪
♪ So we can save... ♪
[ALL]
♪ The day... ♪
Yeah? Are you sure about that?
♪ We never... ♪
♪ Ever... ♪
♪ Lie... ♪
[PAN shouts]
Fine! Just do whatever you have
to do and make it fast, okay?
♪ Sorry... ♪
♪ We're just... ♪
♪ Trying... ♪
[ALL]
♪ To help... ♪
[PAN groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Whew! Now, that was a close one!
Oh, no! I think I'm stuck!
[BON PARA]
♪ Calling Goku. ♪
Huh?
[DON PARA]
♪ Can you hear us? ♪
[SON PARA]
♪ In your head? ♪
Wait! Is that singing?
♪ Aim at... ♪
♪ The red cell
on Luud's chest... ♪
♪ And fire... ♪
The red cell on Luud's chest?
His whole body's red,
but no cell.
Oh, no! He can't see it
from the outside!
All right.
[PAN] Grandpa! This is
what you're shooting for!
[LUUD groaning]
[GOKU gasps]
♪ That was... ♪
♪ Pan firing at... ♪
[ALL] ♪ The place that
you need to shoot. ♪
I gotcha!
That's right above his heart!
Goku, would you get
over here and help me?
The only way to beat this thing
is a blast to the heart!
The heart?
[LUUD growling]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU]
Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
I think he got me!
You had the right idea,
staying on the ground.
Maybe. Let's try again!
[GOKU growls]
Ready?
Yeah!
That did nothing.
[BON PARA] Goku, hitting the
outside alone doesn't work!
You have to synchronize a hit
from the inside with Pan.
You guys lied to me.
You said you had to sing!
Do you suppose we could
discuss this another time?
You should be focusing your
energy on hitting that cell.
Yeah right.
Are you ready Goku?
Yeah!
I'm ready!
[ALL]
Get down!
[PAN, GOKU shout]
[DOLLTAKI grunts]
I swear you fools can't
do anything right!
I told you, you both have
to attack at the same time!
Put a cork in it!
We'll get it right.
We just need to
concentrate a little more.
[BON PARA] All right, try this!
We'll do a three-count.
It's one, two,
three, then shoot!
Uh... Well I get it,
but I've never really been
good at that kind of thing.
It's our best option.
Fine.
Ah-one!
One!
Ah-two!
Uh, yeah, t-two!
Ah-three!
And three!
[DOLLTAKI]
Idiots!
The same time! I told you,
hit it at the same time!
Well, I guarantee you it was
not my timing that was off.
Uh... Let's try
and do this again.
Okay, I'll get it right!
And-ah-one!
And-ah-two!
Three!
Try again!
Uh, oh. I've seen
that look before!
[GOKU grunting]
[PAN groaning]
Grandpa.
♪ Goku... ♪
♪ Has no... ♪
♪ Sense of... ♪
[ALL]
♪ Rhythm... ♪
[GOKU grunting]
You're right. I have no rhythm.
But that's only because
I'm bad with numbers.
Maybe if we chanted some words
instead of counting, I'd get it.
Okay. What kind of words
did you have in mind?
[GOKU] I don't know. Wait!
I got it. Why don't we say,
"Pepper pot, Pickle pot,
Purple pot," then we fire?
Well okay, but those things
sound kind of weird.
[PAN]
So, what is he saying?
He's wanting to chant words
instead of
a regular countdown.
Fine. Whatever works.
I'd just like to get out
of here sometime today!
[PAN] And I want all of you
chanting along with us,
got that!
[BELIEVERS chanting]
All right, Goku,
we're ready when you are.
As long as there's no math
involved, I'll be just fine!
[LUUD roaring]
Time to rock n' roll!
Everybody!
[ALL]
Pepper Pot!
Pickle Pot!
[GOKU]
Purple Pot!
[LUUD roaring]
[LUUD groaning]
[ALL cheering]
You did it!
[LUUD grunting slowly]
[ALL cheering]
[ALL murmuring]
[GOKU laughing]
[PAN] Grandpa!
Hi, Pan! You're safe!
And look, we got the six
star Dragon Ball back.
[GIRU]
Danger! Danger! Giru, Giru.
Just the voice
I don't want to hear!
Wait, have you
guys seen Dolltaki?
Sure haven't.
[BELIEVERS murmuring]
There!
So long, chumps!
We'll be seeing you soon!
Get back here!
I'll tear you apart!
[DOLLTAKI cackling]
[NARRATOR]
In the wake of victory
following their
battle with Luud,
the nightmarish Dolltaki
managed to escape.
Do his cryptic last words
foreshadow the fate
of our heroes
at the hands of
the evil Dr. Myuu?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball GT!